(It's early morning when a cat is still half asleep.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- We're ready. - It's so early in the morning.
Please put on the microphone.
(Dumbfounded)
It's so early in the morning.
Gosh, Ji Hyo.
She's still half asleep.
(The reason they gathered early in the morning)
Today, we prepared a special race for our members,
who have forgotten all about their first meeting with you...
and your values, so they will find their original intention.
(Their original intention?)
- Hang on. The first moment we met? - Yes.
Do you remember the first moment we met?
It was 10 years ago for you, right?
It was 10 years ago. The first moment we met?
(What was it like 10 years ago?)
- For me, it's... - We will reenact the day.
It's been only 3 or 4 years for me. So I remember it a little.
Just a little.
The happy moment when we first met?
My memory is blurry.
The way they treated you was totally different back then.
(Their attitude towards Ji Hyo and So Min changed.)
- It was different. - Totally different.
I was warmly received at first.
- That's not true. - What?
- I don't think so. - You don't?
Ji Hyo definitely received a hearty welcome.
Really? Didn't they welcome me?
(- She was welcomed. - She wasn't welcomed.)
Wasn't I received warmly back then?
Kwang Soo was like this though.
(She barely remembers...)
- "My gosh." He did this. - That's right.
(the reaction Kwang Soo makes every week.)
Anyway, we will have a race to make them go back to the basics.
(A race to make them go back to the basics for Ji Hyo and So Min)
Today, you will get bomb badges...
(They will get enormous power with bomb badges.)
that will give you enormous power.
You can give the badges to the members you don't like...
(They can give the badges to the members they don't like.)
whenever you want before the end of the race.
Members with more badges will get a penalty.
(The 4 members with most badges will be nominated to get a penalty.)
- It's our day. - You two won't get a penalty today.
- We won't? - No.
(These two won't get a penalty today.)
We don't get to win or lose?
You can win or lose, but you won't get a penalty either way.
(That's good news.)
You can just give out as many badges as you want.
I should give Se Chan 10 badges before we begin.
He called me yesterday, and he acted up.
- He acted up? - Yes. He was really mean.
(So Min's expected to be a tyranny.)
Maybe Se Chan will be covered all over with the badges at the end.
(He's expected to be covered with bomb badges.)
Today, I will show him 100 bomb badges...
and tell him to either date me or take all the badges.
- I will... - So today is the day.
(She's going to capture him with the bombs.)
- Is it happening today? - Today is our first day.
I root for this couple.
(Song Ji Hyo used to be Monday Couple.)
They all seemed excited. They think we're having a couple race today.
(Other members think they're having a couple race today.)
- Really? - They seemed really thrilled.
That's what I told them.
Se Chan even went to a beauty salon.
(Offended)
- He went to a beauty salon? - He woke up early this morning.
(He goes to a beauty salon whenever they have a couple race.)
(Se Chan. We're the female guests today.)
Shall we go now?
(Later)
You will feel hot.
It's okay.
- Are you excited? - It's for love.
(Anticipating)
Aren't you too excited?
He wants to fall in love.
- We were in love - Do I look okay?
(He's acting up without knowing who the female guests are.)
You should dress up like this. You look really nice today.
- I'm serious. You look cool. - No.
I think today's guest is Jisoo.
That's total nonsense.
I want them to be a couple.
Who do you mean?
- Se Chan and So Min. - They wouldn't last long.
- Hello. - I think we should stay friends.
(He's especially happy today.)
- They would break up soon. - Exactly.
You think?
(They look more cheerful than usual.)
- Oh, my. - Whose fault would that be?
It would be because of So Min.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - What's with the bubbles?
(The bubbles are prepared to make them believe it's a couple race.)
- What's with the bubbles? - What's with the bubbles?
Look at the bubbles.
- My goodness. - Why bubbles?
(Skipping)
It's a perfect day for dating.
Hello.
- Hello. - In those boxes...
(So Min is excited to play the heroine today.)
It must be a couple race.
(Se Chan is excited to have a couple's race.)
- A couple race? - I'm so excited.
How do you know that?
- I'm excited. - How do you know that?
The writer called me to tell me to dress nicely.
(Dressed up)
- Hey, look at you. - Look at him.
(He's dressed nicely to win the favor of the female guests.)
- I paid extra attention today. - That's so embarrassing.
- I even put on a necklace. - He looks...
- especially cool today. - Do I look cute?
- Today... - You look handsome today.
- My gosh. - You look great today.
(Yes, enjoy it while it lasts.)
- I spruced myself up. - Everyone,
today's guests are waiting right now.
- I see. - Come on!
- First... - It's been a while.
- It's been a while. - He's exhilarated.
We'll reveal the divided photos of them so you can guess...
(The divided photos of the guests will be revealed.)
- who they are. - Are they waiting in those boxes?
- It must be uncomfortable. - Here are the photos.
- We should hurry. - In those boxes...
(Worried about the guests)
We should hurry up and meet them.
It must be hard for them waiting in there.
(The members haven't been worried about Ji Hyo and So Min for long.)
It must be hard indeed.
- Please look at these photos. - What?
Who could they be?
(The photos of the guests are revealed!)
- Hold on. Let me see. - They're pretty.
(Actually, these are photos...)
I think the second one is a member of Girls' Generation.
The one on the left end has light brown eyes.
(of these two.)
- I think it's Hyoyeon. - Hyoyeon.
- It's Hyoyeon. - Right, that's Hyoyeon.
- The lips look like Hyoyeon's. - She must be Hyoyeon.
I'm sure those are Hyoyeon's lips.
(Guessing wrong as soon as the photos are revealed)
- I'm 100 percent sure. - They're so pretty.
- That's Hyoyeon, and... - It must be Hyoyeon.
(Throwing them into confusion)
- Oh, right. I think it's her. - She has light brown eyes.
Isn't the first one Gary?
- The first one looks like... - I'm sure those are Hyoyeon's lips.
(The Precious Sisters give them false hope.)
Kim... I mean, Lee Sung Kyoung.
- Lee Sung Kyoung. - The third one is a member of ITZY.
Wait.
- The second one looks like... - They're so pretty.
(Praising herself)
Don't the lips of the second one look like Hur Young Ji's?
(Completely immersed)
- Hur Young Ji? Oh, right. - Right?
- You're right. - The first one.
- It must be Hur Young Ji. - Right. She looks like Young Ji.
- The second photo... - What about the last one?
(They see those faces every week, and they don't have a clue.)
- Isn't that Jihyo? - The last one...
- I mean, Jihyo of TWICE. - Oh, Jihyo?
(Guessing in a most aggressive manner)
You mean, the third one?
Shall we reveal who they are now?
(The guests will be revealed!)
- Okay. - Okay.
I'm sure that's Hyoyeon.
- No? - Who are they?
- That's not Hyoyeon. - Who are they?
- That's Ji Hyo. - Is that Ji Hyo?
- What? - They're Ji Hyo and So Min.
- Show them the answer. - If we see the whole photos...
(The answers are revealed.)
- Did anyone get a correct answer? - I'm sure it's Hyoyeon.
Did anyone guess right?
They're Ji Hyo and So Min.
(Ji Hyo and So Min)
- What's this? - Who are they?
- My, we look so pretty. - That's Ji Hyo.
(Praising herself loudly)
- How pretty. - They're Ji Hyo and So Min.
- What's this? - Who are they?
- Are they all Ji Hyo and So Min? - What's going on?
- Why did you show us their photos? - What are you doing?
(They can't grasp the situation.)
- What's going on? - What are you doing right now?
The two beautiful guests who will join you today are...
(The two beautiful guests that will join them today)
Song Ji Hyo and Jeon So Min.
(Song Ji Hyo, the ultimate beauty, Jeon So Min, the charming Love Frog)
The two beautiful guests who will join you today are...
(Fatal error)
- Song Ji Hyo and Jeon So Min. - This is ridiculous.
I can't believe this.
I arrived three hours early.
- From Eungam-dong to Gangnam... - They're today's guests?
- It took me two hours... - Are you kidding us or what?
(He lost his speech due to shock.)
- Ta-da. - Today...
(The stars are as bright as ever before their warm welcome.)
You can't do this.
- I took a shower... - Gosh. This is ridiculous.
Se Chan, you became so quiet.
This is the worst. What's this?
- This is ridiculous. - Is that it? Really?
(Resenting the production crew after figuring it out)
Come to think of it, Ji Hyo...
reluctantly dressed up today.
Ji Hyo, it's so obvious.
(Pretending to be a guest)
- Don't make it obvious. - I dressed up after a long time.
Ji Hyo, I see...
- Give me a break, will you? - why you looked annoyed.
(Ji Hyo looked sad as she was reluctant to get a full make-up.)
She didn't want to dress up, but she forced herself...
- She had no choice. - for work.
- He's so cheeky. - That's good for us.
Since you guys seem to have forgotten how you felt...
when you first met the two of them...
(For the members that lost the thrill toward the Precious Sisters, )
and the importance of them,
- That's true. - so we prepared...
(we prepared a race to help them get back the initial feelings.)
this race to help you get back your initial feelings.
- We never had such feelings. - We never had such feelings.
(It's like he lost his country.)
- They're just like... - They're like our own sisters.
They're like family to us.
It's not like there's a spark between any of us and them.
In order to remind you of how you felt about them at first,
(There wasn't any spark?)
(The video of how they felt about the Precious Sisters at first)
- we prepared a video. - We felt just the same back then.
- Please play the video. - You guys were nice to me.
- We were just the same. - No. You guys were nice to me.
(The video plays.)
What's that?
(Do you remember the moment you first met Ji Hyo?)
(We left the on-screen texts as they were written back then.)
That's Ji Hyo.
(On a hot summer day in June, )
You don't have a boyfriend?
(Ji Hyo joined Running Man as the only female cast member.)
- No, I don't have one now. - Of course, she says she doesn't.
(I don't have a boyfriend now.)
- She's beautiful. - Welcome.
(Her answer made some of the men happy.)
- A few of them like you so much. - I guess all men...
- feel the same way. - Exactly.
(However, does she find any of them attractive?)
Why did you play a romantic song like this?
Oh, I remember. We filmed that in Suwon, right?
(The memory of the first encounter is slowly coming back to them.)
- You don't have a boyfriend? - No, I don't have one now.
That's when she first appeared on Running Man.
- Was Haha interested in her? - Look at Gary.
- Haha, were you? - Oh, my.
- Jong Kook, what's with that smile? - Jong Kook.
My goodness.
Jong Kook, what's with that smile?
I must say, back then,
- Ji Hyo was really cute. - Indeed.
I'm asking you this question just for fun.
Which one of us is the closest to your ideal type?
Hey.
Why would you ask her such a question?
(Who makes her heart flutter?)
Jong Kook always falls in love on a variety show.
(Is it Gary who always shows his affection for her passionately?)
(Or is it Jong Kook who starts romance on every variety show?)
Just shut it.
(Or is it Haha who always squabbles with her?)
(Or is it one of these?)
(Find out who that could be, which even she doesn't know.)
(The one who makes her heart flutter will get the Running Ball.)
- Back then, Haha tried to... - He tried to win her heart.
(Unlike what they said, )
- Is it true? - We were in a love triangle.
(they all tried to win her heart.)
They were in a love triangle.
You look like Sandara Park.
Just as I said earlier, things can be hectic...
while we play games here.
But Ji Hyo, there's something you should know.
A few of us...
Not just one, but several men here like you.
I guess all men feel the same way.
(Who could be the men who like Ji Hyo?)
Exactly.
(Is he one of them?)
(Tapping)
(He noticed.)
- Haha, what's the matter? - What do you mean?
Nothing.
- Are you nervous? - What about me?
(Candidate 1: Haha)
- Why are you... - Everything will be fine.
I'm sweating because it's hot.
Look at Haha.
- Why did I act like that? - Didn't you have a girlfriend?
(Confused)
- Jong Kook, take a look at her. - Yes?
(He made Ji Hyo and Jong Kook make eye contact suddenly.)
- Take a look at her. - What are you doing?
She didn't seem to hate it.
(Will they become a couple?)
- Look at Jong Kook. - Is he being shy?
- Were you acting shy? - No.
(It could have been better to leave these unsaid.)
- This is crazy. - What was that?
- I just felt a little... - What's that?
I just felt a little awkward.
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
(First, he called her quietly.)
You see,
(But then, he hesitated.)
there's this song that I became fond of. Would you like to hear it?
Sounds great.
- You're wearing it, right? - Yes.
(They carefully put on each side of earphones.)
(The man with a shy smile)
"The man with a shy smile".
(The man became shy again watching the old clip.)
(They're listening to a love song in the subway.)
(And Jong Kook began...)
(singing a song to confess his love for Ji Hyo.)
(This will make her heart flutter.)
(Watching it again makes them get dry heaves.)
- He's singing for her. My gosh. - Why did you sing for her?
- My gosh. What is he doing? - Why did you sing for her?
- What's that? - What is he doing?
- I did what I was told to do. - It makes me cringe.
- I actually got goosebumps. - However...
(Their search for initial feelings cringe them.)
- That was... - I'm shocked.
I totally forgot the times when we were like that.
- Is it eight years ago? - This is making me insane.
I forgot that he sang for me.
- Do you remember that? - No, I don't.
(The serenade in the subway)
(No one can replace you.)
(My friend, Ji Hyo.)
(You're the only one who can help me get the Running Ball.)
(Touched)
- That was nice. - That's just ridiculous.
That's how we were back then.
Hello?
(It was the time when people used 2G phones.)
Pretty Ji Hyo, where are you?
- Jong Kook, you did that too? - He called her like that?
(They were sweeter to Ji Hyo than they thought they were.)
- "Pretty Ji Hyo"? - Pretty Ji Hyo, where are you?
- Did he really say that? - He called her like that?
- The thing is... - I can't believe him.
They were so sweet to her.
(They were very sweet to her 10 years ago.)
- The tone of voice is different... - There were times like that.
- from the way he talks to her now. - We were so sweet to her.
I do feel bad.
I didn't realize that we used to treat her like that.
Could you repeat, "Pretty Ji Hyo, where are you?"
Pretty Ji Hyo, where are you?
(Smiling)
- I don't need anyone else but you. - He spoke in a different tone.
You're the only one I need.
- "You're the only one I need." - "You're the only one I need."
Ji Hyo.
(He really means it.)
I think you look pretty on screen.
Because you have big eyes.
Then I should look pretty on screen too.
You're pretty.
You're absolutely pretty.
(Is it an attack or a confession?)
(It's as creepy as a horror movie.)
Look at his eyes.
(Shuddering)
- He's so annoying. - Haha.
(He resents himself from 10 years ago.)
- Gosh, you. - He's so annoying.
- I can't bear to watch this. - Hey.
Gosh, Haha.
So Min, you look great in medium-length hair.
(Now it's time to watch when they first met So Min.)
(Do you remember the first time you met So Min?)
So Min's clips.
I think it's hard...
I think it's hard to tear it.
(Whack)
Oh, gosh. That startled me.
(Startled)
Do you need a hand?
(In the gift box that Kwang Soo chose is...)
- Be careful. - She's wearing a skirt.
(So Min when she appeared as a guest in 2014)
That's So Min's first appearance on this show.
(She remembers the moment she first met them vividly.)
So Min, you were pretty back then.
- I know, right? - Yes.
"You were pretty back then."
She's Jeon So Min. Jeon So Min is here.
- Oh, my. Hello. - Jeon So Min is here.
(Overwhelmed)
Look at Kwang Soo.
(He was so polite, which is unimaginable now.)
(He sticks his neck out.)
My goodness. Kwang Soo was so polite to her.
- I greeted her so politely. - She looks coy.
I greeted her so politely.
Oh, my. Look at that.
(They didn't know they would become so close to each other.)
- Who is she? - Who is she?
(Who could be the princess that they've been waiting for?)
Jeon So Min!
- Hello. - We haven't seen you in a while.
(It's good to see you again, Princess Aurora.)
- Have you been well? - It's been a while.
- I remember that. - Princess Aurora.
(So Min notices...)
- Princess Aurora. - She came on the show as a guest.
You guys didn't seem so excited to see me.
(that the other members weren't too happy to see her.)
Why weren't you excited?
(Getting Back Their Initial Feelings for Ji Hyo and So Min)
- Kwang Soo seemed excited. - Were we like that?
(The videos we prepared ended.)
You didn't seem so... That's it?
- No more clips of me? - Getting back our initial feelings?
- Why... - We weren't...
(So Min's video was a little short.)
- We weren't so amazed. - They treated you the same way.
Like I said earlier, we felt the same way about her.
- Nothing changed. - We treated her the same way.
- They didn't treat me differently. - We didn't treat her differently.
I realized that Ji Hyo was really pretty back then.
(They're surprised to see how beautiful Ji Hyo was.)
- She's still pretty, but... - Of course, she's still pretty.
We all look so unsophisticated in her clips.
But she was so pretty.
She looked as sophisticated as she is now.
Ji Hyo was really pretty.
As we all saw in her clips,
(They still can't forget...)
I still can't forget her with that half-up bun.
(Ji Hyo's half-up bun)
- Right. - The half-up bun.
It was nice to watch the clips.
(We were all so young.)
- You all looked so young. - Indeed.
I'm not sure about So Min,
but we did forget our original resolution about Ji Hyo.
Since we've been making this show for 10 years,
(This special was made upon the request of many people.)
these videos are becoming the talk of the town online.
So I prepared them to show you.
Today, you are going to have Precious Sisters Race...
where the two sisters will exercise their power.
- Oh, no. - Precious Sisters.
The two sisters will get 30 bomb badges each.
(They can give the badges to the members they don't like...)
They can give the badges to the members they don't like...
(whenever they want until the end of the race.)
whenever they want until the end of the race.
That's ridiculous.
(Complaining)
We can't do anything then.
Four members with the most badges...
will be nominated for a penalty.
I should've used the transfer card this week.
Your fate hangs upon the precious sisters' decision,
(The Sisters will determine the fate of the rest.)
so you better try your best.
(Peeking)
(The Sisters will determine the fate of the rest.)
While Ji Hyo just listened to him quietly,
So Min turned her head and did this.
- She sent us some signs. - You know...
(She's already giving them signs.)
- she likes to enjoy it. - I know.
I can tell Ji Hyo will stay objective.
(So Min will exploit her power to the maximum.)
- But So Min isn't like that. - She's very tiring.
It's very tiring when So Min has power.
- But we can't be sure about Ji Hyo. - You know what?
- What? - She will stay quiet...
(Ji Hyo will stay calm in the beginning...)
at first, but she will give out the badges at the last moment.
(then hand them out towards the end.)
- At the last moment. - At an unexpected moment.
She just forgets about the badges...
and gives all of them to one person at the last moment.
That's what she does.
(Beware of the last-minute bombs.)
She's unpredictable.
Don't let your guard down.
Everything you do will be taken into consideration.
(Can the members really return to their original intentions?)
No. You should tell us when to begin.
(Their actions until now will be subject to judgment.)
You can't say everything will be take into consideration.
I'll give you the mission bags.
- There it is. - You look pretty.
(Rushing)
You're trying to get on her good side.
- Ji Hyo. - Where is mine?
(They are acting out of the ordinary.)
- Here. - Thank you.
Don't do things like that.
It wouldn't make any difference.
Don't do things like that. It wouldn't make any difference.
(The powerful woman's finger snap)
- What's taking you so long? - Here.
(Furious)
You're too slow. Forget it.
(Kwang Soo get a bomb badge...)
- You're too slow. Take this. - No.
(for making So Min wait.)
I was adjusting the strap for you!
That was too slow. Just take it.
It's better not to do things like that.
(The Sisters emphasizes on the original intention.)
Look. This is too long.
(Picky)
- Too long? - Yes.
Isn't the sun too bright?
My goodness.
(Suk Jin, who didn't do anything, )
- Are you all right? - Let me see.
(starts to suck up.)
- The sun is strong today. - I'll make it short for you.
(Servile)
- Right. - I'm okay.
You should be nice to them all the time.
(Stubborn)
Why are you guys...
"Pretty Ji Hyo, where are you?"
You can't do that to Pretty Ji Hyo.
- "Pretty Ji Hyo, where are you?" - You sound so sly.
- Pretty Ji Hyo. - Don't do that to Pretty Ji Hyo.
(He says it out loud for the first time in 10 years.)
- Don't bother her. - What?
(Pretty Ji Hyo)
It feels strange though.
I didn't know Jong Kook said that to me.
(Bombs can force Jong Kook to find his original intention.)
Ji Hyo doesn't like it when things are too much.
Sure. Don't go too far.
Just act natural.
So Min, you like things like this.
(So Min likes it when guys act thoughtfully.)
(She smiles big at Jae Suk's artificial manner.)
Hey, turn around. It will make her upset.
I love it. You know what I like.
- Sure. - Jae Suk knows what I like.
I know So Min too well.
(She likes exaggerated and superficial manners.)
Now we will go to the first mission...
(This is tiring.)
that's set up by the precious sisters.
Hang on. We will move the cameras first.
(It's going to be a rough week.)
My gosh. Should we move the boxes?
I was really excited.
(He's still disappointed.)
I really looked forward to this.
1, 2, and 3.
(They move the cameras first.)
Do you want me to carry these two boxes?
My gosh.
- Jong Kook. - Ji Hyo and So Min.
- You can't stay still. - Have some water.
He brought only two bottles of water.
(He volunteers to bring water to gain favor.)
- Is it okay not to do anything? - Ji Hyo, have some water.
- You can't stay quiet. - So Min.
Okay.
(She smiles big at such exaggerated manners.)
- He even opened the lid for me. - Drink some water.
It feels new. Did you really do that to me?
- Were you being that kind to me? - It was a long time ago.
(She is surprised at the manners 10 years ago.)
- Back then... - I was kind.
Come here, Ji Hyo. Wait in the shade.
(He acts kind again.)
- My gosh. - What's happening?
(Don't be under the fall sun.)
You can't let them stand under the sun in fall.
Okay? You can't.
(Pretty Ji Hyo will get tanned.)
- It's cool here. - Gosh.
I can see why I was caught up in a love triangle with Ji Hyo.
- You were really beautiful. - She looked pretty.
(They're saying anything to gain favors.)
For So Min,
you're all dressed up today.
This isn't what I expected.
I should stay out of their sight.
(He got all dressed up for nothing.)
She's so annoying.
Let's just stay here.
So Min loves a mission like this.
(They are talking behind So Min's back hiding behind the box.)
She loves it when she's the protagonist.
Gosh, So Min really makes me upset.
So Min. So Min.
Jae Suk said, "I'm so annoyed. So Min likes a mission like this."
"I just hate her." He said that behind the box.
I'm serious.
(The whistleblower instinct kicks in these situations.)
- I'm 100 percent sure that's true. - Right.
- It must be true. - Give him the badge.
Really?
So Min.
Kwang Soo is trying to drive a wedge between us.
(He denies it first.)
He's trying to come between us.
Can I check the video on the camera?
- Did you hear them talk? - So Min, that's not true.
Did I really say that?
(Shameless)
I didn't say it, did I?
He heard you.
- I'm not lying. - That's what Kwang Soo said.
(Jae Suk did say it.)
- It was Kwang Soo, right? - Who was it?
- Kwang Soo said that. - Kwang Soo did?
What's wrong with him?
(Lee Seung Gyul, audio director, only likes Jae Suk)
- So Min, did you hear that? - When did I say it?
It wasn't me. I already have two.
(The crew members only favor the national MC.)
- That's what I heard. - It was Jae Suk.
- He wouldn't lie to me. - It was Jae Suk.
(This is not fair.)
- Why would he lie to her? - Why would he lie?
(Kwang Soo gets 1 bomb badge.)
See? So Min, I didn't say that.
What's wrong with him?
Gosh, So Min is...
Her attitude is just wrong.
You don't do things like that.
(Suk Jin talks bad about So Min to earn Ji Hyo's favor.)
What's wrong with her?
- So Min. - So Min.
- Suk Jin... - Suk Jin just said...
- your attitude is wrong. - No.
- He says you have a twisted mind. - He says it's warped.
(She exaggerates it a little.)
He said you have a warped face and mind.
- That's ridiculous. - He really said that.
- Hey. - He did.
(Suk Jin gets 1 bomb badge.)
I should go easy on the badges. I will run out of them soon.
My goodness.
(She forces them to be quiet by handing out badges.)
I should use them while playing games.
I can't believe this.
- I can't do this. - It feels really new.
(Will the members be able to return to the basics today?)
Gosh, it's so hot.
This is easy for me.
(The Sisters had Suk Jin move the box.)
(Thud)
This is wider than I thought.
- Where should I put this? - Put it behind the chairs.
They are bossing me around with their power.
My gosh.
(Goodness)
This is really ridiculous.
(There are expensive chairs for Ji Hyo and So Min.)
Look at that. This is absurd.
- This is absurd. - Hey, guys.
Se Chan is being ridiculous.
(He suddenly becomes quiet with So Min's entrance.)
He's nice to me only when the camera is on.
(She naturally finds her way to the expensive chair.)
Can you believe this?
Be careful.
Pretty Ji Hyo, be careful.
Be careful. I'm taking good care of Pretty Ji Hyo. Don't worry.
Okay.
(Se Chan comes in late with a huge box.)
- Careful. - This is the worst.
This is the worst day ever.
I'm really upset today.
(What?)
I didn't leave home three hours early for this, So Min.
Are you upset?
- Won't you give him a badge? - Did you say you're upset?
(Are you getting upset?)
- Are you upset? - How could he say that?
Se Chan. Se Chan.
- Yes. - Don't put it there.
It should be here. We have more room here.
Put the box over there. It's too crowded there.
(She requests to move the box.)
Should we leave it here?
(The producer told me to put the box here.)
- No. - I'm really sorry, but...
Who are you listening to? You should bring it here.
It feels like she's our boss.
Aren't we supposed to listen to the producer?
We have more room here. Move it backwards a little.
(She's enjoying her omnipotent power.)
Is it good?
(The box is being placed as So Min requested.)
- Backwards. - This is beautiful.
- This is comfortable. - We will treat you nicely.
- Okay. - Gosh, I'm furious.
It's really hot.
(Suk Jin takes off his jacket.)
- You might be exhausted. - Are you hot?
- Yes, I'm hot. - Give me that.
- Why? - I should do this.
(He shows good manners with someone else's jacket.)
Gosh, I was going to do that.
(I can't believe this.)
- No, you weren't. - I was about to do it.
(He missed the opportunity within seconds.)
(Jong Kook earned points with someone else's jacket.)
That was so nice.
This is crazy.
Jong Kook is good at stuff like this. He knows it well.
(Approving)
- They're so funny. - Pardon?
Pardon?
(I want it too.)
Oh, this one?
No, I want this.
(Everyone else is approaching with a blanket.)
It's hot in here.
Why would she want this?
She's wearing jeans now.
You're wearing jeans. Are you going to be okay?
(The two are enjoying the manner that will never exist.)
- Yes. - Pretty Ji Hyo. It's so funny.
This is the first mission.
(Precious Sisters Race: The First Mission)
It's Precious Sisters' Imagination Theater...
where their imagination comes true.
(Precious Sisters' Imagination Theater)
(Their imagination will come true?)
It sounds fun.
(They feel nervous hearing about the first mission.)
Ji Hyo and So Min are picky Hollywood stars...
just returned home in glory and are making a guest appearance...
(They will be the guest of Running Man today.)
- on Running Man. - A skit.
So it's like a skit.
They will show up from the boxes like our guests...
(They will show up from the boxes like our guests.)
and have some interview like top stars.
(They'll have some interviews like top stars.)
- Like top stars? - Yes.
- Are we top stars? - No. They are.
I see.
- What did you say? - I'm sorry.
Do you still not understand today's race?
(Not yet?)
- They are top stars. - Stay focused.
(It's hard to get into it.)
It's an interview. Okay.
You can tell them about how you want them to react.
(They can tell the other members about how they should react.)
Do you want us to go crazy? Just do anything?
Well...
(Let me see.)
Does anyone of you want to go crazy as I show up?
- Go crazy? - Like how?
- We get carried away? - You're so happy to see me.
I'll do it.
- He's good at it. - Yes.
That's what Kwang Soo is good at.
(That's what Kwang Soo is good at.)
No, I want Jong Kook...
to sing until it ends.
(From the beginning)
So it's like background music.
(It's a request to be a live human music box.)
I want live music.
- Until it ends? - Yes.
- Jong Kook will just... - Until the interview is over?
(So Min can make the winner of Music Awards...)
I want Jong Kook to be the background music.
(to be just a background music singer.)
- So it's like his concert. - Her absolute power...
- It's background music. - Are we playing king now?
(Everyone protests at So Min's plan.)
- She has her absolute power. - This is...
You should give us something too.
- Are we doing this all day? - This is just strange.
And there's something I want to hear.
(So Min continues to make requests.)
"So Min, is your English name George Bush?"
(Please tell me these things.)
I'd go, "Why?"
- "Because you captivated my heart." - Sure.
Gosh, why did you spit on me?
(He just said mean things to her before he knew it...)
(because of So Min's ridiculous remark and spit.)
- I can't let this slide. - She spat on me.
- I couldn't help it. - I can't let this slide.
(Haha gets 1 bomb badge.)
This is...
George Bush?
- George Bush? My goodness. - I can't take this anymore.
(They are already discouraged by exaggerated compliments.)
Here's what they prepared for this.
(To help the members at crisis, )
It's like a sample.
(the crew provides them with a set of compliments to tell.)
- They are really picky. - You can refer to it.
- It's a list of compliments. - This is amazing.
(Luckily...)
Oysters are in season now.
- Why? - I mean your face.
(She loves it.)
(Do they want me to say things like that?)
This is crazy.
- So Min. - Me?
- You're from another province. - Where?
From fantasy called Jeon So Min.
(Laughing)
The problem is she likes stuff like this.
- What's this? - I love it.
(She's the only one who's extremely pleased.)
- This is supposed to be a joke. - It's so good.
(It is meant to be funny.)
- She loves it. - Hey.
- He just read it, and you love it? - She loves it.
Because he read it with his sincere heart.
What's the penalty?
(He's already halfway to giving up.)
Let's just get the penalty.
(It's a mission they want to give up already.)
Ji Hyo. I heard you got hurt.
- Me? - Yes.
When you fell from up above.
(Sighing)
She seems to like it though.
Ji Hyo likes it too.
Ji Hyo, is there anything you want?
(Even Ji Hyo likes such exaggerated compliments.)
Do you like things like this?
I don't know which box I will come out from,
(What are Ji Hyo's requests at her entrance?)
but I don't want...
to walk to this chair.
You want us to carry you.
(She refuses to walk.)
- Right. - Okay.
Okay. I'll carry Pretty Ji Hyo.
- Okay. - Se Chan, hold this.
- All right. - Give this to me, okay?
(Se Chan will be the flower delivery guy.)
Okay.
(Smiling big)
- This is crazy. - Then hit her with this.
What's all this?
- What? - No. I was joking.
(He can vent his anger with the vase later.)
Why did you come up with such a ridiculous theme?
Why must we get back our initial feelings for them?
(They're far from their original intentions.)
I haven't even treated my wife this way.
Exactly. Everyone has his own way of expressing his affection.
Then how do you usually express your affection?
- Me? - Yes.
Well, I need everyone out before showing that.
(He asked everyone to go out.)
You're the one who should get out.
(What's he saying?)
- Hey. My gosh. - How dare you?
(Even if he doesn't hide it, )
It'd be easier if you went out instead of making us all go out.
(they're not interested.)
He thinks he's sexy.
That was so cheesy.
(Jiring)
So Min will enter from this side.
(So Min acts like a top star first.)
Have you decided on the situation?
Well, So Min might not seem like... I mean, we might be mistaken.
- Why? - She looks like a pretty doll.
He's warming up.
(He's warming up.)
She likes it.
Stop it.
(My, I look like a pretty doll?)
- He didn't mean that, So Min. - She doesn't look like a human.
(Don't enjoy him. Stop him.)
- Give him a badge. - She looks happy.
- She's like a pretty doll. - I was going to stop him,
but she seemed so happy.
She really likes it?
(They can never understand her.)
She doesn't look like a human.
That's how middle-aged men joke around.
(Whether they are dad jokes or silly comments, )
- Was it good? - How far should we go?
(it's fine as long as they're compliments.)
- You can do whatever you want. - Okay.
I'll be sincere, So Min.
(Now, it's So Min's skit.)
- Me too. - Me too.
I won't just act. I'll mean every word I say.
(They have to cheer and welcome her...)
(when she comes out of the box.)
- I'll open the door for you. - You can do anything.
This is so nice.
Today, we have a special guest.
(The scene of So Min's entrance)
- Who is it? - Who?
(Let's immerse.)
- From Hollywood... - Gosh, that's crazy.
- Are you serious? - You're lying.
- No way. - I don't believe you.
(Acting as hard as he can)
She just arrived at the airport.
(From Hollywood)
- Could she be... - Then she should...
self-quarantine for two weeks. Am I right?
- Hold on. - Then she should...
She should self-quarantine for two weeks. Am I right?
(He suddenly came back to reality.)
Hold on.
- What was that? - So Min, give him a badge.
(It's only a skit.)
- Give him one. - It's a role play.
- I mean... - It's a role play. Gosh.
(I can't believe it.)
- It wasn't like that. - He ruined the mood.
- It's a role play. - You know...
- This is a role play. Why... - But that's reality.
(They barely immersed, but he ruined it.)
She flew here...
- on her private jet. - So Min, you know it was a joke.
You don't have to be here. You're useless.
- She called him useless. - He's useless.
We were trying to immerse ourselves in the situation.
(Yoo Jae Suk becomes unnecessary as he fails to immerse.)
- This is driving me insane. - Just take a close-up shot.
- Who? - A bust shot of me.
- Hold that camera on the floor. - Go on.
(The camera for the extra person)
Take a bust shot of me.
- A bust shot, okay? - Okay.
(The skit director So Min...)
Zoom in, okay?
(adds a camera director.)
Got it. I'll do that.
Do your best if you don't want to get fired again.
(The scene of So Min's entrance, take 2)
- Let's start over again. - We have a special guest.
(The skit begins again.)
- Who? - Who is it?
- From Hollywood. - What? From Hollywood?
(Acting surprised)
- It was hard to invite her... - No way.
(The guest from Hollywood they had a hard time inviting)
- to our show. - Did she accept the invitation?
- Could it be her? - I think I read a news article.
(She's already nearly out.)
She's Korean, right?
- No way. - Could she be...
(Immersed)
She arrived at the airport just earlier.
(She arrived in Korea just now.)
- I heard she came to Korea. - Yes.
- My gosh. - I think I read about it.
She's Korean, right?
Be careful, guys. I heard that every man faints...
- when they see her in real life. - She's incredible.
(The top actress known for her appearance)
- Really? We might faint? - Yes. Be careful.
- The international top actress... - Could she be Ms. Jeon?
(The person who makes everyone here...)
(including the cameraman nervous)
- The international top actress... - Could she be Ms. Jeon?
- Jeon So Min. - My goodness.
(Jeon So Min is on Running Man.)
(Screaming)
(Everyone stood up.)
(Suk Jin covered his mouth in shock.)
- Hello. - Is she really a human?
(Kwang Soo opened his eyes widely.)
(Top actress from Hollywood who brings glory to Korea)
(The international top actress, Jeon So Min)
She's a real person.
Is she really a human?
(Amazed)
She's a real person.
(As a special guest shows up, )
- Oh, my. - She's a real person.
(the cameraman is also working hard.)
- Please say something in English. - Hi.
- Hi. - Come over here. Stop it.
(Everyone gathers around So Min.)
- Hello. - Don't go near her.
- Here Kwang Soo goes again. - Don't go near her.
(The actor started acting as he promised.)
My gosh. Jeon So Min is here.
He fainted.
(So Min likes the way he reacted for some reason.)
My gosh. Jeon So Min is here.
(He fainted.)
- Gosh. - He just made fun of you.
- That wasn't good. - That was the worst.
That was the worst.
(The actor fainted helplessly after acting.)
He made fun of you.
Wait. Did someone put poison in his water?
(They're suspicious of the water.)
- That was too much. - Check it out.
See if someone poisoned his water.
- His nostrils... - What are you doing?
(The actor woke up thanks to the cameraman.)
- Are you all right? - Yes. I'm... I'm fine.
- He's still acting. - Are you feeling unwell?
- Really? - Yes, she's here.
(Immersed)
- Really? - Is she really Jeon So Min?
- She's Korean. - My gosh.
- How did you get here? - So Min.
You talked as if she was a foreigner.
- That's enough. - Can you look at me just once?
(Another person who immerses with the best effort)
My gosh. It's her.
Please don't touch my hair.
Don't touch me.
- How dare you touch her hair? - Oh, gosh.
(Her bodyguard shows up.)
Have you lost your mind?
My goodness. Could you...
(This man protects the guest sincerely.)
Oh, my. You must...
(Meanwhile, )
You hate it when people do that, right?
(the flower delivery man is looking for his chance.)
Yes. Hi, everyone. It's nice to see you all.
- Hello. - She's gorgeous.
- She speaks Korean fluently too. - She's like a speaking doll.
(When should I give it to her?)
- He keeps... - He does it repeatedly.
(So Min gives him a signal.)
- I have something for So Min. - Go ahead.
I have something for So Min.
(The flower delivery man finally got a chance as she gave him a signal.)
Flowers are blooming on your face.
This is my gift for you.
Suk Jin, I can't do this.
You're good at this.
(In the jungle of skits, )
- I delivered the flowers to So Min. - This is too much.
(he barely carries out his role and exits.)
Hello, everyone.
- Here you go. - Please sit down. Thank you.
(Satisfied)
- May I have a question? - Sure.
"May I have a question?"
(What?)
What does that even mean?
You can have a question if you want.
You should ask, "May I ask you a question?"
(He's extremely polite.)
- So Min. - Give him a badge.
- So Min, do you... - Yes?
fart like everyone else does?
Have you lost your mind?
(No way.)
He has lost his mind.
How could you ask such a question at this important interview?
(Angry)
- Who are you? - Who are you to ask...
(By the way, who are you?)
- You should stand over there. - Why would he...
(The unlicensed cameraman gets isolated.)
- I'm speechless. - Who are you?
- Go away. - It was so annoying.
I have a question as well.
I'm so angry.
(He's forced to move to the best spot for filming.)
It's too quiet here. Can't you play some music?
- Shall we play music? - That'd be great.
(They start playing a music box upon her request.)
You should've given him a badge since he didn't sing.
"A face"?
You picked an English song knowing she can't speak English.
No. She works in Hollywood.
(I thought you were from Hollywood.)
She lost her part because she couldn't speak English at all.
(Extra theme)
- While knowing that... - She was fired?
- Come here. Here's a badge for you. - You shouldn't have done that.
- She was fired? - Come here. Here's a badge for you.
(Why is Ji Hyo giving Jong Kook a penalty badge?)
- Okay. - Here you go.
Why would she give me a badge?
- Why did she give him a badge? - Exactly.
He sang for both me and her.
That's not acceptable.
(Superstar Song recalls the memory.)
- You and Yoon Eun Hye are still... - But she made me do it.
- What did you just say? - Have you ended things with her?
(Recalling the past)
That was a long time ago.
- Have you ended things with her? - My gosh.
(The unlicensed cameraman still lives in the past.)
- What a weirdo. - That was funny.
That's not acceptable.
(They recall the memory while looking for original intention.)
- I can't believe you. - Gosh.
Now, Ji Hyo will make her entrance.
(It's Superstar Song's turn to appear.)
Ji Hyo, is there anything particular you want us to do?
(What's her request?)
I want Kwang Soo to tie his hair.
- Tying his hair? - That'd be nice.
- His hair is a bit messy. - How about we trim his hair?
(She totally agrees.)
- Also, if he doesn't mind... - Yes?
(Tie my hair?)
In order to bring back the memories from 10 years ago,
I'd do anything.
- can you draw a mustache? - Sounds great.
(Like back then)
If he wears a beanie and draws a mustache on his face,
(She requests short hair and a mustache for original intention.)
he would look like the way he looked back then.
I want him to grow a mustache.
(At that moment, So Min stands up.)
- I'll tie your hair. I insist. - It's okay. I can do it.
- Really? - Which hairstyle do you want?
(It's an honor. So Min will tie his hair herself.)
- You should feel honored. - Indeed.
- I'm jealous. - Which hairstyle? Up or down?
(Getting ready to act)
- He should feel honored. - I can't believe she will...
- That's funny. - However...
- So Min. - Yes?
(He seems to habitually faint.)
- That was over the top. - What was that?
- That was too much. - He's trying to get on your nerves.
(He fainted because he doesn't want to tie his hair.)
- This is... - So Min, he's making a fool of you.
(He got caught overreacting.)
- Seriously, that was... - It's not that I didn't want it.
- I mean... - It's not that I didn't want it.
(He was acting to make fun of her.)
- Honestly... - You're mistaken. I fainted...
- because I was too excited. - As if he saw a ghost.
You looked like you saw a ghost.
- That was over the top. - You said you wanted me to faint.
(Too much fainting action...)
- You looked like you saw a ghost. - She didn't want it that way.
(gets him 1 bomb badge.)
- That was too much. - That was too much.
Why did you act like you saw a ghost? I'm not a ghost.
(So Min ties his hair after teaching him a lesson with a bomb badge.)
- You should tie his hair back. - Tie his hair at the back.
Tie his hair at the back. That's not good.
Tie his hair at the back.
(So Min ties his hair on top first.)
Tie his hair at the back. That's not good.
Tie his hair at the back.
I guess he decided to go with that character.
- What about the hair at the back? - She'll tie that part too.
(Kwang Soo's original style isn't going in the right direction.)
Doesn't he look like a barbarian?
(They add a mustache as Ji Hyo requested.)
- Okay. It's done. - Also...
- Hang on. - That won't work. Wait.
(It's hard to tell his ethnicity.)
I'm doing this to avoid getting a bomb badge.
It hasn't even been an hour since I got my hair done.
Why did you even do that?
I woke up two hours early for it.
I've never seen anything like this.
(The sad story of Kwang Soo...)
Because I heard we would have female guests.
(who fell for tricks from early in the morning)
Pretty Ji Hyo made him look better.
- Exactly. Good job, Ji Hyo. - She made him look unique.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo, they get to watch a foreigner.)
Pretty Ji Hyo must've been determined to make him a star.
- Please consider my preferences. - Okay.
(With Kwang Soo's original style, Ji Hyo's skit begins.)
Following So Min,
(The scene of Ji Hyo's entrance)
the next guest came from the UK.
(This guest is from England.)
- From the hottest drama on BBC... - She came from the UK?
(Immersed)
- That's crazy. - Could it be her?
Is she...
Miss Song?
- Who's Mi Song? - I said, Miss Song.
She just arrived.
(The top actress just arrived in Korea.)
- Song Ji Hyo. - This is crazy.
This is crazy. I can't believe this.
(The star they have only heard of is on Running Man!)
- No way. - She's gorgeous.
(He's screaming when she hasn't even come out.)
- This is crazy. No way. - Are you serious?
(She makes everyone's heart race with her appearance.)
- She's gorgeous. - Hey.
(The international top actress, Song Ji Hyo)
Is she a real person?
(Acting hard)
So Min is no match for her.
- She's so beautiful. - My gosh.
(Ji Hyo seems calm as a top star while they're cheering.)
So Min is no match for her.
- My goodness. - She's so beautiful.
(Lifting her up)
(Why is he carrying her?)
What are you doing?
I can't let her feet touch the floor.
- What is he doing? - How dare you touch her?
(The man with a shy smile)
- Please let me through. - Has he lost his mind?
- My gosh. - Has he lost his mind?
(Jong Kook's service discourages many people.)
She's unrealistically beautiful. Look at her face.
My, thanks. You're so cool.
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
Her face is as small as an acorn.
- An acorn? - Her face is as small as an acorn.
(Her face is as small as an acorn?)
- What? An acorn? - That's a weird comparison.
(Is that a compliment?)
- Why an acorn out of everything? - What do you mean by that?
- Ji Hyo, he's making a fool of you. - People usually say a fist.
(Ji Hyo is bugged by his far-fetched compliment.)
If I have a face this small with this body... Here.
(Suk Jin gets 1 bomb badge.)
You just got another bomb badge.
Why did I say that?
Please sit down, Ji Hyo.
- By the way, Ji Hyo... - She's a star for a reason.
Your reputation wasn't exaggerated.
She doesn't know what that means.
(How dare you use a Chinese idiom?)
- Why did you use difficult words? - He's making fool of her.
- He's making fool of her. - He's making fun of her.
(That's prohibited for Superstar Song.)
- Hang on. - Will you let it slide?
- He's making fool of her. - Was that...
- He used a Chinese idiom. - This deserves a bomb badge?
(How dare you?)
- I'll give you three. - She doesn't know what it means.
Why would you make her upset?
(Ji Hyo from Britain has a painful memory of Chinese idiom.)
You know that she had a hard time because of Chinese idioms.
But that deserves these badges?
She doesn't know any Chinese idioms.
No Chinese idioms are allowed.
(Originally...)
Are you kidding me?
(The top actresses, Ji Hyo and So Min came all this way.)
- They're really pretty. - How pretty.
- This is how one should look. - Tell me about it.
(We've managed to secure 20 minutes of the interview.)
So Min, isn't the seat uncomfortable?
- It is. - I bet your back is...
because of the wings you have. Is it okay?
- He's at it again. - She likes it though.
(He's sick and tired of it.)
- I can't believe she likes it. - That's just outdated.
(The old-fashioned comment from the 2000s takes away their energy.)
- She likes the cheesy lines. - Even though they're outdated.
(But the problem is that she likes it.)
People used to say that in the early 2000s.
- No way. - It works on the ladies though.
(Proud)
(Is that what they like?)
Yamada, go ahead and ask the question.
Right.
Hello,
I'm Yamada of Tokyo Daily.
(Yamada, Tokyo Daily journalist)
"So Min, you melt the hearts of viewers..."
"as well as the ice up in the Arctic."
- "If it's okay..." - Did you just come up with that?
(Excited)
No, the question was provided for him.
- I'm only reading what's here. - Really?
(Yamada only read it like a parrot.)
"The viewers..."
This was given to me to read!
(Feeling victimized)
(She throws a bomb at his insincere question.)
I was given this to read!
(You gave me to read it, so I read it!)
Shouldn't you be impressed that a foreigner can read this?
(Trying to defend him)
- It's in Korean. - There's no creativity behind it.
- Mine's in Japanese. - Really?
(Absorbed in his role)
It's in the Japanese alphabet.
(The heated questioning of foreign reporters continue.)
My blood sugar level is dropping due to being nervous.
(Ji Hyo says that her blood sugar level is dropping.)
- Low blood sugar? - Low blood sugar?
(Do we have some snacks?)
- She's craving sugar. - Hold on.
(Kwang Soo immediately looks for something.)
- Isn't this exhausting? - No, I'm loving this.
Why are you bringing us a shot glass?
(What's with the paper cup?)
It's an ashtray.
Just in case.
You never know.
(The international reporter is considerate in detail.)
I know you don't smoke, but just in case.
You never know.
(His immoderate consideration...)
Shouldn't you give him one for that?
(gets him a bomb badge.)
What on earth is this?
Some of you can go and get the chocolate outside.
- You have them? - Do you have some ready?
(Kwang Soo goes to get chocolate for Ji Hyo.)
Her blood sugar level is dropping.
(Kwang Soo is granted freedom thanks to the searching of the chocolate.)
To what extent...
must we play along?
Until the end of the day.
- All day? - Yes.
(Complaining to the assistant director)
Why...
You've got to be kidding me.
Just wait and see next week.
(Seething)
Honestly, I can't take this.
(He harbors a lot of resentment for the two picky celebrities.)
So Min's worse, you know.
- Is that so? - Yes.
(For a while, Kwang Soo complained to the assistant director.)
I mean... To what extent must we play along?
(How does this qualify as going back to our original mindset?)
Anyway,
(The interview with the two stars continue in the meantime.)
I believe that a lower-range voice is one of your charms, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo has a charming lower-range voice.)
Thank you for saying so.
Since it's been a while, why don't we wish our viewers...
(Squeezing out questions)
a good night's sleep?
(Asking her to say, "Good night," to the fans)
Fans might record it...
To listen to it.
(The fans can save it forever.)
- Your fans would love that. - Right.
Could you wish them a good night's sleep?
Everyone, good night.
(They trade in their conscience.)
Get up, guys.
(Superstar Song is delighted by their response.)
(Feeling pathetic)
- Get up. - Wait. What?
- You... - I slept like a baby!
(Superstar Song's fatal voice cures their insomnia.)
Wake up, guys.
This is the deepest I've ever slept.
(So Min is also satisfied.)
- Then... - I slept well too.
My insomnia has been cured.
Why aren't you asleep too?
(Kwang Soo enters but fails to see what's going on.)
- Why aren't you asleep? - We all took a nap just now.
(He instantly drops out cold.)
- Why aren't you asleep too? - You should take a nap.
- Then So Min... - You're good now.
(Kwang Soo had a good sleep thanks to her.)
So Ji Hyo was able to put...
(He gives Ji Hyo chocolate that she wanted.)
everyone to sleep just now.
Can I have some chocolate too?
- Then... - Can I have one too?
(Here you go!)
(While Korea and Japan are brought together over chocolate, )
(Assistant Director Hyeong Gu suddenly enters.)
Her manager has something to say to her.
Is he her manager?
So he's her manager.
- Is he her manager? - Yes.
Doesn't he work at the airport?
(He works hard as a manager putting behind his impressive career.)
Isn't he a lawyer?
He...
He's whispering something in her ear. No way.
(Whispering)
Kwang Soo said he'll get back at you for this next week.
- Doesn't he work at the airport? - Next week?
(So Min stiffens at her manager's words.)
Are you sure?
Doesn't he work at the airport?
- Next week? - Are you sure?
Yes, I heard it myself.
Isn't he a lawyer?
Guys, please know...
that my people are everywhere, so don't talk behind my back.
You jerk!
(She catches the reporter talking behind her back.)
Will one be enough?
- That's not... I'm sorry. - Isn't it worth two?
- You talked smack about her? - I'm sorry.
That's not it.
(He receives two bomb badges for talking behind her back.)
- Two? - How pathetic of you.
- Don't talk behind our backs. - Is this how it'll be today?
(The short interview with the two superstars ends.)
- Don't talk behind our backs. - Okay. I'm sorry.
Anyway, it's time...
(It's almost time for their outbound flight.)
for them to leave now.
("I love you, Running Man!")
(After a brief encounter which left them wanting more...)
Is this a school?
(Are they meeting next in a classroom?)
(Class Motto: Ho Dong's Watching)
"Ho Dong's Watching"?
We must be learning something.
- It's a tricky episode today. - Tell me about it.
Nothing's coming from the heart.
Since when did they...
(Upset)
- They changed too, you know. - Today's shoot...
- I'm mentally exhausted. - The girls...
- I'm exhausted too. - Me too.
How can they be this way?
(They start talking behind their backs.)
- We're not allowed to say anything. - Mentally, I'm a goner.
I hate how they take our generosity for granted.
(Furious)
They think of themselves as actual princesses.
(Dumbfounded)
It's irritating.
I hate how they take our generosity for granted.
(Glancing here and there)
How can they be this way?
(While everyone complains, Kwang Soo's hands move suspiciously.)
We're not allowed to say anything.
I hate how they take our generosity for granted.
They think of themselves as actual princesses.
(Glancing)
Wait, are you recording this?
(Are you...)
Hey!
- You are. - Why aren't you saying anything?
(He was caught trying to record it.)
You're recording us instead of saying anything?
(His phone's microphone is sticking out.)
- You placed it on top. - Say this.
Say, "Jeon So Min and Song Ji Hyo are stupid."
- Say it. - But they're not stupid.
- He's recording this. - Unbelievable.
(The bombs of betrayal go off.)
- How dare you record us. - Just say it.
Suk Jin, wait.
(Suk Jin's chest is filled with bomb badges.)
- I... - Are you a war veteran?
(The war veteran of the Precious Sisters Race)
I see this as love.
(Their love is like war.)
It's their love.
I guess we're taking a break this week.
(Sighing)
(This is exhausting.)
We should consider it as a break.
(Knocking)
- Yes? - Come on in.
They must be in character.
(Are we...)
(at it again?)
- Nice! - No way!
(My gosh!)
(They immediately rise to their feet.)
(The ladies they know so well.)
This is insane.
- Nice! - No way!
(They start off by applauding.)
No way!
(They respond soullessly the same way they did earlier.)
This is insane.
- No way! - This is insane.
- How on earth are you here? - Hi.
(Jeon So Min and Song Ji Hyo)
Are you transfer students?
This is what I call a special episode.
You look like...
(Soulless words)
- real high school students. - Exactly.
Will they be with us all day today?
(Unbelievable)
- Did you just graduate high school? - It's a special episode!
- The guests... - Did you see that?
Haha always does that when he's lying.
(The poses they strike when lying)
They're the last people I expected to see.
(The two superstars returned for their fans.)
This is insane.
So Min, you look absolutely gorgeous.
(Targeting So Min only)
- Hello. - Hi.
(The first transfer student, Ji Hyo)
Ji Hyo, you're so pretty.
I know I am.
- Ji Hyo's loving it. - You're the best.
- Of course, I am. - She's loving it.
(So this type of thing works.)
Ji Hyo's loving it.
"From Running Man, I..."
- Can't you read? - "The prettiest..."
- She's from Hollywood, remember? - Can't you read?
(Getting a warning)
"Hi, I'm Ji Hyo, a transfer student from Gorgeous High School."
- Gorgeous High School. - Nice!
(Gorgeous High School and gorgeous responses)
- Of course. - So that's where she's from.
- Gorgeous High School. - You see,
(Struggling to agree)
I prepared these questions because you still don't know me well...
(For her 10-year-old friends, )
even after 10 years, so listen and answer.
(it's Guess Who I Am questions.)
- Sure. - But we know everything about you.
(Confident)
- We know everything. - But I know...
practically everything about you.
Answer correctly, and you'll be able...
(If they guess correctly, they can give 2 bomb badges to someone else.)
to give two bomb badges of yours to another member.
- Okay. - If we get it right?
- I should focus then. - Be careful though.
- There's also a penalty. - Here.
(You get punched with a giant hand if you guess wrong.)
- Shouldn't it be a toy hammer? - That's what they'll use?
(Don't they normally use a toy hammer?)
- That hurts. - A lot too.
(It's as thick as their friendship.)
- Here's my question. - Sure.
With my ex-boyfriend...
Finally.
(Smashing)
- Busan! - Finally.
With my ex-boyfriend...
(She only mentioned her ex-boyfriend, )
Finally.
(but Jae Suk stood up.)
- Busan! - Finally.
- The guy... - Busan!
- It's Busan. - No, balloons.
(What about Busan?)
- Haeundae. - Busan.
The place you went to in your car...
when we went to Busan to film Running man.
How can you say what really happened?
(She's hearing it for the first time.)
- You shouldn't have said it. - I...
It was a black Mercedes.
No, the S500!
- It was the E Class. - That never happened.
(All eyewitness accounts are revealed which she never heard of.)
- You're framing her. - It happened.
That didn't happen. That's not me.
You offered me a ride uphill,
- but I declined. - That's right.
- Okay. - Let's hear her out.
(The past stories are overly detailed.)
It's all in the past anyway.
Yes, it's all in the past.
While watching a TV series with my ex-boyfriend,
anger built up inside me and we ended up arguing.
- You mentioned that before. - Let me answer.
Your ex-boyfriend...
filmed a kiss scene.
- My gosh. - What are you talking about?
(She's flustered by having his occupation revealed.)
- Was he an actor? - Yes.
- What... - You were together, so...
(I couldn't help it.)
- Sit down. - You said something upset you.
(She smacks him right away.)
What else can you be upset about?
Let me answer.
You were watching TV with your current boyfriend,
but your ex-boyfriend appeared on TV.
- You complimented him and... - That's nasty of you.
Talk about being inhumane.
(The older members take the opportunity to tease her.)
- Good job. - That's just plain mean.
She put more power into the swing.
She's not one to get angry and sulk.
- Let me answer. - Ji Hyo once told me this.
It involves food.
(It's about food.)
- Food? - Let me answer!
You ordered fried chicken while watching TV,
- but he ate it all. - Incorrect.
- It's something similar. - Let me answer.
You came across a scene where the actors were eating.
He mentioned how nice it was when you two ate the same thing,
(To her boyfriend)
- but that never happened. - Nice one.
- He got confused. - Your ex got confused.
(The wrong answers get more specific.)
He mistook you for his ex-girlfriend.
(Teasing)
- Let me give you a hint. - Sure.
(She gives them a clue.)
What resembles Kwang Soo?
(It resembles Kwang Soo.)
Let me answer!
Kim Yeon Koung made a cameo appearance...
(The quiz turns into Guess Who Kwang Soo Looks Like.)
Why would she make a cameo appearance?
- Let me answer! - Let me answer.
You saw a rockfish on TV...
What? A rockfish?
(Absurd)
(He does look like a rockfish, but that wasn't the answer.)
- What looks like me? - Let me answer!
While watching a TV series,
(Jong Kook says his answer.)
you were munching on grilled squid.
(Glancing)
Which part of a squid do you like?
(Which part of squid?)
- Let me answer! - The mantle.
He left the mantle aside...
- and only ate the legs. - So it's a squid?
While watching TV with your ex, you were eating grilled squid.
He only ate the mantle though...
and didn't touch the legs.
- Your ex... - That is correct.
(Her boyfriend ate the squid mantle and left her the legs.)
- Don't you like the legs though? - Why argue over that?
(What does this have to do with dramas?)
It has nothing to do with the TV series though.
The same scene was on TV too.
It was.
Anyway, I actually like the mantle more.
(Ji Hyo likes the mantle of squid.)
- Just like most people. - Most people do.
(Pretty Ji Hyo turned sulky because she couldn't eat the mantle.)
- But he ate it all. - But my ex liked the legs.
This is the next question.
There was a sum of money that I worked really hard to make.
But it ended up disappearing in an absurd way. Why did it disappear?
Let me answer. Seong Mun took it.
(Your brother)
No. Incorrect.
Hold on.
(You lost the money?)
You lost the money all of a sudden?
- You lost it? - Did you lose it?
It disappeared.
- It disappeared? - Yes.
You still can't remember where you placed it.
- That's the answer. - He should get hit for that one.
(That's very likely.)
- That's the answer. - It suits you.
You could forget where you put it.
(Hitting softly)
She hit me in a pretty manner.
(He tries to gain her favor by complimenting her.)
It's so fitting of her.
(Don't only give us bomb badges, Ji Hyo.)
- What is it? - It was in an absurd manner?
- It was in an absurd manner. - Let me answer.
Your 'rents donated it without telling you, Pretty Ji Hyo.
- They donated it. - Isn't that a good thing?
- What does 'rents mean? - Your parents.
(She doesn't know what the term means?)
Did you use slang with her?
- You know she doesn't know that. - He used slang on purpose.
(How dare you use the new word to Ji Hyo?)
- It was on purpose. - Goodness.
She doesn't know what that term means?
(It's too new of a word for Cavewoman Ji Hyo.)
What are you saying?
She doesn't know what that term means?
Can you tell us how much it was?
- It was nearly 1,000 dollars. - 1,000 dollars?
- It was over 1,000 dollars. - That's a lot of money.
If it was 1,000 dollars, that means...
(Thinking)
It was absurd. She must've bought something.
- I'll give you a hint. - Okay.
(An additional hint)
It has something to do with Running Man.
(It has something to do with Running Man.)
(The missing 1,000 dollars is related to Running Man?)
I thought it might be.
- Let me answer. - Okay.
Didn't we collect late fees?
(Going down the memory lane 10 years ago)
- The prize money. - Right.
We collected the prize money.
- You guys got prize money? - Yes.
Let me answer. Lee Kwang Soo took it.
(Try to be more accurate.)
Say the answer exactly as it's written here.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(He's confident he knows the answer.)
- Lee Kwang Soo... - You gave the money you won...
(You wanted to use the prize money...)
to Lee Kwang Soo, since I was the youngest member,
(at the next get-together.)
to hold onto to use at the next get-together.
- But after that, it was... - He never brought it up?
never brought up.
And I used that for personal reasons.
(He exposes himself.)
- Lee Kwang Soo kept it. - Are you confessing?
(He exposes himself confidently and gets it right.)
- Where did you use it? - Are you confessing?
- Correct. - Okay!
- This is... - When was this? What's the story?
At the beginning of the show,
(During the early days of Running Man, )
- we used to win prize money. - That's right.
(there was prize money.)
At that time, we used to have get-togethers often,
(Jae Suk paid most of the team get-togethers.)
and Jae Suk would pay for the get-togethers.
- I paid too. - I felt bad about that.
Why are you bringing that up right now?
Just smile and get over it.
- I've paid too. - I paid twice.
(To be precise)
- Okay. - Goodness.
(It's once every 5 years.)
I felt really bad about that,
(She felt bad Jae Suk paid every time.)
- so I said we should collect... - Right. We agreed on that.
(She decided to save the money for the next get-together.)
- our prize money... - Right.
and use it on get-togethers.
That's what we said. So I never had a chance...
to see it or touch it, and I gave it to Kwang Soo.
(The money was nowhere to be seen again.)
- But it was never mentioned again. - That's right.
- What happened to it? - Hold on. Is it still missing?
Is the money still missing?
- What did you do with that money? - What?
It was at the beginning of Running Man, so I was struggling.
But your situation is much better now.
- Pardon? - It's better now.
I still have it.
- Then Kwang Soo will pay next time. - Okay.
- I think... - Yes! Great idea.
- He could treat us 20 times. - Because it gained interest.
(They'll calculate 10 years' worth of interest rate.)
- It's worth 25,000 dollars now. - Okay.
(The next transfer student is getting ready.)
Cutie, pretty. Pretty, cutie.
- Lovely. - It's Jeon So Min.
- Lovely! - Yes!
- You're so pretty! - Cutie, sexy, lovely!
(Everybody, scream!)
- Jump, jump. - Jump, jump.
(He's shaking out his soul.)
Put your hands up!
(A reaction bot of cutie, sexy, and lovely.)
Cutie, sexy, lovely!
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(Smiling)
- Put your hands up! - Cutie, sexy, lovely!
(Everyone's swamped...)
(in the cutie, sexy, lovely dance.)
Cutie, sexy, lovely!
(It's chaotic.)
- Gosh, she's so sophisticated. - Cutie, sexy, lovely!
(They're shaking to the last bits of the soul with their pelvis.)
- Seriously. - Your dance is so sophisticated.
- "Sophisticated". - Seriously.
(I'll do it again because I feel happy.)
It's different.
- It's amazing. - It's different from others.
(It's a rare sight.)
- It's incredible. - How can she dance like that?
There's going to be trouble today. There will be.
- It's amazing. - My heart is going to stop.
(He's saying anything.)
Hello.
(They act passionately...)
- Hello. - Hello.
(even to a simple greeting.)
I'm Jeon So Min from I Have A Guy In Mind High School.
Okay.
(Yang Se Chan, the guy picked by So Min)
It's a guy.
You guys seem more natural than before.
(She's pleased with their natural reactions.)
- Everything is flowing easily. - You must've practiced.
I'm sorry, but can you smile brightly for us?
- So Min. - What?
Don't smile.
(Refreshing)
- Amazing. - Don't smile!
Gosh!
Are you trying to kill me?
(His sense of shame is creeping up on him.)
(I can't help but laugh.)
(He doesn't just laugh.)
(He faints too.)
(Her smile, which is as refreshing as glacial acetic acid, )
(makes him faint for the third time today.)
My goodness.
This is driving me crazy. Don't do that.
- Do you want to see us go crazy? - My heart is stopping.
(Laughing)
- Don't smile. - Can you turn around...
(Everyone's chiming in.)
- while flipping your hair? - Jong Kook,
don't you have anything to say?
- Goodness. - Don't you have anything to say?
He reached his limit.
(He acts like a robot to the sudden request.)
He's like a robot.
He's about to die. He really is.
Don't do it.
(So Min asks the first question...)
I will give you my question now.
(in the midst of everyone's passion.)
I once had a huge fight...
with my ex-boyfriend over something really small.
- What was the reason? - It was small?
It really wasn't that big.
Let me answer. So Min changed something.
(Passionate)
You cut your bangs or something, and he didn't say anything about...
- the small look of change... - The small look of change?
The small look of change? What does that mean?
(It's slightly wrong...)
(due to his eager passion.)
- What does that mean? - Let me answer!
So Min gave her boyfriend a short kiss,
and he wiped his mouth after.
No.
(It's wrong.)
You were kissing, but he was kissing you while looking at his phone.
No.
(His mouth and eyes act separately.)
- Is that how he did it? - Gosh, that is...
(Everyone is uncomfortable with the bad reenactment.)
Is that what happened?
It's similar to Ji Hyo's question.
(It's similar to Ji Hyo's squid incident.)
Which one?
- The drama. - It has to do with something...
(The two liked the same thing.)
- you like and something he likes. - Right.
- I'll give you another hint. - Okay.
This one is a big one.
It happened at a convenience store.
(It happened at a convenience store.)
At a convenience store?
- At a convenience store? - You ate something.
It was around 2am.
(It was around 2am.)
- At 2am? - My boyfriend...
(My boyfriend said he missed me and came to my neighborhood.)
said he missed me and came to my neighborhood.
We walked around the park...
and went into a convenience store because we were hungry.
(We went into a convenience store because we were hungry.)
- Because you were hungry? - Yes.
Let me answer.
You went on a date and shared a short kiss.
Then he went into the convenience store...
and bought gum for you.
(Gum, my foot.)
- That's the worst. - You said you went into...
a convenience store.
What was that?
She slapped your face with her bare hand.
(Stunned)
She was considerate of you.
(She actually was nice.)
She hit you with a smaller hand.
I hit his neck.
- She hit you with a smaller hand. - You're right.
When did this happen?
- How many years ago? - This was when I was...
- When I was 26 years old. - 26 years old.
- Is it related to your age? - Hold on.
(If you were 26 years old...)
It must be that guy.
Who do you think it is?
(Holding up her guard)
Isn't it the guy from Cheongju?
It's not him.
(An unexpected revelation of past relationships.)
- Why do you want to know? - It's not that.
- I was just curious. - Why?
- Let me answer. - Okay.
He went to pay, but he didn't have money.
- Who? - Your boyfriend.
(He was young and didn't have much money.)
So he left you there and said he'd come back with cash.
Is it a pawnshop?
(He left his girlfriend as a pawn inside the convenience store?)
He said he'd be right back,
and that upset you.
No, but that has happened to me before.
- My boyfriend... - Seriously?
said he would wire the money,
(Her boyfriend did leave her behind to wire the money.)
and he left me there.
- That happened? - But it didn't upset me.
(Happily)
- That really happened? - Yes.
- We didn't have money then. - You weren't upset?
- I wasn't. - So Min...
- has experienced everything. - It didn't upset you?
(She's filled with unique love stories.)
It was when we were really poor.
- So you thought it could happen. - What could this be?
(Penniless 26-year-olds?)
Let me answer.
You bought triangular gimbap to eat,
but he didn't unwrap yours for you.
- Incorrect. - Let me answer!
There was only one left of your favorite, chicken and mayo,
but he ate it himself.
- Wrong. - Let me answer.
He ate the center... of the triangular gimbap...
(He tries again.)
- He ate it? - where all the filling is.
- And he gave her the corner? - Yes.
He gave her the corner.
(He ate the filling and gave the rest to So Min?)
- That's correct. - Seriously?
(That's correct.)
(The love fight among 26-year-olds was for a really small reason.)
- Is this a reason to get upset? - No.
- I can't believe I got it right. - It could be really upsetting.
(He's shocked that he guessed it correctly.)
- I got it right. - This is what happened.
Is this a reason to get upset?
(He can't understand.)
We went to the convenience store to eat a triangular gimbap.
(The hungry couple got a triangular gimbap.)
He opened it up and gave it to me to take the first bite.
(The boyfriend asked So Min to have a bite first.)
- In my opinion, the first bite... - Right.
(The problem is...)
- only has white rice in it. - That's right.
You're right.
- It's like Chungmu-style gimbap. - He ate the center himself,
and he gave me the corners which is like the crust of bread.
(Her sadness exploded...)
(at the bite of the plain white rice.)
- That hurt my feelings. - That's why you were upset.
This was really upsetting to you,
but it wasn't upsetting when your boyfriend left you to get money?
(Laughing)
- It didn't. - It's her style.
The people that So Min dated must be surprised when they watch TV...
(Looking at this...)
since she talks about them.
I don't like how you're making sarcastic remarks.
You were being sarcastic. Besides, you should be jealous...
- when I talk about these things. - Right.
(Me?)
Right. You should ask her why she's talking about her ex-boyfriend.
(She adds another badge in anger.)
- You should get mad about it. - Wait. Why would I... Hold on.
(Flustered)
I'm a student too.
(A jealous, obsessive type)
Even if you're a student,
(It's your fault.)
- you should get mad about that. - Right.
(He accepts immediately.)
- At those jerks? - Why would you laugh?
I'm going to watch you. During the next question,
- you need to get really mad. - Okay.
(She forces him to be jealous.)
- Those jerks. Okay. - Right.
(He gets prepared with fake jealousy.)
- This is the next question. This... - Is it about a guy again?
(The next question after brainwashing.)
Yes.
(His jealousy switch is turned on immediately.)
- Say you don't want her to ask it. - Why are you smiling?
I don't want you to ask it.
Why? Why don't you want me to ask it?
- It's because I'm jealous. - What are you jealous about?
I don't want you to ask it.
(Weekend Drama, "Jealousy Incarnate")
- Why don't you want me to ask it? - It's because I'm jealous.
What are you jealous about? Do I belong to you?
I hate that they treated you that way.
Do you get it?
I hate that they treated you that way. Do you get it?
(The guy's jealousy makes the girl smile.)
- She didn't even ask her question. - Hurry up and ask it.
(I can't watch this anymore.)
- She likes it. - She does.
What's going on between you two?
(Happy)
- What's up with you two? - Are you...
(It's a forced melodrama with brainwashed jealousy.)
Why do you act like this on set?
I almost vomited.
(I don't feel well.)
"Do I belong to you?"
(A tragic romance that makes the viewers sick)
This is fun. I love it.
I almost vomited, seriously.
(It's so hard to avoid the penalty.)
"Do I belong to you?"
(The last question after a drama)
There's something that I did...
for all of my past boyfriends. What is it?
You did this every time?
(It's a quiz on So Min's relationship patterns.)
Yes. It is how I express my love.
Let me answer. You nursed them back to health.
- Incorrect. - Do they all need to be sick?
(All of her ex-boyfriends were quite ill?)
- Must your boyfriends be sick? - My goodness.
But I've done it often.
(She actually took care of her boyfriends many times.)
One of my ex-boyfriends broke his finger,
- so I covered his hand for him. - Right. I remember how you told me.
I heard she's quite devoted.
(He tries to gain her favor in between.)
Yes, I'm good to them.
Let me answer. You make a scarf for them when the weather gets colder.
(Hesitating)
- No way. - Is that the answer?
The thing is... The thing you have to get right...
(If I were to give you a clearer hint...)
There is a specific color.
(Of the scarf)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
- A red scarf. - Hold on.
You make a scarf for all of your boyfriends in the same color?
(What is that?)
- No. - This...
(Wait.)
- This could be upsetting. - It's not that.
Guess it correctly first.
- We have to guess the color, right? - Yes.
Let me answer. Black.
- Correct. - What?
- Did you receive one? - No, I didn't! What are you saying?
(Did you receive one?)
- Did you receive one? - No, I didn't!
("Did Se Chan Receive a Black Scarf from So Min?")
- Did you receive it? - No!
- Isn't this a scarf? - Come here.
- Come here. - Isn't this a scarf?
(The black scarf scandal is getting out of hand.)
You punk. You received one, didn't you?
Hold on.
- Do you know why I got chills? - Why?
- How did you get it right? - Listen.
(Black)
Black isn't the color people usually choose.
(Fact check)
So Min did give me a scarf once.
- It was black. - Really?
(Did she give a black scarf to Se Chan?)
So I thought it might be the answer.
- As a birthday gift, - I see.
(Suspicions grow on the truth about the black scarf.)
So Min gave me a store-bought scarf.
It wasn't handmade. It was store-bought.
(She didn't make it for him. It was a store-bought scarf.)
It was store-bought.
So much effort goes into knitting a scarf.
(Flattering)
It's a work of effort.
You think about that person while you knit.
(Very satisfied)
Isn't it a nice gift? They never really liked the scarf.
- It's a nice gift. - It's a nice gift, So Min.
(They answer right away.)
(They give the answer she wants to win her favor.)
One cold winter day,
a boy I was interested in took off his scarf...
(The guy took the scarf off and put it on So Min.)
- and put it around my neck. - Did it smell like his cologne?
No, it smelled like his spit. But I still liked it.
(Not cologne)
He was someone who drooled.
(Wet)
What kind of comment is that?
(He has creative thinking.)
He probably couldn't help but drool when he looked at you.
That's right.
How was he supposed to close his mouth?
You are the best.
It was like royal jelly.
(Flattering)
(The master of creativity faces a crisis.)
How was he supposed to close his mouth?
Stop it already.
(He is drinking water for the 4th time today.)
It must be exhausting.
I need to give away two bomb badges, right?
(He's passing out for the 4th time today.)
I will give them to Kwang Soo since he went overboard.
(The bomb badge)
- I can't stand watching him. - Good job.
(His overreaction ended up bringing a disastrous result.)
I can't stand watching him.
- Good job. - Yamada.
(Stop it.)
(Yamada explodes due to his surprise attack.)
- Yamada. - Yamada.
- Are you really giving them to me? - Yes.
(He receives 2 bomb badges.)
- Yamada. - This is...
- I will give them to Haha. - Okay.
(The result of badge distribution to those who got it)
It will be a match between three people.
(The current number of bomb badges)
- Okay. - Okay.
- The second mission came to an end. - Okay.
(The second mission ends.)
Hidden rules will now be applied to the female members.
(A hidden rule will be added to Ji Hyo and So Min.)
See you at the final mission.
(The hidden rule will be revealed in the final race.)
- Okay. - Is it the final mission?
The final mission.
You are done, right?
(The bomb badge)
Do you think I am done?
(Se Chan and So Min are fighting before the race begins.)
Se Chan is looking down on me and saying that I am done.
Get it together, okay?
(Recording on So Min's phone)
- What? - Get it together.
For goodness sake! I could knuckle your head!
Come here.
(I can't take it anymore.)
Why? We aren't shooting yet.
(Recording on So Min's phone)
- We are shooting. - No, no.
- Take them. You crossed the line. - No, no.
- There are too many. - Okay. I will take two out.
(He gets a lot of bomb badges for being flippant.)
- Give me two. - Go.
He acts differently when cameras aren't around.
(So Min leaves all angry.)
It's so exhausting.
- What did you say? What did he say? - It's so nice.
(She heard it.)
(Changing what he said)
- What did he say? - I said it's so nice.
(He flatters as So Min returns.)
- Did he really say that? - I said it's so nice.
- Did he really say that? - It's so nice.
Come on out.
(I could just...)
How could she do that when we aren't filming?
(Complaining)
(Smiling)
(His smile is all business and survival.)
(Satisfied)
- You are doing well. - Okay.
(A sweet time with So Min comes to an end.)
- It's time for the final mission. - Gosh, this is...
It's Don't Touch Me: Up and Down.
(Don't Touch Me: Up and Down)
Male members must avoid the penalty...
(Male members must make the others get more bomb badges.)
by making the others get more bomb badges.
As for the sisters, only one can win the prize.
(Only 1 of the sisters can win the prize.)
I told you that you won't have a penalty today.
(Revealing the hidden rule for the sisters)
One of you will receive a penalty during the opening next week.
(There's no penalty today, )
- Okay. - So it won't happen this week.
That makes me feel happy.
(but 1 of them will receive a penalty...)
(during the opening next week.)
One of them will receive a penalty next week.
(Nice)
- He loves it. - A penalty during the opening?
(Snitching)
We were doing it for circulation.
(Startled)
I will explain the rules.
In the building are nine boxes containing a whistle.
(There are 9 whistles hidden in the building.)
A whistle.
The race ends once either of the sisters blows...
(The race ends once either of the sisters blows 4 whistles.)
four whistles.
- It's between the two of them. - The male members...
- will wear a vest like this. - A bulletproof vest.
(They're going to wear special vests.)
As you can see, the number goes up upon touch.
(The number goes up if you touch the pad on the back.)
It's a high-technology.
(High-technology is rare in Running Man.)
Seriously.
Male members need to raise each other's number...
(Male members need to raise each other's number on the back.)
on the back.
(They can't help but laugh upon hearing the rule.)
You can picture what will happen, right?
- Someone will get caught. - Seriously.
(It's obvious. Someone will get caught, )
Everyone else will touch his back and he will go, "Stop it!"
(and everyone else will touch his back.)
- I can picture that. "Stop it!" - But...
(The most number of bombs)
- We need to team up. - But the race isn't so simple.
But the race isn't so simple.
(But that is not all.)
If either of the sister blows the whistle,
(If either of the sisters blows the whistle, everyone needs to pause.)
everyone needs to pause.
The member with the highest number of touches at that moment...
(The member with the highest number will receive 5 bomb badges.)
will receive the bomb badges.
Then the number will get reset to zero.
(Then the number will get reset to 0 after each round.)
When the whistle sounds again, the same process will take place.
The four male members with the most number of badges...
(The 4 male members with the most number of badges...)
(will become the final candidates for the penalty.)
will become the final candidates for the penalty.
Can they give us the badges during the race?
- Of course. - I see.
That sounds like a lot of fun.
It doesn't end.
(The reaction machine is overloaded.)
- Seriously. - You can keep receiving them.
There are multiple boxes which don't contain a whistle.
(There are boxes without a whistle.)
Inside them, you will find a ballot instead.
(A ballot will be inside!)
Male members can write...
(Male members can write...)
the name of a female member who should receive the penalty...
(the name of a female member who should receive the penalty.)
and put it in the ballot box before the end of the race.
- How are we supposed to do that? - We can't write their names!
(Holding back his laughter)
How are we supposed to do that?
(Male members' ballots will determine...)
- It's impossible. - I won't use the ballot.
(who receives the penalty between sisters.)
- This is bad. - Only the 1st and 2nd place matter.
She is nervous. She is nervous about the ballots.
(You deserve it.)
(In despair)
- She is nervous. - Don't be nervous.
So Min, you have no need to be nervous.
(The news of ballots...)
Are you annoyed?
(makes her remember everything she has done today.)
Jong Kook, don't you have anything? Se Chan, hold this.
Don't be like that.
(It's too late to regret.)
Don't worry.
- Don't worry, So Min. - Don't worry.
(Grinning)
It's not like you did anything wrong.
But I...
(Her eyes turn teary.)
So Min.
Let's move to the starting point.
(The final race of cruel revenge begins.)
Okay.
Let's go.
Had I known, I would have been nicer to them.
The race starts.
I need to find the boxes.
(He wants to strike a deal with the whistles and ballots.)
The whistles and...
(Jong Kook goes in search of the whistles and ballots.)
Jong Kook, it's me.
Haha, come here.
(Bowing politely)
All right.
- Haha. - Yes?
Let's raise the count to one.
But we just met.
(Stubborn)
What the... What are you talking about?
(Haha ends up swearing.)
Come on. Let's raise the count to one.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
(Thankfully, Se Chan arrives.)
Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - He is here.
(Lucky)
- Hello. - How far does the number go up?
(Suk Jin joins with no idea.)
I think it keeps going up.
Why don't we take a safety measure?
Shall we do that? Shall we raise his number?
I am sure I will be included in the bottom four.
(The easy targets are here.)
- Hold on. - I am sure I will be included...
- in the bottom four. - Hold on.
(Suk Jin enters the room himself.)
- Why did you stand here? - Shall we go in?
- Let's go in. - Let's go in.
(Shall we have some fun?)
- Let's go in and talk. - Please come on in.
(Gathering)
There is a bed.
It's perfect for lying down.
- All right. - Let's go on the bed.
- Hold on. - Even if I throw someone,
it won't look very violent.
This is meaningless. Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(Desperate)
It's like a team of two.
- Suk Jin, it's like a massage. - Experience it.
- I mean... - It's like a massage.
- A massage. - Let's go.
(Ignoring)
- A massage. - All right.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(It's a massage store.)
(The masseurs are excited to have the first customer.)
- There you go! - There you go!
(Se Chan's crazy touch)
Let's raise it to 100.
(Simply)
A bit more. Let's raise it to 100.
- All right. Okay. - Okay.
(It reached 100.)
That was refreshing.
It was a massage from the younger members.
(Suk Jin wants to return the favor.)
- Thank you. - Okay.
- Thank you. - What?
- What? - Okay.
(Let's give him a massage one more time.)
Let's go.
(It was so nice that Suk Jin came back.)
- There you go! - There you go!
That's enough. I got too much.
I got too much.
(He's 100 percent satisfied with this second visit.)
- You are full, right? - Yes.
Let me pat you on the back.
(I'm grateful.)
- It's okay. - I want to show my gratitude.
- Let's go outside. - I want to show my gratitude.
(His gratitude would never work.)
(One more time?)
- What? - Okay, okay.
(The massage doesn't stop.)
- Okay. - Okay.
You are sneaky.
- You should go on your way. - Okay.
(If you're done...)
I will trust you guys. I will trust you guys to do well.
(Suk Jin doesn't want to receive the massage alone.)
What's my count? Tell me.
- 214. - 214.
Please make someone have a higher number.
- Okay. - Please do that.
(He appeals as he shakes hands like a politician.)
- We will do that. Of course. - Please do that.
This massage shop will be open all day long.
(The massage store is open twenty-four seven.)
Shall I bring someone over here?
- That would be nice. - This is a nice massage shop.
(He wants to tell everyone about this massage store.)
- I will bring someone over here. - That would be nice.
- We will wait. - Please come often.
If I don't come after three minutes,
know that I am held captive.
- I will bring someone over here. - Okay.
(Another customer)
- Just you wait. - Suk Jin.
(Their first regular goes out to do business.)
It will be funny if you show them the number.
Would you yell "The race starts"?
- Would you yell "The race starts"? - The race...
starts.
- Wait here for a second. - Okay.
Whom should I bring?
(Suk Jin's out to attract other customers.)
I need to bring someone who will get a higher number.
I will vote for So Min no matter what.
- She must receive the penalty. - Today,
(The masseurs plan to give So Min a penalty.)
- she enjoyed the perks too much. - I know.
In any case,
- we are a team. - That's right.
- Of course. - Go. Don't worry.
Go. Hey.
(On alert)
- It's not like that. - I don't attack from behind.
- I know that. - Why are you on guard?
- I don't like it when you do that. - Okay, okay.
- Hold on. Why did you... - Look at that.
He is trying to corner me.
(He said they're a team, but he backstabs them.)
- Why did you do that? - It's not like that.
- Why did you do that? - Because of him.
Listen. Are you nervous about something?
Seriously. What are you nervous about?
Look at me. I am comfortable.
(Teasing)
- Why did you do that? - Do what?
- You did this. - It was because of you.
(As Se Chan comes between them, )
It's nothing to be annoyed about.
(Haha's cornered.)
Hold on. Why did you do that?
- It's not like that. - Stay still.
(A massage store opens on the road.)
Stay still. Why did you do that?
Why?
(Former masseur Haha becomes a customer.)
Come on.
- You are done. - Jong Kook.
What do you like so much about that punk?
I am just curious.
(The 1st generation of Jong Kook's right arm is sad.)
- What you did was unnecessary. - That's right.
(That's why...)
To be honest,
you don't need to worry because there is Suk Jin.
You can't beat him. It's game over for him.
(It's not easy to beat Suk Jin's magic number.)
Only one person will receive the penalty badges.
We need to attack 1 of the 3.
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin looks for massage customers.)
(He's making a plan with Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.)
It's meaningless to attack each other.
- We need to team up... - To avoid getting the badges...
(For these 3 to avoid the penalty, )
- and catch one of them. - To avoid getting the badges,
we need to attack 1 of the 3.
(they must give the bombs to the other 3.)
We shouldn't attack each other. What's your number? Let's see.
Jae Suk!
What's your number?
(He moves his finger every time he sees someone's back.)
- This is meaningless. - Don't do that.
To go up,
we need to pull down those who are above us.
(For us to survive)
We can do it.
(Let's trust each other...)
(or not.)
(The free-hug and massage)
(They do ganggangsullae even though it's past Chuseok.)
- Hey! - We shouldn't do that.
- Come to your senses. - Don't be like that.
(Brazen)
- It's meaningless. - Stop it!
(The 3 with most bombs blow up.)
What was that?
Stop it!
Let's put our arms around each other...
as if this is the Oath of the Peach Garden.
- Let's trust each other. - We will be like Liu Bei, Guan Yu,
(The promise of sworn brothers)
- and Zhang Fei. - Let's not attack each other.
(They promise to trust each other.)
It's meaningless. We need to pull down those...
who are above us.
I said it's meaningless!
(Their trust shatters.)
(The ganggangsullae of betrayal is back.)
(The Oath of the Peach Garden broke in 5 seconds.)
(Panting)
What's my number?
(While they betray each other endlessly)
I need to find the whistles.
(Where are the whistles?)
I don't need to win the prize,
but I want to avoid the penalty.
(Haha is looking for the whistles or ballots.)
(He finds something.)
(Haha found a ballot.)
Nice! This is nice.
(People feel that something is up and approach Haha.)
Haha.
(He sees the box in his hand.)
Did you find it?
(They try to steal it.)
(Haha tries to run away.)
Catch him.
(He chases Haha to steal the ballot.)
That's good. Chase after him.
- Come here. - Hey.
(Haha got caught in the end.)
Come here.
Why me?
(He gets a massage since he found a ballot.)
You punk.
I will do it.
(The massage master appears after hearing the news.)
I will do it. I can tap fast.
Who are you to do it?
(This customer is touched.)
Get the number up.
(The expert masseur's gentle touches)
- Come on. - Stop it!
(The number goes over 400.)
Let's go!
(He is a professional.)
(He is so fast.)
- No! - Get the number up.
- Get the number up. - Let go of me!
(The customer is satisfied.)
Get the number up.
You traitor!
(Where is Jae Suk? He was with Haha.)
- That's good. - Stay still!
Everyone.
(He takes out a box from his pocket.)
What is that?
(Is it a ballot or a whistle?)
- It's a whistle. - Is it a whistle?
(My goodness.)
(Does Jae Suk have a whistle?)
(He searched everywhere as soon as the race started.)
(He found a whistle.)
Soon, I will give it to someone.
The member with the highest number of touches at that moment...
(When the whistle is blown, )
will receive the bomb badges.
(the member with the highest number will receive 5 bomb badges.)
(Haha beat Suk Jin with a minor difference.)
Let go of me.
Hold on. He is being a nuisance.
If you blow it now...
(What do I do?)
Hold on.
- Give it to Ji Hyo. - If you blow it now,
(As they approach, )
Haha will get the badges.
(Jae Suk hands over the whistle to Ji Hyo.)
(Haha's count is the highest right now.)
Haha's count is the highest right now.
(Arrested)
- Blow it! - Don't blow it yet!
(Kwang Soo grabs Jae Suk.)
(While he grabs Jae Suk, all masseurs gather.)
- Don't blow it yet! - Blow it! Blow it!
(She's about to blow it.)
- Don't blow it yet! - You need to blow it!
- Don't blow it yet! - Blow it! Blow it!
(Ji Hyo.)
- Don't blow it yet! - You need to blow it!
- Don't blow it yet! - Hey!
(Touching as fast as they can)
Blow it! You need to blow it, Ji Hyo!
(Jae Suk's number rises exponentially.)
You need to blow it, Ji Hyo!
Don't be like that!
(Whistle)
- Don't blow it! - Don't be like that!
(Since she blew the whistle, everyone pauses.)
There you go.
(We could have given the badges to Jae Suk.)
- Why did you blow it? - Why did you blow it?
- You shouldn't have blown it. - It's 150. It's meaningless.
(Thanks, Ji Hyo.)
Let's check the counts.
(Checking the number)
The first set of badges will go...
- to Haha. - Me?
(Haha will receive 5 badges as a result.)
Haha's count is 567.
(It's 567.)
Haha's count rose so much.
(The master of the touch)
Let's go!
You shouldn't have blown it.
(Sad)
(A close call)
Ji Hyo, you did an amazing job.
(Haha receives 5 bomb badges.)
- Did you reset the machine? - Yes!
(The race begins after resetting.)
Let's resume.
Ji Hyo, what is it going to be?
(Haha has nothing to lose.)
Will you hold on to those 15 badges?
- You decide. - Give them to Se Chan.
(He threatens her to give Se Chan 15 badges.)
- Why me? - Se Chan. Okay?
- Okay. - Give them as soon as it starts.
(His anger has reached its max.)
- Right now, he is... - He is sullen, right?
(He means it.)
He is angry at me.
Four male members will be picked.
(This is all because of Yang Se Chan.)
I will make sure to drag him with me.
(The bottom 4)
(He's going to drag Se Chan in.)
Okay?
I put in the ballot.
(If Haha writes So Min's name in the ballot, )
I put in the ballot. Give him 15 badges.
(Ji Hyo will give Se Chan 15 badges.)
- Ji Hyo. - Se Chan, here you go.
(He suddenly gets 15 bomb badges.)
- You're giving him that many? - What is this?
(Haha. You want to do this?)
I am done. It's over.
- I will get you today! - Bring it on!
(He runs over to Haha.)
- Come here. - Bring it on!
Bring it on. Bring it on.
(It's their own league.)
- Let's take this to the end. - Sure.
Don't mind us!
- Let's go! - We are close, that's all.
- Let's go. - Let's take this to the end.
Don't mind us.
(They embrace each other.)
Let's take this to the end.
(Their touches are warm.)
This is good.
(They are pathetic.)
What's the count?
Let's do this until the race ends, okay?
(Their touches never end.)
I refuse to lose!
(After giving each other the warm touches)
What's the count?
You little...
How did it become 443?
(Se Chan 312 versus Haha 443)
Hey!
(The difference is 131.)
- Haha. - How did you do that?
You can't beat me.
(You can never catch up with the touch master.)
This is driving me crazy. What should I do?
(Haha's anger level rises.)
I should find a ballot and vote.
(Jong Kook's looking for a ballot.)
(Looking around)
What? Okay.
(He finds a box.)
Did you find one?
(He touches Jong Kook's screen...)
For goodness' sake.
(and gets caught.)
Why would you touch my screen when other members' counts are high?
(You dared to touch me?)
I wanted to...
(The acupressure masseur is here.)
Listen to me! Listen to me!
(Punching)
Darn you! Stop it!
(Kwang Soo attacked to protect himself.)
- Is this where the party is at? - No.
(He heard the word.)
- Yes, it is. - No, no.
(A massage store opens.)
- No! - Press him down.
(He rejects the massage.)
- Stop it! Stop it! - It's "Tazza: The Hidden Card".
(However)
Hold on. Turn this back on.
We need to pull down the top two.
(The app on Kwang Soo's pad got turned off.)
(Meanwhile)
We need to pull down the top two. Otherwise, it's meaningless.
(Kwang Soo takes off his sock.)
- What are you talking about? - Otherwise, it's meaningless.
(He tries to touch the screen with his toes.)
Your sock...
- Otherwise, it's meaningless. - Your sock...
(The unexpected tactic)
- Your sock... - Lift him up.
(He tries to use his long leg, )
You need to lift him up.
(but fails.)
- Lift him up. - Get back, you punk.
(He vents his anger on the producer.)
- We need to turn it back on. - What are you doing?
(He grabs the producer by his hair.)
Let go.
Reset it.
(Out of control)
Turn it off. Lock it.
Lock it. Otherwise, I will rip off your hair.
(His hair)
Let's go. I need to focus.
(The app is back on.)
Se Chan, you must have played a lot of mobile games.
(The touch master shows what he's got.)
- You must have done that. - Yes, Jong Kook.
The number is already over 200.
(Kwang Soo's misfortune is our happiness.)
It should be over 600.
(His fingers move like crazy.)
He is no joke, right? He is so fast.
(He struggles desperately.)
It should be over 600.
Let go. Let go.
- Let go. - He is no joke, right?
- Hey! I am speaking as a senior. - It's over 300.
- I am in a bad mood right now. - It should be over 600.
Se Chan, I am speaking as a senior.
(I am in a good mood, Kwang Soo.)
When have I ever been...
- It's over 400. - Hey.
When have I ever been so serious?
- Se Chan! - Kwang Soo.
- Let's go. - It's over 600.
(Kwang Soo keeps trying to set the pecking order by himself.)
Se Chan.
I am not joking around. 1, 2...
- All right. - Okay.
(As soon as he gets released, )
(he attacks back.)
Touch the screen from the back.
(However, )
(Jong Kook and Haha attack this time.)
Touch the screen from the back.
It's over 700.
Jae Suk!
(Seeing his call for Jae Suk makes them feel bad.)
Okay, okay. That's enough.
(The touch ends.)
We are done.
(You won't get away with this, Yang Se Chan.)
That was no way to treat a senior.
Wait and see.
(While Kwang Soo suffers, )
I should go and vote.
The first floor.
(So Min shows up with something in her hand.)
What is that mission envelope?
It's a ballot.
(So Min found a ballot.)
Really? Where did you get it? Did you find it?
But So Min can't vote.
(The Sisters can't vote.)
No, I can't. I need to give it to someone.
I need to give it to someone.
Isn't it a bit heartbreaking to see her work so hard?
I feel bad.
(Pitiful)
It's bound to be her, right? It's bound to be her.
(She will probably get the penalty no matter how hard she tries.)
It's an empty box.
Someone must have taken what was inside.
When you think about it, So Min enjoyed the perks.
(She will pay the price for the perks she enjoyed.)
To be honest, she was too much of a nuisance.
Ji Hyo was so polite compared to So Min.
(Ji Hyo's nothing compare to So Min.)
You need to do well when you are in a high position.
(The more power you have, the more careful you should be.)
- That's right. - She enjoyed the perks too much.
What's the current score?
(So Min who didn't take care of others is nervous.)
I mean the number on the back.
(Right then, Ji Hyo blows the second whistle.)
So Min, the public opinion about you...
isn't very favorable.
Kwang Soo will receive five bomb badges.
(Kwang Soo gets 5 bomb badges.)
(Haha, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan keep collecting the badges.)
Kwang Soo, I have a suggestion. Listen to me.
Jong Kook doesn't have any badges.
(Jong Kook and Jae Suk have relatively fewer badges.)
We need to get Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is so annoying. - He needs to get five badges.
Buy me some time.
Just hold him in place.
(They decide to attack Jae Suk together.)
- Se Chan's fingers are the fastest. - Let's do this.
Jae Suk is over there.
(Right on time)
How many bomb badges do you have?
Are these all?
(They approach him as if they're checking the badges.)
I have more.
Jae Suk, let's go somewhere spacious.
(Straightforward)
Your body probably aches.
- You need a massage. - Hold on.
(We'll give you a massage.)
- Just give me a few seconds. - Hold on.
All right.
(As they insist, )
Let's go somewhere spacious. You need to think about your health.
- Come here. - Will you give him a massage?
(he enters the massage store.)
Yes, I will.
- Hey. - Hold his arms.
(He lies down comfortably...)
Hold his arms.
You little...
(and gets a back massage.)
- His fingers are so fast. - Hey.
- He must have played mobile games. - Let go of me. Let go of me!
(Happy)
- Let's switch. - Let go of me.
(Switching masseurs)
I can't believe you guys.
- Gosh, Jae Suk. - Hey.
It looks like he's playing a game.
(So Min was watching from the side.)
- There's a lot more. - Right now...
you're in 1st, no 2nd place.
(She approaches someone in silence and touches.)
- Let go of me. - I won't let you get away.
Let go of me.
(A change in target)
- Jae Suk. - It's going up.
(He has no idea.)
- Let's pass the baton. - Okay.
You punks.
(Se Chan attacks Kwang Soo.)
- Gosh, Jae Suk. - It's going up.
(A Moebius strip of touch that goes around.)
You guys are all...
full of love here.
(A small but certain happiness)
Hey. That's enough already.
(It exceeded 300.)
300 is enough.
(He barely escapes.)
You punks.
(He got caught.)
(Touch nightmare)
Just keep in mind...
(Jae Suk versus Kwang Soo)
that the two of you are neck and neck.
- We... - We need to raise Jae Suk's.
(It'll be a competitive battle among the last 4 people.)
- I have a lot. - I...
You and I are already fixed.
Is Jong Kook a ghost?
Why isn't anyone paying attention to him?
Do you think you could get into his bulletproof vest?
He's impossible to get to.
(Same vest, different feeling)
Someone should pay a bit of attention to him.
I gave him 2 and got 500 in return.
(He learns a lesson with 500 counts.)
How can I go in?
- You can do this. - Let me see.
Isn't this too much?
(Suk Jin checks how many they have.)
- Oh, my. - How many do I have?
You're in the 300s, and he's in the 400s.
- Me? - Yes.
(No way. I have 400?)
You're in the 300s, and he's in the 400s.
- Me? - Yes.
(That's weird. I'm pretty sure I didn't have that many before.)
Jong Kook was being cunning, and he tapped you...
from behind for a while.
- Really? - I've never seen him so happy.
(The man in the bulletproof vest's hidden instinct to be cunning)
(A dark hand slides over.)
- I'm in the top five already. - No, you're not.
(His nose got wider.)
Jae Suk is in second place right now.
(The results of touching it quickly and secretly)
- No, he's not. - Take a look at his badges.
(It has exceeded 400.)
I've never...
(He's so happy.)
I've never seen him so happy before.
- Suk Jin and I... - He has 450.
(He checks with the camera.)
He has 450.
(He is in the last place without knowing.)
What's important is that we must find the whistle.
What's important is...
(At that moment)
What's important is that we must find the whistle.
(Ji Hyo has a whistle in her hand?)
What's important is that I have a whistle.
I have a whistle.
(She has the 3rd whistle in her hand.)
(Se Chan found a whistle earlier.)
- Okay. I found a whistle. - Amazing.
- Is that a whistle? - Yes, it is.
I'll give this to Ji Hyo.
(He gives it to Ji Hyo, who was standing next to him.)
Between the 2 of you, 1 person will be decided.
(Jae Suk versus Kwang Soo)
- I'm blowing it in one minute. - Hold on.
Between the 2 of you, 1 person will be decided.
(They suddenly have a time limit of 1 minute.)
- I'm blowing it in one minute. - Hold on.
I'm going to blow it in one minute.
(The last 4 members exchange looks.)
- Get over here. - Get over here.
(They attack Jae Suk all at the same time.)
- In 1 minute? - In 1 minute.
- Just give us 30 seconds. - 30 seconds.
(The rank can change if Jae Suk gets the badge.)
Grab him. Hurry.
Ji Hyo!
(They plan to escape by making Jae Suk lose.)
- Hold onto his legs. - Ji Hyo!
- Hold onto his legs. - It's going up.
Hold onto his legs.
(The touch masters are very eager.)
(Impressed)
Gosh, Se Chan is fast. We got him.
We got him.
When is the minute over?
(Exceeded 500)
Hold onto him! Blow the whistle!
(But at that moment)
Hurry!
(While Se Chan attacks Jae Suk, Jae Suk tries to fight back.)
(Both of their numbers go up.)
(Both go up rapidly at the same time.)
Just trust me.
Gosh. Jae Suk is fast too.
- What is this? He's fast. - Jae Suk is fast.
(It's close.)
- 2, 1. - We don't know who will win.
- Blow the whistle! - We don't know who will win.
(Interesting)
- 5. 4. - Hurry up!
(After the close match, )
- Three. - Gosh, they're fast.
(who will take the 5 badges?)
- Two. - We don't know who will win.
- One. - Blow the whistle!
Blow it!
(Blowing)
What's the result? Jae Suk was fast too.
(Between Kwang Soo and Jae Suk, who has more?)
I don't know. I couldn't tell who would win.
Let me see. How many do you have?
Let's see. How many do you have?
(Jae Suk has...)
Let's see.
(678.)
(How many does Kwang Soo have?)
- He has a lot too. - No, Jae Suk has more.
(Kwang Soo has 533.)
Okay. Yoo Jae Suk will get five additional badges.
Okay!
Jae Suk will get five additional badges.
(According to the third whistle, Jae Suk gets 5 more bomb badges.)
Okay!
We won't know the results then.
(It's hard to tell who will be the bottom 4.)
- You and I are set. - I'm set.
(Who will be the bottom 4 between Jae Suk and Kwang Soo?)
It's really a fight between the two of you.
It's a fight between these three.
How many whistles did we blow?
(There's only one more whistle.)
Do we only have one more left?
Can you tell us who is fighting whom?
It's a competition between the five of you.
(All five of them have a similar number of badges.)
Right.
But it's pretty much between you and Kwang Soo.
- Bring a whistle then. - How many are there in total?
(It all depends who has the last whistle.)
Everyone, be quiet.
(At that moment)
(Kwang Soo appears with a whistle.)
- Who are you to say that? - Be quiet. Gather around.
(It's the fourth whistle that will determine the game.)
- Be quiet. - Okay.
Give me the whistle.
Give me the whistle. Hurry.
(So Min needs that power because she is losing in votes.)
If you give it to me... No.
- I'm already set. - Hurry up and give me the whistle.
(Jae Suk is pressed for time since Kwang Soo found a whistle.)
If you give the badge to Jae Suk, I'll give it to you.
(The bomb badges)
That's good. Trust him.
I promise. I'll put it around your neck.
(I'm serious.)
- Trust him. - I'm serious.
(Kwang Soo asks her by putting the whistle around her neck.)
This is a TV show.
If you give it to Jae Suk, I'll let go of it.
How can I trust you after all you've done?
(The winners and losers will be determined by this negotiation.)
If you give it to Jae Suk, I'll let go of it.
Hold on. So Min.
(She gives one badge.)
It's meaningless for me to get it.
He can't give it to Ji Hyo.
(Wait a minute.)
Hold on. So Min.
(When the negotiation is about to be completed...)
- It's meaningless for me to get it. - Hey, So Min.
Check to see if there's a whistle. It doesn't look like it has one.
(What?)
(There is no whistle?)
(Grab Lee Kwang Soo!)
Grab him! Grab Kwang Soo!
Grab him! Hurry.
(Exactly 3 minutes ago...)
(Ripping)
(He separates the whistle.)
(After he prepares everything, )
If you give the badge to Jae Suk, I'll give it to you.
(He approaches So Min with dull eyes.)
Grab Kwang Soo! Hurry. Hurry up and grab him.
(But he's found.)
This is the real one. Hold on.
(I caught you.)
(They're seriously fighting right now.)
This is real.
- I'm so annoyed. Gosh. - What do you mean?
(Why are they fighting?)
This is a complete mess.
(One person must die for this fight to end.)
(She uses on-ground techniques.)
- Hey, So Min. - Let's not...
Let's not...
(The Kwang-Fool Siblings return to how they were through a fight.)
Hey, guys.
Someone flip him over.
(Taking off)
Gosh.
(She took off his vest?)
Hey!
Someone flip him over.
(She takes off Kwang Soo's vest...)
(and uses all her might to touch the screen.)
(Let's both die today.)
Do you know how mad I am?
- You know it's meaningless, right? - How many do you have?
(Jae Suk is curious to know his number.)
How many is it? It's hard to calculate it.
- How many do I have? - 101.
(Jae Suk has 101.)
This is meaningless.
(Se Chan has 49.)
(Haha has 85.)
In my opinion, So Min is acting...
(At this rate, Jae Suk will get another five badges.)
out of personal anger.
(Jae Suk realizes he's in trouble...)
(and carefully joins the fight.)
Press it!
(And a lion joins the fight too.)
(As Jae Suk's number go up quickly...)
It would be amazing if someone ran off with this.
(Is he stealing the vest?)
(Jae Suk, who has 150, successfully steals Kwang Soo's vest.)
This is incredible.
(He begins to tap it like crazy.)
(Kwang Soo's numbers are about to exceed Jae Suk.)
You have to blow the whistle now!
(His target is Superstar Song.)
(Will the whistle get blown first, )
(or will his numbers rise up first?)
Don't blow it. Don't blow it, Ji Hyo.
It's over.
(He puts the whistle by her lips...)
(and pinches her side.)
(The final whistle has been blown.)
Jae Suk. Jae Suk!
Okay. Kwang Soo has...
(Kwang Soo has 192.)
- 192. - I could've done more.
How many do I have?
(Jae Suk has 150.)
- You have 150. - Gosh.
(The last 5 bomb badges will go to Kwang Soo.)
Gosh. That was...
(The race is over. Who will get the penalty?)
We don't know how this will end.
I wonder how it ended.
(Which star will win today and avoid the penalty next week?)
(The announcement of the final results)
Everyone. I will announce the results.
(Between So Min and Ji Hyo, a person who gets more votes...)
- Okay. - I lost.
One of you will have to...
(will have to perform a penalty during the opening next week.)
do a penalty during next week's opening.
(The male members have a total of 9 valid votes.)
There was a total of nine votes.
I did everything for this.
(Who got more votes and will receive the penalty?)
Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo has four votes.
So Min has five votes.
Ji Hyo has four, so So Min will get the penalty.
(So Min will get the penalty next week.)
- I'd like to see the results. - Yes.
(After So Min's penalty, it's time to announce men's ranks.)
Okay. The person in first place is...
- It's Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
- Right. - How many did he have?
He had three.
(The first two ranks will avoid the penalty.)
- He only had three? - I was very lonely today.
- Right. - It's true.
I'll announce the person in sixth place.
(Who is in the last place?)
That's the person in last place.
With a total of 29...
- It's not that many. - It's Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo with 29. - I'm in last place?
(Wasn't I a candidate for the 2nd place?)
You had 29.
Why did you have so many?
(Kwang Soo thought he'd be in 2nd place.)
- Last place had 29? - It's because So Min...
(He ranked last after getting badges for fighting So Min.)
kept wandering around and giving me one.
You should've given me the whistle sooner.
I really...
- With 27... - It's me.
It's Suk Jin and Se Chan. You both had 27.
(Suk Jin and Se Chan are tied at 4th place with 27.)
- I had 27? - Yes.
- What's going on? - We're fighting over one spot.
(It's now between Jae Suk and Haha.)
There's only one spot left.
(Only one of them will avoid the penalty.)
- Neither of them survived? - I lived a good life.
What's amazing is that...
1 person has 18, and the other has 17.
(Amazing. It's a close game with a score of 18 versus 17.)
We double-checked it.
(The crew double-checked, and the results are...)
The person who got 18 and will get the penalty is...
(Who came in 3rd place with 1 point and will get the penalty?)
I endured it really well.
Please.
It's Haha.
(Haha will get the penalty.)
(Jae Suk survives with one point.)
(Haha dreamed of a dramatic twist, )
(but it didn't happen, and he will get the penalty.)
- We get the penalty. - What were these two...
(It's the same members again.)
- doing? - What were we doing?
- I'll give you your prizes. - How disappointing.
(It's time to reveal the prizes for the Sisters.)
Look at that.
They're flowers.
(Ji Hyo: flowers and a turntable, So Min: flowers)
Can the 1st and 2nd place winners give them each a bouquet?
- Pretty Ji Hyo. - That's right.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(After Pretty Ji Hyo, it's...)
Okay. Our...
- Our cutie, - He's forcing himself to say it.
pretty,
Jeon So Min. I sincerely congratulate you.
(Star Jeon enjoyed today to the fullest.)
- What's the penalty? - So Min has a penalty next week.
(Everyone's happy at the news of So Min's penalty.)
- What is it? - We'll let you know.
When it comes to penalties... Both of them are good,
(So Min's surprising penalty will be revealed next week.)
- but So Min pulls them off well. - That's right.
- The 4 of you will get the penalty. - I lost by 1 point.
(It's time for the penalty.)
This is driving me crazy.
(Today's penalty: a paint roulette)
You'll sit on this, and someone will spin it.
The person to stop under the bucket will get the penalty.
(The roulette will be turned with 4 men on it.)
(Once the roulette stops, the one underneath the bucket will lose.)
Let's go.
(It's a 25 percent chance.)
This is the real game.
- Let's go this way. - Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. - Let's go!
- Spin it fast. - Let's go.
- Spin it fast. - Spin it faster.
(Even the two top stars are interested.)
- Do you just need to let go? - One more time.
- Yes. - Please.
(Today's race was a mentally draining race.)
- Please. - Please.
- I lost by one. - Red sun!
(Who will be the person to return to the original intention...)
- Please. - I passed it.
(and get the penalty as well?)
- No. Pass it. - It's coming back around.
Pass it. No.
(It passes Suk Jin...)
Pass it.
(and goes to Se Chan.)
- Okay. - No, we don't know yet.
(The person to stop under the bucket and get penalized is...)
I don't know. Who is it?
- Okay. - No, we don't know yet.
Who is this?
Guys.
- It's Haha. - Yes!
(It's Haha.)
(He came in 3rd place, but ended up getting the penalty.)
(Pouring)
- It's pink! - What is that?
(It's thicker than usual. It's the worst paint penalty yet.)
What is that?
It's pink!
(They can't help but groan at the sight of the penalty.)
- It's pink! - Goodness.
- This is the worst. - What is that?
This is the worst penalty.
- It didn't fall on his face though. - It's the worst.
(It's not funny as it misses.)
This is the worst scenario.
It was just one badge!
(Haha's lucky day)
Let's count the badges again.
1, 2, and 3.
(He hits the slate leaving Haha.)
- Darn it. - Let's go.
What just dropped?
(Falling)
Hey. What was that?
Hey, Hyeong Gu!
You're not supposed to be funny.
(The Assistant Director slipped on the paint.)
- Hey, Hyeong Gu. - You're not supposed to be funny.
(Hyeong Gu made people laugh...)
(instead of Haha.)
Hyeong Gu. Are you all right?
(Running Man's involvement system between member and director.)
- It's all over your clothes. - Hyeong Gu.
He's in charge of me.
(Please look forward to the real chemistry of the members.)
Haha, you're so lucky.
Hyeong Gu stole the spotlight.
(The irreplaceable world-class girl group)
- BLACKPINK. - Are they BLACKPINK?
(BLACKPINK is here.)
- It's BLACKPINK! - They're here!
(They are happy to have real guests.)
(BLACKPINK's perfect performance)
(And someone shows up to ruin everything.)
- What's going on? - Is this her penalty?
- That's it. Forget it. - Get out.
(They lose their original intention again only after a week.)
- Get out. - Get out!
(Cross-stitch of BLACKPUNK)
- I'm Jasoo. - BLACKPUNK.
- One more time! - Okay!
(With BLACKPINK, they have an extreme dice race.)
- Roll it. - I got you.
- You have a boyfriend, right? - What are you doing? Stay still!
(If you want to increase the success rate, )
(you have to tell the truth.)
- Do you think you're the prettiest? - Am I prettier?
(Pricking up his ears of the truth)
Do you keep watching the video of my acrostic poem for you?
(Do you keep watching the video of my acrostic poem for you?)
(Pricking up his ears)
You can't hide the truth.
Let's go.
(The war of the girl group begins.)
- Chase the rabbit. - This isn't about killing.
(Who will be the survivor with the highest success rate?)
- It's this realistic? - Chase her!
I've been waiting for them.
(BLACKPINK in Running Man, Save Us From Probability)