- Hello. - Hello.
(Playland in Anseong, Gyeonggi Province)
Hello. Hi, guys.
- Hey. - This place is nice.
(The weather suddenly became cold.)
- I changed my pants. - The weather is nice.
(She's the only one wearing a T-shirt.)
- Why are you guys being so... - It's windy.
- What? - It's a lovely day.
It's chilly in the morning.
So Min says she doesn't feel cold.
She has a hot pack on her back.
- A hot pack in May? - What?
(She's pretending to be strong with a lot of hot packs.)
Why would you need a hot pack in May?
The weather is nice today.
(She's very warm.)
There are Jong Kook and his manager.
I guess he's got a new manager.
- Isn't he the guy who does origami? - He looks like a mischievous boy.
They never wait for me.
It's him. Hello, we're "boogers".
(Is that you?)
Is it Suk Jin?
- He's the origami guy. - Mr. Origami.
I'm a big fan.
Can I get your autograph?
(I'm your big fan.)
He's the guy who teaches us origami.
- It's him. - We saw him a lot in childhood.
(The origami guy is a secret guest.)
They called me the origami guy.
- We're boogers. - He's from the TV show.
- Hello. - I was a big fan.
(They're happy to meet their childhood hero.)
- It's the origami guy. - Wow.
Mr. Ji Young Man.
(Mr. Ji Young Man is on the show.)
He's our guest for today.
- Hello. - Hello, Mr. Origami.
It's him.
(It's really Mr. Origami.)
- Hello. - It's been a really long time.
Hey, how could you call me the origami guy?
(The childhood hero makes her eyes water.)
What?
It's Suk Jin!
What happened?
(They're disappointed that it's actually Suk Jin.)
- It's Suk Jin. - Hello, kids.
It was Suk Jin.
Your outfit is too extreme.
(Serious)
It's not extreme.
You seemed quite close with him over there.
(You seemed quite close with him over there.)
- How could he be like that? - You're the same.
(It turns out he took a step back to make fun of Suk Jin.)
You're being extreme too.
Everyone changes in front of cameras.
(Shaking his head)
You're being extreme too.
The seven of us are attacking him all at once.
(Suk Jin was criticized by seven people for his fashion.)
It's okay.
He's like...
- Shirasoni. - Shirasoni of a variety show.
(He's an amazing talker.)
He fights against several enemies.
"Bring it on!"
(He's the number 1 talker in Korea.)
- He beats us all. - He takes blows well.
He's tough.
(By the way, there's something to talk about.)
All right.
- What's that? - What is it?
(Recently, Jae Suk said,)
- What about Ji Suk Jin? - What's that?
You said this in "You Quiz on the Block ".
("Suk Jin and Kwang Soo are my best friends for life.")
I see. It just came up.
Don't say that. We're not your best friends for life.
(They're not exactly happy to hear that.)
- We are best friends for life. - We just live our own lives.
I mentioned those two because...
I know what you mean.
- You know what I mean, right? - Yes.
(I know what that means.)
I wasn't disappointed at all.
They are the people whom I can control.
- You can control them? - We're not disappointed.
(They know what Jae Suk meant by best friends for life.)
- You all are my best friends. - Sure.
To put it bluntly, we're like his well-trained dogs.
(A best friend means a well-trained dog.)
- Well-trained dogs. - That sounds rough.
(The owner is flustered.)
- To put it bluntly. - That's not true.
You're like his pet dogs.
(That's a cute way to put it.)
Hey.
(Amongst us)
Do you know whom you can't control here?
- Who is it? - It's her.
If you call her, she will call you back a week later.
(It takes a week to get a call back from her.)
- "Did you call me?" - Ji Hyo?
(No one dares to control her life.)
I have no intention to control her.
I texted her after our first shooting of Running Man,
but she hasn't texted me back.
It's been 10 years, but she hasn't replied yet.
(How long does he have to wait?)
- She's Cavewoman Ji Hyo indeed. - Cavewoman Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo cares more about talking in person.)
Let me introduce our guests who will join today's race.
(It's time to introduce the guests.)
- Okay. - Do we have guests?
- This is exciting. - They are there.
(There are four guests who will make today's race special.)
Who are they? He's pretty tall.
(Who are the special guests?)
- It's Chang Wook. - Oh, hello.
Hey.
- Chang Wook. - Have you been doing well?
(The 4 protagonists of "Backstreet Rookie")
Hello, Yoo Jung.
(Ji Chang Wook, Kim Yoo Jung, Han Sunhwa, Do Sang Woo)
Chang Wook, it's been a long time.
Can I start working today?
(Ji Chang Wook, a clumsy but good-looking manager)
She got into a fight with customers, so she's in a police station now.
(A whimsical part-timer, Kim Yoo Jung)
(An unpredictable romantic comedy, "Backstreet Rookie")
You can't sell cigarettes to a minor.
(Han Sunhwa and Do Sang Woo are in the middle of the story too.)
That's when I should've fired her.
(The 4 protagonists of the drama are here.)
She's like a time bomb.
They are the protagonists of the upcoming SBS drama.
"Backstreet Rookie".
Are you their manager or something?
(Kwang Soo)
- What are you talking about? - Are you their manager?
(Manager Kwang Soo says, "Please take care of my actors.")
- Why would you say that? - They are supposed to talk.
- Stay out of this. - The title is "Backstreet Rookie".
- Hang on. - "Backstreet Rookie"?
Sunhwa, are you going somewhere after the opening?
- She brought her bag. - Why did you bring your bag?
(Why is she wearing a bag for the opening?)
- What's that bag? - It's for my fashion.
- It's a fashion item. - I see.
It looks like she's going somewhere.
(They don't understand her fashion.)
After shooting the opening.
Yoo Jung, you're dressed comfortably. You look nice.
Yoo Jung is dressed comfortably,
- but what's wrong with you? - Mind your outfit.
- It makes me dizzy. - You know the origami guy, right?
(The host stands out more than the guest.)
- The origami guy. - We are boogers.
- Yoo Jung wouldn't know him. - I'm trying to look young...
(I'm trying to look young because of Yoo Jung.)
because of Yoo Jung.
You look even younger than her.
(You look even younger than Yoo Jung.)
You're dressed like a newborn baby.
Are you opening a sushi bar or something, Sang Woo?
(Do Sang Woo's Sushi)
You look...
It also looks like a taekwondo uniform.
(It seems like an old sushi restaurant.)
- I know. - It looks like a uniform.
- Martial arts uniform. - I know.
Good. We have Chang Wook here.
There are many celebrities who have Ji as their surnames.
(Ji Chang Wook is the hottest celebrity in the Ji family.)
- And he's one of them. - He's very handsome.
(That handsome guy is...)
He's my junior from high school.
(my junior from high school.)
- Really? - In Anyang.
We went to Shinsung High School.
(Jong Kook cares about school ties.)
Shinsung High School?
(He suddenly starts to sing the school song.)
Nice.
- We went to the same school. - Was it a school song?
Yes, it was.
(He's being childish.)
I thought that's what you said.
(I'll kick you in the butt.)
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
(You may make fun of me, but not my school.)
It just sounded like that.
Is it your real name?
Yes.
(Chang Wook and Suk Jin are from the Chungju Ji Clan.)
- The Chungju Ji Clan? - Yes.
Maybe I should trace my genealogy.
You'll get some colored paper today.
(Booger Chang Wook will get some colored paper.)
Because he's the origami guy.
He will get a hundred origami cranes.
(Chang Wook has both school and blood ties.)
Or origami turtles.
Have you been in a drama with So Min before?
(Have you been in a drama with So Min before?)
- No. - Not even once?
(It's their first encounter.)
No. I don't think we've met.
- Is this your first time? - You haven't met before?
I did a drama with him.
(Chang Wook)
- With Kwang Soo? - What was the drama?
It was "Bachelor's Vegetable Store".
(We did the drama called "Bachelor's Vegetable Store".)
- You were the vegetable man. - Yes.
(Oh, I know.)
- Right? - "Bachelor's Vegetable Store".
(They've found the prey.)
You were the vegetable man.
- Right? - Yes.
You were the eggplant.
- Vegetables. - You were the cucumber.
(Or were you the cucumber?)
He was a vegetable.
No, he was a dried radish.
(Spitting)
(The vegetable man explodes with anger.)
- He was a dried radish. - He was a Chinese yam.
(Calm down, vegetable man.)
- Vegetables. - That's what he was.
(Attacking)
At a vegetable store...
He was a bamboo shoot.
(Bamboo shoot, apple box, scallion)
- Green onion. - An apple box.
(A shishito pepper)
A shishito pepper.
A shishito pepper?
I hate it when the three of them are standing together.
- I feel much better now. - Celery.
(There are inexhaustible kinds of vegetables.)
- That's what he looks like. - Celery.
Celery tastes good though.
(Kwang Soo)
Be patient.
- Patient? - Corn that's gone bad.
(The vegetable man is surprisingly patient.)
Please tell us about your new drama, Yoo Jung and Sunhwa.
(By the way, what kind of drama is "Backstreet Rookie"?)
It's been a long time, Yoo Jung.
The title of our new drama is "Backstreet Rookie".
(It's their only chance to promote their drama.)
(Chang Wook plays the manager.)
I play the manager there.
The manager.
- What about you, Yoo Jung? - I'm a part-timer.
(Yoo Jung plays the part-timer.)
She's a part-timer. It sounds about right.
I work at the head office of the convenience store chain.
(Sunhwa and Sang Woo work at the head office.)
What about you, Sang Woo?
I'm the director at the head office.
- I see. - He's the director.
- So who's the rookie? - The rookie.
(Obviously, the part-timer is the rookie.)
Isn't it obvious? Gosh.
It's obvious who the rookie is.
- Hey. - Suk Jin.
You're dressed like a rookie today.
You're the rookie.
It's the rookie look.
- You're dressed like a rookie. - Hey.
Hey, kid.
He seems to like it.
(His rookie look shocks the original rookie.)
He's the rookie.
All right.
(The four guests will join today's race.)
Please give the four of them a big hand then.
Before I explain the rules,
you will decide your teams.
(They'll divide the team first.)
- Please bring in the mats first. - Mats?
(How will they divide the team?)
What?
Everyone.
There will be 4 groups of 3 members.
(It will be 4 groups of 3.)
The guests will wait in the square.
(The guests will wait in the square.)
And the members will jump into the square of the guest they want.
(And the members will jump into the square of the guest they want.)
(It's a team.)
Once three of you get together, you're a team.
- What if we bounce off? - If you bounce off,
(If the guest doesn't like a member,)
you will have to try again at the end.
(the guest can push the member out of the square.)
- At the end? - Okay. Please stand in the squares.
Which team should I pick?
(They start choosing a team.)
All right then. Ji Hyo and So Min will go first.
So Min, you go first.
- Me? - So Min.
(Do I go first?)
What should I do?
- Whom should I pick? - I know.
(Happy problem)
I feel uncomfortable to go first.
(Snooping)
Can we ask who they want for their teams?
(Interrupting)
Gosh, it's so old-fashioned.
(He's sick of it.)
Mr. Origami!
You're dressed in an old-fashioned way.
(You're embarrassing us.)
I just don't know where to go.
Does anyone of you want me to be your team?
(Me)
- Yoo Jung wants you. - Yoo Jung.
(Thank you, but you're all women.)
- Cool. - Yoo Jung.
- If they raise their hands... - You keep staying...
(Stop right there.)
around Chang Wook.
You were there only for a moment.
She wouldn't go over there.
(She couldn't hide her feelings.)
You keep staying around him. Don't pretend to hesitate.
(So Min got caught just after a few steps.)
Just go to him.
Just go.
I want you two to play rock-paper-scissors.
(She suggests rock-paper-scissors.)
Why? It doesn't even matter.
(Two men play rock-paper-scissors over So Min.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Sang Woo wins.)
(He looks happy to win.)
You don't even care who wins.
Are you going to the winner?
(Congratulations)
He won. He won me.
I should go to him.
(My goodness. I lost.)
I feel bad for him.
He won me.
(Sang Woo won So Min after the fierce match.)
- I should go to him. - What?
I should step on the square.
(Jumping)
You can push her if you don't like her.
(Without hesitation)
I'll go to Chang Wook.
You can push her out.
(She picks Chang Wook.)
- He didn't push me. - This is only the beginning.
(They're both satisfied.)
- He can't push you. - Right.
- He can't do it from the beginning. - Who's next?
(Next up is Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook goes next.
Who would push you out?
(Just go.)
- I know. - You can just hold out.
(It's impossible to reject Jong Kook.)
Okay.
I was going to pick my high school junior.
(Chang Wook)
Chang Wook is fine with it, but Ji Hyo doesn't want you.
(Chang Wook is fine with it, but Ji Hyo doesn't want you.)
Ji Hyo doesn't like me.
(She crosses her arms firmly.)
He wants to take care of his junior from Anyang.
But Ji Hyo is about to kick you out.
(Look at her eyes.)
(I don't know what to do.)
Gosh, I think Ji Hyo is going to kick me out.
I'm interested in the sushi bar too.
(Out of the blue)
- It's a nice place. - It's a nice place.
(It smells great here.)
It's not bad.
I think Sang Woo... How should I explain this?
(I think Sang Woo is...)
- I think he's like us. - Right.
(kind of like us.)
Judging from the way you look, I think you'll be like us.
- And he looks a bit clumsy. - I know.
(He looks clumsy which is familiar to them.)
- He does. - He looks...
(I felt it too.)
a bit like Maeng Gu.
He's a handsome version of Maeng Gu.
(He tries to defend him.)
I know what you mean.
(Chil Deuk admits that he's a handsome version of Maeng Gu.)
- How can Chil Deuk say that? - I already feel close to him.
He does remind me of Kwang Soo.
(He's kind of like Kwang Soo.)
- I like him. - First...
(Will he choose the handsome version of Maeng Gu?)
- Are you going there? - All right.
(They get ready to take a customer.)
This is good.
So Min...
(Jong Kook enters the restaurant.)
(Denied)
(So Min is flustered and Sang Woo grabs him.)
(She felt a chill.)
- She pushed him away. - That's not it.
And Sang Woo caught him.
(The air is cold.)
So Min pushed him away, but Sang Woo caught him.
What?
- I mean... - Okay, I get it.
(She blames Sang Woo all of a sudden.)
You said you wanted Jae Suk on your team.
So Min is in an awkward situation now.
(They'll be like this the whole day.)
She got caught.
All right.
(Now it's Jae Suk's turn.)
- Go. - It's my turn now.
- You're choosing between the two. - I'm choosing between...
(Fixed answer)
- Yoo Jung and Sunhwa. - I know.
- I'm not even looking at the guys. - I can't decide.
(He's not interested in men.)
Are you sure you don't need any knee pads?
(You'll be pushed quite hard.)
- You might hurt yourself. - Put a helmet on him!
Guys, as soon as I join a team,
I'll manage the team closely.
- Who do you think you are? - I'll manage the team closely.
(He'll manage his team closely.)
Keep that in mind.
(They try to avoid eye contact.)
I'll manage my team very closely.
I choose Yoo Jung.
(The strict man chooses Yoo Jung.)
- You're not pushing him away? - You're not pushing him away?
Okay!
(He feels at ease.)
All of them are so nice.
(Special treatment to the first customer)
- You're the first person, so... - Okay.
I've made myself clear.
(Sunhwa is feeling anxious.)
- Gosh, I'm the last one. - It's my turn.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
- Se Chan... - I'll jump...
(He'll skip.)
Please don't feel hurt.
What's with...
(Wait.)
his outfit today?
- Is it me now? - No.
(Taking off)
Is this the problem?
(He takes off his clothes before they tease him.)
- That looks better. - That looks better.
- That looks better. - This looks better?
(Feeling much better)
Let me have a word with Yoo Jung.
(Consulting)
(Desperate)
- Gosh, I can't stand him. - Okay.
- Did she decide? - Yes.
(Okay. We're ready.)
That role suits him so well.
Jump, jump, jump...
(Skipping)
(Strict defense)
Jump, jump, jump...
(Se Chan is pushed away.)
(His feelings are hurt.)
Who are you to push me away?
Yoo Jung was okay with you,
but I don't like you.
You pushed my mouth!
(Sad)
I didn't mean to...
(What?)
- What? - What?
(What? Jae Suk got pushed out?)
Jae Suk got pushed out.
(Did Yoo Jung refuse Jae Suk?)
Nice!
(This is crazy.)
- Good job! - We should decide together.
- I said I like Se Chan. - I can't believe this.
- You didn't even let me catch him. - You said you like me?
(Glowing)
- Jae Suk! - He was only pretending.
(Yoo Jung is even stricter...)
Good job!
(than Jae Suk.)
- I mean... - Suk Jin.
- I'll go for Sunhwa. - I'll go for Sunhwa.
(They want to go to Sunhwa after watching how strict Yoo Jung is.)
- We should choose Sunhwa. - We should.
Otherwise, she'd feel hurt.
I'm coming.
(He tries to flatter her too late.)
Leave a spot for me.
- Well... - Now?
(After all this time?)
- Sunhwa, leave a spot for me. - Sunhwa.
Don't feel hurt.
They only chose Yoo Jung to be funny.
- Don't feel hurt. - They were trying to be funny.
(They try making excuses too late.)
- That's why. - We just wanted to be funny.
It's not your fault.
- I feel even more hurt now. - Sunhwa.
I was feeling okay.
(Really)
I didn't feel hurt. Why are you doing this?
- Sunhwa is the best. - Sunhwa.
- They were just trying to be funny. - I'm coming, okay?
(You know we have to be funny, right?)
We have to go to Yoo Jung to be funny.
- Sunhwa likes to have space. - I'm doing great.
(I'm fine.)
I'm the one who made her a star on "Star Golden Bell".
(My Sunhwa)
- Who? - Sunhwa.
(Me?)
You did?
You didn't become a star on that show yourself.
What are you talking about?
(Suk Jin was the only one who didn't become a star.)
- Seriously... - All right.
(Suk Jin is getting ready to jump to Sunhwa.)
You don't look so happy.
(Right then...)
It's not like that.
(Suk Jin's T-shirt stretches.)
(Jumping)
(This is how you make it funny.)
(He finishes it by running with his chicken legs.)
- That was hilarious. - The situation was funny.
How did he jump like this?
(How do you jump like that?)
- That was funny. - He jumped 3cm.
(Instead of choosing a team, Suk Jin only made people laugh.)
Go back to your place. Let's do this again.
- Let's do it again. - I failed?
He failed?
You failed.
(Annoying)
(How long will this go on?)
This is never going to end.
Oh, that's the wrong direction.
(Being funny again)
He went to Yoo Jung instead.
(Jae Suk tries Yoo Jung's team again.)
- Sunhwa would feel hurt. - "Oh, that's the wrong direction."
I was going to push him away.
(Close)
- You were going to? - Gosh.
(I knew you'd push me.)
- He's annoying, right? - I jumped in the wrong direction.
I'll definitely choose Sunhwa.
- Jump, jump, jump. - Jump, jump, jump.
(Se Chan...)
(jumps into Sunhwa's box.)
She didn't push him away.
- Next up is Kwang Soo. - Yes.
(Is it my turn now?)
(No one cares,)
Here comes celery.
- He's only interested in two teams. - A shishito pepper.
(but he tries to build the tension with his Chil Deuk steps.)
Hey, no one is getting nervous.
(Which team will Kwang Soo choose?)
No one cares.
(Jae Suk slaps his face.)
(It becomes funny again.)
(Where did Kwang Soo land?)
You're in.
No, I'm not.
I'm not in.
- You're in. - I'm not.
(Welcome.)
- You're in. - No.
You're in.
(He joined Team Chang Wook without his intention.)
- This is not okay. - Good job.
You landed right in there.
(I saw it.)
- You're in, Kwang Soo. - You went right in.
(I made it happen.)
- I wasn't even considering. - You're in.
(Why is he over there?)
I like this team too.
I like this team too, but...
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are in Team Chang Wook by fate.)
Is it my turn?
Here we go.
(It's Haha's turn.)
(I didn't get pushed out.)
- Good. - Then I'll join this team.
(What?)
- Hold on. What? - He got pushed out.
(Was he pushed out later?)
- Why did you push him out? - He was in.
(I'll just stay here.)
Let's just end it here.
Didn't we agree to push him?
I get kicked out and that's it?
(Excuse me.)
- You're in. - You're in.
(This is ridiculous.)
- You're in. - Haha!
- Haha! - Is Haha by himself?
(Se Chan and Sunhwa welcomes him.)
- We're sorry. - Don't worry.
That was a mistake. I thought it was Suk Jin.
(Team Selection Result)
With today's guests, who are playing convenience store employees,
(Today's race with the four actors of "Backstreet Rookie")
we'll have Convenience Store Hot Item Race.
(Convenience Store Hot Item Race)
The four guests will be the branch manager of each team.
(The 4 guests will be the branch managers of each team.)
- They're the branch managers. - They're the branch managers.
In today's race,
you have to guess the most popular items...
(The 40 popular products in the convenience stores are...)
sold at convenience stores...
(very important in today's race.)
and try to get as many of them.
There are top 15 items...
(The 40 hot items include top 15 items and 25 randomly chosen items,)
(and they have different points according to their sales rankings.)
and 25 randomly chosen items,
and they have different points according to their sales rankings.
After each mission, you get to choose items.
(At the end, the points from each item will be added up,)
At the end, the points from each item will be added up,
(and the two teams with the highest score will win prizes.)
and the two teams with the highest score will win prizes.
One more thing. There are...
- two brokers among you. - What?
(There are two brokers among them.)
- What? - Brokers?
There are two brokers among them.
Hey. Are you a broker?
(Fixed eyes)
- Stop acting. - A broker?
(Why would you look at me?)
You're not a broker, are you?
(Are you...)
I can't believe you.
We're going to choose the two brokers randomly.
- Really? - It's not decided yet.
- We're going to choose them now. - I'm sorry.
(Feeling unfair)
- See? - I'm sorry.
I saw the old look in her eyes.
Gosh.
(So they doubt people here.)
She's scary.
- What's with you? - The two brokers...
(The two brokers will carry out hidden missions...)
will carry out hidden missions...
and propose a deal to a team of their choice.
(and propose a deal to a team of their choice.)
After each mission,
(The proposed deals will be revealed after every mission.)
the proposals will be announced.
If the team accepts the deal,
(If the team accepts the deal,)
(they can choose an additional item, and the broker also gets the item.)
they can choose an additional item.
At the same time, the broker will win another item too.
(If the team turns down the deal, they get no additional item...)
If the team turns down the deal, they get no additional item...
(but can win a hint about the broker.)
but can win a hint about the broker.
If a team manages to catch a broker using the hints,
(If a team catches a broker at the final vote...)
(with the hints,)
they'll get a chance to turn the game around.
(the members will get a chance to turn the game around.)
- We'll have to make a choice. - If we turn down a deal...
So there are 2 brokers and 4 teams.
(With four teams and two brokers,)
They'll compete against each other,
and the top two teams will win prizes.
(only the top two teams will win prizes among 6 teams.)
Let's choose two brokers now.
(It's time to choose the brokers.)
- We choose them randomly? - Yes.
- We choose them? - Each of you will draw one.
- Let's start. - Two of them will say, "Broker".
(They will draw cards to choose two brokers.)
I usually choose the one left.
(The two brokers will be decided with the random cards.)
I want to choose the one left.
(Even the brokers don't know who the other broker is.)
(They have to compete against each other too.)
(The two brokers are given hidden missions.)
All right.
(Which of them are the 2 brokers?)
- I'll see you at the next spot. - Okay.
(They change and move to the next mission spot.)
Who could be the brokers?
I know they're not on my team.
So Min, I think the broker thing is too complicated.
(So Min tries to guess who the brokers are with Sunhwa.)
What do you mean?
If the broker's deal is accepted, he or she wins another item.
(Simple)
What if it's turned down?
(The offer)
But what are you worried about?
(She's certain already.)
As a broker, you just have to propose a deal.
Gosh.
(Shocked)
- You're scary. - Right?
You're scary.
You are a broker.
So Min. Seriously...
How can you be so shameless? You're a broker.
(She corners Sunhwa with no reason.)
- How dare you? - You're scary.
You're scary.
Even innocent people are suspected here.
You haven't been on this show in so long.
(Slapping)
You're really scary.
You are a broker.
(Is she certain?)
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo gets on the car at that moment.)
- Something didn't feel right. - Sunhwa is a broker.
- She's a broker? - Yes.
No, I'm not.
But Se Chan and Haha...
(Same team)
That sounds tough, right? They're on her team.
What are they like?
(She listens to Sunhwa's teammates and sighs.)
Don't trust them.
Don't let them sweet-talk you.
(The two)
- You think so? - Yes.
Don't trust So Min.
(Talk about yourself.)
- I can't trust anyone? - I'm different.
- I'm different. - So Min is the most dangerous one.
(She's the 1st person on the blacklist.)
- Are you buckled up? - Are you buckled up?
(They move to the next spot with advice.)
- Yes. - They'll shoot us eating too?
- Sunhwa, are you buckled up? - Yes, I am.
Those cup noodles looked so tasty.
- Chapaghetti too. - I want Chapaghetti.
I'm sure they're some of the top-selling items.
Definitely.
The numbers are from 2019...
(The numbers are from 2019 to this year.)
- and this year. - 2019?
- They're from the past year? - That's recent.
(It's about the number of units sold, not the sales price.)
And we're talking about the number of units sold.
- The number of units sold. - The number of units sold.
I'd guess Yoo Jung goes to convenience stores often.
- I do. - Right?
Young people go there a lot.
What's the first thing you pick up there?
- Bottled water. - Bottled water.
Many people buy bottled water at convenience stores.
(They get hints on the hot items from Yoo Jung.)
- I often buy bottled water. - They do.
Or Coke.
- Ice cubes in cups. - Coke?
Packed meals, triangular gimbap, ramyeon...
- Triangular gimbap, definitely. - Definitely.
You can only get it at convenience stores.
(Agreeing)
I'm sure it's in the ranking.
You could even say, without triangular gimbap,
convenience stores wouldn't be where they are now.
Convenience stores were made by companies.
(Jong Kook disagrees.)
- What's with you today? - Hey!
(Timid)
There's an item I'm thinking of, but I'm not going to tell you.
- Tell us. Come on. - What is it?
(He must have thought of an item that's ranked high.)
- I'm sure it's near the top. - Tell us.
- Sausages. - Sausages?
(Sausages?)
- Sausages... - That's just what you like.
They sell more than you think.
I think hangover drinks sell a lot too.
- Gosh. - Hangover drinks. That's right.
(Most people buy hangover drinks at convenience stores.)
That's the only place where hangover drinks are sold.
Yes, you can only buy them at convenience stores.
(The hangover drink expert wholeheartedly agrees.)
- You're right. - That's what I also said.
Hangover drinks. Ji Hyo knows it well.
(I knew it.)
Everyone's just pointing out what they mostly buy.
- Sausages, fish cake bars... - Ramyeon...
(Their answers reflect individual tastes.)
Suk Jin, what do you think?
Isn't he more used to union sales shops?
(People his age would be more familiar with that.)
Is that the actual name?
I bet you called for barmaids.
(Should I play along with this?)
- Barmaid! - I'd order rice and soup...
(He plays along.)
before climbing the mountain range.
How long would your straw shoes last?
They'd wear out after walking up two hills.
(I can't believe he's playing along with this.)
Instead of coins or actual money, we paid with shells.
(He even goes further.)
- Really? - With shells?
- Didn't you have currency? - No, it was before that.
(This is more like BCE.)
- He's playing along. - Clamshells?
(I can't believe it.)
Have you seen a royal insignia before?
(Will he play along with this too?)
Didn't I tell you about this?
A good friend of mine from school became a secret inspector.
(His classmate is a secret inspector.)
- A friend from school? - Yes.
I felt betrayed because we'd play together all the time.
(The secret inspector...)
But he still managed to study hard.
- He studied at night. - Without you knowing?
He studied hard behind my back.
(He takes the conversation to another level.)
- Unbelievable. - That's insane.
Anyway, I was surprised to see how he turned out.
(Will he keep play along?)
Did Shim Chung exist in real life?
- What about Chun Hyang? - Did you ever get to see her?
Chun Hyang? Well, I had only heard rumors about her.
What about Shim Chung?
- What about Shim Chung? - That inspector is my friend.
(From "Chunhyangjeon")
- Really? - What?
- No way. - Are you kidding me?
(Is he classmates with Yi Mong Yong?)
- He's my friend. - The puzzle pieces come together.
(Suk Jin has a vast network.)
Exactly.
What does the poison taste like?
- What? - The poison.
I didn't die by drinking it.
He said he never died.
(Ji Suk Jin, the immortal)
Didn't you once drink it until you were full?
I heard that you ate rice with your poison.
(Now everyone wants to know how far he'll play along.)
No way.
Suk Jin will be exhausted after this.
You're draining his energy.
Suk Jin, you won't have enough energy for later.
(We haven't done any missions.)
As you know, back then,
(Suk Jin continues to talk.)
we weren't able to meet with women freely.
- But I saw Chun Hyang. - How was she?
(He talks about the story of meeting Chun Hyang,)
- Was she pretty? - She didn't have double eyelids.
Magistrate Byun? He was pure evil, so don't get me started on him.
(and even on the personality issue of Magistrate Byun.)
- There weren't photos back then. - Exactly.
- Someone drew a picture. - A drawing.
- How can it be trusted though? - I know.
- Can this be aired? - No way.
(It won't be aired.)
(It's deemed inappropriate for airing.)
It sounds too fake to even be a joke.
(He went too far.)
Jae Suk drew an X.
- It'll never air. - But it sounds true...
(Addictive Suk Jin)
coming from him.
We all pitched in at first, but we sneaked out one by one.
It became boring once Suk Jin found it funny.
Jae Suk's analysis is funnier.
Jong Kook's jokes shouldn't be returned so easily.
It lost its appeal because Suk Jin found it funny.
(Suk Jin talked about his experiences endlessly.)
He played along too easily.
Jong Kook kept going to see who would give in first.
I heard that Magistrate Byun was quite handsome though.
- You have no idea. - Really?
(Wasn't it over?)
He could even be better looking than Chang Wook.
(The talking immortal is back again.)
- Better looking than Chang Wook? - Yes.
- I feel bad for you now. - Can you please stop?
- This isn't a pretty sight. - Please stop.
(He is the only audience.)
- Jong Kook, please stop. - But it's funny.
- It's funny though. - Jong Kook...
(It's actually interesting if you listen to it.)
- Did you hear him or not? - You're exhausting him.
He's only doing this to entertain you, Jong Kook.
(They arrive at the first mission site...)
(with Suk Jin's never-ending Joseon dynasty stories.)
- But Suk Jin... - This...
- I was bored. - He kept going for you.
(Will the first mission take place at a convenience store?)
Gosh, what is this?
(A mysterious monitor)
What's this for? Are we doing something in secret?
(There's something.)
- Also... - Yoo Jung, you can sit here.
There must be some sort of mission.
(What's this monitor for?)
There must be.
- It's a convenience store. - What?
(The monitor is for the CCTV inside the convenience store.)
Is this security camera footage?
(What kind of game will they play at the convenience store?)
The first game is called Sweet Combinations.
(Convenience Store Hot Item Race, First Mission)
(Sweet Combinations)
- Sweet Combinations? - Right.
Each team will go in turns.
(Each team will take turns.)
You are to successfully make and bring back...
(They are to successfully make and bring back...)
the three customized items that have been pre-ordered.
(the three customized items that have been pre-ordered.)
We must make them?
Four members of the staff already placed their orders...
(Four members of the staff already placed their orders.)
to us.
One other team...
(Inside the store will be another team...)
will enter blindfolded but with a toy hammer.
(who will enter blindfolded but with a toy hammer.)
If you get hit by the hammer, you will be out.
(If you get hit by the hammer, you will be out.)
- No way! - We'll be driven out.
The ones remaining must make the dishes themselves.
- We shouldn't make noise. - So you must stay quiet...
(It's important to stay quiet and make the dishes fast.)
and make the dishes fast.
You will go in turns.
(The team who makes the fastest will win the game.)
The team with the fastest record...
- will win the game. - Got it.
The teams will now choose a member of the staff.
(It's time to pick the team who will go first.)
Please show it to the camera.
1, 2, 3, and 4.
Did Sunhwa choose number three? Good.
When Team One enters,
(First Round, Team Sang Woo versus Team Yoo Jung)
Team Two will follow with toy hammers.
(No way.)
- Jong Kook's coming for us. - We'll go after Team Four.
- Gosh. - It's his team?
(Catching him is already hard, but we are even blindfolded.)
- Are you Team Two? - It'll be doomsday.
All right. Team Two will enter...
(Team Yoo Jung will enter first.)
- and get ready with the hammers. - Unbelievable.
Yoo Jung...
Jong Kook will be a tough opponent.
He'll use his strength to stop us.
Then go ahead and hit him.
(Bluffing)
We need to take these.
(They first pick their eye masks and toy hammers.)
They'll be making the dishes on a table.
- Right? - How can we possibly miss?
Will we have to wear blindfolds?
(Of course.)
Of course.
Right? We must be blindfolded.
(They forgot about the rules after just 1 minute.)
Isn't that obvious?
I knew it wouldn't be that easy.
(She found something.)
Why would you even ask that?
The microwave is over there, so that's where they'll go.
(A microwave at the corner of the store.)
Right?
(Microwave 2, Drinks, Microwave 3)
(Snacks, Ramyeon, Gimbap and Drinks, Microwave 1, Counter)
They'll have to come over here.
(They also check places with many ingredients.)
This is where the ramyeon and other things are.
- We should... Yoo Jung! - Yes?
We'll each take an aisle.
We're responsible for one lane each.
(They are responsible for a lane each.)
One each? I'll take this one.
Someone from Team One will step forward...
(Team Sang Woo must choose the menu.)
and pick a staff member.
- Team 1, go ahead. - Team 1?
- Let me see. - Sure.
(The orders made by the members of the staff)
Go Ji Yeon, the youngest director.
Kang Chae Ra, the floor director.
Kang Chan Hee, the director of photography.
I choose Mr. Kang Chan Hee.
I doubt he knows...
(Extremely pleased)
a lot about what you can make in convenience stores.
- He wouldn't mix things. - It won't be too complicated.
(I can tell.)
- I'm not sure about this. - He'd keep it simple.
(I was wrong.)
- Are you sure? - There's a lot written down.
"Heat in the microwave for 30 seconds..."
(Filled)
(What did Chan Hee want?)
- What's the menu? - Let me read these to you.
(A peeled triangular gimbap...)
A peeled triangular gimbap...
that's been heated up in the microwave for 30 seconds.
(that's been heated up in the microwave for 30 seconds.)
A cup of grain latte made from a grain snack and grain milk.
(A cup of grain latte made from a grain snack and grain milk.)
A sandwich made from a cheese bun and potato salad.
(A sandwich made from a cheese bun and potato)
(He can't believe his ears.)
But...
You're quite picky, Mr. Kang.
(He is a man with an exquisite taste.)
- That's what you enjoy? - Those aren't easy to make.
I had no idea that he enjoyed grain latte.
I like his recipes though.
(After taking orders from an extremely picky man,)
The grain snack would be delicious though.
I'd like to try them.
- Did you have to pick number one? - Sang Woo...
(Team Sang Woo takes off to make them.)
No, you did great.
(They are ready to defend.)
- They're here! - Are they here?
They're here!
(The soldiers are ready with their toy hammers.)
Are they here?
They haven't entered yet.
Actually, I have no idea.
- What do we do? - Actually, I have no idea.
Make sure you don't hit the stands.
(Are they inside?)
They could be in here already.
(Team Sang Woo enters covertly.)
- Are they inside? - Are they in here?
- Can't you tell us? Who's there? - What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
(Wrong)
They don't know that Team Sang Woo entered.
(Thump!)
- Is someone there? - No, I hit something else.
(While Team Yoo Jung wanders around...)
(They spot a triangular gimbap.)
- Is someone there? - No, it's just the stand.
I'm...
(They pick up a triangular gimbap.)
- But... - I'm checking the back too.
(They must heat it for 30 seconds.)
The microwave is over there.
(He quickly moves to a microwave.)
They won't even let us know if they've entered.
(Suk Jin is standing guard.)
Who's this?
- Are they not... - Who's this?
(He quickly passes by.)
- Aren't they inside yet? - They're over there.
- Team Sang Woo is already inside. - Already?
Really?
(Suk Jin's right next to Jong Kook.)
Team Sang Woo is already inside.
Already? Really?
(But Jong Kook has nowhere to go.)
(Jong Kook tries to slide past him.)
We need to locate them.
(Jong Kook gets past Suk Jin undetected.)
I can't see a thing.
(Jong Kook escapes but fails to heat up the gimbap.)
- Where are they? - It's not easy.
We should keep in mind that they don't make any noise.
Help me.
(I need to heat it up.)
Did you hit someone or not?
(Jong Kook squeezes through.)
There's someone here!
(The old man waves around his hammer.)
I sense someone.
Where?
(Jong Kook successfully puts it inside the microwave.)
Over here.
Where? Someone ran past me.
(Sang Woo, distract him for me.)
- Hold on. - Someone threw something.
Someone's here!
(Suk Jin is behind them,)
- Where? - Where?
(Yoo Jung is in front of them.)
- I heard something. - Where?
(So Min and Sang Woo have nowhere to go.)
Where?
- Where? - Charge!
(Sang Woo barely escapes.)
Where?
(So Min quickly makes an escape too.)
Where are they?
I heard them over here but...
I can't tell where they are.
(Now I just have to heat it up.)
(Beeping)
- The microwave! - The microwave!
(Busted!)
(Jong Kook is surrounded by Yoo Jung and Suk Jin.)
- Where are they? - By the microwave.
(He sees an opening and manages to escape.)
- Where are they? - I heard someone over here.
- Is there another microwave here? - Where?
(Microwave)
- Where are they? - By the microwave.
- Where? - Over here.
- Gosh, it's just me. - Where?
- Where are they? - I'm sorry.
(The zombies are killing each other.)
- Someone's here. - Hold on a second.
- Here. - I heard the microwave beep.
- Who is this? - Who am I hitting?
- It's me. - Yoo Jung, is this you?
(They pick out the ingredients as Team Yoo Jung struggles.)
- It's me. - Who's this?
- It's me you're hitting. - I found someone.
- Where? - Who is this?
- Who are you? - I'm the cameraman.
- The cameraman? - I'm sorry.
(Jae Suk zombie can't see anything.)
Are you sure?
(Meanwhile, he picked up another triangle gimbap.)
Someone should stay behind there. Don't stay here.
(Jong Kook heads to another microwave.)
(Beeping)
I heard something!
(While Jong Kook distracts them,)
- Right? - There are two microwaves.
- There are two microwaves? - There's one up front.
(So Min and Sang Woo quickly prepare the food.)
Wasn't it the microwave beeping just now?
(Microwave)
- There's one up front? - Really?
Hold on a second.
I heard something.
(Is it not ready?)
- What's this? - It came from the left.
Over there.
(30 seconds is up.)
I heard it again!
(The moment the microwave beeps...)
- Over there. - I heard it again!
(Jong Kook comes flying forward.)
Over there.
(Jong Kook gets in between Suk Jin and Jae Suk.)
I heard it again! It's the microwave.
- Where? - The timer's up.
(Jong Kook's surrounded though.)
The timer's up.
(He makes a run for it through the small opening.)
(He escapes through space underneath Suk Jin's arm.)
- Where? - The microwave is done.
I definitely heard something.
(So Min and Sang Woo are almost done too.)
It came from the left.
- It came from across the store. - I can smell the food now.
(Everything is ready.)
- Suk Jin, stay there. - Okay.
(They only have to leave the store now.)
Hold on.
(Will Team Sang Woo be able to safely exit the store?)
(Sang Woo makes it out first.)
(Jong Kook also makes it out safely!)
The dishes will be evaluated outside.
(So Min teases Jae Suk.)
Hold on. Someone just poked me.
Really?
- Here... - Unbelievable.
- I hit someone. - You did?
Yes, I just did.
(Zombie's reflexes are too slow.)
Didn't I hit anyone?
Are they done already?
(Team Sang Woo returns.)
- I had a blast. - Did you make all the dishes?
You have to go back in if you didn't follow the recipe.
- Really? - Sang Woo,
- what kind of milk did you use? - Good job, So Min.
It was...
(Flustered)
normal white milk.
You got the menu wrong, so you have to make it again.
- Again? - You have to make grain latte.
(He failed because it's plain white milk.)
Grain latte?
- What's this? - Is that grain milk?
(It's hard to follow the order.)
- What's that? - Grain...
Quick, Sang Woo. You messed up.
(He checks the recipe one more time.)
I don't hear anything.
(He enters carefully.)
Did they take their shoes off?
I don't think they left yet.
(Zombie Yu has neither reflex nor wits.)
They're still inside.
(He gets the ingredients again.)
Hey.
(While Sang Woo picks out the ingredients...)
(Hitting)
(So Min tries to confuse him.)
What are they doing?
Somebody just hit me.
(Swinging)
(Sang Woo throws a trap as well.)
(He strikes Suk Jin's belly.)
Hey!
(The toy hammer got his sides.)
(They find the blunder hilarious.)
Who makes that sound after getting hit by a toy hammer?
It made full contact.
(Fussing)
I hear footsteps. Footsteps!
(What's he doing by himself?)
I hear footsteps. That way!
(This time, he got grain milk.)
Where?
Ahead of me.
(They just have to get out to complete all items on the menu.)
Where are they?
(This is a bait.)
Hey.
(They fell for it.)
(So Min escapes too.)
- It's me. - Is it you?
(Team Sang Woo completes all items.)
How many times did you hit me?
(They showed the worst teamwork.)
- This fell off. - The mission is over.
(Round 1 ends.)
- Suk Jin. - Jae Suk keeps on hitting me.
We thought you were going to die.
- Why? - They keep fighting.
Jae Suk hit you too many times.
Why did you hit me so many times?
(To them, it looks like Suk Jin got beaten.)
You made weird sounds.
I stood next to you for the longest time.
(Didn't you know?)
- How? - Right in front of you.
You were like zombies in front of the microwave.
I turned on the microwave, and you were all there.
(They all moved toward the microwave every time they heard it.)
There were two microwaves.
Gosh, the microwave.
You were like zombies.
("Walking Dead")
It's our turn next. We should do well.
(Team Yoo Jung will try this time.)
Try Go Ji Yeon, the youngest director.
You have to microwave it for a long time.
Please get back.
(Go Ji Yeon's order)
(Tteokbokki microwaved for 1 minute)
- This is better. - What?
(Cocktail with plain yogurt and orange juice)
(Ice cream with chocolate snack)
Let's turn off the microwave.
(Team Sunhwa's strategy)
- When they come. - Jae Suk.
Look. It's this button.
(They turn the microwave off.)
Increase the time or turn it off.
How did they do it so perfectly?
(Team Yoo Jung versus Team Sunhwa)
Which team is inside?
(They enter quietly.)
I think Jae Suk is good at this game.
Are they inside?
- They're inside. - They're inside!
(She's nervous.)
- Go. Go around. - Are they inside?
- They're inside! - Go.
(She patiently picks out the ingredients.)
- Are they inside? - Go around.
(Tteokbokki microwaved for 1 minute)
(She gets tteokbokki and backs off.)
I'm off.
(He's on full alert.)
(Ice cream with chocolate snack)
I hear footsteps.
- They're inside, right? - I think so.
(Yoo Jung makes tteokbokki in the corner.)
They're inside. It's this way.
Where?
(While Haha turns away,)
(he gets the ice cream cone.)
I heard them.
(He strikes with his toy hammer.)
(That was close.)
I don't think they're coming this way.
(Sunhwa's blocking the way.)
- Over there. - I heard them.
I heard them.
It's this way. I heard them.
(Haha's blocking their way on the other side.)
- Where are you? - Where?
(Inching slowly)
- Who's this? - It's me.
(Jae Suk escapes to the corner.)
Welcome.
(What are you doing over there?)
(Then they block from both sides.)
I think somebody is over here.
- Come this way. It's me. - Where are you?
(What do I do?)
- Corner them! - Left side.
(He avoids it by lying down.)
- Did you touch them? - Didn't I hit them?
Didn't I?
- It's me. - I can't see anything.
(What a relief.)
What was that?
(Meanwhile, Se Chan...)
They're nowhere.
(Sniffing)
(He follows the smell and reaches the microwave.)
(I smell something.)
What's this?
Somebody microwaved food.
They did?
It smells sweet. What's this?
I think it's triangular gimbap.
(It's the triangle gimbap Jong Kook failed to remove.)
I'll put it in my pocket.
Se Chan.
(He keeps the inheritance Jong Kook left.)
- Se Chan. - Yes?
- Did they microwave something? - They did but couldn't take it.
(He's happy.)
Really? Take it out.
(Se Chan's proud of himself.)
- I did. It's in my pocket. - Is it?
(Ice cream with chocolate snack)
I found it.
(Team Yoo Jung starts making food.)
- I heard a sound. - Here.
- Se Chan. - Did you get them?
(Team Sunhwa gets near them.)
I opened the microwave, and I smelled ramyeon.
(Suk Jin and Yoo Jung get away.)
(Jae Suk gets cornered.)
I heard a sound.
(He uses his sense of touch and hearing.)
It's over here. This way.
(He's a psychic who uses his five senses.)
I don't know where they are.
- I hear a sound. - Haha.
Come this way.
(He covers his mouth.)
(The situation is about to escalate.)
- Who are you? - No one's here.
(Help me.)
Hey, Jong Kook!
(Is this the cameraman?)
Haha, does the cameraman have a microphone?
Hey!
(I caught you, rascal!)
(This coward can't catch nor hide.)
Who are you?
- Did you get somebody? - Jae Suk is out.
(Jae Suk is out.)
- It was Jae Suk. - Good job.
Who did it? Good job.
(He doesn't care even though his team member is eliminated.)
- My gosh. - Haha.
Please return everything.
I smelled him.
(A man who uses his five senses)
He smells so good.
(Subtle smell)
Wait.
(Sighing)
He smells so good.
Oh, my gosh.
(He exits without getting anything done.)
- They're coming this way. - It's me.
(As soon as Jae Suk is eliminated,)
Hey.
(Yoo Jung is out.)
- Yoo Jung is out. - Yes!
Suk Jin is out.
- Is Suk Jin out? - Is he out?
(When did Suk Jin got eliminated?)
How am I out?
(While Se Chan was going after Yoo Jung,)
Hey.
(he barely touched Suk Jin.)
- Is everybody out? - Yes.
(All 3 members of Team Yoo Jung are out.)
Okay!
(Team Sunhwa defended perfectly.)
- Really? - How am I out?
Was it me?
Gosh, Jae Suk.
How did he get caught?
- I smelled him. - You smelled him?
(Jae Suk left a trace of his smell.)
He smells good.
Move that way.
We have to make sounds for each other.
(Team Sunhwa versus Team Chang Wook)
You have to keep moving.
(What's Team Sunhwa's mission menu?)
With potato chips.
(Choi Yun Sang's order)
- Oh, gosh. - We're done for.
(Potato chip nacho microwaved for 30 seconds with cheddar cheese)
(Pear frappuccino with pear drink and pear ice cream)
- I always get caught. - With cheddar cheese.
(Canafe with vegetable tuna on crackers)
Nacho? Microwaved.
Where are you?
(Team Chang Wook is getting ready.)
I'm over here. I'm by the door.
(This is Kwang Soo's territory.)
- By the door? - Yes.
We won't know when they come in.
(Kwang Soo is already nervous.)
(Hitting)
- Oh, dear. - What was that?
- What was that? What did I hit? - Are they inside?
- Are they inside? - I don't know.
(What's this?)
Did I break something? Where was that?
(This team looks sloppy already.)
I don't think they're here yet.
What's this? I can't see.
(Team Sunhwa enters.)
(They pass by Kwang Soo's territory.)
(They see Chang Wook waiting in ambush.)
(We must pass.)
- Where are they? - They're inside.
They're inside.
(He stands up.)
(He's making way for them?)
- Are they inside? - Are they?
(Taking)
(They got vegetable tuna.)
- We have started. - They're inside.
(Canafe with vegetable tuna on crackers)
(Pear frappuccino with pear drink and pear ice cream)
(Pear ice cream is in here.)
- We have started. - They're inside.
- What's this? - Over here.
(Rushing)
- Where? - Where?
(Kwang Soo is worked up.)
- Here. - Where?
Here. The freezer is open. Who is this?
- Where? - Here.
- The freezer is open. What's this? - Where?
(Se Chan is getting cornered.)
- Here. - Where?
(He escapes behind Kwang Soo.)
- Over here. - Where?
(Haha breaks through the sloppy defense and gets the snack.)
- Where? - Here.
Where?
(Bang! Bang!)
Don't break things!
(Frustrated)
(He plays a warning alert.)
Ice cream.
Somebody took ice cream.
(Screaming)
Hey.
(The stupid brothers are dumbed down.)
- Who are you? - Are you okay? Me.
It's you.
(Meanwhile, Haha...)
- Where are you? - Wait.
They're not here.
(He gets an item easily from Kwang Soo's territory.)
Snacks!
(He tries to get ice cream again.)
- It's me. - They're not here.
(Pear frappuccino with pear drink and pear ice cream)
- Here. Ice cream! - Where? Which one?
(He runs away in a hurry.)
Which one?
(It's too late.)
They got away.
(These two dummies can't even block the freezer.)
- This is open. - I know.
(They're making a fuss when it's already too late.)
They need something from here.
(They're like automatic doors.)
- They left. - I heard the bell.
(After making canape, she delivers it to the head office.)
They left? They're already done?
- This is not the camera. - What?
(He bumped into something.)
- Where are you? - No, I'm in pain.
Wait, the microwave is done.
(Chang Wook, I'm coming to help!)
The microwave is done.
Where was it? I smell it.
(Zombie Ji smelled money from the ATM.)
Is this it? Is this the microwave?
It's open. They can't take it.
(Kwang Soo reached the microwave.)
(He finds tteokbokki that was being made.)
(However)
(He's eating it with his hand?)
Kwang Soo, you can't eat that.
(This is a new way of defending.)
This is hot.
What are you eating?
(He's jealous.)
This is hot. It's a rice cake.
(Ji Hyo lived under a rock and protected only her territory.)
What are you doing?
What's this?
(She felt something.)
(It's Se Chan.)
What? Did they eat something?
(He holds his breath.)
(She can smell a man in his 30s.)
(Hitting)
Hey.
(I caught you, rascal!)
I got them!
(Ji Hyo eliminates Se Chan by luck.)
- I got Se Chan. - I was almost done.
- Se Chan is out. - I got him.
(He was almost done.)
(There are 2 items and 2 people left.)
They're over here!
(Excited)
(He almost had Haha.)
They're over here!
- Where? - Kwang Soo!
(Suk Jin almost caught someone.)
They got away.
- Who was it? - By the door!
(Haha escapes from Ji Hyo.)
- They're getting away. - Who was it?
(He runs away like a coward.)
- Where did he go? - Where did he go?
(There's only one menu left.)
- My gosh. - What did you have to make?
- What is it? - One person is out.
(Team Chang Wook rearranges their position.)
Chang Wook. I smell something.
I smell something.
It's hot. I'm eating right now.
I smell something. Kwang Soo, what are you eating?
(What are you doing not doing your job?)
(It's actually good.)
What?
- I think it's tteokbokki. - They're over here.
Ice cream!
They're over here. Ice cream!
(He lost it again.)
- Ice cream! - Ice cream!
Please don't hit too hard.
(She escapes from Kwang Soo easily.)
- Where are they? - Where are they?
- Over here! - It's me.
(Excited, scared)
- This is good. - What are you having?
- I want it too. - I finished it.
You finished it?
(What a bummer.)
Is it cheese or pizza tteokbokki?
(He enjoyed the food without doing his job.)
(She's not even hiding, and nobody is stopping her.)
(She's relaxed.)
(She finished the drink without anybody interfering with her.)
Hey!
- Hey. - I heard a sound.
(Meanwhile)
It's me! It's me!
(Hitting)
- Hey, it's me. - Where?
(What?)
Hey, it's me.
- You brat! - Where? My bad.
- Are you okay? - Where are you?
Everybody, the mission is over.
(The mission ends.)
They must be gone.
(Team Chang Wook used up their energy for nothing.)
I heard something.
(Team Sang Woo is here to block them.)
This is like cardio.
(This is good.)
(Kwang Soo comes in ambitiously...)
(and gets caught in front of the ice cream stall.)
- Who is this? - I got someone.
Who is it? Who did you catch?
(He gives Chang Wook some tips as he leaves.)
Gosh, I'm out already.
Okay.
(I'm furious!)
Why is he holding a real hammer?
Isn't it a real hammer?
(Team Chang Wook's turn ends in vain.)
(The results will be announced.)
Let me announce the results of Sweet Combinations.
Team Sang Woo won without getting caught...
(With the record of 7 minutes 49 seconds and no one caught,)
for 7 minutes and 49 seconds. They're in 1st place.
(Team Sang Woo won 1st place.)
We're the best.
Team Sunhwa who finished the mission with two members out...
(With the record of 10 minutes 12 seconds and 2 caught,)
in 10 minutes and 12 seconds won 2nd place.
(Team Sunhwa won 2nd place.)
- Good. - This is nice.
Team Chang Wook and Team Yoo Jung are all out.
(The members of the other two teams were all eliminated.)
Team Chang Wook who held out for 11 minutes and 6 seconds is the 3rd.
(Team Chang Wook won 3rd place for holding out 11 minutes 6 seconds.)
Okay.
Team Yoo Jung is the 4th with a record...
(Team Yoo Jung wins 4th place for being eliminated in 5 minutes.)
- of 5 minutes and 45 seconds. - Only 5 minutes?
- That's a big difference. - We were very quick though.
(Optimistic)
Let's move to the next place...
(They'll move to the next mission spot and choose the first hot item.)
and pick the first item.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(What's the popular convenience store item they will pick?)
- Well done. - Okay.
Do we have two spies here?
- Brokers. - What do brokers do?
(They wonder who the brokers are.)
- What's the deal with the brokers? - What are the brokers for?
What do they do?
The brokers...
already threw...
their offers many times while performing the mission.
(Have they already made their offers?)
- Really? - What?
- They threw their offers? - To whom?
When did they do that?
(The two brokers were told to offer their proposal earlier.)
(You're a broker. Pick a member...)
(whom you want to offer a proposal to.)
(During the mission,)
I think I heard someone's breath.
(the brokers approached the production crew.)
They offer their proposal to the production crew?
(They're already told the production crew whom will they offer to.)
To the production crew? I see.
What happens if we catch the brokers?
(The prize for catching a broker)
If you find out the brokers,
you will get a doubling sticker per each.
(They get Multiply Stickers...)
You can double your points with the sticker.
(which will double the point of the chosen hot item.)
It's a good one.
- If you fail to find the brokers... - We should catch them.
Who are the brokers?
(All of a sudden...)
Suk Jin just said that when he doesn't even care.
I thought he was talking in his sleep.
Chang Wook, are you the broker?
(What?)
(He yells at Chang Wook all of a sudden.)
- He just yelled out of the blue. - I didn't even say anything.
(What's wrong with him?)
- Who is it? - What's wrong with you?
I think...
this is what Suk Jin can do.
I think so. It's no big deal.
(It means it won't hurt the show.)
- It's not that big a deal. - I know.
- It's a small role. - Even if he gets caught,
(Ji Suk Jin, specialized in small roles)
- it doesn't ruin the whole race. - I know.
- Suk Jin sounds right for it. - That's what Suk Jin can do.
It doesn't affect the whole race.
(His face glows as people are paying attention to him.)
- He seems so happy to be suspected. - It's you, right?
(The broker)
Yes. Sure.
- How did you know? - It can't be him.
(It's definitely not him.)
- It's not him. - My gosh.
I shouldn't suspect him.
- Chang Wook. - Yes?
Who do you think the brokers are?
I think it's either Sunhwa...
I agree.
Can you tell us the truth, swearing on our drama?
(Chang Wook)
- You're the broker, aren't you? - No.
She even mentioned her drama. They sound serious.
Why would you say it on our drama?
Can you swear on our drama that you're not the broker?
(Is finding a broker that important?)
That's not what we do.
What will you do with your drama?
(If you're going to swear...)
- It's just... - What if you're lying?
We will leave the drama.
- Leave the drama? - Leave?
(Startled)
- What? - Leave the drama?
- Do you have to do that? - Why would you quit it?
(Should they leave the drama for being a broker?)
He's right. We should enjoy.
It'll be funny if you quit the drama because of Running Man.
("Sunhwa leaves the drama because of her promise with Running Man.")
"I have no choice. I made my promise with them."
"What's the reason?"
- "In Running Man..." - I was the broker in Running Man.
"I have no choice. I made my promise with them."
(Exchanging the role in the drama for the role of a broker)
"I hid the fact that I was the broker."
Is the mission for the brokers something like this?
(Sudden)
- Hey, Bones. Stay quiet. - Bones.
- Me? - Which one?
(Bones? Does he mean me?)
- He has bones. - He has bones on his shirt.
I see. That's what he means.
Why did you put this on? Dream can't go out because of you.
(As Jong Kook makes a slight joke,)
(they burst into laughter.)
You're wearing Dream's shirt.
Do you know what's funny here?
Only his two underlings laugh at his joke.
No one else laughed.
(Underling 1, Underling 2)
Why did you put this on? Dream can't go out because of you.
(While everyone is quiet,)
(only the two of them burst into laughter.)
You're wearing Dream's shirt.
- Only the two underlings. - Hey.
(The original underling studies Jong Kook's face quietly.)
- Why would you call us underlings? - No one laughed.
(At least have the decency to say, "Subordinates".)
Use good words. Like subordinates.
Only his underlings...
(Purifying the term)
Only his subordinates are laughing. No one else laughed.
Why did you not laugh? You're his underling number four.
Because...
(She bursts into laughter as if she was waiting.)
(Our captain is so funny.)
He's really funny.
Good.
(The captain is pleased.)
Jong Kook, your underling number five is not laughing.
(Smiling)
- He's laughing now. - He's laughing quietly.
He was laughing quietly.
I'm number four.
(Enraged)
- He says he's number 4. - "I'm number 4."
Suk Jin is...
(Ranking the underlings,)
You guys are mistaken. He's a mole.
(they head to the next destination.)
(They arrive at the destination.)
Everyone.
It's time to pick your first hot item.
(It's time to choose the first hot item.)
Team Sang Woo won the convenience store mission.
(Team Sang Woo will choose first as they won first place.)
You get to pick one item you want and put it on your table.
There are two kinds of water. The big one and the small one.
(Different points will be given according to the rankings.)
What matters is how many of them were sold.
There are many kinds of water.
For your information, the brokers might want to pick bad items...
(If there is a broker on the team,)
on purpose for the competition.
(he or she might induce their members to pick bad items.)
Can we pick three items?
(Team Sang Woo will pick first.)
- No, only one. - We get to pick one.
- Triangular gimbap? - Triangular gimbap.
- I should pick triangular gimbap. - Let's do that.
(Certain)
- Triangular gimbap? - Isn't this it?
(They think for a second.)
Hang on. What if triangular gimbap is sold out?
If you pick the most popular item, you will get 15 points.
(The most popular item will get them 15 points,)
And 14 points for the second popular item.
You get 1 point for the 15th item.
(and the least popular item will get them 1 point.)
All right. I guess this is it.
- Triangular gimbap? - No.
- Is it over? - Are you done?
Yes. We picked triangular gimbap.
- Okay. - It's triangular gimbap.
(Team Sang Woo picks triangular gimbap.)
Who's next?
There are a lot of popular items.
(Team Sunhwa goes second.)
- This is red bean jelly. - Hang on. I think...
(What will they pick?)
it's either cup noodles or water.
(They're discussing between cup noodles and water.)
No. Just trust me this once.
All right then.
Let's go with that.
- I guess he's right. - We picked this.
- Is that what you got? - Okay.
(Doubting)
Are you sure?
(Team Sunhwa picks cup noodles as Se Chan insists.)
They picked cup noodles.
(Doubting)
I'm sure about this.
(Team Chang Wook will go third.)
It's a 500ml bottle of water.
(They pick 500ml water in confidence.)
- Do you have any idea? - Sausage.
- But people don't eat it a lot. - No, it must be sausage.
(Jae Suk has been insisting sausages.)
- I don't think so. - Suk Jin.
- But... - I'm telling you.
- Is he the broker? - I don't think it's popular.
(He's being weird.)
- No, I'm serious. - It doesn't sound right.
- People don't eat it a lot. - Do people really eat it a lot?
(Certain)
I read something.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
No.
- Isn't it soda? - I'm sure this is it.
(They have different opinions,)
- Are you sure? - Seriously?
- Yes. - What about chewing gum?
(but Jae Suk insists it's sausages.)
I don't think so.
- Are you sure? - What about ice cream?
Are you serious? Do you not want to pick ice cream?
He's the broker. He's being strange.
(He's so suspicious.)
(Jae Suk picks sausage despite the strong opposition.)
- We eat ice cream even in winter. - You're the broker.
(Is he inducing them to pick a bad item?)
I'm telling you.
Jae seok is the broker.
- I think he's the broker. - You're the broker.
(Jae Suk is being suspicious. Is he really the broker?)
You're the broker.
I'm sure about this. Listen to me.
(Desperate)
Why would we listen to you?
You're unreliable.
You can't pick what you like.
Jae Suk, you don't even go to a convenience store.
We don't have anything else to pick. Just listen to me this once.
- Come here. - What about ice cream?
(Team Yoo Jung chooses sausages as Jae Suk persists.)
What about fish cake bar?
- What about ice cream? - What do you mean?
Just come here, Yoo Jung.
(They are all done picking their first items.)
You guys made your choice.
Now I will reveal the offers from the brokers made in Round One.
(The offers from the two brokers are revealed now.)
The first broker, A...
made an offer to Team Sang Woo.
(Broker A made an offer to Team Sang Woo.)
- I didn't hear it. - And Broker B made...
(Broker B made an offer to Team Sunhwa, Yoo Jung, and Chang Wook.)
an offer to Team Sunhwa, Yoo Jung, and Chang Wook.
Even to us?
I guess they tried to confuse us.
(The brokers were busy making offers during the first mission.)
- Broker B is... - We can catch them.
Oh, my.
Now you should think about it. If you accept the offer,
(If they accept the offer,)
you can pick one more item.
(they can pick one more item.)
But if you accept it, the broker will...
(But the broker will also get the chance to pick one more item.)
also get one more chance to pick an item.
- What's the offer? - What if we don't accept it?
(If they decline,)
You can't pick an extra item,
(they won't get to pick another item.)
but you can get a hint about the broker.
(But they will get a hint on the brokers instead.)
- Let's not accept it then. - Okay.
We'd better get a hint.
(Will they get one more item or try to catch the brokers?)
- I think getting a hint is better. - If we pick one more item...
Let's get a hint.
Let's just accept the offer.
We should accept it.
- No. Are you the broker? - I'm not.
We should find out who the brokers are.
- Do you want to get a hint? - We can double our points.
(If they catch a broker, their point will be doubled.)
Let's accept the offer.
- What do you want to do? - We should accept it.
(Team Chang Wook is still discussing.)
- I'm thinking about it. - We should get it.
Do you want to get a hint?
It will be over if our team wins.
If you're not the broker, you won't accept the offer.
She wants to accept the offer.
(Team Chang Wook wants to accept the broker's offer.)
Captain Kim, we will follow your opinion.
- I think it's okay to accept one. - Okay.
Our captain, Yoo Jung, wants to accept the offer.
(They accept the broker's offer as Yoo Jung wants.)
- Are you accepting the offer? - Yes.
We want to accept the offer too.
(Team Chang Wook also accepts the offer.)
- We will accept it. - We will accept the offer.
They accepted it before you did, so they get to pick first.
(Team Yoo Jung will choose first as they accepted earlier.)
- Okay. - Good.
- Captain Kim. - We made a good choice.
The brokers can pick the same items later.
- This is about the number of sales. - Exactly.
(The rankings are based on the number of units sold.)
Do you want ice cream?
(Captain Kim wants to pick ice cream.)
Do you want it? Okay.
- Wait. Ice cream and... - This isn't right.
(Team Yoo Jung picks...)
That's what she wants.
(ice cream that they've been thinking about.)
- Captain Kim, bring this. - What?
She picked ice cream.
(I don't think it's ice cream.)
- It's just the color of your shirt. - That's what our captain wants.
- They picked only strange ones. - It matches their shirt.
(Complaining)
We picked this.
(Team Chang Wook picks corn tea.)
Corn tea?
But you wanted this.
I didn't see this coming.
Okay.
(Team Sunhwa also accepts the offer and chooses Chapaghetti.)
- What did you say before? - We'll pick Chapaghetti.
- Let's take the risk. - We will accept the offer.
(Team Sang Woo accepts the offer and picks a lighter.)
- A lighter? - Yes.
The brokers must be excited.
(The brokers get to pick more items as well.)
- We all accepted the offer. - All right then.
All the four teams accepted the offer.
(What will be their points at the end?)
Let's move on to the second mission.
(The results of their first choices)
The second mission is...
(The second mission)
Your Fate in Your Hands where you control...
(Your Fate in Your Hands)
the fate of your own team.
Do you see the water balloons over your heads?
(They have one water balloon for each team.)
They have water in them.
And it has 10 layers of balloons.
(There are 10 layers.)
We will give you an eyebrow razor later.
(If they cut it carefully with an eyebrow razor,)
You can cut it carefully, you can survive 10 times.
(the can survive 10 times.)
If you do it wrong, it will burst immediately.
(It'll burst immediately if they cut it wrong.)
- I'm scared. - I know what it is.
If we do it right, it won't burst for 10 times.
(We should be careful.)
So this is what you're going to do.
The production crew will present a question.
(The production crew will present a question.)
And you will name a member to the question.
(And 1 representative will name a member to the question.)
The rest of the members will hear it and guess what the question is.
(The rest of the members will hear it and guess what the question is.)
(If they fail to get the correct answer, they must cut the balloon.)
If your balloon bursts, you will get one more balloon.
(They'll be given 2 water balloons.)
You get two balloons.
The first team to pop the two balloons will lose the game.
(The first team to use both of them will be ranked last.)
- Okay. - And the 2nd one is in 3rd place.
- I want to win. - Then you should decide...
who will answer the question.
(Team Sang Woo will go first.)
So Min.
(They choose So Min.)
But So Min is quite imaginative.
(Nervous)
Pick one question...
(She picks a question among the ones presented by the production crew.)
and tell them your answer to the question.
Tell them your opinion.
This question is tricky.
(Scoffing)
- The question is too hard. - Is it hard?
(What is the question?)
What is it, So Min?
- It's not about love. - Is that so?
(First of all...)
- It's about the opposite sex. - Okay.
(Who does So Min think is top 1 regarding this question?)
It's about the opposite sex.
The answer is clear.
- Anyone would have chosen him. - Who?
Jae Suk.
(Top 1 is Jae Suk.)
- I am serious. - Let me answer.
(Haha is ready to answer right away.)
- The person who is ugly in my eyes. - No.
(Wrong)
- The person who is ugly in my eyes. - I didn't try to throw people off.
(No way.)
- The answer is clear. - Did you think of him right away?
(Confident)
Other people just don't fit.
There is only one possible answer.
Yoo Jae Suk.
You are Michael Jordan of this question.
(The King of Basketball)
Had this been an encyclopedia entry,
(Yoo Jae Suk, the living legend of this question)
- his name would have been there. - Really?
The man who shouldn't take off his glasses before women.
(If that's the case...)
(Wrong)
Let me answer.
(Sunhwa attempts to guess.)
The man who thinks he is popular among women.
(She quietly criticizes Jae Suk.)
- Incorrect. - The man who is delusional.
(Wrong)
You are nowhere near the answer.
(What's the question?)
- Jae Suk... - I can't get it right.
The production crew agrees with So Min's answer.
- Really? - Everyone agrees.
The answer has to be Jae Suk.
(This question is made for Jae Suk.)
Even if I choose the top two, the gap would be too big.
Jae Suk is way up there.
- Really? - Is he way up there?
(Is it really?)
It must be something about appearances.
(If there's a big difference...)
- Is it about being rich? - Appearances?
Is it about being rich?
(It's either about the appearance or the money.)
Why would it be about being rich?
You lack in so many ways.
(He tells the harsh truth.)
- It's hard to choose one. - Why would you say that?
(The ugly loses his temper.)
- It's true. You lack... - Let me answer.
The man whose child must take after his or her mother.
(Wrong)
Incorrect.
Is it a good thing or a bad thing?
(He feels dizzy from countless attacks on his appearance.)
It's a good thing...
because you are Yoo Jae Suk.
- Is it a good thing? - If there is someone like him...
(If...)
who isn't Yoo Jae Suk, it would be really bad.
Someone like him who isn't Yoo Jae Suk?
- Then it would be really bad. - Yes.
(It's bad if there's another me that's not me?)
You are saying it's a good thing that he is Yoo Jae Suk.
(Let me summarize.)
It's a good thing that he is Yoo Jae Suk.
(Precisely.)
Would you give us a motion hint that fits the situation?
- This is hard. - Right, give us a motion hint.
(It's really hard.)
A motion hint?
Hello, everyone. I am Yoo Jae Suk.
(Motion hint)
Today...
(A fans cheers upon seeing Jae Suk.)
- Jae Suk! Let's shake hands. - Let me answer.
The man who should be glad that he became a celebrity.
(Incorrect)
It's close to the answer.
- Right? - Is it close?
- Yes, it is. - I knew it.
(They are getting closer.)
Okay, okay.
Come on, guys.
Let me answer.
The man who wouldn't have succeeded if he weren't a celebrity.
The man who wouldn't have married if he weren't a celebrity.
(Incorrect)
The man who would be a celebrity even in his next life.
(A series of wrong answers.)
The man who is popular among women only because he is a celebrity.
Yes!
(Correct)
The man who is popular among women only because he is a celebrity.
How could you say that?
(Everyone agrees.)
(They finally understand why Jae Suk is top 1 by landslide.)
(Jong Kook gives a ceremony with a man who avoided misfortune.)
Thank you.
- So Min, that was neat. - Thank you.
(Thank you for making me a celebrity, my fans.)
- That was neat. - Thank you.
- I chose the right one. - That was neat.
(Everyone else except Team Sang Woo needs to slash the balloons.)
It hit me.
"Only because he is a celebrity" was like a wakeup call.
(He admits too.)
It's true.
Let's start with this team. Slash the balloon once.
(Team Sunhwa will slash first.)
Should I do it?
How much do we need to slash?
(It's impossible to fathom.)
While it can be small, at least one layer must come off.
(They can cut as much as they want, but it must be at least one layer.)
- This is scary. - Do it like this.
- Slash lightly. - Do it lightly.
There you go.
- Do it lightly. - There you go.
(One layer came off when she put the blade against it.)
It came off so easily.
That was no joke.
(Team Sunhwa succeeds.)
- It's a different color. - She barely touched it.
- It was so scary. - She barely touched it.
- Team Ji Chang Wook. - Who wants to go first?
(Ji Hyo of Team Chang Wook tries.)
- Do you want to go first? - Hold on.
You need to sit down and do it.
(Slowly)
- Do I need to sit down? - Of course.
- This is insane. - Do it gently.
(Nervous)
Give it a small poke.
(He gathers both his hands.)
A small poke.
I can't do it. Hold on.
Do it the second time.
(Ji Hyo gives up because she is too nervous.)
- Go first. - Okay.
(Chang Wook gives it a shot.)
- A small poke. - I'll try my best.
- I will slash it here. - A small poke.
- Hold on. - You need to slash it.
This is nerve-wracking.
(Even the audience is nervous.)
How did you do it?
(The blade hasn't even touched the balloon yet.)
A small poke.
(He is slashing in the air.)
The blade touched the balloon, but it wouldn't pop.
The blade...
(They are overreacting.)
- The blade touched the balloon. - It didn't touch the balloon.
What's wrong with you guys?
(Chang Wook gets too scared and tosses it to Kwang Soo.)
Hey, this is...
Give it a light poke.
It isn't working.
- Kwang Soo, drive it in there. - Come on.
Drive it in there.
(It popped!)
I did it really gently.
(Kwang Soo did it again.)
- Hey. - I did it really gently.
- Good job. - I did it really gently.
(Trust me.)
- Good job. - Good job.
(He feels wrongly accused.)
- Good job. - I did it really gently.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
(All 10 layers have been slashed.)
You really slashed all 10 layers.
I just put the blade gently against the balloon.
(This is really not fair.)
- How did you do it? - Sunhwa did a great job.
(Team Chang Wook only has one more balloon.)
- I did it gently. - How did she remove one layer?
I did it really gently.
- Yoo Jung. - All right.
(Yoo Jung of Team Yoo Jung tries to slash the balloon.)
Let's go.
This is fun.
(She succeeded to remove one layer.)
Good job.
(She is surprised.)
(Jae Suk makes a big fuss.)
It was so nerve-wracking.
(Captain Yoo Jung succeeded courageously.)
Good job.
The second team should pick someone who will answer the question.
(It's time for the second question.)
- Let's keep it simple. - Se Chan.
- Let's keep it simple. - Okay.
(Se Chan of Team Sunhwa comes forward.)
If it's about ugliness, the answer is Kwang Soo.
That goes without saying.
- Se Chan. - Watch me.
(Feeling guilty)
I will be able to guess the question once I hear the name.
(Confident)
- That's right. - Let's go.
(He checks the question.)
I will figure it out right away. Who is it?
Hold on.
(Deliberating)
- Let's hear it. - The question must be vague.
(What's the question?)
- Sit here. - Keep it simple.
- No one fits it perfectly. - That's right.
(Thinking)
- Don't lie. - I won't.
(After much deliberation, he chooses...)
- I will figure it out right away. - Let's go.
- Sunhwa. - Me?
- This is hard. Sunhwa? - Sunhwa?
(Why is Sunhwa top 1?)
- I... - Let me answer.
The person who can lie the best.
(Incorrect)
Let me answer. The person who is a scatterbrain.
(A self-criticism?)
(Incorrect)
Let me answer. The person who is ignorant.
(Simple)
(Incorrect)
That was forever ago.
(Gritting her teeth)
- I don't watch TV. - You are stuck in the past.
Let me answer. The person who has never dated.
(Incorrect)
- What? - Sunhwa?
- I have dated a few men. My gosh. - Is it a compliment or what?
(She suddenly defends herself.)
Please reveal the top 2 and 3 as a hint.
(They are not even close.)
- The top 2 and 3? - Okay, that will help.
(For this question, 2nd and 3rd places are...)
- I will get it right. - This is hard.
- Then I choose Yoo Jung. - If he mentions Chang Wook...
(If I have to choose...)
Yoo Jung?
And Chang Wook.
I see that sex doesn't matter.
It's related to our job.
(It's related to being a celebrity as a job.)
- Our job? - Yes.
Let me answer.
- If Se Chan were to meet someone... - That's right.
- It's too long. - in the industry...
Is that your guess?
- If Se Chan were to meet someone... - What are you talking about?
(Everyone criticizes Jae Suk's answer.)
That's not how you play this game.
- Is it incorrect? - It's incorrect.
(He quickly apologizes.)
Let me answer.
The person who is the worst at investing.
(Incorrect)
Being a celebrity, we have many worries and...
What are you doing?
(He can't help but answer in long sentences.)
- What are you doing? - That's ridiculous.
- What did I do wrong? - Your answer is too long.
(Harsh criticisms)
- It wasn't too long. - Let me answer.
(He denies.)
The person who has given the most amount of autographs.
- No, that's not it. - Let me answer.
When you are in the entertainment industry,
you come across people who haven't...
- Hurry up and answer. - What are you doing?
(Frustrated)
Are you a doctor?
(It's too elaborate.)
Can't I guess?
(Doctor Yu often gets too wordy in these types of games.)
- It was ridiculous. - Can't I guess?
For goodness' sake.
Give us a hint.
(Se Chan gives a motion hint.)
- Would you like a motion hint? - Yes.
(Rubbing his eyes)
Let me answer!
(Confident)
- I haven't done anything yet. - The person with bad sight...
- Incorrect. Let me keep going. - It's incorrect.
(Incorrect)
- I am not done yet. - He hasn't given a hint yet.
(Let's wait.)
- I will keep it simple. - Don't show unnecessary motions.
I got confused because you did this.
- I wanted to bring out the detail. - Why did you rub your eyes?
(It's your fault.)
I wanted to bring out the detail.
- Why did you rub your eyes? - I will keep it straightforward.
(His motion hint continues.)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
- Let me answer! - Sunhwa was faster.
I was faster.
She was faster.
(Sunhwa earns a chance.)
The person who looks up his or her name the most.
That's it!
(Correct)
I rubbed my eyes to express doing so on a search engine.
(The person who will most likely search his or her name...)
(in search engines or social media.)
- Good job. - So that was the answer.
(Team Sunhwa succeeds, and they are exempt from slashing.)
I did think of that.
(It's too late.)
Then why did you sit still?
(He thought about it, but it took too long to express it.)
I said "Let me answer" too late.
Team Sang Woo, go first.
(Team Sang Woo will slash first.)
Team Chang Wook, you are out if you pop this balloon.
(Team Chang Wook will be last if they pop the balloon.)
What? Out?
We only get two balloons.
You will do well.
(Sang Woo will slash.)
Sang Woo will do it.
Do it gently. Relax your wrist.
Just put the blade on the surface.
- It will pop if you push. - Pop.
(I hope it pops.)
Pop. Pop.
- Just put the blade on the surface. - Yes.
Gently.
- Why isn't it working? - Scratch it.
- No. - Scratch it.
- It isn't... - There you go.
(He succeeds to slash 2 layers.)
- Two layers. - My goodness.
(Gasping)
(Good job.)
How many layers did you slash?
Two layers? That's a lot.
- Team Yoo Jung. - Shall we go first?
(It's Team Yoo Jung's turn.)
Yoo Jung.
- Yoo Jung, we believe in you. - She is...
(The two men trusts Yoo Jung to do the job.)
a professional.
Come closer. If it pops, we should get wet together.
(We are one team.)
That's right.
Suk Jin, move your head.
Yoo Jung, we believe in you.
- Yoo Jung, please. - You can do it.
- Do it gently. - Come on.
- Yoo Jung, do it gently. - There you go.
- There you go. - Gently.
- It's in. - That's enough.
- My goodness. - You are practically slicing it.
- Hold on. - For goodness' sake.
(She can't focus.)
Yoo Jung, you need to ignore them and do it.
(You must focus.)
- I am sorry. - Just do it.
- I am sorry. - I can't concentrate.
I couldn't help but talk.
- We will keep quiet. - Okay, okay.
(He covers his mouth to protect Yoo Jung.)
The balloon doesn't pop easily.
(Frowning)
- That's right. - Don't listen to them.
(She manages to slash one layer this time as well.)
Yoo Jung.
(She finds her talent unexpectedly.)
How are you so good at it?
You are a genius.
(It's awesome.)
It peeled off so fast.
(Jaw-dropping)
If you pop this balloon, you are out.
(If the balloon pops, Team Chang Wook is out.)
All right.
Do it gently. Do it gently.
- Do it gently. - Gently.
- Gently. - Gently.
Rub it back and forth.
No. Keep it on the same spot.
Hold on.
- I am sorry. - You keep blowing air...
into my ear.
I am sorry.
(It's a new ear attack.)
Stop blowing air into his ear.
Why would you blow air into his ear?
Do it gently.
(He covers his ear.)
- Gently. - Keep it on the same spot.
- It pops very easily. - Hit it lightly.
- Hit it lightly. - There are 10 layers, so it's okay.
- Hit it lightly. - No, no. Don't listen to him.
No, no. Don't listen to him.
(Hitting)
- Don't listen to him. - Seriously.
(Frustrated)
- How could you listen to him? - Keep your ears closed.
Don't listen to anyone.
(Chang Wook's naive.)
Do what you want to do.
- Just keep your touch gentle. - Let's focus.
(Telling himself)
He will do it now.
Chang Wook.
(Exclaiming)
Hey, that's...
(Shaking)
- There you go. - Hit it lightly.
- Hey, hey! - Hold on!
- I can't do it. - You should do it.
(He gives up.)
- Do it gently. - Do it as if trimming your brows.
(Chang Wook is scared. He tosses the knife to Ji Hyo.)
It's almost done.
- Okay. I got it. - Give it a try.
Do it gently.
(Chang Wook is a coward.)
- Do you want me to do it? - This is our last chance.
- Hold on. - Don't hit it.
That tactic won't work.
Jae Suk...
(Popping)
(They get a splash of water.)
(She failed to control her strength.)
My goodness.
(That team is out.)
That happened because you kept scratching.
Okay!
(Blaming)
I am so annoyed.
- They did the worst job. - Okay.
(They failed without getting any layer.)
You shouldn't have scratched the surface.
Other teams removed 1 or 2 layers.
You are in no place to say that.
(They blame each other.)
I told you to do it gently.
I couldn't keep my touch gentle since I was too annoyed.
(Frustrated)
They are terrible at it.
(I know they're not my team, but they are terrible at it.)
- Okay. - Team Chang Wook is the last place.
(Team Chang Wook is guaranteed to place last.)
They are out.
(It's a bummer.)
You can still answer the question.
Shall I give a question?
(Kwang Soo will pick the third question.)
Can we get the answer right?
No.
(Firm)
Just enjoy the game.
- What? - Just enjoy Running Man.
Are we only allowed to give the question?
(Because they used 2 balloons, they can only give a question.)
Yes. Give them your answer.
Who is it?
You can sit down and do it.
I bet he will give a strange answer on purpose.
(I bet he will give a strange answer on purpose.)
- Who is it? - I bet he will throw us off.
It's what I think.
(Hesitating)
- I am going by the person's image. - Hurry up.
(Frustrated)
- Sunhwa. - Why?
- Sunhwa? - Her image?
- What is this about? - Let's hear more about it.
(Why did he mention Sunhwa?)
- What is this about? - Sunhwa.
It's about dating.
(A hint)
- Dating? - It's about dating.
- Dating? - It's about dating, right?
(It's about dating, and I'm the top 1?)
- Dating. - Let me answer.
The person who would break up in the coolest fashion.
(Incorrect)
No. I am not cool about a breakup.
Is it about two-timing?
(Confessing)
The person who gets obsessive...
- Is it about dating? - Is it a good thing or a bad thing?
Well, it's not a good thing.
- Really? - Is it about a breakup?
Is it about a breakup?
A breakup.
It's related to a breakup.
(It's about a breakup.)
- Really? - Let me answer.
The person who would break up the fastest.
I am sorry, but this could be a bit worse than that.
- Is it worse than that? - Then why did you give my name?
(My goodness.)
It's not something that comes after a breakup.
(A hint)
- I see. - Then during a relationship...
(Then who's the top 2?)
Who is the top two?
Is it So Min?
(Quietly)
Why would it be me? He said it's something bad.
- We are the same. - That's exactly why it's you.
(For some reason, it feels like a sad love story is all So Min's.)
Why do people choose me for all the bad things?
You are a bit...
So Min is within the top three, right?
The top two is...
- Haha. - What?
- What? - Me?
(Am I the top 2?)
- Really? - Let me answer.
The person who swears when he or she breaks up.
(A big blow)
It's not something that comes after a breakup.
(Dizzy)
- That's right. - He said that before.
(She quietly strikes a blow.)
This is something that comes during a breakup.
The person who doesn't pay for the date.
- I pay a lot. - I...
(Explaining)
I practically sell the house.
I can't help but explain myself.
(She gives an excuse.)
- "I am not like that." - It's about...
dating someone...
(That's what it says on the cue card.)
There is a word, "The other".
(It's a big hint.)
- The other? - Yes.
Let me answer.
The person the other would tire of the fastest in a relationship.
(Correct)
Come on!
Why is it Sunhwa?
(The person the other would tire of the fastest in a relationship)
Why is it me?
(Angry)
- Explain. - Why is it Sunhwa?
- I mean... - How could you do this to me?
(Sorry)
- It's not like that. - Come here!
Take this!
(She runs to Kwang Soo and demands an explanation.)
- Why is it Sunhwa? - I had to pick someone.
I'm not saying you're like that.
(Don't take it personally.)
What do you know about Sunhwa?
I am already hurt because of my past relationship.
(She hasn't recovered yet.)
Seriously.
Don't misunderstand.
How could you be so mean?
- I had to choose someone. - My relationships...
- last long. - Is Haha the top two?
Why am I the top two? Explain.
(Another victim)
- My relationships last long. - It's...
What do you know?
(Everyone, calm down.)
My ex-girlfriends still have feelings for me!
The celebrities you have dated always say...
(Joking)
they are sick and tired of you!
- Look at yourself objectively. - I know that, but...
(Out of control)
I just went with my feeling.
(Kwang Soo's in trouble due to what he said.)
I got confused because he picked Sunhwa.
No one would have thought that about her.
Seriously. My relationships last long.
I know that. I am sorry. I had to pick someone.
(Discouraged)
The two teams will take turns to slash the balloon.
(Team Sang Woo and Team Sunhwa will cut their balloons.)
I don't know why we need to sit down and do it.
(Crazy So Min's getting ready.)
No, no. It's a rule.
(Please calm down.)
- All right. - We need to sit down.
I will sit down.
- I hope their balloon pops. - We need to do it, right?
It's so frustrating.
(Getting ready)
No, no. Hold on.
What?
(No one can stop her.)
Move the blade sideways.
- That's right. - Move the blade sideways.
Move it sideways.
(She removed 4 layers.)
(In any case, she succeeded.)
- Did you see that? - Good job.
You did a good job.
(Triumphant)
This is how you do it.
I will stay close.
(Next is Team Sunhwa.)
(Bursting)
(She took out her anger on the water balloon.)
The water splattered everywhere!
(Sunhwa slashed without holding back.)
- You... - I did it gently!
She is angry because of you!
- I am sorry, Sunhwa. - She is really angry.
I picked you because I had to pick someone.
(Kwang Soo's wrong choice makes her lose her mind.)
- Come back to your senses. - I could have done...
- better. - Okay.
(In the next two questions,)
- Come back to your senses. - Sunhwa, let's go.
Someone from Team Chang Wook.
(Team Sunhwa and Team Sang Woo both lost once.)
Give us the name.
(Chang Wook checks the question this time.)
- Whom will you choose? - Well...
(Thinking)
- Why is he looking at me? - Whom will you choose?
- Suk Jin. - Me?
Let me answer. The person who doesn't act his or her age.
(Incorrect)
- Me? - The person who is cold-hearted.
The person who frequents the toilet at night because of residual urine.
Don't say something that's true.
(Conspiring)
- Residual urine! - He frequents the toilet at night.
(It's not true.)
Residual urine!
Let me answer. The person who says he peed...
even though you didn't hear any sound.
(Incorrect)
There was no one else.
(The silent toilet)
Chang Wook must see Suk Jin differently from us.
- That's right. - Chang Wook, tell us...
how you see Suk Jin.
(What does Chang Wook think of Suk Jin?)
Since he has a way with words,
(He has a way with his words.)
- Really? - I think...
he will do this when he has a conversation.
(He will do this when he has a conversation.)
A conversation?
Let me answer.
The person who laughs at his own joke.
(Incorrect)
That was perfect.
(He reacts to what he says on his own.)
Let me answer. The person who isn't serious at all.
(Attacking Suk Jin)
(Incorrect)
The person who has been punched during a conversation.
(He can't say no.)
That's correct.
That's perfect.
Chang Wook, give us a motion hint.
During a conversation, he would go, "Hey, I..."
(A motion hint)
Let me answer.
(Upon seeing the motion hint,)
(Jae Suk yelled out.)
The person who brags about the celebrities...
- he knows. - Let me answer.
(Correct)
The person who brags about the celebrities he knows.
(Who would brag about the celebrities he or she knows?)
My goodness.
Brag about how well-connected I am? I don't do that.
(Denying)
- Chang Wook. - But...
you bragged too much earlier.
(Experienced)
Chang Wook.
You started from Magistrate Byun and...
(Starting from District Magistrate Byun)
- He did that. - Magistrate Byun.
(He knows a lot of people beyond time and border.)
- I am sorry. - The former classmates.
I bragged too much earlier.
(Team Sang Woo's turn to cut the water balloon.)
That's right.
- That's right. - Okay.
Slash the balloon.
So Min, do it.
- Should I do it? - She is Dr. Romantic.
(Scalpel)
I don't know if I would be able to do it again.
(So Min the romantic doctor)
She is Dr. Jeon.
(So Min cut 4 layers of balloons at once before. What about now?)
Dr. Jeon, I believe in you.
It's over for them.
- Dr. Jeon. - It's okay if I fail, right?
Dr. Jeon, it's okay. Go ahead.
(She brandishes the scalpel.)
What was that?
(What? It fell?)
- What? - What was that?
- It fell. - It's on the floor.
- What happened? - We are still in.
We are still in.
(The water balloon didn't burst.)
- How did you do it? - We are still in.
It looked like a turtle was laying an egg.
So Min is good.
(Because it fell,)
- She is daring. - It didn't burst.
(Kwang Soo will hold it for her.)
I will try again, but there is a good chance it will burst.
I bet Kwang Soo will burst it with his hands.
(She read Kwang Soo's evil intention.)
I wouldn't do that. Don't be ridiculous.
- In that case, - I am nervous.
cut his finger.
(Cut his fingers. Then he can't burst it.)
Come on. I will just hold it.
Keep your fingers relaxed.
- Okay. - Let's do it.
(Pressing)
- Don't press it! - All right.
(He can't control his DNA to cheat.)
All right. I will just hold it.
I am simply applying force.
(Shameless)
- Why would you do that? - Action and reaction.
I will stay still.
Why did you bring up action and reaction?
(Why did he bring up action and reaction?)
Be careful.
(Will So Min be able to succeed?)
(She succeeds to cut one layer.)
I did it.
What was that?
(But...)
(Kwang Soo's action and reaction came into play.)
I did it.
- What was that? - It didn't burst!
- I did it. - It was Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo pressed the balloon,)
Kwang Soo pressed it.
(but due to action and reaction, only he got wet.)
He got water all over him.
- He is stupid. - So Min succeeded.
(Kwang Soo sacrificed himself.)
Are you okay?
- So Min succeeded. - I succeeded.
- Team Yoo Jung takes first place. - Okay.
(Team Yoo Jung, Team Sang Woo, Team Sunhwa, Team Chang Wook)
Yoo Jung, you did it.
Yoo Jung made all the difference.
Starting from the winning team,
(Time to select the second hot item)
you will choose an item each.
Yoo Jung, let's go.
(Team Yoo Jung chooses the lunchbox.)
A packed meal.
A packed meal is popular.
All right.
- Pick an item, Sang Woo. - Wet wipes.
(Team Sang Woo chooses the wet wipes.)
Okay.
(Team Sunhwa chooses the hangover drink.)
- Okay. - A hangover drink.
We choose an energy drink.
(Team Chang Wook chooses the energy drink.)
- Okay. - That can't be popular.
You have an offer from a broker.
(Then the brokers' offer arrive.)
- What is it? - Team Sunhwa,
(Brokers made an offer to Team Sunhwa.)
will you accept it?
- What should we do? - Let's turn it down.
- Turn it down. - What happens if we turn it down?
(If they don't accept it,)
- We receive a hint. - What happens if we accept it?
(they don't get to choose an item, but they will receive a hint.)
- Then we can catch the brokers. - A hint?
- Two hints. - Don't do that.
You are a broker, right?
- No, I am not. - That's why...
We aren't brokers,
- so we want a hint. - We won't be able to find them.
No, Haha.
- Don't be like that. - Are you a broker?
(They're discussing whether to take the offer or not.)
- We need a hint. - Everyone.
I will give you a crucial hint.
The top 1, 2, 3 items in terms of sales are still here.
(The top 1, 2, 3 items in terms of sales remain.)
Really?
The top 1, 2, 3 items in terms of sales are still here.
- Then let's accept it. - Let's accept it.
(They decide to take the broker's offer.)
No way.
Could chewing gum be one of them?
(They carefully make a deduction of hot items.)
- I don't think so. - People don't buy it often.
I think they're around here. I think they're drinks.
I think banana milk is one of the top three.
- I agree. - Banana milk, definitely.
(Team Sunhwa chooses popular banana milk.)
- Let's go for it. - Let's go for it.
- It's very popular. - We've made our choice.
Guys, a broker just proposed a deal...
to Team Yoo Jung.
(Team Yoo Jung just received an offer from a broker.)
- Make up your mind. - We'll accept it.
- We'll accept it. Let's go. - What?
(As soon as he hears it...)
- Why? - We have to accept it.
(Without discussing?)
- Why? - Don't we need a hint?
(Don't we need a hint?)
- Isn't it better to get a hint? - Do you want a hint?
(Team Yoo Jung rejects the offer to receive a hint.)
- Let's get a hint. - I think that'd be better.
Okay, let's get a hint. Yoo Jung.
What could be the top three?
Brokers, propose deals to us too.
Brokers, propose deals to us!
(I want to get an offer.)
I have no idea.
(They get a hint instead of choosing an additional item.)
What's that?
- Here's a hint. - What?
- What's this? - What's this?
(They receive a hint from the staff.)
The broker wrote it.
(It's the broker's...)
- It's the broker's handwriting? - The broker wrote it?
(handwriting.)
Is the handwriting the hint?
(Kim Yoo Jung)
- Goodness, that's unbelievable. - This...
- It's a label from clothes. - It's a label from clothes.
(Making a deduction)
Is it from the broker's clothes?
- Is this the same? - This...
No, they're different.
(They compare it to the label on their clothes.)
(They're different.)
Where is it from? Let me see.
- It's from a towel. - It's from a towel?
(Is the label...)
(from a towel?)
A towel... Let me see.
- A towel... - I know.
The broker is not among us. Do you know why?
- We didn't use any towels. - None of us are wet.
- The towel was the hint. - When did the broker write it?
(The broker used a towel in the previous game?)
(The broker is one of these 9 people.)
I think there's a broker among you guys.
(I think there's a broker among you guys.)
Propose a deal to us, and we'll accept it.
- Propose a deal. - Let's propose a deal.
- Let's do it. - Do it.
- Let's propose a deal. - Please.
- Propose a deal to us too. - We'll accept it.
(Are you brokers?)
- Do you want it first or... - We'll accept it.
(Haha and Se Chan offer a deal.)
- We want it first. - We'll accept it.
We'll propose a deal to this team.
You have to...
(Are these two really brokers?)
You have to signal the staff.
- It has to be done the proper way. - We'll do it.
Start.
(Haha and Se Chan prepare a deal.)
- We are the future - We are the future
(What?)
(The two childish brokers are proposing a deal.)
(What were we expecting from them?)
- That was the brokers' sign? - Yes.
(That's ridiculous.)
Why haven't I seen it before?
(The 40-year-old broker is trying hard.)
Gather up, everyone.
- The broker is incredible. - The broker is so quick.
(Team Yoo Jung received a hint.)
Good job. That was so quick.
(Do they know who it is?)
- When did the broker do it? - When did the broker do it?
All right.
(They move to the next place with a hint on brokers.)
Let's get ready for the last mission.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Hot Item Selection Status)
(The last mission to win hot items)
Bounce more!
(A refreshing water-sled race with the brokers)
No!
(The third mission is finished.)
- Good job! - Gosh!
Let me announce the results of the last mission.
(The result of the third mission)
Team Sang Woo is in 1st place with 11 points.
(Team Sang Woo in 1st place)
Team Sunhwa is in 2nd place with 10 points.
(Team Sunhwa in 2nd place)
Team Chang Wook is in 3rd place with 8 points.
(Team Chang Wook in 3rd place)
Team Yoo Jung is in 4th place with 7 points.
(Team Yoo Jung in 4th place)
That's a shame.
Please choose your last item.
(They'll pick hot items according to their place.)
- Are we choosing 1? - Yes, choose 1.
- We choose Coke. - Let's go for Coke.
(Team Sang Woo chooses gimbap, lighter, wet wipes and coke.)
Really?
(Team Sunhwa chooses cup noodles, jjajang ramyeon, hangover drink,)
(banana milk and stockings.)
- All right. Let's choose stockings. - Okay.
(Team Chang Wook chooses bottled water, tea, energy drink...)
- I vote for tissues. - Tissues?
- Tissues. - Okay, tissues.
(and tissues.)
(Team Yoo Jung chooses sausage, ice cream, lunchbox...)
(and ice cubes in a cup.)
Ice cubes in a cup?
This is what I buy most often.
(Ice cubes in a cup)
- Yoo Jung. - Let her choose.
(Suk Jin keeps talking about the fishcake bar.)
I think we should choose a fish cake bar.
Yoo Jung, you get to decide.
I think she's a broker.
(Seriously? Ice cubes in a cup?)
- Trust me. - That's a surprising choice.
- I know. - Gosh.
(Are ice cubes in a cup really a hot item?)
Let me announce the brokers' last proposals.
(The brokers' last proposal)
Broker A proposed a deal to Team Yoo Jung and Team Chang Wook.
(Broker A made an offer to Team Yoo Jung and Team Chang Wook.)
Broker B proposed a deal to Team Sang Woo.
(Broker B made an offer to Team Sang Woo.)
- Broker B. - Should we get a hint?
- We didn't get any proposals? - No.
(Team Sunhwa is the only team that didn't get any proposal.)
I think...
(They have to decide whether to accept the deal or not.)
We should accept the deal...
- and win another item. - Right.
- Let's do that. - I know one of the brokers.
What did you see?
(He knows one of the brokers?)
I saw the broker...
write something and submit it.
(He's sharing what he saw.)
- I saw it clearly. - Really?
I saw it with my own eyes.
- Really? - Yes.
(Does Chang Wook really know who the broker is?)
I know who it is.
We want a hint...
- It's a hint about Broker A, right? - It's about Broker A.
(Team Yoo Jung decides to receive a hint on Broker A.)
- We want the hint. - We want the hint.
- Let's have a look. - Just a second.
We won't swipe.
- What's that? - Is that a hint?
(A picture from Broker A)
It's from the broker.
- The broker took this picture? - Yes.
Think of what's going on in this picture.
(They must recall the memory and make a deduction on the broker.)
- Where was this? - So the broker is...
The broker is not one of the people in the picture.
- Where was this? - Isn't that me?
(Observing)
- No. - That cap is mine.
(Is that my cap?)
- No, it isn't. - It isn't?
(It's not Suk Jin's cap.)
- No. - No?
It's Sang Woo.
Why are they looking at you?
(It's Sang Woo's cap.)
- Why are they looking at me? - They looked at you.
(Sang Woo has no idea.)
It must be a picture.
- The broker sent this picture? - Yes.
(Broker A took a picture of Jae Suk...)
To choose the team?
(and made an offer to Team Yoo Jung.)
(Who took that picture?)
What do the other teams want?
- We want a hint. - We want a hint.
You want a hint about Broker B.
(They rejects the offer.)
We have no hints, so we'll have to take a guess.
(A hint about Broker B for Team Sang Woo)
What's this?
The broker submitted this to choose us?
(A glove?)
Is this how he proposed a deal?
(Broker B made a proposal on a glove.)
Try to think of the situation and guess whose handwriting this is.
(They make a deduction based on the situation and writing.)
- Kwang Soo and Jae Suk were... - Kwang Soo was wearing gloves.
He was, right?
(A moment ago)
- Can I decide? - You can do that.
That's not going to work.
(Kwang Soo was wearing gloves the whole time.)
(Is Kwang Soo Broker B?)
Let me try it on.
- Let's see. - How big is it?
(They make a deduction based on the size of the hand.)
- Well... - The broker has big hands.
The bottom of my hand is here.
This is a lot bigger than my hand.
(The glove is a lot bigger than So Min's hand.)
(So Min examines Kwang Soo's hand.)
- Spread your fingers. - Why?
- Can we get the picture? - Can we get the picture?
(Like the prince looking for the owner of a glass slipper,)
- We sent it. - To who?
(So Min is looking for the owner of the glove.)
(Laughing)
- It's a man, right? - It is.
(Jong Kook. I think I found him.)
- Right? - Because...
the fingers are so long.
(It's Kwang Soo.)
Look at this.
This is where the fingers bend.
(Broker B is Kwang Soo with long fingers?)
Is Kwang Soo a broker?
Why? What's the hint?
(Is he playing innocent or does he really have no idea?)
- Kwang Soo, are you a broker? - No.
All right.
- What do you want to do? - We accept the deal.
- You do? - Yes.
Then choose an item.
(Team Chang Wook chooses an additional item.)
I want to choose coffee.
Coffee?
(Team Chang Wook chooses a canned coffee.)
- Canned coffee? - Let's do this.
All teams are done choosing items.
(Team Yoo Jung)
(Team Sunhwa)
(Team Sang Woo)
(Team Chang Wook)
(Both Brokers A and B made 3 successful deals.)
(It's time to catch the brokers.)
First, you'll catch the brokers.
If you choose to catch the brokers,
(If they choose to catch the brokers,)
you have to guess both brokers.
You can put a "multiply by two" sticker...
(they have to guess both brokers.)
on as many items as the number of brokers you catch.
(They'll put a "multiply by 2" sticker on as many items...)
- On the items we choose? - You'll also put...
(as the number of brokers they catch.)
a "divide by two" sticker on as many items...
as the number of brokers you fail to catch.
(They'll put a "divide by 2" sticker on as many items...)
- "Divide by two"? - We have to catch both brokers?
(as the number of brokers they fail to catch.)
Yes, then you'll get two "multiply by two" stickers.
(If they catch 2, 2 "multiply by 2" stickers)
- What if we catch only one? - You'll get one of each.
(If they catch 1, 1 "multiply by 2" and 1 "divide by 2")
Also, the brokers will lose...
(If they catch 0, 2 "divide by 2" stickers)
as many items...
as the number of teams that catch them.
(The brokers will lose as many items...)
(as the number of teams that catch them.)
- We'll... - We'll stay out.
We have no hints.
(Team Sunhwa decides not to catch the brokers.)
We'll stay out.
Team Sunhwa stays out.
- Do you want to catch the brokers? - Yes, we do.
(Team Yoo Jung,)
- We want to catch the brokers. - Let's try.
(Team Sang Woo,)
- We want to catch the brokers. - Okay.
(and Team Chang Wook...)
(decide to catch the brokers.)
Three teams want to catch the brokers.
Discuss for a minute and tell us your decision.
(If they catch the broker, they can turn the table.)
- Come here. - Since we know...
- We know one broker for sure. - We know one.
(Chang Wook said he knows one broker for sure.)
Who is it?
- One of them is Kwang Soo. - Me?
(Chang Wook suspects Kwang Soo.)
- Right? - It's not me.
Right?
What are you talking about?
(They're whispering without Kwang Soo.)
I thought so too.
(Kwang Soo follows them.)
I saw it.
Shut it.
(Kwang Soo is cornered and swears at Chang Wook.)
(When the brokers were being decided...)
(You're a broker.)
(Write someone's name and give it to the staff.)
(Kwang Soo was chosen as a broker.)
(While everyone was busy carrying out missions,)
I think they're here.
(he wrote down names on all kinds of things,)
(including a blindfold and a ramyeon seasoning bag.)
If I look...
(The glove was Kwang Soo's too.)
(Han Sunhwa, Ji Chang Wook, Kim Yoo Jung, Do Sang Woo)
(He wasn't afraid to propose a deal in any situation.)
Banana milk...
(In the end, he was witnessed by Chang Wook.)
(Is Kwang Soo a broker?)
- I saw it. - Shut it.
(The broker tries to shut Chang Wook's mouth.)
(Kwang Soo, you're busted!)
Shut it before the other teams find out.
(Kwang Soo makes a deal like a professional broker.)
Can't we just guess one broker?
- You have to guess both. - Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(I'm doomed.)
I told you.
I'm not entirely sure whose handwriting this is, but...
(Yoo Jung seemed to figure something out.)
(Kim Yoo Jung)
- Who do you think it is? - I think...
(She observes Kwang Soo's handwriting for a while.)
this is...
Chang Wook's handwriting.
(What? It's Chang Wook's handwriting?)
- Can't we make him write something? - It's similar.
(Yoo Jung makes a wrong guess.)
- You've seen his handwriting? - Yes.
- I've seen it. - Really?
I'm sure.
(Yoo Jung is confident after making a wrong guess.)
- Let's do it. - I'm 100 percent sure.
Chang Wook, who do you think the other broker is?
(Chang Wook and Ji Hyo know one broker for sure.)
- The brokers were chosen randomly. - Yes.
(If they guess both right, they get 2 "multiply by 2" stickers.)
I should try to catch the other broker too.
(Kwang Soo joins the investigation.)
- The other broker took a picture. - The other broker...
sent a picture.
Who used a phone?
(Who used a phone?)
I'm suspecting Sunhwa and Yoo Jung.
(Chang Wook thinks...)
(it's either Sunhwa or Yoo Jung.)
Yoo Jung kept hovering around there.
(Is the other broker one of the two?)
- Yoo Jung? - Yoo Jung?
(Team Chang Wook picks...)
(Kwang Soo and Yoo Jung.)
Kwang Soo!
We're done.
Let's just write it.
(Team Sang Woo and Team Yoo Jung have made their choices too.)
I'm not sure about that one, but it's probably right.
Right?
(If they catch the brokers, they can turn the table.)
Everyone is suspecting everyone.
Let me announce the three teams' choices first...
- and then who the brokers are. - Okay.
Team Sang Woo chose...
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.
(Team Sang Woo picks Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.)
Me?
- And... - Why me?
(They figured out.)
He sounds surprised.
Team Yoo Jung chose...
Chang Wook and Jong Kook.
(Team Yoo Jung picks Chang Wook and Jong Kook.)
- Me? - Yes.
Team Chang Wook chose...
(Lastly, Team Chang Wook picks...)
Kwang Soo and Yoo Jung.
(Kwang Soo and Yoo Jung.)
- They picked one from their team? - I'm speechless.
(They picked from their own team?)
I don't know.
I kept saying it's not me, but they won't listen.
- Kwang Soo came out as a broker. - True.
(Kwang Soo is a broker.)
- They were whispering behind me. - Hey.
(The broker feels ostracized.)
That's not why.
(Ji Chang Wook, the whistleblower)
I caught him.
- What are you talking about? - What?
- He was passing off a memo... - Shut your mouth!
(He explodes.)
(Were you a broker?)
- Really? - It is you.
- What? It's not me. - It's you.
(Chang Wook messed everything up.)
It's not.
Let me announce the brokers.
(Kwang Soo got exposed,)
(and there's one more.)
The brokers are...
(Unlike him, Broker A is still a mystery.)
The brokers are Kwang Soo and Chang Wook.
- Hey! - Chang Wook.
That's what I said!
(Chang Wook was a broker!)
This is unbelievable.
- It was so obvious. - Hey!
(Everyone is shocked.)
- See? Chang Wook acted weird today. - That's what I said!
(He feigned innocence...)
(and exposed Kwang Soo.)
(There's nobody you can trust in the world of brokers.)
I have to look by myself.
(When the brokers were being selected...)
(You're a broker. Take pictures of members you want to make offers to.)
(Chang Wook was selected as the broker.)
(He approached them quietly...)
(and took pictures.)
(Chang Wook was a silent photographer.)
I caught him.
(When he realized what Kwang Soo was, he diverted attention.)
- What are you talking about? - What?
- He was passing off a memo... - Shut your mouth!
(That's how Broker Ji Chang Wook gained everybody's trust.)
(The two brokers were on the same team.)
I did catch you though.
You're Broker B, right?
I was right!
(Naively)
She guessed it right.
(She feels happy even if it was a lucky guess.)
Yoo Jung said it was Chang Wook's writing.
(We were completely fooled.)
That was good, Chang Wook.
Where did they go? Crazy people.
(Ji Hyo had a rough day with the two brokers.)
I did catch you though.
- They're fighting. - It was them.
(It's just awesome.)
Hey, you...
(Cursing and grabbing him by the throat after being betrayed)
Hey.
Did he lose?
(A perfect crime by Broker Ji)
Chang Wook exposed Kwang Soo.
We're both brokers, and he ratted me out.
(He didn't follow the rules for a broker.)
Kwang Soo, you got arrested,
(Kwang Soo was caught 2 times.)
so you can choose one item.
(He can select 1 item.)
Chang Wook, you can choose two.
(Chang Wook was caught 1 time.)
Only two? Rather than that...
(He can select 2 items.)
See? We're in first place.
We might win.
(Maybe we can win!)
- See? We're in first place. - That's true.
We might win.
Three teams, please add "multiply by two"...
(The three teams that caught one broker each can choose...)
and "divide by two" on items you want.
("multiply by 2" or "divide by 2".)
That was close.
Yoo Jung, you can put "multiply by two" wherever you want.
Brokers, please decide.
Do they steal our items?
(Yoo Jung puts "multiply by 2" on an ice cup.)
Go ahead.
Do whatever you want.
This is the ice cream.
We have to put "divide by two" on an item with a low score.
- Low score. - Something that'll sell the least.
(They attach "divide by 2" on the lunchbox.)
Let's choose the packed meal.
Brokers, please use items as well.
(The broker will now choose items.)
- I'll choose canned coffee. - Canned coffee?
(Kwang Soo chooses canned coffee.)
What about you, Chang Wook?
I'll choose stockings...
(Chang Wook chooses stockings and ice cream.)
and ice cream.
- Ice cream? - Ice cream.
(They put the stickers on.)
(Brokers chose their items as well!)
I'll announce the final rankings.
(It's time to announce the rankings.)
I really want to know.
- You never know. We might win. - I know.
(We don't know yet.)
- Should we open this? - Yes.
(How were the convenience store hot items ranked?)
1, 2, 3.
I see the large bottle of water.
A cup of ice is in first place?
- We're first! - It's us!
(A cup of ice is in 1st place!)
Is this in first place?
I told you it was ice.
- Look at second place. - We got it.
(Banana milk is ranked 2nd.)
See? There's banana milk.
Banana milk...
How is the large bottle of water here?
(Water is ranked higher than they thought.)
It's what we said.
- People buy water a lot. - Exactly.
- We were right. - I suggested it.
- We were right. - Where are the stockings?
(Stockings were a bad choice.)
They're not here at all.
- This was unexpected. - This is not what we thought.
(The 15 most popular items were different than they thought.)
Yoo Jung, you did great.
Yoo Jung.
(Yoo Jung successfully guessed a cup of ice!)
Here are the scores.
(It's time to announce the scores.)
First place is...
(Which team got 1st place?)
Team Yoo Jung with 30 points.
(Team Yoo Jung with 30 points)
Yes!
Team Yoo Jung with 30 points.
(They won with the cup of ice, with points multiplied by 2.)
No way. Only if it wasn't in first place...
We were in last place the whole time.
(They were able to win because of the final choice.)
We won hands down because of her.
- How did she think of cup of ice? - It was just one item.
(It's a twist caused by a cup of ice that no one chose.)
We would have won with that.
How did she think of cup of ice?
- I didn't think of it at all. - 2nd and 3rd places...
(2nd and 3rd places were only 2 points apart.)
were 2 points apart.
It's us.
2nd place is Team Sunhwa with 22 points.
(Team Sunhwa with 22 points.)
- We did well. - Good job.
(Banana milk 14 points, cup noodles 8 points, total 22 points)
3rd place is Team Sang Woo with 20 points.
(Lighters 10 points, coke 5 points, multiply by 2, total 20 points)
- Are we in third place? - That was close.
At least we're not in last place.
Team Chang Wook, Ji Hyo earned 13 points,
(Ji Hyo of Team Chang Wook, 13 points)
Kwang Soo earned 4 points, and Chang Wook earned 0.
(Broker Kwang Soo, 4 points)
(Broker Chang Wook, 0 point)
- This is fun. - This is fun.
(They worked hard all day to earn 0 and 4 points.)
You darn brokers.
- Brokers. - Serves you right.
The prizes are 10 popular items from the convenience store...
(The prizes are 10 popular items from the convenience store...)
(and convenience store gift card.)
- Really? - and convenience store gift card.
- There's a gift card? - I'm envious.
(We would like to thank Chang Wook, Yoo Jung,)
(Sunhwa, and Sang Woo for joining us in early summer heat.)
- Great work. - Thank you.
- Great work. - Great work.
I'm scared.
(There are three kinds of people in this world.)
- What's this? - Suk Jin! Where are you going?
- Suk Jin! - Ji Hyo!
(Those on top,)
I'm on the eighth floor!
Ji Hyo!
(those on the bottom,)
What's going on?
(and those who betray)
- What's this? - But I can't take this.
This is not a competition. We can all survive.
(This coin sharing is to test the loyalty of Running Man members.)
United we stand and divided we fall.
(United we stand and divided we fall!)
- I have no faith in you. - What did I do? I have no coins!
(It's an intense race where people without their trust get eliminated.)
This is insane!
(Viewers' reports finally get revealed.)
This is where Jae Suk had his first kiss!
(From Jae Suk's first kiss...)
(to seeing him at the sauna)
Jae Suk was at the sauna.
Can this be on TV?
A woman who lived overseas.
(Does Jong Kook's love story get revealed for the first time?)
- Is this true? - Correct.
So Min was in front of the waiting room with somebody else.
(Does So Min's past make her put her head down?)
They were very affectionate to each other.
Who was it?
(The viewers' eyewitnesses add substance to the revelations.)
How many of my boyfriends are you going to mention?
Get off your high horse.
(Is there no loyalty? You can look forward to next week!)
You can look forward to this! This is exclusive.
(Running Man Loyalty Race: Sharing Playbook)
Let's all survive together.