- Hello. - Hello.
(One sunny day in June)
Hey.
- Hello. - This is pretty.
- This place looks like a cafe. - Hello.
(It's pretty.)
It also looks like an escape room.
(They're checking out the pretty studio.)
- This is pretty. - Look at that.
This is so nice.
We have a flasher here.
(We have a flasher here.)
Shouldn't it be X-rated?
(Kwang Soo's shorts...)
- What? - He looks like a flasher.
(catch people's attention.)
Hey, listen.
Kwang Soo, do you have a problem with your stylist?
(Do you have a problem with your stylist?)
Why? It's my style.
- Are you wearing underpants? - Aren't they too short?
(Kwang Soo's embarrassing fashion...)
(is receiving a lot of attention.)
- No. - Which one is your pants?
- He tries so hard. - Seriously.
(You're unbelievable.)
You're so gutty.
(Your fashion)
What did you say?
He told me earlier...
that this is what a celebrity should wear. But with the camera on,
(Feeling betrayed)
- he says "You're so gutty." - He woke up.
(What's your identity?)
Isn't that what Sherlock Holmes wears?
- The checked jacket. - It's similar.
(They don't stop commenting on Kwang Soo's fashion.)
- You need a hat though. - His pants are too short.
You look better without the jacket.
(He ends up taking it off.)
- Right. This is much better. - I like that.
You look more sophisticated this way.
(They feel better.)
You look better without the jacket on.
My goodness.
I'll just wear a white shirt and jeans next week.
- I know. - This is a lot better.
(It's easy if you give up.)
That's how you end up.
Today, we have special guests waiting.
- Wow. - I see.
Let's bring in the guests then.
(Special guests are visiting Running Man?)
- Who are they? - I guess there are a lot.
(Is it a male guest?)
- I just hope... - What?
Hey.
- My goodness. - They all are here.
(Who are the special guests that surprised everyone?)
- I just hope... - What?
What's going on? What are you guys doing here?
(More and more diverse charms)
- They all are here. - What are you guys doing here?
(The charming TWICE)
- What's going on? - They all are here.
(Everyone is surprised...)
- What are you guys doing here? - I can't believe this.
(by their sudden visit.)
This is amazing.
- Hello, guys. - My goodness.
(Fresh)
- This way. - They all are here.
- When did you come? - Hello.
- They all are here. - When did you come?
(TWICE performs their new song as soon as they show up.)
This is amazing.
("More and More" by TWICE)
When did you guys get here?
This is crazy.
(They make everyone flutter as soon as they appear.)
Let's go!
They've become even prettier.
There weren't any articles about them.
(It was thoroughly kept secret.)
- I know. - Move over!
(Don't get in the way.)
- It was a secret. - Move over!
Back off.
- This is amazing. - They've become even prettier.
(So one more time)
My gosh.
(Getting hyper)
TWICE! TWICE!
- They dance so well. - They are amazing.
I love them.
(Addictive beats)
They are so cool.
(Everyone's addicted to the song.)
They all are great dancers.
They are really good.
(TWICE's fresh performance makes people want to watch it again.)
(Truly impressed)
That was great.
(Today's guests are TWICE.)
- What's going on? - I'm really surprised.
I had no idea.
(He's getting nervous to see the whole group.)
- Me neither. - How did you come?
When TWICE comes, they usually release articles first.
(All members of TWICE are in the show without any notice.)
- I know. - Please say hello first.
(It's time to introduce TWICE.)
Okay.
(Nervous)
It's been a long time.
- 1, 2, and 3. - One in a million.
(One in a million, TWICE)
- Hello, we are TWICE. - Hello, we are TWICE.
(His enthusiasm is at max.)
It's TWICE!
Today's going to be fun.
I'm very thankful...
(Running Man is the only show that all 9 members appear together.)
that they visit our show like this every time.
First of all... Hang on.
(They're about to start the interview.)
Ji Hyo and So Min are being too quiet now.
(2 people are quiet.)
Why are you so deflated?
- So Min, you're dressed like TWICE. - You look like them.
- Look at the color. - Stand next to Tzuyu.
- Stand here. - Go ahead and do it.
(So Min stands next to them after hearing she dressed alike.)
You look like their manager.
- I know. - That's true.
(TWICE and their manager)
- Look at her. - So Min.
(Please support TWICE.)
Ji Hyo, stand next to them.
(Ji Hyo stands next to them too.)
- You're wearing similar colors. - I'm their road manager.
She's a road manager.
- I'm their road manager. - Right.
(TWICE and 2 intruders)
- TWICE is our guests for today. - It's a TWICE special.
I'm really glad to see them.
The nine members of TWICE are back...
(TWICE is visiting Running Man after 2 years.)
in Running Man after two years.
I wish I knew about it.
(It's a bummer.)
Right. We would've gotten ready for this.
We would've worn outfits that match theirs.
What would you do if you knew about it?
If I knew, I would've dressed like a hippie.
- I would've worn... - I would've worn matching ones.
(We're glad they didn't know.)
- Kwang Soo is like a hippie. - All right then.
Please say hello to our viewers one by one.
(Tzuyu says hello first.)
Hello. I'm Tzuyu of TWICE.
Tzuyu.
(He loves it.)
She's Tzuyu. Tzuyu is...
I remember something about Tzuyu. Thanks to her...
(Suddenly)
Stay quiet.
This is an interesting story!
This is really funny, but I'm not going to tell you.
That's enough.
- This is hilarious. - This situation is funny.
(Disappointed)
- I'll hear it in the waiting room. - We want to hear TWICE's voice.
- I don't want to hear your voice. - He's right!
Do you not want my funny story? Okay.
(Don't you regret it.)
I guess it's a funny story.
Tell us about it.
(I'll give you a chance.)
It can't be fun this way!
Don't say it then.
If it's a funny story, it will still sound funny this way.
(He can't do it even if he gets a chance.)
We need to hear TWICE's voice. I don't want you to cut in.
(Keep it to yourself.)
- I'm sorry. - It was my mistake.
(Don't interrupt while talking to TWICE.)
Stay focused.
- Okay. - Please say hello.
(They continue to introduce themselves.)
Hello. I'm Sana of TWICE.
- All right. - Sana.
Sana for today and tomorrow.
Don't make silly jokes like "shy shy shy".
(Talking gibberish)
- It's old-fashioned. - What's "shy shy shy"?
- Do you not know it? - I don't know.
He means "shy shy shy".
- "Shy shy shy". - He sounded like "Sa sa sa".
(They're suddenly talking about "Shy shy shy".)
The word is "shy".
I'm sorry, but we seem a little nervous now.
(TWICE is here.)
Don't be nervous.
(He's nervous, so he's talking like an amateur.)
It's okay. We all are friends.
Relax. It's okay.
- We are celebrities too. - Don't feel nervous.
(We're celebrities too.)
- Just relax. - It's all right.
Don't be nervous. Relax.
- We are celebrities too. - 1, 2, and 3.
- Let's do this. - We need to show them.
(They're discouraged by TWICE. They cheer desperately.)
- Relax. - It's all right.
- Hey, act natural. - We are celebrities.
(He's feeling most nervous.)
- Act natural. - Okay.
(Please relax.)
- Hey, relax. - About Sana.
Whatever Sana sings becomes the highlight.
(They relax and continue talking.)
It's like "shy shy shy".
(Sana makes every part appealing.)
It's actually nothing special.
It could've been something normal.
(Especially her "Shy shy shy" made a lot of men flutter.)
But it sounds special when Sana sings it.
It wouldn't have been special if she just said shy shy shy.
How did you do it? Can you show us?
(Elder's request)
I don't remember.
- This is it. - My gosh.
This is what we call a highlight.
(So Min tries "Shy shy shy".)
I think So Min can do this.
- Try it. - "I was seeing my friends".
Oh, dear.
(Groaning)
- That's not it. - Shy shy shy
(Turning away)
- Ji Hyo, give it a try. - Ji Hyo.
(They ask Ji Hyo too.)
- Shy shy shy? - Yes.
(Excited)
(He can't control the look on his face.)
(She tries to hide out of embarrassment.)
- She's got her own vibes. - Right.
(Kwang Soo moves.)
It shows how experienced she is.
(We're family. Please don't do that.)
- She seems experienced. - Hey.
I'm just afraid her makeup would get on my jacket.
(What a lame excuse.)
My goodness.
(She never gives up.)
I can do it in a sexy way.
(They don't know how to react.)
Okay. So Min is trying hard.
- There you go, So Min. - Well done.
(Everyone's more enthusiastic than usual.)
It's not good, but I appreciate it.
I think you all are in good condition today.
But don't do anything that I didn't ask for.
(It's a warning.)
- At least during the opening. Okay? - You need to control yourself.
(I will calm down.)
So Sana just showed us her part for "shy shy shy".
(Sana demonstrates how to do "Shy shy shy".)
Then why don't you sing one of Turbo's songs?
(This time)
What? Jae Suk.
(Why Turbo all of a sudden?)
- "Goodbye Yesterday" by Turbo. - All of a sudden?
- "Goodbye Yesterday". - Let them sing it.
(She'll do "Black Cat" which is easy to try.)
- Let them sing "Black Cat" instead. - Maybe I loved you
That would be better.
(Elder's request)
- Show us the original dance moves. - Black cat Nero
- It goes like this, right? - Start.
(What?)
Who dances like that?
(Flustered)
Who are you talking about?
(Suk Jin interprets it on his own.)
- What was that? - This isn't just right.
- What is it then? - Black cat Nero
(The point is catchy moves that anyone can easily follow.)
- This is it. - All right.
This cute friend of mine
It is a black cat
This is it.
(They can't wait to see...)
Please try it with your own feelings for us.
(Sana's version of "Black Cat".)
She'll be cute.
(Anticipating)
Start.
(Cute)
- She's so cute. - She's lovely.
My friend is a cat.
(Sana makes everyone a cat lover.)
- "My friend is a cat." - "My friend is a cat."
My mom is a cat too.
Next up is Chaeyoung. Let me ask her a question.
(Lastly, it's Chaeyoung the youngest of TWICE.)
Fans say she can do an impression of Lim Kim.
(Fans say she can do an impression of Lim Kim.)
(They ask her to show them.)
- Please show us. - That sounds nice.
Please do an impression of Lim Kim.
(Anticipating)
This is quite old though.
(Shy)
(What?)
- It's really old. - It is.
("All Right" by Lim Kim was released in 2013.)
It's really old.
- It is. - It was about 10 years ago.
(That's almost 10 years old.)
- It was from "Superstar K". - I thought of something else.
Isn't it about 10 years old?
She prepared something new.
- She does? - Yes.
(What a relief.)
We just got a report. What is it?
It's from "A World of Married Couple".
(Hesitating)
- That's a good one. - Nice.
(They're getting their hopes up.)
- It's new. - It's popular.
I can imitate the facial expressions.
- Who can you imitate? - Yeo Da Kyung.
- Yeo Da Kyung? - It's Yeo Da Kyung. Nice.
- This is when she's upset. - Okay.
(She's getting ready to make the angry face.)
Her hair is like this.
- Exactly. - Right. She looks like that.
- Exactly. - That's it.
(They look alike.)
She has the look.
Half of her face looks the same.
(99 percent alike)
(They can all relate to the impression.)
- I know what it is. - She looks exactly like her.
- I know what it is. - You know what it is, right?
And this is how Lee Tae Oh looks when he's in trouble.
(Adding)
(He does look like Lee Tae Oh for some reason.)
Try it together.
(Everyone thinks it's so funny.)
- Wait. Suk Jin. - What?
You didn't watch the show. Do you know what this is?
- To be honest, I don't. - Then why did you laugh?
Should I cry then?
(It's weirdly persuasive.)
- Why did you laugh? - I mean...
- Should I... - Why...
It's just that I didn't laugh that hard.
- You should be honest on TV. - I should be honest?
(But still...)
(Then what should I do?)
- Should I cry? Should I frown? - Why did you laugh?
You don't even know what this is.
I just laughed because everyone else did.
(The reason he's always smiling is revealed.)
- He should laugh with us. - Of course.
(Jae Suk introduces the next member.)
All right. Next up is...
Sana.
- Sana already talked. - Sana already talked.
(What?)
- You can do this! - Next up is Sana.
(He just talked to Sana.)
- Sana already talked. - You can do this!
- What's with you? - You can do this!
(Is he still nervous?)
- Let's give him a hug. - You can do this!
(He's still nervous.)
- Give him a hug. - You're too nervous.
- You don't have to be nervous. - It's okay.
(Embarrassed, he gulps down the water.)
It's okay.
- It's okay. - We can do this!
- We can do this! - We can do this!
(We can do this too!)
(TWICE is full of energy.)
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
- Should we throw in the towel? - Today...
It's okay.
We're at war with TWICE today.
We can do this.
All right. Next up is Nayeon.
(It's followed by Nayeon's interview.)
Fans say that some idol singers look like juicy fruits.
(Asking Nayeon who looks like a peach)
Can you compare the Running Man members to fruits?
(How would you describe the Running Man cast as fruits?)
Me?
(Flustered)
We've been compared to animals and many other things,
but never fruits.
(They feel sorry for their looks.)
- That's right. - That'd be fun.
Can't I compare you guys to vegetables?
- Vegetables are okay too. - Vegetables count too.
(Including vegetables)
- Just tell us what you think. - Okay.
(Is he looking forward to it?)
- It's just the appearance. - Vegetables or fruits.
- This is going to be interesting. - I can't wait.
What does Jae Suk look like?
(She'll describe Jae Suk first.)
- What do I look like? - Jae Suk.
- Bean sprouts. - Bean sprouts?
You do look like them.
- You slightly look like them. - You look like them.
- You look like bean sprouts. - You do look like them.
(He does look like bean sprouts.)
- Okay. - You look like them.
(It suits him well.)
- I had bean sprouts this morning. - Dried-up bean sprouts.
- Bean sprouts. - All right.
(Then it's Haha's turn.)
What about Haha?
What's that called?
Pickled radishes you eat with fried chicken.
- Pickled radishes? - Pickled radishes?
It smells bad.
(He looks like it.)
- I love that. - They're very nice and refreshing.
(Appropriate)
They're nice. They go very well with fried chicken.
(Thinking positively)
They're a perfect match.
- Pickled radishes? - I love that.
- I've never heard that before. - Even the juice is tasty.
- That's hilarious. - Right.
(Nayeon is a living naming center.)
What about Se Chan?
- No one has compared me to fruit. - It's not going to be a good one.
(Is he looking forward to it?)
(She can't think of one that easily.)
A durian?
A guava?
(He recommends tropical fruit.)
- It's different this time. - No.
- A blueberry. - A blueberry?
- Se Chan looks like a blueberry? - Why?
(Blueberries?)
Aren't you being too mean? Why would you call him a blueberry?
(Why would Se Chan look...)
- Why do I look like a blueberry? - Why does he look like a blueberry?
(like fresh blueberries?)
Well...
(Hesitating)
She doesn't like blueberries.
(No one questions it anymore.)
(Nayeon, TWICE, doesn't like blueberries.)
What were you expecting?
For a second...
It was because she doesn't like me.
(He had some hopes,)
Now I understand.
(but now he doesn't.)
- Now I understand. - That feels a lot better.
I didn't understand at first.
(They all admit after listening to the reason.)
- Okay. - Now I understand.
- Please step back. - There was a reason.
I think I know what Kwang Soo looks like.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn.)
- Really? - What does Kwang Soo look like?
A yam.
- I was thinking of that. - A yam?
(Did you say, "Yam"?)
Seriously...
- I was thinking of that. - He looks like it.
(She sees it.)
- Unbelievable. - He looks like a yam.
(Nayeon, psychic, specializes in naming)
That's hilarious.
That's so funny.
(His feelings are hurt.)
- Unbelievable. - He looks like a yam.
- That makes sense. - Goodness.
A yam was perfect.
(From bean sprouts to yams,)
- Everything she said makes sense. - Totally.
(they all look like the members.)
Everything was perfect.
By the way, I'm so happy...
(With all members of TWICE,)
- to have all members here. - It's great.
Today, the mission fund and the captains are very important.
(today's race finally begins.)
It's the Running Man Captain Race.
(Running Man Captain Race)
According to the results of each round, each team will receive...
(According to the results of each round, each team will receive...)
an amount between 500 dollars and minus 200 dollars.
(an amount between 500 dollars and minus 200 dollars.)
The money will be distributed among the members by the captain.
(The money will be distributed at the captain's discretion.)
The captains can give all the money to one member if they want,
(The captains can give all the money to one member if they want.)
which makes the captains absolutely powerful.
And everyone can see how the money is distributed.
(And everyone can see how the money is distributed.)
After the money is distributed, you can stand up to your captain...
(After the money is distributed, one can stand up to the captain...)
by trying to take the captain position away.
(by using the money one has to become the next captain.)
You can try to become the next captain...
using your money in the next round.
Whoever bets the biggest amount becomes the next captain.
(Whoever bets the biggest amount becomes the next captain.)
After the race, the top five people...
(The top 5 people with the most money will receive prizes.)
with the most money will receive prizes.
(The bottom 3 will be penalized.)
The bottom three will be penalized.
- The top 5? - The top 5?
Teams will be decided randomly.
(Team Selection Result)
- Sana! - Sana!
- Okay! Chaeyoung and Momo! - Yes!
(Let's go, team!)
- And Mina. - Mina.
- Yes! - All right!
Each team will go to a different place...
to decide the captain.
- Please change first. - Okay.
(They'll change and move to each place to decide the captains.)
The captains have more power.
(They go to choose the captain.)
Who should be the captain?
While you were away, I tried to win their support.
(Se Chan wants to be the captain.)
I told them, "If you choose me, I'll..."
(So you want to be the captain.)
"You can wait and see."
- Today... - It's TWICE's day.
(Meanwhile, Team Gray...)
- They should decide. - Right.
(decides to follow the TWICE members' decision.)
We have a shared bank account,
(The members of TWICE)
- and Jihyo manages it. - Really?
- That's perfect. - Then it's decided.
(Jihyo is in charge of accounting in TWICE.)
Are you the general affairs manager?
And no money has ever disappeared?
(Double-checking)
It's happened, but I always put the money back.
(Honest)
- It's happened? - It's happened?
(Shocked)
For example, when I buy a birthday cake for a member,
- I use our money first. - You use the team's money.
(She uses it for public use only.)
- But you put it back? - Yes.
- That's understandable. - Right.
(It seems that Team Gray will choose Jihyo as their captain.)
- We could take turns. - Really?
(Meanwhile, Team Orange is...)
- Every round? - All right.
(Touching)
- If we bet... - Exactly.
So Min is touching this.
- Because it's so pretty. - Be careful.
I'm touching it because it's pretty.
So Min has...
Sticky fingers?
(Kwang Soo is slapped.)
(So Min slaps Kwang Soo so that he can't say anything.)
If it disappears, suspect So Min.
(Firm)
You'll find it in her pocket.
- He's so annoying. - I'm serious.
She touched it because she likes it.
(Kwang Soo tries to make them distrust So Min.)
- I just think it's pretty. - I mean it.
Before you know it,
it'll be replaced with some plastic bag. I'm serious.
(She sees his intention.)
- Stop buttering her up. - What?
- You're buttering her up. - I'm buttering her up?
(The suck-up wants to be the captain.)
Yes, you are.
He's buttering her up, right?
(By the way, they need to decide who will be the captain.)
Should we decide the captain here?
I just don't want to end up in the bottom three.
- Guys. - Yes?
(Suddenly...)
We're going to start...
the Cheer Up! Unexpected Name Tag Elimination.
- What are you saying? - Already?
- We'll start Name Tag Elimination. - What?
(Name tag elimination all of a sudden?)
As soon as we start?
(Weren't we supposed to choose the captain?)
- What? - What?
But we're a team, right?
We're going to start the Cheer Up! Unexpected Name Tag Elimination.
(Grabbing)
- What? - What's going on?
(As soon as she hears the announcement,)
(So Min rips off Jeongyeon's name tag.)
What's going on?
- We haven't started yet. - See?
(There will be an announcement.)
Jeongyeon, did you see that?
- We haven't started yet. - Jeongyeon, did you see that?
- So Min! - Did you see that?
(She killed her teammate before it even started.)
- So Min! - That's how she is.
(She feels betrayed.)
- How could you... - I was trying to protect you.
(Appealing)
Did you see how I was trying to protect you?
- So Min. - Jeongyeon, you got the wrong idea.
(It doesn't count as it was before the race began.)
- Jeongyeon. - Can you eliminate...
a team member?
- So Min should be out! - Gosh, this is crazy.
All right.
(They calm down and listen to the rules.)
Let's hear the rules now.
All teams will play Name Tag Elimination at the same time.
(All teams will play Name Tag Elimination at the same time.)
A team is out of the game when all members are eliminated.
(A team is out of the game when all members are eliminated.)
Money will be distributed according to how long each team lasts.
(Money will be distributed according to how long each team lasts.)
(Reliable)
We have Jong Kook.
Whoever survives longest in each team becomes the captain...
(Whoever survives the longest in each team becomes the captain...)
(regardless of the team's result.)
regardless of the team's result.
Whoever survives longest in each team becomes the captain.
(To become the captain with the right to distribute money,)
regardless of the team's result.
(survive longer than your team members.)
If you think your team is going to lose,
(If his or her team seems to be losing,)
you could try to become the captain instead...
(one can decide to eliminate the teammates to be the captain.)
by eliminating your team members.
(My goodness.)
- Can we eliminate our team members? - Yes.
- That's too mean. - Hold on.
- That's too... - We couldn't do that.
(That's a bit harsh.)
No way.
- We couldn't do that, could we? - Never.
(Distrust)
(His eyes shake.)
- Are you sure? - Yes.
- We shouldn't eliminate each other. - Not yet.
(Calm down.)
You should try to survive for a long time...
(He explains the rules once again.)
to become the captain...
and save the team.
(Thinking)
Haha, Chaeyoung keeps calculating.
- Really? - Chaeyoung.
If you keep calculating, I'll rip off your name tag first.
(She got caught.)
- You shouldn't do that. Not yet. - Stop thinking.
There are envelopes hidden all over the place.
(There are envelopes hidden all over the place.)
The envelopes have money in them,
(There's money in each envelope, and the finder will have it.)
which belongs to the person who finds it.
- The person who finds it? - Yes.
Try to find as much money as you can before you get eliminated.
(It's better to find as much money as possible before elimination.)
At the same time, try to become the captain.
Do you understand what he said?
- Rip off others' name tags. - Okay.
You can rip off the name tags of your team members too.
(Se Chan adds.)
Okay.
No, don't do that.
(She understood.)
You can eliminate your team members too.
(They wait for the other teams to get ready.)
- Let's say two of us are left. - Let me see.
Can we start now?
- Not yet. - You saw something?
(She acts like it's nothing.)
- Is someone out there? - No one.
(What is it?)
- Did you find money? - No.
Okay, there it is.
(He finds the envelope too.)
Whoever picks that up, I'll eliminate that person.
(That didn't last long.)
How about we play rock-paper-scissors?
- Okay. - That's a good idea.
(The winner of rock-paper-scissors will get the envelope.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Yes! - Okay.
(By the game of rock-paper-scissors,)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - No!
(Se Chan wins and gets the money.)
I'll have 10 more dollars from the beginning.
- I can try to pick it up, right? - Of course.
Hey, wait. You can't do that.
(Then why did we play rock-paper-scissors?)
Why did we even play rock-paper-scissors?
(Dahyun almost smells like a bully.)
- Dahyun has a point. - Right?
Let's start the race.
5, 4...
(Flinching)
- Hold on. - Why...
- Here we go. - 5, 4,
(5 seconds before the race)
3, 2, 1.
The race starts.
Stay away from the money.
(As soon as it began,)
- Gosh. - I can't believe her.
(Dahyun gets the envelope.)
- Yes! - Seriously.
- How much is it? - How much is it?
(In the envelope,)
(there's 10 dollars.)
- It's 10 dollars. - That's not bad.
Put it in your bag.
(Dahyun gets 10 dollars.)
I shouldn't lose it, right?
- Put it in your bag. - Put it in your pocket.
- We should try to find money. - Right.
(Team Gray looks for the envelopes together.)
It might be hidden around here.
(Where is the money?)
(A surprise attack)
(Startled)
- Be careful of these attacks. - This is...
(Playing)
I just wanted to try.
I wanted to tell you to be careful.
(I thought he was ripping off my name tag.)
- I don't want to be eliminated. - My heart is racing.
(Team Orange was falling apart before the race began.)
My heart is suddenly beating so fast.
There it is.
(Jeongyeon has good eyesight.)
(She found an envelope on the 1st floor.)
I want to go downstairs.
Don't go off on your own.
(He pretends as if he's worried.)
- What? - You shouldn't be alone.
You're scary.
(He's too fast that it doesn't seem like he's protecting her.)
- I... - Don't come any closer.
(They run at full speed toward the money Jeongyeon spotted.)
(Kwang Soo acquires the mission envelope.)
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, how could you?
Sorry, it's empty.
(I'm sorry, it's empty.)
(It's the ending of a greedy person.)
What is this?
There's nothing in there, right?
(Se Chan arrives right then!)
It's empty.
- Jeongyeon... - Tzuyu, this way.
(Team White all head to Kwang Soo and Jeongyeon.)
Shouldn't we look for the money first?
(They try to stall making excuses that they need to find money.)
Exactly. We should gather the money first.
It's Tzuyu.
(Nayeon and So Min saw this!)
I see Jae Suk.
It's Jae Suk.
There are too many people. I counted at least three.
(After seeing Team White...)
(they decide to run away.)
We should hide.
- It's blocked. - What?
(But they hit a wall.)
You've got to be kidding me. This is bad.
Guys, over here.
(Team White blocks them.)
- Don't be like this. - Why?
- You... - I want to participate in the race.
(Nayeon tries to act cute.)
- The three of you... - You can't be all cute.
It's unfair to have 3 people gang up on 2.
(So Min and Nayeon are cornered.)
You guys go ahead. I'll watch.
(She detects danger.)
I think I hear our teammates.
- I promise. - Come on.
(Se Chan grabs her, Dahyun and Tzuyu try to rip the name tag.)
You can't...
Be careful!
(Ripping off)
- You can't... - Be careful!
(So Min's surprise attack)
What's going on?
What?
(Jae Suk joins them.)
Hurry!
Dahyun, you're out.
(Team White, Dahyun is out.)
Rip So Min's name tag off.
(Jae Suk rips off So Min's name tag.)
- So Min, you're out. - I still...
(Team Orange, So Min is out.)
- eliminated someone. - There's no other way.
- Get her name tag. Gosh, Nayeon. - She got it.
(Tzuyu removes Nayeon's name tag.)
Nayeon, you're out.
- She got it. - Good.
(Team Orange, Nayeon is out.)
Nayeon, you're out.
- Are you all right? - Are you okay?
(Abruptly)
My hair was ripped out!
- What? - What?
- What the... - What is that?
(Her name tag was ripped off and so was her hair.)
Why did you rip out her hair?
(A hook-and-loop fastener was attached to her hair extensions.)
It was So Min.
- My hair was ripped out. - Sorry.
Jeongyeon, don't go there.
(While they are running...)
- Jeongyeon... - We should help our team.
Forget about them.
What do you mean?
- But... - Forget about them.
(Jeongyeon wants to help, Kwang Soo wants to ditch them.)
- Don't bother. - We must help them!
Just forget about them!
Why did you rip out her hair?
It was So Min.
(He sees Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo's coming. - Sorry.
(Kwang Soo bulldozes forward to assess the situation.)
It's 3 against 2. Let's get them!
(We have the advantage.)
(He makes a run for it.)
(What's going on?)
Let's get them!
(He runs for it leaving Jeongyeon behind.)
(If Jeongyeon is eliminated, Kwang Soo will be the captain.)
- There's Jeongyeon. - Let's get her. Come here!
(Team White is on the left, Team Purple is on the right.)
I also see Haha.
(She is stuck.)
Nice.
(If I stay there...)
It's a death trap.
All that matters is that I stay alive.
(I'm about to be the captain.)
- Haha... - Watch your backs.
(Jeongyeon is caught between Team Purple and Team White.)
You guys can eliminate Jeongyeon.
- No, please don't. - We don't have a choice.
- Please help me. - We'll help.
- No, no. - Let us help.
(Jeongyeon is surrounded.)
Jeongyeon, be careful.
Come any closer and I'll go after you.
Where on earth did Kwang Soo go?
Hasn't Jeongyeon been eliminated yet?
(He checks again.)
Why hasn't she been when she's surrounded?
(Haha makes a proposal.)
Let's call a truce.
- We'll go after Kwang Soo first. - Sure.
(A change in target)
Let's make Jeongyeon team captain and go after Kwang Soo first.
(They are united.)
Jeongyeon, what do you say?
- I'd love that. - Okay.
(I like that.)
Okay, gather around then.
(Other teams don't want Kwang Soo as the captain.)
Jeongyeon, isn't it in your best interest...
to be team captain too?
- Exactly. - You can rip off his name tag.
(They support Jeongyeon as the captain.)
Do you get what I mean?
- Eliminate him yourself. - Go ahead.
You should get going, Jeongyeon.
(She earns freedom thanks to Kwang Soo.)
- All right. - Let's trust one another.
- Of course. - You go first.
No, you go first.
There's no need to worry.
(Team Gray is very confident with Jong Kook's support.)
Just look at the members on this team.
The others will choose to run away.
Over here. Jihyo, here you go.
(They even share the money they find.)
(Suk Jin wrecks the mood.)
I'll give it back.
I only played a joke to keep you alerted.
(It's an envelope!)
(Suk Jin constantly trains them to be on high alert.)
Jihyo!
(Thanks to Suk Jin, they collect a lot of money.)
You guys are good at spotting these.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo searches for the money.)
Where is he?
Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo!
Why weren't you eliminated?
(That's impossible.)
I can't believe you just left me there.
(Jeongyeon is angry.)
- I didn't run away. - You traitor.
- I didn't... - You wanted to be the captain.
(She read his intentions.)
I was trying to draw them away from you.
(Kwang Soo is acting.)
As if.
(Kwang Soo deserves his award at Baeksang Arts Awards.)
You ran away and left me there.
Jeongyeon, let's go.
(Just then...)
Jeongyeon, run!
(He discovers Team White walking from the opposite side.)
- Run! - See?
He's leaving me behind again.
(Kwang Soo runs off once again.)
Jeongyeon, hurry.
(They barely managed to escape.)
Why don't we go up?
- Is that possible? - Sure.
(Grabbing)
(That was close.)
(She's suddenly embarrassed.)
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
(So this is how it feels to be betrayed.)
Can we make up?
(She apologizes.)
Do you consider us a team?
(He gets angry.)
Let's make up.
(Naive Jeongyeon keeps apologizing to make up.)
We have to be a team for the entire day.
- Right. - Must you be this way?
- I won't. - What will become of us?
(He plays the victim.)
Let's get going then.
I won't betray you again. I promise.
(Kwang Soo pretends to give in and stands up.)
We'll walk side by side.
(Wriggling)
(He can't help but be the traitor he is.)
Okay, fine. Let's go upstairs for now.
(Running)
(Kwang Soo spots an envelope.)
(He then suddenly runs off somewhere.)
(Meanwhile, Jeongyeon runs the other way.)
(She runs into Team Gray.)
(Kwang Soo makes a run for it using Jeongyeon as bait.)
- No... - Guys, get her.
(It's too late to escape.)
- Please don't. - Finish her.
(Jeongyeon tries to fight the inevitable.)
Eliminate her.
(She can't fight them alone.)
Be careful though.
Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo ran away again.
It's every man for himself.
- Sorry about this. - Kwang Soo...
- We're sorry. - You should've been alone.
(Poor Jeongyeon's name tag was ripped off.)
- My gosh. - Goodness.
(Jeongyeon of Team Orange is eliminated.)
Gosh.
(I can't believe he betrayed again.)
- Kwang Soo... - He ran away.
We should teach him a lesson then. Let's go.
That traitor.
(Kwang Soo has been decided as Team Orange's captain.)
(Jeongyeon...)
Was she eliminated?
(He checks again.)
Was Jeongyeon eliminated?
Okay!
You're the last to survive on your team...
which makes you the captain.
(He gathers his hands.)
(Glancing)
(Don't misunderstand.)
This is my mourning for Jeongyeon. I feel terrible.
Nice. Let's do this!
(Team White and Team Purple are confronting each other.)
It's 5 against 3.
- We'll eliminate all of you. - Go ahead!
(Team White is outnumbered.)
- We're dead serious. - I am too.
(Team Purple is confident.)
- No. - Bring it on.
(Haha is charismatic.)
You're so cool, Haha.
Hold your ground, guys.
Wait, who's that?
(Who's coming?)
Someone's here.
- Jeongyeon, did you get him? - It's over.
(Jeongyeon was on her way to the jail.)
Did you eliminate him?
- She got eliminated. - She was eliminated instead.
(Everyone sighs to see her name tag removed.)
- Oh, dear. - Who was it?
Team Gray.
(At that moment...)
What the...
Team Gray.
(Ripping off)
What the...
I did well, right?
Haha, you're out.
(Se Chan's blitz attack was successful.)
- You four can get going. - Go ahead.
Get going.
(That was one of the most futile elimination.)
Did you have to do it this way?
Instead...
(She is happy to find her accompany to the jail.)
- We can go together. - Let go of me!
Let's start over.
I'll let you eliminate me,
(He asks for a retake.)
so make it look like it was 1 on 1.
- This just isn't right. - Let's go to the prison.
(He is in denial.)
- Must I be eliminated this way? - Bye.
(Good-bye, Haha. I won't walk you out too far.)
- Haha... - Jeongyeon, wait.
You acted all tough but was caught off guard.
(Dumbfounded)
Must I be eliminated this way?
(Haha of Team Purple is out.)
(New members join the jail.)
Unbelievable, this is upsetting.
Haha...
It was 5 against 3.
(He keeps mumbling as he enters the jail.)
- It was 4 against 2 for us. - Yes, 4 against 2.
(Everyone has a story.)
2 guys and 2 girls.
(Sighing deeply)
What's wrong?
Nothing is going my way.
(Depressed)
- Same here. - Absolutely nothing.
Exactly. Nothing's going my way either.
I mean it.
No one calls me anymore.
(Depressed)
(You can give us your number.)
- Give me your number. - Me too.
- Really? Can you text me sometime? - Sure.
(They decide to be her friend after hearing her sad confession.)
I like texting others.
I would've given out my number if they had been male guests.
(To be honest...)
(Since they're girls, she'll only accept their gracious offer.)
Can't you see that I'm not pulling out my phone?
Not one guest on this show has asked me for my number...
for three whole years. Can you believe it?
- Isn't it insane, Jeongyeon? - Does that normally happen though?
(Do you often ask for it?)
- Exactly. - I've never heard of it.
Still...
(When a guy and a girl meet...)
Was there someone you were particularly fond of?
(She definitely liked someone.)
There was.
I think I know who it was.
- Didn't you like Jinyoung? - Yes, Jinyoung.
(I saw...)
(Out of 100 men she likes, Jinyoung is one of them.)
- Isn't he super handsome? - He is.
It was the first time I felt my heart do a flip.
(Mumbling)
He was incredibly handsome.
Why didn't you ask for his number instead?
- Exactly. - You could've asked him first.
(She is embarrassed just thinking about it.)
What?
She was rejected.
(That's enough.)
(That's a sad story.)
He openly rejected her.
When did that happen?
That never happened.
(No way.)
Why would he reject someone as sweet as you?
Which celebrity had your heart beating the fastest?
(Which celebrity had your heart beating the fastest?)
- How can I answer that? - It's more fun in here.
(He's intrigued.)
It's a talk show...
(A Love Story in Jail)
which is what I love.
How can I name all of them? There were so many.
Which celebrity is close to your dream guy?
(Jeon So Min, people's representative, What about TWICE?)
There must be an actor or singer...
(They remain silent when the question is towards them.)
whom you thought was cool or handsome.
For me, it was Yang Se Hyeong.
- What? - That's right. She said it before.
(Jeongyeon always named Se Hyeong as her ideal type.)
And yet you asked me that question?
- Se Hyeong? - Yes.
- Do you like Se Chan too? - Yes.
(If that's the case...)
But in person, he's quite ugly.
(They're dazzled by her brutal opinion.)
(She strikes with hard facts.)
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo...)
Since the team captain will be put to a vote afterward,
this will be my last time as one.
(He realizes his fate.)
I'll collect what I can while I have the chance...
and leave for good.
(At that moment...)
I'm sure he's here somewhere.
- Over there. - Where?
Here's Kwang Soo.
(They found the traitor.)
He's here.
(The others finally caught up with Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo!
(He runs at high speed for over 5 minutes.)
(Kwang Soo's cameraman has given up on filming him.)
Where is he going without his cameraman?
(Kwang Soo)
Yes.
Give up.
(Kwang Soo stops at a dead end.)
You're in first place anyway. Jae Suk.
(Persuading)
(When Se Chan is about to eliminate him,)
Kwang Soo.
(he takes out 10 dollars from his pocket.)
I'll let you go.
(Polite)
(If you give it to me...)
I'll rip Jae Suk's name tag.
(The deal is made.)
Okay, let's rip his.
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo gave me 10 dollars.
(For 10 dollars? How could you...)
Hey, you're doing this over 10 dollars?
(Petty offenders are easily swayed by small amounts of money.)
Kwang Soo, if you give Jae Suk 10 dollars too, we'll let you go.
(You want more?)
- What? - Give him 10 dollars.
Or he might rip yours.
(Flustered)
That's not what you said.
- Give him 10 dollars. - If I give away 20 dollars...
(Pay me too.)
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo hesitated,)
(but he pays 10 more dollars.)
Grab him.
We'll hold him,
- and Tzuyu can eliminate him. - She can.
We'll hold him, and Tzuyu can eliminate him.
- She can. - We won't rip yours.
- Oh, gosh. - Tzuyu, you can rip his name tag.
(Tzuyu enters cheerfully.)
- Hold on! - Do it.
- I'll give you money. - Rip his name tag.
- Tzuyu, rip it. - Do it.
(Tzuyu. I'll pay you 10 dollars.)
- Rip it now. - I'll give you 10 dollars.
(Unlike the petty offenders, Tzuyu's not swayed by money.)
10 dollars.
I'll give you 10 dollars, Tzuyu!
Good.
(Captain Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
- We kept our promise. - Okay.
- I'll give you 10 dollars, Tzuyu! - Good.
(He justifies himself.)
We kept our promise. We didn't rip his name tag.
- Good. - I'm sorry.
(Cheerful)
We didn't rip yours.
- Good. - Good job, Tzuyu.
(This is the end of the unjust deal.)
Go inside, you brat.
You thought you could convince us with money?
- I didn't get swayed by 10 dollars. - Let's go.
(Goodness. They were begging for money.)
Kwang Soo is out, and his entire team is out.
(Team Orange is guaranteed to get minus 200 dollars.)
- Okay. - What a messy game.
(Kwang Soo is thrown out after spending money.)
- Right? - We didn't die.
This is great.
(He enters the prison plaintively.)
Welcome.
(Out of the blue)
Our team was cool.
We all got eliminated, but you guys were the best.
(You were the best team members.)
- We argued so much. - Seriously.
(They forgot about their captain a long time ago.)
They're not disappointed in you anymore.
(He shows off.)
Anyhow, I'm the captain.
(While Kwang Soo shows off about being a captain...)
- Look at her. - Thanks.
(Captain Kwang Soo.)
I could give away money...
(Wiping Captain Kwang Soo's sweat)
or keep all the money for myself. We have a minus balance.
(Captain Kwang Soo is the best.)
Okay.
Why did you give it away?
Let me say this. I have minus 200 dollars.
I'm going to give it to one person.
Let's give up.
(Softly)
That's more terrifying. "Let's give up."
(Laughing)
She's so cool about it.
- You can't do it. - They did a survey on their own.
You got voted as the worst man on Running Man.
(Kwang Soo got voted as the worst man on Running Man.)
They think you look old.
(The secret of being number 1)
I do?
(Shocked)
I look old?
Were you just gossiping?
(Gossip talk show pretending to be a TV show)
This is so funny.
(While they're busy talking in the prison...)
I don't see anybody.
We've been looking, and we can't find anybody either.
They must be in the other building.
(Team Gray meets Team White.)
Have a seat.
We keep missing each other. We haven't met anyone.
(It's time to finish the game.)
Who's hoping to be the captain on your team? Who wants to be it?
(Who's the captain candidate in Team Gray?)
We're rooting for Jihyo.
(They're supporting Jihyo.)
- You planned it out. - Jihyo?
Yes, because she usually takes the secretary role on TWICE.
(Sometimes the balance isn't correct.)
- I see. - She's fair.
(No, that's not true.)
(I'll be the captain.)
Don't exchange glances.
(Complaining)
(Suk Jin desires to be the captain secretly.)
- What are you talking about? - They're here.
- It's Momo. - There they are.
(Then Team Haha appears.)
Ji Hyo, this is a ceasefire.
(All three teams are watching each other.)
Ceasefire. Where's Se Chan?
- I'm over here. - Oh, right.
(Ripping)
Hey.
(Suk Jin ripped Chaeyoung's name tag.)
(Suk Jin's attacking Chaeyoung while she let her guard down.)
- Good job. - Right?
That was the most swift you've been in 10 years.
(He hasn't been this sharp in the last 10 years.)
I played dumb. I stayed still.
(Team Gray gains momentum. Their next target is Team Purple.)
I got her.
- I did it. Okay. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo is out in an instant.)
(Ji Hyo is eliminated after Haha.)
My gosh. What now?
Let's clean this up.
(Only Mina and Momo remain in Team Purple.)
We don't have an option.
- Right? - We have to attack.
We don't have a choice. We have to finish round one.
(Se Chan fails to ambush.)
(Help me, Jae Suk!)
- My gosh. - Come over here!
(Se Chan gets out of danger.)
- Hurry, Jihyo. - Oh, dear.
(What?)
(Jae Suk kills his own team member.)
Hey! Jae Suk!
(I can be the captain.)
Come here. I'll grab him, and you can rip his.
(Even though he killed his own team member,)
- Do it. - Hey.
- Come here. - Rip it.
(he got arrested in 10 seconds.)
- Rip it. - We did it.
(Jae Suk is out!)
(Tzuyu is the captain of Team White.)
- We did it. - Hey. Tzuyu.
(The current survivors)
- Mina first. - He's out.
(Team Purple, Team Gray, Team White)
Let's take care of her first.
(The next target is Team Purple.)
Come here. Mina first. Come inside.
Come here. Let's take care of her first.
(What?)
(Suk Jin eliminated Jong Kook?)
Hey.
My bad. I want to be the captain.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
(He got me.)
(Culture shock)
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook. - Jihyo.
We'll be in first place.
(Embarrassed)
- Girls. - We will be.
(With Jong Kook gone, Suk Jin is the strongest.)
My bad.
(Mina is out.)
- Okay, good job. Rip it. - What's this?
(Sana ripped it!)
- Rip it. - She's so tough.
(Only Momo and Tzuyu remain in the other team.)
(At that moment,)
My bad.
(he attacks Sana.)
I'm sorry. Wait.
My bad. I'm sorry. Wait. I'm sorry.
(Sana is puzzled.)
I think this is a disease.
I'm sorry. I think this is a disease.
I'm sorry. Jihyo, you and I can dominate.
(Suk Jin's plan to become the captain is coming to pass.)
- Let's go, Sana. - You have to keep your promise.
(Team Gray is the only team with 2 left. Their 1st target is Momo.)
Hey.
(Momo is out, and Team Purple is 3rd place.)
- Jihyo! Jihyo! - Okay.
(They attack Tzuyu next, who is their last target.)
(Team White is 2nd place.)
Tzuyu is out.
- Tzuyu is out. - Tzuyu is out.
(The only people left are...)
Tzuyu is out.
(Jihyo and me.)
(It's the rule.)
- I'm sorry. - I shouldn't have trusted you.
(As his team is guaranteed to win,)
I'm sorry.
(he's becoming greedier.)
Let's not make this messy.
I'm sorry.
(Jihyo is out.)
Jihyo is out. Suk Jin is the ultimate winner.
(Team Gray wins. Suk Jin is their captain.)
(The result of the first mission)
Everybody, Cheer Up! Unexpected Name Tag Elimination is over.
Fourth place team is Team Kwang Soo.
(Team Orange's captain: Kwang Soo)
- Team Kwang Soo. - Last place.
Their captain is Kwang Soo.
(Obtained team money: minus 200 dollars)
- Yes! - Sadly.
- He's always like that. - That team...
is in the last place, and they have the worst captain.
He's deceitful.
(Hardship is expected for Team Kwang Soo.)
- What are you talking about? - He won't keep any.
He'll be in trouble.
Third place is Team Haha. Their captain is Momo.
(Team Purple's captain: Momo)
(Obtained team money: minus 100 dollars)
Momo.
I knew you'd be the captain.
(Captain Momo will distribute the team money obtained.)
She will distribute minus 100 dollars.
Second place is Team Jae Suk. Tzuyu is the captain.
(Team White's captain: Tzuyu, obtained team money: 300 dollars)
- Okay. - Captain Tzuyu.
- Good job. - Good job.
- Captain. - First place is Team Suk Jin.
(Team Gray's captain: Suk Jin, obtained team money: 500 dollars)
They have 500 dollars, and Suk Jin is the captain.
Suk Jin is the captain.
- This is going to be fun. - Thank you.
(Coincidentally, Suk Jin eliminated all three.)
- What's this? - I'm looking forward to this.
(Suk Jin's never been this good in the last 10 years.)
Suk Jin is so good these days.
Please be understanding of me.
I think I have a disease. Please be understanding.
(Sorry)
(Suk Jin can't control his petty greed.)
That's all fine. Just distribute the money fairly.
(I'll let it go. Just make sure to distribute the team money well.)
- Of course. - Pay attention.
Of course. I'll distribute it fairly.
(Trust me.)
We'll distribute the money now.
(It's time to distribute the team money.)
(Captain Suk Jin in 1st place team will go first.)
First place team, Captain Suk Jin will go first.
- I'm looking forward to this. - But...
- we picked a good captain. - I agree.
If it were you or me, it would have been bad.
(If Jae Suk or Se Chan were a captain,)
(it would've been tiring.)
It was part of my plan.
(Unlike Captain Tzuyu...)
Will it be one-on-one later?
(Double-check)
Yes.
Can we trust you?
We'll show you a board with the amounts written down.
(Current Dollar Amounts)
How do you have 130 dollars?
We're all around the same.
(Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Sana, Jihyo)
(Jong Kook's suggestion)
Suk Jin, keep 200 and give us 100 each.
Do the right thing.
- Right. - Okay, I'm trying to.
- This is not hard. - I didn't achieve this alone.
This is not a difficult decision to make.
(As Captain Jee raises his voice, they feel more worried.)
I know you don't do that. No way.
We might become the captain later.
Of course. I know.
Momo has a lot of money.
(Captain Momo must distribute minus 100 dollars.)
- This is not hard. - Or...
make everybody 0. Deduct 10 from me,
(Haha's suggestion)
deduct 20 from Mina, and deduct 10 from Chaeyoung.
(Make everyone 0, and deduct the rest from Momo's money.)
There's 70 left then.
If you take that, you still have 30.
- You'll still be the captain. - Is this a secret?
Yes, that sounds good.
(She agrees.)
- Isn't that good? - Yes.
Isn't that really cool?
You'll be all over social media.
(Haha's best excuse is going viral on social media.)
Because she's nice?
My gosh.
(He's embarrassing his team.)
Think about it. Everybody will have 0, and she'll have 30.
(Making Momo Hero Project)
You'll still be the captain. Please applaud.
- That sounds great. - Captains, please come on up.
(All captains start distributing the team money.)
We have no expectations from Kwang Soo.
- We trust Captain Tzuyu. - We trust you.
(After discussing with the team, they're distributing smoothly.)
Momo will be all over social media.
(However, Captain Suk Jin is still hesitating.)
Do you need that much time to think?
- What? - We already talked about this.
- You can't do this. - I need to calculate this.
I want to calculate this...
(As Captain Jee speaks, his team members get nervous.)
so that you don't end up in the last place.
If you don't do this properly,
Jong Kook will drive your car home.
Suk Jin, you live in that apartment, right?
He does. How did you know?
(If Jong Kook doesn't like how it's distributed,)
- My gosh. - Of course I know.
(he'll visit Suk Jin's house.)
I'm going to give him one for that.
I'm going to give you one for that.
(At the news of Jong Kook visiting Suk Jin's house,)
(Suk Jin quickly changes the amount.)
- Stop it. - Hurry up.
(The first distribution is done.)
Round one is over.
Please come up one by one.
(It's time to check their individual amounts.)
(Captain Kwang Soo's Team Orange goes first.)
(Result according to Captain Kwang Soo's distribution)
She glared at him. She glared at Kwang Soo.
She's mad.
- I knew he would take all. - She glared at him.
(Jeongyeon got betrayed.)
- She glared at him. - He probably turned her into zero.
(Avoiding her eyes)
(I lost 150 dollars.)
Was it a lot? I guess you lost a lot.
- This is just the beginning. - Kwang Soo.
(Next is Captain Momo's Team Purple.)
She's criticizing him.
I'm really curious what Tzuyu did.
(Haha has minus 100, and everybody else has 0.)
(He's flustered.)
What's this?
(Only I have minus 100?)
(Goodness, Captain Momo.)
Darn it.
(She avoids his eyes.)
- Laugh and get over it. - This is one-on-one.
(It became awkward at once.)
- We're barely starting. - Laugh.
Laugh.
That was wild.
(Captain Momo)
Right?
Okay.
(Result according to Captain Tzuyu's distribution)
Loyalty.
(Se Chan has 30, and everybody else has 90.)
What? That's all she gave me?
That's all she gave me?
(Tzuyu?)
- That's all you gave me? - You still got some.
You still have some money.
That's still a lot.
- It's a lot. - Okay.
(The rest are satisfied.)
I'm satisfied.
Great job, Tzuyu.
(Captain Tzuyu earns trust.)
- Tzuyu. - I knew it.
I like Captain Tzuyu.
(This is the result according to Captain Suk Jin's distribution.)
Next team.
(Suk Jin has 290, and everybody else has 70.)
He gave us some.
- It's tricky. - But he gave us more...
(Thanks to Jong Kook's visit, Team Gray avoids the worst.)
than I thought.
(Rankings Post Distribution)
(So Min, Jeongyeon, and Haha will be receiving penalties.)
We'll pick captains...
(It's time to pick the captains for Round 2.)
- for round two. - What?
Here are the rules.
Each of you can bet as much money as you want...
(They can bet as much money as they have.)
within the amount you own in secret.
(The person that wrote the highest amount becomes the captain.)
And we will reveal the money you bet all at the same time.
Those with the largest bet will be the second captains.
What if we have a negative balance?
If you have a negative balance or no money to bet,
(For those who have a negative balance,)
we offer the loan service...
(we offer a loan.)
- called Running Man Surety System. - We have a loan system?
(Running Man Surety System)
- By how much? - Regardless of your team,
you can get a loan from the production crew with one surety.
(With 1 surety regardless of the team,)
(they can get a loan of 200 dollars per surety.)
You can get 200 dollars per surety.
When the race is over,
if the debtors pay their debts,
(When the race is over if the debtors pay their debts,)
the sureties also get the interest of 50 dollars.
(the sureties also get the interest of 50 dollars.)
- That's nice. - If the debtors don't pay it back,
the sureties will have to settle the debt.
(The sureties have to settle it if the debtors fail to pay it back.)
- That's not good. - Who would stand surety then?
- I'd never do that. - We can't trust anyone.
No matter what happens,
(Opposing)
you should never stand surety.
I never stand surety no matter what.
(Opposing)
(He'd rather lend the money than stand surety.)
I can lend my own money,
but I can't stand surety.
- You know how much you have, right? - Yes.
(Now they'll make a bet.)
Now you will make a bet. Does anyone of you need a loan?
(Raising his hand)
Name your surety.
Chairman Jee, please help me.
(Haha goes to Chairman Jee ranked number 1 in financial circles.)
What are you doing?
Chairman Jee, please help me.
- Please guarantee my debt. - How much do you need?
(Crawling)
- That's what matters. - Momo now has 100 dollars.
(I need to defeat Momo.)
You get a loan of 200 dollars in all cases.
(The amount of loan is fixed at 200 dollars.)
- It's 200 dollars. - 200 dollars?
Gosh, that's a lot of money.
If the amount is too high,
(They can borrow 100 dollars with the interest of 30 dollars.)
we can make it 100 dollars with the interest of 30 dollars.
Okay. 100 dollars sounds better.
(I can take 100 dollars.)
- I need 200 dollars though. - Why?
I need to beat Momo.
- Just trust me this once. - How much does she have?
(Haha wants to win the bet by borrowing 200 dollars.)
- I've been with you for 10 years. - How much does Momo have?
- She has 100 dollars. - I'm sure...
(He wants to defeat Momo and be the captain.)
he will definitely pay his debt. I know what he's like.
I'll do this right. Just trust me this once.
- Okay! I can do this. - Okay!
All right. I'll stand surety for Haha.
(Coming to an agreement)
- You're like my brother. - You're so generous.
(Chairman Jee stands surety for Haha.)
I'll stand surety for him. It's 200 dollars.
- Thank you so much. - You need 200 dollars.
(If Haha pays it back, Suk Jin gets 50 dollars of interest.)
- Thank you, Suk Jin. - All right.
(He gets the surety name tag.)
Let's do this. Okay.
(Who will be the captain of Team Purple?)
I have to do this right.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
(Nayeon approaches Se Chan.)
- Can I get some money? - What?
I need some money.
I'll send 200 dollars to your account now.
(Can I wire it to you?)
Kwang Soo, you're not supposed to do this.
Why would you send money to my account?
(He tries to use his actual money.)
- Real money? - He says he'll send me real money.
Send me your account number.
Listen, Se Chan. I'm sure I can win.
(I'll pay this back...)
- Hang on. - On the name of TWICE.
(in the name of TWICE.)
- Are you serious? - Yes.
I swear.
- You swear on the name of TWICE? - Yes.
(Why would she bet the name of TWICE for this?)
I'll stand surety for Nayeon.
- You're standing surety for her? - Yes, I'm the guarantor.
(The blueberry is now a surety.)
She possessed me to do this.
(Se Chan stands surety for Nayeon.)
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Se Chan. Can you stand surety for me too?
I have no money.
- Se Chan. - It's over.
(He declines it.)
Se Chan, please.
What did she say?
- Aren't you two friends? - We're friends.
She's even a few months older than me.
Is she crazy?
- Go find someone else. - What are you talking about?
(Se Chan decides not to stand surety for her.)
Go ask Suk Jin.
(While everyone is busy standing surety...)
This is a mess.
(Momo goes to Jong Kook who said he'll never stand surety.)
- You're the captain, Momo. - Can I get a loan?
- You're the captain now. - I have to be the captain again.
(Help me.)
Otherwise, Haha will be the new captain.
(He just can't believe what's happening.)
Hold on, Momo.
Is Momo talking to Jong Kook now?
(Attracting foreign capital)
- My gosh. - Hey.
I thought they were having a private talk.
You're the captain now.
I see. You want to be the captain?
I think he will bet a lot of money.
(She's determined to be the captain.)
I need a loan.
Momo.
- Why would you... - You've got 30 seconds left.
(Pondering)
Do you really have to do this?
This is crazy. Hold on.
It's driving me crazy.
Why are you coming out?
Have you lost your mind?
(You said you'd never stand surety for anyone!)
- Jong Kook. - Hey.
- My gosh. - Are you standing surety for Momo?
(My mom told me...)
I was told not to stand surety no matter what.
You shouldn't do this.
You can't do it.
(Momo is determined to stay as the captain.)
Is this what Momo is up to? All right.
- Chairman Jee. - How much do you have?
I'm asking you for the last time.
Suk Jin, we're in the same team.
It means one of us will be doomed.
- If we keep doing this, she will... - We can't do this.
(Their team will collapse at this rate.)
- Right. - Are you here to stand surety?
- No, I'm still thinking about it. - I can't believe you're doing this.
If you want to do this, you can stand surety for me.
(Sudden)
My gosh.
(My gosh.)
You were talking to Se Chan.
("The World of the Sureties")
- She's got a lot of money. - She does?
- That's not true. - Hang on.
(Momo's desperate eyes...)
My goodness.
- Look at Momo. Look at her eyes. - Momo.
(open Jong Kook's wallet which was tightly shut.)
Momo. All right then.
- I'll do it for her. - Thank you.
(200 dollars)
Of course I should do this for Momo.
(Jong Kook stands surety for Momo.)
My gosh.
- Did you just stand surety for her? - Chairman Jee!
(He can't believe his eyes.)
I should never let my mom watch this.
Wait. Listen.
Kwang Soo will stand surety for me.
- Is it true, Kwang Soo? - What?
(I did?)
What about me?
(So Min tries to steal it.)
So Min just got 200 dollars with Kwang Soo as the surety.
I'm standing surety for So Min?
- What nonsense is this? - Stand surety for each other.
- I'm trying to borrow money here. - No, Kwang Soo.
- I'm looking for a surety now. - Just come here.
- Why would I... - Are you crazy, Kwang Soo?
- It's not like that. - Are you insane?
- Listen to me. - Why would I do that?
Just stand surety for me.
(You'll stand surety, and if I pay it back,)
I won't bet my money to become the captain.
Once I pay the money back, you'll make 50 dollars.
(you're earning 50 dollars without doing anything.)
Or I can get a loan of 100 dollars.
(It sounds plausible.)
Round One is over. Please sit down.
(Kwang Soo stands surety for So Min.)
Wait. He said yes.
I'll leave my phone with you.
I don't need your phone.
(Jae Suk stands surety for So Min. Will she be the captain?)
Just get me 100 dollars.
Okay. I'll do it for you, So Min.
(The amount of money)
Just get 100 dollars. Only 100 dollars.
(Sureties)
I'll try my best.
(Amount of loans)
I'll be good.
Everyone, now you should make a bet.
(It's time to bet.)
Those with the largest bet will be the captain using the money.
(Those with the largest bet will be the captain using the money.)
The rest of you will get your money back.
(The rest of you will get your money back.)
- We get the money back? - Yes.
(If you bet a large amount of money,)
If you bet a large amount of money,
the captain will have to spend more money.
(the captain will have to spend more money.)
That's right. You should think about it.
You won't bet your money anyway.
(One can distribute the money in the next round by becoming the captain.)
I need to become the captain now.
(Team Purple has Momo against Haha.)
Let me be honest with you.
I love my team members.
I'll take good care of you guys.
Just stay out of this.
(Are you watching, Momo?)
I'll make you get your money back by being in second place, at least.
(How will the two turn out?)
- Are you serious? - I'll be the captain.
- Nayeon, you have to be a captain. - Sure.
(Surety)
I'm smart. Don't worry, Se Chan.
(Nayeon, the debtor)
I'll pay your money back.
(I have faith in you.)
Really? Thank you.
Even if I fail, I'll pay your money back anyway.
(The debtor is likely to pay it back if one becomes the captain.)
But Jihyo doesn't agree.
Are you serious? Okay.
- Okay. - Nayeon sings the first part.
(Adding)
And the lyrics go like this. "I'm not going to please you anymore."
- Seriously? - Dahyun, you're amazing.
("I'm not going to please you anymore"?)
Is that the lyrics you sing?
(I'm not going to please you anymore)
Even if I fail, I'll pay your money back anyway.
Is that the lyrics you sing?
(The surety is worried about the lyrics now.)
(The result will be announced.)
- Let me announce the results. - Okay.
First, Team White.
(First, Team White)
Who is it?
(Who's the captain of Team White in the 2nd round?)
The captain for Round Two is...
Yoo Jae Suk who bet 10 dollars.
(It's Jae Suk who bet 10 dollars.)
We helped him become the captain.
(He became the captain with the least amount...)
Did you not stop him?
(thanks to his teammates.)
It's amazing that he became the captain only with 10 dollars.
(Cost-effective)
- It's the best, right? - It is.
- He's so lucky. - This is easy.
All right. The captain of Team Gray is...
(Now it's Team Gray's turn.)
Ji Suk Jin who bet 110 dollars.
(Suk Jin becomes the captain with 110 dollars.)
You said you didn't bet much money.
Jihyo bet 50 dollars, and Sana bet 30 dollars.
Jong Kook didn't bet his money.
How much?
- Did you not bet your money? - No.
- You needed only 50 dollars. - I think...
(Chairman Jee paid a lot to become the captain.)
- he will get a penalty today. - No. The thing is...
they have about 100 dollars.
(Anxious)
Chairman Jee.
I'll pay your money back immediately.
- Okay. - All right. Team Purple.
(The results of Team Purple is announced.)
(Momo and Haha got loans to become the new captain.)
(How did it go?)
Momo who bet 220 dollars is the captain.
(This is why I spend cash.)
But...
Haha didn't bet his money.
(Haha made Momo spend a lot of money to become the next captain.)
- He's so mean. - He's so...
(She lost 220 dollars...)
- He's really nasty. - Haha!
(and her trust in her teammates.)
- Next round. - Help me in the next round.
She spent 220 dollars to become the captain?
(A lot of money)
- This is unbelievable. - It's too expensive.
(The bet cost her a lot of money.)
She spent a lot.
(It also cost the surety a lot of money.)
- Momo has to win. - 220 dollars to become the captain.
(He pretends to be okay.)
Team Orange.
- I'm curious about this team. - Nayeon should be the captain.
(Announcing the results of Team Orange)
Nayeon who bet 20 dollars is the captain.
Yes!
(The surety is pleased.)
Kwang Soo bet 10 dollars, and the rest of them didn't bet.
(What about So Min who got loans?)
- Why did you not make a bet? - So Min, why did you not do it?
- Why did you not make a bet? - You got a loan.
I just got a loan to keep the money.
(I just got a loan to keep the money.)
(What?)
What is she up to?
Hey, what you're doing is...
- like getting a loan for saving. - But once I...
Once I pay the money back, you'll get the interest.
Why would you get a loan and save it up?
(He doesn't understand.)
- This isn't about the game. - What are you doing?
She's making money in her own way.
(She found a way to invest.)
I don't want to lose.
This is Round Two.
(The 2nd round is for differential prize money and lunch menu.)
This round is for differential prize money and lunch menu.
(Second Mission, Graceful Signal Dance)
The second mission is Graceful Signal Dance.
Momo has to try hard in this round.
She has to win.
(She can't back out now.)
I have to try hard.
- You must be hungry now. - Right.
(The lunch we prepared for them)
So we prepared lunch for you.
You'll hear various signal songs.
(Various songs will be played,)
(and the members have to dance the way that suits the song.)
Listen to the songs carefully...
and show dance moves that are suitable for them.
You can give it a try in any order you like.
(The dance battle is for the side dishes.)
Once you're done dancing, the three judges will...
(The objective and fair judging system of Running Man)
lift up the color of the best dancer.
If you get one or more votes,
(If a team gets at least one vote, they get the dish.)
- you can get the menu for lunch. - Okay.
We have an advantage here.
(The team with the most side dishes win the most money.)
And you will get differential rates of prize money...
according to the number of dishes you win.
- Let's do this. - Let me play...
- the first song then. - Shall we dance together?
- We should try hard. - Cue.
(First song)
(The combination of trot and EDM, "Amor Fati")
Go ahead and dance.
(Dahyun of Team White goes.)
- She's doing it. - You can do this by yourself.
- Dance with your guts. - You can do this.
(Dahyun, the random dance machine of TWICE, gets ready.)
Good, Dahyun.
- Chaeyoung. - Go.
Good job, Chaeyoung.
(Her steps may seem normal,)
(but her face is not.)
Mina, that's good.
Dahyun's face is so funny.
(The master of facial expressions)
She makes the same expression, but she looks different.
Momo, you should show something.
(Tzuyu joins her.)
Show us.
(Trying to keep up with the master of facial expressions.)
How would we beat her?
Good.
(Momo joins them popping and locking.)
It's so cool.
Good. It's so cool.
Great.
(They fight for the center position.)
That's nice.
(She sublimates her bitterness for paying too much for the captain.)
They are fighting.
That's really good.
(The image of her loss of assets)
Why would she dance like that to a song like this?
(Momo pops and locks to "Amor Fati".)
Momo, that's great.
I love it.
Okay.
(The first song is finished after the battle over the center.)
When Dahyun takes the stage, I can't go out there.
She has that air about her.
(Dahyun, always at the center.)
Dahyun is too strong.
She is too scary.
(Even the other dancers are afraid of Dahyun.)
I am afraid of her.
Raise the color of the team whose dance you liked the most.
(An objective and fair Running Man evaluation system is in progress.)
(Will it be Momo who is desperate for food?)
(Or Dahyun who has a variety of facial expressions?)
Three.
(They voted unanimously for Team White.)
- Okay! - Yes!
It's okay.
(We won!)
- Dahyun, you did it. - You did it.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Team White earns braised short ribs.)
Thank you.
Good job.
The second signal song is for bulgogi and mushroom hot pot.
(The second song is over bulgogi and mushroom hot pot.)
That's all we need.
Music, cue.
(The song begins.)
(Hold on. This song is...)
Hold on. Isn't that the song?
(Haha and Jae Suk's bodies react first.)
"Infinite Challenge".
My goodness.
Isn't this a song for "Infinite Challenge"?
(They heard this song a lot in their "Infinite Challenge" days.)
(Their teamwork on Saturday became a fond memory.)
"Infinite Challenge"!
(The former members party as if their time has come.)
There you go. There you go.
(The two old men dominate the stage.)
This song is for Jae Suk and Haha.
(Excited)
(Today's Sunday.)
How could you play this song?
This song is for Jae Suk and Haha.
(She is more excited than the former members.)
- Haha and Jae Suk will take it. - There you go, Sana.
(Meanwhile, in the corner...)
(Sana and Suk Jin are dancing like an old couple.)
There you go, Sana.
This song is for Jae Suk and Haha.
(The "Infinite Challenge" song sends the ballroom into chaos.)
- The dance needs to suit the song. - That was great.
Our team will win.
(We still have many dances.)
- Haha and Jae Suk. - I haven't done this dance.
I haven't done this dance.
(It's time to check the result.)
The round was for bulgogi and mushroom hot pot.
(This round was advantageous for Jae Suk and Haha.)
It was a song for "Infinite Challenge".
1, 2, 3.
(What will be the result?)
Okay.
(Team Gray and Team White get the dish!)
- Okay. - Okay.
(You should have danced better.)
Good job.
- Haha danced with Jae Suk. - He danced too.
Didn't he get a vote?
(No one voted for Haha?)
Haha danced too.
Is this because I am not on "Hangout with Yoo"?
(Inferiority complex?)
Haha danced too.
(He is on a variety show on both days of the weekend.)
- Haha danced too. - Okay.
- Okay. - The decision is objective.
(I accept.)
This one is for the rolled omelet.
(The third song is over the rolled omelet.)
- Rolled omelet. - Let's take it.
- Music, - The two of us will go out first.
- cue. - Run out shortly afterward.
Let's go.
All right, Jae Suk.
(They charge to the stage.)
- This step looks weird. - Try to look cool.
(They grab each other's neck and dance in a cool way.)
Why did you guys come to us?
(Why are you passing through here?)
- What is this? - Why did you guys come to us?
Why did you guys come to us?
(Peek-a-boo)
- What is this? - Why did you guys come to us?
- Hold on. - What is this?
Hold on. Why did you guys come to us?
(A tollgate opened.)
What are you guys doing?
Why did you guys come to us?
- Why did you guys come to us? - What is going on?
(Tzuyu blocks the entrance.)
Hold on. Guys. Guys.
(A dancing tollgate sends the entire stage into chaos.)
The teams should take turns.
- Why did you take over the stage? - Seriously.
(Amidst the chaos)
The teams should take turns.
- Why did you take over the stage? - Seriously.
- This isn't a collaboration. - What is this?
(She's dominating the camera lying on the cold floor.)
- The teams should take turns. - That's right.
So Min, what are you doing?
(She is enjoying the camera...)
What are you doing?
(she couldn't see while she was on a break.)
- The teams should take turns. - Look at So Min.
What is So Min doing?
(Even after everyone cleared out...)
What are you doing?
(Rolling)
Hey!
You should focus on paying off the debt!
(Outburst in laughter)
- I am working hard. - All right. Okay.
(The song has to change to resolve the dance chaos.)
Gosh, this song is...
Let's go.
(Is it "Honey" by Park Jin Young?)
Gosh, this song is...
- It's Park Jin Young's song. - They know the dance.
(It's almost like a reflex.)
- Go out there. - JYP Entertainment.
They are like a machine.
(All members of TWICE dance to Park Jin Young's song.)
All of them know the dance.
(The master dancer jumps onto the stage again.)
They all know the dance.
There are more members of other teams.
(Dahyun is at the center again.)
This is...
(She commands the stage.)
- Dahyun. - Look at Dahyun.
(The center...)
- Dahyun. - No one can take the center.
It's Dahyun's spot.
No one can go near Dahyun or Momo.
(Dahyun and Momo dominate TWICE's dance ecosystem.)
Dahyun.
Momo, go to the front.
(The 2nd war to take the center begins.)
Let's see what happens.
Hold on.
(She fails to get in between.)
Why do you keep trying to go to the front?
Why are you going to the front?
(The song ends after Dahyun and Momo's impressive dance.)
That was incredible.
- We did it. - What was that?
Dahyun, what kind of dance was that?
(The third battle is finally over.)
This result reflects the dance you have shown so far.
All right.
(From So Min to Dahyun, who will win this dance round?)
- Dahyun should get a vote. - She was the best.
1, 2, 3.
(Team Orange and Team White succeed to get a side dish.)
(Bowing)
Where are you going?
(After adding 3 rounds...)
Thank you.
Kwang Soo's team has 100 dollars.
(The current rankings:)
Team Gray has minus 200 dollars.
(1st place Team White, 2nd place Team Purple,)
(3rd place Team Orange, 4th place Team Gray)
Captains, come on out...
- and distribute the money. - Do they distribute the money?
(Team money rankings)
- Nayeon. - Nayeon, I have no doubt.
(Team White 500 dollars, Team Purple 300 dollars)
- Me neither. I trust you. - I have no doubt.
(Team Orange 100 dollars, Team Gray minus 200 dollars)
Suk Jin, do this right.
We can't place last.
(Come on, Captain Jee.)
Minus 200 dollars?
(We believe in you.)
Wait right there.
(How will Captain Jee distribute minus 200 dollars?)
- Don't worry. - We showed great teamwork.
(Captain Momo starts the distribution.)
Turn it in if you are ready.
(The 4 captains finish distributing the money.)
I will give you the money.
(It's time to check the distribution.)
Write down the amount here.
Kwang Soo's team, take the money.
(Kwang Soo checks the amount.)
(Kwang Soo got 0 dollars.)
What? What?
- Why do I have 230 dollars? - What?
Didn't we have 100 dollars?
- When will we do that? - What?
(The dividend rate is 0 percent.)
Okay. Here.
(How did Captain Suk Jin divide minus 200 dollars?)
(Jong Kook got minus 200 dollars.)
- This is driving me crazy. - It's fun this way.
- He gave all of it to you, right? - This is driving me crazy.
(Minus 200 dollars)
I didn't take any money from you guys.
(He tries to win their approval.)
- This round was so hard. - Hey.
(Haha got 0 dollars.)
- Why did I get so much? - I know. Why did I get so much?
Why did I get so much?
(Haha's feelings are hurt.)
You gave money to everyone except for me.
I will give you money later.
(Feeling guilty)
I will give you a lot of money later.
(The result of the captains' distribution)
(So Min, Momo, Dahyun, Tzuyu, and Nayeon will get a prize.)
(Kwang Soo, Jeongyeon, and Jong Kook will get a penalty.)
Now, write down the money you want to bet to be the captain.
(It's time to bid for the captain.)
Who wants to be the captain this time?
(It's a chance to be the captain with great powers.)
Do you want to be the captain?
Sure. I will be it.
- Go ahead. - Team Jae Suk is done, and...
(You can.)
Can I take out a loan? Then you will get 50 dollars anyway.
(Kwang Soo tries to get a loan.)
- 40, 40, 40, 40 dollars. - Can we take out a loan?
(He really wants to be the captain.)
I will stand surety for 100 dollars.
- 200 dollars. - 200 dollars?
(With So Min's surety, Kwang Soo loans 200 dollars.)
For how much did you stand surety?
- He wanted 200 dollars. - 200 dollars?
- Make me the captain this time. - Sure thing, Dahyun.
Okay. So we write down zero dollars.
It will be okay.
(They agree to write down 0 dollars except for Dahyun.)
To make Dahyun the captain,
everyone else wrote down zero dollars.
(They boast their loyalty.)
- Okay? - Dahyun, write 10 dollars.
(Team White agrees to write down zero dollars.)
You wrote down zero dollars, right?
All right.
(Everyone is done with the bidding.)
- We will announce the results. - Okay.
- Jae Suk's team. - Okay.
- Tzuyu bet zero dollars. - See?
- Jae Suk bet zero dollars. - That's right.
- Se Chan bet 20 dollars. - Okay!
Se Chan bet 20 dollars.
Okay!
That's...
(Se Chan betrayed to become the captain.)
- He is unbelievable. - That's...
- Dahyun bet 30 dollars. - What?
30 dollars.
Dahyun bet 30 dollars.
(She is scolding him with her eyes.)
- What? - 30 dollars.
- What? - I knew this would happen!
- Dahyun didn't trust you. - I knew this would happen!
(He was too short-sighted.)
- That's incredible. - He isn't...
a part of the team.
- How could you be like that? - I am sorry, Captain.
(Feeling betrayed)
- How did you know? - All right. Just you wait.
(Boiling with anger)
Dahyun is the captain.
Captain, please remember this when you distribute the money.
(Sneaky)
- I will do that. - This is a disaster.
(Se Chan's treason failed.)
Unbelievable.
Ji Hyo and Mina bet zero dollars.
(Ji Hyo and Mina bet zero dollars.)
- Chaeyoung bet 10 dollars. - Really?
- She is ambitious. - You gave it a try.
(She displayed her ambition with 10 dollars.)
Momo bet 220 dollars, and Haha bet 50 dollars.
Darn it!
When did you write down 220 dollars?
(Haha gave up the last round to be the captain this round.)
- Did she bet 220 dollars again? - 220 dollars?
(He was once again betrayed by Momo.)
Does she have that much money?
How will you pay back the money?
(Feeling uneasy)
- Please give me some time. - Seriously.
- We have the last round. - I lent you 300 dollars.
(Chairman Jee feels unsure after a series of failed investments.)
220 dollars?
How did Momo bet 220 dollars?
(Momo becomes the captain after her large sum of bidding.)
Haha!
Suk Jin's team.
Jong Kook, Sana, and Jihyo bet zero dollars.
Suk Jin bet 30 dollars.
Suk Jin.
(Ji Suk Jin, only cares about being the captain)
You keep being the captain.
He is in power for a long time.
(Teammates are saddened by his long-term in office.)
I have never seen Jihyo and Sana make that kind of a face.
What is wrong with you?
Kwang Soo's team is last.
(The result of Team Orange's bidding)
Jeongyeon bet zero dollars.
(Jeongyeon bet zero dollars.)
- You didn't bet any money? - No.
Nayeon bet 30 dollars.
(Kwang Soo even took out a loan to become the captain.)
Kwang Soo bet 220 dollars, and So Min bet 230 dollars.
Kwang Soo bet 220 dollars and So Min bet 230 dollars.
(So Min stood surety and backstabbed him.)
She went all in.
She is unbelievable.
(So Min impresses them every time.)
Even if she comes in last...
(She is savoring the happiness 10 dollars brought her.)
I wanted to be the captain for once.
- So Min, you are unbelievable. - You are incredible.
(I was happy for 1 second.)
- You are incredible. - Now,
(It's time to enjoy the meal with the food they earned.)
let's have lunch. We will bring in the food.
- Okay. - I can't eat right now.
I lost my appetite.
(The side effect of battle to be the captain)
Eat up, everyone.
(They enjoy a meal with the side dishes they earned.)
- Enjoy the food. - Enjoy the food.
- What is this? - What is this?
(A giant golden pyramid and...)
This is amazing. What is this?
It smells good, right?
(the scent of shampoo welcome them at the site of the third mission.)
It's the scent of shampoo.
Oh, my sponsor is here. Mr. Sponsor.
(Bowing)
- So Min. - Yes?
You need to pay me back soon.
(The collection day is coming up.)
Mr. Sponsor.
(Being loyal)
(Staring)
(She approaches Kwang Soo.)
(Ripping)
I wanted to rip it once.
What is...
(You scared me.)
- She ripped it off. - Why...
(Bright)
You did a good job. You ripped it off tastefully.
(Kwang Soo's name tag is popular.)
I was sad that it ended so quickly.
- You didn't get to rip one off. - No.
- This is the final mission. - Okay.
The final mission is Touch More and More.
(The final mission, Touch More and More)
Touch More and More.
(TWICE loves it.)
They're witty.
(She loves it.)
It will be like a tournament.
(It's a tournament.)
The 2 representatives of 2 teams will play the game first.
(2 representatives will play the game first.)
On the slippery pyramid that is made of Styrofoam,
(It's made of Styrofoam. It's safe.)
they will play tag on offense or defense.
Both players will start with paint on the gloves.
(Both players will start with paint on the gloves.)
If the offensive team touches the defensive team's name tag...
(If the offensive team touches the defensive team's name tag...)
and gets paint on it, that person is out.
(and gets paint on it, that person is out.)
The moment one member is out,
(The moment one member is out, another member will enter.)
another member of the same team will enter.
The offense and defense change every 30 seconds.
(The offense and defense change every 30 seconds.)
You win when everyone in the opposing team is eliminated.
It will be hard.
(It's important to get the paint on the name tag fast.)
We just need to touch the name tag.
That's right. You just need to get some paint on the name tag.
The female members will go first.
(The finals)
Tzuyu and Dahyun need a hair tie.
(So Min puts on the helmet with help from Se Chan.)
Thank you.
Let's see how slippery it is.
(Sliding)
(Smiling)
(Cheering)
I look cool, right?
(He doesn't mean it at all.)
Don't I look cool?
Haha.
(Haha, look at me.)
It's seriously cool.
I got goosebumps.
That's incredible.
(For whom is she putting on a performance?)
(She is cute.)
- That's incredible. - Why am I doing this?
(Having a reality check)
Seriously. I got goosebumps.
Please put paint on your gloves.
Okay.
Give me a pair of gloves.
I have gloves right here.
(Throwing)
(Hurling)
I am sorry.
(Flustered after throwing)
(His feelings are hurt.)
I am sorry.
(Sorry)
- I got flustered too. - I could have gone to you.
I got flustered too. I'm sorry.
It looked like you were throwing a snack to a dog.
(That was mean.)
He was on his way to you too.
(Today's treat)
I am sorry. I got flustered.
That was too...
(I didn't think you would be like that.)
My goodness.
(Dahyun is putting paint on her gloves.)
There we go.
Put enough paint on the gloves.
(Soaking)
Dahyun is putting a lot of paint on them.
That's good.
Are you dying your gloves?
(Are you dying your gloves?)
- Are you ready? - Yes.
(Their enthusiasm is at its max.)
Please enter.
(She enters looking determined.)
Dahyun, are you on your way to perform surgery?
Will you perform surgery?
(Doctor Dahyun will perform this surgery.)
Dahyun, perform surgery.
We are on offense, right?
(Team Dahyun attacks first.)
I will blow the whistle after 30 seconds...
(The positions change after 30 seconds.)
to change the offense and defense.
I am scared. I am scared.
Get ready. Set.
(The 1st round starts.)
Set.
Hang in there for 30 seconds.
(Team Dahyun attacks upon start.)
The positions change when the whistle sounds.
- Okay. - There you go.
- Oh, my goodness. - That's good.
(Jeongyeon heads to the top which is easy to defend.)
- She is good. - Hang in there for 30 seconds.
- Jeongyeon, let's go. - Jeongyeon.
(Dahyun dashes toward Jeongyeon.)
She is almost there.
- She is almost there. - Come on down.
Hang in there for 30 seconds. No!
(Jeongyeon. Bear it for 30 seconds.)
Come on.
Hang in there for 30 seconds. No!
(Will Jeongyeon get eliminated right away?)
Tzuyu, she is coming down.
(You should attack.)
Jeongyeon!
Hang in there for 30 seconds. No!
- I got her! - Jeongyeon!
(Dahyun touches Jeongyeon.)
- She is out! - No!
- I got her! - Jeongyeon!
(Jeongyeon is out.)
- Jeongyeon is out. - Go in there, So Min.
(So Min goes in.)
(Team So Min will attack now.)
This is...
She is over there.
(Dahyun runs to the top.)
So Min, eliminate someone.
- Get her. - Get her.
(With the sound of whistle, Dahyun moves to attack!)
(She isn't too far from So Min.)
(Will she eliminate So Min after Jeongyeon?)
Hang in there for 30 seconds.
(Sliding down)
That's good.
(She shows slapstick comedy on her way down.)
- Are you okay, Dahyun? - That was great.
(That's the whole point of it.)
Dahyun.
Dahyun brought out the best of this game.
(That meets the purpose.)
(This is fun.)
I haven't seen that in a while.
(Her instinct to attack doesn't subside.)
- So Min, you are much faster. - Tzuyu, get So Min.
(Lying down)
No, no. What are you doing?
(She hands in her name tag.)
I got her! I got her!
- I got paint on her name tag. - You can slide in your hand...
(So Min is out.)
- since the floor is slippery. - Kwang Soo, come on in.
(The last player of Team So Min is already in.)
Both of them are good.
(Kwang Soo gets a chance to attack as soon as he enters.)
Run away!
(He takes big steps with his long legs.)
- Kwang Soo is fast. - Here comes Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Are we on offense?
(Confused)
Yes. Why are you running away?
- Are we on offense? - Yes.
(She runs away by bouncing on her butt.)
(This master of slapstick comedy has a bright future.)
(Kwang Soo attacks Tzuyu.)
Run away.
(He falls on his side.)
(Thanks to Kwang Soo's hard work,)
(Tzuyu is out.)
Kwang Soo, are you okay?
(Kwang Soo goes crazy.)
Tzuyu is out. Tzuyu is out.
(I'm scared.)
He is scary.
(He gives a big bow.)
(The viewers find it entertaining.)
(Kwang Soo gives a lesson...)
(to the rising star of slapstick comedy.)
Dahyun is out!
(Dahyun is out.)
- Go. - Go in there, Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan are in.)
Go in there, Jae Suk.
Hurry up. Kwang Soo is right there.
You need to catch Kwang Soo.
Eliminate Kwang Soo first.
(He's overly enthusiastic in front of TWICE.)
- Kwang Soo is on the roll. - Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Are we on defense?
(Team Dahyun will attack.)
- We are on offense. - The other way!
Hurry up and attack him!
(They start surrounding Kwang Soo.)
(It's slippery.)
(He slides down the pyramid to attack.)
(Kwang Soo runs away with his long legs.)
Kwang Soo is running away well.
He is fast.
(He slides down and blocks Kwang Soo.)
Jae Suk, this way.
(The positions change.)
My goodness.
Go, go. Catch him.
(Decalcomania slapstick comedy)
- His legs are too long. - Hurry up!
(He goes after Jae Suk.)
Push him.
(The positions change!)
The positions changed, right?
- Yes. - Did it change?
(The tables have turned.)
(Jae Suk paints his face.)
The positions changed.
(Se Chan quickly joins.)
Put your hand under his back.
Come on.
I touched it.
(Kwang Soo's out in the end.)
- Kwang Soo is out. - He did it.
We are on defense now.
(Nayeon is the only member left.)
Nayeon, attack!
(It's a chance to attack.)
Attack.
(Exhausted)
Nayeon, I am sorry!
(Look at his face.)
Nayeon, we need to place first.
(I am scared.)
- Nayeon. - Come on.
(Team So Min's only survivor Nayeon is cornered.)
Kwang Soo.
Run away! Run away!
(Take this!)
(They create wind with their butts.)
Okay. We did it.
(Everyone's out including Nayeon.)
I am scared.
Jae Suk's team wins the first round.
(Team Dahyun enters the finals.)
Okay.
(Team So Min will fight for 3rd place.)
We are up next.
Sana and Jihyo's team will attack first.
(Team Suk Jin versus Team Momo)
The two members...
She is so scary.
(Eyes wide open)
- No, one member goes in at a time. - She is scary.
Jihyo is so scary.
(Just you wait.)
(Team Suk Jin attacks first.)
Let's go.
Let's begin. Get ready. Set.
(The 2nd round starts.)
(Both teams move to the top.)
- They are going up. - They are going up.
- They are going up. - Why is Jihyo so fast?
(Lightly)
Jihyo is so fast.
(Ji Hyo and Chaeyoung hurriedly run away.)
Jihyo.
(Touch)
Ji Hyo is out!
Jihyo.
(She slides down...)
Ji Hyo is out!
(and quickly paints Ji Hyo's name tag!)
You are doing great!
(Jihyo eliminates Ji Hyo.)
- She is incredible. - Go in there.
(Ji Hyo is out. Momo is in.)
Go in there, Momo.
Go in there. Go in there, Momo.
(Momo's team will attack now.)
Momo.
(Jihyo was chasing after Chaeyoung.)
Get her. Go this way, Momo.
(She runs away.)
- Get her. - Go this way.
Over there.
(The baby beasts have a face-off.)
Get her.
I got her!
(Jihyo is out.)
- Really? Did it get on my name tag? - Jihyo is out.
- Jihyo was fast. - Go in there.
(Jihyo is out. Jong Kook is in.)
Do I go in there?
- Get him. - Do I need to run away?
Run away, Jong Kook.
- Do I need to run away? - Did Jong Kook enter already?
(The way he walks doesn't match his size.)
Jong Kook is fast.
(Suk Jin's team will attack now.)
- Attack. - Run away!
(The final boss makes everyone panic.)
Run away!
(Falling down)
What is Chaeyoung doing?
- Let's go to the final round. - I am sorry.
- No! - Chaeyoung is out.
(Chaeyoung is out.)
Chaeyoung is out.
Take her out.
- There you go. - Good job.
(Meanwhile, Momo is out.)
Let's go to the final round.
This is the last batch already.
(Chaeyoung and Momo are out. Mina and Haha are in.)
Did Momo go in?
(Momo's team will attack now!)
Corner him.
- Corner him. - Corner him.
Who is out?
(Jong Kook occupies the top.)
Look at Jong Kook.
You need to take Jong Kook out right now.
- My goodness. - Mina, I am sorry.
(Despite Jong Kook's thorough defense,)
This is your last chance.
(Mina keeps attacking.)
Mina, I am sorry.
(Slipping)
(Mina spots a chance!)
She did it!
(Will Mina's attack be successful?)
Mina, I am sorry.
(Jong Kook is out.)
Jong Kook is out.
(Mina eliminates the final boss Jong Kook.)
- Jong Kook is out. - Jong Kook, what was that?
Mina, good job.
(The positions change as Suk Jin enters!)
Are we attacking now?
Mina, be careful.
(Suk Jin goes after Mina.)
Be careful.
(Falling down)
(His weak legs make people shed tears.)
(His arms are even weaker.)
Mina, hang in there.
She will beat Suk Jin.
(Mina will beat Suk Jin.)
Mina, hang in there.
(Suk Jin and Mina have a fierce match.)
(Slipping)
Suk Jin.
(It's Mina's turn to attack.)
Look at Suk Jin.
(It's fish covered in shampoo.)
- Attack! - Suk Jin is so fast.
- That's hilarious. - Suk Jin can crawl so fast.
(The predator goes after the fish.)
That's cute.
- Attack! - Suk Jin is so fast.
(Crawling on four helps Suk Jin move faster.)
Suk Jin is so fast.
(However, due to Haha's attack,)
Suk Jin is out.
(Suk Jin is out.)
- That was hilarious. - Suk Jin, what was that?
That was hilarious.
(That was hilarious.)
(Sana is the last member of Team Suk Jin.)
- She's going up. - Sana, it's your turn to attack!
(It's Sana's turn to attack.)
(Lightly)
- She's fast. - She's fast.
You can do this. Be careful.
- No! - Run away.
(She's steady.)
- Slide! - Haha is out.
(A jump shot)
- Run away. - Slide!
Haha is out.
(Haha is out.)
(Sana is the hidden ace in Team Suk Jin.)
- Go, Sana! - Incredible!
Will Sana save us?
(If Sana eliminates Mina, Team Suk Jin will win.)
Why is she so fast?
(Amazed)
(Sana, the predator on the Styrofoam pyramid, charges at Mina.)
(Will she eliminate Mina...)
Will Sana save us?
(and dramatically turn the game around?)
Will she save us?
Sana will...
(Touch!)
Will Sana save us?
- Mina is out. - Mina is out.
(Mina is out.)
We won!
(Team Suk Jin enters the finals.)
- Sana! - Sana!
(Sana saved us.)
- Sana saved us! - Yes!
(Sana made up for Suk Jin's lousy performance.)
- Sana saved them. - Unbelievable.
Let's start the third-place match now.
(Team So Min versus Team Momo)
Team Haha will attack first.
(Team Momo attacks first.)
(They move to the starting point.)
Kwang Soo, come over here.
Hey, what's that?
Why are you wearing your name tag on the front?
(What?)
(So Min is wearing her name tag on the front?)
Hey, what's that?
(What's wrong?)
- So Min. - Don't do that!
(This is how crazy So Min is.)
- Go ahead and rip it off. - What are you doing?
She hasn't changed a bit.
(Culture shock)
- She's even meaner now. - She's become even weirder.
(She's become crazier.)
- Wear it on the back. - You can't do that.
While she was away from the show...
(The match for 3rd place begins.)
What happened to her?
(Chaeyoung, Jihyo, Momo and So Min are out.)
Chaeyoung is out.
Song Ji Hyo is out.
Momo is out.
Go in, Nayeon.
(Nayeon and Jeongyeon versus Haha and Mina)
What am I supposed to do?
- Run away. - You're on defense.
(Nayeon and Jeongyeon's turn to attack)
- Attack! - You're on offense.
(Nayeon approaches Haha.)
- Haha! - Yes?
Go away.
(Nayeon hit Haha?)
(Haha is hit on the head.)
Gosh.
She hit me.
You're pathetic.
Haha, you're...
- You're pathetic. - Run away!
(Sorry, Haha.)
You're pathetic.
(Jeongyeon eliminates Mina.)
Run away!
(Haha, left alone, is determined to win.)
(Jeongyeon is eliminated in no time.)
Jeongyeon is out!
- Am I out? - Haha is pathetic.
(Jeongyeon out, Kwang Soo in)
Kick him!
(Nayeon)
(Following Jong Kook's advice, Nayeon uses her feet.)
Haha!
(A proper low kick)
He told me to kick you.
Jong Kook told me to kick you.
(Jong Kook told me to kick you.)
He told me to kick you.
- He told me to kick you. - Rip off his name tag!
(He got kicked right in his bottom.)
(She's laughing so hard that she can't breathe.)
Hey! Timeout!
His big toe got in!
(It was docked in no time.)
I had no idea.
(Shameless)
That's hilarious.
Look at Kwang Soo's face.
(He's gone crazy a while ago.)
I can't believe him.
- Haha, you're still in the game. - Let's do this!
(Kwang Soo and Nayeon attack.)
- Let's attack! - We're attacking now.
Attack! Get him!
(He lost focus.)
(Kwang Soo slides down with a blank look on his face.)
Attack! Get him!
- Okay! - Haha is out.
(Touch)
(Haha is out.)
(An angry headlock)
We won!
(Team So Min places 3rd.)
- We won! - We won!
- We won! - We're in third place.
(They're still happy to place 3rd.)
Team Haha is at the bottom.
(Team Momo is guaranteed to place last.)
They're at the bottom.
- Let's start the finals! - It's the finals.
(Team Dahyun versus Team Suk Jin)
- Let's win! - Let's do this.
You guys are attacking first.
(Team Dahyun attacks first.)
- We are? - Yes.
- We're attacking first? Okay. - We're attacking first.
Ready.
(We have to win 1st place.)
Get set.
(The finals start.)
Slowly. 30 seconds is short.
(They're aggressive from the beginning.)
Way to go, Sana!
- Run away! - Go, Sana!
(Ace Sana easily avoids her.)
- Sana is so good. - Way to go!
- Sana is amazing. - Okay!
(Taking big steps)
- Sana is running! - Nice!
(Jaw-dropping)
(The pyramid is extremely slippery.)
How can she...
No!
(Jihyo is surrounded.)
- This way! - My gosh!
(Tzuyu was so close.)
- Hold on. - Be careful.
You're not out yet.
(Team Suk Jin attacks.)
- Tzuyu! - Attack!
(As soon as the whistle blows,)
- No! - Attack!
(she turns.)
- Attack! - Gosh.
(Sliding)
Dahyun.
(Fast running)
(Dahyun slides down, and Sana runs down.)
Dahyun.
(In the end, Dahyun is out.)
Dahyun is out.
(Dahyun out, Se Chan in)
Run away. Don't attack yet.
- Tzuyu! - Tzuyu!
(Sana and Jihyo attack Tzuyu together.)
We're going to win. When Tzuyu is out...
(They did touch Tzuyu's name tag, but...)
- I touched it! - The whistle was blown first.
(it doesn't count because the whistle was blown first.)
- Wait! - Tzuyu is not out.
- She's not out. - Why not?
- The whistle was blown first. - Don't attack yet.
(They attack Jihyo in chaos.)
- Hey, not yet! - It hasn't started.
(Angry)
We were talking. You should wait.
- Why... - Why are you angry?
(All of a sudden)
- Why are you angry? - Why are you angry?
(Why so serious during a game?)
- Why is he so serious? - Why is he angry?
Why is he so bossy?
Why are you angry?
(He's aware of TWICE fans and overprotects her.)
- I mean... - Why are you so bossy?
- We were deciding if she was out. - Why are you angry?
- Why are you angry? - He looked so serious.
(Still, why are you angry?)
Of course, I'm angry.
You shouldn't have approached her at that moment, you punk.
Why...
Why are you so serious?
(After Suk Jin was acting like an old fossil, the game resumes.)
What's with you?
- Let's continue. - All right.
You shouldn't have hit her while we were talking.
(Don't attack while having a discussion)
Team White is on offense.
Okay. Tzuyu is still in the game. Let's go.
(The game resumes with Se Chan and Tzuyu attacking.)
Ready, go.
- Nice! - There you go.
- Hey. - Se Chan.
(As there's no retreat, they run to the top.)
- Go up! Sana is so good. - There you go.
(The pyramid is my playground.)
Look at them.
(Sliding)
(Jihyo runs away.)
(But Se Chan slides down too.)
- Kick him! - She's out.
Jihyo is out.
(Jihyo is out.)
Jihyo was incredible.
Should I go in?
- Go in! - Go, Tzuyu!
(As soon as Jong Kook's in, it's time to attack.)
- Tzuyu, you're on defense. - Run!
(Jong Kook eliminates Tzuyu right away.)
(Tzuyu is out.)
Tzuyu is out.
(Oh, my goodness.)
- Jae Suk, come in! - It's my turn.
(Tzuyu out, Jae Suk in)
You can do this!
(Just when Jae Suk and Se Chan are pushed into a corner,)
(Team Dahyun attacks.)
The positions have been changed!
(I have to get to the top.)
The positions have been changed! We have to get to the top!
(Both teams fight for the top.)
We have to get to the top!
We have to...
(How dare you!)
(Jong Kook kicks everyone away from the top.)
Way to go!
(Pharaoh Jong Kook holds absolute dominance on top of the pyramid.)
This is unfair.
- They can't do anything. - They won't get to the top.
- Way to go! - We want to go up.
(Helpless)
We have to get to the top.
(Kicking)
Nice!
(Jong Kook Fortress)
Gosh.
That's so unfair.
(They keep rolling down the pyramid.)
We're going to win!
(It's Jong Kook's turn to attack.)
Gosh, this is not okay.
Let's go!
(I've been waiting for this moment.)
Hold on!
From the other direction, Sana.
(Trembling)
Attack from the other direction, Sana.
(Sana blocks their way from the other side.)
- From the other direction. - They're surrounded.
(Sana tries to intercept Se Chan.)
- It's over. - She caught him.
He's out!
(But she fails.)
She failed.
- Am I out? - No.
(Jong Kook's target changes from Jae Suk...)
- No? - No.
(to Se Chan.)
(The whistle blows again.)
(Jumping down)
(His eyes, nostrils, and mouth open wide.)
Jong Kook!
(Jong Kook is surrounded.)
(What should I do?)
Gosh.
(He blocks by sitting on the ground.)
I can't believe this.
(The airplane takes off.)
(Where are you going, sir?)
Good job.
(The customer is 200 percent satisfied.)
Not even Ji Ho does that anymore.
(Jae Suk's son)
Good job.
(The airplane takes off again.)
- Jae Suk flew. - Jae Suk flew.
(Fly with Jong Kook Air.)
Good job.
- Let's run away. - Go away.
(He gives up.)
Change!
(They're all exhausted, and it's time to switch.)
This is hilarious.
(They compete to get to the top first.)
She's getting him.
(Jae Suk is eliminated while catching his breath.)
Jae Suk is out.
(The last survivor, Se Chan, is exhausted too.)
(Se Chan is out.)
(He eliminates everyone including Se Chan.)
We won!
Team Gray wins!
(Team Suk Jin wins!)
I won without even playing.
I've only played airplane with my nephews before.
This is humiliating.
Everyone,
according to the final mission results,
Team Suk Jin wins 500 dollars.
(Team Suk Jin wins 500 dollars.)
500 dollars? We won 500 dollars!
Team Dahyun wins 300 dollars.
(Team Dahyun, in 2nd place, wins 300 dollars.)
Team So Min wins 100 dollars.
(Team So Min, in 3rd place, wins 100 dollars.)
Lastly, Team Momo wins...
minus 200 dollars.
- Oh, my gosh. - 200 dollars?
- Minus 200 dollars. - We won 100 dollars.
Please distribute the money.
(It's time to distribute money.)
- I'll divide it equally. - Really?
(We'll be down soon.)
Doesn't it hurt?
Dahyun, I trust you.
You can trust me.
Do you want to win prizes?
Sana and Jihyo, do you want to win prizes?
- That'd be nice. - Of course.
(Of course.)
I don't...
expect anything from him.
I'll be different this time.
(How will Suk Jin distribute 500 dollars?)
As the oldest member... Of course.
The top three might come from our team.
(Team White aims to take all prizes.)
If the money is distributed in the right way...
Suk Jin spent too much money.
(On assurance)
Haha, pay me back.
Are you going to pay me back or not?
I'm sorry.
(Shameless)
Then I have a negative amount.
(My goodness.)
Let me announce how the money will be distributed in this round.
(The money is distributed.)
Suk Jin is giving...
(Result according to Captain Suk Jin's distribution)
300 dollars to Jong Kook and 200 dollars to himself.
What? Really?
(Suddenly he's being a big brother to Jong Kook.)
Why?
He doesn't want to get in trouble.
Suk Jin doesn't want to get in trouble with Jong Kook.
(Suk Jin who doesn't want to...)
(get in trouble gives Jong Kook 300 dollars.)
- So Min is giving... - I had no choice.
50 dollars to herself,
(Result according to Captain So Min's distribution)
20 dollars each to Nayeon and Jeongyeon,
and 10 dollars to Kwang Soo.
- That's not bad. - Right?
- I... - That's pretty fair.
(She distributed 100 dollars fairly.)
- That's nice of her. - Next up is Dahyun.
- Our captain, Dahyun. - It'll be simple.
(They trust Captain Dahyun.)
She's giving 70 dollars each to Jae Suk and Se Chan...
(Result according to Captain Dahyun's distribution)
and 80 dollars each to Dahyun and Tzuyu.
- That's not bad. - Unbelievable.
(The fair distribution makes them happy.)
- What is this? - I like it.
- Se Chan. - That's enough.
That's more than enough.
Why is this team so peaceful?
(I'm jealous.)
Captain Momo got...
minus 200 dollars.
(How did Captain Momo distribute minus 200 dollars?)
It all goes to Haha.
(Haha gets minus 200 dollars.)
It all goes to Haha?
- Seriously... - Haha gets minus 200 dollars?
- She's very consistent. - Gosh.
(Captain Momo gave it all to Haha.)
- She's incredible. - She's unbelievable.
- Momo is amazing. - I'm sorry.
(Into the air)
If Haha gets minus 200 dollars...
- He'll definitely be penalized. - Definitely.
(It's time to pay back what they owe.)
All right.
Nayeon has paid Se Chan back 200 dollars.
(Nayeon has paid Se Chan back 200 dollars.)
Se Chan also gets 50 dollars in interest.
(Se Chan also gets 50 dollars in interest.)
So Min borrowed money from Jae Suk and Kwang Soo,
(So Min borrowed 100 dollars from Jae Suk...)
(and 200 dollars from Kwang Soo.)
but she can pay back only one person.
(She can only pay back one person.)
And she chose to pay back Jae Suk.
(She decides to pay Jae Suk back.)
- What about Kwang Soo? - What happens to me?
Jae Suk gets 30 dollars in interest.
And we'll deduct the deficit from Kwang Soo's money.
What?
- What do you mean? - I had...
- no other way. - You're going to deduct 200?
(I'm sorry. There was no other way.)
Haha owed Suk Jin 300.
(Haha can't pay 300 dollars back.)
- He can't pay it back. - I have to pay it back.
- 300 dollars? - Yes.
(Chairman Jee must pay for Haha's money.)
- Why did you lend him so much? - I might get the penalty.
First, I'll reveal prizes...
(It's time to reveal the prizes to beat the summer heat.)
- perfect for the summer. - That sounds great.
I wonder what it is.
It feels cool already.
Third place gets a circulator,
(Wine cooler, a portable refrigerator,)
second place gets a portable refrigerator,
(A circulator, a portable fan, fans)
and first place gets a wine cooler.
It's a wine cooler.
It's a cooler.
(They are impressed by the prize line-up.)
- Is that for wine? - You're giving these away?
I have the results.
(It's time to reveal the result.)
Top five will win prizes,
and the lowest three will get penalties.
(The first 5 win prizes, the last 3 will receive a penalty.)
- 1st place is... - 1st place.
(The 1st place, the wine cooler)
Se Chan with 340 dollars.
(Yang Se Chan)
Really?
That's awesome.
- I get to have a wine cooler? - You don't even drink wine.
(Is it for real?)
You'll put kimchi in there.
(You don't drink wine.)
- I'll put something in it. - He doesn't drink wine.
(Just touched)
Am I in first place?
If Haha paid me back, I would have been in first place.
(That was close.)
That's true.
Second place is...
(The 2nd place, portable refrigerator)
Jae Suk with 320 dollars.
(Yoo Jae Suk)
Jae Suk. What happened to our team?
(Team White wins both 1st and 2nd places.)
Third place is Tzuyu with 310 dollars.
(3rd place is Tzuyu.)
Fourth place is Dahyun with 300 dollars.
(4th place is Dahyun.)
We took it all.
(Cheering)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The 4 members with great teamwork take all prizes.)
What happened to them? Why did they have so much money?
(Envious)
Besides the harmonious team,
(Who is in 5th place to win the prize?)
there's one other person getting a prize.
- Is it Momo? - It's Suk Jin with 270 dollars.
Sir.
(Am I in 5th place?)
Congratulations, Mr. Jee.
(Biting his teeth)
- Where did you get 270 dollars? - Do I have 270?
(He tried to avoid the penalty but won a prize.)
Sixth place was a tie.
(Sana and Jihyo...)
With 100 dollars,
Sana and Jihyo.
(tied in 6th place.)
(But I am still happy.)
It still feels good.
I'll give you the fan. Take it.
(Is he being generous?)
- It's okay. - It's okay. We don't need it.
Please take it.
Tied in eighth place were...
Mina and Nayeon with 60 dollars.
- Nayeon. - How?
- Chaeyoung had 50 dollars. - Chaeyoung.
(Chaeyoung is in 10th place.)
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo had 40.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook are in 11th place.)
I got 40?
Jeongyeon had 30.
(Jeongyeon is in 13th place.)
There are four people left.
Momo, Kwang Soo, So Min, and Haha.
(The 3 out of 4 will receive penalties.)
Three of you are getting penalties.
In the last place is...
(The last place...)
Haha with minus 290 dollars.
(is Haha.)
I'm sorry, Mr. Jee.
(Goodness.)
- It's your fault. - I'm sorry.
16th place.
(16th place So Min...)
Momo, you have to join me.
So Min with minus 200 dollars.
(will also be getting the penalty.)
Am I exempt?
(She misheard.)
- You're getting the penalty. - It's a penalty.
(You're wrong.)
You're getting the penalty.
Okay!
(She realizes the truth and screams.)
- What's wrong with her? - What's wrong with her?
- I thought I was exempt. - So Min, that includes you.
We have 14th and 15th places left.
(Who will receive the penalty alongside So Min?)
- What happened? - 14th place is exempt.
Who's exempt then?
1 person has minus 160, and the other person has minus 170.
(Only one of them will avoid the penalty.)
- Okay, it's a 10-dollar difference. - My gosh.
(Who is the lucky one that avoided the penalty by 10 dollars?)
In 14th place with minus 160 dollars is...
Congratulations,
Momo.
- Count again! - Okay.
(That's not possible.)
- Congratulations, Momo. - You did great.
(She is happier being in 14th place than being in 1st place.)
Is it because she got 10 dollars near the end?
That's true.
(Saddened)
- You saved her. - Let's do the penalties.
- What is it? - What's the penalty?
- What do they do? - Here's today's penalty.
There are 3 buckets. 1 contains flower petals,
(Each bucket has flower petals, water, and black paint.)
one contains water, and the last one contains black paint.
(It's a random game.)
This is insane.
Please choose a number randomly.
(His body shakes in fear.)
Let Momo choose for me.
Number two.
(Haha chose bucket number 2 that Momo chose for him.)
Number two? Okay.
- Kwang Soo, I'll choose yours. - Okay.
Number three for Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo picks Nayeon's choice of number 3.)
I want...
number three.
- Do rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
(They'll decide with rock-paper-scissors.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, we'll get the penalty in this order.
1, 2, 3, okay?
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
- I'm sorry. - One,
(What will be the result of this random game?)
- It's okay. - two...
- It's okay. - This is not me.
(Please.)
Three.
Flower petals!
What?
(Black and white)
Flower petals!
- So Min. - So Min.
(Even TWICE members are shocked at their appearance.)
My gosh!
- So Min. - So Min.
- Why is it always you? - So Min.
(A crow appeared...)
(after the paint swept away.)
- Why did you choose that one? - Wipe your eyes.
Why did you choose that one?
I said I wanted number three!
(I didn't choose this.)
It was great seeing all of you after a while.
(The bucket penalty gave a pleasant surprise to everyone.)
TWICE, please come to the middle.
Let's hear what Momo has to say.
(He holds grudges.)
- Momo? - Yes.
I'm sorry to his fans.
That's a relief. I don't have too many fans.
- Hey. - What?
(They didn't stop bickering.)
What are you talking about?
We'll do our best with our new song "More and More",
so please check it out and send lots of love.
Also, Running Man was so much fun.
See you again!
(We would like to thank TWICE for joining us today.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Running Man convenience store is open.)
- It's nice to see you. - Seon Hwa.
(4 store managers are here to protect the convenience store.)
- It's Seon Hwa. - You Jung.
(Ji Chang Wook, Kim You Jung, Han Seon Hwa, Do Sang Woo)
- It's triangle gimbap, of course. - I think it's cup noodles.
(An intense competition to obtain best convenience store items!)
They're in here!
(All of a sudden,)
- Where? - They're in here.
They are?
(somebody is screaming inside the convenience store.)
I'm so scared. I think they're here.
(It's a secret robbery...)
(away from the eyes of the store managers!)
Who is it?
- They're at the end. - It's okay. I can smell it.
(They must steal the hot items without anybody finding out!)
(Their territory tightens.)
- I hear something. - I can smell it.
You got an offer from the broker.
(Those who try to steal the hot items,)
(and those who are ready for new deals)
- Will you accept it? - He's acting weird.
- He's weird. - He's a broker for sure.
It's either one of them.
(Their fates are in their own hands now.)
- Broker. - Let's just accept the offer.
(The temptations can come any time. They cannot let their guards down!)
They're starting to doubt their team members.
(A secret deal from the broker. What will be the result?)
- We'll accept the offer too. - They're here!
- Where? - Here!
(Secrete Broker Race: Hot Items from Convenience Store)