It's Do Kwon. He went too far.
- I'm sure it's him.
- Right.
He shouldn't be doing this, right?
I saw an empty envelope though.
He went too far.
- It was so obvious I could tell.
- Right.
- It's okay. I understand.
- Say something to explain.
- No. We should wait and watch.
- He's not saying anything.
I'm sure it's him.
- I told you.
- He has nothing to say.
(The members of the top club
promised to turn in 200 dollars.)
(But he hesitated as he heard he
can get his share without paying.)
(He pretended to pay
all his money.)
(He turned in only 10 dollars.)
(I turned in all my money.)
(He even showed
an empty envelope shamelessly.)
I can't believe
he turned in only 10 dollars.
Do Kwon, you look different
from the opening.
What happened to your hair?
My hair?
- Where's my cap?
- It's good that you're comfortable,
- but it's just too funny.
- You shouldn't have said that.
You should've just let him be.
Why did you say that?
Do Kwon is unbelievable.
He's the only person who'd do it.
- Jong Kook, I...
- Here. Take this.
You can distribute it.
Oh, this is my share.
- I can't believe this.
- Gosh.
- It's not much.
- Oh, no.
(So Yeon turned in 100 dollars.)
I got six.
That's good.
(The members of the top club
get 340 dollars each.)
But this is...
(Focused)
(Glancing)
Where else would
Ji Ah have a chance...
to count the play money
so seriously like this?
- So how much did I get?
- What's wrong?
- 340 dollars.
- It's 340 dollars.
340 dollars. Is that right?
- Yes.
- She likes it.
I have to get away from this team
as soon as possible.
On this team...
This isn't just about me.
So Yeon needs to leave this team.
- This team is terrible.
- So Yeon is...
Only So Yeon turned in 100 dollars.
Honestly, we can't be sure
if she turned in 100 dollars.
- Who else would it be?
- No one can be sure.
I'm sure she did.
- Did you turn in your money?
- We never know.
- Hang on. She probably didn't.
- Maybe she didn't pay 100 dollars.
You never know
what Cheon Seo Jin is up to.
(You never know
what Cheon Seo Jin is up to.)
- Eugene.
- She's her rival.
- But...
- Stop being so immersed!
She keeps thinking
about the drama even here.
(Cheon Seo Jin starts acting.)
Oh Yoon Hee.
- Now you will have a lunchtime.
- Okay.
The top club will eat
Korean beef at a nice place.
My goodness. It's Korean beef.
(It's the prime Korean beef.)
(They shout for joy.)
(Are they eating Korean beef?)
It must be delicious.
And the bottom club will eat
instant cup noodles in a tent.
- Instant cup noodles?
- Yes.
It's Korean beef versus cup noodles.
That's terrible.
- I know.
So how do we go to the top club?
Is it even possible?
Yes. You can make it to the top club
through this mission.
The members of each club
may change after the mission.
The bottom club will go through
a mission first...
and decide the members
to advance to the top club.
(The result of the mission will
decide members for the top club.)
The top club will go
through a mission as well.
If they fail the mission, they will
be demoted to the bottom club.
- So it's like a waiting number.
- Exactly.
I really don't want
to go to the bottom club.
This is sad, but I don't think
So Yeon will leave this team.
Me?
(Laughing)
When So Yeon laughs like that,
it means she swore at you.
I think so.
"You are not in a position
to say that to me."
- I guess she meant that.
- No. I'll do a good job this time.
(I'll do a good job this time.)
- What?
- She never stops.
What was that?
"I'll do a good job this time."
- "I'll do a good job this time."
- That's how So Yeon is.
- But...
- She looks so haughty,
- but she sounds so kind.
- She has an unexpected charm.
She keeps laughing.
Is it real or fake?
She's laughing for real.
She's innocent.
The mission
for the bottom club is...
Compliment on Me.
What is it about?
The six of you will lie down
with your eyes closed.
One of you will pick
a name you want...
and compliment the person.
The rest of you will hear
the compliment lying down.
And if it sounds like the compliment
is meant for you, you can get up.
If you're correct,
you get two points.
If you get it wrong,
you lose one point.
And if you don't get up when it's
for you, you also lose one point.
(If they get up when it's not
for them, they lose 1 point.)
So you should say something
that can apply to many people.
You should make the other
members lose more points.
Let's begin.
- You should sound ambiguous.
- Exactly.
I should do that
to make it to the top club.
Have you made up your mind?
Okay. You may start.
Well... First,
this person has a lot of charms.
(The person has a lot of charms.)
It's me. Don't talk about me.
It's about me.
- Gosh, it's So Min again.
- It's mine.
Se Chan is thinking
about So Min again.
(She thinks she's full of charms.)
(He's talking about me.)
- My heart is racing now.
- It's mine.
Can I get up now?
(They all try to show off
their hidden charms.)
(Laughing)
What was that? That startled me.
Her laughter makes me feel drowsy.
Exactly. It tickles my heart.
It sounds dreamlike.
This is how she starts laughing.
(Laughing)
(She has an addictive
sound of laughter.)
You should sound relaxed.
Say one more.
And...
this person's smile...
My goodness.
(This person's smile...)
(My goodness.)
The smile is a little attractive.
- Should I get up?
- Just a little?
- What should I do?
- It's not a lot.
This is crazy.
- The ranking by looks?
- Yes.
Well... My gosh.
I don't think I can say that.
- Why not?
- He can't say that.
Hang on. He can't talk about the
ranking by looks, so it's Jae Suk.
What?
Is it Jae Suk?
I think this person's appearance...
from the back...
(The person's appearance
from the back?)
What? The back hair?
- I think...
- Back hair?
I bet he's talking
about the back hair.
Hey.
He's talking about the back hair.
Are you talking about the back hair?
- If you are, it's Kwang Soo.
- I got it.
All right. One.
(It's time to get up.)
Two.
(They wouldn't budge.)
- Two.
- Is So Yeon sleeping?
(Laughing again)
Three.
(Kwang Soo gets up
with a lot of back hair.)
(Was Se Chan talking
about Kwang Soo?)
All right. It's done.
Lee Kwang Soo and Kim So Yeon
lost one point each.
What?
It was you, So Yeon.
You lost your point.
(She sees her name...)
(and feels excited.)
Why are you happy
when you lost your point?
(It looks like she won the game.)
You lost your point, So Yeon.
Oh, I see. I'm still grateful.
What is she talking about?
- Because I gave you a compliment?
- Sure.
- Because of the compliment.
- Right.
Thank you.
(She likes to be complimented.)
She gives a lot
of strange reactions.
I see. I lost the game.
Thank you, anyway.
This is so nice. Thank you.
(Excited)
It's fun to trick them.
I should get up at the right moment.
I guess I'll make the top three.
Hang on. It's So Yeon's turn.
(So Yeon is trying to pick
whom to compliment.)
(Snatching the cushion)
This round... I mean,
this round will decide...
(I think I had a cushion here.)
(After pathetically
pawing the air several times,)
(he gets up
to look for the cushion.)
I'm sure I had a cushion.
Oh, your cushion?
- Was it you?
- Yes.
You're quite irritating today.
We should take this outside.
All right.
I should give him some money.
He wants us to think he's nice.
You should pick one.
(So Yeon decided
whom to give compliments.)
(Everyone wants her to
compliment them.)
This person is...
someone I really wanted to meet.
- I see.
- My goodness.
I think Kwang Soo
is getting excited.
You're right.
- He loves this type of compliment.
- Kwang Soo.
- He loves this type of comment.
- Anything else?
- And...
any clothes look good
on this person.
Kwang Soo is a model, you know.
(This model is ready to get up.)
So anything looks good
on this person.
Unexpectedly,
this person could've been
a good student.
(Unexpectedly, this person
could've been a good student.)
(A good student?)
Kwang Soo
suddenly put his legs down.
(As he heard "a good student",
he politely put his legs down.)
It sounds like she's describing me.
Wait a minute. I think it's me.
- I'm sure it's not me.
- It sounds like me.
I really think it's about me.
Wait a minute. Do you mean that?
- I'm sure it's not me.
- Wait a minute.
The last thing is...
that my best friend...
likes this person a lot.
That's difficult to guess.
Can you tell us
who your best friend is?
- Lee Sang Woo.
- Who?
- I think I know now.
- He likes this person.
Why am I expecting it to be me?
It's possible that it's So Min.
- Stand up if you think it's you.
- All right.
1, 2, 3.
(The person who looks good in
any clothes and was a good student)
- Three!
- It's me.
- I think it's So Min.
- Yes, I think it's me.
No one else?
So Min, Suk Jin, and Se Chan
get one point deducted.
- Why me?
- It was Se Chan?
- Me?
- Why?
- It was Se Chan?
- Me?
But that's ridiculous.
That didn't sound like me at all!
He looks good in any clothes?
I look good in any clothes?
That is a lie.
I look like a smart person?
That's another lie.
- I wasn't lying!
- And her best friend.
- I really meant that.
- But he's ignorant.
It seems you would've been
a good student.
Not at all.
Shouldn't I get 1st place?
Now I'll tell you the rankings.
The person who gets to the top
of the waiting list is Jae Suk.
Good for you.
- The 2nd place goes to So Min.
- You?
- The 3rd place goes to Suk Jin.
- Yes!
The 4th place goes to Kwang Soo.
The 5th place goes to So Yeon.
The 6th place goes to Se Chan.
- I came in last.
- Se Chan is...
So Yeon got the 5th place,
but she's just happy about it.
Because I thought I'd come in last.
- I'm sorry. You came in last.
- You're a positive person.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's fine.
- My goodness.
- She's super positive.
We have to focus
on our defense because...
their 1st, 2nd, and 3rd
are too strong.
So if all of them get wrong answers,
we all can take their places?
- Yes, that's possible.
- Okay, what should we do?
If they get six wrong answers,
we can all move up.
But to be honest,
I don't want that to happen.
- Why not?
- Me neither.
Because that's impossible.
If I can't make it,
I don't want anyone to move up.
We should stop them no matter what.
If one of them comes here,
- we'll fall apart.
- Yes, we should stop them.
They're evil.
(He already betrayed
the others, so he's evil.)
Here's the mission for the top club.
It's called Lyrics Kungkungtta.
The rules of the game is
the same as Kungkungtta.
It's Kungkungtta, but you should
come up with a three-syllable word.
But the last player...
should sing at least one measure of
a song that starts with your word.
For example, if the fifth player...
says "Lee Ji Ah",
the 6th players could sing...
Ah, my beautiful land
of beautiful scenery
- So the sixth player should sing?
- Yes.
(Desire for winning
to protect the top club)
But it doesn't matter
which song, right?
Is it okay to sing
from the middle part of the song?
- It doesn't matter?
- It doesn't matter.
You can sing any part.
- Can we practice?
- Yes.
You know a lot of
Korean pop songs, right?
Yes, but only the old ones.
She must know a lot of children
songs too since she has kids.
- That's right.
- All right.
You should sit here then.
- You'll be the last player.
- Well, let's...
- Let's practice first and see.
- Okay, sit there.
- If it works, I'll stay.
- All right.
Then we'll go in this order.
- You'll move up to the top club.
- What?
- You'll move up.
- I'm sure of it.
Well, of course I'll move up.
You don't even have to say it.
My goodness, he sounds so arrogant.
Just because he came in first,
he's being arrogant.
- You came in first just this once.
- And suddenly he's arrogant.
I'm sure I'll enjoy my Korean beef.
Let's practice.
This is a practice.
- Yes, let's practice.
- All right.
Ji Ah, you go first. Go!
Squid.
- I'm sorry.
- 1, 2, squid.
(Squid)
I'm sorry, you're not
supposed to do it like that.
- Kung, kung.
- Please focus.
- You should be bouncy.
- 1, 2, squid. Like this.
- All right.
- Do it like this.
- Ready, go.
- Kung, kung, kung.
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta.
(To a novice game player Ji Ah,
the beginning part is a challenge.)
(The beginning letter is "Go".)
Hometown.
- No.
- Three syllables.
- 3 syllables.
- A 3-syllable word.
My goodness, what are you doing?
Change seats!
- You haven't played much, have you?
- Gosh, hometown?
- You should hit knees first.
- You haven't played much, have you?
Hit your knees, then clap once.
- Practice.
- Then say the word.
She says she can do this.
- Okay, let's practice.
- I won't get to say anything.
- You'll practice again?
- Yes.
- Again?
- Come on.
How many times
do they get to practice?
- Let's just begin!
- They should...
You try it then.
- Yes, let's show them then.
- All right.
- We can do this right.
- Let's see if you can succeed.
- Of course we can.
- Let's do this.
- Let's show them what we've got.
- Don't be nervous.
Ready, go.
(The top club is having trouble,
so professionals are demonstrating.)
- Go, go, go!
- Go fast.
(The beginning word is "Kang".)
Kang Ho Dong.
- Dongmakgol.
- He's giving them answers.
- How can they play so badly?
- Cardboard.
- Good.
- Earthworm.
- What was that?
Earthworm. Earthworm.
Bruce Lee.
- You say "Yong"
- That's it.
What is that?
(You say "Yong")
(He wrote a new song
while he's under pressure)
What on earth is that?
I told you this is difficult.
You say "Jung"
And get along with each other
That's what love is about
(Is this a real song?)
Is that a real song,
or are you making this up?
Hey, guys.
Why aren't you singing along?
- Why do you keep singing?
- This is a difficult game.
- It is difficult.
- Yes, this is too difficult.
Ji Ah, you're already
here to film the show.
So you have to do this.
- Lee Ji Ah, you can do this!
- Let's go!
Thank you! Yes!
You should be here again next week.
Now the real game begins.
Don't say it's a practice.
Ready, go.
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta.
Do, re, mi.
(The beginning word is "Do",
so she said, "Do, re, mi".)
Midopa.
- What? Midopa?
- Seriously?
(You're going with "Midopa"?)
- What? Midopa?
- Seriously?
But it no longer exists.
Ji Hyo.
It's a department store
from the old days.
- Midopa?
- Midopa.
She said that word before.
- She did that before.
- Ji Hyo.
(She uses the name whenever
she has to begin with "Mi".)
(Midopa)
(She still calls out the store
that existed 18 years ago.)
- I loved Midopa though.
- Stop saying the word.
- That's all you can come up with?
- All right, all right.
Lotte Shopping absorbed Midopa.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
- So Jae Suk goes to the top club.
- Congratulations.
(Jae Suk joins the top club
right from the start.)
- Congratulations.
(In the next round,)
(they keep failing.)
(So So Min and Suk Jin
get in the top club.)
They'll replace all of us.
- It's my turn.
- It's Kwang Soo's turn.
We all should stop
Kwang Soo from getting in.
- We should stop him.
- What are you talking about?
- Cheer up, guys!
- Come on!
Cheer up!
- We'll be ruined if he gets in.
- Don't say that.
So it's Kwang soo's turn to get in?
Okay.
(An important round for Kwang Soo
because it's his turn to advance)
(The beginning word is "Na".)
Na Hoon A.
Next is "A".
- Madam.
- Next is "Ma".
Malatang.
Tangsuyuk.
Yukgaejang.
Jang... Jang.
(If she succeeds, they can stop
Kwang Soo from joining the club.)
- Jang...
- Okay!
She almost made it.
I can't believe it.
This isn't a joke
We did our best.
- We did well, didn't we?
- Yes.
We're done. Lee Kwang Soo
and Jeon So Min joined.
(Ji Hyo fails in the next round, so
everyone gets out of the top club.)
So all members are changed?
Can't you let them play
a group jump rope or something?
- Look at Ji Hyo's face.
- Give them another chance.
- My goodness.
- It gets hard when you sit here.
- I'm serious.
- It wasn't a real game, was it?
So all members are changed?
- We have no other choice.
- Yes, all members are changed.
- All right.
- Let's all change seats.
The top club gets 200 dollars.
(The top club gets 200 dollars.
The bottom club gets 100 dollars.)
We should increase
the amount of our money.
- We'll get double this time.
- Be quiet if you're not paying.
We can get double,
so we should pay a lot.
We'll get double.
- This time...
- All right.
(Even if you pay only a little,
you get one-sixth of the total.)
- We'll get double this time.
- Let's do it right.
- Seriously.
- You won't pay much, right?
No, I'm going to turn in all.
I'm serious this time.
We can double it.
Let's do it right. We should...
(Kwang Soo goes up first
to pay for the lodge money.)
Here it is.
You can't look.
What are you doing?
Wait.
What are you doing there?
I can't just say it?
I should turn in the money?
I'm sure So Yeon
will be smart this time.
(They're not revealing
how much Kwang Soo gave.)
Honestly, guys. Come here.
Let's be honest.
- How much did you turn in?
- 150 dollars.
- Come on.
- I gave 150 dollars.
Don't lie to me.
Then let's turn in 100 dollars each.
We can do that, can't we?
- You can turn in 100 dollars, no?
- So Min, turn in 100 dollars.
100 dollars.
- Okay, go turn in the money.
- So Min, go.
You'll have many thoughts
on your way there.
- But don't think too hard.
- So Min, just go.
- You'll struggle, but...
- I'll hold this for you.
You should overcome it.
Just take three steps.
Don't think about anything
on your way here.
Come on, So Min.
Go turn in the money.
This is an individual race
after all.
It isn't the first time
they betrayed you.
(Encouraging her to betray them)
So Min, don't open the envelope.
I'm not opening it.
I'm really not going to open it.
I didn't open it.
I just gave the money.
Okay, 10 bills.
(Se Chan, Suk Jin, and Jae Suk
paid for the lodge money.)
They really turned it in.
(It's So Yeon's turn
to turn in her money.)
(At the first gathering,)
(she trusted the other members
and turned in all her money.)
It's 170 dollars.
(And she got betrayed.)
(So Yeon experienced the heinous
universe of Running Man.)
(If she still trusts them,
she will turn in 100 dollars again.)
(So Yeon turns in 50 dollars.)
(She turned in only 50 dollars
instead of 100.)
So Yeon, did you
turn in 100 dollars?
(The members' betrayal
has rubbed off on So Yeon.)
- We get 100 dollars, right?
- So it's 600 dollars in total.
Let's turn in 100 dollars each.
Then we will get 200 dollars each.
We have to watch Do Kwon
carefully as he turns around.
No, Do Kwon. Make sure
to turn in all your money.
This is an individual race
after all.
Do Kwon, this is
an individual race after all.
We should win.
- I'm not feeling good.
- All right.
Here.
The results are in.
- Okay.
- The top club...
- It should be more than 600.
- I guess...
- It's at least 600.
It should be at least 500 dollars.
Good.
We're the top club.
- The top club has gathered...
- It should be at least 500 dollars.
(What's the amount of the gathering
fee from the top club?)
170 dollars.
(170 dollars)
- I can't believe this.
- It's just like before.
- You guys are unbelievable.
- It's the same as before.
It doesn't matter whether we're
in the top club or the bottom club.
170 dollars.
(Even So Yeon who betrayed the
members is surprised to hear that.)
(Unbelievable)
Our team is really...
- Hey.
- We're in the top club now.
- Hey, this is...
- They gathered over 1,000 dollars!
(What's wrong with them?)
- They are so funny.
- Did So Yeon pay 100 dollars again?
How could it be 170 dollars again?
Look at your face.
You seem really upset.
- All of you look the same.
- Hey.
- Except me...
- I turned in 100 dollars.
The 5 of you turned in
70 dollars in total.
You guys are unbelievable.
You know what?
I really turned in 100 dollars.
- I turned in 100.
- That's enough.
I thought they would pay this time.
Hey, So Min. I got it.
They all say they paid.
- My gosh.
- What's wrong, So Yeon?
- What's wrong?
- You guys are so mean.
- My goodness.
- I told you, So Yeon.
We have the worst members
on this team.
- But you guys are unbelievable.
- So Yeon...
So we will double the amount
and divide it by six.
You get 60 dollars each.
(They get 60 dollars each.)
We're getting extra money anyway.
Whether I turn in 100 or 200,
I get the same amount of money.
It's always the same.
- It never changes.
- You should make it big.
- This is funny.
- We can't make it big with 60.
My gosh.
It's the bottom club now.
- They got 100 dollars each.
- 100 dollars each.
We all promised
we'd turn in all we have.
- I won't let it slide.
- There are six members.
- It's 600 dollars.
- It should be 600 dollars.
- The amount gathered is...
- It has to be 600.
(The amount gathered is...)
600 dollars.
Hey, look at that.
The bottom club
gathered 600 dollars.
So you will get 200 dollars each.
- Yes.
- Well done.
- So they got more money than us.
- It was a good plan.
(I hate you.)
It will be hard for them
to restore faith in each other.
It will be hard for them.
So whether we're in the top club
or the bottom club doesn't matter.
It's good that
the members aren't mixed up.
- I'm so glad.
- It's better this way.
(Current Amount of Gathering Fee)
Now it's time to eat lunch
at your clubhouse.
At the clubhouse,
you will find something...
that might help you
get into the penthouse.
Please make sure to look for it.
- Okay.
I'm eating instant noodles,
but I feel good.
- My gosh.
- I really turned in 100 dollars.
(The luxurious house
for the top club)
(There are various kinds
of snacks in the neat house.)
Gosh, the fridge is full of food.
(Their lunch is Korean beef
cooked by a chef.)
(In the front yard
of the top clubhouse,)
(there are 4 SUVs
with special settings.)
(Unlike the well-equipped
top clubhouse,)
(the bottom clubhouse is...)
(empty.)
(There are only a few
cup noodles in an empty tent.)
This is the 200 dollars you earned.
- Thank you.
- All right then.
- Unless we betray each other,
- things will go smoothly.
- It's really nice.
This is thick.
- I know.
- This is so good.
Can we eat cup noodles now?
You don't have
enough cup noodles now.
- What?
- You have only three.
(What did you say?)
We need at least six.
The top club has a lot.
So you should go ask them for food.
- I see.
- Or...
- They will never give us food.
- We should bring five more.
We should give these two
to our guests.
No, it's okay.
- No, it's okay.
- Please. This is for you.
- Why would you give it to Do Kwon?
- I'm not giving it to Do Kwon.
This isn't for him.
I'm not giving it to Do Kwon.
(Aren't I a guest here?)
Why would I give it to Do Kwon?
Let's give this to Ji Hyo
since she's a girl.
- And the men will go get food.
- You're so cool.
Jong Kook, it's better to send
the three women.
- You think?
- Yes.
Then let's just stay here and...
Can we share these together?
Ji Ah, you've never begged
for food in your life, right?
I'm really sorry, but you should...
bring these with you.
To get some meat.
They might have some plates there,
but just in case.
- Should we go there...
- Do Kwon. You got the money.
- So you should...
- You should go too.
Think about what you did to us.
You should go get some food.
- That's what I can do.
- Okay.
- He took it right away.
- You should go there...
and get three cup noodles
and some meat.
I'm so hungry, Se Chan.
- Come here, So Yeon. So Min.
- Okay.
The meat is so juicy.
Let me try the meat.
So Yeon, have some.
The meat tastes so good.
(The top club enjoys
their luxurious meal.)
The meat is really good.
Who cooked it?
Some chefs cooked it outside.
- Chefs?
- Are there chefs?
- Yes.
- Did they bring in chefs?
(The members who fit the bottom
club better are enjoying the food.)
- It's good, isn't it?
- It is.
By the way, Suk Jin,
did you take off your shoes...
to get in here?
Why?
(It's a filming set,
but he took off his shoes.)
We all are wearing shoes.
But you took off your shoes.
- Hey.
- He's not wearing shoes.
Why are you wearing shoes here?
So Yeon got in here
with her shoes on,
but she took them off
after seeing your feet.
(A while ago)
Should I take off my shoes?
(As Suk Jin takes off his shoes...)
What? Did they take off their shoes?
(She placed her shoes neatly
next to Suk Jin's.)
(Their shoes are
outside the carpet.)
This isn't a real house.
I just took them off
because of the carpet.
I think he's totally
immersed in our show.
If you get him a set,
he can actually live in it.
- Excuse me.
- You guys are eating already.
Did you eat cup noodles?
- We have only 3.
- We got only 3 servings.
- Really?
- It's 50 dollars per serving.
What are you talking about?
- You should pay.
- Right. Give us some money.
It's 50 dollars per serving.
(I'll give you this!)
(So Yeon shows a warm spirit
of comradeship among the frauds.)
- We should share it together.
- But we should...
What are you doing, So Yeon?
What are you doing now?
Oh Yoon Hee!
- What are you doing?
- Shim Su Ryeon.
- So Yeon.
- Ma Doo Ki.
(She holds out a plate
to her generous friend.)
So Yeon, you're...
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Can I get one ramyeon?
- Ramyeon.
- Oh, right. We need ramyeon.
- We need at least six.
- We... I know.
We need at least six.
I feel so miserable.
It's 10 dollars for 5 bowls of rice.
10 dollars
for 5 bowls of rice? Okay.
It's a deal. I'll buy
five bowls of rice.
I can spend 10 dollars for my team.
Do we really not get any food?
- Can't we eat?
- No.
I didn't even have breakfast
before coming here.
- I'm really hungry now.
- Hey, it shouldn't be too cheap.
Ji Ah, so you should
give us some money.
We need 200 dollars for this.
- This is worth 200 dollars.
- Definitely.
- My gosh.
- It's 200 dollars.
- I'm hungry. This is too expensive.
- We're eating them off.
What are you doing?
- Thank you.
- What are you doing now?
- Hey!
- What was that?
- Thank you.
- What are you doing now?
(She picks up some meat...)
(and runs away!)
- Hey, Lee Ji Ah!
- What was that?
(She begs for food
and even steals it.)
- What was that?
- My gosh.
(She's doing so many
exciting things for the first time.)
Gosh, I can't open it.
- What was that?
- Shim Su Ryeon!
- She stole the food.
- What did Ji Ah just do?
- She stole it.
- Shim Su Ryeon.
- Did she take the food?
- She just swept it.
(Su Ryeon was faster than light
stealing the meat.)
My gosh. You guys did a good job.
I paid 20 dollars for this.
- Really?
- Yes.
And this is...
- I stole it.
- She stole it.
Well done.
Very good.
It must've been your first time
to steal something.
- She stole meat on our show.
- It's so funny.
Let's be honest.
- You got some money earlier.
- Bring it here.
- Let's gather the money together.
- I didn't get any money.
Just go bring the money.
This won't do.
Se Chan got 10 dollars.
We both got 10 dollars.
This is it.
- This is from Do Kwon.
- All right then.
We all should share it,
so turn in another 10 dollars.
(We all should share it,
so turn in another 10 dollars.)
- What? That sounds strange.
- 10 dollars.
- We should make it 60 dollars.
- We need 60 dollars.
- Turn in 10 dollars.
- It should be 60 dollars.
We should make it 60 dollars.
We all turned in 10 dollars each.
- How much is it now?
- Give me that.
- Why?
- Why did you get the money?
- I told you to turn in 10 dollars.
- I did.
Suk Jin, give me 10 dollars.
- Okay. I'll turn in 10 dollars.
- All right.
But why?
To make it a divisible amount.
Where's my money? What?
- Darn it.
- What?
Who is it?
- My goodness.
- You have no money?
- I can't believe this.
- Do you not have money?
You were wearing the bag.
Hey, who was that?
I didn't do it.
- Who did it?
- What?
- It's not me.
- I can't be on this team.
- This team...
- This is unbelievable.
My gosh.
- I didn't do it.
- Who did this?
How is this happening?
We're a team though.
Eat your meat and calm down.
- How...
- Do you not have any money?
Jae Suk, if he has no money,
he should be out.
If he can't pay the fee, he's out.
- Hang on.
- You have money here.
- You have.
- Just turn in your money.
- Turn it in.
- But this is...
(He lost most of his money
and has only a few bills left.)
(He lost about 300 dollars.)
- You have it there.
- You have some.
Darn it.
Who would take your money?
You're mistaken.
Who took my money?
- You have your money.
- Why would you slander others?
Here's 60 dollars
that you earned earlier.
- Oh, right. I forgot about that.
- Yes.
(They receive the lodge money
they earned.)
Who on earth did that? Hey.
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo, was it you?
- No. You were carrying the bag.
- Is my name written here?
When could I steal it?
- It wasn't me. Believe me.
- Why can't you look me in the eye?
I caught you trying to
steal his money.
- You heard me... Suk Jin.
- You were carrying it.
You heard what I said to So Min,
didn't you?
(While continuing
the meaningless interrogation...)
What about mine?
I gave all the envelopes.
- We all received the money.
- Give me my money.
- She just distributed the money.
- What are you doing?
- Gosh, seriously.
- What is wrong with him?
What is wrong with you?
- Who took two envelopes?
- I don't know what happened.
Who took two envelopes?
- Come on. Give me mine.
- Who did that? I took only one.
- It wasn't me. It wasn't me.
- Give me my money now.
- Who took all the envelopes?
- It really wasn't me.
- Who distributed the envelopes?
- "You brats."
- You brats. I won't let it slide.
- I can't believe this.
- Who on earth...
- Hey, listen.
Who took all the envelopes
right in front of everyone?
- That's impossible.
- Listen. I gave one for each.
- Who did that?
- How could you take it?
- Who took it?
- Hey.
(No one took it, but his money
disappeared like magic.)
(This is what really happened.)
(Se Chan took 4 envelopes!)
(Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
took 1 envelope each.)
(Se Chan gave 1 to So Min...)
(and 1 to So Yeon.)
(He put the 2 remaining envelopes
in his bag!)
(The protruding mouth thief
stole from the original thief.)
- And he received one, right?
- Just give him back his money.
So there should be four envelopes.
- How many do you have?
- Just give him his money.
- I have three.
- You should give it to him now.
Think of how old Suk Jin is.
- Hey, give it to him.
- Think of my age, seriously.
- I'm not even wearing shoes now.
- Suk Jin is...
- Darn it.
- He's... Listen.
He's the second oldest
after Immortal Chan Hee.
- And you guys...
- Give it to him now.
He's a legend.
- You guys...
- He's a legend.
Why won't you immerse yourselves
in your roles? You're wearing shoes.
We're shooting in an indoor set!
- Hold on. This is...
- Just give me my money now.
- Give me one dollar each.
- It wasn't me.
This is driving me crazy.
(The lunch break is over while
Suk Jin is looking for the thief.)
We'll begin the second missions
starting with the bottom club.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Before we begin, I think
we all should keep it together.
- Absolutely.
- We should really turn in money.
- You shouldn't steal others' money.
- Someone actually did that.
- Who stole it?
- Someone stole money?
Yes, it really happened.
Suk Jin's money he kept in his bag
disappeared.
While I was trying to figure out
who stole my money,
my share of the lodge money...
Do you know the only good thing...
- about being on our team?
- What is it?
You know that we steal from
and lie to each other, right?
But we never question each other
so persistently.
We give up before we find out
who did it.
- It's so great.
- We always...
The bottom club will be the 1st team
to complete the 2nd mission.
- Okay.
(1st, Eugene, 2nd, Lee Ji Ah,
3rd, Kim Jong Kook)
(4th, Song Ji Hyo, 5th, Haha,
6th, Ha Do Kwon)
I'll explain the rule of
the top club's last mission.
- Okay.
The top club's second mission is...
It's Dangerous Outside the Blanket.
It's dangerous indeed.
Each of the six of you will take
turns. Throw the blanket in the air,
and lie down under it properly
to succeed.
(It's a success if the blanket
covers more than 2-3rd of the body.)
- Each of us will do it?
- Yes.
Isn't it too easy?
- Your lower body must be covered.
- It sounds easy.
If you succeed 6 out of 10 times,
all of you will remain on the team.
- It sounds...
- I think we can do this.
- You'll be eliminated after that.
It's okay if the feet are
outside the blanket, right?
No, the feet must be
under the blanket.
- The upper body is okay?
- Yes.
Your legs and belly must be
under the blanket.
- We can do this!
- Let's go!
- Let's all finish it at one try.
- Okay.
Let's complete the mission
in six attempts.
And we all submit 200 dollars.
Gosh, I'm so sick of it.
All right. Here we go.
Throw the blanket and follow it
to lie down.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Watching the blanket?
- Exactly.
- You'll watch how it moves?
- Would you be able to see it?
- Of course.
(- Would you be able to see it?
- Of course.)
You won't have enough time for that.
I'll have enough time.
- The blanket will fall fast.
- It's because you're weak.
- I can move fast, you know.
- Indeed.
I can move as fast as you can.
Even though I'm weak,
I'm not as weak as you are.
- It's because you're so weak.
- I can do as well as you do.
- I'm not as weak as you are.
- I can move fast.
- No. I'm much stronger than you.
- You're weaker than me.
Even though I'm weak,
I'm not as weak as you are.
- I can do as well as you.
- You're not as fast as me.
Here they go again.
It's like an online video.
Let's subscribe.
The blanket won't wait for you.
- No, but I'll make it wait.
- You can't move that fast.
- How are you going to do that?
- Here I go. Throw it high.
(Jae Suk, the 1st person to try
who boasts his speed)
The blanket should float.
Throw it lightly. That's good.
(Jae Suk threw
the blanket lightly.)
(Will he succeed
for the 1st time on his team?)
- He succeeded.
- Oh, no.
(Jae Suk failed.)
- It's dangerous outside of it.
- It's as not easy as it sounds.
- It doesn't seem easy.
- It's not so easy.
Gosh, it's not easy.
Should he have moved
toward the back a little?
- It moved in that direction.
- The position was wrong.
Kwang Soo, you must succeed.
The position was wrong.
(The speed enthusiast failed
in his 1st attempt.)
Don't lie on your belly.
You should lie on your back.
- Lie on your back while sliding.
- Exactly.
You should listen to him.
I'm so nervous.
The key is to make the blanket
fall straight down.
- Keep your head up.
- That's right.
Good. He's being cautious.
Kwang Soo, don't lie on your belly.
He'll lie on his back and cry
because he gets poked by his mic.
(He's moving the blanket
with care and affection.)
- That's good.
- Kwang Soo,
you look as if you're making a bed
for Zo In Sung.
(You look as if you're making a bed
for Zo In Sung.)
What... Hang on a second.
Why would you bring him up
when we're playing a game?
- That's what it looks like.
- Why would I make a bed for him?
You would do that for him
if you two go on a trip together.
- I wouldn't do that.
- Kwang Soo,
making a bed for In Sung...
- wouldn't be so embarrassing.
- Right. Do it for him.
- He didn't tell you to wash it.
- Right.
Think that In Sung is lying here,
and you're covering him...
- with that blanket.
- Why...
Understood? In Sung is lying here.
Cover him with the blanket.
- Sleep well, In Sung.
- That's good.
(He's on butler mode.)
Cover him with the blanket.
That's good.
He did it.
(Kwang Soo spread the blanket
carefully using his imagination.)
(Will he succeed
thanks to the imagination?)
(He threw the blanket well.)
(And he lied down quickly.)
(His feet are outside the blanket.)
Did you see that?
- Your feet should be covered.
- It's because he has long legs.
It's because he's tall.
His head is right here.
- His feet should be covered too?
- It's because he's tall.
- The blanket is too small.
- What kind of rule is that?
But you did a good job because you
thought In Sung was here.
- I'll go next. I'll do it.
- What a shame.
- So Min.
- Suk Jin... Okay.
Good. That's how it should be done.
You should make it float high. Yes.
- Go under it quickly.
- She did it.
(So Min threw it boldly
and rushed under it.)
- He almost succeeded.
- She did it.
(Plopping down)
(She's lying on the floor
without the blanket over her body.)
- So Min, you might catch a cold.
- Good job.
- Great job.
- Cover yourself with the blanket.
- You did well.
- Good job.
- I've been saved.
- Many of us will move to that team.
- That was funny.
- My gosh.
- It was going well.
At least 1 or 2 of us
should be out of our team.
- I agree.
- Some of us should be eliminated.
- We should change members.
- He almost succeeded.
- It's So Yeon's turn now.
- She'll do well.
I'll give it a try!
- I have a feeling she'll succeed.
- I'll give it a try!
(Will she be able to succeed
unlike the other members?)
(So Yeon gives it a try.)
I have a feeling
that she'll succeed.
(Giggling)
(She slipped
while standing on the same spot.)
- What just happened?
- Wait.
- That doesn't count.
- That doesn't count as an attempt.
- She didn't start.
- That doesn't count.
- Jong Kook, please.
- What did you do?
- So Yeon, what happened?
- That doesn't count.
Why? So Yeon, did you slip?
- She didn't start.
- She'll do it now.
- She slipped.
- Obviously, that wasn't an attempt.
- She slipped. It's okay.
- Listen.
- You slipped, right?
- I was so surprised.
- She was surprised.
- Let's ask her.
I'll ask her. So Yeon,
did you start or not?
- I... I didn't start.
- That's right.
- She didn't start.
- You can start now.
She didn't start.
She was surprised too.
- The blanket slipped off her hands.
- That's right.
- She dropped it.
- It's because she was taken aback.
- We'll give her another chance.
- Thank you.
- It's understandable.
- Yes.
- So Yeon, you should go under it.
- You're doing well.
- I'll give it a try now.
- Okay.
- Okay. Good.
- So Yeon, go under it.
Go under the blanket. Go.
My goodness.
(Sitting straight down)
- My goodness.
- No. That's not how you do it.
(Dumbfounded)
- So Yeon, listen.
- Is she serious?
- Put your head on this side.
- You see...
- Your head should be on this side.
- This is ridiculous.
- You tried to do that, right?
- So Yeon, try one more time.
She didn't lie down
when we told her to.
She didn't play the recorder
when she was supposed to.
- We'll give her 5 more chances.
- Try 1 more time.
- Try just 1 more time.
- So Yeon, try again.
- Gosh.
It's not that she's not good at it.
She doesn't understand the rule.
- Your head should be on this side.
- So Yeon, you should...
- Why can't I...
- move forward. That'd be better.
- I see. Then I throw the blanket,
- You should go under it.
go to this side, and lie down
like this...
- No, no. That's not it.
- You should just...
- And lie down like this...
- No, no.
- You can lie on your belly too.
- Just lie down like this.
- So Yeon, that's how it's done.
- You can do that too.
Go under the blanket.
- Lie on your belly.
- Right. Lie on your belly.
Like diving.
(Rushing forward)
My gosh.
(Like this?)
So Yeon. So Yeon.
Go back. You should say you'll
start before you begin.
Say you'll start
before you begin, okay?
- So Yeon, it was okay.
- It's okay.
Say you'll start before you begin.
- I don't know how to do it.
- You did well.
- Just lie down.
- You should lie on the floor.
- With your head on the pillow.
- Exactly.
- This bag is so uncomfortable.
- That's good.
(The magic to summon thieves)
- No, no.
- This bag is so uncomfortable.
(So Yeon runs to the staff
avoiding the thieves.)
Please watch my bag.
- You can put it there.
- Okay.
So Yeon, I think you should
carry your bag.
- I can't.
- In front of the camera...
- You would steal it anyway.
- The last attempt. Say, "Start".
I'll start.
She made it.
- What?
- I can't see her.
- What's going on?
- Where did she go?
(1 of the tiger moths gets excited
as So Yeon is under the blanket.)
(She's stealing
a mission fund envelope quickly.)
- That's crazy.
- She might think we did that.
- Look what So Min is doing.
- Look at her.
- What? Hey!
- Look what So Min is doing.
Hey! I mean, excuse me.
- Wait. Stop. That's my money.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Goodness gracious.
- That's funny.
My goodness. I can't believe this.
(So Yeon found her bag with her
triple combination reaction.)
Five members.
- 5 of you should be replaced.
- 5 members?
If five members should be replaced,
So Yeon should remain on the team.
Okay.
- Do Kwon.
- Let's go.
Finally, we eliminated Do Kwon.
Good riddance.
I think Do Kwon will
complete our team.
I belong to this team.
(He thinks
he belongs to the other team too.)
I belong to this team.
I can't believe we all are
on the same team.
All the trustworthy people
gathered this time.
- Let's increase our mission funds.
- Welcome, So Yeon.
I can't believe we all are
on the same team.
I ended up
being Jong Kook's enemy again.
Let's all turn the full amount in
this time.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo.
- Suk Jin, turn in all the money.
- Okay. I'll do that.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
If we don't turn the full amount in,
we won't be able to win.
We must increase our mission funds
because they have more money.
Let's all turn the whole envelope in
this time.
- Or else, we can't win.
- We can't turn the game around.
We should turn all the money in.
Don't be greedy and turn it in.
- Let's turn it in.
- Let's do that.
All right. I'll announce the amount
of the top club.
- Our team?
- Yes.
I hope someone on that team
betrayed the others.
Each member received 200 dollars.
The total amount of money
you turned in is...
- 1,200 dollars.
- Okay!
(They turned 1,200 dollars in.)
That's perfect.
- Without Do Kwon here...
- Nice.
So this is how it feels.
She said, "So this is how it feels."
How much did we collect?
- You each received 100 dollars.
- Right.
- The total would be 600 dollars.
- Exactly.
Please...
You collected 130 dollars.
- What?
- 130 dollars?
(The bottom club
only has 130 dollars?)
- What?
- 130 dollars?
But I handed in 100 dollars.
- You guys are awful.
- I handed in 100 dollars.
- Suk Jin...
- I'm telling the truth.
- I handed in 100 dollars.
- No, I did.
I handed in the entire envelope.
I did too.
You won't be able
to win that way though.
It's more than I thought.
I'm guessing that
everyone handed in...
about a dollar or two.
Do Kwon must've paid up.
I doubt it.
The top club receives
400 dollars each...
while the bottom club
receives 40 dollars each.
(400 dollars each for the top club,
40 dollars each for the bottom club)
Nice.
That's more than I thought
the bottom club would collect.
Shortly, the briefing session
for residency...
regarding the move to the penthouse
will begin.
You are all to attend it...
after a short break
at your respective lounges.
Okay!
(Who will get to move
into the penthouse?)
This is the worst.
We're on a different level
with the other club.
(The clubs get to enjoy a break.)
It's so cool that
we all stuck together.
I'm curious as to how much I have.
I don't know how this money
will come into play,
but we each have a hefty amount.
I love the proud expression
Ji Ah holds...
when counting her money.
- Her fake money.
- Right, her fake money.
- She absolutely loves it.
- She's so different from...
when we met her in the beginning
of the show.
(She shows off her fake money.)
(It wasn't easy to earn
amidst the hyenas.)
She's showing off.
There really is a lot.
It'll take a while to count.
(Quietly, they all
count their money.)
Look at you all
cherishing your fake money.
It's useless at home, but still.
It's just paper once filming ends.
(At this moment though,
they couldn't be happier.)
The other club won
at least 300 dollars each.
Darn it.
It doesn't matter though...
- because only four get to win.
- The others will receive a penalty.
(Glancing)
(Jae Suk keeps
glancing to the side.)
(Boxes in the corner)
(They heard of items in the lounge
that could help them win.)
(Those boxes were there
since lunch.)
(Eugene was also
suspicious of them at one point.)
Hold on.
I'm starving. Se Chan?
- I want a latte.
- A latte?
(Jae Suk spotted the same boxes
in the top club lounge as well.)
(Will those boxes
help them get into the penthouse?)
What are these?
What are those?
(Something's on them.)
They're empty boxes.
(He chooses to lie for now.)
(He then hides one in his jacket.)
(Jae Suk discreetly
brings out a box...)
(that obviously seems
like a clue to the race.)
(What is the box
that Jae Suk spotted?)
A cell phone for
the penthouse resident.
(A box sent from the penthouse?)
(He urgently opens the box.)
(In the box are 3 phones
for penthouse residents.)
What's this?
(In the box are 3 phones
for penthouse residents.)
"Bring two others
to the waiting room."
(The 3 of you must come discreetly
with these phones.)
(He's to form a group of 3
and go to the waiting room.)
(He must bring 2 members
without the others knowing.)
Where is everyone?
- Our team's a mess.
- Right?
- You don't have enough money.
- Right.
- So why don't you...
- Hey.
If someone was to use yours...
My gosh.
- What is it?
- Let's go.
- Where?
- There's no time. Hurry.
- Where are we going?
- Hurry up.
Why? What is it?
(He runs off without explaining.)
(Kwang Soo)
Jae Suk?
(Kwang Soo spots
the 3 of them running.)
(So Min sees them too.)
Give me the money.
(The 3 enter,
heads filled with doubt.)
Give me the money.
I want the money.
- You can't.
- Give me the money, Jae Suk.
Can you stay outside?
- The money...
- Me too?
- Just a second.
- I just want the money.
What's this about?
- I...
- What's going on?
I just...
- Let me close the door for now.
- Guys...
- You'll go next.
- Next...
- You'll get your turn next.
(What secret lies
within this container?)
- What's going on?
- Congratulations.
- Lock the door.
- Just a second.
Did he just congratulate us?
You see... Guys, hold on a second.
What on earth?
(While the staff tried
frantically to get inside...)
Guys, hold on a second.
(Cameraman Kwang Soo
entered without permission.)
What on earth?
Seriously?
- You...
- Why?
- Get out!
- What is this about?
- But...
- Get out!
- I had no idea.
My gosh.
- Get out.
- Get out!
(Kwang Soo's left with a camera
and unresolved questions.)
There was something on the door.
- What's this?
- Here.
Congratulations. You found the key
that is needed for the final race.
The final race will take place
in another location.
In order to compete,
you must go there...
and submit your application.
- Just the application?
- Yes.
You will now be given access...
to a digital key.
You must work together
in order to get to the location.
What you'll have access to
will be chosen randomly.
You've got to be kidding me.
(The 3 commands provided are
unlocking the doors,)
(starting the car,)
(and opening the trunk.)
They will be chosen randomly.
We'll each receive
access to something.
Each envelope...
contains a different command.
Choose one each...
and show me.
- Can we take a look?
- Sure.
I can start the car.
Then, I'll give Jae Suk
access first.
- Can't you just leave us?
- What's going on?
(The two tiger moths barge in.)
What is this all about?
- Get out.
- Get out for now.
- It's in turns. We go first.
- What do you mean?
- Just leave for now.
- You three can come back.
- You three can be a team.
- The three of you are next.
- Right.
We all get our turns.
- Can you close the door?
- Get out.
- Let me give you access.
- What did you get?
I can start the car.
I can unlock the doors.
I can open the trunk.
I'll first give Jae Suk access
to the car ignition switch.
- Is this a digital key?
- Yes, let me send give you access.
Can this really be done?
- What on earth?
- From our smartphones?
(Access will be granted
to the 3 smartphones in the box.)
I get it now.
You'll start the car,
- I'll open the door and...
- What about the trunk?
There must be something in it.
Jae Suk, you'll be allowed
to start the car.
- Is this really possible?
- It's done.
You can start the car
using that phone.
I get to unlock the doors.
Suk Jin, you have been
given access to the door lock.
I got the access.
I get to open the trunk.
(Suk Jin can unlock the door
and Se Chan can open the trunk.)
You have each been given access.
For your information,
the location of the race...
can be found in the trunk.
- Then let's go.
- Only the one who can open it...
will be able to check the address.
- We'll each play our role.
- Let's go.
(The 3 hurry out.)
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and Se Chan
take the first car.)
Team up with the others.
- Go in there.
- Get what you need in there.
Team up with the others.
Go in there.
(Kwang Soo goes with them.)
(What's going on?)
Kwang Soo, you're not with us.
- Kwang Soo!
- You're not to join us.
Hurry up and team up with the rest.
- Why?
- Get what you need.
- Let's go.
- You need access.
No, you can't.
You should get your own.
Kwang Soo.
- Hurry up.
- Get your own phone.
Don't ruin the advertisement
unless you'll pay up yourself!
(Kwang Soo isn't allowed
to access the car.)
- Unlock the door.
- How do I do it?
This must be it.
Yes, that. Okay, we're good.
Get going. I'll start the car.
Do it.
(He opens the trunk.)
- I got it.
- You did?
- Where's the location?
- I'll get in the car.
Now, start the car.
(Jae Suk gets the car running.)
- We're good.
- It's done.
Ilsanseo-gu, Goyang,
Gyeonggi Province.
(They manage to get in the car
by teaming up.)
Ilsanseo-gu, Goyang,
Gyeonggi Province.
- I'll get going for now.
- Sure.
We got lucky.
- Because we...
- I happened to run into you two.
Will there be a mission
at the location?
- Probably.
- Right.
Getting there first
will give us an advantage.
(What'll be the final race
that they'll face?)
I wouldn't have known
had it not been for Jae Suk.
- I know.
- Goyang.
What's going on?
I was on my way back
from the restroom.
You need to find the clue first.
- The clue? Where?
- Yes.
You need to meet
the conditions first.
You must find the clue.
That's not it.
(She tries to reuse
the card the others left behind.)
What...
I mean...
Are you kidding me?
(Frustration sweeps over
those left behind.)
We need to get in this car.
I'm sure there's a hint somewhere.
(The top club can't even hear
the commotion outside.)
- There's a lot.
- We probably all have enough.
(They're just satisfied
with what they earned.)
(Kwang Soo enters.)
Kwang Soo's here.
- What's wrong?
- What's the matter?
- What?
- You hid money here.
- Did you hide your money here?
- No, that's not it...
You must've hidden your money here.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
Did you hide your money here?
- No, that's not it.
- Yes?
Let me see. Then what?
(What is he looking for?)
The treasure hunt begins.
- What's going on?
- What is it?
What are you looking for?
(The ladies of the top club
are still clueless.)
(They've come to search for the clue
that's obviously here too.)
Should we get looking too?
Is something here?
What's he looking for?
(Did he find the box?)
(Jong Kook found...)
(the delivery boxes!)
(He takes all three
without getting caught.)
(However...)
(Kwang Soo finds him.)
What am I supposed to do with these?
What am I supposed to do?
- Hold on.
- Give me that!
(Kwang Soo manages to secure a box.)
Kwang Soo...
What on earth...
What's going on?
What is it? What's going on?
Hold on a second.
What just happened?
Why did Kwang Soo
take it away from me?
Give it to me. What is it?
I don't understand.
I've been meaning to open this box.
"Bring two others
to the waiting room."
"Bring the phone in the box."
"The three of you must come
discreetly with these phones."
- To go there secretly...
- It's too late for that.
- You already revealed it.
- I read it out loud. What do I do?
"Bring two others..."
What was that?
(He overheard the hidden mission
and became taken aback.)
A box?
- Let's hurry up and go.
- To where?
Where is
the container waiting room?
(The 3 actresses teamed up at once
thanks to Eugene.)
Where is it?
Where is the container?
I think this is it.
(The actresses entered
the container.)
What is this?
- Oh, my.
- Please close the door.
Congratulations. You obtained
the keys for the final mission.
We'll give the three of you
the access...
to digital keys you'll need
to move to another location.
- I see.
- "Unlock the doors".
- "Open the trunk".
- Kim So Yeon.
Okay. Thanks.
What's this?
They really don't tell us anything.
Exactly. I mean,
we could've done nothing
if we hadn't found this.
True. We owe it all to you, Eugene.
- We made it to this container.
- Thank you, Eugene.
I wasn't thinking about anything
while eating jellies.
I was eating cookies too.
(Overwhelmingly excited)
Now...
(They use the access
to move to the final race location.)
9.9km.
Oh, wow. This is amazing.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo hasn't
teamed up yet.)
- So Min...
- Don't bring her onto our team.
Wouldn't it be better
if she was on our team?
- Would it be better?
- Please take me with you.
Wouldn't it be better with her?
- Don't you think?
- So Min?
Oh, with this?
We can start the car
using this application?
You can unlock the doors with this?
- We don't need a key?
- I can open the trunk with this?
I won't believe it
until I see it with my own eyes.
When you're on Running Man,
you must not trust anyone
to the last minute.
You're not disappointed, right?
Of course, I'm not.
I should get used to it.
In the world
with people with one eye,
- a person with two eyes is odd.
- Exactly.
(Team Jae Suk, Team So Yeon,
Team So Min, Team Haha)
The teams that left earlier
have an advantage.
I think we left much earlier
than the other teams.
I saw you as soon as I got out.
Suk Jin, you got so lucky.
- I know, right?
- You were the first one I saw.
We got so lucky.
All the comedians gathered.
- Exactly.
- You're right.
- It's about time the comedians...
- We were the first team to leave.
joined our forces.
- Exactly.
- It's been a long time.
Oh, right. We're the only comedians
among the cast members.
- Exactly.
- I feel so confident with you two.
I didn't realize that.
By the way, I don't know
what we'll do later,
- we don't have much money now.
- True.
- We don't have much money.
- We can't beat the other teams.
We can't beat them with our money.
We just have to find the penthouse
before the other teams do, right?
Yes.
- This is it.
- Right. I see the camera.
- We're here. Are we the first?
- We're the first to arrive.
Okay. Let's go.
(The application submission table
is right in front of them.)
We're here.
(They're rushing into the building
as the other teams are coming too.)
(But at that moment)
(Se Chan took off
Suk Jin's name tag.)
Suk Jin, you can't move
for three minutes.
Why did you do that?
It wasn't like that.
- Hey.
- There was a hidden rule for me.
(There was a hidden rule
for Se Chan?)
Okay. It's open.
(Se Chan opened the trunk
to check the address.)
(He found 2 cards in the trunk!)
(Only 2 of each team can submit
the application.)
(Take off the name tag of 1 person
after you arrive at the location.)
"Take off the name tag
of one person..."
"after you arrive at the location."
(Only the people in charge
of the trunk know about this rule.)
(Se Chan read the address,
not the hidden mission card.)
- That's it?
- Yes.
Okay. We're ready.
(Se Chan understood
the hidden mission at once.)
(He distracted them saying
they should join their forces...)
(while making a plan
to eliminate Suk Jin.)
My gosh, Yangsebari.
The hidden mission card was
in the trunk?
I'll write down my name.
Jae Suk and Se Chan,
you may move into the penthouse...
40 minutes later.
Two members on the team can
submit the application.
And you may move
into the penthouse...
exactly 40 minutes
after you submit the application.
That means members from each team
will move in at different hours.
However, if you try to enter
the penthouse...
before the time comes,
you may be eliminated
by the security guards.
The four people
who enter the penthouse...
at the right time
before the others will win.
And the bottom four
among the ones who failed...
to move into the penthouse will be
the candidates for the penalty.
(The bottom 4 will be
the candidates for the penalty.)
You can take off the name tag
of another member...
to send the person to the prison.
The person who is sent
to the prison...
can revive using his or her
mission fund,
but the move-in time will be
delayed 10 minutes.
You can't revive if you don't have
enough mission fund,
and you'll be eliminated
from the race.
- Check the time on the clock.
- Yes.
Write down
the time of submission too.
5:57 p.m.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan's move-in time
is 6:37 p.m.)
- Three minutes have passed, right?
- Yes.
I'll wait here.
(He has no choice but to wait
for the next team to come.)
Until someone arrives.
- Where are we going in the dark?
- Exactly.
I didn't know everyone would be
this enthusiastic.
(She respects
their professionalism.)
They all seemed so serious.
All of them are so good at this.
- I think you're the best, So Yeon.
- That's not true.
I think you and Eugene are
better than me.
Don't you think we've been doing...
- a lot of unusually tiring things?
- I think so.
I think so too.
I feel like I'm going to faint.
I'm mentally exhausted.
(She feels like she'll get sick
in 5 seconds.)
I feel like having a drink.
(The true charm of Running Man,
it makes you crave alcohol.)
I think I'll sleep deeply tonight.
(They're on their way
while trying to keep it together.)
Ji Ah, you shouldn't have
eaten those cookies earlier.
- Cookies?
- Yes. The cookies you ate.
- Oh, that.
- Could you turn off the music?
- What?
- She asked to turn off the music.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
They must be listening to us.
That's scary.
- Where are they?
- Oh, my. How?
Oh, we're wearing microphones.
Oh, I remember.
When I was on "We Got Married",
there was always a van
in front of us whenever we drove.
Are you saying they're watching us
in the van?
I think that's the case.
(Surprised)
Hello.
None of us knows anything
about a variety show.
What should we do in the car?
(They've been learning a lot
on Running Man.)
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin is waiting
hopelessly.)
One of them will take off
the name tag of someone else.
So I can just take off that person's
name tag when he or she does that.
(It's a keen analysis as he majored
in business management in college.)
Please come out.
Yes, you can come out.
- We're not shooting right now.
- Why haven't you been eliminated?
- Pardon me?
- I'll be out later.
- Really?
I got eliminated and then revived.
(Giggling)
(While Suk Jin is meeting
his fans unexpectedly...)
There they come. That's it.
(They're arriving peacefully
without knowing what will happen.)
Hey!
- Hi.
- He must've recognized me.
- He could've said hi to me.
- Who is he?
He wants us to stop here?
He's one the cast members.
(Suk Jin is approaching them
calmly.)
The three of you came together.
- Who started the car?
- I did.
Who opened the trunk? You did?
- What else?
- I opened the doors.
- You opened the doors.
- Shouldn't we bring the phones too?
We should bring our phones.
(The signal is being transmitted.)
(He's giving a signal to Eugene
who knows about the hidden mission.)
(They exchanged signals secretly.)
Let's go.
You came later than I thought.
- They told us to follow them.
- The traffic was bad.
I used to come here
to shoot a drama.
(Eugene, take off Ji Ah's name tag.)
Ji Ah, you're very tired, right?
- Here... I'm fine.
- You're very tired, right?
- You want to go home, don't you?
- No.
(Taking off the name tag)
What's going on?
(But Suk Jin eliminated Eugene
at the same time!)
- What's going on?
- Come here. Hurry up.
- Wait.
- You can come with me.
Why is this allowed?
Come on. Hurry up. Don't worry.
Are we allowed to eliminate...
- other teams' member?
- I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
You can just wait here and eliminate
another team's member.
- What?
- Just like I did.
- I got eliminated just like you.
- Gosh. This is unfair.
- This is so unfair.
- Okay.
- I have no idea.
- Sorry.
Can we take off
others' name tags now?
Please write down
the arrival time here.
(3 minutes later, Eugene and Ji Ah
submitted the application too.)
(Ji Ah and Eugene's move-in time is
6:58 p.m.)
I can't keep it together.
Maybe I should walk backward.
What should I do?
Should I wear the jacket backward?
(She's extremely nervous as this is
her 1st name tag elimination.)
I'm so nervous.
(Ji Ah is as nervous as So Yeon.)
I feel as if someone is
following me.
It's scary.
- Is that Eugene?
- After getting eliminated once...
Is that Ji Ah? Oh, my goodness.
There's no way they will
eliminate me.
They won't do that
since I was on their team.
My goodness. Ji Ah.
(Ji Ah found So Yeon!)
Ji Ah, stop. What's wrong with you?
Ji Ah. Ji Ah, come on.
Shim Su Ryeon. Shim Su Ryeon!
(The war to move into the penthouse
has begun.)
Ji Ah, don't do that.
Don't take off my name tag.
No, you can't do that. No.
(Take off others' name tags
to delay their move-in time!)
Stop it.
Ji Ah, please.
(Ji Ah, calm down.)
Hold on. There will be other people.
I will rip off your name tag.
Hold on, Ji Ah.
Let's not betray each other
when we get there.
Of course not.
We should join forces until the end.
Let's do that.
Seriously.
Let's do that until the end.
- I trust you guys.
Let's trust each other
for coexistence.
(So Yeon becomes even more nervous
after a crisis.)
(Startled)
My gosh.
(She spots Se Chan.)
Hello.
(Suk Jin, So Yeon, and Se Chan meet
with a wall between them.)
When did you get here?
- When did you get here?
- I got here the second.
- The second?
- Yes. When did you get here?
- What?
- When did you get here?
- Us?
- Yes.
We got here the third.
- Did you just get here?
- Yes.
(He is like a lynx.)
There is no one behind you.
Really?
In that case...
(At that moment, Suk Jin attacks!)
(Screaming)
(Ripping off)
(Professional name tag hunters
took out So Yeon.)
- Out?
- Yes.
Look at her reactions.
I had to buy time.
I am sorry. I had to buy time.
- Where do I go? Here?
- Yes. Please go inside.
Okay.
- I am sorry.
- For goodness' sake.
My wish came true today.
I should stay here.
That's hilarious.
I mean...
All three of us got
our name tags removed by Suk Jin.
What should I do?
All right.
What could it be?
When you are in jail,
you can use the mission fund
to purchase a revival pass.
I see.
A revival pass costs 300 dollars.
My goodness.
Every time you use a revival pass,
the price increases by 50 dollars.
Then I will end up using
all of my mission funds.
A revival pass.
(Thankfully, she could purchase
a revival pass!)
Thank you.
I will be back. "I will be back"?
(So Yeon's move-in time
got pushed back by 10 minutes.)
Gosh, the time is...
Why is the time passing so slowly?
Someone is here. Who is it?
It's me, Jae Suk.
A member of Team Comedians.
All right.
The three of us should join forces
and enter together.
- Jae Suk.
- What do you think?
(Suk Jin suggests
that the comedians win together.)
- What should we do?
- What?
Should we take out Jae Suk?
Let's take out Jae Suk once.
- Let's do a cheer first.
- Okay.
Let's take out Jae Suk.
Let's do that.
- The 3 of us...
- We can move in 1st.
can join forces
and take out anyone who comes near.
Then we can win.
In terms of the move-in time,
we are 1st, 2nd, and 3rd.
- I know.
- Are you first?
- We are.
- The two of you are the same.
- We are the same.
- We are first.
Ripping off someone's name tag
delays him or her by 10 minutes.
- 10 minutes?
- We can continue to do that...
and move in together
at the perfect timing.
We had a heartwarming conversation
in the car.
It's the first time
the comedians came together.
Let's do this.
We should keep a safe distance.
- Give me your hand.
- Seriously.
- The first time on Running Man.
- That's right.
- I learned when we came together...
that there are three comedians
on the show.
- I had no idea.
- Suk Jin.
- The seniors and a junior.
- Haha is a singer.
We should have a gathering.
- Yes.
- We should really do that.
Suk Jin, you should figure out
a time to meet.
Please do that.
You should do it
since you are the youngest.
Shall we put our arms
around each other?
(He makes a sudden suggestion.)
- Hold on.
- This time...
It sounds like he wants to betray
the comedians.
Suk Jin, is your bad habit
getting the better of you?
It's a trust exercise.
I can show my back to you.
- But it's too...
- I can do it.
Suk Jin. It's too much.
- Putting arms around each other...
- As a sign of trust,
- Team Comedians.
let's put arms around each other
and hold for five seconds.
- Really?
- Let's do it.
- Aren't you planning something?
- We will keep our palms open.
- Okay.
- Like this?
- Let's put arms around each other.
- I held his arm.
I will have to do the same.
(Grabbing)
- Suk Jin.
- Don't do that.
Why do you want to put your hand
on my back?
(The tables are turned.)
Rip it off.
(Ripping)
(He gets punished mercilessly.)
I can't believe them.
- My goodness.
- What is your problem?
- The two of you...
No. We were trying...
- to join forces.
- Seriously.
- Why did you do that?
- You made us suspicious.
It wasn't like that.
It was a trust exercise.
For goodness' sake.
Suk Jin, you are out.
All right. For goodness' sake.
What is up with the alarm?
It's time for me to go.
- You guys...
- Suk Jin, we are sorry.
- It's time for us to go.
(We will get going now.)
- Already?
- We will get going.
- Comedians 1 and 2 will get going.
- Guys.
- Don't trust each other.
- Let's go.
Let's go. For goodness' sake.
Who are there? Suk Jin and...
- Jae Suk.
- Se Chan? Hey,
- Yes.
let's make a promise
although it's pretty meaningless.
Jong Kook, don't say that.
We should come together this time,
Kwang Soo.
- Seriously.
- That's right.
The three of us should go together.
Make Kwang Soo promise.
- I have a lot of money.
- Give me the address.
Kwang Soo, you...
Hold on.
Why do you need the address?
It's nothing.
(Jong Kook gives Kwang Soo
the hidden mission.)
You can keep a promise, right?
Seriously, this is...
This is...
(He spots something!)
I am serious. So Min.
(He quickly scans
the hidden mission.)
Me? I will do anything.
What should I do?
(Haha, Ji Hyo, and Do Kwon
arrive first.)
I guess other teams are behind.
Aren't we the last team?
Please enter the building.
Okay.
- What was that?
- I am sorry, Haha.
- Haha, you are on pause.
- I am sorry.
Haha, it's not like that.
I had a hidden mission.
We are here.
What do we do?
Can we enter 40 minutes
after we fill in the application?
What is it?
So Min, hurry up
and get out of the car.
- What is it?
- Hurry up.
(Haha decides to enter with So Min.)
- What is it?
- Hurry up and run!
- Why?
- We should go together.
- Hurry up.
- Why are we running?
- That team needs to be the last.
Why?
What are you doing?
Go and rip off her name tag.
Hurry up.
(He runs after So Min
with his long legs.)
What is going on?
All right.
- What is this?
- Why...
(As he planned,
Kwang Soo removes her name tag.)
So Min, you need to pause
for three minutes.
What is going on?
- Three minutes?
- Anyone can...
(Ripping off)
- Three minutes?
- Anyone can... Kwang Soo.
You are with me now.
He needs to pause for three minutes.
Please fill out the application.
You aren't even looking at me.
It's not like that.
How could you be like that?
You aren't even looking at me.
- He suddenly...
- Okay.
Hey.
You... Do you know what's funny?
- What?
- Kwang Soo knew the plan.
You should have acted quickly.
For your information,
two people moved in already.
- What?
- There isn't much time.
(Did people move in already?)
Is it 6:35 p.m?
- That's right.
- 6:35 p.m.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan waited
one floor below the penthouse.)
- Let's go!
- We need to go.
My goodness.
- There it is.
- Let's hurry up.
(They entered the penthouse
before anyone.)
Don't do it! Don't do it!
It's meaningless!
The two of you won.
(Comedians 1 and 2 won.)
- It was the perfect scenario!
- Okay. We did it.
(The competition turned fiercer.)
Jae Suk and Se Chan entered
the penthouse.
- Really? Already?
- Yes.
I didn't get to rip off
their name tags.
Did they move in?
Did they move in already?
(Haha's move-in time is 7:18 p.m.)
(The limited spots
make the others anxious.)
This is ridiculous.
We need to hurry up and take off
people's name tags, Kwang Soo.
- Hey.
- Right now...
(The member at the bottom
is anxious beyond belief.)
(He spots his target!)
Don't do that.
- Listen.
- Let's not do that.
We promised not to do that.
Hold on.
It's only a 10-minute delay.
We promised not to do that.
I will tell Jong Kook.
This is how you begin.
I need to find Suk Jin.
He hasn't moved in yet.
(He spots another target.)
(He runs at full speed.)
(A crazy man runs after Ji Hyo.)
Gosh, why is he running after me?
I got here after you did.
What are you doing?
(Ripping)
What was that?
I need to rip off the name tags.
Give me the reason.
Why did you rip off my name tag?
- Are you insane?
- I need to delay the time.
Is he insane?
(The monster of the penthouse
seeks the next target.)
- We can't trust anyone.
- Seriously.
You are walking sideways.
I can't walk straight.
Maybe I should do the moonwalk.
(Boo!)
Oh Yoon Hee is scary.
Stop it.
So Yeon, don't let your guard down.
Ta-da!
- "The Penthouse".
(They spot the drama poster.)
In front of the poster...
Shall we strike a pose?
- Let's do that.
My goodness.
Here.
(They move over to the poster
while covering their backs.)
Here.
(They promote the drama.)
(At Running Man, a show
that is worse than "The Penthouse")
- We are so funny.
- This is insane.
All right. Let's keep going.
(As soon as they are done,
they become wary again.)
We are wary of each other.
What are we doing?
(The newbies have a war of nerves
for no reason.)
(She gets startled on her own.)
I shouldn't be too trusting.
We should meet someone.
- Let's go downstairs.
- Downstairs?
We should join forces.
For goodness' sake.
Seriously.
Let's take out anyone we see.
(Since they arrived late,
they have no time to rest.)
- We need to go to the fourth floor.
- Where are they?
The stairs.
(They hear Eugene's voice.)
They are coming upstairs.
(They meet in the end.)
(Rushing down)
(She responds calmly
to Kwang Soo's attack.)
(Eugene is a strong candidate
everyone is wary of.)
Eugene. Eugene.
Get off! Get off!
(Eugene is out.)
I did it. I ripped off her name tag.
What? Eugene!
Eugene!
(So Yeon runs over to help Eugene
upon hearing her scream.)
No! Don't come!
(Kwang Soo appears.)
Don't come!
(The next target walked over
of her own volition.)
No!
(So Yeon gets eliminated
without much of a fight.)
So Yeon is out.
Let's move to the prison.
(She is out for the 2nd time
in 20 minutes.)
Am I out?
I didn't get to do anything.
Where is it? Here?
(She enters the prison.)
Eugene!
I should have known.
Are you guys in a line?
(Running Man's prison
is full of stories.)
Who ripped off your name tag?
Kwang Soo did.
Kwang Soo is running around wildly.
It's rare to see the prison so full.
The atmosphere is nice.
(So Min is disheartened.)
I don't have it.
I don't have 500 dollars.
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
- Did he rip off your name tag?
- Kwang Soo!
I will buy it
since I have the money.
(The rich girl is ready to flex.)
Eugene.
Eugene,
would you lend me...
(I am sorry to ask when we met
for the first time today.)
some money?
(So Min asks for a private loan.)
I didn't get to rip off
anyone's name tag.
(So Yeon rips off the name tag
in prison.)
(Suk Jin is at home,
So Min refuses to give up,)
(and So Yeon is full of resentment.)
(With three members behind,)
(Eugene finishes purchasing
a revival pass.)
What time is it?
I can enter the penthouse
if I hold out for nine minutes.
Let's go up.
That's a life lesson.
Money is nothing but paper.
If you can get out with real money,
you would do it, right?
- I can pay 1,200 dollars.
- Would you...
Transfer the money.
- I can pay 1,200 dollars.
- Would you...
(So Yeon is hesitant.)
Would you give me one?
I want to give it to my nephew.
You can take all the game money.
- One is enough.
- Take it.
So Yeon, take a name tag.
- It's a souvenir.
- Take a name tag.
- Here you go.
- Take my name tag as well.
No, no. It's okay.
That's enough.
- I mean...
- The game money.
- The game money is enough.
- You prefer the game money.
- Your nephew will like this too.
- He is a fan, of course.
But...
(He is a fan,)
(but you should keep it.)
- I guess he doesn't like me.
- No, no.
- I guess so.
- He is a big fan.
Take the top.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Take mine as well.
- You don't have a name tag.
- You don't have it.
I don't have it.
(His back is empty.)
He insisted
when he didn't have a name tag.
- I don't know where Ji Ah is.
- Jong Kook.
I swear you can trust me.
Jong Kook, you have no reason
to remove my name tag.
You should take him out
and go after the others.
- This is the only path.
- Time is ticking.
Eugene and the others are close
to their move-in time.
- I ripped off her name tag earlier.
- Where is Eugene?
Aren't you intimidated
because she kicked you earlier?
To be honest,
I am a bit intimidated.
(To be honest,
I am a bit intimidated.)
Go and rip off her name tag.
I did it earlier.
Think about the conversation we had
on our way here.
Hurry up and go.
(At that moment)
(Eugene appears
at the perfect timing.)
- Is it Eugene?
- Yes.
- We...
- Go.
Where is the staircase?
(Eugene was looking for a way
to the penthouse.)
Hurry up and go. Go.
It's your last chance. Go.
Are they guarding the staircase?
I mean...
(He approaches Eugene
with a scared facial expression.)
Eugene, you don't have much time.
(The 1st candidate for moving in,
Eugene runs away.)
(She suddenly changes direction.)
(She loses Kwang Soo.)
Jong Kook! Get her!
Get her!
- Jong Kook!
- No!
(It's Kwang Soo's turn.)
- Hey.
- What's the time now?
- There isn't much time.
- It will her move-in time soon.
- Help me. I will do it.
- Come here. Don't be like that.
- Help me.
- Come here.
- I will do it.
- Don't be like that.
- I mean...
- There is no other way.
- Hold on.
- No funny business.
Hold on.
Come on. Come on.
(Biting)
(Screaming)
(The former fairy
succeeded to bite him.)
- Did you really have to do that?
- She bit him!
Did you really have to do that?
She bit him!
(Annoyed)
Kwang Soo is annoyed.
He is annoyed.
(Are they practicing taekkyeon?)
(Kwang Soo only kicks
because he is intimidated.)
My legs...
(Kicking for the 2nd time)
- Hold on.
- Get her.
My goodness.
(Eugene gets caught by Haha
in the end.)
My goodness.
This is wrong.
(Ripping off)
(Eugene is out.)
Did he rip it off?
I did it! I did it!
He did it.
I should run away now.
Thank you.
(They used up their energy.)
I need to enter the penthouse.
Do Kwon.
- Do Kwon.
She is out. Don't annoy her further.
- She is out.
- I am out already.
- Really?
- Yes.
Eugene, please go to the prison.
(Eugene goes back to prison!)
I don't have a chance anymore.
(She doesn't know if she can buy
another revival pass.)
- Eugene, a revival pass...
- Don't go that way.
All the male members are there.
You will get your name tag
ripped off.
Instead of the security,
- they are blocking the path.
- Seriously.
2 spots remain. 2 spots.
Two spots remain at the penthouse.
I know that, Do Kwon.
Do Kwon, it will be
your move-in time soon, right?
Do Kwon's move-in time
is the closest.
- That's right.
- That's right. It's the closest.
(Jong Kook's move-in time is
the closest at 7:18 p.m.)
In any case,
you can't enter
without taking me on.
You will have to negotiate
with me...
or take me on.
You will stop us?
I will stop you.
What? How?
I am sorry,
but who do you think you are?
- Seriously.
- How will you stop us?
It's a touch-and-go situation.
Haha, if your time is approaching,
go up.
I will stop them.
- What?
- What is going on?
- Me?
- Yes. I will stop them.
We formed an alliance in the car.
- Then I will pass.
- Okay.
Pass. You can pass.
Jong Kook, they formed an alliance.
Two spots remain, right?
- You and I could go together.
- You are right.
There are four people here.
- I have no reason to betray you.
- Wait. We should attack together.
I will collapse.
- I will collapse.
- Don't be absurd.
Don't rip off my clothes.
- My son...
- This top doesn't rip easily.
My son will be heartbroken.
(He pleads with father's love.)
- Your son will be heartbroken?
- My son will be heartbroken.
You shouldn't say
something like that.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Time out.
He is buying time.
- We don't have much time.
- No, no.
- Come here.
- Come on.
- Get him instead.
- Hold on.
Hey.
(Do Kwon has a face-off
for the 1st time in 10 hours.)
Can we go up here?
If we go against each other,
both of us might get eliminated.
- Okay.
- You know that, right?
Okay. Let go of me then.
- Okay. I let go of you.
- Okay.
- Let go of me.
- I let go of you.
What?
- Let go of me then.
- Okay. I let go of you.
Okay.
(Jong Kook runs away.)
What?
(Jong Kook's move-in time is
7:18 p.m.)
- Get him!
- Is it your move-in time?
- It's my move-in time?
Is it your move-in time?
I know it isn't!
- It isn't your move-in time yet!
- Really?
(The security runs after Do Kwon.)
Where do I go?
I can enter now, right?
(Jong Kook arrives at the entrance.)
Someone is coming.
- It's Jong Kook.
- Okay, okay.
(Jong Kook is
the third person to move in.)
- Did you pass?
- My goodness.
What a grand entrance!
Do Kwon entered...
before his time.
He is getting chased.
- By whom?
(Do Kwon runs all the way...)
(to the 1st floor.)
(The remaining members
go against each other.)
(Haha is out.)
Haha, please go to the prison.
You are out.
(Then Kwang Soo took on Do Kwon.)
Out!
(He made Do Kwon lose
for the 2nd time.)
I am sorry.
- It was about my time.
- Do Kwon.
- I had two minutes to go.
(Kwang Soo is the only one
at the staircase.)
Hello. I will be moving in soon.
Hello.
When I move in,
I will send rice cakes to everyone.
My goodness.
After 37 years,
I ended up moving into
the penthouse.
I also had a lot of hardships.
I ended up moving into
the penthouse...
because I didn't give up and
I saved up money little by little.
(I look forward to
your kind cooperation.)
I'm starting to get excited.
I'm moving into the penthouse.
(Someone's on the penthouse floor?)
(Someone made an appearance
on the penthouse floor silently.)
- Someone is here.
- Who is it?
- Ji Hyo?
- What happened?
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Is Ji Hyo the fourth person
to move in?)
- Ji Hyo?
- Is time up?
- Ji Hyo.
You moved in?
- Jae Suk.
- How did you survive?
(Everyone is surprised.)
(How did Ji Hyo get past Kwang Soo?)
- So...
- Ji Hyo.
The men are all gathered over there.
There's 1 over here,
and there another 1 in the end.
(She went round and entered
a course that made a long detour.)
- I can go in from now on, right?
- Yes, you can.
I also had a lot of hardships.
That's right, this is it.
(She hid behind the staff
right next to Kwang Soo.)
Excuse me.
- They're right there. Thank you.
- Someone is here.
(She succeeded in dramatically
moving into the penthouse.)
Okay, four people moved in...
to the penthouse,
so the race is over now.
Who moved in?
You can go there and check.
The race is over.
- Really?
- The race is over.
(Kwang Soo's moving-in speech really
ended up being meaningless words.)
I'm sorry, I ended up
not being able to move in.
Who is it? Did Ji Hyo survive?
- Ji Hyo survived.
- Ji Hyo came in.
- Kwang Soo, what happened?
- How did you come in?
I took another path.
There was another path?
- Of course.
- Which path?
How many paths
does the penthouse have?
It's over? I just escaped right now.
I just came right now.
- I barely escaped.
- So Min, what happened?
- What happened?
- I just barely saved money.
So Min, isn't it my first time to
see you after we got out of the car?
- So Min, what happened?
- At the comedian meeting...
- Junior Ji.
- He's coming.
Be quiet.
I'm telling you to be quiet.
(He's really upset.)
Okay, everyone.
The four people who won
by moving into the penthouse are...
Yoo Jae Suk, Yang Se Chan,
Kim Jong Kook, and Song Ji Hyo.
(Yoo Jae Suk, Yang Se Chan,
Kim Jong Kook, and Song Ji Hyo)
- That's unbelievable.
- Yes.
These are Korean beef sets
for the winners.
- They prepared these for us.
- Korean beef was good today.
There were five candidates
for a penalty...
that were eliminated.
Only 2 people will receive
a penalty among the 5.
Okay, that's enough.
I can just get out from that.
- Am I also not included?
- You're not.
- I'm not?
- I told you I won't let you...
receive a penalty.
The penalty is...
eating patbingsu while soaking
your feet in an ice basin.
- That sounds good.
The five people should come here.
1, 2, 3.
(The result of drawing spoons to
select people to receive penalties)
(Suk Jin and Eugene
ended up being selected.)
Kwang Soo...
(Surprised)
Suk Jin and Eugene
will soak their feet...
I feel very awkward eating
patbingsu with Eugene.
Suk Jin was the first to come here.
I was the first to come.
These punks eliminated me.
(He was the first one to come,
but he will be the last to go.)
Gosh, I can't believe it.
The first comedian meeting is
a failure.
- That was so funny.
- Gosh.
Please give a round of applause to
the four leads of "The Penthouse".
- Thank you. You did a good job.
- Thank you.
- They're receiving a penalty here.
- We must put our feet in.
(Suk Jin and Eugene stay behind
to receive the penalty.)
- It's so cold.
- Oh, my.
That's intense.
- That's intense.
(They can feel the cold
from the tip of their toes.)
This is intense. It's smarting.
Gosh, this is...
This is...
- I can't do it.
- Good job.
(We'd like to thank Ji Ah, So Yeon,
Eugene, and Do Kwon.)
(We wish for your drama's
continuous success.)
(At one point,)
(all the doors of the room closed.)
We must escape from here, right?
(A mysterious confinement case,
How did it begin?)
(A few hours ago)
(The premiere of
the 1st Friendship Awards)
(Jong Kook's best friend Tae Hyun
joined the show for the first time.)
(He can't hide his smile because
his best friend made an appearance.)
(Celebrity best friends,
Yang Dong Geun and Jang Dong Min)
(So Min's friend Mi Joo,
Huening Kai, and Yeon Jun)
(What does Jong Kook
mean to Tae Hyun?)
(He's like protein to me.)
(A proper friendship fight
among celebrity best friends)
(I heard you are on bad terms
with Son Ye Jin.)
(Son Ye Jin didn't even appear
in the movie.)
(The string of friendship was
cut off mercilessly.)
(I will do everything I can
for my friend.)
for my gain.)
(With a mysterious bag theft case,)
(who are the best friends to
make the Friendship Awards shine?)
(The Best Friends Friendship Race,
The 1st Friendship Awards)