(One winter day when you want
to listen to ballad songs)
(There's Running Apartment
in a quiet place.)
Hey, good morning.
Hello.
It's been a while.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- My gosh.
- You all are here.
(The residents of Running Apartment
are having a neighborhood meeting.)
- Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Is that how
a laughter therapist talks?
- He sounds like...
- Hello.
(HaHa: Unit 101, laughter therapist,
Se Chan: Unit 310, magician)
(Kwang Soo: Unit 306,
bar exam taker)
(He's full of laughter energy.)
Clapping hands is
good for your health.
- Hello.
She's a simultaneous interpreter?
(So Min: Unit 208, poet)
(Ji Hyo: Unit 103,
simultaneous interpreter)
(A simultaneous interpreter doesn't
match her real-life personality.)
Ladies and gentlemen.
Please translate it.
Hello, everyone.
Is that right?
Isn't this modernized hanbok?
Are you a laughter therapist?
- Why is he a laughter therapist?
- I have no idea.
You should treat me.
- I have to treat myself first.
- Treat me.
- Okay.
- He's a bully.
- What?
(He's a bully.)
He's a bully.
- Are you sure you're a trainer?
- This is real.
- He's here to work out.
- He's a real trainer.
(Jong Kook: Unit 205,
health trainer)
What is Jae Suk?
- What?
- It's Hurricane Blue.
Hurricane Blue.
(He's full of rock spirit
in a leather jacket.)
Come here.
Jae Suk seems familiar, but
I don't remember where I saw him.
(Jae Suk, Unit 207,
indie band rocker)
Who are you guys?
This is how he talks
when he's wearing a wig.
- He speaks like that in a wig.
- It looks great on you.
- It's a habit.
- He looks good.
- I look good, don't I?
- It's not strange at all.
- It just feels natural.
- I've seen a guy like him.
I'm a little sensitive because of
my music. Don't get on my nerves.
- Really?
- You write your songs.
I'm working on my new song,
but it's not going well.
Do you want me
to make you wail instead?
(Do you want me
to make you wail instead?)
(He wants to help Jae Suk
find his own voice.)
- What?
- Instead of singing.
What is this guy up to?
You're working on your new song.
Are you a bully or something?
- What's that? What did you write?
- I'm a poet, remember?
Really?
"Music is magic."
(The poet hands a note over to him.)
- Gosh. She's a poet.
- I'm...
- I just...
- So she just wrote a poem.
- Really?
- She wrote about music.
"Music is magic."
And she wrote this
for the interpreter.
"Translate my heart."
- That's good.
- She's a crazy poet.
Yali yali yala sheong.
"Yali yali yala sheong"?
- What about a trainer?
- Isn't "Yali yali yala sheong"...
- a folk song from Goryeo?
- Anything for a trainer?
- For a trainer?
- Yes.
Like "You're a trainer of love"?
(The poet writes a phrase
for the trainer right away.)
"I hope I could
build up muscles in my heart too."
"I can help you grow muscles
that withstand breakups."
They're good, but they sound like...
I've heard them before
from somewhere.
Abracadabra, that's nice!
They're something
that I wrote just now.
"Grow me muscles
that help me withstand breakups."
(Satisfied with what he said)
My goodness.
- The wig is so uncomfortable.
- Wait a minute.
- Did you write this? No, right?
- No.
- There are many sitting mats.
- This is so funny.
How many sitting mats are there?
I guess we have many guests today.
(Are we having many guests today?)
Se Chan, do you know
who'll be here today?
- Goodness.
- Gosh, Suk Jin's here.
- Good morning.
- Suk Jin!
(Suk Jin enters
when no one's interested in him.)
(Good morning!)
- Are you a taxi driver?
- Who are you supposed to be?
- Taxi driver.
- Who's he supposed to be?
Excuse me!
- Who do you think I am?
- Genie?
Are you a recreation instructor?
Excuse me!
- Genie?
- Who do you think I am?
- He's "Genie".
- Oh, Genie?
He's Genie.
I see. He's Genie.
Hello, everyone.
- So you...
- Wait.
- You should cover yourself.
- What? Why?
- This is in style now.
- But...
I can see things through your shirt.
Then cover them with something.
- I'm fine.
- You can see Genie's things too.
- Genie is always like that.
- Then cover them with something.
Yes, he's always topless.
- Why don't you use these to...
- Don't do that.
- Cover them with the Post-its.
- Don't.
But if you want me to, then I will.
- As you know, I'm your servant.
- Yes.
- Put them inside.
- All right.
You want me to put them in here?
Genie, I want to watch SBS.
- SBS?
- He's not that Genie.
- Not that Genie.
- No, he's not.
- Genie!
- Turn on "Banana Chacha"!
All right. How this?
(Ji Seok Genie
isn't that kind of Genie.)
I can still see them
through the Post-it!
Where?
- Post-its won't cover them.
- Don't...
Everyone.
Don't focus on things like this.
- But I can see them.
- Don't.
I can clearly see them.
Suk Jin's sweating. He's nervous.
It's because
the shirt is too small for me.
But everyone,
just don't look at them.
- How can we not notice them?
- I mean,
- they're looking at us!
- That's right.
- They're very noticeable.
- Don't mind them.
So let's start this.
I'm the manager of this apartment.
Yes, so if there are any requests,
- This is an apartment?
- please let me know.
- My goodness.
- Look at Suk Jin's face.
- He's overwhelmed by pressure.
- I know.
I think he didn't
get enough sleep last night.
Yes, he said he didn't sleep well.
- So he's hosting it today.
- Yes.
No wonder.
This morning, he screamed
when he got out of the car,
"I can do this, I can do this!"
So that was why you did it.
Because you had a big mission.
You lie so well
that it seems like it's true.
So today, we're gathered here...
- because...
- How many times are you saying it?
Wait a minute.
You be quiet!
- Ji Hyo finds this fun.
- Sure.
- Are you having fun?
- Yes, this is fun.
- All right.
- You're doing great.
Three writers are sitting there...
- biting their nails right now.
- All right.
- They're regretting it.
- So today,
you can tell me anything
if you have any requests.
- Is that so?
- Yes, I will fix it for you.
So should I call you Ji Seok Genie?
You can call me either
Genie or Ji Seok Genie.
Why don't you practice? 1, 2, 3!
- Ji Seok Genie!
- That's not it.
Why aren't you saying it?
That's too old-fashioned.
What are you going to do about it?
- Gosh.
- This is getting boring.
- Catch the mouse.
- Squeak, squeak, squeak.
(Catch the mouse, catch the mouse.
Squeak, squeak, squeak.)
How many mice?
Three mice.
I got them.
(Genie was a host of a popular
show of KBS 15 years ago.)
(He's Ji Seok Genie now, but he was
the best MC in the old days.)
- How many mice?
- Three mice!
Three mice.
- I got them.
- I lost them.
It feels good to see you
play along so well.
Yes, he was good in the old days.
That's right. I was a famous MC
in the old days.
So we're all here today...
because we have to welcome
some new residents.
Let me introduce them to you.
Here are our new residents.
Please come out!
(Who are the new residents
of Running Apartment?)
- Here he is.
- My goodness.
- Hey.
- Jin Wook!
My goodness.
- It's Jin Wook.
- Hello, Jin Wook.
Hey, Song Kang!
(Song Kang: Unit 210, actor trainee)
- Gosh.
- You're here again.
- Si Young, long time no see.
- Back then...
- Do Hyun.
- Hello.
(Lee Do Hyun: Unit 305,
bar exam taker)
(Lee Si Young: Unit 309, landlady)
(Four leading actors of Netflix's
new original series, "Sweet Home")
(Thriller drama with a fresh concept
and strong visuals)
My goodness, Jin Wook.
So you moved in here?
- It's good to see you.
- Here.
Thank you.
They're giving us rice cake.
- Gosh.
- Have some.
(As soon as he sees Si Young,)
(teasing boxer
suddenly starts shadowboxing.)
- Stop it.
- Why?
Stop it and have a seat.
- Gosh, Si Young.
- Sit down.
You're supposed to do this
when you see Si Young.
(He'll be knocked out
if she really fights him back.)
- Just stop it.
- Why?
You two should stand here since
you're wearing the same sweats.
Gosh, you're a bar exam taker also?
- Why are we dressed up...
- What is this?
Why are we dressed up the same?
They're both exam takers,
but they look so different.
You can compare the two.
Do Hyun looks great.
- He really looks like one.
- Yes, he looks real.
How am I different from him?
Everyone, these are
our new residents.
Please give them a big hand.
(Welcome to our apartment!)
He's a bar exam taker.
Now they'll introduce themselves.
Starting from Jin Wook.
I live in Unit 206.
I'm a detective,
and my name is Lee Jin Wook.
- A detective?
- He's a detective.
I haven't seen Jin Wook
for a long time.
- Yes, he's right.
- That's not it.
He's on our show for the first time.
Back when I...
It's the first time I've seen him
since "Family Outing".
Yes, he was on "Family Outing"
12 years ago.
- 12 years ago.
- It's been so long.
- Yes, it's been a long time.
- Hello.
I live in Unit 210.
I'm an actor trainee,
and my name is Song Kang.
Gosh, he's handsome.
Yes, Song Kang.
So Min's looking at him
like she's interested.
Actually, we've met before.
- Yes, on "Village Survival".
- Right, on "Village Survival".
- Lee Si Young.
- Hello, guys.
Hello, guys.
I live on the top floor.
Why are you speaking casually?
(Why is she speaking casually?)
- She's the landlady.
- She is?
I should keep my eyes on him.
Aren't you a boxing trainer?
No, I'm the landlady.
Come on, you're a boxer.
Gosh, you'll get beaten up.
Stop provoking her.
- Stop it.
- What's wrong with him?
But I've seen her boxing.
No, she's the landlady.
- She's the owner of this building.
- I see.
- I should suck up to her.
- Do Hyun, you're next.
Hello, I live in Unit 305. I'm
Lee Do Hyun, and I'm an exam taker.
- His voice is...
- I know him very well.
- He has a great voice.
- As you all know,
Running Man raised Do Hyun.
You're right.
I'm right, aren't I?
What do you think, Do Hyun?
- Aren't I right, Do Hyun?
- Yes, it's true.
We raised Do Hyun ourselves.
- We did.
- Yes, we did.
(We understand how they want to
take credit for raising him right,)
(but the truth is,
Do Hyun raised himself well!)
We raised Do Hyun.
And we took care of Suk Jin
with fake nipples since infancy.
Yes, we changed his diapers too.
Right, we did.
I joined you as an adult.
- What are you talking about?
- I was an adult.
- Nipple Genie. Nipple Genie.
(He's Nipple Genie.)
(As they pay much attention to him,)
(he dances along.)
- He loves it.
- He does.
- He's excited.
- Just call me Genie.
He's Nipple Genie.
Jin Wook, how does it feel to be
on our show for the first time?
- How do you...
- What?
- Your way of hosting is old!
- Why? What did I do?
- This isn't the 60s.
- So how do you feel?
- I feel good.
- Do they normally ask that?
- Oh, is that so?
Suk Jin, try to make him talk more.
- Don't listen to others.
- Don't.
- Just stay focused.
- Don't listen to others.
Weren't you two in the same
military base?
- Yes.
- Yes, you're right.
He was my superior
when we were in the military.
- You two must be close then.
- Sure, we are.
- What kind of superior was he?
- Yes, tell us that.
Just as you imagine.
He was quiet and nice.
- Really?
- He was nice to the others.
And he's more humorous
than you think.
Yes, I'm sure he is.
He's funny, but Genie
isn't good enough to bring that out.
He's a funny guy,
but Genie isn't helping.
He doesn't talk
when he's intimidated.
Why is he intimidated?
Jin Wook keeps shaking his head.
Well, to be honest,
Suk Jin is really good.
(He gives an empty compliment
as his senior comedian.)
Gosh, this is funny.
Suk Jin is so funny today.
Why don't we all have a seat now?
- All right.
- Are we sitting down?
I'll explain the rules to you.
Please pay attention.
Through today's mission,
you'll increase or reduce the number
of members who will get a penalty.
The race is called
The Apartment You Live In.
Through the mission, more members
could get a penalty...
or fewer members
could get a penalty.
If you fail, one more person
will get a penalty,
which means every member
could end up getting penalty.
Every time the mission ends,
each of you will go back
to your room and use the laptop...
to vote for the member
you want to give penalty to.
Gosh, they make us
do that all the time.
(They can vote for the person
who they want to give penalty to...)
(by writing a name in the chat room
during their free time.)
I'm going to write Genie first.
- Can I get a penalty too?
- It's okay to write nothing, right?
- I can't get a penalty.
- Why can't Genie get a penalty?
I can't get a penalty.
Instead of not getting penalty,
I have to take care of
all of your requests.
So I'll be very busy today.
But if everyone votes for no one,
then one less person
will get a penalty.
If you don't vote, one less
person will get a penalty.
- One less from all members?
- Then I won't vote.
Yes, from all members.
I won't vote.
(If every member doesn't vote,
one less member will get a penalty.)
But if even one of you votes,
the same number of members
will get a penalty.
And the members with most votes
Can't you read the script
prior to the shoot?
- I'm reading it for the first time.
- Yes, you're reading it now.
But they gave me this a minute ago.
- My goodness.
- So many times do you vote?
Only two times.
- You only get to vote twice.
- Excuse me.
- Anyone can tell...
- Genie, no one's listening to you.
- Hey!
- They're busy eating the rice cake.
I'm explaining the rules.
But the new residents and the
landlady brought us the rice cake.
- So we should eat it.
- All right.
Well, since you have ears,
just listen.
- What?
- How can you say it like that?
You only use your mouth to eat
so listen while you eat.
- Gosh.
- Just listen.
And when there's a request
you want to file,
- use the notes on the table.
- All right.
Write your request on it...
and put it in my mission bag.
Then I will take care of
all of your requests.
- Really?
- All of them?
- All of them.
- Okay.
- You'll take care of all of them?
- I'll do my best...
- to take care of them.
- Here is one.
- What did you write?
- What is it?
Maybe he wrote, "Please go home."
"Genie, get lost."
(Genie, get lost!)
Why would you want me to get lost?
I can't take care
of this kind of request.
- Really?
- I can't get lost because...
Can't you go back
into your magic lamp?
- Get lost.
- Go back into the lamp.
- In this apartment,
- Please get lost.
I'm being paid.
- My gosh.
- So I can't get lost.
Even the guests
can give me a note...
- Really?
- if there's anything they want.
Then I will be sure to take care
of all of your requests.
Because I'm Ji Seok Genie.
Suk Jin, will you go
wash my car then?
I can't do that.
- He says no to everything.
- But...
He's not doing anything.
It requires a lot of work, but it
wouldn't get me enough screentime.
Ask me something else.
What kind of Genie
cares about his screentime?
- You know what I mean.
- Actually, that sounds good.
It takes about an hour, but it will
be on screen only for two minutes.
Suk Jin, washing his car
sounds hilarious.
- Right? You should try.
- Write it down here.
- Put it in here.
- Put it in?
I didn't know there would be
so many requests.
I can't take care of all of them.
Who put this in?
What should I make him do?
"Cover this."
Who wrote this?
"Get a crew cut."
- Can't you do that?
- Who wrote this?
That's my request.
Can't you do that?
Why do you want me
to get a hair cut all of a sudden?
Why can't you do that?
I have my own style.
I can't do things like this.
- He can't do anything.
- It's not like that. Guys.
- He's giving you one.
- It's from Kang.
Read it for us.
This is from Song Kang.
"Please take good care
of the guests."
(Please take good care
of the guests.)
On our show,
- no one takes care of others.
- Kang said that.
- He really meant it.
- We all are on our own.
He's serious about that.
I'm getting too many requests
all at the same time.
- He says no to everything.
- I'll keep reading.
- Oh, this one! Who wrote this?
- What is it?
- This is something I can do.
"Please get me some coffee."
Who wrote this?
- Okay. Wait a second.
- Okay.
I like a request like this.
- He wants to drink coffee.
- I'm from Unit 208.
- He wants coffee for himself.
- I really like it.
Why? Is it his mission?
Why does he like it?
This is strange, isn't it?
- Really?
- You should order coffee.
I can make coffee... Hang on.
- Iced coffee.
- I can get you coffee.
Genie, make it one shot.
- What?
- Make it weak with one shot.
- Hang on. Did you see that?
- Make it weak.
Suk Jin said he liked it,
but he was just like this.
(He just spun round and round
on the same spot.)
- He was like this.
- What are the writers doing?
They should get me some coffee.
I gave you enough time
to get me coffee.
I kept running around in here.
You should get me coffee...
so I can continue my skit.
We just don't click.
He was like this.
(He just kept turning
round and round at the same spot.)
All right. This is what I can do.
- You're not doing it yourself.
- He's the worst.
Here you are.
- This is...
- He's the worst.
- Genie.
- We all want coffee.
You should give coffee to all of us.
- You will have some free time now.
- What?
Do we have free time?
For 10 minutes,
you can either vote for a person
to get a penalty...
or get some rest in your room.
Like Suk Jin said,
if none of you vote,
the number of people to get
a penalty will be reduced.
We shouldn't vote at first.
- We shouldn't vote.
- Then it will be reduced by one.
- Why would we vote?
- Otherwise, it'll keep increasing.
If someone votes,
the person who gets the vote will
be more likely to get a penalty.
If someone votes, the person with
most votes will get a penalty.
- Please go back to your places.
- Okay. Let's go home.
Make sure not to vote.
Okay.
It would be stupid to vote.
It would be really stupid
to vote now.
I wonder what's in our rooms.
- There's Genie's room.
- This is Genie's room.
This is Genie's room.
I'm wearing thin clothes,
but my room is outdoors.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Is this my room?
My place is Unit 310.
- Mine is Unit 208.
- They bring requests here.
(This is where
he receives requests.)
I'll receive requests here.
(He's being nice to the residents.)
Gosh, I've got a lot of requests.
Let me check them.
(He checks the requests
he's received.)
"Pick up my second son, Soul,
at his kindergarten..."
"and get me cheonggukjang
for lunch."
My gosh.
"Order jjamppong
and fried dumplings for me."
(Order jjamppong
and fried dumplings for me. )
Hello?
Is this a Chinese restaurant?
I'd like to have jjamppong
and fried dumplings.
What is this?
(What is this?)
What is this laptop for?
What's this?
(There's a laptop for voting
with a chat room on it.)
Gosh. What is this box for?
(What is this box for?)
(There are 3 boxes
next to the laptop.)
(All 3 boxes are locked up.)
I guess something's in here.
(What's the secret of these boxes?)
This is strange.
Why are there books?
Let me see. What is this book for?
(All the residents have books
in their rooms.)
I can have a chat with others.
(They can chat online
before the voting.)
Is this how I cast a vote?
(Is this how I cast a vote?)
"Kim Jong Kook."
Why would she call me like this?
"Why would you call me like that?"
(He's giving her
an etiquette lesson online.)
"You punk."
(Why would you call me
like that, you punk?)
(I think this is
the room escape game.)
(Jong Kook, try to type faster.)
He wants me to type faster.
(He types fast with webbed fingers.)
- Can I create a group chat room?
- Sure.
(He creates a group chat room
without Kwang Soo.)
(Hello. This is a group chat room,
and only 10 of us are in here.)
(They have a friendly conversation
without Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo isn't in here.
(While the residents are busy
building a friendship...)
Cookies and iced coffee.
My gosh. Where's the cafeteria?
Excuse me.
- Come in.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I got you the cookies.
- You brought them here?
- Sure.
Please tell me if you need anything.
- And send me a lot of requests.
- Okay. Thank you.
It's been a while
since I sent my request.
What is it?
I haven't checked it yet.
Please tell me what it is.
I asked for jjamppong with rice
and a lot of pickled radish.
Gosh, I'm in trouble. Okay.
- Jjamppong with rice?
- And a lot of pickled rice.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Is it possible?
My goodness.
They could order
jjamppong themselves.
Don't they have phones
at their places?
(While Genie is busy
taking care of the requests...)
Hello?
I got a message.
"This is the chat room
to take a ballot for the penalty."
"If you want to cast a ballot,"
"send me the name of the person
whom you want to give a penalty."
(If you want to cast a ballot,)
(send me the name of the person
whom you want to give a penalty.)
If we don't cast a vote,
none of us will get a penalty.
So I shouldn't probably vote.
I've never seen...
the members
keep their promises before.
But this time,
(He will trust other residents
and abstain this time.)
I'll trust them.
(If you want to cast a ballot,)
(send me the name of the person
whom you want to give a penalty.)
(Is it anonymous?)
(It is anonymous.
Will you cast a ballot?)
(He votes for
Lee Si Young immediately.)
(Because of Kwang Soo, the number of
people to get a penalty is still 1.)
I'll vote for Lee Jin Wook.
He's a great guy.
(Kang votes for Jin Wook.)
I sent the message.
(Kwang Soo votes for Si Young,
and Kang votes for Jin Wook.)
(The magician votes for Si Young
without hesitation.)
(At that moment...)
(The password of Box 1
is "1218".)
(Those who cast a vote
gets the password of Box 1.)
It's 1218. Hang on.
Do they give me the password?
(Kwang Soo also
gets the password of Box 1.)
What?
(The password of Box 1
is "1218".)
Hang on.
(He tries to open the box with the
password from the administrator.)
(It's open.)
What is this?
(What's in the mysterious box?)
Can I take this off? What is this?
(1 R coin)
R coin?
(Those who cast a vote
got 1 R coin each.)
What is this?
This is an R coin.
I got the password
because I cast my ballot.
The password is like a benefit.
(The sweet benefit
of the ballot is an R coin.)
(Yoo Jae Suk.)
(Can I cast a ballot again?)
(He wants to cast a ballot
for everyone to get more coins.)
When you meet other members,
don't talk about the coin.
(You can cast a ballot
only once in each round.)
(The ballot in this round
is already over.)
I knew it. They wouldn't let us
cast a ballot for nothing.
(Kwang Soo found out that he can
get a coin by casting a ballot.)
There's something.
(Only the three of them
know the secret.)
(The residents are gathered together
after the short break.)
I won't send him any more requests.
I won't ask Genie
for anything anymore.
Why not?
He's a big senior,
but he got me this coffee.
He said, "Here's your coffee."
I can't do this anymore.
Hey, since when did you
care about things like that?
You should do it more for him.
You think? Okay.
He'll become healthy this way.
Okay. I'll do it for his health.
Sure. He should move a lot.
- Give us the coffee.
- All right.
- Oh, no.
- This is what I heard...
from the hallway.
(They heard Genie groan
in the hallway.)
Genie was sweating a lot.
I'm like your servant.
I'm not Genie. I'm a servant.
- Hurry.
- This is crazy.
The first test is called
Nerve-wracking Quiz.
- What?
- Have you heard of it before?
The 11 residents will be...
divided into 3 teams
of 4, 4, and 3 people...
- to solve quizzes of each category.
- What? "Catagory"?
- "Catagory"?
- Did you say "catagory"?
If you find fault...
- You're like this every time.
- People make mistakes.
I hope time will
fly by quickly today.
The host should speak clearly.
- It could be "catagory".
- It's category.
- You know what I mean.
You know what?
It seems that Suk Jin has to
deal with five of us...
- while talking for one minute.
- Please...
Please go easy on me.
- He's the Sirasoni of MCs.
- That's right.
- He's incredible.
- The Sirasoni of MCs.
- Ji-rasoni, you're amazing.
- Ji-rasoni.
You'll be divided into 3 teams
of 4, 4, and 3 people.
The category for Team One
is "Singers".
"Singers"?
The category for Team Two
is "Entertainment".
"Entertainment".
The category for Team Three
is "Common Knowledge".
Jae Suk, you'll choose
"Common Knowledge", right?
You should choose
"Common Knowledge".
Then Jae Suk and I...
- Yes... Why you?
- "Common Knowledge"?
Don't choose that. Are you insane?
- Exactly. Don't do that.
- Maybe that's best for him.
- He doesn't know anything.
- Hold on.
Don't you think it's too mean to
to call me insane...
- because I chose that?
- Don't be ridiculous.
He can't be in that team.
- Do Hyun, which team will you join?
- I choose "Common Knowledge".
"Common Knowledge"? Really?
- Really?
- I choose it too.
- Si Young, are you serious?
- You choose "Common Knowledge"?
- Really? That's unexpected.
- Si Young, choose "Entertainment".
- Sorry?
- Choose "Entertainment".
No. I choose "Common Knowledge".
- That doesn't suit you.
- Don't be upset.
- What's with her?
- Why would you be upset?
- I don't understand...
- I think Kwang Soo is targeting me.
- I said nothing wrong.
Please sit with your team members.
- 4, 4, and 3 people.
- Where's Team Entertainment?
Team Singers, please sit
on this side. Thank you.
If even a single team succeeds
within seven attempts,
the number of people
to get the penalty will remain.
I see.
You have to succeed consecutively.
Team Singers, you will see a photo
of an idol singer,
and guess the group name
in three seconds.
- That's easy.
- It's easy to succeed.
- Indeed.
- It's easy.
Team Entertainment, I'll tell you
the name of an actor or actress.
Each of you has to say a movie
that he or she acted in.
I can do that. I'm confident.
Movie titles?
- Lastly, Team Common Knowledge,
- Yes?
you will take an open book quiz.
- An open book quiz?
- You'll receive a newspaper...
- from which the questions are made.
- I see.
Say the correct answer written on
the newspaper in three seconds.
- It's so difficult.
- A newspaper?
- Each member will receive it.
- Read it as much as you want.
Oh, my. Look at this.
It's too difficult.
- This is too difficult.
- They can find the answer in it.
Wait. This is an economy newspaper
for middle and high school students.
- It's too difficult.
- This is an economy newspaper.
- It's so difficult.
- From the newspaper,
we made easy questions.
We'll begin the first round.
- Okay.
- Okay, Jae Suk?
You can browse the newspaper
to find the answer freely.
- Do I go first?
- I'm sure Jae Suk will succeed.
I'm sure he will.
This isn't a tabloid.
Janet Yellen, the former Federal
Reserve chairwoman, has been...
nominated as
the Treasury Secretary...
for Joe Biden's cabinet that will be
formed in January, 2021.
Then...
who is Biden's running mate
and the vice-president-elect?
Kamala Harris.
(He said the correct answer
without hesitating.)
I knew it!
(Kamala Harris)
(Impressed)
Kamala Harris.
(Jae Suk, the undisputed king
of common knowledge of Running Man)
(The smartest member of Running Man
made everyone proud.)
We all can trust Jae Suk!
- My, he's so cool.
- We all can trust Jae Suk!
(Everyone is amazed
by the smart rocker.)
- He didn't even look at it.
- He's so cool.
Jae Suk, you looked so sexy.
(Jae Suk is enjoying
their compliments.)
He's a close friend of mine.
His pronunciation was also
very good.
Jae Suk, that was so sexy.
(Jealous)
Next up is Jin Wook.
Jin Wook, you have to succeed.
Jin Wook reads newspaper every day.
- Does he?
- You must not tell him the answer.
- Okay.
- How did he know the answer?
Due to the COVID-19 pandemic,
the global debt increased...
by 15 trillion dollars
through September this year.
There are concerns...
that many developing countries
will declare this.
What is this?
5, 4,
- Three...
- A default.
Okay!
(Smiling)
(Default)
(Amazed)
(Jin Wook got the correct answer
following Jae Suk!)
- That was awesome.
- My goodness.
(Even his brain is sexy too.)
- "Fault"?
- It's "default".
Right? It's "fault", right?
I knew that word.
- No, it's "default".
- You should know that much.
- Haha, that's common knowledge.
- All right. Good.
- "Fault"?
- Yes, "fault".
If Si Young gets the correct answer,
- this team will succeed.
- Then we'll succeed at once.
We'll definitely succeed.
- Si Young, you can do it!
- Si Young, keep reading it.
- It's not easy to make it this far.
- Go, Si Young!
Be quiet.
She tells me to be quiet
whenever I say something.
You did talk too much.
- I was cheering for her.
- Be quiet, Kwang Soo.
- This is also in the newspaper.
- Okay.
"Multi-personas" means to express
a person's various identities...
by transforming into
a different person.
Then what are the three characters
of Comedian Yoo Jae Suk...
who's shown his multiple identities
that were reported in the newspaper?
(What are the 3 characters
of Comedian Yoo Jae Suk?)
(You know the answer, right?)
What... Three characters
in the newspaper?
But it's not in here.
- Locust.
- Yoo San Seul.
It's in the newspaper.
- Yoo San Seul and Jimi Yu. Right?
- Really?
Yoo San Seul, U-Doragon, and Jimi Yu.
It's in the newspaper.
But this is...
This is common knowledge.
- She should've known...
- What a shame.
They were so close,
but Si Young ruined it.
(Glaring)
I mean, it's hard
to make it this far.
Team Entertainment will go next.
The four of you have to
say the movie titles...
that this actor appeared in
consecutively.
- If anyone fails, the team fails.
- Okay.
The actor is...
Lee Kwang Soo.
"Collective Invention".
Darn.
What was that?
"Collective Invention".
(Murmuring)
(Is it that difficult?)
I was going to say
"Collective Invention".
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
"Once Upon a Time in a Battlefield".
- I'm relieved.
- "Atka Mackerel Seven".
"Atka Mackerel Seven".
You should've known all these.
What's "Atka Mackerel Seven"?
- Didn't you play in that movie?
- Hey, it's "Sturgeon".
- Oh, right. "Sturgeon".
- What about "Once Upon a Time"...
- Yes?
- "in a Battlefield"?
- It's "Battlefield Heroes".
- Oh, right.
I can't believe none of you knows
any of my movies.
- He played in "The Treacherous".
- Did you play in "The Treacherous"?
- I didn't play in that movie.
- You didn't?
I didn't play in "The Treacherous".
I thought you did
because you're so treacherous.
I didn't play in that movie.
- Kwang Soo, "An Eagle Family"?
- I didn't...
- Come again?
- "An Eagle Family".
- It's "A Dynamite Family".
- Oh, right.
Enough, you punk!
- He can't say any title correctly.
- That's enough.
- Just shut it.
- This is the hardest category.
- "A Dynamite Family". I knew it.
- Gosh. What do we do?
- It was quite difficult.
- You don't know any of my movies.
- Jin Wook...
swallowed saliva many times.
As if he was thinking,
"I can't do this with these idiots."
"These idiots..."
(Jin Wook was frustrated
by their childish conversation.)
- Kang, switch seats with me.
- Movie titles are confusing.
- Okay. I'll go there.
- What a shame.
I think I'll do better
in this category.
- Let our team try.
- It's Team Singers' turn.
- All right.
- See the photo and say the answer.
And then, the next person
will do the same.
Why am I so nervous
when this is just a game?
Here we go. Ready.
Get set. Go. Two.
- Turbo.
- That one was easy.
- Go!
- 2, 1.
- TWICE.
- Wow. He did a great job.
You're almost there.
(Half of them succeeded easily.)
2, 1.
- Who is he?
- ZE:A.
- Who is that punk?
"I can't stop crying somehow".
The singer of "Aftereffect".
- Who are you?
- He's Kim Dong Jun of ZE:A.
He's so cute.
- He's a member of ZE:A.
- So Min.
It's not the time for you
to compliment Dong Jun's face.
(She doesn't care about the quiz.
Love Frog just can't stop smiling.)
Jong Kook, move to
Team Entertainment.
I'll move to Team Entertainment.
So Min, join our team.
Ji Hyo, join our team and solve
common knowledge questions.
- No, Ji Hyo, stay here.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo, it's an open book quiz.
- Stay here.
- No, Jae Suk. I won't go.
- Come with me. Give it a try.
- Give it a try.
- Just give it a try.
- Gosh.
She ended up joining
Team Common Knowledge.
I hope she gets a question
from the article she's reading.
You can just read the answer.
- You can just read it.
- I'll find it for you.
- Hey, submit a request.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Ask me to find it for you.
- She ended up in that team.
Suk Jin is simply trying to
get more screen time.
So don't mind him.
- The same goes for you, Jae Suk.
- Pardon?
I think you're trying to
get more air time too.
I'll help you find the answer
when your turn comes.
How about we continue
while they're reading it?
- Which team should go next?
- Team Singers.
- Team Singers?
- Yes.
Please give me a chance
to say something.
- Ready.
- We can do this.
- Go.
- Three.
- H.O.T.
- That's easy.
That was so easy.
- 3, 2...
- Solid.
- It's Snail, you punk!
- Gosh, it's Snail.
(Snail!)
- The answer is Panic.
- Oh, right. It's Panic.
(Snail will sing "Panic".)
I'm panicking right now.
He and I formed a duo
called Sagging Snail, you know.
- He's called Snail.
- I was...
- My gosh.
- We were Sagging Snail.
He yelled at me when he didn't
know the answer either.
Chul Min, Si Young wants to
try again.
Si Young wants to try again.
Ji Hyo, you can do this.
Give Ji Hyo double points.
Okay.
(Chuckling)
(The embarrassing demand...)
(and the director's quick consent)
Hey, bring it on. Let's do this.
That's the spirit.
- Ji Hyo will pull it off.
- She'll pull it off.
- Bring it on. I can do this.
- Go, Ji Hyo!
- I've never seen her like that.
- Ji Hyo, prove yourself.
- Will Ji Hyo go first?
- Yes.
- Go, Ji Hyo!
- She's good at an open book quiz.
Let's overcome this.
Here's your question.
(Ji Hyo's challenge
for common knowledge quiz!)
In "Parallel Lives"
written by the Greek historian...
Plutarch, the name
of Alexander's horse is...
Bucephalus.
- Then what's the name...
- She doesn't seem to know.
of the horse Lu Bu and Guan Yoo ride
that can run 420km in a day?
(What's the name of the swift horse
that Lu Bu and Guan Yoo ride?)
(Let's go!)
You know the answer, right?
(What's the name of the swift horse
that Lu Bu and Guan Yoo ride?)
- Red Hare!
- That's correct!
(Throwing the newspaper)
(Red Hare)
(Ji Hyo got the correct answer.)
(Unbelievable)
(All the residents are cheering.)
Song Ji Hyo! Song Ji Hyo!
(Her success makes their jaws drop.
They give her a standing ovation.)
That's amazing.
She got the right answer.
Song Ji Hyo!
(The graduation ceremony of
the opsimath of Running Man)
- I did it! I got it right.
- Good job.
- Ji Hyo, you did a great job.
- She actually pulled it off.
- Next up is Jin Wook.
- She sure is an interpreter.
- She knew the answer.
- She's so smart.
That was sexy.
- She's so cool.
- Intelligent and sexy.
She's happy.
I haven't seen her smile like that
in a while.
- I'm proud of her.
- Ji Hyo seems so happy.
Ji Hyo, I'll ask you
about difficult questions later.
I'll tell you the answers.
She's so cool.
She'll probably watch this episode
real time this week.
(Her family and friends will gather
to watch the show together.)
Queen Red Hare.
Let's move on to Jin Wook.
- Let's go.
- Jin Wook, here's your question.
Jin Wook, please succeed.
(I must succeed not to let
Ji Hyo's success go to waste.)
This literally means to glare at
someone showing the white.
This refers to look down on...
Prejudiced view.
That's correct!
What was that? What did he say?
Jin Wook, great job!
He didn't even need to
look through the newspaper.
- That was good.
- He's amazing.
My goodness. He's so smart.
You knew that expression, right?
- It's written here.
- Oh, my.
I knew it would be in the quiz.
(The only person who can't smile
despite her team members' success)
- Si Young, you're up next.
- Sure.
She needs to get it right this time.
This is our last chance.
- We'll be better off giving up.
- Help me, guys.
Si Young said herself
that she had a lot...
- of common knowledge.
- Yes, she did.
- She insisted.
- If you get it wrong again,
you should switch places
with Suk Jin.
Oh, dear. Anyway, I'm ready.
- Get it wrong, and we'll switch.
- Sure.
- Si Young, here's your question.
- Right.
Let's see.
- We all need insurance policies.
- Right.
Which coffee house in London...
gave birth to
the modern insurance industry?
What did you just say?
A coffee house?
A coffee house. Hold on.
A coffee house in London.
(All she did was
repeat the question.)
You should've named
any coffee house you know!
Starbucks!
(Starbucks?)
- Starbucks is everywhere, right?
- Come on!
Starbucks! Unbelievable.
You should've at least
said Star Coffee House.
Si Young...
You should've said it
at least for a laugh.
Tell me about it!
- Si Young!
- It wasn't even funny.
You should've at least
said Mindeule Youngto.
- There are many shops to name.
- MY!
- Star Coffee Shop.
- A punch is what you need.
You'll get beaten up instead.
You deserve a punch.
Not again.
Look at Ji Hyo studying.
How cool!
(Clearing throat)
I haven't seen her like this before.
(Ji Hyo reading a newspaper.
Who would've thought?)
- I should get her a subscription.
- How about this?
Let's give Si Young another chance.
Team Singer should go first.
She must be feeling bad.
Genie, is the color of the mat
rubbing off on you?
Unbelievable.
It's like he's dressed
for a green screen in movies.
- Can you see me?
- What?
No, we can't tell you apart.
Are you sure it's not
rubbing off on you?
- Director.
- We'll start with Si Young.
Si Young, Jin Wook,
- and then Ji Hyo.
- Let's do this.
(Si Young gets a chance
to redeem herself.)
What's the distance between
Dokdo and Ulleungdo,
the two most well-known islands
in Korea?
What's the distance between
Dokdo and Ulleungdo,
the two most well-known islands
in Korea?
It's written in there. I saw it.
- Where...
- It's on this page.
What?
Count it down for her.
(Dokdo that is 88km
apart from Ulleungdo...)
Seriously, Si Young?
Count it down for her.
(She fails to answer
3 times in a row.)
- Seriously?
- Si Young!
- What on earth?
- Unbelievable.
Southwest of Ulleungdo
80km by sea
- A lonely island
- The hometown to birds
- Despite others claiming
- It's theirs
- Dokdo is our land
- Our land!
The answer is in the song.
What's wrong with her?
Even traitor Lee Wan Yong
would know.
- Lee Wan Yong?
- Hold on.
Lee Wan Yong?
(Unbelievable!)
Hold on a second.
(No wonder the sly face
looked familiar.)
(The insult leads
to an altercation.)
My surname is Yang!
You're Lee Wan Yong.
Are you Lee Wan Yong today?
(The laughter therapist
shows no mercy to traitors.)
Traitor, get back here.
I'm done with the mustache.
Lee Wan Yong, you traitor!
(He gets rid of the remnants
of the pro-Japanese traitor.)
- Lee Wan Yong...
- He makes me sick.
Anyway, I've been reborn.
All right!
Lee Wan Yong...
"He makes me sick."
- Let's get back to the quiz.
- Let's do this.
- Red Hare!
(They put their faith in Ji Hyo
and Team Common Knowledge.)
Ji Hyo should go first.
The Red Hare of Mapo-gu.
- Ji Hyo, let's do this.
- You've got this!
(Ji Hyo is ready to gallop.)
- Here we go.
- Go, go!
Novels are treasure chests
filled with vocabulary.
What is the spelling
for the English word "squeeze"?
S, Q, U, E, E, Z, E.
(She even gets the spelling right!)
- Song Ji Hyo!
(The interpreter squeezes
out the spelling...)
(with perfect pronunciation.)
- Song Ji Hyo!
(First "Red Hare",
and now "squeeze"!)
Song Ji Hyo!
(They chant her name
with the same thought in mind.)
- Red Hare!
- Unbelievable, Ji Hyo!
(Proud)
(They ride off like Ji Hyo...)
(who only rides toward
the correct answer.)
- She did it!
- Nice one.
She did it!
- No, wait.
- She did it.
- Hey!
- I'm amazed.
You're amazing.
(Go, Ji Hyo!)
You're amazing, Ji Hyo.
- You did it.
- Unbelievable.
(Finally, Ji Hyo wins the battle
against common knowledge.)
- Nicely done.
- She actually spelled the word.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo,
they're close to success.)
- No way.
- I got the chills.
She didn't even hesitate.
History, English...
What doesn't she know?
She's a genius.
The lady with a sexy brain.
She must be
taking classes or something.
Si Young must really
be feeling the pressure now.
- That was so cool.
- Jin Wook should go first.
- I'll read one more.
- Jin Wook's up.
- All right.
- The man with a sexy brain.
Let's go.
What's the English word
for only seeing...
people in a neutral way
regardless of their gender?
- Gender neutral.
- All right!
(That is correct!)
Gender neutral.
(Once again, he answered
without looking at the newspaper.)
Nice!
(Si Young collapses
on the table again.)
Come on up.
Okay!
All right.
(Joy is shared
by tossing him in the air.)
Okay!
The man with a sexy brain.
Okay, gender neutral.
- That was incredible.
- Okay.
You both couldn't be sexier.
It's like I'm watching art.
That's 2 down, 1 to go!
Si Young, you've got this.
It's the final question of the day.
Guys, get ready
to rise on your feet.
Si Young must feel burdened.
Here we go.
- Oh, no...
- Si Young, focus.
Focus. I got it.
She's been reading this
for over an hour now.
Adam Smith!
Sorry?
He didn't even ask the question.
- I was just getting fired up.
- Here we go.
Si Young, focus.
Focus. I got it.
In "Snow-falling Map"
by poet Yoon Dong Ju,
who is "Soon Yi"...
that he desperately searches for?
- 5, 4...
- Soon Yi, Yoon Dong Ju.
"Snow-falling Map"!
(She repeats the question.)
(Time's up.)
Give her 10 minutes, will you?
- Just 10 minutes.
- I'll give her 5 seconds.
- What was it again?
- 4, 3...
Jin Wook, what's the answer?
The snow. The snow!
- Darn it.
- Wait, it's the letter.
- The letter.
- Let's get going.
- Have a good day.
(He's holding back harsh words.)
The letter.
Letter.
- The answer is "our people".
- The letter.
Seriously?
Don't you know what a metaphor is?
- It was a metaphor.
- So much for laughter.
Why insist on being on
Team Common Knowledge?
All you had to do is read it.
"Our people". How hard is that?
Why not sit around and guess
names of celebrities instead?
Names of singers.
- She's clueless.
- Sit down, everyone.
Okay, I'll see you all
in the chat room.
(It seems like the residents
have come to an agreement.)
Come on.
(Now 2 people will
have to receive the penalty.)
- Unbelievable.
- What else can we do?
We should open
another chat room immediately.
I smell jjamppong!
- You're right.
- I smell jjamppong too.
Jjamppong?
I bet you're hungry.
- It's here!
- Your meal is here.
(It's time to eat!)
I see it receives applause.
Take whichever you want.
- We'll serve ourselves.
- Sure.
You should serve this for us.
Got it. Can you wait though?
There's quite a lot.
Unbelievable.
Suk Jin has never done
anything for others his whole life.
- You ordered a lot though.
- Jong Kook...
Of course. This is tangsuyuk.
- Tangsuyuk's a good choice.
- Here you go.
- Si Young.
- Yes?
Here are fried dumplings.
- They had it on the menu.
- Here you go.
No way.
Here you go.
It's what you wanted, right?
- Can I get some wet wipes?
- Wet wipes?
Coming right up.
He must be the part-time server.
(He must be the part-time server.)
We're missing the sauce.
He doesn't like it
when people tell him to sit down.
- We wanted to dip.
- We wanted it as a dip.
Are you kidding me?
Did he pour the sauce over?
(Sighing)
- That's insane.
- We wanted it as a dip.
How inconsiderate!
This is plain crazy.
We explicitly told you
that the sauce would be a dip.
Who pours the sauce over tangsuyuk?
No wonder that they say
"Beating is the answer."
I mean it.
(Beating is the answer?)
Kwang Soo, hold on.
Beating is the answer?
- "Beating cures all."
- Isn't it "cure"?
You do know that
knowledge is power, right?
Kwang Soo's just as clueless.
(Even Se Chan's vocabulary
is wider than the bar exam taker.)
"Beating is the answer."
- Beating...
- Beating is the answer.
Here's some Coke.
(Meanwhile, the genie
delivers Coke to the residents.)
Here.
Why are you pouring it here?
This is rice.
Coke and rice? Are you insane?
- There aren't any cups.
- But the rice...
- Just drink it.
- You poured it over rice.
- Hold on.
I'm busy too, you know.
I need to eat as well.
What's wrong with you?
Who pours Coke over rice?
How many are angry with him
right now?
Suk Jin, my gosh.
(Anyway, I dealt
with all of their requests.)
(They vote for the second time
after lunch.)
(Kwang Soo gets busy right away.)
(Lee Si Young.)
I'm already casting my vote.
What's this though?
"Books are the legacy..."
"left to mankind by great geniuses."
Why is this quote here?
The books must be a clue.
We opened a chat room
and left Si Young out.
I mean...
I couldn't be more disappointed.
(Se Chan, goodness.)
Look at Se Chan.
How many chat rooms are there?
(Si Young was terrible
in the last round,)
(so I thought we should
leave her out.)
Si Young's been left out.
(Se Chan tries something.)
(He holds a video conference.)
- My gosh. This is...
- No way.
What's this?
This is incredible.
(While Se Chan pats
himself on the back,)
(Kwang Soo gets busy.)
(Si Young, there's a chat room...)
(He tells on Se Chan to Si Young.)
(Shocked)
(Kang, So Min, Haha agree
about casting a vote your way.)
No way.
Se Chan made a chat room
and left Si Young out,
so I told her that.
This way,
she won't cast a vote my way.
(Kwang Soo,
Se Chan did the same earlier,)
(but left you out instead.)
- Hold on.
- No way.
Can you believe this?
(Se Chan got caught
making multiple chat rooms.)
I can't believe this.
Which room is Se Chan in?
(You made a chat room
and left me out?)
Just a second, guys.
Si Young's here in my room!
(She's here in person
to rattle his cage.)
(Streaming live)
I bet you'll get a punch
in the side.
(The scary, forced union)
Hold on.
(Kwang Soo is going somewhere.)
Hey.
- Is it true?
- What is?
Did you really open a chat room?
- What do you mean? What chat room?
- "Si Young..."
- Did you leave me out?
- What?
- No, I didn't. Trust me.
- Did you really do that?
- How could you...
Wait. Hang on a second.
- She's actually hurting me.
- Did you really leave me out?
Hey, she's actually hurting me.
Wait.
I think he's getting beaten up.
She went to his room.
Leave now.
Can she take those boxes?
- Shut it...
- You can't take the boxes.
She's like a game destroyer.
- You can't ignore the rules.
- How dare you?
Do you all want to get beaten up
by her?
Will you come to your senses
after that?
She always does everything
as she pleases.
Kwang Soo, hurry up
and cast your vote. Let's vote.
- My gosh.
- Guys.
- Jin Wook.
- Yes?
The people in this chat room are...
Ji Hyo, So Min, Haha, you, and me.
So I think we should all vote
for Si Young or Kwang Soo.
- I should vote now.
- I'm still here.
What?
- Hey, Se Chan.
- I'm sorry.
I said, I'm still here.
(His camera is turned off.)
Hey.
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
(While the others are doing
underhanded things to each other...)
I think I should vote for Se Chan.
(Jae Suk cast his 1st vote
for Se Chan.)
(Do Hyun also quietly cast
his 1st vote for Si Young.)
(These 7 people voted
for the 1st time.)
(He got the password of Box 1
after casting his 1st vote.)
Oh, I have to cast my vote
to get the password.
(He finally found out the secret
and opened the box.)
This is so unexpected.
(The 7 people who voted
finally got to open Box 1.)
There's an R coin.
(While Jae Suk obtained
an R coin in the box...)
Should I vote?
(If you want to vote, send me
the name of the person.)
I won't vote.
(He decided to trust the others
like he did at the 1st voting time.)
(The 3 people who won R coins
earlier voted again right away.)
How could you be so clumsy?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
(The password of Box 2 is "0128".)
All right.
(He's opening Box 2
as soon as he got the password.)
(There's a mysterious message
with 1 R coin.)
"If you want another benefit,
vote again."
"But if you vote, there will be
another person to get the penalty."
(He can get another benefit
if he votes again!)
(He votes for Se Chan right away.)
(He's like a train of greed
with broken brakes.)
(The password of Box 3 is "9516".)
Has everyone left this chat room?
(He got the password of Box 3.)
(He's opening the box hastily
hoping for a better benefit.)
"Among residents,
you can find one monster."
(There's a message with an R coin
in this box as well.)
(There's a monster
among the residents?)
"To survive, you have to
eliminate the monster,"
"or escape before the monster
eliminates you."
(Among residents,
you can find one monster.)
(It'd be advantageous
if you kept this from the others.)
(Among the 11 residents,)
(there's 1 monster.)
Who could be the monster?
(Se Chan opened Box 3
at the same time!)
He's voting again.
(Kang also opened Box 3.)
I have to escape? From where?
(Only the 3 of them know
about the monster.)
(Escape before the monster
who tries to eliminate the humans.)
(Which of the 11 residents
could be the monster?)
(The others don't know
about the monster.)
"The residents must escape
this place in one hour."
"Among the residents
who fail to escape,"
"the number of people that we just
announced will receive the penalty."
"The ones with the most votes..."
"among those who failed to escape
will receive the penalty."
"Below is how you can escape here."
"Collect seven R coins,"
"and put them into
the coin box in front of your room."
"And you will obtain
the Certification of Victory."
"Go to Ji Seok Genie
with the certificate,"
"and he will take you
to the room of winners."
(Ji Seok Genie will take you
to the room of winners.)
(In the room of winners,
there are comfortable chairs...)
(and all sorts of snacks
for the winners.)
"If you find tickets
that are hidden in random places,"
"you can enter the room of coins..."
"where you can get more coins."
I see. The room of coins?
(The 3 people want to escape
before the monster eliminates them.)
Okay.
(And the other 8 people think
they just have to collect 7 coins.)
(They all need to get 7 coins
and go to the room of winners.)
(And the monster among them
will try to eliminate them.)
(Where is a ticket?)
Who could be the monster?
(Who could be the monster?)
Right now, my goal is...
to get seven coins
and escape from here.
(Get 7 coins and escape
before the monster finds you!)
(They need to find a ticket
to get more coins.)
- Kwang Soo, let's go together.
- Okay.
Darn it.
Tell everyone not to throw garbage
like this.
I thought you found a ticket. Gosh.
(Put your garbage in the bins.)
Gosh. This is driving me crazy.
(It's hard to find a ticket.)
(At that moment!)
(Si Young came right behind him
quietly like she's shadowboxing.)
Where is it? My goodness!
You scared me.
- Why would you do that?
- Kwang Soo.
- What?
- Show me what's in your bag.
Why?
- Do you have any coins?
- Yes, I do. But why...
Give me just one.
This is ridiculous.
What's wrong with you?
- I have only one coin.
- Or do you have a ticket?
This is no joke.
It's like a battlefield.
Wait.
She's trying to rob me of my coin.
Why would you do that?
What has gotten into you?
- She's so scary.
- Did you find any tickets?
Isn't there a ticket there?
- Why? What's wrong with you?
- My gosh.
- Don't be like that.
- Come on.
- You're scaring me to death.
- Right. I'm so scared.
(Jin Wook, the only person with
no coin is searching for a ticket.)
(It's not here.)
(He doesn't have a coin either.
He has a long way to go.)
How would I know where a ticket is?
Oh, my. Oh, yes.
I found one already.
"You want more coins!"
"Come to the room of coins
with this ticket!"
(Mission Ticket)
Where is the room of coins?
(She can enter the room of coins
with this ticket!)
- Did you have any?
- No, I have none.
- What do you mean?
- Pardon?
- What don't you have?
- Nothing.
(She just has to go downstairs.)
(The laughter therapist noticed
her suspicious behavior.)
- Si Young.
- You must have found something.
- What is this?
- She must've found something.
What's in that bag... Gosh.
You startled me.
- What are you doing?
- Stop it. Why...
(You startled me.)
(Running away in fear)
Is there something in the bag?
Is it that big?
Where is she going?
- So soon?
- Can she do that?
What's that?
(The room of coins is opened.)
- Is she going in there?
- Why? Why did she go in there?
- How could she go in there?
- Si Young already went in there.
That can't be.
To get a chance to try
the mission for getting more coins,
you have to cast a vote
for a person to receive the penalty.
- Would you like to vote?
- Yes.
I vote for Yang Se Chan.
You've won a chance to try
the mission by voting.
It's a can-rolling mission.
Roll a can, and you'll get coins...
according to the number that's
written where the can stops.
I'll begin now.
I'll start.
(She can get 2 coins at most.)
(She got no coin.)
Why did you stop there?
(Disappointed)
I failed, right?
You obtained no coin.
- Where is it?
- You mean, the room of coins?
- I can go around too, right?
- Yes.
What... Hey, what should we do
to go into the room of coins?
I read the instruction earlier,
but I'm confused.
(He's writing a request
to Ji Seok Genie.)
The room of coins...
(Please give me a tip
on getting coins quickly.)
The thing is...
I'm trying to figure it out,
but the writer won't tell me.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Thanks.
- I'm here to help you all.
- Exactly.
I got another request
for a hint on the mission.
Give me just one tip.
Ji Seok Genie is...
Entrance tickets are hidden
in random places.
They have to find a ticket to enter
the room of coins and get more...
Oh, I see. I'm going to take care of
this request.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
- I found out something.
- What is it?
- Come this way.
- Your uniform looks too thin.
- I'm very cold.
- Of course.
- I should wear a jacket.
- What is the hint?
- If you find an entrance ticket...
- I already know that.
- Come on. My role in this game...
- Of course, I know that.
Listen to me. My gosh.
(Everyone else knew it
except for Ji Seok Genie.)
You should...
give me some information
so I can grant the request.
Gosh, seriously.
(Kwang Soo feels more impatient
as he knows about the monster.)
- Of course.
- Really?
(Haha is looking for a ticket
enthusiastically.)
Si Young, did you...
(He found a ticket!)
- Hey!
- What's going on?
Hey, give me that.
- I'm the one who found this.
- Hey.
I'll use that ticket. Give it to me.
I'm the one who found this.
(Groaning)
(She's even using
grappling techniques.)
Hey, stop it.
- Let go of it.
- I found this ticket.
(The laughter therapist
lost his laughter.)
Si Young!
(Head-butt)
(She dominated both of them easily
using her entire body.)
I didn't do it.
Leave me out. Leave me out.
- Si Young is so cool.
- She's so scary.
- She's too scary.
- No.
You can't take that!
(Let go of me
when I'm asking nicely.)
No!
- You can't... You can't...
- She's so cool.
- Si Young, wait. Si Young.
- What's wrong with her?
Why does she have to do that?
There must be something
related to the books.
Maybe I should collect
all the books.
We should collect the books
and figure it out together.
How could you have the books
all to yourself?
Exactly. What does it mean?
Try to find some words
to combine or something.
Were these books in your room?
The title of one of the books I had
had "resident" in it.
And it was underlined in yellow.
- "Resident"?
- Yes.
(Jae Suk started looking for other
books after talking to Jong Kook.)
What could this mean?
(He's looking at the books
left in a room.)
There it is.
(Find the other books
with an underlined word!)
Gosh. Someone took
all the books from this room.
Come here and lift this mattress.
(So Min has the books
that Jae Suk is looking for!)
Check this out.
This is number 205.
Let's start with this one.
"One..."
"Monster".
- "You can find one monster."
- "Monster".
(Among residents,
you can find one monster.)
A monster? There is a monster?
Did you see the sentence
the syllables make?
We should combine them.
- Did you see it?
- What was it?
- It was something about a monster.
- Se Chan and So Min figured it out.
- "You can find one monster."
- A monster.
There is a monster
among the residents!
That's right.
There is a monster
among the residents!
"Among residents,
you can find one monster."
There is a monster
among the residents.
(The residents become more nervous
upon finding out about the monster.)
(Se Chan is writing something down.)
(What is Se Chan doing?)
(Se Chan leaves
as soon as Do Hyun comes.)
- What did you write?
- Nothing.
I saw you write something.
No, I erased it.
(He goes to the place where
Se Chan was writing something.)
("Protein" is written
at Jong Kook's room.)
Why did you write "Protein"?
It's Jong Kook's nickname.
"Protein" is the name
of the monster in our drama.
("Protein" is the name
of the monster in our drama.)
- What?
- Excuse me?
What?
Why did you write it?
- It's Jong Kook's nickname!
- Why did you write it?
Hold on. Stop cornering me.
I am not cornering you.
Protein is the monster in our drama.
- Seriously.
- Really?
Yes. Se Chan wrote "Protein"
on the whiteboard.
- What?
- It must be his mission...
to write the monster's name
at each room.
Gosh, I don't know
what he is talking about.
Protein is the monster in the drama?
Then Jong Kook must be the monster!
Is Se Chan the monster?
Doesn't it add up? Think about it.
Se Chan is writing things
on the whiteboard.
- What is he writing?
- Seriously.
- Earlier,
- The name of the monster.
- he wrote "Protein".
- Really?
Where?
There is a high chance
you will be the protein monster.
- Me?
- Yes.
Is there such a thing
as the protein monster?
It's a monster that appears
in our drama.
Really? What does it do?
- It's just the protein monster.
- Really?
- Hey, watch what you say.
- It's just the protein monster.
(Jong Kook, the human protein,
feels uncomfortable.)
Is there such a monster?
- Yes, there is.
- Really?
If it's a lie,
Jong Kook will go after you.
It's in the trailer too.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Is it in the trailer?
- Yes. But...
Are you the protein monster?
Am I the protein monster?
That could be the case, right?
- There he comes.
- Hey.
- Come here for a second.
- Come here.
It's not like that.
Why did you write "Protein"?
I wrote it to tease you.
He says it's the same as the plot
of the webtoon.
- Last week...
- Jong Kook,
he suddenly put his hand
in the pocket.
I collected all the coins.
Congratulations.
A resident received
the Certification of Victory.
(They suddenly hear
that a resident has won.)
What?
(Did someone collect 7 coins
already?)
A resident received...
(Hold on.)
Isn't that your voice?
I recorded it in advance.
- That startled me.
- Seriously.
That really startled me.
- I recorded it in advance.
- Gosh.
(Before the shoot today)
(Suk Jin automated
all the time-consuming tasks.)
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- That startled me.
- Seriously.
I was so surprised to see Suk Jin
when the announcement came on.
I thought you were a genie for real!
What was that? That startled me.
I recorded it in advance.
I recorded a few comments
because I was busy.
Do we have a winner?
It seems that way.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
There is a winner.
- Is it Se Chan?
- Who escaped?
- What is it?
- Come here for a second.
- Something isn't right.
What is it?
Something isn't right.
Should I go in here?
Do you have a request?
(He takes something
out of the pocket.)
(The Certification of Victory)
(Se Chan opened 3 boxes
by voting 3 times.)
(He started out rich
with 3 coins from the boxes.)
(In the 1st room of coins,
he acquired 2 more coins!)
(Then he acquired 2 more coins
in another room of coins.)
Through the mission...
(Thus, he collected 7 coins...)
(and became the first member to get
the Certification of Victory.)
(The Certification of Victory)
This is the room.
(He becomes the first person
to enter the room of winners.)
Congratulations.
Please take a seat...
- and eat tasty snacks.
- Thank you.
- You can wait here.
- Okay.
Congratulations on entering
the room of winners.
Let's have a toast!
That's impressive.
You became the first winner today.
What's your role?
I just show people around and stuff.
- It drives me insane.
- Why didn't I get such a role?
You are working so hard today,
Suk Jin.
It drives me insane.
They are making me do everything
I hate today.
- Seriously.
- I hate running errands.
How did it happen?
I think they gave me this role
to torment me.
(While Ji Seok Genie complains
about his situation)
Is Se Chan done?
He is done.
When did he collect so many coins?
When did he do that?
How did he complete it so fast?
We need to get seven coins
no matter what.
(The residents become anxious
now that there is a winner.)
Is this how it's going to be?
There are no tickets.
(She finally found one.)
I am anxious. Director, hurry up.
(She received another opportunity.)
- Please vote for someone.
- Okay.
I am sorry. Se Chan.
(She votes for Se Chan
to participate in the mission.)
It didn't hit the floor.
(She succeeded to catch the bottle
after it bounced over the ball.)
Thank you. Hold on.
- Director, did I add one earlier?
- Yes.
Did I add one earlier?
I added two!
(I added two!)
Look, there are two coins.
3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
(Si Young collected 7 coins.)
Please take this to Ji Seok Genie.
- Please take me to the room.
- Yes?
Let me see the certification.
(She meets up with Ji Seok Genie.)
- Thank you.
- Okay. Please enter.
It's the room of winners.
My goodness.
(So Min was looking for the coins.)
What was that sound?
Why did I hear a bell?
It wasn't me.
It must have been the whistle.
See? The sound didn't come from me.
What?
(Jae Suk stares at So Min
without a word.)
I didn't know...
(I didn't know...)
you would come of your own volition.
Please don't be like that.
It can't be helped.
Don't be like that.
I am the monster.
(I am the monster.)
(Is Jae Suk the monster?)
(Jae Suk says he is the monster.)
No way.
- No way. Are you serious?
- Yes.
Are you serious? Why?
I am dressed in black.
How could you be the monster
just because you look like one?
(Was he picked as the monster
because of his looks?)
That's so annoying.
Jae Suk.
How could you say
that I look like a monster?
Then there is no twist whatsoever.
I will let you off this once.
That's your pride talking.
(He finishes the skit
by acting cool.)
That's your pride talking.
Jae Suk, are you the monster?
- Of course not.
- Right?
(Who could be the monster
that is hiding among the residents?)
(Jin Wook found a ticket
for the first time.)
All right. I will enter.
Hello. What is this?
You must vote for a member
who will receive the penalty...
to participate in the mission.
Will you vote for a member?
Can I win coins
if I vote for a member?
I won't vote for a member.
(It's the first time
a member refused to vote.)
(Jin Wook didn't vote either
in the 1st vote or the 2nd vote .)
(He decided not to vote
even in the room of coins.)
(Sitting)
Please pick one.
(Please pick one.)
(After refusing to vote,
he is suddenly asked to pick one.)
(There was a hidden rule
of today's race.)
(You can receive a hint
on the monster's identity...)
(if you refuse to vote
in the room of coins.)
(Other residents have voted
without hesitation.)
(But Jin Wook refused to vote.)
(Jin Wook's belief brought
an unexpected chance!)
(Jin Wook picks one
without knowing what it is.)
"Investigation Log Number One,
witness accounts on the monster".
(Investigation Log Number 1,
witness accounts on the monster)
(Hyo Im: The monster is a man.)
(According to the Investigation Log,
the monster is a man.)
(There are 7 men besides Se Chan
who have already won.)
Congratulations. A resident received
the Certification of Victory.
It's the room of winners.
(More residents receive
the Certification of Victory.)
- I am here.
- Here.
It's this room.
This is incredible.
(After Song Kang,
residents enter one after another.)
Here comes another resident.
(Jin Wook figured out a way
to receive the hints.)
(He focuses on searching
for the tickets.)
(He finds a ticket.)
(He enters the room of coins
with ease this time.)
I won't vote.
(I won't vote.)
(He receives another hint...)
A hint.
(by refusing to vote.)
(What could be the second hint?)
(Ga Eun:
The monster was born in April.)
(Five men are remaining.)
(Do Hyun and Jong Kook
were born in April!)
(Could one of them be the monster?)
What are you doing here?
I am looking for tickets.
- Did you find a lot?
- No.
- I didn't find a single ticket.
- This is driving me crazy.
I looked everywhere.
(Do Hyun stops in his track
with a serious expression.)
What is up
with that facial expression?
(What is going on?)
What?
Are you the monster?
You are the monster, right?
I am not the monster.
Didn't you receive something?
You must have a mission.
No.
I don't understand
how Se Chan escaped...
when he was writing things
on the whiteboard.
I guess Se Chan wasn't the monster.
Then you must be the monster.
- Why?
- "Collective Invention".
You...
(I can't believe you.)
I am the fish-man in that movie,
not a monster.
- The fish-man.
(Jin Wook searches everywhere
for another ticket.)
(While looking at the desk,)
(he moves in a hurry.)
(This laptop...)
(stayed with the members
since morning.)
(Does the laptop contain
information?)
(He sees something.)
(The laptop is locked
with a password.)
(Hint for the password)
(What does the hint mean?)
The hint.
(Jin Wook studies the notebook
for a while.)
(Then he goes through the rooms.)
- Jin Wook.
- Yes?
You know something, right?
No, I don't have a clue.
Putting the books together...
You are looking for books.
- The number...
- You need a number, right?
That's right.
- You aren't the monster, are you?
- No.
I can't be the monster.
I know the number.
(I know the number.)
(Does Jae Suk know the number?)
Avoiding the penalty
isn't the end of it.
It's here.
(While looking for the hints,)
All the books are here.
(Jae Suk put the books together.)
(If you put the books
in the order of the room number,)
2028.
(you get four numbers
at the bottom.)
What does 2028 mean?
(Jae Suk didn't know
the purpose of the number.)
What is the number for?
- Shall we work together?
- That's right.
Okay.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- You aren't the monster, are you?
- Of course not.
(They enter in 2028.)
(The laptop becomes unlocked.)
"Only those who received
the Certification of Victory..."
"by collecting seven coins
become the monster's targets."
Collecting seven coins
makes you a target.
(The secret behind today's race)
(They could make
fewer people receive the penalty.)
(To receive coins,)
(some residents voted for the others
to receive the penalty.)
(For the tickets,)
(they even had scuffles.)
(As a reward, they won
the Certification of Victory.)
(But the Certification of Victory
actually is...)
(the Certification of Greed.)
What?
(Se Chan was the first to receive
the Certification of Greed.)
(He got eliminated by the monster
that feeds on greed.)
(The other residents who entered
the room of winners...)
(became the monster's targets
as well.)
You are out.
What?
(The greedy residents met
a tragic end.)
I see.
The message is that you die...
if you live selfishly.
(The second piece of information
in the memo)
"The monster's name tag..."
"contains the password of the exit
for humans' survival."
"Rip off the monster's name tag
to acquire the password."
(Humans win if they get the password
and escape through the exit.)
We need to eliminate the monster.
Who could the monster be?
(Humans win if they avoid the coins
and rip off the monster's name tag.)
(Hiding behind the secret identity,
the monster takes out the winners.)
(The hints suggest...)
(that Jong Kook and Do Hyun are
the monster candidates.)
Where did you receive
so much information?
I didn't vote for a member.
(He didn't vote for a member
in the room of coins.)
That way, I received a hint.
This game teaches you
various lessons.
My goodness.
You shouldn't desert the others...
no matter what.
Will you vote?
No, I won't vote.
Please pick one.
Gosh, I should have done this
from the start.
(He looks back on the days
he was busy voting.)
"Witness accounts on the monster".
(Jae Suk receives
the Investigation Log as well.)
(Investigation Log Number 1,
witness accounts on the monster)
(A Reum:
The monster is among the guests.)
I won't vote.
(Upon receiving the tip-off,
Ji Hyo refused to vote as well.)
This is why you shouldn't be greedy.
(What does her hint say?)
This is driving me crazy.
"The monster isn't wearing glasses."
(Yeon Ju:
The monster isn't wearing glasses.)
(Investigation Log Number 1,
witness accounts on the monster)
(The only member who fits
the witness accounts is...)
That means the monster is Do Hyun.
(Lee Do Hyun.)
(All the hints point to Do Hyun.)
- Hey!
- Yes?
- He wasn't born in April, right?
- That's right.
I wasn't born in April.
Do Hyun, were you born in April?
Yes.
- Jong Kook was born in April.
- I was born in April.
(Jong Kook was born in April,
but the monster is a guest.)
(What are you doing?)
(Ripping off)
(Do Hyun is out.)
You are the monster, right?
(Four hints pointed to Do Hyun.
What's his identity?)
What was that?
- You are the monster.
- I am not the monster!
What?
(Isn't Do Hyun the monster?)
I mean... I mean...
Aren't you the monster?
(All the hints pointed to Do Hyun.)
(But Do Hyun was a human.)
(Sad)
I mean...
All right.
(At that moment)
We will give a coin to Jin Wook.
- What?
- Why?
- Why does he get a coin?
Why?
- You ripped off the wrong name tag.
- What is going on?
- What?
- Why does he get a coin?
- I don't know.
- The race will continue.
I don't know.
What is going on?
So Do Hyun isn't the monster?
(Jin Wook knows that coins
will get him closer to elimination.)
- What?
- Why does he get a coin?
- I don't know.
- The race will continue.
- Are you the monster?
I am not.
The hint said
the monster is among the guests.
I am not the monster.
So Do Hyun isn't the monster?
(Who is the real monster?)
(The eliminated members: Se Chan,
Si Young, Song Kang, Haha, Do Hyun)
I should gather more hints.
I think...
My goodness.
I found it.
(She finds a ticket
for the room of coins.)
Let's hurry up and go.
(She picks the Investigation Log.)
(What will it say?)
"Investigation Log Number One,
witness accounts on the monster".
Hold on.
(I get it now!)
Guys! Guys! Guys!
Guys! Hold on.
Did you find a hint?
Listen.
Seo Rim, Yeon Kyung...
"A Reum is lying."
- "A Reum is lying."
- A Reum?
(Investigation Result:
Among them, A Reum is lying.)
(A Reum:
The monster is among the guests.)
It's a lie.
The monster isn't among the guests.
(A Reum's witness account is a lie,)
(so the monster isn't
among the guests.)
- A Reum?
- Earlier...
What was A Reum's witness account?
Where is it?
Then the monster is among us.
Then I am the only one
who fits the description.
You are the only one.
- Jong Kook.
- While that's the case...
You are the only one
who fits the description.
- Let's rip off his name tag.
- I am the monster?
(Jong Kook denies it vehemently.)
(What's his identity?)
(Panting)
No! That's not enough!
More. More.
More.
I love it.
(While pumping up his muscles,)
Who is it this time?
(Jong Kook receives a call.)
Hello.
You couldn't suppress your desire
for muscle growth.
You will turn into a monster
from this moment.
What are you talking about?
My muscles are being well-fed now.
Gosh.
No, it's not enough.
(He starts lifting weights after
hanging up the mysterious call.)
(But...)
(He turns into a muscle growing
monster with high skit engagement.)
(A protein monster was
born like that.)
You will win if you induce
the residents to give in to desire,
and put out eight humans.
(Induce 8 humans to give in
to desire, and put them out.)
They shouldn't be hidden too well.
(He relocates the tickets so he can
arouse the desire of humans.)
Okay.
(He relocates the tickets so he can
arouse the desire of humans.)
That's it.
(He must enter the room of coins
from time to time...)
(to avoid suspicion.)
I'm a monster,
so I can't do it anyway.
(Grinning)
Okay, I got it.
It's hard.
(To humans who went to the room of
winners after collecting 7 coins...)
- What is happening?
- Did you succeed? Okay.
- Did you?
- Gosh, Jong Kook.
- Okay!
(Ripping)
Jong Kook, gosh. What happened?
You punk. You came back so quickly.
(What happened?)
Wait a minute, this is unfair.
(Jong Kook came to kill the winners
in his spare time.)
- I'm really okay.
- How could you do this to me?
- So follow me.
- No.
(3 people couldn't be his target
since they didn't collect 7 coins.)
- I...
- Grab him quickly.
So Min, grab him quickly.
Do you think it will be okay
to do this to me?
Do you think it will be okay?
(They ripped his name tag.)
- Do you think it will be okay?
- We had to rip it off.
- What is it?
- Is he a monster?
- Let's take a look.
- Gosh.
- Yes.
- You... This is...
(The sign of monsters
and the password)
- You punk!
- Gosh.
- He really is the monster.
- Jong Kook.
- How could you look in my eyes...
- Wait a minute.
79?
Why is it "79"?
- The race isn't over yet.
- Jong Kook was born in 1977.
(Monster Jong Kook is out,)
(but the race isn't over yet.)
- He was born in 1976.
- That's right, 1976.
(Does the emergency exit password
only have two digits?)
It's different from
the book hint earlier.
There's one more monster.
(There is more than one monster?)
(According to the book hint, there's
one monster among the residents.)
(For some reason, there seems
to be another monster.)
Isn't it either Kwang Soo
or Jin Wook then?
No, it's really not me.
- How could we trust you?
- He also ripped the name tag off.
It's Kwang Soo then.
- Naturally...
- Let's go to Kwang Soo.
- Let's go to Kwang Soo. Hurry up.
- Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo is outside.
- Hurry up.
(They get separated to go to
each building to find Kwang Soo.)
(At that moment!)
This is unbelievable.
(So Min found the mission ticket.)
(She received another
investigation log.)
"Monster eyewitness account".
(Investigation Log 2,
Monster Eyewitness Account)
(Min Hee: The monster
isn't in their 50s.)
It's Kang!
Wait a minute, investigation log
1 and 2 are different.
(There are also numbers
for the investigation logs?)
Are they the same or different?
(If you look closely, investigation
logs have numbers written on them.)
(But the members couldn't figure out
the difference of the numbers.)
(Even after acquiring
"Investigation Log 2",)
(they mistook the hint thinking it
was pointing to the same monster.)
(Yeon Ju:
The monster isn't wearing glasses.)
(The number of investigation logs
implied there are two monsters.)
Yoo Jae Suk.
(But at that moment...)
- Since you collected seven coins,
- I didn't.
the Certification of Victory
has been issued to you.
I didn't collect seven coins.
(At that hour, Kwang Soo is
in front of the coin bank.)
(He puts in several coins and
gets up mysteriously.)
(Yoo Jae Suk's room?)
Do I really have to go there
after receiving the coins?
- I...
- Just come.
(While Genie left the room,)
(the protein monster appeared
after hearing the news.)
- I heard that you...
- Oh, my!
(Lee Kwang Soo is out.)
- I already told you.
- Isn't that right?
- What?
- Did we get something?
(The humans who were dejected
from being out received a message.)
(Running Man Administrator 1,
Will you remain as a human?)
(Or will you resurrect
as the monster's underling?)
If I go out as a monster
and the monster wins,
I won't receive the penalty, right?
Can I be the one to choose?
(1. They can resurrect
as the monster's underling.)
(2. But they can't rip
name tags off directly.)
(3. They will automatically receive
the penalty when they're out.)
I...
will become the son of the monster.
But I suddenly became
so embarrassed of myself.
I was suddenly reminded
of the things I did.
I'll just become a monster.
(Song Kang and Se Chan took long
to announce their resurrection.)
(Kwang Soo was putting coins in
secretly as an underling.)
Kwang Soo.
(But Jae Suk and Jin Wook
appeared.)
(As soon as he got caught,)
(he started a grand release
of the coins.)
(Lee Jin Wook is on the way.)
(Ripping)
- Kwang Soo.
- Where did you put them?
Come here.
(Underling Kwang Soo is out
permanently after doing his job.)
This is it.
- He's a monster.
- "Underling 3"?
Lee Kwang Soo is completely out.
The race isn't over yet.
- What is this?
- Monster Underling 3?
Am I number three in rank?
(He's the last in ranking
among the underlings.)
Kwang Soo, are you number three
among the monster's underlings?
(You're also not a monster?)
(In the meantime, Ji Hyo received
another investigation log.)
"All of the eyewitnesses are lying."
(Investigation Log 2,
Monster Eyewitness Account)
(Investigation result:
All of the eyewitnesses are lying.)
(Yeon Ju and Min Hee are lying.)
(The monster is wearing glasses.
The monster is in their 50s.)
(The real monster is leading
his two underlings.)
(Ji...)
(Seok...)
(Genie.)
Please go up.
No, don't crash. Don't crash!
No!
(His mood swings maximize
according to the KOSPI index.)
Please go up.
Who is it? I'm really busy!
Hello?
You couldn't suppress your desire
to become rich.
You will turn into a monster
from this moment.
What is this? Don't make
prank phone calls!
It has to go up.
(He was only watching the chart
crashing while ignoring the call.)
(He turned into a monster
that went crazy because of stocks.)
(He's the number one actor when it
comes to this kind of acting.)
I will also turn all of you
into monsters.
(A stock monster was born.)
(This comment confused the members.)
("There's 1 monster
among the residents.")
(Among the residents,
there was Kim Jong Kook.)
(Aside from the residents,
there was Ji Suk Jin.)
(The secret behind
the requests is...)
And there's another mission...
- for Suk Jin.
- Okay.
Write down the requests all day,
and pass them on to
the administrator Ji Seok Genie.
Ji Seok Genie has to take care
of all of those requests.
- Me?
- Yes.
Taking care of those desires...
will seem like a joke to others,
but we will give you two a coin
for each request.
You can give all of the coins
to someone who doesn't have seven.
(They can save their coins
in the human coin banks by force...)
(with the coins they earned
from the requests.)
(Ji Seok Genie's request time
started like that.)
(Plus 1 coin)
(Ji Seok Genie saved coins
from inducing the desire of humans.)
(Plus 1 coin)
You got a total of 12 coins.
Okay.
Si Young made me mad today.
(Ji Seok Genie's first target is
Si Young.)
(He saved coins by force.)
Si Young's room...
(Si Young mistook all of them as
her coins blinded by desire.)
I added 2!
Look, there are 2 coins.
(She was out with the monsters'
cooperative play.)
(He was teased all day, but monster
number 2 was preparing for revenge.)
Okay.
Kwang Soo, I helped you.
(Ji Seok Genie)
(He appeared imposingly
with his underlings.)
Am I number three in rank?
- Kang, why did you come out?
- Me?
- I'm his tour guide.
- I requested a tour.
Yes, please come this way.
(He gathered his underlings with
the ridiculous excuse.)
(He's a monster, but he was
mistaken as a zombie.)
Wait a minute.
(Jae Suk and Jin Wook still don't
know that Suk Jin's a monster.)
- Jin Wook, are you a monster?
- No, he's not.
Kang, why did you come out?
(Ji Seok Genie's preemptive attack)
- Wait a minute.
- Rip his name tag off.
Kang, rip his name tag off.
- Is it Kang?
- Rip it off.
Kang, grab him.
(The two didn't see the hint,)
(so they think that guest
Kang is a monster.)
Grab him.
- Let me go.
- Rip it off.
- Song Kang!
- Grab him.
(Song Kang is out.)
- I ripped it off.
- He's a monster.
- He's out.
(Jae Suk, the 7th human,
is out as well.)
Who is it?
Grab him.
Is Suk Jin a monster?
What is happening?
(Hey! Is Suk Jin a monster?)
Who is it? I'm out.
Jin Wook!
You need to rip Suk Jin's
name tag off.
(Detective Lee Jin Wook versus
Monster Ji Suk Jin)
- No!
- Oh, my.
(Jin Wook just grabbed
Suk Jin's name tag.)
(The person who rips it off first
wins. Who will be the winner?)
Wait a minute.
(Ripping)
(Human Lee Jin Wook is out.)
Good job.
(It was Suk Jin.)
(Team Monster won after
putting 8 humans out.)
(The race ended.)
Okay, I will tell you the results.
The monster among residents
who eats the desire of humans...
- was Kim Jong Kook.
- Gosh.
The monster aside from the residents
was Ji Suk Jin.
- Yes.
- It was Genie.
- Genie betrayed us.
- Gosh.
Why do you have
so many underlings?
As such, Team Monster won.
- Gosh.
- Really?
- Honestly, I...
- You made this happen?
- Suk Jin...
- I could have won.
- He did such a good job.
- Really?
He left while leading underlings,
but he was really not trustworthy.
I blamed you.
Among all of the humans, five of
them will receive the penalty.
That's a lot.
Kwang Soo and Kang,
who used to be humans,
had their name tags ripped off.
They're penalty candidates.
Me?
That was the condition
of resurrecting.
That's right.
And 5 among the humans... We ended
with 5 humans earlier, right?
In that order, a total of seven are
penalty candidates.
Penalty candidates.
Please draw a card now.
(They will select 3 people to
receive the penalty with a draw.)
He survived.
- I survived.
- Haha survived.
- I also survived. Next.
- What is happening?
- Are you okay?
- Do Hyun...
Did you die?
- Penalty.
- Gosh.
Wait a minute. Who will receive
the penalty between the two?
1, 2, 3.
(Between Kwang Soo and Song Kang,
who will receive the penalty?)
- 1, 2, 3.
- Penalty.
- Gosh, Kang.
- Song Kang...
He's really unlucky.
That's amazing.
For today's penalty, you will
get your cheek slapped with water...
to cleanse your human desires.
- It's simple.
I understand why people want to come
again because they're upset.
- That's right.
- Come again.
- I kept thinking about that.
- You will be reminded of this...
when you go back home.
(He takes a refreshing shower.)
1, 2, 3.
(Splash)
Be careful.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I'm sorry.
- I was too fast.
- That was cheap.
I would like to thank the four leads
of "Sweet Home".
- Good job.
- "Sweet Home"!
"Sweet Home"!
(2021 Running League
Rookie Draft)
(This is 2021 Running League
Rookie Draft.)
(The two club owners
made an appearance,)
(and distinctive rookie players
followed them.)
(I will never select that player.)
(That player is kicked out.)
(Only players whom you don't
want to pick have participated.)
(Real world-class players
finally came.)
(Korean Monster, Monster pitcher,
Ryu Hyun Jin)
(The crown prince
of masterpiece sliders!)
(Korean Big Leaguer, Ace KK,
Kim Kwang Hyun)
(He'll finally show his masterpiece
slider at Running Man.)
(He threw it to the ground.)
(We're better than him.)
(Because of their inadequate
performance,)
(their annual salary is
decreasing mercilessly.)
(Are you going to cut my salary?)
(Did they even end up breaking off
the deal with the club owner?)
(I will quit.)
(Running League's big match will
continue right away after that.)
(Are they playing baseball
with a frying pan...)
(and flippers?)
(Running League ended up
with a bench-clearing.)
(World-class Ryu Hyun Jin
and Kim Kwang Hyun's...)
(variety show baseball match,
what will be the result?)
(Ryu Hyun Jin and Kim Kwang Hyun,
Fiery Stove League)