(It's a summer day with drizzling rain.)
Hello.
It's a cloudy morning.
(It's cloudy, but they still say hi brightly.)
Hello. Good morning.
I'm in Yangpyeong now.
(All the members start the shooting separately.)
It wasn't raining until just a few minutes ago.
(What are we doing today in this rain?)
I know.
(The phone rings right at the moment.)
What's going on?
(What's going on?)
Answer it.
What?
Why are you calling me when you're standing right in front of me?
Just pick it up.
(The director calls Kwang Soo who stands right in front of him.)
Hello?
What are you doing?
(What is going on?)
What is going on?
Hello. This is Running High School.
I hear double voices.
Hello?
(They got a call from Running High School.)
Hello. This is Running High School.
(Running High School?)
What? High school?
What did you say?
Running High School?
Your youngest sister, who's a model student of Running High School...
and expected to go to a prestigious university,
skipped school saying she would take an audition to be a singer.
Darn it.
Please find your sister and send her to school.
(Find your sister and send her to school.)
My youngest sister skipped school?
My youngest sister is acting up again.
(Rapidly immersed)
She wants to give up school to become a singer.
- Exactly. - I actually support her dream.
(His universe collapses.)
- You can't do that. - Why not?
That's what I did.
(They have to send their sisters to school.)
Today, we're going to have Unstoppable Sisters Race.
(Unstoppable Sisters)
There will be 4 teams of 3 members.
Suk Jin, your goal is to collect as many academic points...
(2 members and 1 guest are a team.)
as possible with your siblings.
(They have to collect academic points...)
And you should make the top two teams...
(to have their sisters graduated.)
to have your sister graduate...
(Top 2 teams will get exempted from the penalty.)
and get exempted from the penalty.
So there will be a penalty today.
At the same time, your youngest sister...
(The youngest sisters will collect audition points.)
can collect audition points without her siblings.
The youngest sister with the highest audition points...
(The youngest sister with the highest audition points...)
will win a prize and get exempted from the penalty.
(will win a prize and get exempted from the penalty.)
And the second place will also win a prize.
(And the 2nd place will also win a prize.)
You should keep your sister from winning audition points.
(The youngest sisters have to collect audition points.)
She will definitely try to get more audition points and win.
(The members have to collect academic points.)
(Their youngest sisters are selected randomly.)
Among the four sisters,
you should find your real sister and send her to school.
(They should find their real sister and send her to school.)
Then you will get academic points by the order of arrival.
(Then they will get academic points by the order of arrival.)
Including the youngest sister, once three siblings get together,
your siblinghood will be judged.
(Once three siblings get together, their siblinghood will be judged.)
You should hold each other's hands and say "We are siblings."
(2 members and 1 sister will say,)
If you say it with a fake sister,
("We're siblings.")
the sister will get 10 audition points.
(Once the 3 siblings get together, they can move to the opening place.)
(If at least one of them is not a real sibling,)
(the sister gets 10 audition points.)
If we pick a wrong person,
(The youngest sisters might lie to get audition points.)
we will be helping her pass the audition.
They are going to lie to us to get 10 points.
They all are going to say they are my sisters.
This is the cue card that has your sister's location and number.
(They got a cue card with the sister's information on it.)
Ennik and Yong Sun?
(Hyun Ju, Young Ji, Ennik, Yong Sun)
I don't have a sister with such names.
Are these their real names?
(The youngest sisters' real names sound new.)
- They are their real names. - Really?
Yong Sun?
I'm in trouble. I don't know any of them.
(The identity of youngest sisters are only revealed to viewers first.)
Is Young Ji a member of Jewelry?
Gosh, there's no way I can go to an Ivy League college.
(The first youngest sister is the high school rapper, Lee Young Ji.)
I'll just try my best.
(A high school rapper with a sweet voice, Lee Young Ji)
(Popular rapper Lee Young Ji is known for her sweatsuit.)
(High school student, rapper, sweet voice, likable, Lee Young Ji)
(They randomly picked their siblings before the race.)
Can I just pick anything I want?
(Who are Young Ji's siblings?)
Can I take a look at it?
(Laughing)
(Young Ji's siblings are Haha and Kwang Soo.)
Nino Maximus Keyser Soze
(She seems really excited even before the race.)
Sonador and Sparta
All right.
Hang on. Hyun Ju? I think I know who she is.
(The second sister Hyun Ju is...)
One of the sisters already picked her team.
(Jessi. Her real name is Ho Hyun Ju.)
Please pick one of the three cards.
(Jessi picks a card among three cards.)
Yoo Jae Suk!
(Jessi's brothers are Jae Suk and Se Chan.)
Yang Se Chan.
Just go up, Ho Hyun Ju.
(She's the natural enemy of Jae Suk and Se Chan.)
- Why are you yelling at me? - Come here.
Don't look down on Korean Americans.
(She's a Korean American with a strong pride, Jessi.)
(Her natural enemies are her family for today.)
My goodness.
I found it.
(The third sister, Ennik's identity is revealed.)
Ennik is Jeon So Mi, right?
(Jeon So Mi, Ennik Somi Douma)
(So Mi is back with her new song, "What You Waiting For".)
(Today, she's a daring sister who never listens to her brothers.)
(As soon as she checks her siblings...)
Oh, no.
(Who on earth are her siblings?)
Am I supposed to be happy about it?
(She's positive.)
I picked Jong Kook and Suk Jin.
(So Mi's siblings are Suk Jin and Jong Kook.)
So Jong Kook is coming to catch me...
while shouting "Sparta"?
(He's a scary brother with a big build.)
Can I just go back to school?
(She became a model student again.)
Yong Sun? Who's Yong Sun?
It means a ship for the king.
(Yong Sun is...)
Hello.
(Solar of MAMAMOO.)
(Solar has an enthusiastic zest and brilliant charisma.)
(Her real name is Kim Yong Sun.)
(This is her first time to join Running Man alone.)
(Solar's siblings are Ji Hyo and So Min.)
Solar, your siblings are...
Song Ji Hyo and Jeon So Min.
(The siblings)
Okay.
(Jae Suk, Jessi, Se Chan, Jong Kook, So Mi, Suk Jin)
(Ji Hyo, Solar, So Min, Haha, Young Ji, Kwang Soo)
This is what I'm going to do. They all are my family.
(The youngest sisters can get audition points...)
(if they call members who aren't their siblings.)
Okay? The problem is they will recognize my voice...
once I call them.
(They would recognize my voice.)
Hang on.
Hello? It didn't sound like me. It was like a guy.
(She practices a low voice.)
Hello?
I should fake my voice.
Hello? Right. I'm your sister.
(Then she receives the first call.)
Can I say I'm their sister?
Okay. Gosh.
(She clears her throat.)
- Hello? - Hello?
Is this Hyun Ju speaking?
(He hasn't noticed yet.)
Yes.
Are you Ms. Baek Hyun Ju?
(He's totally wrong.)
Yes, I am.
(Low and husky)
- I see. It's you. - Right.
(Glad)
I know who you are. You're a member of SEEART.
(He's talking about something else.)
- Right? - Yes.
It's you. I know everything about SEEART.
(He looked up Hyun Ju and thinks she's a member of SEEART.)
I already know everything about today's guests.
(He shows off even when he's wrong.)
Because Hyun Ju is my sister.
(Too confident)
Suk Jin, I'm your sister.
(Suk Jin has no idea that he's being fooled.)
- Shall we go together then? - Let's do that.
(He will come to see Jessi.)
- All right then. - Okay.
(He totally fell for my lie.)
- Bye. - Bye.
My gosh.
(She gets another call while feeling excited.)
What? It's Kwang Soo.
(Low voice)
Hello?
- Hello? - Hello?
What...
(He hangs up right away.)
Isn't it Jessi?
What was that? He hung up on me.
(Her identity is revealed after saying hello.)
I'm very offended.
Jessi, I'm sorry.
Why did you hang up on me like that?
(Her plan failed.)
I'm so sorry, Jessi. I was just surprised.
(He was surprised by her charisma.)
Did you pick two members?
Yes. I picked two members.
Who are they? Am I one of them?
You are one of them. And there's one more.
(She's trying to fool Kwang Soo.)
Who is it?
Well... It's Suk Jin.
(She lies to Kwang Soo.)
(Hanging up)
What? My gosh.
What was that? He hung... Hey!
Hang on. It's Jae Suk.
(It's Jae Suk's call.)
Hello?
(She changes her voice even when she is talking to her real brother.)
- Yes? - Hyun Ju.
Yes.
Hyun Ju, are you my sister?
I'm your family. Come over here.
You're Jessi, aren't you?
(Laughing)
I told you you shouldn't say, "Hyun Ju".
(She fails in altering her voice.)
It said, "Hyun Ju", so I thought that was your name.
(She couldn't hide her Korean American voice.)
I didn't know you were Jessi.
I mean...
Hurry up and come over here. You're my family.
(She can't be stopped.)
- Hurry up. - Come on.
(Should I trust her or not?)
Come on. Hurry up. It's raining, and I have a stomachache.
(Complaining over the phone)
My T-shirt is too tight.
Hey.
(Grumbling about her T-shirt all of a sudden)
It's not like I picked it out. Why are you complaining to me?
Anyway, come over here. You're my brother.
(She summons Jae Suk using her T-shirt.)
Are you sure?
- Okay. I'll come over. - There's one more person.
(I'm going to call all of them.)
- I trust you. Okay, see you. - See you.
(Meanwhile, Solar...)
- The phone is ringing. - Take it.
(Solar's siblings: Ji Hyo and So Min)
- Hello. - Hello.
(She discreetly talks to him.)
Hello. Hi.
Do you even know who I am?
Is this Haha?
Wait, Solar. I'm obviously not your brother.
That's not it. You are. That's why.
(She fails because she didn't recognize his voice.)
To me, you totally sound...
like you're lying.
You totally sound like you're lying.
(Solar sounds like she's lying.)
I'm not your brother,
- but you want 10 points. - That's not it.
You're one of my siblings.
(She firmly lies to him,)
- So just come over here. - Okay.
(then starts to pester him.)
Anyway,
just come.
I can't really tell from your voice,
so let's meet.
Okay.
(It worked.)
Where are you, my precious sister?
(Se Chan arrives without knowing it's a trap.)
- What are you doing? - Hi, Se Chan.
(It's a bit awkward with her.)
- Hi. - Hi.
- Should I go out? - You're wearing a school uniform.
Yes.
(Awkward)
I'm not going to school.
(All of a sudden)
All of a sudden?
(She suddenly starts acting?)
I'm not going to school.
All of a sudden?
- What are you talking about? - I mean...
(The role-play was too sudden.)
- You brat. - I'm not going to school!
Come on, Solar. Your brother...
(He plays along for now.)
has been looking everywhere for you.
Hold on.
- Hello. - She's always looked down on me.
Hello.
- Who is it? - Yong Sun.
(The second person who fell for Solar's lie appears.)
- Yong Sun! - Her eyes... Oh, Haha is here too.
(Haha, another expert on role-playing)
- Yong Sun! - I'm sorry. I have to go.
(He's already immersed in it.)
- Hey. - Yong Sun!
- Yong Sun, please don't do this. - I'm not going to school!
(They start acting.)
- Hey. - I'm not going!
Think of how Mom raised us.
Go away!
(The two professional role-players act passionately.)
I'm not going to school!
Are you insane?
- Don't hit her. - How dare you...
(The master of role-playing is pleased.)
The thing is, we somehow look like each other.
- Kind of. - Right?
You look like both of us, but in a good way.
(She quickly admits it.)
- Don't you admit it? - You're right.
All right. I'm sure we're siblings.
(Haha and Se Chan decide to be judged.)
- Yes, definitely. - Definitely.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- We're siblings. - We're siblings.
You're not real siblings.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(She fooled us!)
What happened?
It's raining.
(Leaving them quickly)
I'm sorry.
Bye.
Solar, you gained 10 audition points.
(Solar gets 10 audition points.)
- Unbelievable. - Yes!
You... Okay, I get it now.
(After getting what she wants, Solar says goodbye to them.)
- Goodbye. - You should become a good singer.
Neither of us is her sibling?
(Running)
(They called each other brothers until just a minute ago.)
Let's run.
- Solar wasn't my sister. - Gosh.
(They start looking for their real siblings.)
I have this nagging feeling that Jessi is my sister.
(The scary Korean American sibling)
I wish So Mi was my sister.
Please.
She's in the van?
(Kwang Soo came to meet Jessi.)
(Happy to see her, he bursts out laughing.)
- Come on, get in. - You're wearing a school uniform?
This school uniform is way too tight.
- Get in. - I mean...
Is no one else here?
(Kwang Soo also walks into Jessi's trap.)
Too much is happening right now.
Hyun Ju!
(Her real brother, Jae Suk, appears.)
- Jae Suk is here. - Hyun Ju...
He's not my brother.
- Hyun Ju... - Tell him he is.
Hi, Jae Suk.
(He greets Jae Suk with a big smile after giving Jessi a mission.)
Why is it so crowded here?
- Is it really Hyun Ju? - I just got here.
Hyun Ju.
Why are you wearing so much perfume?
A girl should smell good.
(Feeling a headache due to too much perfume)
I mean...
Gosh, it's giving me a headache.
I'm dizzy. I breathed through my mouth in the car.
(Breathing with his mouth)
My shirt is too tight. I can't breathe.
(Her shirt is too tight.)
- You're the one who tightened it. - Hey.
(She did it herself.)
- Loosen it. - Unbelievable.
- It's tight around here. - I mean...
(She made the shirt tight by herself.)
- Hey, come on. - It's tight in the armpits.
You tightened the shirt yourself.
It's tight around here.
(Her complaint about her shirt won't seem to end.)
I get it. Stop.
- Gosh. - Okay.
Why did you only tuck your shirt in the front?
(The shirt...)
- It's a style. - Why would you do that?
- It's a style. - What is that?
You're unbelievably tall.
(Speaking out her mind)
How can you say that to your big brother?
(Enraged)
How can she say that to her big brother,
- looking him up and down? - "You're unbelievably tall."
(Jessi's siblings: Jae Suk and Se Chan)
Let's give it a go.
- No. Hold on. - No?
I'm not sure if you're my sister.
(He's still not sure.)
She's been saying this the whole time.
She told me you were her brother.
(Helping Jessi)
- To tell you the truth, - Gosh.
(The audition points are right in front of her.)
you guys are my siblings.
We are siblings.
- Let's give it a try. - Okay.
(Let's get judged.)
- What are we supposed to do? - Say, "We're siblings."
- Let's hold hands. - We're siblings.
1, 2, 3.
- We're siblings. - We're siblings.
You're...
- not real siblings. - See?
(Jessi gains 10 audition points.)
See? I told you.
She told me you weren't her brother.
(What?)
- Bye. - Suk Jin and I are her brothers.
(Kwang Soo trusts Jessi's words.)
Gosh, why are you doing this?
I don't know.
- So you are her brother? - Yes.
(She wants to use Kwang Soo to gain audition points.)
- My goodness. - From the beginning...
Why didn't you tell me?
- I'm leaving. - How does this work?
Just wander around in the rain for a bit...
(He's one to talk.)
- and be penalized later. - This is so annoying.
(I'll call you again soon.)
Should I try with Young Ji?
(Jessi's real brother, Jae Suk, hurries to the next person.)
Young Ji, are you sure I'm your brother?
(Young Ji's siblings: Haha and Kwang Soo)
- Is this Jae Suk? - Yes, that's right.
Oh, my. Jae Suk.
(Using her nasal voice)
Nice to meet you. Hello.
(She tries to deceive Jae Suk while being polite.)
From the way you talk to me,
- I can tell we're not siblings. - Right? No.
Don't I totally sound like your little sister?
(Brazen)
We're family.
All right, Young Ji.
(Then who's the other sibling?)
Who is your other sibling then?
- My siblings are... - Okay.
you and...
(Lying)
(Her real sibling)
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo says he is Jessi's brother.
What? Why would he do that?
Can you bring him over to me?
(Who's lying to my brother?)
- Is Kwang Soo your brother? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo is Young Ji's sibling?)
Jessi says he's her brother.
(Jae Suk calls Kwang Soo after Young Ji's sincere appeal.)
- If someone comes... - Jae Suk is calling me.
Hi, Jae Suk.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
(Whispering)
- Listen carefully. - Okay.
You're not Jessi's brother.
- What? - Young Ji...
- Just keep quiet and listen to me. - Okay.
I'm listening. I'm right here.
(He gets caught by Jessi.)
- Hey, I mean... - Who is it again?
- We're on the phone. - Who is it?
Just because you whisper doesn't mean she can't hear you.
You hang up!
Hold on. Hello?
(Jae Suk, Jessi's real sibling, is abandoned once again.)
Gosh, they hung up on me.
They hung up on me.
Be honest with me.
(Kwang Soo has been held up without getting anything.)
- Seriously. - Ji Hyo is not my sister.
- So who is it? - I'd feel bad if she comes.
(He gets a call from Se Chan.)
- Who is it? - Kwang Soo, where are you?
I'm with Jessi. She's driving me crazy.
- What's his name? - The thing is...
I'm in trouble.
- This is driving me crazy. - Why?
I can neither stay nor leave.
(He can't go anywhere.)
(Meanwhile...)
(Haha came to meet...)
(So Mi who isn't his youngest sister.)
- Haha! - Ennik!
(My little sister, Ennik!)
Ennik!
(So Mi's siblings: Jong Kook and Suk Jin)
Am I...
You're my brother, seriously.
- Are you sure? - I swear.
(Uncertain)
Ennik!
(Se Chan, who isn't her brother, arrives.)
You...
- You... - Hurry!
When did you run out?
Hold on.
(And her real brother, Jong Kook, also arrives.)
Se Chan is running to her. Gosh.
- Four people... - Hold on. Let's wait for Jong Kook.
- Hurry! - Hold on.
(Her strong brother appears.)
- So Mi! - What's going on?
- I'm scared. Let's say it already. - What's with him?
So Mi!
Why are you not going to school?
He's getting into it. Look at him.
(Surprised by his muscles)
- These guys... - Look at him.
(Walking up)
- We're siblings. - You brats...
You're hanging out with So Mi?
- No, we aren't. - She should go to school.
- You little... - Hold on.
(Let my little sister go.)
- Hold on. - You know me, right?
- You two might be brothers. - I'm your little brother.
- I'm your little brother. - You two might be brothers.
(Let me go. I'm her second oldest brother.)
I'm your little brother.
- All right. - You're my big brother.
(Things get out of her hands.)
- Gosh. - She's trying to win points.
- I'm sure she's my little sister. - We're siblings. In 1, 2...
(Certain)
(Except for Jong Kook,)
- We're siblings. - We're siblings.
(she gets judged by her fake brothers.)
- No. - You're not siblings.
(The three of them are not siblings.)
We aren't siblings.
(So Mi gains 10 audition points thanks to the gullible members.)
- Move. - Wait. I'm not her brother?
- You're not. - Neither of us?
(Haha believes that he's her brother.)
Jong Kook, hold her hand.
(He calls Jong Kook to try it again.)
- You gained 10 audition points. - So Mi.
(How lucky am I?)
- I'm your brother, right? - Yes, you are.
I'm pretty sure.
- Let's give it a try. - Ready, go.
(So Mi who wants to become an idol singer...)
- We're siblings. - We're siblings.
(gains more audition points thanks to Haha.)
You're not siblings.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
- But... - So Mi.
- Wait, is Jong Kook your brother? - You gained 10 audition points.
(She lets go of Haha's hand...)
(and holds on to Jong Kook's.)
- I must be her brother. - Yes.
- Really? I am? - Yes.
- You three... - Go away, you punks!
(Get away from my sister!)
- Go away! - How dare you mess with my sister?
(I love my spartan brother.)
You're a bad influence.
Hey, you and I might be brothers.
Se Chan and I might be brothers.
(Is Jong Kook deceiving them?)
- Let's try. - Hold hands.
- Hold hands. - They're only getting her points.
(Se Chan takes her hand as Jong Kook persuades him.)
Let's try.
- We're siblings. - We're siblings.
(With her increasing audition points,)
- No. - You're not siblings.
(she can't hide her smile.)
That was a good idea, right, So Mi?
(Glad)
- Good job. - Right?
Go away.
(Se Chan gets a call from Jae Suk.)
Jae Suk.
Se Chan.
- Hey. - Go away!
I'm with So Mi, and she's not my sister.
(If neither Solar nor So Mi is my sister...)
She's not?
No. The problem is,
I might end up with Hyun Ju.
Gosh, this is bad.
I don't want to be siblings with Jessi.
(Fierce little sister, Jessi)
Even if she's my little sister, I'm scared of her.
- Hey, Brother! - Hi!
(Everyone walks into her trap.)
- Hyun Ju! - My brother!
(Jessi's siblings: Jae Suk and Se Chan)
- My little sister! - This is real.
- Seriously... - Finally...
- Why did you not listen to me? - All my siblings are here.
(You guys are my siblings, right?)
- We're siblings, right? - Suk Jin. Gosh.
Here we are, finally.
- The three of us. - I mean...
- She said it from the beginning. - I know.
(These two have no doubt that Jessi is their sister.)
- To be honest... - You didn't sound so convincing.
Also, she doesn't know the rules.
(Our little sister...)
Be quiet.
- Let's give it a go. - Let's try. Stand here.
(Guileful)
(It's time to be judged with the fake brothers.)
- Stand in the middle. - If we're siblings...
- Say, "We're siblings." - All right.
- We're siblings. - We're siblings.
(Holding her laughter)
You're...
We're siblings.
not real siblings.
Hey, you.
- You're not my brother. - This is driving me crazy.
To be honest,
- you're not. Go now. - Hey.
- You're not my brother. - Hey!
- Who is it then? - I ran all the way here.
(Frustrated)
- Am I your brother? - Yes.
- Why didn't you tell me? - You said it was him and me.
(She gains 20 audition points thanks to Kwang Soo.)
Gosh, I'm leaving. Hey.
You're not her brother either, you fool.
(It's obvious.)
- You're not. - You said from the beginning.
- You're not. - Suk Jin isn't my brother.
He's a fool.
- Where are you? - Jong Kook, where are you?
(At that time,)
Where are you now? I'm with So Mi now.
(her real brother, Jong Kook, calls right on time.)
(As So Mi continues to find her siblings,)
I'm with So Mi.
I don't want to study.
(Solar, who's very into the skit, and Ji Hyo finally united.)
You should at least graduate.
What's the use of graduating?
(She's too into it.)
Hang on. Your second sister is coming, you brat.
(Ji Hyo is the real sister.)
Gosh, you are unbelievable.
(You're definitely my sister.)
If you're my sister, you'll be doomed.
(At that moment, a car arrives.)
- Hello, Ji Hyo. Hi! - So Min.
(The real family, So Min, appeared.)
Hello, So Min.
Wait... Well... You...
Hang on.
(Solar finally got her sisters together.)
If she insists that we're her sisters, that means we're not.
(They'll be the first sibling if they pass the judgment.)
- They're here. - I just abandoned So Mi.
All right. We are... You should say it with me.
(Staring)
- We are siblings. - We are siblings.
Hang on. I just saw Yong Sun's eyes.
- No, I'm serious! - Her glaring eyes.
(The two older sisters get suspicious.)
Seriously, I'm your sister.
(The two older sisters don't trust people from years of Running Man.)
Look at her.
- She seems very excited. - Hang on.
- This is strange. - That's because I'm your sister.
(I'm telling you the truth.)
- Hang on. - Because it's true.
- This is crazy. - We are...
(Urgently)
- We are siblings. - We are siblings.
(Not syncing)
(Discord)
Are we siblings?
- Please say that again. - Should we say we're siblings?
(The three sisters all have strong personalities.)
Yes.
- We are siblings. - We are siblings.
(They barely managed to say it.)
The three of you are...
(Their relationship is finally being revealed.)
siblings.
- Really? - Yes, we are!
(Solar is the first one who met her siblings.)
I'm your sister!
All right. I got you. Let's go home.
- Let's go. - No. I'm not going home.
(Solar met sisters who like to nag.)
- You should graduate. - I'm not going, sisters.
Come on.
- Ennik. - Suk Jin.
- Where have you been? - What took you so long?
(So Mi meets her siblings a few minutes later too.)
- We are siblings. - We are siblings.
The three of you are...
(She's the second one to meet her siblings.)
- siblings. - Yes!
- She is our sister. - Let's hurry.
(Now there are 1st place and 2nd place winners.)
- You are my sister. - Yes, I am!
(Who will take 3rd and 4th place?)
Let's go.
- Hello, Jae Suk. - Young Ji.
(They have no time to waste.)
- It's nice to see you. - Are you my sister?
(Jae Suk visits Young Ji.)
Of course I am. Isn't it obvious?
I look like your sister.
(Are you my sister?)
You do?
- Young Ji! - Yes?
(It's my third time meeting my sister today.)
Young Ji.
Hey, Young Ji.
I've been looking for you.
(Let's do this fast.)
Can I hold your hands once?
- Just once. - Why are you...
- Are you sure? - Let's do this.
(Are you telling the truth?)
You said Kwang Soo and I were your brothers earlier.
- That's not true. - You said that to me too.
No. Just hold my hands first.
- Did she say that to you too? - I'm serious.
(Avoiding eye contact)
- Are you lying to me? - Gosh, no.
Just hold my hands.
- Is she lying to me? - We're siblings of the same blood.
(She rushes to judgment.)
- 1, 2, and 3. - 1, 2, and 3.
- We are siblings. - We are siblings.
The three of you are...
- not siblings. - Darn it.
(Young Ji acquires audition points.)
It's Haha.
- Darn it. - It's Haha.
- Are you serious? - Haha and Kwang Soo.
(She finally tells the truth.)
- Is that true? - Haha and Kwang Soo, forever!
- I'm serious. - Are you serious?
- I am. - Can you swear?
- Is it true? - Young Ji.
- Feeling! Cross! - Intuition!
- Am I Intuition? All the sudden? - Yes.
Young Ji! I can't believe this. Hold on.
(I fell for it again.)
- We need Kwang Soo now. - Hold on. Then I should...
We should hurry.
(They can complete the sibling once Kwang Soo arrives.)
We need Kwang Soo.
- Okay. I'll call him. - Where is he?
(Jae Suk goes back to Jessi.)
Come right away. I just sent Jae Suk away.
(Kwang Soo gets a call from Haha.)
I'm on my way.
Jessi lied to you to earn more points.
I should get going now.
Haha, this is a good chance to run away from her.
I'll be right there.
(While Jessi talks to Jae Suk, Kwang Soo tries to escape.)
Haha, this is a good chance to run away from her. I'll be right there.
Hurry.
(He gets in the van hurriedly.)
Lock the door!
Please start the car. Don't open the door! Never!
Hey! What is she doing?
(Where are you going without me?)
Call the police.
- Call the police now. - Kwang Soo.
(Creepy)
You are my brother! I told you.
No, I'm not.
I'm serious. Wait.
(Jessi never gives up.)
(She threatens her brother as she knocks on the door.)
- You're not my sister. - Hey, you're my brother.
- Come on out. - Why are you being so scary?
- Come on out. - That's not true.
- Kwang Soo. - Why did you jump at the car?
(Brother.)
(Come out already.)
- Just come on out. - We are not siblings.
Yes, we are.
Get out.
(She's crazy.)
Why is she being like this?
It's Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk calls again.)
Hello?
- Why? You have to trust me. - Please start the car.
(Now.)
I'm on my way.
(Kwang Soo escapes when Jessi lets her guard down.)
- Hey! - Hurry up.
I told you to come here.
(I finally escaped...)
(What?)
Hey!
You should hurry.
(Where are you going without me?)
I'm on my way. Why is she being like this?
(Kwang Soo finally escapes after being stuck with Jessi until now.)
Jessi was sticking to my car.
- You have to hurry. - Come right away, Kwang Soo.
(You must get here quickly.)
- Okay. - Jae Suk just left.
I just started off on the wrong foot.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk went to see Jessi.)
- My gosh. - Hey, come on!
- It's Ho Hyun Ju. - You have to hurry.
(They start to nag each other.)
- I was... - It's raining.
And call Se Chan.
(Jessi will form a team once Se Chan arrives.)
Hello, Jae Suk.
Se Chan, hurry and come over. I told you to hurry.
(Se Chan is nearby.)
Jae Suk, I'm almost there. I'm only 1km away.
- Are you sure I'm your brother? - Definitely.
(He double checks.)
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Nino Maximus Keyser Soze
Sonador and Sparta
(She tries to prove that she's his sister by singing his hit song.)
I will not die
- I'm so touched. - See? I'm your sister.
(But Kwang Soo hasn't arrived.)
- Okay. I'll keep calling Kwang Soo. - Thank you.
Hey, bro!
- Come on! - Hurry. What took you so long?
(Se Chan arrives.)
What have you been doing?
(Why did you fool me?)
Jessi, why did you lie to me?
(As soon as Se Chan arrives, they ask about their siblinghood.)
We are...
- He's here. - Hurry.
(Kwang Soo finally makes it.)
- Hurry and come on out. - Hold my hand first.
Hold our hands.
(They don't even say hello.)
- We are siblings. - We are siblings.
("We're siblings.")
(The two families shouted it out almost at the same time.)
The three of you are...
- siblings. - Gosh.
(Jessi's family finally unite.)
- Hey, Jessi. - See? Why did you not trust me?
- Earlier, you said... - You three are siblings.
- Yes! - I told you to hurry.
Why were you there for such a long time?
(Kwang Soo wasted 40 minutes with the wrong sister.)
- Nice to meet you. - It was a long time.
- Let's go. - Get in the car.
(Now everything depends on the time of their arrival.)
You are my sister.
Gosh, this is so fun.
(Whoever arrives first will win 3rd place.)
- Why did you not trust me? - We have to hurry.
We have to get there as soon as possible.
I had no idea.
(Who is the first one to arrive at the opening place?)
Gosh, Ho Hyun Ju.
It's good to see you again.
(Jessi sounds cute when she feels happy.)
You sound quite moody.
- I really like Jae Suk. - You do?
He's like my real brother.
Anyway, don't look down on Korean Americans.
(Brother's warning)
When did I look down on them?
- I'd never do that. - You know what? That day...
(I totally respect Korean Americans.)
I respect them.
- When did I do that? - You did look down on me that day.
(She frames him.)
- I was deeply hurt back then. - Were you hurt?
I was also hurt because I didn't understand your English.
(Extremely childish)
- Why? - I'm a native Korean,
and I was hurt.
- You looked down on me. - You're lying.
(Don't look down on Korean Americans.)
No. Seriously, you looked down on me.
(Don't look down on native Koreans.)
- They are so funny. - Whatever.
(The three siblings are already tired.)
- Now that we're here... - It is going to be a long day.
- I'm feeling dizzy already. - I'm dizzy too.
In fact, the production crew wouldn't let me team up with Haha.
- Kwang Soo and me. - Because we're too good.
(The two brothers tell lies to act strong.)
- I see. - It's not fair.
- You two are too good together. - We're just too good.
(She even bluffs more.)
- So it's forbidden. - Yes.
It's like a team of Hulk Hogan and Warrior.
(The wrestling celebrities)
- Okay. I get it. - You don't know them, do you?
Of course I don't know.
That's disappointing. She's like a machine.
- She just answers. - She's a machine.
(Lee Young Ji, a reaction machine)
- She's... - That's true.
She's from a factory.
Young Ji, I think you got yourself a perfect character.
It just suits you perfectly. You're still a great musician.
(She has her own color in every area she tries.)
You're like Lee Kwang Soo in the world of rappers.
(Will she be Lee Kwang Soo in the world of rappers?)
(She sounds hesitant and confused.)
She's been showing machinelike reactions, but she just stopped it.
I'm honored.
He still wins awards as an actor.
(They enter the opening place.)
That's nice.
- You didn't hear me, did you? - No.
Jessi's team is around here.
(They are only apart by 30 seconds.)
Really?
- We have to run. - Are they behind us?
(The team who finishes in 3rd place gets 20 points.)
(The 4th place gets only 10 points.)
Please stop here.
(They start running immediately.)
(Young Ji's team finally arrives at the opening place.)
Where is the flag?
Where is it?
(What place will they win?)
Are we the last one to come?
- Are we the last? - You're in fourth place.
(They win the last place.)
- I told you to hurry. - Are we in fourth place?
(We came 30 seconds ago.)
What's with your hair?
What's wrong with you?
(Everyone succeeds in bringing their youngest sisters.)
- Kwang Soo. - Are we in fourth place?
I can't believe this.
Like I said before,
(They can get academic points and audition points today.)
you can get academic points and audition points today.
You will get academic points as a team.
(Academic points are team points.)
The two teams with the lowest academic points...
(The two teams with the lowest academic points will get penalties.)
will get a penalty.
(You'll need to get as many points to avoid the penalty.)
Isn't it just for the fourth?
Both the 3rd and 4th will get a penalty.
And the youngest sisters will get audition points as an individual.
(The youngest sisters will get audition points as an individual.)
The top two sisters will get a prize.
(The top two youngest sisters with highest points will get a prize.)
And the one with the highest points will be exempted from the penalty.
(Audition points are points given to the youngest sister.)
- Really? - That's great.
(The sister with the highest points will be exempted from the penalty.)
- Wow. - Okay.
Solar, Ji Hyo, and So Min who arrived first get 40 points.
(The points will be rewarded depending on the order of arrival.)
(Team Solar gets 40 points.)
- Wow, you liar! - Yes.
What?
So Mi, Jong Kook, and Suk Jin who came in second get 30 points.
(Team So Mi gets 30 points.)
- I'm envious. - That's not bad.
You liar!
20 points for Jessi, Jae Suk, and Se Chan.
(Team Jessi gets 20 points.)
- Come on! - Come on!
And 10 points for Young Ji, Haha, and Kwang Soo.
(Team Young Ji, the last place, gets 10 points.)
- Look at her. - This is so upsetting.
(They'll decide whether to use them...)
- I thought Jessi was my sister. - It's his fault.
(as audition points or academic points.)
And your sisters got...
audition points according to the number of times...
(Audition points gained by fooling other members...)
- they fooled you. - Okay.
(will be revealed now.)
Jessi fooled you twice, so she got 20 points.
(Jessi gets 20 audition points.)
- What? Only twice? - Yes.
(She celebrates with just 20 points.)
That's not much. You'll see.
- Isn't it big? - No. It's not a big number.
Solar got 10 points.
(Solar gets 10 audition points.)
Solar lied only once?
So Mi got 30 points.
(So Mi gets 30 audition points.)
(She fooled them 3 times?)
I helped her with it.
And Young Ji got 30 points.
(Young Ji gets 30 audition points.)
- Okay! - Okay!
- That's a lot. - You did a good job.
(Celebrating)
It's all from me.
How did they get so many points?
Jessi, why did you send me away?
I didn't tell you to leave.
Hey.
They got together again. It will be uproarious today.
(Feeling tired all of a sudden)
They are so loud.
(Jae Suk and Jessi tend to wear everyone down.)
- Hey. - He seems embarrassed.
It's loud already.
Come on.
Let me introduce our guests one by one.
(It's time to introduce the guests.)
We have Solar here.
(Solar of MAMAMOO with a delightful voice)
What's with your hair, by the way?
(Looking closely)
Are you shooting a historical drama or something?
(If...)
(Her hair is neatly combed straight back in half.)
This is the real Korean-American style.
(She pokes Jae Suk with her fingernail.)
(It stings.)
This is...
This is the real Korean-American style.
- Is it a Korean-American style? - This is the Korean-American style.
- No. - Yong Sun...
(What's he talking about?)
- is from Daejeon, I think. - It's Korean-American style.
- I'm from Seoul. - You're from Seoul?
Stop acting like a know-it-all.
(He's humiliated for pretending to know.)
Don't act like a know-it-all.
(She lived in Seoul for her whole life.)
- Seoul. - She's from Korea.
(He apologizes right away.)
I'm sorry.
- But you look prettier like that. - This is...
Be quiet. Come on.
(Please)
I'm not going to talk anymore.
(Sulking)
You still say what's on your mind though.
(Don't be ridiculous.)
(Admitting)
- Right. - This is nice.
You look so pretty.
- So pretty. - I heard...
(Solar's personal channel is popular.)
Solar's personal channel for posting videos...
- has... - She has a lot of subscribers.
(2.25 million subscribers)
2.25 million subscribers?
- Yes, I do. - That's insane.
(Haha has 100,000 subscribers.)
- That's incredible. - She's a queen.
2.25 million subscribers?
(Surprised)
That's incredible.
She's a queen.
What did you just do?
This is my signature greeting.
(For her personal channel)
Can you do it for us?
Sol, la, ti, do
(That's cute.)
- Sol, la, ti, do - How cute.
- Sol, la, ti, do - Sol, la, ti, do
(Future YouTubers copy her.)
- My goodness. - I guess that's necessary.
- Yes. - It's a YouTube special.
(Personal channel)
I should start a channel too.
- You should. - You could make a channel too.
(Trainer Jong Kook's channel)
- I'm going to. - It will do well.
(He requests a collaboration.)
Let's do it.
(Hitting)
- What was that? - Hold on.
(He smashes down with a fly swatter.)
There was a fly.
(He catches a fly out of nowhere.)
- Did I get it? - Yes, you did.
- Was there really a fly? - There was really a fly there.
- Did you get it? - I did.
(The fly catcher is in action.)
- I got it. Look. - He really did.
- Here it is. - Gosh.
(Catch and release)
- Look. - He really did.
(Flying away)
- Here it is. - Gosh.
(He's helpless as there's no evidence.)
- It's still alive. - Was there really a fly?
- There really was one. - There was.
- Luckily, it survived. - It did.
(It's healthy.)
- It survived. - Thank goodness.
I think you hit me a bit too hard.
(Maybe I'm imagining.)
- No. - You were hitting the fly, right?
- That's how you kill a fly. - Right?
It wouldn't die if you hit it lightly.
("Fly People" ends.)
The next person is Ennik.
(The fruity human vitamin, Jeon So Mi)
Ennik.
Didn't you recently release a new song, Ennik?
That's right. I released a new song. It's coming out as a single.
(So Mi returned with a new song.)
You've returned with a single. What's your song called?
"What You Waiting For".
(Her new song is "What You Waiting For".)
- What are you waiting for? - We should hear her new song.
(My sister)
- Let's see it. - Let's see it.
Let's go!
(Very excited)
("What You Waiting For" by Jeon So Mi)
Let's go, So Mi!
The song is so good!
(My sister is the best.)
- It's so good! - They're all great dancers!
(It's a great combination of a fresh melody and powerful choreography.)
(Is he cold?)
It's fast.
(It's hard to wait for Jeon So Mi's charms.)
So Mi's "What You Waiting For".
Waiting for.
(Please listen to it.)
It was so good.
- "What You Waiting For". - She's really good.
(Out of nowhere)
(Feeling tired)
- It's okay. - Come on.
- Let's go. - This is not a competition.
- I know. This is not a competition. - Yes. Okay.
(Uncontrollably hyper)
- Let's go. Okay. - Okay.
Jessi is coming out with a new song too.
My album is coming out on the 30th.
(Jessi recently returned with a new song too.)
- Your album is? - Yes, my new album.
What's your song called?
"Nunu Nana".
- "Nunu Nana"? - "Nunu Nana".
(Excited already)
- "Nunu Nana". - Let's hear Jessi's new song.
- Okay. Let's do it. - "Nunu Nana".
- Let's go! - We don't have expectations.
- "Nunu Nana". - Please turn up the music.
Yes, Jessi!
("Nunu Nana" by Jessi)
(A groove full of vibes)
- "Nunu Nana". - Aren't you doing this?
(She rushes towards Se Chan all of a sudden.)
"Nunu Nana". Why are you looking at me? Look at the cameras.
(Feeling pressured)
(Ignoring)
Hey, listen!
(She shows off her true swag by turning her back to the cameras.)
- 1, 2... - Look over there.
(Why Se Chan?)
Why was she looking at me?
(She finally looks at the camera.)
- That's right! - Here we go.
(She flexes her coolness.)
This is so cool.
(She loves it.)
Put it up, put it up.
(It's a powerful groove from a charismatic singer.)
(He's cold again.)
The song is good.
(She finishes with a spin.)
(She's not done yet.)
(My performance starts now.)
(Stop the music.)
(She ignores him and continues.)
How long is she going to promote her song?
Nobody can stop her.
(In a trance)
- Enough. - Cut!
- Cut! - Cut!
- Cut! - Cut "Nunu Nana".
(She stops as the audience complains.)
Okay!
- Hey. - Hey!
- Hold on. - That was amazing.
(Who said 1 minute?)
They told me to do it for one minute.
- No. It was 30 seconds. - It was good.
(It's only fair.)
Why is everyone so scared of her?
(Everyone watched her performance quietly.)
- I purposely went to Se Chan. - Why?
- I know why. - In the lyrics...
Every time she forgot the lyrics, she turned around.
No.
- It's true. You didn't sing... - That's not true.
(It wasn't a performance?)
- until you remembered the lyrics. - That's not true.
There is no choreography here.
(Explaining)
But here, I sing,
What did you say? What are you saying?
(It's getting too lengthy.)
Okay. That was "Nunu Nana".
(Interrupting)
- Come on. - Come on.
(He stops her before he gets exhausted.)
- Wow. - It's okay.
Come on. Wait.
(He quickly moves on to the next question.)
You're the youngest of three siblings?
You have two older brothers?
- Yes. I have two older brothers. - This is exactly the same then.
(That's right.)
- It's exactly like that right now. - Right.
But my brothers aren't like them.
What do your brothers do for a living?
(What do her brothers do?)
- One of them... - Your oldest brother.
This is my first time hearing this.
- One of them... - It's interesting.
- What does one of them do? - One of them...
(One of my brothers)
I'm not really sure what he does.
- Is he unemployed? - No.
(This is how a real sister treats her brother.)
- He's not unemployed. - It's okay if he is.
- No. - Are you not in touch with him?
He's an entrepreneur. He does a lot of different things.
He does various things.
My other brother works at the top for Samsung.
He works at the top?
He works for Samsung in the US.
- Semiconductors? - At the top?
- Does he have a high position? - He works in finance there.
(Is that how you say "semiconductor" in Engish?)
- Semiconductors? - Semiconductors?
I couldn't remember what it was.
- I got confused. - Was that supposed to be English?
(That was terrible.)
(He never reflects on himself.)
- Semiconductors. - Semiconductors.
He works for a big company.
(Anyway, her brother works for a company.)
Do your brothers worry about you...
(What did her brothers say about her working in Korea?)
working here in Korea?
(Nothing)
No.
They raised me to be strong ever since I was young.
- I could tell. - Ever since I was young,
(She's charismatic.)
they told me I would do well and that they weren't worried.
(My brother said...)
What did they see in you?
What do you mean by that?
(She has a straight face.)
(Speechless)
Don't get so upset.
(Sad)
- Can't I ask you a question? - Don't look down on her.
I can ask, can't I?
Don't look down on Korean-Americans.
- When did I look down on her? - Hey!
(The Korean American is upset.)
Why do you think they said that?
(The native Korean looks sad.)
- I was asking a serious question. - Don't look down on her.
I don't. Don't worry.
(The talk ends up as a disaster.)
- Okay. - It's been a while,
(Finishing up)
- but we are... - Is this how it's ending?
(Is that all?)
Yes.
This is enough.
(Let's stop.)
- So I guess if you get serious, - Jessi, that's enough.
(She never gets exhausted.)
- it ends like this. - No.
I'm sorry, but I'm getting exhausted just watching you guys.
- I'm exhausted too. - My stomach hurts.
(Exhausted)
- I'm getting dizzy. - Me too.
(Many feel tired because of Jessi.)
- "Nunu Nana". - Why are you dizzy?
(He's still finishing up.)
There isn't enough oxygen.
(Jae Suk finishes it up before it gets worse.)
Okay. The next guest is Lee Young Ji.
(The monstrous teenager rapper, Young Ji)
Lee Young Ji!
Nice to meet you all.
You may all know Young Ji from "High School Rapper".
(She was the winner of "High School Rapper 3".)
Yes.
- First... - She's going to tear up the stage.
She's really amazing.
(Respect)
Since Young Ji has joined us,
we would love to hear you rap.
(They must listen to Young Ji's rap.)
- Let's see it. - Our eardrums are in for a treat.
("I Am Lee Young Ji" by Lee Young Ji)
(It's amazing from the start.)
(Is he shadowboxing?)
(They regrouped as Z-KIRI.)
(Her rap makes everyone groove from side to side.)
(I'm Lee Young Ji!)
Young Ji!
(Exclaiming)
She's good.
(Young Ji's rap cleaned our eardrums.)
The younger kids are really good.
(Jessi's a hip-hop audition senior.)
- They're good. - They are.
- Her style is different from Jessi. - So Mi...
(That reminds me...)
and Young Ji are the only ones born in the 21st century.
- 21st century. - That's right.
We're a new generation. We're Generation Z.
- You're Generation Z? - I'm Generation X.
- I'm Generation X. - No, you're not.
(What are you talking about?)
- No, you're not. - I am.
How are you Generation X?
(The real Generation X is upset.)
I'm Generation X.
- You're Generation 50. - You're from the Joseon era.
- Generation 50? You punk. - Yes.
You're from the generation of acoustic guitars.
Yes, you are.
(They say it together.)
- C'est Si Bon. - C'est Si Bon.
- C'est Si Bon. - You are.
(He can't deny it.)
- C'est Si Bon. - You grew up in that era.
I'm Generation X. You and I are Generation X.
(He drags Jae Suk into it.)
No. Generation X is...
- C'est Si Bon. - C'est Si Bon.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G
(He calls upon Song Chang Sik, a member of C'est Si Bon.)
It suits him.
(That's it.)
(He sings the best hit from his era.)
- This is it. - He made it work.
(He made everyone laugh.)
Why do I know all the lyrics?
Only the people who know Song Chang Sik's song...
(The 21st-century kids can't relate to it.)
laughed at this.
(The 20th-century men are sad because they get it.)
- I know. - Right.
- They don't know the song. - Everyone.
You guys got academic points by finding your sisters.
(Each team earned points for finding their sisters.)
The scores haven't been added to your team's score.
(The points haven't been added to their team's score.)
We're going to have a time called Sister's Room...
(They're going to have a time called Sister's Room...)
with the points you gained after every mission ends.
(with the points they gained at the end of every mission.)
What's Sister's Room?
During every time we have Sister's Room, the sisters will...
(4 classrooms with sisters' names on them)
go into their classrooms...
(The sisters will go into their classrooms...)
and have a choice to either...
answer an essay question...
(and either answer an essay question or film an audition tape.)
or film an audition tape.
If the little sister decides to answer the essay question,
(If sisters want academic points,)
the points they will get will be added to your academic points.
(they will answer the essay question.)
However, if she chooses to film an audition tape,
(If they want audition points,)
then the points will go to her audition points.
(they will film an audition tape.)
If the older siblings don't trust their younger sister,
(If the older siblings don't trust their youngest sister,)
you can open the classroom door and go in to find out.
(they can open the classroom door and go in to find out.)
We can find out if they're answering the question or filming an audition.
If they're filming an audition tape,
(If she's filming an audition tape,)
the points received will go to the team as academic points.
(they will get academic points for catching her filming.)
But if they were answering the essay question,
(If they were answering the essay question,)
(they will lose all the points they have gotten.)
you will lose all the points you have gotten.
(The Possibilities for Sister's Room)
You have to be smart. We need to work well together.
(Trust, Find Out)
(Answering an essay question)
(Filming an audition tape)
(The team's point changes depending on whether or not you trust her.)
- This is insane. - You have to use your wits.
If you trust your little sister later,
go to the place where you leave your stamp on the classroom door...
(If they trust their sister, they'll leave a stamp on the door.)
and mark it with a good job stamp...
- and come back. - Look at her.
If you don't trust her, you can open the door.
(If they don't trust her, they can open the door.)
You're a broadcasting machine.
The little sisters will go to their classrooms.
(The youngest sisters will now go to their classrooms.)
Are we starting right away?
Do I have to do this for my team or for myself?
(Will they answer the essay question for the team?)
(Or will they film the audition tape for themselves?)
We are a family.
We're a family, so my happiness is your happiness.
Don't you agree?
My brothers... What should I do?
(All the sisters have entered the relevant room.)
Shall we go?
(The older siblings get into action.)
- Yes. - Let's go together.
I can't figure out what Young Ji is going to do.
(My sister)
(They have arrived in front of their sisters' rooms with headphones on.)
(What is Jessi doing?)
(Ho Hyun Ju's room.)
(Is Jessi answering the essay question?)
(Or is she filming an audition tape?)
Jong Kook, this is So Mi's room.
(What did So Mi finally decide to do?)
Can we open it now?
(Their siblings plan outside their doors.)
Yes, you can.
Jessi won't be bothered to film an audition tape.
(Jessi probably won't...)
I doubt she'll film one.
(Agreeing)
(They decide to trust her.)
(If she's answering the question, they'll receive 30 academic points.)
My brothers put their trust in me, right?
(She's answering the essay question.)
(Team Jessi receives 30 academic points.)
Do we trust her?
(So Min and Ji Hyo trust their sister too.)
(Team Solar receives 50 academic points.)
They decided to trust her.
I think my sisters will trust me.
The other two teams trusted their sisters.
They showed their trust.
- Really? Who? - Let's enter the room.
(Then...)
- Did you also? - Not yet.
Are you going to enter the room?
(Nodding)
Let's do this.
(They don't hesitate to choose to enter.)
(If Young Ji is answering the question,)
(they'll lose all their points.)
(If she's filming the audition tape,)
(they'll receive all the academic points.)
(She was filming the audition tape!)
What did I tell you?
(She is busy filming herself.)
(Then she puts on a straight face.)
(I can't believe you didn't trust me!)
What did I tell you?
I knew it.
(The academic points they earned will be added to their team points.)
Of course, I'm right.
- Young Ji! - What did I tell you?
(Young Ji fails to gain her individual audition points.)
Why didn't you trust me?
- You're seriously asking that? - We knew this would happen.
(She was caught by her two cunning brothers.)
- Right? See. - She was filming.
- See? She was filming a video. - I knew it.
(We got you.)
I thought you'd trust me.
(You guys are mean.)
I was wondering whether you'd come in or not.
- I knew it. - That's what I was wondering.
(Feeling hurt)
- We knew it. - It's over now.
- Our team is done for. - Nice!
There's no trust between us at all.
But I want to be an idol singer.
But you should study, Young Ji.
The essay question should come first.
Let's barge in there. I bet she's filming.
Shall we?
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook decided to barge in too.)
(Will So Mi be filming just as they suspect?)
There's no trust between us at all.
See?
(Dancing her head off)
What did I tell you?
(She was filming just like her days on "Produce 101".)
See? What did I tell you?
See? I knew it.
(Sobbing)
- Right? - Good thinking.
So Mi, really?
- Right off the bat? - Why did you come in?
I thought you'd at least study in the first round.
(So Min wanted audition points, and it turns into the academic points.)
Right? We made the right decision.
My brothers are like real parents.
I can't believe all their nagging.
(The first round of Sister's Room is over.)
(Current points)
(Where the first mission awaits the members)
(Three chairs...)
(and six water balloons?)
Everyone,
I hope you're fond of your siblings.
- Sure. - Yes, of course.
(Our Solar is the best!)
- We're the perfect family. - I'm loving my siblings.
- I finally met my family. - Me too.
(Bringing the family together)
What does that matter anyway?
(Cranky)
Is there no bond?
(Team Jessi is already showing bad teamwork.)
Come on.
The first game...
will allow you to show your brotherly and sisterly love...
(Unstoppable Sisters Race, first mission)
by asking for phrases you want to hear.
The game is Just Say Anything.
(Just Say Anything)
- I love it. - Just Say Anything?
(It must be about being quick in saying something.)
- Just Say Anything. - Hold on a second.
Bo Pil, wait a second.
I bet you came up with this game...
- to make us lose. - He's right.
- Be honest with us. - It's because she lived abroad.
(Wait.)
- Be honest with me. - You're targeting her, aren't you?
(The combination of Jessi and random words make them nervous.)
You know that Jessi's bad at games like this.
Of course, he does.
- It's why we're playing it. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Jessi's siblings are sensitive to the rules.)
- Unbelievable. - They'll have a lot of screen time.
(Quiet)
- Okay. - They'll steal the attention today.
Jae Suk, wait.
- Suk Jin's jealous. - Why?
(Our big brother is getting jealous.)
He's jealous of you getting all the attention.
You can't speak Korean well, right?
(I also want attention.)
- He's jealous? - I don't speak Korean.
(She plays along.)
- Yes. - No.
- You don't speak Korean? - I don't speak Korean.
(He starts to smile thinking about all the attention they'll get.)
So the little sister...
will sit under the water balloons...
(The youngest sister will sit under the water balloons...)
with a phrase on her forehead.
(with a phrase on her forehead.)
She must guess correctly what her siblings describe.
(She must guess correctly what her siblings describe.)
- This will be fun. - Every 10 seconds though,
someone from another team will remove one of the sticks.
- What? - Every 10 seconds?
Time is of the essence then.
You fail if the balloons all fall before you answer correctly.
The remaining number of balloons will be converted to points.
- I'm the one answering? - That's right.
Let's do this.
- Let's see who goes first. - What's this?
(Deciding on who will go first)
Why?
- What? - Why?
(Jessi gets angry all of a sudden.)
- Jae Suk, are you kidding me? - What?
(They have to go first.)
We're going first?
I need to watch other teams play first.
(I wanted to see how other teams play.)
- But... - Guys.
Guys, let's begin with a laugh.
(This is going to be fun.)
We know who'll come last.
(It'll be hilarious.)
Can I ask for a favor? Since I'm going first,
(Jessi sat down, but she still hasn't understood the rules.)
(Please let us practice once.)
let us do a practice run.
- No way. - We'll just go ahead.
(Her two brothers are firm.)
- No. - How about an example?
Come on!
- Is it a difficult one to guess? - No.
(They calm her down in order to begin the game.)
Am I the one guessing the answer?
(The given word Jessi has to guess)
Is it difficult?
- It's super difficult. - It's difficult.
Do I know these Korean words?
- Yes, of course. - They wouldn't be that cruel.
(Of course.)
- I know these words? - Yes.
- We'll describe the situation. - You know these words.
- Hold on. - You have to do a good job.
Just do it already!
- Let's just begin the game. - Begin the game!
(They protest that they begin the game.)
- Begin the game! - Begin the game!
Oh, my gosh!
(The game begins even when she doesn't know the rules.)
Ready, set, go.
(You aged but didn't grow up)
So this is said...
to immature...
- Brothers or sisters. - Yes, brothers or sisters.
(Said to immature brothers or sisters)
We say this to them.
- What would you say? - When they act foolishly.
- "Gosh..." - "Gosh..."
"Gosh, you stupid cow."
(She says swear words as she gets splashed with water.)
"Gosh, you stupid cow"?
No, no one curses.
(Restless)
There are no curse words.
- Then... - Jessi, listen up.
(The youngest sister isn't so good with Korean.)
Hold on a second.
You need to make it easier for me.
Did you purposely pull the one that would let a balloon fall?
- Darn you. - No, of course not!
- That's not true. - Jessi, don't swear.
(Denying the accusation)
- How could I... - Jessi, come on.
- The clock is ticking. - Calm down.
(10 seconds have passed, and another stick is being pulled out.)
- Okay? - Kwang Soo, pull out another one.
That's a lot of water for just one balloon.
It's all right.
- He got it. - Did you just poke at it?
(Poke!)
He got it.
- Did you just poke at it? - Seriously?
- Hey! - That wasn't my intention.
- I'm sorry, Jessi. - You poked it.
- No, I didn't. - Hey.
(Shameless)
- You popped it. - No, not on purpose.
- Time out. - Jessi, I'm sorry.
(We know that you meant to do it.)
He popped it deliberately.
- I can't believe him. - I swear.
(Kwang Soo is thrown out as he was playing dirty.)
You're out.
- What did he do? - Ji Hyo,
- you do it. - Why would you play dirty?
- But... - Ji Hyo, you can do it.
(Ji Hyo, who's trustworthy, will come in.)
Sure thing.
Jessi?
Jessi, you need to answer this quickly.
(The game will continue fairly.)
- Jessi. - Calm down.
I'm 35, right?
Someone two years older than you...
(Explaining the meaning)
is acting like a child.
What would you say in that situation?
(What do you say when someone older than you is being immature?)
How would you mention one's older age?
I don't know.
(Frustrated)
What do we do with food?
- With our mouths... - That's right.
- Yes, keep going with that. - Add on.
(Is it about the mouth?)
"Shut it!"
Why on earth would that be the answer?
- Calm down. - That's what you came up with?
(She makes a U-turn when she was close to the answer.)
Calm down. Come on, Jessi.
What do you call the length of time we've existed?
- The length of time. - That's right.
(They start explaining the word, "Age".)
- What do you mean? - What's the word for that?
Wordy?
We go from 1, 2, 3...
(Forced laughter)
- What do you call that? - Age!
(I got it.)
- Yes, that's right. - All right, good! So I'm...
- two years older than you. - That's right.
- "Gosh, he's..." - "Gosh, that..."
- "Age..." - Yes?
- "Age..." - She's getting there.
(Did Jessi get the hang of it?)
- "Age..." - What about it?
- Jessi, you're almost there. - I'm almost out of sticks.
(The balloons might fall when one stick is pulled out.)
- I cleared most of them. - Your time is almost up.
The answer is right in front of you.
(You aged but didn't grow up)
The food...
(She might get the answer.)
- What do you do with it? - What do you do?
- You eat it. - Exactly!
- Age. - Yes.
- Eat. - Yes!
(She's not going in the right direction.)
Why are they saying that she's on the right track?
- She's right. - So the age...
(The problem is the brothers, not Jessi.)
- You're only confusing her. - So the age...
- She's not on the right track. - So what we eat...
(As they stutter while explaining,)
- Tell me what comes next. - Okay.
(the water balloons are about to drop.)
What do we call the next location we go to?
- How do we say it? - They'll all drop at once.
- The next location... - They'll drop at once.
(Risky)
- I know. - When we move locations...
Hold on a second.
- You're almost there. - What comes next?
- What do we say... - What comes next?
(Jae Suk tries to explain "where".)
when we need to go to a new location?
"Go!"
"Grow up and leave."
No, that's not it.
(Desperate)
- You're almost there. - You are.
You almost got it.
(They're about to drop.)
When we're on the move...
- It's over for you guys. - What do we say to the taxi driver?
(She'll be drenched in water if she doesn't get the answer now.)
- Just say anything. - Shoot at random answers.
What's the relative pronoun we use?
(They're in their final moments.)
- Your older brother... - "Where."
(Using English)
When he acts silly...
(Welcome to the water park!)
- Your older brother... - "Where."
(The water balloons fall like a stack of dominoes.)
When he acts silly...
Your older brother is being immature!
(Drenched)
What's the answer?
(What on earth...)
- An immature brother. - What...
"Age..." What?
You can't just read it!
She still doesn't know what it means though.
(It doesn't mean you'll understand when you read it.)
"You aged but didn't grow up."
She doesn't know what that phrase means.
- It's too difficult for Jessi. - She doesn't know what it is.
(Resentful)
I've never heard of this phrase before.
It's too difficult for Jessi.
(Team Jessi fails to earn points.)
What's this about one's age?
What does it mean?
(Next up is Team Solar.)
- I bet Solar will do well. - Look.
This is something many of us say.
(Fortunately, it's not that difficult.)
- It could be easy. - It's not a bad one.
(Don't you dare tell people that we're related!)
- Ready, set, go. - I didn't get mine.
If only this was our phrase.
(She starts to act.)
You and your terrible memory.
Solar, keep watching.
Can't you at least shower more often?
(She acts the youngest sister who's embarrassed by her older sister.)
- "Dirty!" - You embarrass me.
No, that's not it. My friends...
(She flutters her arms after getting splashed.)
What was that?
(Their eyes widen after her high-frequency reaction.)
It was only a splash of water.
- What's up with you? - It wasn't a bug, you know.
(Embarrassed)
- I was completely shocked. - It startled me.
What on earth was that?
(The cute little sister is afraid of the water balloons.)
- This is quite scary. - It's all right.
(What was that?)
It's not like the water's hot.
- Yong Sun, calm down. - What's up with her?
How is that scary?
(She focuses again.)
Let's try this again.
Watch me, okay? You...
- You... - "What do you think you're doing?"
- "Do you have a death wish?" - One's scolding the other.
(Has it been 10 seconds?)
These days...
- What on earth... - I'm only removing the sticks.
(Her reaction is like a blockbuster when the water balloons are tiny.)
I'm not spraying the water on you.
All I'm doing is removing the sticks.
It's just...
You're almost there.
"That we're sisters..."
(Frustrated)
- You're almost there. - Stay put, Jessi.
- Do better when it's our turn. - So Min...
(Startled)
(Every time, she responds with a high-pitched scream.)
Look at her.
You and your reactions. Please take your seat.
- She's hilarious. - You're almost there.
(Yong Sun's reactions are the pride of the family.)
- She's great. - I love her reactions.
No wonder her online channel is a hit.
- We should take notes. - She's doing an amazing job.
(Solar, the textbook of reactions)
- You... - I know!
"How dare you talk back to me."
- No. - But it's similar.
(Don't you dare tell people that we're related!)
- You're almost there. - It's similar.
Goodness.
(She smashes into the case of water balloons.)
- Solar, stay calm. - What's wrong with you?
(The master of reactions don't do it normally.)
Please stay seated.
"Don't you dare say that we're related!"
It's similar. You're almost there.
(It has to be "tell".)
- "Don't you dare..." - You're younger, right?
"Don't you dare..." Hey!
(Screaming)
(Instead of the answer, she lets out a high-frequency scream.)
Hey! Hey!
- What's wrong with her? - Hey.
(Solar dolphin flaps to get the water off.)
- Why is Yong Sun... - It's water, not a bug.
Oh, my. That's awesome.
- She's good at reacting. - Indeed.
- Have a seat. Sit here. - Yong Sun.
(All she needs to do is to guess the "say" part.)
- I'm the younger sister. - Use a different word for "say".
Yong Sun.
- So my older sister... - Oh, I know.
"Don't you dare tell people that I'm your sister."
- But I'm the younger sister, so... - Correct.
We'll accept that as a correct answer.
(Team Solar got the right answer with three balloons left.)
- Great job, Yong Sun. - Good job.
(She is the master of reactions.)
"Don't you dare tell people..."
- You did well. - Yong Sun is good at reacting.
(Good job, sister.)
That was awesome.
I'm a fan of Yong Sun's as of today.
(Her funny reaction made him a fan.)
I'm a huge fan.
- Jae Suk. - Yong Sun was...
(Team Young Ji and So Mi failed to acquire points.)
Is it over?
Everyone, if one of the siblings succeeds,
- the team wins additional points. - We'll do it.
- Let's go for it. - Of course, we'll do it.
(Of course!)
- We'll do it. - No matter what.
(Team Young Ji tries to make up for 0 points.)
- Everyone, let's begin. - Okay.
Look. Okay. Good.
- Right. - I guess it's an easy one.
(How dare you talk back to me every time I talk to you?)
- No, no. - That's also easy.
- Ready. Go. - Oh, I see.
(Jae Suk messes with the sticks as soon as it begins.)
It's not hard, right?
- It's short, right? - Okay.
- A short word? - Let's explain it to him.
- Ready. Go. - Is it a short word?
- Jae Suk. - What is he doing?
- What? - It's hard to pull out.
(It's Kwang Soo's excuse, "It's hard to pull out.")
- It's hard to pull out. - It's true. It's hard to pull out.
All right.
(How dare you talk back to me every time I talk to you?)
(He starts off smoothly.)
- "Horse"? - Yes.
- "Hey, you..." - "Listen to me."
- It's close. - "How dare you talk..."
(That was my mistake.)
- Oh, no. I... - What?
He said the exact word again.
(You can't say that.)
- "How dare you..." - "How dare you talk back?"
(He gets the hint.)
Good. But... What sound is this?
(How dare you talk back to me every time I talk to you?)
"How dare you talk back to me..."
- What sound is this? - "How dare you talk back to me..."
Yes! He got the right answer.
What sound is this?
(Jae Suk pulled out the sticks powerfully.)
"How dare you talk back to me..."
(What?)
- "How dare you..." - Yes! He got the right answer.
(Jae Suk silences Kwang Soo by pulling out the sticks.)
"How dare you... How dare you..."
"How dare you talk back to me every time I talk to you?"
(Correct)
(Jae Suk pulls out more sticks pretending he didn't hear it.)
- You saw that, right? - "How dare you..."
(Is he allowed to do that?)
- But Haha said, "talk". - Yes, he did.
(It's the same.)
- True. - He gave him a word.
It was a mistake.
Give us another chance.
- Try it again. - Forget this round.
(They're asking to let us start over?)
- It doesn't count. - Exactly.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong?
- I said the word. - He said, "talk".
(It was a little helpful, but...)
It's against the rule.
- Start over. - Even my underwear is wet now.
- Kwang Soo, you did well. - How about we deduct a point?
You did well, Kwang Soo.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo's effort,)
Kwang Soo did a good job.
(Team Young Ji got the right answer with three balloons left.)
- He got the answer quickly. - He did a great job.
You thought of it when you pulled it out, right?
(That's fortunate.)
It's okay.
- That was cool. - It's So Min.
(So Min from Team Solar will try to guess too.)
- So Min... - Kwang Soo will do it, then.
Kwang Soo should do it for So Min.
(Kwang Soo will pull out for So Min.)
- Enjoy it. - Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo, once exiled, is allowed back in.)
- It's showtime. - It's okay.
If you think about the previous questions...
Look at him.
Oh, my.
(Why is everyone surprised by Kwang Soo?)
Look at Kwang Soo.
Oh, my.
(He brought a whole bucket of water balloons.)
- Turn around. - Look at that.
I brought them for the next round.
(Shameless)
(You can clearly tell his bad intentions.)
- Seriously. He's so mean. - I just...
- brought them for the next round. - I'm so excited about this sitcom.
I'm so excited.
So Min, I'm sure you expected that.
- This is... - I'm so excited about this.
(Kwang Soo slowly comes forward.)
Look at that.
(He's bringing drinking water.)
(He's stacking up materials for his bad deed.)
- My goodness. This is... - Kwang Soo.
(The most anticipated skit of 2020, Kwang Soo and So Min's show)
I'm looking forward to it.
This will be a great comedy skit.
(Sister, have you lost your mind?)
(Difficulty level: two stars)
- That's easy. - That's easy.
- Ready. Go. - It's too easy.
- "What is wrong with you?" - "Who are you?"
(Doing a skit)
"What is wrong with you?"
"Is something wrong with this?"
- "Hey." - "Are you out of your mind?"
Yes! But...
What?
- "Are you out of your mind?" - Yes! But...
(Kwang Soo drops a lot of water balloons.)
What?
Yes! But...
(Falling down)
What?
I didn't...
(The new technique to pop balloons without pulling a stick out)
- Listen. I didn't... - What was that?
- I didn't do anything. - He didn't do anything.
(His most popular excuse)
- He didn't even pull a stick out. - I didn't do anything.
(I didn't touch it, but balloons popped.)
- He didn't do anything. - I really didn't do anything.
- It's close, but... - "You're out of your mind."
(I'll pay back later.)
No. Who am I to you?
- Who am I to her? - Sister.
- "Sister, are you insane?" - That's close.
You know, the right mind...
(Kwang Soo won't stop dropping water balloons.)
I didn't mean to...
- "Are you out of your mind?" - No.
(Biting her teeth)
- When you... - You're running out of time.
"Sister..."
(Hitting)
(So Min threw a water balloon at him.)
I didn't mean to do that.
It wasn't my intention.
(Are we on?)
(Pouring water)
(Water balloon war)
- My goodness. - "Sister..."
- Here they go again. - "Sister..."
(Giving a peck...)
"Sister, are you out of your mind?"
(and getting a bushel)
"Are you in your right mind?"
(She's totally lost.)
It's close.
(He poured the whole bucket.)
(The audience is fully satisfied.)
(They're too immature...)
- "Sister..." - What is wrong with you two?
(for people with a younger sibling.)
- Pull another one out. - What is wrong with you?
(They are out of control.)
- Try a different verb. - A verb?
Yes, a verb.
When you... How should I put it?
- "Have you lost your mind?" - Correct.
- "Sister, have you lost your mind?" - Yes!
Good job.
(Team Solar got the right answer.)
- She succeeded quickly. - I expected it, but...
(The battlefield is a complete mess.)
- Gosh. Although I expected that... - I have a question.
Is the penalty worse than this?
- Or is this worse? - My gosh.
(This mission was tougher than the penalty.)
They say this is worse than the penalty.
The penalty is worse than this?
(Worn out)
- No. - This is worse than the penalty.
(The two moths make games as worse as penalties.)
What is wrong with you guys?
So, this is it.
We tallied the points including the ones from the additional rounds.
(The result including the additional challenges)
- Please. - The first place team is...
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Solar.
- The team gained 50 points. - We did well.
- We did great. - Team So Mi, 2nd place, 40 points.
- Team Young Ji, 3rd, 30 points. - Okay.
- Why are we in last place again? - Team Jessi gained 20 points.
- I thought we'd be in second place. - I'm not happy with the result.
Now, we'll begin the second round of Sister's Room.
- A lot of points are at stake. - According to your scores,
(They'll get lunch based on their academic points.)
you will also be given lunch.
Jessi, we're going to open the door.
- We'll open the door this time. - We'll open the door.
(Brothers of Team Jessi restrict Jessi from auditioning.)
- What will you do again? - We'll open the door.
Trust me.
- Will you take the test? - Loyalty.
To get more points,
(To increase academic points,)
the only way is not opening the door while you're taking the test.
(the brothers must trust her and she should take the test.)
- If you want to win. - Okay. Then don't open it.
- Trust me. - We won't.
- Trust me. - Because...
- 1, 2, 3. Go, Team! - Go, Team!
(Team Young Ji decides to trust each other.)
- We won't open the door. - Listen.
I really like our teamwork.
(So Mi's door was opened as she was auditioning.)
- Teamwork? - We had great teamwork.
- We have great teamwork, - Yes.
- and I want to eat a nice lunch. - Okay.
Right. Let's eat this time.
(She promises that she'll take the test.)
- I'm serious. - I know.
Yong Sun, let's eat lunch.
- Will you take the test? - Let's eat.
(The sisters all agree that they'll take the test.)
- Let's eat. - The first place team can eat.
The younger sisters, please go to your rooms.
(Will they keep their promises?)
Young Ji, I trust you.
I think that I need to gain...
more academic points.
Since I got almost no individual point,
(Her strategy is to focus on the academic points.)
I'm going to continue...
(She'll trust her sisters and take the test.)
to write an answer to a question.
I have a feeling that they will trust me.
I asked them to trust me, but...
(So Mi promised that she'll take the test.)
Oh, no. The strap got stained.
I'm going to dance because I'm upset.
(She betrays them and decides to audition.)
All right. Let's go. Let's do this.
(What option will Young Ji and Jessi choose?)
It's a little hard to decide.
My team is in last place, right?
We can't trust So Min, but we must trust So Mi.
(The brothers and sisters now appeared.)
- Shall we trust her? - Sorry?
Do you want to go in?
(They promised to trust her, but they are still unsure.)
- We should give her a stamp, right? - Yes, we should.
(They decide to trust So Mi.)
- We should give her a stamp. - Shall I?
- Shall I? - Yes. Let's do that.
(But she's busy auditioning.)
Okay. We trust her.
(Stamping)
We trust So Mi.
(The two brothers are fooled.)
We're leaving because we trust her.
Can we open the door now?
Yes, you can.
One.
(The two brothers betrayed and opened the door.)
(They'll acquire academic points if Jessi is auditioning.)
(Jessi was taking the test diligently.)
Did you not trust me?
Oh, my gosh.
What happens now?
(They made the wrong move.)
I think that you are not compatible with us at all.
We keep choosing the opposite.
Gosh, Se Chan. I clearly told you.
(Annoyed)
- Come on. Get it together. - We doubted you.
(Team Jessi failed to earn academic points.)
- Se Chan. - I'm going to be bad now.
I think my team will be in first place.
(Solar trusts her sisters and is confident she'll win.)
I'm worried because I think we'll win too easily.
See? They won't come in.
(Full of trust)
(What?)
Guys.
(The two trusting sisters opened the door.)
Oh, no. We couldn't trust you.
(Team Solar failed to acquire points thanks to trusting sisters.)
- Because we have a high score... - We have a high score.
Let's trust her.
(Haha and Kwang Soo haven't made up their minds.)
Wait. Wait. Hold on.
She might be studying. I have a feeling.
(Young Ji...)
(No way.)
No? Are you sure?
(Backed by Kwang Soo's confidence, they enter the room.)
Darn it. I told you so.
(She was taking the test.)
She's studying. I told you she must be studying.
(Awkward)
- I said I'll go to the Ivy League. - It's not like that.
I said we shouldn't come in. Young Ji, listen.
(It got in the way of the sister who finally made up her mind.)
- You'll see later. - Okay.
- He insisted. - Now, we've become a real family.
- He didn't trust you. - We've become a real family.
I trusted you.
You see...
Oh, she was... She was writing an answer to an essay question.
(Write about how it feels to complete...)
See? I told you she was studying. Gosh.
(the mission with your siblings.)
- We should've trusted her. - I'm going to be bad now.
- Hey, I trusted you. - I'm going to be bad.
- I trusted you, but he didn't. - You see,
(Because they couldn't trust Young Ji,)
we finally became a real family.
(Team Young Ji fails to earn the academic points.)
I trusted you.
- Forget it. - My gosh.
(Current points)
- Listen. - My brothers doubted me.
- Let's do it. Let's do it now. - Young Ji, I trusted you.
As a result of the 2nd round of Sister's Room, the 1st place team...
(Current rankings)
- Is it us? - We were in first place.
(In growing distrust,)
- Yes, but it might've changed. - We were in first place.
(who won the 1st place?)
- Because we didn't trust her. - The first place team is...
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Solar.
(The 1st place team is Team Solar.)
- We're still in first place. - We're in last place?
- We're still in first place. - I think all the other teams...
(They maintained the 1st place thanks to their reliable sister.)
- went into the rooms. - Right.
- What? - Why?
(Acting surprised)
Gosh. She filmed the audition tape.
- Hey, you filmed... - No, I studied.
- I studied. - She filmed the audition tape.
(She omits the subject.)
I guess she filmed the audition tape.
- No, I didn't. - She was the only one I trusted.
(Feeling betrayed)
Next.
2 teams came in joint 2nd place in academic point.
(The 2nd place team is revealed.)
Which teams?
Team Jessi and Team So Mi.
(Team Jessi and Team So Mi came in joint 2nd place in academic point.)
- Come on. - Jessi.
- My gosh. - Come on.
- Come on. - Earlier, we...
- Good. We're in 2nd place. - We're in 2nd place?
(What a relief.)
- Last place? We're in 2nd place. - We're in 2nd place at least.
Are we in last place?
(Team Young Ji is on the verge of getting a penalty.)
- So Mi... - I asked you to trust me.
I can't believe this.
(Only if they trusted Young Ji...)
I knew it. We're not family.
- How could it be? - Now, I have to stop her.
(They finish the meal according to their academic points.)
This is a disaster.
- I think we'll play a game... - Like throwing balls.
(In the intense battle of graduation...)
where we throw balls.
This is the last mission before the graduation...
- that requires teamwork. - Okay.
It's Guard Your Sister, a basketball game.
(Guard Your Sister)
- So we have to guard her. - Okay. You guys will guard me.
You will be given 10 minutes in 1st and 2nd halves,
(In 1st and 2nd halves of 10 minutes,)
and the team that gets most balls in the hoop...
(the team that gets most balls in the hoop wins.)
that the other teams carry wins.
In the first half, the little sister will carry the hoop,
(In the first half, only the younger sister will carry the hoop.)
- and one of her siblings will... - Okay.
(The sister and 1 of her siblings will carry it in the second half.)
- carry it in the second half. - Got it.
However, you must find balls that are hidden in different places,
(They must find balls that are hidden in different places...)
and write your sister's name on them to score a goal.
(and write their sister's name on them to score a goal.)
Or else, it won't be considered a goal.
(If they score, they get 3 points.)
- Oh, we have a rule like that. - We must find the hidden balls.
(If they concede a goal, they lose 1 point.)
In the order of the number of goals scored by each team,
(In the order of the number of goals scored by each team,)
the teams will gain 50, 30, 20, and 10 points.
(the teams will gain 50, 30, 20, and 10 points.)
- This is our last chance. - Okay. Got it.
- A chance to turn the game around. - If we fail again this time,
(Team Young Ji placed last in academic points.)
- it's over. - Okay, okay.
- A chance to turn the game around. - Or you can be an idol singer.
- Okay. - Become successful...
(The brothers want to help her avoid the penalty...)
- Being an idol singer sounds great. - Exactly.
(with audition points.)
- We want you to be successful. - To study...
- Okay. - But let's do our best in this.
(Competitive)
Okay. Understood.
- The game will begin shortly. - Let's do this!
(Write the sister's name on the ball...)
- 3, 2, 1. - We must find the balls first.
(and get it in the other team's hoop.)
- The race begins now. - Okay.
(The first half starts.)
Is there no ball in here?
(Team Jessi approaches the sister's rooms to find a ball.)
There might be one.
- I don't think so. - I'll take a look around.
(They search every room.)
I'll go check that room.
The trash can.
(Jessi has a hunch.)
- How does a ball look? - My gosh. Gross.
- Why? - The trash can was full of trash.
- Of course, it's full of trash. - But...
But there might've been something in it.
(The trash can)
There's no ball in here.
(Where's the ball?)
- I think... - We wasted our time.
We came down here because you told us to.
(Blaming Jae Suk)
(Patient)
- You're right. I'm sorry. - I like how she points things out.
I'm sorry.
(Haha is searching for a ball too.)
Wait.
(He found something!)
There it is. I found one.
(Awesome)
(Finally, he found a ball.)
(As soon as he finds a ball, he write his sister's name on it.)
"Lee Young Ji". I wrote down her name. Let's go.
(Kwang Soo found a ball too.)
(He's heading somewhere with the ball he found.)
Where are you going?
(He ran into Suk Jin who's not a threat.)
Wait.
(But!)
- Wait. - What is it?
(Jong Kook blocks their way.)
Just let me pass through.
- No. - Just let me pass through.
(Figuring out what's going on)
- Give me that. - Young Ji, run!
- Hey. - Oh, gosh. Let me go.
(Running away)
- No, no. - Did they see me?
(While Jong Kook lets his guard down,)
- Where is it written? - Hey, be careful.
(he tries to throw the ball.)
Don't worry.
(Moving to the sides)
(Screaming)
(Lee Kwang Soo has been kicked out.)
- Bye. - What?
(Flustered)
- Why would this door... - Let's go.
Wait! Wait.
(Confined)
Why did the door open?
(I'm inside.)
Let's hurry.
- Hurry up and write it down. - Haha!
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook writes his sister's name on the ball.)
They're coming.
- Hey, where is Kwang Soo? - Be careful.
(Kwang Soo. Where are you?)
Hurry up and go. Kwang Soo.
(At that time)
(Jong Kook rushes to Young Ji.)
(Lying on the floor)
Be careful.
(She's blocking the ball with quick movements.)
(Unexpected break dancing)
Hey!
(She blocks it successfully.)
You're supposed to stop them!
(The 21st-century girl doesn't feel intimidated by Jong Kook.)
No. Come on.
(Her blank look confuses her opponents.)
- No. - You see...
- No. - The net is turned inside out.
(The hoop)
(While Jong Kook is confronting Young Ji,)
(Kwang Soo goes after So Mi.)
Be careful!
(Kwang Soo is fighting with So Mi one on one.)
Hey!
(Kwang Soo tries to shoot.)
I failed.
(Bricked)
Haha.
(Haha showed up out of nowhere and successfully scores a goal.)
No, no. Run. Run.
(Suk Jin runs to her.)
- No, no. - We already lost a point.
(But Team So Mi loses 1 point for conceding a shot.)
It's turned inside out.
(So Min finally finds a ball.)
We lost a point.
Gosh. Where have you been?
(She proudly enters the battlefield.)
Where?
(So Min is waiting for the right time for the attack.)
- Okay. Gosh. Give me that! - So Min.
(At that moment)
(Kwang Soo snatches her ball while chasing after her.)
Give me that!
(Lee Kwang Soo!)
(Kwang Soo ran away from So Min.)
Where did he go?
- So Min. - He stole my ball.
I mean, this is...
(Solar and her sisters are weak.)
There she is.
(He chose the target.)
(Haha's target is the weakest Solar.)
(He scores.)
Kwang Soo, no.
(Solar barely blocked the second shot.)
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo tries to shoot.)
Okay. It's done.
(Haha and Kwang Soo scored goals against Team Solar.)
I stole the ball.
(He only goes after Solar.)
Haha, this is our chance.
- They have so many balls. - Stop. Come back.
(Team Jessi hasn't found a ball yet.)
- Come on up. - Hey!
(They retreat for now.)
Hurry up.
- Okay. - Don't get involved in that.
(Facing the reality)
You don't even have any balls.
- Hey. - We have to find a ball.
(They must find a ball to join the battle.)
I think there's one in a trash can.
(She's into a trash can.)
- I found one! - Great.
(He finally finds it.)
(Team Jessi finally found their first ball.)
- Did you find a ball? - Jae Suk.
We should write down your name.
I told you it was in a trash can.
(Showing off)
(Speechless)
I'm sorry, but it wasn't in the trash can.
(Childish)
It was behind the trash can.
(It wasn't a trash can.)
Hey, we... Oh, here it is.
(Jae Suk is searching around.)
Did you find another one?
(He finds another ball.)
- Come on. Wow. - Wow.
Let's go. Let's go.
(Excited)
Let's go. Move it, move it.
Solar.
(Kwang Soo pulls off as a former basketball player.)
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- What's wrong with you? - Watch out. So Mi is here too.
- Be careful. - So Mi, be careful.
(Jong Kook is protecting So Mi perfectly.)
Come over here.
Kwang Soo, I really don't like you.
(Insulting)
What... Wait. You don't like me?
(So Mi made him lose his will to fight.)
- This is how the game is played. - Hey.
- So Mi. - What? Hey.
(Snatching)
What? Hey.
(Suk Jin is taken aback as he loses it in an instant.)
- Darn it. - Why did you let him take it?
- I'm sorry. - Why did you do that?
(Sorry)
- Let's go to Solar. - No.
(The weakest team)
But we... Oh, no. Run. Hurry.
(He runs at full speed toward Solar.)
(Only Ji Hyo is guarding Solar.)
- He's coming. - Goal!
(He easily scores a goal.)
Goal!
- Gosh. - My goodness.
(Before she gets sad,)
I mean... Not again. Stop!
(Jong Kook goes on the offense.)
Not again. Stop!
I mean... Not again. Stop!
(Ji Hyo blocks the ball with her elbow.)
Hey, our net is full now.
(Please stop.)
Be careful with that.
(Then Jessi quietly approaches her.)
Be careful.
(The ball hits the hoop and bounces off.)
- Hey! - Jessi!
(Kwang Soo saw the ball bouncing out and went crazy.)
(Let go of me.)
(They're punishing Kwang Soo together.)
(While they're taking him down,)
(he successfully scores against Solar.)
It fell on the floor.
Don't bite me.
Let go of me. Let me go!
(However,)
(Ji Hyo is drawing something.)
I said, let go!
I said, let go. What are you doing?
- Gosh, my hair. - Who is it?
(A piece of art on a long paper created by Ji Hyo)
- What are you doing? - Gosh, my hair.
- Who is it? - My hair.
(Finally, they're all calm.)
- Jessi. - My gosh.
We should score a goal.
(Ragged)
Jessi. Jessi.
- I'll be here. - Jessi.
- Who is that? - Oh, my gosh.
(Now she sees him.)
- What happened to your face? - What happened?
- What's wrong? - What happened?
(They're touched by the artwork.)
What happened?
- It wasn't me. - What color is it?
(He's looking for the culprit.)
- What color is it? - It wasn't me.
- What color is it? - Kwang Soo.
(Pretending innocence)
It's drawn in this color.
- It wasn't me. - It was So Min.
- No. - I think...
(However,)
(Ji Hyo doesn't have the lid of the marker.)
It's easy to move.
(I got you!)
(Kwang Soo is in a frenzy with a revengeful spirit.)
Come here. Let's go.
(I don't want to be dragged into that.)
(You are watching a basketball game.)
Where is it? An orange ball.
(Meanwhile, So Mi is looking for a ball.)
(Ball, please come out.)
(Team Solar is also busy looking for a ball.)
Where did they find so many balls?
- Did you find one, Ji Hyo? - No.
(She needs a ball to attack.)
I think...
(At that moment!)
No. Ji Hyo! No!
(Kwang Soo, the incarnation of revenge, suddenly appears.)
No. Go away. Go away.
- I got it. - What was that?
(So Min blocks the shot.)
That was awesome.
(So Min blocks the shot and gets the ball.)
- So Min. - Let's get out of here.
Haha!
(It's sad to watch the three sisters struggle.)
Solar, take this and run.
(I'll block him.)
- Run. - He lost the ball.
(She runs away from Kwang Soo.)
Wait.
(He tries to chase her, but he's exhausted.)
Wait. No.
Close the door. Close it, Ji Hyo.
(So Min grabs his arm, and Ji Hyo closes the door.)
Close it. Close it now, Ji Hyo.
Close it. Close it.
I said, close it. Close it now. Close it.
(He has no energy to resist.)
Where did my marker pen go?
- My marker pen... - It's not here.
What do you mean it's not here?
(Hiding)
- Here... - I don't have it.
(Why would you still want to hide it?)
It's right here!
- Don't make me laugh. - I'll take it out.
(His body reacts instinctively even when he has no energy.)
- Why... - I'll take it out for you.
- Give it to me. - I'll take it out.
- Give it to me. - Stop pressing. I'll give you.
- How? How? - What?
I'll take it out now.
(The clock keeps ticking.)
Wait. You should give it to him.
(There are only 2 minutes left.)
What? When and who did this?
Jessi, earlier... Calm down.
(Jessi. Calm down.)
- Jae Suk! - Calm down.
- When did this get in here? - One ball is okay.
- It's okay. - No, it's not okay.
(Jessi will not allow any balls.)
That could happen to any team.
Wait.
(If she was in Team Solar, she would've gone crazy.)
Gosh. You can't keep it under your shirt.
(The ball)
But we have only girls in our team.
I don't care. Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo appears out of nowhere.)
Gosh. What are you doing? What are you doing?
(He looked like he was stealing the ball.)
Stop it. You can't do that.
Hey, what are you... Oh, gosh.
(How dare you write on my face? Take this.)
Stop it.
(The battle for revenge)
- What are you guys doing? - Hey.
(Unbelievable)
That's ridiculous.
(Biting)
Hey, you brat.
(A headlock)
You shouldn't do that to her.
(And new face painting)
That's bad.
(Kwang Soo is in trouble.)
Hey, stop it.
(Jong Kook takes this chance to attack.)
- Go. Good job. - Stop it.
- What? What was that? - Jessi.
(Solar concedes a shot again.)
- Help me. - Jessi.
(While everyone was looking at Kwang Soo,)
(So Mi scored a goal too.)
Everyone, the first half is over.
(I can't believe I let her score.)
- The first half is over. - I put a ball in Young Ji's net.
(Devastated)
- Did you? - Yes.
Please go to your team's starting place.
(The result of the first half)
(Team Young Ji, 26, Team So Mi, 14, Team Jessi, 8, Team Solar, minus 10)
There's no way we can...
(Solar and her sisters got defeated.)
We lost too many points.
I was so surprised. They came at me like crazy.
(Culture shock)
It's no joke.
Which one of you will carry the hoop?
(One more person has to carry a hoop in the second half.)
- Ji Hyo, you do it. - I'll do it.
(Ji Hyo will carry the hoop.)
She's better at dodging than me.
I don't know. There's nothing we can do.
(They need a groundbreaking strategy for the second half.)
How about we forget about scoring goals and beat Kwang Soo up?
- I won't let it slide. - I'm sure...
(Calm down, Ji Hyo.)
that Kwang Soo will carry the hoop because he's tall.
(The younger siblings want to close the score gap.)
- He's fast too. - You're right.
I'm so annoyed.
(The big sister is still upset.)
I think Jae Suk will cover for me better.
(Meanwhile, Team Jessi is in 3rd place.)
Who didn't cover for me earlier?
- What do you mean? - Who didn't cover for me?
(Jessi is still angry that she conceded one shot.)
You? We both protected you.
- Jessi. - Get the ball in whenever you can.
(Please calm down, Jessi.)
- I'm worried about this guy. - Why?
- I just have a feeling. - No.
Worry about yourself.
(Look who's talking.)
- Don't fight. - We're not fighting.
(Stop fighting.)
I was complimenting her.
(It's a misunderstanding.)
- Hey. - I'll be there for you.
- Are you looking down on her? - No.
- Never. - The whole time, you're...
- No. - Oh, my gosh.
- I was... - Hey, do you watch NBA games?
(Korean American's pronunciation)
- What? Yes, I do. - You watch NBA games?
(Fighting)
- Can you play basketball? - I can.
I think I got a nosebleed.
(He's too tired.)
- Is this the last game? - Because you said that...
(He can't take it anymore.)
- Is this the last one? - To be honest,
(Spending a day with Jessi is tough.)
I'm happy I'm not on Kwang Soo's team.
- It's best if you carry the net. - Me?
(Team So Mi placed 2nd in the 1st half.)
If I do it, everyone will target me.
(Once Suk Jin carries the hoop, he'll become everyone's target.)
- Of course. - Everyone will come at me.
- It's better if I defend. - Yes, you should defend.
(Jong Kook will carry the hoop.)
All right.
(Team Young Ji placed 1st in the 1st half.)
Who should carry the net?
Who should? Do you want to play offense?
They were all coming at you, right?
I think...
(It shows that everyone came at him.)
I'll play offense.
(The tall attacker)
I'll attack.
Okay, I'll carry the net.
(Haha will carry the hoop.)
Let's start the second half.
- I'll get many balls in this time. - Let's do this.
(She keeps putting on a blank look.)
The race starts.
(The second half starts.)
(Team So Mi looks for a ball.)
There will be more nets this time.
Here he comes. Kwang Soo has two balls.
- Gosh, that crazy punk. - Here he comes.
- We have no balls? - Where did he find them?
(Kwang Soo only lives for today.)
- He's running here. - They...
(Even though he's alone, he moves forward.)
They already have balls.
- What's with him? - I found one.
(She hides in a classroom to avoid Kwang Soo.)
Watch out!
- Watch out! - Watch out!
(Screaming)
(He charges at So Mi.)
(Jong Kook subdues him.)
Fine, I'll leave.
(He even stole Kwang Soo's ball.)
I'll leave.
(He gets scared and runs away.)
Come here! Stop!
(Se Chan is confronted with So Min while carrying a net.)
(He tries to steal So Min's ball.)
Hey!
(So Min swears...)
(and punches him.)
(He gets punched in the left frontal lobe.)
Hey!
How could you slap me?
(After the first half, Yong Sun's sisters are determined to win.)
(Young Ji looks for balls on the 2nd floor alone.)
This is insane.
(She finds a ball under the sink.)
You're good at this.
(The staff is impressed.)
(She hides the balls inside her T-shirt.)
Run!
(There is a war going on.)
(Young Ji is hiding in the corner.)
Haha! Jae Suk!
(She lowers her body.)
(She gets a ball in.)
(She scores a goal without anyone finding out.)
(Celebrating)
- You got a ball into mine? - Yes. Okay.
(Jong Kook hasn't noticed it.)
- Why me? - Why her?
(Young Ji finds another opportunity...)
Here she comes. Hey!
(and takes action.)
(Her second attack succeeds too.)
Here she comes. Hey!
Hey, look at her.
Okay!
(The 21st-century girl challenges the invincible Jong Kook.)
Here we go. Okay.
(The 20th-century singer versus the 21st-century girl)
(The chase of the century)
(Screaming)
Young Ji!
Young Ji, what happened? Young Ji!
(Young Ji. What's going on?)
- Young Ji. - Young Ji!
(Everyone is shocked at the unexpected situation.)
- Hey. - Young Ji!
- Young Ji, what happened? - Young Ji!
(When Jong Kook finds his target, he never gives up.)
Young Ji!
(In the end, Jong Kook gets 2 balls in.)
(Her eyes blaze with anger.)
What's with her face?
(Shocked)
What happened?
(Even her face intimidates everyone.)
- It's me. - Young Ji!
Hey!
(Young Ji looks for her next target.)
(She suddenly takes her shoes off.)
(Her steps to the battleground feel much lighter now.)
Hold on.
(Her feet move incredibly fast.)
Hey.
Hey!
(No one dares to attack Young Ji...)
Gosh.
(with her shoes taken off.)
- Did you see that? - Young Ji, come here!
Young Ji is hilarious.
Young Ji, why did you take your shoes off?
(He finally notices it.)
To run faster.
(Determined)
Young Ji.
(Jae Suk chooses Young Ji as his target.)
- Do you have it or not? - It's mine!
(Running)
Give it to me!
Kwang Soo!
(She tries to defend against Jae Suk...)
Stay still.
(but unfortunately fails.)
Hey, you're good at this.
(Approved)
Young Ji, I love your energy.
(She likes how Young Ji plays hard.)
- Young Ji, you have so much energy. - Young Ji, you're amazing.
Very good.
(I'm Lee Young Ji.)
- We have 30 seconds left. - We got 30 seconds left.
(The second half ends in 30 seconds.)
(Faking)
(His ball is so fast that no one can see it.)
Give it to me.
(What's he doing?)
Look at Kwang Soo.
Good. We can't see it.
(He moves...)
What are you doing?
(like his role model Han Gi Beom.)
- This is hilarious. - It's so fast I can't see it.
I can't see it.
Gosh, it's so fast.
(Jae Suk approaches Kwang Soo.)
(Jae Suk slaps him.)
(Kwang Soo's one-man show is over.)
(What's with him?)
In the end, it finishes in a silly way.
- 3! - 3!
(There are 3 seconds left.)
- Two! - Gosh.
One!
(Exhausted)
Game over.
(The game ends.)
- Everyone. - Yes?
(The results are announced.)
In first place...
With 40 points,
(With 40 points,)
Team Young Ji.
(Team Young Ji finishes in 1st place.)
(Young Ji took her shoes off and Kwang Soo didn't spare himself...)
(to make this possible.)
They got many balls in?
(Team Young Ji wins 50 points.)
Our strategy paid off.
In second place, with only one less ball in...
I hope we're in second place.
- With 37 points, - Team Jong Kook.
(Team So Mi places 2nd...)
Team So Mi.
(with 37 points.)
- I knew it. - I'm relieved.
(Satisfied)
- I'm relieved. - So am I.
(I think we lost.)
- We're in second place. - We won't be penalized.
With four less points...
(With 4 fewer points than Team So Mi,)
- Team Jessi is in third place. - Okay.
(Team Jessi places 3rd.)
- Gosh. - And then...
Team Solar has...
minus nine points.
Minus nine points?
(She's surprised that she's choked.)
What is that?
They ended up with so many balls that they carried in their bags.
(We're sorry, Yong Sun.)
- It's the last Sister's Room. - We're at the bottom.
(The last round of Sister's Room)
- We have to trust each other. - Exactly.
(This will determine the penalty and prize.)
- Trust me. - Okay. Go to your room.
- We'll trust you. - We shouldn't open her door.
(The family tightens their bonds...)
- We shouldn't. - No, you shouldn't.
(before the last round of Sister's Room.)
- Gosh, what should I do? - What do we do?
(They go to their rooms.)
- I don't know what they'll do. - Me neither.
Is Jessi already in her room?
(Peeking)
- What? What's with you? - What are you going to do?
(Surprised)
(Jessi is still thinking.)
I don't know. What about you guys?
But from my experience...
(The 21st-century kids share their audition experience.)
Let's say you're working on your computer.
They'd think you're doing this.
(They're saying her brothers wouldn't believe her.)
- Right? - They want me to work on this.
Don't trust them.
Do whatever you want.
They can do whatever for the show.
(Those people)
I'm going to play you against them.
(Really?)
They've betrayed you, right?
(With advice to walk her own path,)
They betray me all the time.
So should you.
(she recommends Jessi betray her brothers.)
But I don't want to.
I promised them...
5, 6 times.
I'm playing them against each other.
I'm going to dance this time too.
In my opinion...
(Young Ji has the lowest academic points.)
I'm having an inner conflict right now.
I'll give up on my Ivy League dream.
I need to set this up first since I'll become an idol singer.
(Going back on her word, Young Ji prepares for an audition.)
If they had won my trust in the 1st and 2nd rounds,
I would be answering essay questions now.
They should have trusted me.
(Like brother, like sister.)
It's not my fault.
Okay. I choose this.
(The model student Yong Sun answers the essay question.)
I'll stick to this.
Oh, my gosh. What do I do?
Tell me what to do.
(Are you asking me?)
What do you think?
(Jessi is still thinking.)
I'll trust them.
(She decides to trust her teammates again.)
Jae Suk.
(All of them have made up their minds.)
Young Ji, we trust you.
(Their siblings arrive.)
We should trust our little sister.
Let's trust her.
(They trust So Mi completely.)
- Let's give her a stamp. - Do it. Let's not think too much.
Rather than losing it...
(Backstabbing her brothers)
- Let's trust our little sister. - Let's do this.
(Jeon So Mi's room)
- We should trust her. - Come on.
Stop bragging and stamp it already.
(He gives the stamp of trust.)
Why are you bragging so much?
- I can't hear you. - Okay.
(Jeon So Mi's room)
Let's go.
(Thanks to their trust, So Min wins audition points.)
Oh, my.
Did they leave?
(Solar wins a stamp of trust from her sisters.)
(Thanks to Solar keeping her word, her team wins academic points.)
All teams seem to trust their little sisters.
(Two teams are still thinking.)
We never know.
What if she is filming an audition tape again?
She might.
(Zero trusts)
(They're 100 percent sure Jessi is filming an audition tape.)
They're betraying me.
They think I'm filming an audition tape.
(They fail to trust her and decide to open the door.)
Come on!
(Jessi can't take it anymore.)
You...
(I can't believe you're my brothers!)
Jessi.
- Jessi. - Jessi.
- I'm not going to see you again. - Jessi.
(You guys!)
(She slams the door on them.)
- Jessi, I'm sorry. - I told you.
Jessi, you're mistaken.
(The 21st-century kid told her to betray her brothers,)
- Jessi. - Jessi.
I told you we should trust her.
(but she believed them.)
- I wasn't sure. - Jessi.
(Just like the firmly-closed door to her room,)
- Jessi, let us explain. - You promised me!
- Calm down. - Knock, knock.
(she shuts the door of her heart.)
Come on!
- Come on, Jessi. - Jessi.
I wanted to give you a stamp, but he insisted on opening the door.
(Blaming)
(Team Jessi fails to win academic points.)
I'm sorry, Jessi.
Jessi, come on.
I trusted you! Oh, my gosh.
(Two people watched other siblings fall apart.)
- You... - Oh, my gosh.
- Let's give her a stamp. - I...
Let's trust her.
- I... - I...
(They don't want to end up like Team Jessi.)
- On the far right. - Has it been three times?
(They give Young Ji a stamp so that they don't end up like Team Jessi.)
- You were too nice. - Exactly.
(Kwang Soo isn't feeling good about this.)
Let's trust her.
(And he has a good reason for that.)
I feel a lot more guilty than expected.
(Young Ji wins audition points.)
Thank you.
We're family.
The race for your little sisters' graduation is over.
(The final result is announced.)
In the last round, all the teams except Team Jessi...
(All teams gave a stamp except for Team Jessi.)
decided to give stamps.
(Other siblings don't know what was going on in the rooms.)
- It's touching. - Let's see.
- Are we really family? - You guys really are my brothers.
(Brazen)
- You should trust your family. - Let's see what happens.
It's touching. It's really touching.
- This is what family is all about. - It's a happy ending.
You should trust your family at crucial moments.
(Nervous)
- We were at the bottom before this. - What is this?
When Team Jessi opened the door, she was answering essay questions.
(Team Jessi failed to earn academic points.)
- Oh, my. - Too bad.
Solar, who was trusted by her sisters,
(Thanks to their trustworthy little sister,)
was answering essay questions.
(Team Solar wins academic points.)
- Moving on. - Team So Mi.
So Mi, who was trusted by her brothers...
(Team So Mi trusted her.)
- was filming an audition tape. - What?
We beat them.
- We beat them. - Yes!
- We beat them. - We'll move up then.
(Young Ji's brothers have hope as So Mi auditioned 3 times in a row.)
- We did it! - We're in second place.
- I can't believe this girl. - If she was answering questions...
(Feeling betrayed)
I learned it from you.
I hope Team Young Ji beats them.
(This time)
- Beat them. - I trust Young Ji.
(Complete trust)
- Young Ji, who was trusted, - They beat them.
was filming an audition tape.
(She fooled us.)
- We beat them. - Yes!
(She shows off her dance moves she has been practicing.)
(He's swearing with his eyes.)
So the sister who came in first place in the audition is...
(It's time to announce the sister who came in 1st place.)
It's Jeon So Mi, who got 100 points.
(It's Jeon So Mi with 100 audition points.)
What?
I didn't come in first place?
(Because she tried 3 auditions,)
Then we don't get the penalty.
- She got 100 points? - No, it's just So Mi.
(she wins both the prize and penalty exemption.)
Only So Mi gets exempt from the penalty.
(Even Jong Kook gave up at her persistence.)
The other two members will get the penalty.
The sister in second place who will get a prize is...
(The person who came in 2nd place and gets a prize is...)
It's Lee Young Ji.
Goodness.
(They're both swearing with their eyes.)
My gosh.
(Young Ji, who came in 2nd place, will get a prize.)
- We just need to avoid the penalty. - Right.
Only the teams in 3rd and 4th place will get the penalty, right?
(It's time to announce the academic points to decide the penalty.)
- It's time to announce the penalty. - It's the penalty.
- The penalty... - Let's just give up.
(Only the teams in 3rd and 4th place will get the penalty.)
- I don't think it's going to be us. - This is fun.
- We won't get the penalty. - I can get the penalty,
(Excited)
- but... - She's going to get it too.
I need to get the penalty with her.
- That's my goal. - I will get the penalty with her.
(The brothers desperately want to share everything.)
The team that will graduate with the highest academic points is...
(Today's race was filled with mistrust and betrayal.)
(Despite that, the team that protected their sibling love...)
(and came in 1st place is...)
It's Team Solar with 70 points.
(Team Solar graduated with top marks.)
This is a good memory.
(A miracle of the weakest team)
Girl power!
Solar!
Hey, Yong Sun!
(The youngest sister had a tough time with two sloppy sisters.)
- Our youngest sister, Yong Sun! - Yong Sun is the best!
- Our youngest sister, Yong Sun! - Gosh, Yong Sun!
The second place team will avoid the penalty too.
The team in second place.
- In second place... - Tell us it's Jessi.
(The 2nd place team who will avoid penalty)
- Please hurry! - I think we're in third place.
The point difference between the 2nd and 3rd place team is 10 points.
- Let's come in 2nd place. - I think we might be in 3rd place.
Let's come in 2nd place.
- In 2nd place with 30 points... - 2nd place.
(The team that came in 2nd place with 10-point difference...)
Second place.
(and gets to avoid the penalty is...)
Let's come in second place.
The team that will graduate and avoid the penalty is...
Jeon So Mi.
(2nd place, Team Jeon So Mi)
- Yes! - Thank goodness.
Jeon So Mi.
She came in 1st place, but her team also gets exempt.
(So Mi won both as an individual and as a team.)
Our little sister came in first place, and we...
If only...
- Stop bragging. - she studied hard in school...
- Did we lose again? - And we got exempt too.
(I'm sorry.)
Why are you bragging so much?
Team Jessi came in 3rd place with 20 points.
(3rd place is Team Jessi)
Team Young Ji came in 4th place with 10 points.
(4th place is Team Young Ji)
- This is... - We're in last place?
We came in last place?
- It's better to be in last place. - We got everything we wanted.
Get your hand away from me.
(Their youngest sister fulfilled her dream to audition.)
Shall we bring in the prize?
(It's time to reveal the prizes for the top two audition-point winners.)
- Are we in fourth place? - What's the prize?
- No, we're in third place. - Wow.
(An expensive soundbar to achieve their dreams as singers.)
A sound bar.
The 1st and 2nd place winners of the auditions,
(Both So Mi and Young Ji win a soundbar.)
Jeon So Mi and Lee Young Ji, will each get one.
Congratulations on your debut.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
They came in 1st and 2nd place on their 1st time on Running Man.
(The 21st-century kids obtain their dreams.)
- 21st-century kids. - 21st-century kids.
Congratulations to the 2 people born in the 21st century.
Amazing.
We'll go straight into the penalty.
(It's time to reveal the penalty for the bottom two teams.)
Each of you must stand behind 1, 2, and 3.
The 3 doors will open, and 2 of them will have a flour bomb in them.
(Random flour door)
- Okay. - Okay.
Okay. It's behind there.
(1 door for 3rd place and 2 doors for the last place...)
- It's not us. - It's behind there.
- Young Ji gets the penalty too. - Right.
(will have to face the flour bomb.)
Because she's in second place.
- Thank goodness. - Nice.
We came in 2nd place because of them
(Thank you.)
- Right. - Then I...
(Team Young Ji will start. Only one of them can avoid the flour.)
- Are you in position? - Will it reach here?
Does anyone want to switch spots?
(Kwang Soo and Young Ji switch spots at the last moment.)
(1 of these 3 will be exempt from the penalty.)
- Okay. - One.
(Who'll get to avoid the penalty?)
Two.
Three.
(Young Ji avoided the penalty.)
(Are we in paradise?)
How is that possible?
She avoided it.
(That's amazing.)
- Hold on. - Why?
Who got hit with it?
How did the two of you get it?
(It's an overwhelming view. They're covered in flour.)
(They gave it their all.)
- Young Ji is really lucky. - You look handsome like that.
(Young Ji avoided the penalty...)
- I know. - We changed spots too.
(by switching with Kwang Soo at the very last minute.)
Wait. Hold on. Is it random?
Yes, it's random.
Seriously. Please.
(Team Jessi gets ready.)
- Door number two? - I don't know.
It's either 2 or 3.
(Only 1 of them will face the flour bomb.)
- Okay. - Okay. Come on. Let's go.
Does anyone want to switch?
Do you want to switch?
I don't know. I'm just standing here.
- Okay. - Face the door.
(They chose their spots.)
- Jessi chose door number two. - You don't want to switch?
You can't complain to us if you get hit because you didn't switch.
My gosh. Be quiet, please.
(Very sensitive)
(Only one of them will face the penalty.)
Okay. One.
(Who'll get the penalty?)
Two.
Three.
Oh, my gosh!
(What?)
(This is 100 percent real. Jessi gets the penalty.)
Oh, my gosh!
(Why did Jessi get hit with it?)
- Oh, my. - Jessi, come on!
(Everyone can't help but be surprised...)
I'm so sorry, but I love you. It's all a lie.
(at Jessi's tragic fate.)
Oh, no. Jessi.
Jessi, come on!
(The strong sister has been adorned with white.)
I'm so sorry, but I love you. It's all a lie.
Oh, no. Jessi.
- Jessi. Come on. - Jessi. Come on.
(The childish brothers are excited about their sister's punishment.)
Jessi.
- Jessi. - Oh, my gosh.
(She's had a rough day.)
You didn't switch!
- You've become flour dough. - Jessi.
Jessi.
Don't touch me!
Hey! Don't touch me!
(It's all because of you!)
Hey. You. "Nunu Nana".
Jessi.
Jessi. Come on.
No, I... I... Today...
(Who are you?)
- You look so scary right now. - Don't speak.
- You look funnier when you speak. - You look so scary right now.
- Oh, my. - She looks like a ghost.
(Blowing)
- You spat on me! - No, I didn't!
- He spat on me. - I didn't!
- Why did you spit on her? - I was blowing the flour off.
I was really blowing the flour off.
- Jessi. - Can you tell us how you feel?
(He can't read the room.)
You want to know how I feel?
Jessi, come on.
(Thanks to Jessi, Solar, So Mi and Young Ji...)
- It was so funny today. - Good job, everyone.
Good job, everyone!
(for joining us today!)
(Iron gates are shut tightly here.)
Everybody be quiet!
"Reformation activities. Conversation time."
(8 inmates are being held inside a prison.)
Why did you lock us up in here?
- You must be the new guys. - I'm here to get one of you.
(New inmate 2371, Kim Young Min. New inmate 2370, Ha Do Kwon.)
Hurry up and get over here, newbies.
I was a top executive...
of an illegal group called Monster in Busan.
(New inmate 2372, Ji Seung Hyun. New inmate 2369, Kim Yong Ji.)
These are the rules.
(The rules of Running Prison)
- We're connected by partners. - We're connected?
(The inmates here are connected in pairs of 2?)
If my partner gets eliminated, so do I?
How is this the big picture?
The two of them were partners.
(However, nobody knows who they are connected with.)
- We don't know? - We need to escape together.
(They must find their partner without getting caught and escape.)
- What happened? Who got eliminated? - I got it.
- Hey. - Run! Run!
(Only those who escape can survive.)
- Lock the doors, hurry. - Hurry.
It's done.
We just need to find the boss and their member.
(This was all planned by a powerful boss and their members?)
- Are you the boss? - I was always the boss.
Hold on!
(Who will be the first 2 people to escape?)
Did you get them?
We just need to find a way out of here.
(2 Person Prison Break Race, My Unfamiliar Partner)