Please clap the slate once.
- One...
- Shall we begin?
- Do I clap it now?
- Yes.
1, 2, and 3.
(She claps her hands once.)
Hello, everyone.
(Then she starts hosting the show.)
Hello, everyone. Welcome
to Jeon So Min's Running Man.
All right. We're going to have
five male guests today.
Well...
Today's special is
Win Over Jeon So Min Race.
(She comes up with her own race.)
Which one of the handsome guests...
will be falling in love with
this beautiful woman, Jeon So Min?
Please look forward
to the exciting couple race.
Director, please follow me.
(Host Jeon has a lot of requests
for her show.)
(Just about when she finally runs
out of ideas for her show...)
Hurry, Yoo Jae Suk.
Let's start right away.
When we worked out the day before...
Hello.
- Hello.
What are you doing here alone?
- I was busy working.
- Hello.
- I was working.
- You came early.
- You were?
- Okay.
Hello.
After the shooting yesterday,
I talked to Kwang Soo.
Apparently, he was
very disappointed.
- Why?
- Hey.
- Don't do that.
- I mean...
- Why were you disappointed?
- Well...
- Nothing.
- The thing is,
- July 14 was Kwang Soo's birthday.
- Hey.
- Right.
- It was your birthday?
And the episode we filmed
would be aired around that day.
So he thought we prepared
some prank for him.
(He thought we prepared
some prank for him.)
(Kwang Soo counted
his chickens too soon.)
- But...
- That's not true.
- No, it's not like that.
- Nothing happened, so...
It was nothing like that!
- Kwang Soo was...
- No, that's not true.
(The members didn't plan
anything for Kwang Soo's birthday.)
So when I was wearing the blindfold,
I thought you guys would
do something to me.
(When he was told
to put on the blindfold...)
(Maybe this is some kind of prank.)
(Nothing ever happened.)
(This is a little too rough
for my birthday party.)
- Did you expect something?
- Not really. Se Chan...
I had no idea.
The day before, he asked, "We should
dress like card sharks tomorrow."
"Do you know what it is about?"
- "Am I the main star tomorrow?"
- "A card shark?"
"Hang on. The episode
will be aired around..."
"Maybe Se Chan is not
supposed to tell me that."
(Kwang Soo thought
Se Chan made a mistake.)
"Isn't he supposed
to keep it a secret?"
- Because I didn't hear it.
- He was in the movie, "Tazza".
- Right.
- That's what it is.
"Hang on. The show will be aired
the day after my birthday."
(Gosh, I know what is going on.)
That's ridiculous.
So during the shooting,
I kept looking for cameras.
I was sure something would happen.
Are you the only one
who has a birthday?
That's not it.
- Are you the only one?
- That's not it.
We should prepare
a surprise for him.
- He was counting on it.
- We had no idea.
Today,
you're going to compete in pairs.
- Oh, my.
- In pairs?
By the way, the caramels...
- Based on yesterday's results...
- He has only three.
- What can I do with 30 cents?
- You'll get 30 cents, and...
(Why does Jae Suk
look so depressed?)
(In War of Sharks last week,)
(he raised the stakes
as the chairman.)
(He soon went broke
and was thrown onto the floor.)
(Having only 3 caramels left,)
(he'll be given 30 cents
as his mission fund.)
(Current Number of Caramels)
(Jong Kook: 6.8 dollars,
Suk Jin and Haha: 5.4 dollars,)
(Kwang Soo 4.9 dollars,
Se Chan: 4.8 dollars)
After yesterday's shoot,
I was given a huge bag of caramels.
- That's all you get?
- I'm sick of it.
I don't want any more caramels.
- I even found one in my sock...
- Be quiet.
Hey!
Be quiet.
- The director is talking.
- I never get to talk.
You know what?
- What?
- There's a compilation...
of you interrupting him
on the internet.
- Really?
- When it's all put together,
it's almost 15 minutes long.
For 15 minutes, he interrupts...
Think about it.
- I mean...
- Really?
What just happened
isn't even a minute long.
- I never get to tell stories.
- There's a compilation of it.
- Cut it out.
- I'm wearing this for the opening.
Please welcome your partners
for today.
We're excited to have guests.
- Oh, my.
- Oh, hey.
- What are you doing here?
- You're finally here.
- Hi, Soyou.
- Welcome.
(Soyou, Doyeon of Weki Meki,
and Mijoo of Lovelyz)
(And they're followed by...)
(Yuqi of (G)I-DLE
and Won Young of IZ ONE)
- Hi, Doyeon.
- Hi.
(Everyone is busy
greeting each other.)
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
(So Min looks around.)
(Do we have any male guests?)
- Won Young, you're here.
- You're tall.
- Who?
- Won Young...
- She's really tall.
- She's so tall.
We were just talking about
how tall she's become.
I was so surprised.
She's become even taller.
Everyone is avoiding her.
We have one more guest.
- Let's welcome the last guest.
- There's one more?
- Yes.
- Please come out.
(Who is the last guest?)
- Who could it be?
- What's going on?
- Oh, my. It's Dong Jun.
- Dong Jun.
- It's Dong Jun.
- Hey, Dong Jun.
- Dong Jun.
- Look who's here.
- How have you been?
- Hi.
(They seem really happy.)
(So Min has mentioned many times...)
(that she likes guys like Dong Jun.)
("After Effect" starts playing.)
- It's automatic.
- I keep feeling sad
- So Min is finally smiling.
- You look so manly now.
So Min is finally smiling big.
- She's finally smiling.
- He looks so manly.
- Hi.
- What's with So Min?
- She's getting her hopes up again.
- It happens every week.
- She's tucking her hair back.
- She never gives up.
- Good. Go for it.
- No.
- Your ears will start bleeding.
(She can't even look at Dong Jun.)
- What's with So Min?
- What's with her?
All right.
Let me introduce our guests
one by one.
- First, Kim Dong Jun.
- Dong Jun.
- Hello.
- Yes!
- He's so good-looking.
(They welcome him enthusiastically.)
Back in 2015... That was long ago.
- It's been 5 years.
Last time, I appeared
together with SHINHWA.
- That's right.
- We went to the beach, right?
(While Dong Jun's interview
is going on...)
- He's so good-looking.
- We went to the beach, right?
(Se Chan laughs.)
What? Do you have a problem?
What's wrong?
- She says he's good-looking.
- She says, "He's so good-looking."
Stop it now.
- That's why it never works out.
- I never did that.
You said he's good-looking.
It's been recorded.
- She can't even look at him.
- Hold on. So Min, you should move.
- This is not okay. Come here.
- Switch with Ji Hyo.
- No! I don't want to.
- Go over there.
- I don't want to!
- Switch with her.
- Tears keep falling
- Go over there.
(She is sent away from Dong Jun.)
Okay.
Anyway, Dong Jun, is there anyone
you want to be partners with?
- There is.
- Who?
I've been curious about this person.
- Tell us.
(There is someone
he's been curious about?)
- Who?
- So Min.
- Oh, my.
(So Min's heart skips a beat.)
This is not good.
Why would you set her heart on fire?
- He planned this.
- Why would you...
- He planned this beforehand.
- What's with her?
- Oh, my.
- "Set her heart on fire"?
You're going a bit too far there.
- Hey.
- That's exaggerated.
- Why do you exaggerate so much?
- That's too dramatic.
- Be quiet.
- Don't be so dramatic.
- Anyway, he agrees.
- Don't exaggerate.
Don't set her heart on fire.
Don't say that if you don't mean it.
She's serious.
I mean it. I've been really curious.
But Dong Jun,
her boyfriend is right here.
- No.
- What are you talking about?
- People keep asking me...
- It's not true.
- Tears keep falling
- Seriously.
- Jae Suk.
- People get the wrong idea.
- What are you talking about?
- Se Chan is excited too.
- Really?
- You're right.
- I'm excited too.
- Look at him.
He may not have a swim ring, but
he looks like he's on a vacation.
- I'm taking someone with me.
- Where's your swim ring?
- I see.
- I'm going away today.
He came prepared.
- I can see it now.
- Yes.
Next up is Won Young.
By the way, I'm sorry to ask this,
how much have you grown
in the past year?
Since we last met,
I think I've grown...
at least 2 or 3cm taller.
- Right?
- So she's still growing.
Jang Doyeon should be nervous now.
- I'm getting nervous too...
- Be quiet.
I'm nervous too!
Don't I get a chance to talk
since they brought up Jang Doyeon?
Stop it.
- After me...
- Stop it.
- During the opening...
- Won Young is talking.
- Why do you cut in?
- You've interrupted him twice.
- Jae Suk interrupts him again.
- Gosh.
Stop it.
Aren't you stressed out
about people asking you...
about your height?
They do ask me a lot.
I'm starting to get
a bit stressed out.
What do they usually ask?
First, "Are you still growing?"
Second, "I think
you've grown taller."
You just said both.
(Jae Suk said both today.)
- Hey. You hurt her.
- I'm sorry.
Why did you do that?
- I...
- Why do you stress her out?
- Seriously.
- I almost didn't recognize her.
Someone walked up to me
and greeted me.
- So I said hello.
- That's right.
Okay.
She's so good
with her facial expressions.
Apparently, she has some tips
about facial expressions on stage.
It's not easy
to depict the lyrics...
- with your expressions.
- No.
Is there anything you think
is the most important?
My part goes,
"Your magic wakes me up".
If I do it the ordinary way...
Should I look in this direction?
(This is how she practices
the ordinary way.)
- Something like that.
- That's ordinary?
- That's supposed to be ordinary.
Then please add more emotion.
- And then...
- Do it your style.
On stage, I'd do...
(Your magic wakes me up)
- It has much more emotion.
- She moves her eyebrows.
- She moves her eyes a lot.
- She's really good.
- It's not easy.
- She's so good.
Jong Kook, what do you do
to covey the lyrics?
- Try it.
- I don't...
My eyes are too small.
They can't express anything.
In the old days, the expressions
were not this detailed, right?
This is all we did.
(They didn't use
a lot of facial expressions.)
(Regardless of the lyrics,
all the moves were exaggerated.)
I don't know how many times
I did this.
Why do you always kick
even when you're singing?
- What's with you?
- I poked a lot too.
But I didn't use
a lot of facial expressions.
- Please give it up for Won Young.
- Thank you.
Let's move on.
- Next up is... Oh, my.
- Who is it?
This is her first time
on Running Man.
- Yuqi.
- Oh, yes.
- You're from China, right?
- Yes.
This is your first time
on Running Man.
How are you feeling?
Yes, I've always wanted
to be on this show.
Actually, I was a host
on Running Man China...
last year.
- Running Man China?
- That's right.
- Yes.
Apparently, Yuqi loves giraffes.
- That's right.
- You actually love giraffes?
He's getting excited.
My dream used to be
riding on a giraffe.
- Ride on it today.
- Ride on it.
- Try it.
- She means a real giraffe!
- Ride on him.
- Why would she ride on me?
- Get on the giraffe.
- She means a real giraffe!
- Just try it.
- You are a giraffe.
- I mean...
- Hurry up and jump on him.
- Wait.
- Kwang Soo.
- Even if I get down on all fours...
- Get on his back.
- Not you.
- Why would you get on?
- You should stand up.
- Stand up.
- The giraffe should stand up.
- Like this.
Run around like a giraffe first.
- Try walking.
- Why do I have to do this?
- For Yuqi...
- Do it for Yuqi.
- A real giraffe is taller.
All right. You can get on
his back now.
A little lower. There you go.
- Get on his back.
- Seriously?
Riding on a giraffe is her dream.
She got on my back for real?
(It's her very first ride
on a giraffe.)
- Giddy up!
- Run!
- I mean...
- Give him the leaf.
- Run!
- Here we go. Run!
- Let's go!
The ground...
Her dream is riding on a giraffe.
- Why would she get on my back?
- That's enough.
- That's enough. Okay.
- Good job.
- Her dream came true.
- Okay.
- We're done.
- How are you feeling?
- Yuqi's dream...
- How does it feel?
- came true.
- Her dream came true.
Thank you.
- We make your dream come true.
- Yuqi.
Next up is Mijoo.
- Yes!
- Mijoo!
How are you doing these days?
With the pandemic going on
much longer than expected,
I guess it's hard to plan...
new albums and everything.
- That's right.
- Why is the question so hard?
- Ask an easy one.
- I'm not an anchor or anything.
My heart almost burst.
- "What is he talking about?"
- What do you mean?
- "How is she going to answer?"
- It's not that hard.
- I almost hit him with my elbow.
- Hey.
All Yuqi did is get on a giraffe.
- Why would you ask her...
- Mijoo...
- about her future plans?
- About the pandemic.
- She's been on the show a lot.
- It's a tough time.
That's why I asked her
that question.
After your appearance
on Running Man,
did your mother say anything?
- I got scolded a lot.
- Why?
- Why? You were the best!
You did a good job.
- She was the best.
- It was fun,
- It was fun.
- but because I'm a girl...
When my mom saw me
sitting like this, she said,
"Are you crazy?
Why were you sitting like that?"
(Her mom scolded her
out of love.)
"Why were you sitting like that?"
She scolded me so much.
Mijoo takes after her mother.
"Why were you spreading
your legs like that?"
- Mijoo is so funny.
- I love it.
- She's very straightforward.
- She's very cool.
- Seriously...
- Her mom is so cool.
Isn't she amazing?
She said my face looked so big.
Won Young is the one
panicking the most right now.
- I'm sorry.
- Right?
Mijoo is an idol group member too.
- But she's so straightforward.
- Not all members are the same.
- Of course.
Variety shows love
people like Mijoo.
Won Young keeps giving her
a meaningless thumbs-up.
- I mean...
- Why is she doing that?
Why are you doing that?
All right.
- Next up is Soyou.
- Soyou.
It's been a while, Soyou.
Her real name is Kang Ji Hyun.
- How did you know?
- Really?
Actually, this is what we say...
- every summer.
- SISTAR?
SISTAR is...
- I know.
- That's true.
We have no girl groups
for summer anymore.
Do you still get that a lot?
I do get that a lot.
So a new album is coming out.
(I do get that a lot.
So a new album is coming out.)
(Is SISTAR releasing a new album?)
- Really?
- It's big news!
Jae Suk.
- See?
- The three of you?
- I'm doing it alone.
- Alone? Hang on.
(What's wrong with you?
I'm doing it solo, not as SISTAR.)
- Hey.
- You seem too disappointed.
Why did you talk about yourself
when we asked about SISTAR?
- Suk Jin! Why are you doing this?
- I'm a member of SISTAR.
- I know you're SISTAR, but we...
- Soyou.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Please understand him.
- I'm quite upset.
- You should understand him.
I'm sorry about that.
- But we were talking about...
- It's the flow of the conversation.
It sounded like SISTAR was
going to release a new album.
I misunderstood it as well.
I thought it was about SISTAR.
- See?
- I'm sorry. It's my fault.
So you're releasing
a new summer song.
Yes. It will be a cool summer song.
As you just said,
your new summer song...
- is coming out soon.
- Right.
We should hear it then.
(Soyou's new song, "Gotta Go"
is coming out in two days.)
Soyou has a nice voice.
(Surprised)
("Gotto Go" by Soyou)
This is it.
- It's summer.
- I love it!
It sounds great
from the beginning.
Let's go.
It's nice.
Head.
(Head and shoulder)
- Head.
- Shoulder.
We need a song like this in summer.
- All right.
- This is a summer song.
Now it feels like summer.
- It feels so cool.
- We definitely need this.
- She's really good.
- It's really cool.
She's different.
Now we have Doyeon here.
(Performance queen and characterful
actress, Doyeon of Weki Meki)
We have Jang Doyeon for comedy.
- And we have Kim Doyeon for K-pop.
- Right.
How have you been, Doyeon?
I've been getting ready
for my new drama.
- I see.
- You're starting a drama.
She appeared in a drama before.
- It was "Be Melodramatic".
- "Be Melodramatic".
That's right.
You watched the drama. You liked it.
- I did. I really liked it.
- You should say that.
Aren't you going to work?
No, that's not it.
You should work.
Talk about the drama.
You're lost in admiration.
Gosh, no.
Dong Jun, you should wait outside.
- That's not true.
- Look at her.
So we have Doyeon here.
Please give a round of applause
to the six guests...
who are joining us today.
Today, we're going to have
Don't Worry Be Happy Partner Race.
The eight members of Running Man
acquired the mission fund...
according to the results
of last week's missions.
- I feel bad for my partner.
- The guests will choose...
their partners without knowing
the amount the members have.
There's definitely a dud.
So you'd better try to choose
a partner...
who seems to have
a lot of money for the race.
Since the guests don't
have the mission fund,
- we will give them 10 dollars each.
- 10 dollars?
(The guests get the mission fund
of 10 dollars each.)
- 10 dollars?
- Are they getting 10 dollars?
- It's no problem then.
- What?
He seems pretty happy.
- Now I don't feel pressure.
- I bet Jae Suk has no money.
(He seems very happy.)
- He's happy.
- 10 dollars is big money.
- Do you have no money?
- What?
- Do you not have any money?
- That's not true.
- He doesn't.
- I guess he has no money.
- He's completely broke.
- He's totally penniless.
You will play Dice Proposal
to decide partners.
The seven men will
get a blank dice each.
And they will take turns
to find a partner.
Once a man comes out,
women will put a sticker...
on his dice if they like him.
(The women will put stickers
on the dice of a man they want.)
And you will pay a dollar
every time you put a sticker.
If they want to be picked,
they will spend a lot of money.
You can put stickers on six faces
if you want.
- Gosh, So Min.
- Don't look at me.
(So Min, Soyou, Mijoo,
Ji Hyo, Won Young, Doyeon, Yuqi)
If you want to be
Ji Suk Jin's partner,
please raise your hand and tell me
how many stickers you need.
- This is cruel.
- Soyou is moving.
The girls are busy.
- Mijoo is going through her bag.
- They're going through their bags.
Everyone.
Ji Hyo is opening her bag now.
- She makes a lot of gestures now.
- She's opening it.
- Look at him.
- I have some money.
- He has a lot of money.
- Can he show his money like that?
- I'll buy six stickers.
- All right.
Six stickers?
- You're buying all the stickers?
- Do you have to do that?
She wants to make sure.
- He's got a lot of money.
- Just stay still.
- You have a lot of money.
- Just stay quiet!
I'm doing this for money.
- I told you to just stay still.
- Look at them.
- I said I'm buying them all.
- Song Ji Hyo!
If there's anyone else who wants
to buy it, Suk Jin gets to choose.
But there's no one.
Who knows? You should
give them some time.
- He likes it.
- There's no one. Don't look back.
- Hey.
- No one wants you.
Mijoo, did you just shake your arm?
(She just expressed her feelings.)
Ji Hyo is the big player here.
- I think so.
- I know. She's so cool.
(It's the meeting
of Big Nose and Big Player.)
- One.
- Suk Jin.
All right. It's settled.
(As expected, Suk Jin
and Ji Hyo have become partners.)
He did this.
Yes!
- Who's next?
- Dong Jun.
If you want to be
Dong Jun's partner,
(Laughing)
- please tell me.
- She's about to sell her soul.
Look at her face.
There's one woman
who's raising her hand bashfully.
- She's willing to sell her soul.
- So Min.
- She's acting cute.
- Why are you being so shy?
- How many do you want?
- I'll buy one sticker.
Just one?
- One is enough.
- Then I'll buy the rest five.
- What? So suddenly?
- Can I do that?
No. I'll buy six.
(Surprised)
I'll buy six stickers.
For whom are you
buying five stickers?
For So Min.
(It's all for So Min.)
What?
- Can I do that?
- I didn't know.
- What was that?
- My gosh.
For So Min?
- Why are you doing that?
- He's so nice.
- Hang on.
- What is going on?
- He's sweet.
- We're just...
playing games with partners.
This is just a game.
This isn't about dating someone.
- Isn't this "X-Man"?
- This isn't "X-Man".
You might not see her ever again
after this show.
Exactly.
I'll just buy six stickers.
Is there anyone else
who wants to join?
That's not possible.
- You two are partners now.
- Okay. I bought six stickers.
So Min and Dong Jun are partners.
How can I play games spontaneously
when he's being like this?
Come here.
Hello.
Hello. Let's do this.
(And the rest of them
chose partners as well.)
(Se Chan and Doyeon,
Kwang Soo and Won Young)
(Jong Kook and Soyou,
Haha and Mijoo)
(So Min and Dong Jun,
Jae Suk and Yuqi)
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo)
So your partners are decided now.
I'll give you prize money according
to the results after each round.
The top two partners
with the most money...
can buy any items we prepared...
with your prize money.
- Really?
- Yuqi, this is the day.
- It's the day.
- This is the day.
And the partners
with the least money...
- will get a penalty.
- There's a penalty as well.
- Oh, the team that comes in last...
- Once you put on your team uniform,
- we will start the mission.
- Let's go!
Let's bring it on!
(They've changed
into the team uniform.)
(So Min is the first one
to show up.)
She came early again.
- What?
- You're early again.
Why?
(She fixes her makeup
since she's here early.)
(She rubs her hands.)
It's cool in here.
(This is what she always does,
but she seems somewhat nervous.)
I guess we're doing something.
(It's a mission where you dance.)
Are we dancing? Dance?
(As soon as she hears
about dancing,)
(she starts to stretch,
feeling shy.)
I can't dance.
I have a bad back.
(She says she can't dance.)
I have no money. I'm broke.
But I don't want my partner
to get a penalty.
I'd feel bad
if he got a penalty here.
Please gather around.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Here's the first mission.
It's an extreme battle between
a defender and an attacker.
Freeze Tag Dancing King.
I bet Jong Kook will be good at it.
- It's done. We're ready.
- You'll be divided into two groups.
And each team will dance
in the red zone in turn.
Once I point out the best dancers,
the music will stop.
Then they can push out
the opponents for 10 seconds.
And we will give them money for
the number of members pushed out.
- We have to be strong.
- Jong Kook must be good at this.
- Soyou is just as strong.
- And we should dance well.
That's right.
The important thing
is the list of matches.
We have seven spoons
divided into two groups.
You will pick one. Those with
the same color will dance together.
- Yuqi, you must pick a good group.
- Really?
We can't be in the same group
with Jong Kook and Soyou.
You have only 30 cents anyway.
You will see who smiles at the end.
But you have only 30 cents.
(They all picked a spoon.)
- My gosh.
- They all are really strong.
Let's begin then.
If you're pushed out,
you're not eliminated.
You will just lose your money
every time you're pushed out.
How far can we go
when we push out the opponents?
Why would you ask a question
like that, Soyou?
Soyou, just don't kill them.
- It can be as hard as you can.
- What is she doing with her hand?
You can also tickle them.
I don't feel ticklish.
- He's not tickled either.
- I'm not ticklish.
- Really?
- I feel nothing.
- How can I play games with them?
- I'm not ticklish at all.
Jong Kook and Soyou...
look like trainers at a gym.
- That's true.
- We should open a gym.
- It's so funny.
I think we should hug
each other to win.
(Scoffing)
No, that's not what I meant.
- Hang on.
- I'm sorry.
- Wait.
- Don't say that.
- I made a slip of the tongue.
- Se Chan...
- told Doyeon,
- Stop it.
"I think we should hug
each other to win."
(Se Chan says they should
hug each other to win.)
No, it was a slip of the tongue.
- I didn't mean it.
- Hey.
- What was that?
- I mean we should stick together.
What are you trying to pull off?
What are you doing?
I just meant
we should stick together.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's not like that.
It's a mistake. I meant to say
we should stick together.
- Look at him.
- Let's hold together, okay?
- Gosh, I was surprised.
- I tried to ignore it.
He's painting a big picture.
- We should stand together.
- You know what?
We've never seen Se Chan so happy
for the past year.
He's so energetic.
- He's smiling broadly.
- He's smiling a lot.
You look bright today.
I'm happy today.
I'll play the music then.
Music, please.
Dong Jun is a good dancer.
I bet Dong Jun is good.
(No one is excited
about Kwang Soo's dance.)
(Warming up)
Mijoo is on fire.
(The audience is excited too.)
- Show us what you've got.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- There they are.
- Show us your dance.
The music is too slow.
Show us the workout dance.
Go ahead and do bench presses.
They are lifting dumbbells.
It's a dumbbell dance.
- Go ahead and do bench presses.
- Okay.
- List it up.
Let's do some bench presses.
Okay.
- Okay.
- It suits you.
- I know.
- Okay.
(Kwang Soo and Won Young step up.)
There they go.
What are they doing?
(The dance that Kwang Soo and
Won Young will do is...)
(The 1st step is a fatal gaze.)
(The 2nd step is various model poses
using their long arms and legs.)
What are they doing
instead of dancing?
Stop doing model poses.
What are they doing
instead of dancing?
(He's not bothered
and continues being annoying.)
(Jae Suk comes up to him...)
What is he doing?
(and punishes him with a headlock.)
Why is he doing this?
Why?
(This is the cost of acting cool
instead of dancing.)
(Just you wait.)
Gosh, that was so annoying.
It was really annoying.
(The next song is...)
("Shake It" by SISTAR)
(As soon as she hears the song,)
(Se Chan and Doyeon step up.)
- SISTAR!
- Is it SISTAR's song?
(She dances to SISTAR's
choreography perfectly.)
Wait.
She's really good at dancing.
She only came up to show off.
Nice.
(Shake it, shake it.)
(They do a couple wave dance.)
(Doing his best)
I think Se Chan...
- is so funny.
- Hey, Se Chan...
Se Chan looks like her helper.
He's serious.
(Yang Helper does his best.)
(Even if she doesn't look at him,
he does his best behind her.)
(The music changes.)
(The look in his eyes changes.)
(So Min and Dong Jun
step up carefully.)
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Goodness.
(He begins breakdancing.)
(His coolness explodes.)
- Did you see that?
- All of a sudden.
(The idol singer
of 11 years rips apart the stage.)
Did you see that?
(There's no break to her heart
as she watches him breakdancing.)
So Min!
- So Min, pull yourself together!
- So Min!
(She loses her mind
and lets go of herself.)
(The frog lets go of herself
without any breaks.)
She's break dancing too.
So Min, pull yourself together!
Pull yourself together!
3, 2,
One. Dong Jun and So Min.
- Dong Jun.
- Hold on.
(The couple that is called on
will get prize money...)
(according to how many people
they push out in 10 seconds.)
(So Min and Dong Jun
were called on.)
Dong Jun.
- Hold onto me.
- Pull them out. Okay!
- I'm frozen.
- He's frozen.
I'm frozen. I'm frozen!
(Is he getting dismembered?)
- He's almost out.
- I'm sorry, Se Chan.
(He grabbed his belt
and pulled him out.)
He's out.
(Dong Jun is incredible.)
- I'm sorry, Se Chan.
- Sit down.
(Dong Jun's next target is...)
- No.
- I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
- Wait. This is... Hey!
- No!
- Hey!
(This time, he goes for
Kwang Soo's belt.)
Gosh, this is...
(Kwang Soo endures it,
and the time ends.)
Se Chan...
- Se Chan...
- You almost hung him.
- Se Chan almost got hung.
- Where did he grab?
He grabbed me at a weird place.
- Get up.
- So...
- There's no place to grab, so...
- It's okay...
- to grab us by our pants,
- It was too...
but why would you put your fingers
in between my cheeks?
He tried to rip them off.
When Se Chan and Doyeon
were dancing,
it looked like a guy who was dating
a girl that's out of his league.
(I'm undeserving
of such a girlfriend.)
- It's hard for him to handle her.
- Right.
She's a girl that's out of
his league.
This is the second round of
the mission. Cue the music.
(The music starts.)
("After Effect" by ZE:A)
You should go up.
I don't know your dance.
Just do this.
(All Dong Jun did was dance.)
I can't do it.
Look at So Min.
- What are they doing?
- Come over here.
- Why are they dating here?
- Seriously.
Hold on. Wait.
Hold on. So Min is really...
in the middle of date right now.
I'm serious.
- My goodness.
- So Min. Enough already.
- So Min is...
- Don't date here.
It's not that. Dong Jun
looks at people with warm eyes.
Do we look at you with cold eyes?
Yes.
Look at his eyes. They're so warm.
- You're too much.
- No.
Gosh, it's so hot.
(They put their date on hold
and get back to work.)
Whose song is this?
(Kwang Soo and Won Young
step up immediately.)
(Flapping around)
Gosh. Doesn't he look like a bug?
He really does.
(A new kind of bug dance)
He looks like a bug.
(He gets rid of the bug.)
- What now?
- You're so annoying!
- Why?
- Goodness.
- What song is this?
- We should go up.
(Back to the millennium.)
Is this it?
- How do you do this?
- Soyou is really good.
Oh, my.
(Soyou is really good.)
How do you do that?
(It's a retro dance that minimizes
muscle loss.)
- It's over.
- They're good.
- Do it harder.
It's over.
(An event balloon intrudes.)
(Jang Won Young the balloon
begins spinning her sangmo.)
(Won Young is so cute.)
Jeon So Min. Why is she going up?
(I shouldn't sit out
during a retro dance.)
Look at So Min.
(A retro dance party featuring
event balloons)
Okay. 3, 2,
One. Kim Jong Kook and Soyou.
Oh, my gosh.
Kim Jong Kook and Soyou.
(As soon as they are called on,
Won Young goes flying.)
Oh, my.
Gosh, that surprised me.
(Soyou is incredibly strong.)
You shouldn't do this.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, guys.
He keeps grabbing me
in a weird place.
- Oh, my.
- Gosh, this is incredible.
Gosh, this is incredible.
(Trainer Kook can pull two people
at once with his strength.)
He's so cool.
- Amazing.
- There you go.
- Jong Kook!
- We did it.
It's clean.
How can we beat them?
They're too strong.
That was nice and neat.
- They got six dollars.
- That was nice.
I thought he was a bulldozer.
An adult joined a game with kids.
So Min and Dong Jun got 1 dollar.
Jong Kook and Soyou got 6 dollars.
Okay.
(The second group will go next.)
She's warming up.
This is going to be interesting
because of Mijoo.
- Nice.
- Hey.
Why didn't we get songs like this?
They came up.
They played this song a lot
on "X-Man".
- This song is hard to dance to.
- It is.
(She warms up a little...)
That's right.
(and releases
her dancing instincts.)
That's right.
That's it.
(Behind her cute appearance, her
powerful dance skills were hidden.)
(Making a fuss)
What is this?
Why are you dancing for so long?
Go back in.
(Acting frivolous)
(Stopping)
You wanted to do something,
but you couldn't, right?
(Nodding)
(The next song is...)
("Gang".)
It's "Gang".
(The look in her eyes changes
as soon as she hears the song.)
It's "Gang".
- "Gang".
- Hey.
Mijoo, you look so cool.
She's good.
She's good at it.
What was that?
(Haha is crawling on the floor.)
Do you know what that is?
- What is that?
- That's not how you do it.
That's not how you do it.
(She does it perfectly.
She must watch it 3 times a day.)
(The Rain Effect is when you
entrust your body...)
(to the "Gang" rhythm.)
(At that moment)
(The reason why everyone
is cracking up)
(She suddenly transforms into
a gorilla.)
("Gang" has reached its limit.)
We should've done it.
Why are you going that far?
(Her tenacious DNA
goes beyond "Gang".)
She's incredible.
Just as I expected her to be.
- You guys should go.
- Ji Hyo, let's go.
Suk Jin looks so cheesy.
(Slow dancing)
What are they doing?
(What are they doing?)
What is this?
- Suk Jin, what is this?
- What is this?
What is this?
(The music changes.)
- They know how to have fun.
- You should go.
It's KOYOTE's song.
(They reject the normal.)
Gosh, Mijoo.
(It's a surprising dance
that goes beyond our expectations.)
She's unbelievable. Seriously.
Her energy is unbelievable. Oh, my.
She's unbelievable.
(Her hair came out?)
She's unbelievable. Seriously.
(The fantastic outing
of her hair extensions)
- What is this?
What is this?
(She's doing her best.)
- Mijoo.
- She ripped out her hair.
Who's going to beat her?
Nobody can beat her.
- Who's going to beat her?
- What's with her prop?
- Is that necessary?
- What is going on?
- She's doing her best to win.
- How can anyone beat her?
Just give her the win.
Mijoo, stop!
She's the best.
(She can't stop herself.)
What did she pull out of her hair?
- Why did she rip out her hair?
- She's the best.
Are you okay? Hey.
(Yuqi also takes out
her extensions.)
This isn't a game where you
rip out your hair!
Do you have any? Do you?
(She joins the line
with disheveled hair.)
(You can't escape
the insane hair party.)
(What on earth is this?)
(We didn't come up with this game
to see this.)
Mijoo is incredible.
(It was a feast
of unexpected dances.)
- That's enough.
- Three,
2, 1. Haha and Mijoo.
- Are they coming again?
- Yes.
Why are you so strong?
He got him. He's dragging him out,
but he's not coming along.
They're strong.
The other side. Goodness.
What is this?
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
Song Ji Hyo is out.
It was a close call,
but we came to that decision.
It's impossible to beat Mijoo.
- We can't beat her.
- She's unrivaled.
How can they beat her?
I don't think you can meet with
your mom for a while again.
Will your mother be okay with this?
She'll call me crazy again.
- What?
- That's what she'd say.
Why do K-pop idols
always have additional hair?
- Right.
- I'm fascinated...
by her reattaching it.
- Is she reattaching it?
- I didn't know it was possible.
Here are the results
for the second group.
Jae Suk and Yuqi got 4 dollars.
Haha and Mijoo got 3 dollars.
- Suk Jin and Ji Hyo got none.
- Three dollars?
I bet you're hungry now.
- Right.
- We are.
You'll play...
for the dish you want
with the money you earned.
This is Random Delivery.
- Goodness.
- What now?
Inside the 10 delivery cases
are 10 different dishes.
Each team will come forward...
and choose a delivery case.
In secret,
the team will check what's inside.
The other teams,
while not knowing what's inside,
will ask questions about the dish...
to decide how much they'll bid.
The team with the highest bid
will win the dish.
- My gosh.
- We have to bid on the dishes.
Some dishes are enough
for the both of you,
but some will leave you hungry.
We need to fool them so that
they'd bid on a small portion.
- Right.
- We need to fool them.
Let's set up the cases first.
(What kind of food
are in the cases?)
- We'll now begin the auction.
- Sure.
Please come forward, choose a case,
and check what's inside.
Watch carefully
when they pick it up.
Which one? Take your pick.
(After pondering,
he chooses case number nine.)
- Case number nine.
- It must be light.
- Dong Jun, it seems light.
- It's not.
Your shoulder is still relaxed.
It must be light.
Please check what's inside.
Look at them stalling.
- So Min...
- Check So Min out.
The dish is on the upper shelf.
That means the dish
isn't of a big portion.
- Exactly.
- Really?
So Min, please describe the taste.
Well...
It's sweet and heavy.
- Right.
- Right?
It must be a dessert.
I say it's yogurt.
- Yes, a dessert.
- It must be.
- A piece of cake?
- A dessert.
It must be.
- Dong Jun seems flustered.
- Hold on.
Like we said, it's sweet but heavy.
- Then it's a dessert.
- A dessert.
- It's not a main dish.
- Something sweet?
To be honest, it's not a main dish.
But it can be served as a starter.
Right, but it can also
be a main dish.
- Of course.
- It can?
So Min, who would you
enjoy it with the most?
(Who would So Min
enjoy it with the most?)
With me.
(Her level of happiness
is at 200 percent.)
Dong Jun,
stop playing with her heart.
He's mean, isn't he?
- Dong Jun...
- I didn't think he'd be like this.
- He...
- Look at you being all cheeky.
- Have at it then.
- He's unbelievable.
So Min, have a seat.
We'll keep the questions coming.
Don't. My gosh.
Dong Jun, can we focus on our work?
- Gosh.
- She wants to work.
- What a player.
- You're the worst.
He's the kind of type to not let go.
- Right.
- I need him to promise something.
If you don't call me after today...
She's right.
I guess you didn't know
what she's like.
Dong Jun, you should
rush out of here once we're done.
"Start the van. Drive. Drive!"
But So Min will chase him.
(He will be escaping for his life.)
"Get him!"
I'll buy her this
when we meet again.
- The next time?
- You'll buy her this?
Really?
There's a place where they serve
a tasty one in my neighborhood.
Sounds good.
It must be a waffle!
(We got you.)
- Where she lives...
- It could be that.
There are famous waffle shops
near Sookmyung Women's University.
- A waffle.
- It must be a waffle.
It could be ice cream.
Something like vanilla ice cream.
It's the whole package.
- So please don't bid on it.
- He's right.
It's like one of those
snack packages.
I want a main dish though.
The auction will begin.
Dong Jun and So Min will bid first.
This will tell us.
They could bid less
just to throw us off.
- How about a dollar?
- How much will it be?
- A dollar?
- 1.5 dollars?
1.5 dollars? A dollar?
- A dollar.
- So it's a dollar.
You don't seem pleased at all.
- Can't we resell this?
- Sure.
- But this...
- It's not appealing, right?
- Not really.
- Me neither.
I can guarantee you this though.
- Jae Suk loves this dish too.
- Really?
I've seen him eat this a lot.
- What about me?
I can bet all 10 fingers
on the fact that...
Suk Jin loves this dish.
1.7 dollars.
You won't regret it.
Let me remind you that
you only have 50 cents.
- What?
- Really?
- You didn't know?
- We do?
- Seriously?
- And you're coveting the food?
- What are you talking about?
- You're broke!
You can't have the food for free.
- We have the money.
- You spent it all on the dice.
As far as we know,
you have 50 cents.
You guys are broke.
This is because you bought
all six sides.
So they're out of
the bidding war, right?
- But we can take out a loan.
- Sure you can.
However, you'll have a higher chance
of coming in last.
Sure. But we should still eat first.
Then 1.7 dollars.
- We'll bid two dollars.
- No!
I won't go any higher.
- Don't be this way.
- Got it.
- Did they bid two dollars?
- Right.
- Then we bid 2.5 dollars.
- Sure, 2.5.
- Hold on.
- We don't have to eat,
- but we bid 2.7 dollars.
- Stop it!
That's our last bid. I mean it.
Then we bid 2.8 dollars.
- Right.
- 2.8 dollars.
Three dollars!
- 3.1 dollars.
- My goodness.
We'll bid 3.5 dollars.
- Then we bid 3.6 dollars.
- 3.6 dollars.
That's too high for us
to compete with.
Don't you dare bid anymore.
This is ours to keep.
They're trying to trick us.
- Suk Jin, bid four dollars.
- They want it for themselves.
Zip it, will you?
Stop encouraging him!
You know how it is.
- Don't fall for it.
- Stop that.
Let me add this then.
Suk Jin has taken
many photos of this dish.
3.8 dollars!
(Smack!)
(He bids big for the pig in a poke.)
(That earns him
a smack on the head.)
What's wrong?
You're being smacked around today.
We're seeing
a truly battered spouse.
Are you kidding me?
I promise to make up for it
by earning more.
It's just...
(I'll do better from here on out.)
I promise to make up for it
by earning more.
I'll bring you a fatter paycheck.
- You bid 3.8 dollars.
- 3.8
(The highest bid is 3.8 dollars.)
- It's too expensive.
- It's too high.
3.8 dollars is too much.
I can feel it, you know.
The dish is something worth eating.
5, 4, 3...
Four dollars.
I swear, that's my last bid.
(Not again!)
- I'll leave this with you now.
- You already promised.
No way!
- Listen to Won Young.
- No, no.
This will be my last bid.
- So Min's delighted.
- We can't even bid any higher.
Kwang Soo and Won Young
bid four dollars.
5, 4,
- 3, 2, 1.
- Unbelievable.
(Sold to Kwang Soo and Won Young
for 4 dollars.)
- Okay!
- Four dollars.
Suk Jin added a photo of this
to his profile page.
- His profile page?
- Mine?
- Yes, that's right.
- It's of lamb chops.
- 1, 2, 3.
- 2, 3.
(What did Kwang Soo
bid 4 dollars on?)
(TFS set:
Tteokbokki, fritters, and sundae)
You see?
- It's not bad!
- I said you'd like this.
- What did I tell you?
- It's not bad.
What the...
- This is my favorite.
- It was a good one.
- They look delicious.
- What did I tell you?
- They look tasty.
- I need to take a break.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, of course.
- I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
- Don't be.
(Haha and Mijoo are up next.)
Sniffing isn't allowed.
- That's equal to cheating.
- Don't you dare.
I can't believe
we lost the last round.
(After pondering,
they choose case number 3.)
- It's light.
- It must be.
- It sure is.
Can we sit this one out?
- It's light.
- No, it's heavy!
- It's extremely light.
His arm didn't show
any kind of tension.
It really must be light.
(After carrying it over with
difficulty, they drop it.)
I doubt it.
(Gosh, it's heavy.)
- I think they're snacks.
- Take a look.
I could tell by Haha's face.
(They cautiously
check what's inside.)
- No way.
- That was brief.
I can tell that
he's putting on an act.
He said, "No way" though.
Is it hot or cold?
- I like it when it's cold.
- Me too.
Tell us its color at the same time.
At the same time?
- 1, 2, 3.
- 2, 3.
- Green.
(They weren't in sync.)
- Say it simultaneously.
- Why?
- I don't like green food.
- What food is green?
It must be a salad.
A salad?
Is it a salad?
He said he likes it better
when it's cold.
- Maybe it's broccoli.
- I hate that.
It could be two pieces of broccoli.
Mijoo, when did you have it last?
About two years ago.
- Two years ago?
- It's not favored.
She doesn't eat it often.
I don't get to eat it often
because it's so good.
Eating this
leads to catching a cold.
- They're trying awfully hard.
- Something green?
- I doubt it's anything good.
- I don't think so either.
Also, what can be green?
Nothing I know that's green
is tasty.
It's time to bid.
Say something good about it.
Although, I doubt
it'll lead to a bid.
Guys...
- We'll start at 10 cents.
- See?
(He starts with the minimum bid.)
He could be bluffing.
No way.
It's too late for that.
We bid a dollar.
A dollar. That sounds good, right?
Won Young isn't pleased.
Won Young, they're bluffing.
- I think I chose the wrong partner.
- It sounds like a good deal. No.
- Over a dollar?
- You're just learning that?
- I just realized it.
- Over a dollar?
- Come on. It's not bad.
- What's wrong with you?
- A dollar?
- Yes, a dollar.
- What's wrong with you?
- Over here.
What if we end up having broccolis?
(Blocking)
Over here.
(Shut that hole.)
She hit him for real.
- She hit him.
- She actually hit him.
1.1 dollars.
- 1.1 dollars?
- Yes.
1.1 dollars.
Suk Jin, we'll go bankrupt
because of you.
You have five seconds.
- Unbelievable.
- Five.
- You can bid more.
- Four.
3, 2.
Two dollars!
- How much was it?
- What?
- They bid 2 dollars.
- 2 dollars?
- Yes, 2 dollars.
- 2 dollars.
- 5...
- We're serious.
- Four.
Over here. I bid 2.3 dollars.
Are you insane?
- Darn you.
- She hit him again.
- Ji Hyo's furious.
- What's your problem?
- I want to eat that.
- It could be anything!
- But...
- Is it worth taking out a loan?
I mean...
This is a marital spat.
- Tell me about it.
- They're like a bickering couple.
The money we have
is enough for just that.
This is our only chance
to eat anything.
All right.
I'll say this again.
- Should we get it?
- Children love it.
- 2.3 dollars.
Let's buy this.
The fact Haha keeps saying
good things about it...
Five,
four,
- three,
- Won't you bid more money?
- 2,
- Won't you bid 2.40 dollars?
one.
Congratulations.
What is it?
Congratulations!
(2 banana milk?)
(Laughing)
I feel so bad.
He paid the proper price.
- These are nice.
- He paid the proper price.
- Ji Hyo.
- Thank goodness.
Thank goodness.
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo.
(He got banana milk
as well as the delivery case.)
These are nice.
Ji Hyo, banana milk is good
for the skin.
It's good for the skin.
You can take the delivery case too.
Thank goodness.
It could have ended badly.
Kwang Soo, we are in your care.
(Kwang Soo and Won Young
are up next.)
I will tell you honestly.
We have to buy from now on.
- Case number seven?
- Sure.
- We choose case number seven.
- Okay.
(He chooses case number seven.)
- It seems to be heavy.
- There is food inside.
It's heavy.
We should eat it.
It's swaying too much.
- It's heavy.
- May I take a look?
- Of course not.
- It's swaying.
I hear the rattling sound.
(Hitting)
If there are no worries about
spilling, it can't be anything good.
(They scan the food first.)
(My goodness.)
Say the color of the food
at the same time.
1, 2, 3.
- Beige.
- Yellow mountain.
1, 2, 3.
- Beige.
- Yellow mountain.
What did you say?
Mountain?
- It's beige.
- Yellow.
- Mountain?
- I would say it's yellow.
Is it curry?
- Beige? Cream pasta?
- Yellow?
It must be pickled radish.
It must be!
It must be pickled radish
that comes with jjajangmyeon.
- Pickled radish is yellow or beige.
- Yellow or beige.
- You are right.
- That must be the case.
- For goodness' sake.
- That's not it.
Say how many words are
in the name of the dish.
1, 2, 3.
(Say how many words are
in the name of the dish.)
Two.
Won Young says two.
One.
(She changes the fingers.)
Won Young says two.
- 2?
- Won Young says 2.
The name of the dish
can be two words.
- Really?
- One word.
- It's something you crave.
- It's on the expensive side.
- Is it on the expensive side?
- Yes.
Let's start the bid now.
You won't be disappointed.
How much is the starting bid?
We will start at three dollars.
That seems excessive.
It's too expensive, right?
It's too expensive.
For some reason,
I don't want to bid on their dish.
Seriously.
Haha, shall all of us forgo a bid?
- Let's do that.
- The starting bid is three dollars.
- We haven't forgone a bid before.
- Shall we do that this time?
The starting bid is three dollars.
- Pay three dollars and eat it.
- It's too expensive.
- Shall we stay this way?
- In that case,
we will start at two dollars.
In that case,
- You can't do that.
- What are you doing?
- Wait a minute.
- You already said three dollars.
- Let's see the next one.
- You can have it.
There are many delivery cases left.
- Enjoy the dish.
- Three dollars. Enjoy it.
Take a look at the dish.
Thank you.
Stay.
- Stay.
- 5, 4,
- 3...
- We will bid 3.5 dollars.
- Okay. Go ahead and eat it.
- 3.5 dollars.
- Everyone, stay.
- Stay.
We will give you one more chance.
- 3.5 dollars?
- Are you sure you don't want it?
3.5 dollars.
- 3.5 dollars.
- Why don't you want it?
3.7 dollars.
- 3.7 dollars.
- 5,
- 4,
- Take it if you don't have food.
three,
two...
You really should take it.
- Okay.
- What could it be?
(Sold to Kwang Soo and Won Young
for 3.7 dollars.)
- What is it?
- Look at Won Young's face.
- Did you see her face?
Look at her face.
- She is swearing with her eyes.
- What is it?
- Why didn't he stop at 3 dollars?
- Seriously.
- He raised the bid.
- Why did he raise the bid?
- Why did he...
- What is it?
Why did he raise the bid?
- Is there no food?
- Pickled radish.
Boiled eggs.
(4 boiled eggs)
Good shot. Good shot.
(He ended up spending
3.7 dollars on eggs.)
They are perfect with the TFS set.
Good shot.
- It's a health dish.
- Okay.
We did well.
- Okay, okay.
- We did well.
Why did he raise the bid?
Se Chan almost fell for it.
That's too bad.
Let's bid this time.
Why did he do that?
Suk Jin's dish looks like
a good one.
(It's Suk Jin and Ji Hyo's turn.)
- We should bid this time.
- I know.
It's about time we get a nice dish.
(She maintains a poker face
as she looks inside.)
- The bottom shelf must be full.
- Her eyes moved down.
- What could it be?
- The bottom shelf must be full.
- I know.
Ask us questions.
Say the color of the food
at the same time.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Brown.
- Beige.
Brown.
- Is it curry?
- Is it chicken?
- Curry?
- It could be chicken.
- Chicken.
- How many words are in the name?
- 1, 2, 3.
- 1 word.
(They say it in unison.)
- Chicken.
- Is it really chicken?
- I am not sure.
Gimbap?
- What?
- Gimbap.
Are you asking me if it's gimbap?
I think it's gimbap.
I'm just talking to myself.
(Why are you listening in?)
- I am talking to myself.
- But you spoke so loudly.
- You spoke so loudly.
I have a loud voice, okay?
Let's start bidding.
How much is the starting bid?
Shall we make it two dollars?
- 1.5 dollars?
- 1.5 dollars.
Let's start at 1.5 dollars.
They will make us spend money.
(What kind of food has
the starting bid of 1.5 dollars?)
(Hardtack)
I bet it's something tasty.
When they made the starting bid
1.5 dollars,
their eyes met.
- Ji Hyo was unwavering.
- Ji Hyo...
agreed with the price.
- We will bid 2 dollars.
- 2 dollars.
It's about time
we get something nice.
We will bid 2.5 dollars.
- 2.5 dollars.
- 2.8 dollars.
- 3 dollars.
- Stop.
- 3.2 dollars.
3.2 dollars.
- 3.5 dollars.
- 4 dollars.
- Four dollars?
- Let's wait.
Let's bid 4.5 dollars
and eat the dish.
No, no.
Let's wait.
The price might go up.
We will bid 4.5 dollars.
Five,
four,
- three,
- We will eat it.
two,
one.
- 4.5 dollars.
- 4.5 dollars?
- Really?
- Then how much are they in debt?
4.5 dollars is a hefty price.
They are in a lot of debt.
Then they will be
at the very bottom.
We have no hopes of winning.
- That's right.
- We will have a good meal.
We will have a good meal
before we go down.
- We will have a good meal.
They are in a lot of debt.
Then they will be
at the very bottom.
- Shall we join forces again and...
- Stay?
- Stay.
Would it be okay if we join forces?
That's a good idea.
Let's give them tasty food.
- Okay.
- What?
- Eat.
- It's 4.5 dollars.
You should eat tasty food.
- Hold on.
- You deserve to eat.
You should bid more money.
- You should eat tasty food.
- No, no.
- Stay.
- You can have it.
Why are you controlling them,
you punk?
- He is trying to back down.
- You can have it.
If you bid five dollars,
we might give up.
It's important to make them use
a lot of money.
- They used a lot of money.
- Let's make them use more.
- 5,
- If we spend 4.5 dollars on it...
- four,
- Let's just eat it.
- three,
- Doesn't anyone want to bid?
two...
- It must be something tasty.
- I know.
One.
Okay. Let's enjoy the food.
That's right. It will be nice
to eat tasty food.
It will fill us up.
(Hardtack)
Thank goodness we stayed!
(Thank goodness we stayed!)
Okay!
It was hardtack.
We did well by raising the bid.
- What is this?
- We did well by raising the bid.
You should have let another team
spend four dollars.
I thought someone would outbid us.
You should have let another team
spend four dollars.
I thought someone would bid
five dollars.
Suk Jin and I don't get along.
It's hard to make people spend
more than four dollars.
Hardtack is...
very filling.
If you drink water with it,
you will be full.
(Current Amount of Money)
- It's tasty.
- You got jjajangmyeon.
- I am full.
- Let's go.
(They are waiting inside the bus.)
Your song is nice.
(What?)
Shall we take a selfie together?
What?
I was taking a selfie.
- When I looked to the side...
- I was taking a selfie.
(A good angle)
Shall we take a selfie together?
(They are cute.)
(An unexpected selfie)
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
- Shall I send it to you?
- Sure.
How do I send it to you?
(I need her number
to receive the photo.)
(He gets ready to get her number.)
What?
Shall I share it via AirDrop?
(Shall I share it via AirDrop?)
How do I do it?
(Kids these days share photos
via AirDrop.)
That must be my phone.
I share photos this way.
(The old and the young
share a photo.)
Hold on tight. We will hit the road.
Se Chan is in good condition.
Yes.
Yuqi, where are you from?
- Beijing.
- Beijing?
- Yes, Beijing.
- She is from Beijing.
- I know the city well.
I visited it so many times.
I visited it as if it were my home.
- You mean Beijing?
- Yes.
- I see.
- One time,
Jong Kook got on the plane
by chance...
with other girl groups.
We were going to an event in China.
As soon as he got off,
his fans crowded the airport.
- His fans crowded the airport.
- He is a Korean Wave star.
- Seriously.
- "Jong Kook!"
They thought the same thing
would happen with Suk Jin,
so 20 bodyguards came for him.
They were as relaxed as ever.
They seemed confused.
- It was the easiest job.
That's right.
I told them to go back.
Seriously.
The bodyguarding agency goes wild
when Suk Jin is coming.
"I will take the job!"
- It's the easiest job.
- "The easiest job".
Mijoo, what will you do
from now on?
- Me?
- Yes.
Will you keep going that way?
Will you switch over
to the variety shows?
- You should.
I should.
Do you have a role model
in variety shows?
- Lee Hyo Lee.
- Lee Hyo Lee? I see.
- How about you, Doyeon?
Who is your role model?
I admire Lim Soo Jung.
- An actress.
- I see the resemblance.
She was in "Lump of Sugar".
- That's such an old movie.
"Lump of Sugar" came out ages ago.
- "Lump of Sugar".
- It's a really old movie.
Out of all the movies she was in...
I watched "Lump of Sugar".
How about you, Dong Jun?
Dong Jun is going into acting.
- He is going into acting.
- Acting.
My role model
is Jong Kook, of course.
- I want to bulk up.
- What are you saying?
- He wants a body like Jong Kook's.
- I guess you like to work out.
Do you want to own a gym?
- When I worked out a lot...
- Listen.
If Dong Jun has a nicer body
to go with that face,
he would look incredible.
Women don't like a man
whose body is too perfect.
- What?
- That's right.
- If his body is too bulky...
- You shouldn't enforce your idea.
I am serious.
You just touched a raw nerve.
- You...
- It's okay, Jong Kook.
- Don't tease him.
- He hates those words the most.
Jong Kook is a bit angry.
- He is proud of his body.
- All right.
All right. It's okay.
It's not wrong to think that.
Jong Kook got annoyed with So Min
for the first time in a long while.
How about you, Won Young?
I admire Jun Ji Hyun.
Oh, Jun Ji Hyun?
- She has that vibe.
- Ji Hyun.
- Are you close to her?
- What?
- Don't you know Jun Ji Hyun well?
Have you met her or not?
We once filmed a commercial
together.
- Which commercial was it?
- She must be the only one...
you can't call by her first name.
- What?
- You can't call her Ji Hyun, right?
No, I can't.
(He is sure of it.)
- Really?
- Really? I want to see that.
I can't speak casually to her.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I want to see that.
- I can't speak casually to her.
- I see.
- I can't do that with Jun Ji Hyun.
I can speak casually to Won Young,
but it's different with Jun Ji Hyun.
Kwang Soo, who is your role model?
- Isn't it Han Gi Beom?
- It must be Han Gi Beom.
- Han Gi Beom.
- I like him,
but he isn't my role model.
He is an athlete.
- How about an actor?
- Yao Ming!
(Yao Ming!)
Hey!
A basketball player.
Why would Yao Ming
be my role model?
Since he's very tall...
Why would Yao Ming
be my role model?
- Yao Ming.
- Your face reminds me...
of the Chinese version
of "Produce 101".
That trainee.
There is one trainee
who looks exactly like you.
There is one comment I remember.
What is it?
"I can't stand seeing someone
with Kwang Soo's face act cool."
(Kwang Soo can't argue with that.)
For goodness' sake.
I still refuse to believe
he is a different person.
- He is Kwang Soo.
- It's so funny.
How did you go back and forth?
What are you talking about?
- It was you.
When did you learn Chinese?
- What?
- You spoke Chinese like a native.
What are you talking about?
That trainee looked
exactly like you.
I think Doyeon is pretty happy
to be Se Chan's partner.
- Doyeon is.
- Me?
- Doyeon,
have you always been
a fan of Se Chan?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Why do you like him?
- We have...
- a similar sense of humor.
- Really?
- I guess you like it...
when comedians paint on their faces.
- How do you see him as a man?
- I am curious.
What do you think?
- My goodness.
- Did you just laugh?
She became so startled.
How would you rate my looks
from 1 to 10?
Why would you ask her that?
- Why would you ask her that?
- Your looks can't be rated...
from 1 to 10.
Why not? Why not?
- You need to go lower.
- There is one.
- We need negative numbers.
You can just pick a number.
Se Chan is a junior
I really cherish.
Overall, he is a good man.
He is really fine
when you see him from afar.
When you see him from 4km away...
- 4km?
- Seriously.
- That's ridiculous.
- Then he wouldn't be visible.
He is handsome when he wears a mask.
That's right.
He looks cool when he wears a mask.
Se Chan isn't half bad.
- That's right.
- He is fine.
- Se Chan isn't half bad.
- He is nice.
We are talking among ourselves.
None of the guests are agreeing.
- None of the guests are agreeing.
- Seriously.
(The guests stay silent.)
"That's right."
"He has nice looks."
You could have said that once.
We are talking among ourselves.
I saw everyone
look outside the window.
All the members are nice.
- That's right.
- Jong Kook is nice.
- All of us are kind.
- So Min too.
- All of us have a nice personality.
- Kwang Soo too.
They want us to come this way.
What is this?
I don't know. Is this soy milk?
- Is it flour?
Flour is good for the skin.
I think my skin will improve.
It's good for brightening the skin.
I am optimistic, right?
Why aren't the others coming?
It will be funny if we fall over.
- This is fun.
- You might fall backward.
If I were close to you,
I would have pushed you.
- You would have pushed me?
- Of course.
(They gather around one by one.)
My goodness.
- What's taking them so long?
- I know.
(What is going on all of a sudden?)
Ji Hyo is mischievous.
Come on.
(She couldn't help
but pull a prank.)
(She seems so excited
after pulling a prank.)
Okay. Okay.
Ji Hyo found someone
in her weight division today.
(The rest of the members enter.)
It's flour.
Oh, it's flour?
If we fry Kwang Soo in there,
he will look like a fried loach.
(If we fry Kwang Soo in there,
he will look like a fried loach.)
- Why would you fry me in there?
- He looks like a loach.
Se Chan will be fried catfish.
This is the last mission
for the prize money,
the Sinking Three-Legged Race.
What?
In each round of the tournament,
two couples will participate.
You will get the prize money
in accordance with the results.
In 100 seconds,
the couples will tie their feet...
and move as many balls
from the other team's area...
to their basket.
The team that moves more balls
will win...
and move on to the next round.
If you lose, it's over.
Yes. The prize money you receive
will reflect the results.
- The prize money.
- The winners will get more money...
since they can move on
to the next round.
So it's important
to avoid Jong Kook's team...
in the preliminaries.
I'm sorry, but are you talking
with your back to us?
- How could you do that?
- He refuses to go against them.
Are you talking
with your back to us?
The healthy couple is scary.
- For goodness' sake.
- This is the starch pool.
If you run fast,
it will feel like the ground.
If you stay still,
your feet will sink.
- Really?
- Yes.
So it's important to run fast.
It has nothing to do with strength.
We need to move fast.
Stop turning your back to us.
It has nothing to do with strength.
Soyou, stop hitting me
when you talk to me.
- Stand like this.
- Female members, take a pick.
The teams with the same number
will go against each other.
Number four will win by default.
(Current Amount of Money)
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo
versus Haha and Mijoo)
(So Min and Dong Jun
versus Jong Kook and Soyou)
- Please.
- We need to win.
It'll be good to pick number four
and win by default.
All right.
- Okay.
- What?
What is it?
(What is this?)
Make sure your feet
touch the ground.
You need to move fast.
- I can't move.
- Is it okay if you run fast?
- It's like the mudflat.
- I can't take my feet out.
She is good!
- It's like the mudflat.
- I can't take my feet out.
(Mijoo adjusts quickly.)
It's like the mudflat.
There you go.
- 1, 2, 1, 2.
- Keep moving. Don't rest.
(As soon as they stop,
starch pulls their feet.)
Don't rest.
We will start right away
when you stop moving.
Get ready.
(Haha and Mijoo
versus Suk Jin and Ji Hyo)
- 1, 2, 1, 2.
(You win by having more balls
in your basket after 100 seconds.)
- 1, 2, 1, 2.
Grab a lot of balls.
Let's go. Let's go.
Are you okay?
- What is going on?
- What?
For goodness' sake! Haha!
(Their feet got stuck
because they stopped briefly.)
You can get up!
This is ridiculous.
- It's over for them!
- What are we going to do?
It's over for them!
- What are they going to do?
- Is it that bad?
- They are done.
It looks that way.
(We should keep moving.)
Hold on.
- Is it that bad?
- Get going.
What is going on?
Suk Jin, give me a pull.
- I am stuck.
- 1, 2.
What a bunch of amateurs!
- Look at Haha.
Is it that bad? My goodness.
Is it that bad?
My goodness.
- Is it that bad?
- This is insane.
Let's take more balls.
- Come on.
- Where are you going?
It will be over if you fail
to put those balls in the basket.
- Good luck.
- This is hard.
(During the struggle,)
(an armed conflict occurs.)
How could you slap me?
Don't hit me!
They are the absolute worst.
Let's keep going.
- Ji Hyo is winning.
- Let's go.
- 1, 2.
- My goodness.
One.
(Which team put more balls
in the basket?)
(100 seconds are up.)
- This basket has more balls.
- Please come on out.
- Seriously.
- Gosh, how tiring.
- I am exhausted.
- Really?
- Seriously.
- Is it that bad?
I really can't move.
This team has nine balls.
This team has five balls.
Five balls.
Suk Jin's team will move on
to the next round.
Okay.
All right.
(So Min and Dong Jun
versus Jong Kook and Soyou)
My feet keep sinking.
(So Min takes tiny steps.)
This is no joke.
Okay! Never stop moving, Dong Jun.
Keep moving all the time.
Unbelievable.
This feels like a penalty.
- Look at how she walks.
- What?
Se Chan, can you keep
my glasses for me?
Jong Kook, it's not that hard.
- Look at how she walks.
- What?
(The two trainers
have adjusted perfectly.)
- Soyou, what's going on?
- Me too.
- You can walk like that?
- Really?
Oh, your feet keep sinking.
What's going on?
- Those two...
- Jong Kook.
- It's different from walking alone.
- Their strength is speed.
- Speed rather than energy.
- Our strength is speed.
Dong Jun is competitive too.
- Right.
- He's good.
- He's very fast too.
- He's very athletic.
- He's not an easy opponent.
- I feel bad...
that I'm his partner.
- No. I'm happy.
- I feel so bad.
You've never apologized to me once.
I'm already tired.
It's nothing once you get out.
Exactly.
He's so sweet.
After saying something,
- he gazes at the person.
- Right.
"I didn't do it."
(He copies Dong Jun.)
Right?
Dong Jun says something
and gazes at the person.
I learned something today.
That's what I learned as a kid.
I was told to look the person
in the eye.
That's why I feel so shy.
He keeps looking me in the eye.
- Seriously.
- I should do it too.
I think this couple is
too unrealistic,
but I really hope
those two will become a couple.
- For real?
- Yes, for real.
What about us?
All four of you, please stand up.
- Three.
- This is so uncomfortable.
- Two.
- This is...
- It must be hard.
- One.
- Are you ready?
- It's exhausting.
- 1, 2, 1, 2...
- My legs feel weak.
- They're good.
- We don't know who will win yet.
- Look at that.
- We don't know yet.
- They're neck-and-neck.
- They're both good.
- Both teams are good.
- What are they doing?
- What?
- What's going on?
- They're throwing all the balls?
- Is it okay?
- It's okay to remove all the balls.
But you can only throw them
from the middle.
That doesn't seem so smart.
You can pick them up on your way.
- That's not a good strategy.
- Hang in there.
- Oh, my.
- That's not a good strategy.
It takes too long.
We can do this.
- Pick these up.
- They can't pick them up.
- 1, 2...
- Oh, my.
(Now it's a head-on competition.)
(The gym master...)
(and the rising star
go head-to-head.)
- Dong Jun, you're doing great.
- Dong Jun!
- Oh, no!
- Oh, my.
(Jong Kook grabs Dong Jun.)
- My goodness.
- No!
Oh, my.
- It's over now.
- Oh, no.
That's it. Goodbye!
Goodbye!
Dong Jun, good job!
Good job.
So Min, aren't you tired?
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
(Speed can't beat energy.)
Is it over?
- Stay calm.
- You can do this!
It feels like I'm hugging
a telephone pole.
Jong Kook!
Hold on. Hey.
So Min is grabbing Jong Kook's neck.
(So Min counterattacks
by grabbing Jong Kook's neck.)
So Min is grabbing Jong Kook's neck.
- We don't know yet.
- So Min.
So Min, we don't know yet.
- Oh, my!
- This is getting so messy!
So Min looks like squid in batter.
It looks so messy.
(The squid counterattacks.)
Oh, my.
- My goodness.
- So Min, what are you doing?
So Min!
Is this the UFC?
- You're all covered in batter!
- Is this the UFC?
- Why are you dipping her in there?
- So Min...
- Is this how you play this game?
- She's blowing air into my ears.
Your hair...
- Do something about your hair!
- Dong Jun...
Soyou's hair looks like
deep-fried seaweed rolls.
- Soyou...
- Gosh.
(Deep-fried seaweed rolls and squid)
Oh, my.
(Time is up.)
- Let's do this.
- Unbelievable.
- Gosh.
- Are you okay?
Does it have to be this fierce?
- They have 17 balls.
- 17.
- What about the other team?
- They have seven.
Seven.
Jong Kook and Soyou win.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, my.
- Does my hair look okay?
- What is she going to do?
- It looks like a seaweed roll.
- It's covered in batter.
- What is this?
- Oh, my.
What is she going to do?
Soyou, will you be okay?
There's nothing I can do.
Oh, my cap is attached to my hair!
No. Your cap is over here.
That's not your cap.
- That's not your cap.
- That's your hair.
Don't try to take it off.
What is this then?
Soyou, your cap is here! Your cap...
Your cap is here.
(So Min digs up something
that's supposed to be Soyou's cap.)
Will you be able to use it again?
You can untie it. Give me a second.
- Do you want to wash your feet?
- This cap has been sponsored.
- It's a seaweed roll cap.
- Is that a cap?
Next up are
Team Suk Jin and Team Jong Kook.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo
versus Jong Kook and Soyou)
This round will be...
really messy.
I'm scared.
Team Suk Jin, if you make it
to the finals,
you can end up at the top.
- Right?
- If we make it to the finals?
Bo Pil, you're so mean.
- We don't know yet.
Suk Jin, we don't know yet.
- We don't know if they win.
- Jong Kook, don't feel sorry.
- We don't know what will happen.
- Please.
Who knows if he'll get stuck
in the starch?
Everyone...
Our strategy is...
Suk Jin is coming up
with a strategy.
A strategy?
- From here...
- I wonder what his strategy is.
I can't wait.
Do you know Mike Tyson's
famous quote?
"Everybody has a plan until
they get punched in the mouth."
(Everybody has a plan until
they get punched in the mouth.)
Everybody has a plan.
Until they get punched?
Hey, don't say that.
Is Suk Jin finally
getting punched today?
It's about time.
He should be brought to his senses.
- There is a good reason too.
- Of course. It's a game.
I'll keep what you said
deep inside my left chest.
Okay? Please understand
if I get aggressive.
Sure.
3, 2, 1.
Keep taking steps.
Gosh, why are they so fast?
They have surprisingly
good teamwork.
- I'm their fan.
- They're good at the game too.
- I'm a fan.
- Oh, my.
We don't know
which strategy works better.
- Right.
- Not yet.
- Oh, my.
- It's not easy.
- I'll focus.
- No.
- The balls are stuck.
- They're stuck.
Jong Kook's strategy works better.
Right. We should do that too.
They make it look so easy.
- I think it's over.
- This won't work. Give up.
- The balls are stuck.
- It's harder than it looks.
In the beginning...
They're guarding their balls.
The gate is locked now.
- It's locked.
(Locked)
(It's locked?)
It's locked.
- Unbelievable.
- Suk Jin is going to get punched.
(A shield that no spear can pierce)
(A dull spear
that can't even pierce tofu)
- Here we go!
- He's going to get punched!
- Suk Jin-Punching Show.
- He's going to get punched.
- Has it started?
- All right.
Suk Jin, it's time to...
Suk Jin, it's time to
carry out your strategy now!
But since there's Ji Hyo...
- You'll turn into a plaster figure.
- Ji Hyo, don't be so weak.
Don't be so weak!
What's with you?
- You should thank Ji Hyo.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Come on.
We should at least give it a try.
Here we go.
- Hold on. 1, 2, 1, 2.
- Gosh.
(The dull spear
and the muscular shield...)
(go head-to-head.)
Here we go.
(As soon as they start...)
- Oh, my.
- Here we go.
- Unbelievable.
- Is this professional wrestling?
Left, right.
Why did he have to compete
with Jong Kook?
- Oh, my.
- Jong Kook...
- Oh, no.
- He's being covered in batter.
- No!
- He's dipped in the batter.
- Oh, my.
He's being covered in batter.
(Flavorful)
- Please.
- Ji Hyo, stand up!
Stand up!
Stop!
(A starch man is born.)
Stand up!
Ji Hyo, stand up!
Stop! Stand up!
- Stop!
Hey, stand up!
- This is too sad.
- Stand up!
- This is sad.
Hold on. Give me a second.
- Hurry up and stand up!
- This is too sad.
(He got covered in batter without
a chance to show off his strength.)
- Stand up!
- This is too sad.
Hold on. Give me a second.
- Hurry up and stand up!
- Spare them!
Are you okay?
Gosh, I can't believe you.
(Ji Hyo is angry
at her incompetent partner.)
- Why are you doing this?
- I can't believe you.
Why are you doing this?
(The starch-covered fighter)
I'm fighting against our opponent!
You should stop Suk Jin!
Suk Jin, don't give up!
- Here we go again.
- Oh, my.
- Are they okay?
This will happen to
whoever makes it to the finals.
(Making everyone scared
of the finals, the game is over.)
- What?
- Suk Jin, are those your tears?
- Suk Jin is crying!
- Are those your tears?
Suk Jin!
- Is he crying? Are they tears?
- He's crying.
He's crying.
Here we go.
(The monstrous team
helps Ji Hyo and Suk Jin up.)
- Stand up.
- Okay.
You're amazing.
You fought so well.
Your strategy worked.
(Jong Kook and So You: 17,
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo: 9)
I'm impressed.
You weren't embarrassing.
- Seriously.
- You fought well.
- I admit it.
- You lost, but you fought well.
Guys, Jong Kook...
(Jong Kook...)
is impossible to beat. Just give up.
Suk Jin.
(Jae Suk and Yuqi compete
with Se Chan and Doyeon.)
(Jong Kook and Soyou)
(Jae Suk and Yuqi)
This round is going to be
interesting.
- I can't wait. It's a big match.
- This is going to be fun.
- It's going to be a dog fight.
- Yuqi...
- Let me tell you.
- Get in here.
I'll do my best,
but I won't go to the finals.
It's going to be so fun.
He'll do his best, but he won't...
- I won't go to the finals.
- He gives up.
- Do you understand?
- I think I do.
Soyou, do we go first?
It's starch
that's flowing down my face.
- So this is how it feels.
- It's going to be interesting.
I can't wait. It's a big match.
- You win by losing.
- It's going to be a dog fight.
It's going to be interesting.
I can't wait. It's a big match.
It's going to be a dog fight.
3, 2, 1.
- Let's go!
- 1, 2...
- 1, 2, 1, 2...
- How can you grab us already?
Already?
- If you fall, it's over.
- Let's wait just a minute.
- Just a minute.
- If you fall, it's over.
- Let's wait just a minute.
- Just a minute.
- Oh, my.
(Screaming)
(Jae Suk attacks first
using his teeth.)
- I didn't know...
- You better fall!
Let's go. 1, 2, 1, 2...
1, 2, 1, 2...
He kicked for real.
- He does that.
- He kicked for real.
They're taking all the balls.
- How...
- 1, 2, 1, 2...
- Slowly. 1, 2, 1, 2...
- Wait!
- 1, 2, 1, 2...
- His legs are so long.
His legs are long, so he's fast.
No!
(Usain Bolt running across
a pool of starch)
Please don't grab us.
Don't grab us!
(Yuqi squeezes in.)
- Yuqi is unbelievable too.
- Don't do this.
Don't do this.
Yuqi.
(While Yuqi blocks
Kwang Soo and Won Young...)
Kwang Soo's strategy...
(This time, Kwang Soo bites him.)
Did you hear that?
(Kwang Soo, a young man with strong
teeth, who's best at cheating.)
The prize money isn't worth
doing this over.
(Screaming)
(What's this noise?)
(He retaliates
with his front teeth.)
Do they have to go this far?
Don't do this.
What are you talking about?
- Where are you going?
- It will end like this then.
- It will end like this.
(Team Jae Suk will win if they get
rid of Team Kwang Soo's balls.)
It's over.
It looks like Team Jae Suk is
going to go to the finals.
Hey, Jae Suk.
If you do that,
you'll end up going to the finals.
Won Young. Grab him.
Yuqi, we can't go to the finals.
Hold on.
- Hold on.
- Yuqi.
You'll be in trouble
if you go up to the finals.
There's 1, 2.
We don't have to.
- Don't you have to take them out?
- Put it in their basket.
- In their basket?
- We can't go to the finals.
What is he saying?
He said they can't go to the finals.
Give it to me. I'll put them in.
We can't go to the finals.
If we go to the finals,
we're going to die.
Where are we supposed to put these?
Over there.
Wait, Kwang Soo.
I'm going to send them
to the finals.
(He blatantly puts all the balls
into Kwang Soo's side.)
Who knows? You could end up going.
(They're putting the balls
into one another's baskets.)
- This is hilarious.
- This is how it's going to be.
This is a game to avoid winning.
- You have to lose this game, right?
- Right.
(An unprecedented game to lose)
(Soaked)
- I know.
- I'm scared.
- We have to put it in.
- He looks so scary.
(The Starch Man thrashes about.)
Won Young is crying.
- Won Young is crying.
- He looks terrifying.
He looks so scary right now.
Where do we put the balls?
- My gosh.
- Over there.
Over there.
How many do we have?
(At this rate, Kwang Soo's team
will go to the finals.)
At this rate, Kwang Soo will win.
- Kwang Soo will win.
- We have a lot, but we must lose.
- Come here.
- 1.
- 1, 2.
Just put one in there
and take all of yours out.
(He suggests a strategy.)
You have 30 seconds left.
- Take it out.
- Take it out and go up.
- You look like a ghost.
- 1, 2.
One.
(Jae Suk and Yuqi are protecting
Kwang Soo's basket.)
Are they really playing to lose?
(If they empty Kwang Soo's basket,
Jae Suk's team will win.)
(This is the chance!)
Won Young, take them out!
It's nice that they're exhausted as
they're going up against us next.
- I'm exhausted.
- Don't take them out.
- No.
It hurts.
Don't take them out.
(Who will win this desperate battle
to fail to move on to the finals?)
- It hurts.
- Don't take them out.
- Here. It hurts.
- 10 seconds left.
Gosh, I'm confused.
Who's going to win?
Won Young!
- I'm working on it.
- I'll put one in.
Jae Suk is likely to win.
- I took them all out.
- How many do we have?
(The whistle sounds, and
the last ball leaves Yuqi's hand.)
There were so many balls in there.
I took them all out.
- I took them all out.
- How many do we have?
- We have to have something.
Jae Suk wins!
- Yoo Jae Suk's team wins.
- Darn it!
Let's go right away.
(They tried so hard to lose.)
- Why?
- No.
Why are we going to the finals?
Okay. Let's continue.
You've won.
Okay. Congratulations.
- It was a dramatic win.
- I can't do this.
I couldn't even laugh.
Kwang Soo was too... Gosh.
- Did you fart?
- No, I didn't.
Did you just fart?
No, I didn't. I swear.
- Kwang Soo.
- It wasn't me.
- I heard it.
- I didn't fart.
Why would you fart?
It was my foot.
Why would you fart in front of
idol singers?
Does that make sense?
- Where did the towel on my head go?
- Why would you fart?
It's because he's no longer
under pressure.
Sometimes you fart after being
under pressure. It's okay.
- Hey.
- It's because your legs are weak.
- This...
- Since it turned out this way,
- Move after releasing your legs.
- Yuqi, let's win in the finals.
(Hitting)
I told you to release your legs
before you moved.
(There was a collision accident
because Kwang Soo's legs are weak.)
- Goodness.
- Jae Suk is going to sleep well.
My goodness.
(It was a messy win,
just like everyone expected.)
This is a complete mess.
(He has no strength
to control his body.)
I guess Kwang Soo really
used up all his energy.
Let's go up, Kwang Soo.
3. 1, 2, 3.
(They move Kwang Soo,
who has no energy.)
- Oh, no.
- Move your legs.
No. You should try to get up.
Don't just lie there.
What do I have to do?
Get up.
Kwang Soo, get up.
- That's not easy.
- 1, 2, 3.
His hair is going to get
ripped out.
Be careful. He got hair plugs
in the back of his head.
Don't you get hair plugs
in the front of your head?
Why would you get hair plugs
in the back?
He got some hair from the front
and implanted them in the back.
Why would he do that?
He wanted to look cool.
- He wanted to do that.
- Really?
He wanted to be hip.
(He's full of coolness and hair
in the back of his head.)
- Kwang Soo.
- You have no energy.
It was another dirty game today.
(An exhausted water strider)
- Stay still.
- Oh, my. Come here.
- Goodness.
- My pants.
I got your pants.
- She grabbed them.
- Hey.
I'm sorry, Won Young.
I'm sorry, Won Young!
This is a line guys always say.
They say "I'm sorry"
after they drink.
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry."
- "I'm going to go."
- "I'm sorry I'm so pathetic."
Come get him.
Next time you're here,
- team up with Jong Kook.
- No, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
- Oh, my.
- He's insane.
(I want to be on your team
next time too.)
- I'm going.
- "I'm sorry I'm so pathetic."
Come and catch us if you can.
He looks like the ghost
in "Ju-on: The Grudge".
(As the ranks are changing...)
The results of this game
can change...
- the rankings significantly.
- Right.
We didn't put in a lot of balls
in the last round.
You have this round
to make up for it.
Do you think we stand a chance?
I'm just doing it because
I made it to the finals.
(This is so funny.)
My gosh, this is...
I didn't want to go up
into the final round.
I think I know what will happen.
I think I saw a preview of this.
I saw you getting stuck
in the starch.
3, 2, 1.
(The final round starts!)
They're off to a good start.
(The two teams cross the starch.
Who will win?)
Both teams are showing manners.
- They're throwing their balls out.
- They're emptying their baskets.
They're gathering them,
and they're throwing them out.
I don't think throwing them out
is a good strategy. We did that.
I think gathering is better too.
They're really good.
(They are picking up the balls
they threw out.)
(A sound of a fart)
(What?)
I didn't fart.
- Maybe Kwang Soo didn't fart.
- Hey.
- Yuqi.
- Was that fart?
I told you it wasn't me.
It came from Yuqi's direction.
- It really wasn't me.
- Yuqi.
- You must be healthy.
- It'll become the talk of the town.
(It's so much fun to tease her.)
But you shouldn't do this
to do that.
Yuqi's fart sounds healthy.
The sound is a bit...
- It was a healthy sound.
- This is better.
- They're neck and neck.
- Let's go.
- It's similar.
- I think Jae Suk...
I think Jae Suk's team is winning.
Who?
- Who's winning?
- Your team!
- We are?
- Yes.
Then we need to stick ourselves
into the starch.
What?
- Okay.
- Really?
They're going to do that?
- We're here.
- If you do that, you'll win.
- They're coming. Do it.
- They're coming.
- Do it!
- Here they come.
- Get yourselves in the starch.
- They're coming. Do it.
(We're going to open up
the locked door.)
- Lock yourselves in the starch!
- We have to get through.
The balls are coming out so quickly.
(They successfully take over
Jae Suk's basket upon arrival.)
This is the scene that I saw.
(This scene)
- Hey!
- It's over.
Is this how you're going to be?
He can't get up.
(He doesn't even get a chance
to pull Jong Kook in properly.)
He got sucked in.
(He ended up getting sucked in.)
- He got sucked in.
- Goodness.
- Oh, gosh!
- He got sucked in. It's over.
- Goodness.
- I'm sorry.
- It's over.
Just end it!
Don't do that.
You dirty guy!
- Hey!
- Okay!
It's done!
(As his last-ditch effort, he puts
his aggressive teeth into play.)
Just end it quickly.
Jae Suk's biting.
Don't bite me.
(I'm going to leave a mark
on your chest muscles.)
He's still biting him.
(Even if they try to rip off
their name tags in vain,)
(the pendulum of victory
has already been tilted.)
We did it.
I...
- This is like a penalty.
- Gosh.
Are you okay, Jae Suk?
- Are you okay?
- Goodness, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk is crying too.
- Oh, no.
- Jae Suk.
Gosh, that's too bad.
I feel so bad for him.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
- Jae Suk.
- "I'm sorry."
Was I like that too?
I'm sorry, Yuqi.
I just heard someone fart again.
Right?
I'm sorry you had to meet
such a pathetic senior.
I'm sorry, Yuqi.
Okay, everyone. Thanks to you,
an intense match occurred.
And the ranks have changed a lot.
As I told you before, the teams in
1st and 2nd place...
can use the prize money to purchase
the prize we prepared.
The team in last place
will get a penalty.
- What?
- I hope we're not in last place.
The penalty for the last place team
is for them to lie in here...
- while we make our closing remarks.
- That's easy.
They have to lie in there until
the end and get out by themselves.
- That's hard.
- After being in there for a while?
I see. That's hard.
The team that came
in last place is...
(The penalty is enjoying the
starch swamp during the ending.)
With a difference of 80 cents,
(Which team came in last place
with a difference of 80 cents?)
it's Kim Dong Jun and Jeon So Min.
- Yes!
(The last place team is
So Min and Dong Jun.)
(We're in trouble.)
- Oh, no.
- It was 80 cents?
That was the difference?
How much did we have?
7.30 dollars.
7 dollars?
If only you didn't get tteokbokki.
- That's true.
- If we didn't eat...
- We only played two games...
- Please go in.
I'm sorry, Dong Jun.
- I'm sorry, Dong Jun.
- "I'm sorry."
- It's all my fault.
- It's okay.
I'm sorry!
So Min, just imagine that
you're on a date.
- Gosh, I waited for this.
- This is like a scene from...
- "Love Letter". No, "Love story".
- You're right.
A scene from "Love Story".
It's like a field of snow.
In first place is
Kim Jong Kook and Soyou.
- Right.
- They got 62.10 dollars.
- What?
- 62.10 dollars?
- That's a lot.
- You guys are rich.
We're like Mansour.
The second place team can get
a prize,
but the third place team can't.
But the difference between
the 2 teams is 20 cents.
- 20 cents?
- It must be Yuqi and Jae Suk.
With 16.7 dollars,
this team is in 2nd place...
and can get a prize. It is...
(Who is the 2nd place team that beat
the 3rd place team by a hair?)
Jae Suk and Yuqi.
(Jae Suk and Yuqi came in 2nd place
with 16.70 dollars and get a prize.)
They got more money at the end
for going to the finals.
Okay!
Let's bring in the prizes.
- What is this?
- Summer blankets and sweet corn.
- Corn.
- This is nice.
They even have corn.
As a result, the 1st place team
can get all three of them.
And the team in second can pick
either summer bedding...
or sweet corn.
I want summer bedding.
- Summer bedding it is.
Dong Jun, how did you like it today?
I don't want to be rude,
but my head...
Go ahead and do it.
How can you talk to us
lying down like that?
He's lying down in a TV show.
I can't believe he's doing this.
Answer me.
Thank you for today, So Min.
Dong Jun, you did a good job.
We had a lot of fun.
(The money from the 10th anniversary
was donated to children's charity.)
(They get a call one day.)
(They have to find their youngest
sister who cut school.)
(Solar of MAMAMOO, Jessi)
(Lee Young Ji, Jeon So Mi)
(They are the younger sisters
who want to be idols.)
Are you sure it's her?
(They never get to know
who's the real sister.)
(The sisters are a little tough.)
(I said I'd go to
an Ivy League college!)
(But the sisters are doing
something else in their rooms.)
(There's only one way.)
(They should believe
their sisters...)
(or doubt them.)
This is a mess.
(They start to have doubts.)
(And they even
have family squabbles.)
(No matter whatever they do,)
(they are still family.)
(Family Search Race,
Unstoppable Sisters)