(One refreshing day
with a nice spring breeze)
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hi.
(Jae Suk is coming in.)
Did you soak your pants
in bleach or something?
- What's wrong with them?
- No.
You're not supposed
to put them in bleach.
What are you talking about?
You should let
experts take care of it.
(He starts the day
by teasing Kwang Soo.)
- Hello, Suk Jin.
- Hello.
I'm not wearing my microphone yet.
Okay.
- He's professional.
- He's not wearing a microphone.
- He's a pro.
- He wouldn't talk to us...
if it weren't for the show.
- He just sounded...
- I'm disappointed...
that you don't want to talk to us
without a microphone.
You could at least say hello to us.
I know. He could've said hello.
Why are you staring at me?
Look straight ahead.
What?
We didn't do anything, but our
viewers will be quite surprised.
I think so.
- Have a seat.
- Look at his face.
- He changes his face immediately.
- My gosh.
He was frowning over there.
But he's smiling
in front of cameras.
You're so... My gosh.
- Have a seat.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- You seem to have lost weight.
No, I gained weight.
- We have two extra seats.
- Why are there two seats?
- We have guests for today.
- Who are they?
- Jong Kook is not here yet.
- Where's Jong Kook?
What? Is Jong Kook bringing someone?
Jong Kook is not here yet.
- What?
- What about Jong Kook?
- Jong Kook is...
- Who is that?
Isn't that Hyosung?
- She's Hyosung.
- Hello.
- What?
- Welcome.
- She's Hyosung.
- Hello.
- What is she doing here?
Hello.
- Hyosung.
- Yes.
- A devoted daughter, Hyosung.
- Hello.
You're here again?
- What?
- Hello.
- A devoted daughter, Hyosung.
Have a seat.
- How have you been?
- Hello.
Did you come alone?
Mingyu is here too.
It's good to have him again.
- Mingyu came here alone.
- Right.
I see.
- Where's Jong Kook, by the way?
- Please have a seat.
- Why isn't Jong Kook here?
- There's no seat for Jong Kook.
- You're right.
- I bet he's doing something.
Today,
we are having Tiger Jong Kook's
Birthday Party Race.
- What?
- It's Jong Kook's birthday.
It's April 25.
How can you remember all that?
It must be tough.
That's what his assistant does.
- So he remembers it.
- I'm not his assistant.
- He should flatter Jong Kook.
- I'm not flattering him.
He even got a medical
checkup with In Sung.
Why would you talk about it?
- He's always like that.
- It's just for my health.
It's not flattery.
Did you carry around
his underwear there?
Why would I carry his underwear?
While he gets changed.
I changed my clothes too.
Why would I do that?
That's what he does all the time.
If you assist him like that,
does he pay for your checkup?
- He should pay for it.
- He does pay for it.
- But that's not why.
- So he paid.
In Sung works hard to make money.
Sure. It's not like
he gets money for free.
Do you get paid monthly or what?
I'm just curious.
You guys are so mean.
(You guys are so mean.)
He doesn't get paid.
They've ganged up on me.
Do you work 52 hours a week?
No, he's paid
on a case by case basis.
On a case by case basis?
What are you talking about?
What 52 hours?
Case by case.
- Case by case.
Why are you nodding your head?
Mingyu is cheering you up.
Mingyu wants you to cheer up.
It's been 10 minutes since I came,
and all I've heard is them
taunting you.
My gosh.
That's what we always do.
We haven't even started the day,
but I'm exhausted already.
It's good that you're paid.
All right. This Saturday,
April 25 is Jong Kook's birthday.
So we will give out special gifts
at the end of the day.
That sounds nice.
You will see a roulette
with 16 different items.
It has 12 gifts that Jong Kook
will pick and 4 duds.
Jong Kook will spin
the roulette at the end...
and take the item he picks
as a birthday gift.
And one of you will pay...
for the gift with your own card.
(One of the members except for
Jong Kook will pay for the gift.)
My goodness.
Things have been quite
expensive lately.
I didn't give you my bank card.
You will be paying after the race.
- Can I make a transfer instead?
- One of you will have...
an honor to pay for the gift.
- My gosh.
- It's an honor.
And we will decide
who will pay with the Running Ball.
We have balls with each
of your names on it...
including Jong Kook's
in the machine.
If you complete a mission
hidden in each round,
you can add Running Balls
with the names of members you want.
(Those who complete hidden missions
in each round can add the balls.)
I don't get rid of my name,
but I can add someone else's.
It means you guys should complete
missions without Jong Kook knowing.
And if you succeed,
you can add someone else's name.
I see.
What if we get caught by Jong Kook?
If Jong Kook finds out about
your hidden missions at the end,
he will get more chances
to spin the roulette.
No.
And it means you will
have to pay for more gifts.
So it's important not to get caught.
- I see.
- I will give you the missions...
you need to carry out today.
- What's this?
- They are all the same.
(Ask Jong Kook where he is
and make him say "Here I am".)
(Make Jong Kook call your name.
Talk using Chinese idioms.)
(Link your arms with Jong Kook.
Put a sticker on Jong Kook's body.)
- All right.
- During the entire show,
just like last week,
ask him "Where is Jong Kook?
And if he answers "Here",
five balls excluding the person
who asked will be added.
Let me try.
(Where's Jong Kook?)
(Here I am.)
(It's the answer
that only Jin Young can hear.)
- He'd never answer if we ask him.
- He would never answer us.
He might say that if Hyosung asks.
- Right. It's advantageous to you.
- Yes!
- "Here I am."
- Ask him to say that.
- You can try this mission...
anytime today.
During the opening, you should
make him call your name.
- Okay.
- You can add as many names...
- as he calls your name.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook...
- That won't work.
Make him call my name?
He never calls Se Chan, Kwang Soo,
and me by our names.
- How does he call you?
- "Hey, you."
(Hey, you.)
- Hey.
- You idiot.
(You idiot.)
You punk.
Every time he says that,
I look at him.
I just look at him
when he calls the three of us.
(He responds quickly
to the personal pronouns.)
I look at him
when he makes this sound.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
And for the first mission,
you should use
Chinese idioms as you talk.
We will count the number of times
you say it.
- I say it?
- Can I say the same idioms again?
- No, you can't.
- Only once?
- So I should say it first.
- If you say it wrong...
or more than twice,
it doesn't count.
What if we say it wrong?
Does it have to suit
the circumstances?
What about hyeongseoljigong?
Please count it
if it's close enough.
I might want
to say it wrong for fun.
I'll say hyeongseoljigong.
It's mine.
Hyeongseoljigong is mine.
- Okay?
- Wait.
This is just like hyeongseoljigong.
I'll say cheongomabi.
The second mission is to link
your arms with Jong Kook.
For the last mission,
you need to put a sticker on
Jong Kook without him knowing.
- We will definitely get caught.
- That's risky.
If he finds out one of these,
we won't be able to do anything.
Right.
Let's not try the sticker thing
at the beginning.
It's only for the third mission.
It says the third mission here.
- One for the first mission.
- What are you doing?
For the second mission...
- I get it.
- I thought a ghost was talking.
- There are three missions.
- I knew it.
You should send him
the script in advance.
- Okay?
- We're doing it in order.
I want you to act like you just met.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's get it.
This isn't the opening.
It's a secret opening.
There's no way he will call my name
during the opening.
Where's Jong Kook?
Here I am.
Here you are.
If I say hello to him, he'll say...
"Hey, you rascal."
He's here. Hello, Jong Kook.
Hello.
The season of shorts is back.
- It's a little early though.
- Hello.
He's not wearing white today.
Are you wearing shorts already?
- These days...
- You try to spruce up these days.
- He's been wearing bright colors.
- Do you not wear shorts?
It's a little chilly this week.
- It's warm today though.
- It rained yesterday.
It will be cold today...
- because it rained yesterday.
- Really?
(Nervous)
I should buy something like this.
- This one is good.
- It looks nice.
You know what, Jong Kook?
You said "here" and it became
the talk of the town.
Gosh, it's nothing.
- It's just...
- Where's Jong Kook?
(He tries the mission carefully
pretending to have a conversation.)
- You should answer us too.
- Right.
(He tries to steal the mission.)
(Ji Hyo tries to steal it too.)
Where's Jong Kook?
Don't be silly, guys.
Why aren't you saying that to us?
We prepared something for today.
- What is it?
- What did they prepare?
- My gosh.
Oh no. It's for Jong Kook.
My gosh.
(It's a birthday cake
for Jong Kook.)
Oh no. It's for Jong Kook.
Don't do things like that.
Happy birthday to you
(Happy birthday, Jong Kook.)
My gosh.
He finds it really embarrassing.
Come here.
(Jong Kook is very shy.)
Gosh, I hate it.
- I hate it so much.
- We have to do this.
- I hate it.
- You have no choice.
I hate it!
- Seriously.
- It's for the show.
- I hate it.
- Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday
- Yes!
- Hey!
Why couldn't you wait
for us to count to three?
- I hate it.
- Look at his clothes.
I hate it when people sing
"Happy Birthday" for me.
What's worse, look at his hands.
- He's doing this.
- What?
(The figure is making hearts
with his hands.)
Birthday cakes and hand hearts
are the two things I hate the most.
In addition to that...
- Where is Jong Kook?
(And this?)
(While Jong Kook is embarrassed, Jae
Seok asks, "Where is Jong Kook?")
(Please, Jong Kook.)
(Will he answer this time?)
I'm here. I'm right here.
(I'm here. I'm right here.)
Happy birthday, Jong Kook.
Stop it.
- We don't have to celebrate.
- He's wearing shorts and leggings.
(Everyone except Jae Suk gets
5 Running Balls.)
- Happy birthday.
- My goodness.
To celebrate Jong Kook's birthday,
we're having Tiger Jong Kook's
Birthday Party Race.
- Today's guests are his favorites.
- Really?
- Unbelievable.
- Hello.
Mingyu.
Hello.
- Nice to see you.
- Hyosung, the good daughter.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Nice to see you.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Where should I stand?
- Mingyu is so handsome.
- Right.
- He is.
- Thank you.
- He reminds me of some celebrities.
- He does.
Kangta, for example.
- Choi Si Won too.
- That's right.
He reminds me of them.
He has well-defined features.
- Doesn't he look like them?
- Yes.
He has the perfect
SM Entertainment face.
- The "SM Entertainment face"?
- He has the SM face.
- Definitely.
What about Se Chan?
- Which agency likes his face?
- Which agency?
Is there any agency at all?
- I know.
- Which one?
Oyang Seafood.
- Okay.
- Oyang Seafood.
- Oyang Seafood?
Mingyu has something in common...
- with Jong Kook.
- That's right.
- They're both from Anyang.
- He's from Anyang too.
- What's Jong Kook's status there?
- Are there any rumors?
What rumors?
- I doubt he's heard anything.
- No?
(Jong Kook says Mingyu's name,
which is the hidden mission.)
- You haven't heard anything?
- He was a legend 10 years ago.
- 10 years ago?
I heard there's a statue of him
next to the statue of...
Admiral Yi Sun Sin
at Anyang Elementary School.
It looks like this.
The statue is doing this.
But the Anyang community is
very close-knit.
- We benefit from it a lot.
- The "Anyang community"?
Whenever I win an award,
- they put up...
- They put up banners?
- banners at the intersection.
- Right.
Your neighbors put up
a banner for you too.
They did? What does it say?
That you got a health check-up
with In Sung.
What are you talking about?
(Lee Kwang Soo Accompanies
Zo In Sung to His Health Check-Up)
Why would they put up such a banner?
Kwang Soo is running.
It's big news.
You escorted In Sung
to his health check-up?
It's definitely worth
putting up a banner.
They didn't put it up?
Why would they?
You're being ridiculous.
Why are you dressed...
like a moron today?
A "moron"?
- Hey.
- Hold on.
How could you say that?
- No one has ever called me that.
- What's with you today?
Did you dip your jeans
in bleach or something?
I'm dressed like a moron today?
- A moron?
- Unbelievable.
(Today's star is feeling happy
after teasing Kwang Soo.)
Today, we're having...
Tiger Jong Kook's
Birthday Party Race.
At the end of the race, Jong Kook
will win a gift he picks...
- by spinning a roulette wheel.
- Me?
- Only him?
- Here's the thing.
The roulette wheel has...
12 slots filled with
gifts Jong Kook want...
and four slots that are duds.
What? Gosh.
For the missions,
you'll divide into 3 teams of 3.
If Jong Kook's team wins, one
dud slot will be filled with a gift.
If his team finishes at the bottom,
a gift will be replaced with a dud.
- We should win.
- What if we come in second place?
If another team wins,
they can add their team sticker
on a gift they want.
If Jong Kook spins
the roulette wheel...
and happens to pick that gift,
the gift goes to the team
that added the sticker.
- Jong Kook, here's a list...
- Yes?
- of gifts you can choose from.
- I can see it?
There are many nice things
these days.
- You're right.
- What should I choose?
Choose a sofa.
- A sofa?
- A sofa would be nice.
I got a sofa
from Kwang Soo's father's company.
(Jong Kook says Kwang Soo's name.)
- I got it for free.
- Really?
I didn't pay for it.
Please thank him for me again.
Okay.
- Thank you. I really like it.
- You're welcome.
Do you have a dryer?
What's that?
- A clothes dryer.
- It's really useful.
- It'll give you a new life.
- At home...
- It uses too much electricity.
- No, it doesn't.
- Gosh.
- It doesn't.
What about soccer socks?
I have a ton of them at home.
- Soccer socks are a bit...
- Suk Jin is being so petty.
Why would you choose soccer socks?
(One of them has to pay for the gift
with his or her own card.)
Things have been quite
expensive lately.
What about tanning oil?
I have a lot.
Why would I choose that?
- Choose a coffee machine.
- I have one at home.
Just choose it.
- I don't use it a lot.
- Choose workout clothes.
Wouldn't workout clothes be nice?
I already have a lot.
Don't choose anything then.
(Jae Suk explodes.)
Leave him alone.
(Who cares if it's your birthday.)
Why do you say no to everything?
Will you take this
a bit more seriously?
My goodness.
How does a gym equipment
voucher sound?
- That sounds good.
- A gym equipment voucher.
- Please write them down.
- Gym equipment sounds nice.
- He has to choose six, right?
- Yes.
Pick 6 gifts, and fill 2 slots
with each of them.
A clothes dryer is really nice.
It's too expensive.
Why are you doing this?
It's not like you're paying for it
anyway.
- What's with you?
- What do you care?
Still, SBS should save money.
Since when do you worry about that?
If you want SBS to save money,
go home.
- Jae Suk.
- Go home.
- We'll put you on the phone.
- That sounds good.
Let's just talk on the phone.
A clothes dryer costs
at least 1,200 to 1,300 dollars.
- My goodness.
- It's way too expensive.
- A laptop is expensive too.
- That's hilarious.
Since this is Tiger Jong Kook's
Birthday Party Race,
Jong Kook gets to decide teams.
- That's unfair.
- Really?
- Is that okay?
- In a moment,
we'll go up to the gym
on the 17th floor.
- What?
- Is there a gym?
While Jong Kook is outside,
the rest of you will put
a number assigned to you...
on the equipment
you think Jong Kook likes.
- I know it exactly.
- Me too.
I have no idea.
Jong Kook will pick
his two teammates...
by choosing two numbers
on the equipment.
Kwang Soo, Haha, and I have to know.
But here's the thing.
It might not be such a good idea
to team up with Jong Kook.
- Why not?
- If Jong Kook's team wins a gift,
it goes to Jong Kook.
If another team wins a gift,
it'll go to one of them.
- There's no point in winning.
- Right.
Just think of it
as you're giving me a gift.
And who knows if Jong Kook will
give away the gift to a teammate?
- You never know.
- That's right.
You know what I'm like.
I'll definitely give it away.
Do you think I'll accept it?
- I'll give it away.
- All right.
- Let's go up to the 17th floor.
- Okay.
Get your bags.
Let's go.
- Thanks, Se Chan.
- Here you go.
Thank you.
- He said my name.
- What?
- He did?
He just said my name.
I'm sure it was caught on camera.
- What's this place? I had no idea.
- It looks very nice.
There's some gym equipment I prefer,
but when I go in,
I'll try everything out anyway.
If I find something...
- And then you'll make a choice.
- that works really well,
I might choose that equipment
instead.
Each of you has to choose
a different piece of equipment.
- Who goes first?
- You can all start now.
- All at the same time?
This is...
Hello.
- Hello.
- Give them to me.
The gym looks nice.
- Hello.
- Three.
- In order.
- How many do we get?
- The equipment looks very nice.
- This is not it.
This is definitely not it.
Chest? Shoulders?
He's never going to choose
a treadmill.
This is it.
(Kwang Soo has worked out
with Jong Kook a lot.)
- The leg press?
- Yes.
It's Jong Kook's favorite.
- It's for the legs?
- I put my number on it.
Gosh, I wanted this.
- Who's number four?
- I'm sure. It's me.
I wanted to choose this too.
- I'm confident.
- He might choose a treadmill.
For your information, Jong Kook
trained his upper body yesterday.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Hyosung can't tell the different
kinds of equipment apart.)
Where do I put my number?
- Would he choose the bench press?
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- This is it.
- He definitely likes it.
- This...
- The Smith machine?
(Haha picks the Smith machine.)
- The arms and shoulders...
- Have a seat.
Would he choose this?
- The Smith machine?
- This?
- Okay.
- The leg curl.
I choose this.
He might choose this.
He likes leg exercises.
He's still outside, right?
You sounded so awkward
in the elevator.
- Does Jong Kook do cardio?
- It's Hyosung's fault.
- Hyosung made it so obvious.
- What?
You want to be aggressive?
I watched the show yesterday,
- and "I'm here" was hilarious.
- Gosh, it's embarrassing.
If I say, "Where is Jong Kook?"
will you answer me?
Where is Jong Kook?
Please stop.
(Is this how she's going to play?)
- She's determined.
- I can't believe her.
- Where is Jong Kook?
- Hold on.
- Say it for me.
- Why are you doing this?
- Where is Jong Kook?
Guys.
If we don't play this right,
we all lose.
We should be careful
in the beginning.
If we win,
we get to add a sticker, right?
- Yes.
- That's right.
- We should try to win.
- In that sense,
it's better not to team up
with Jong Kook...
- to win a gift.
- But someone has to.
"Someone has to"?
Someone has to.
- Hold on.
- It's better not to.
Then I'll choose something
he's not going to choose.
It's better not to team up with him.
- He might not give the gift away.
- I think I'll choose that one.
I know he's definitely going to
choose this.
You should choose it.
- I chose that one over there.
- This stands out too much.
I know he's never going to choose
a gym ball.
- I can choose this, right?
- Of course.
Then I'll choose this.
(They're suddenly trying
not to be chosen by Jong Kook.)
(Se Chan chooses
a small medicine ball.)
You have only one minute left.
(Kwang Soo chooses a latex band
used for Pilates.)
(Which 2 pieces of equipment
will Jong Kook choose?)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Welcome, Jong Kook.
- It's good to see you.
Jong Kook, hi.
Please take a look around.
It's nice.
Here's the inverted machine.
- Do you like that?
- Someone stuck a sticker on that.
I thought you liked that.
I do.
That's for the shoulders.
- The back machine.
- Oh, yes. My goodness.
You love this one, don't you?
I should try the ones
with the stickers on them.
Go ahead.
Jong Kook, how's the taste?
- How delicious!
- What does it taste like?
- Jong Kook?
- How tasty!
Is it that good?
This is Homecook Mr. Back.
Homecook Mr. Back.
It provides Jong Kook's back
with all the right nutrients.
It'd be incredible
with some soy sauce.
My gosh.
Then...
- No way.
- This one.
Are you choosing this one?
- This...
- It tastes incredible.
- That's it.
- How tasty.
Jong Kook's first choice
is equipment number eight.
- Number eight.
- Who chose that one?
Number eight, okay.
- Number 8.
Jong Kook, here's another one
that works the lat muscles.
(It's another machine for the lats.)
- He's loving it.
- I love this one.
- This one's nice.
- This one?
It has a lot of features.
How does this work?
There's one of these in every gym.
Shouldn't you sit down?
You can stand if you want.
- If you do it while standing...
- How tasty.
Your muscles
are like hyeongseoljigong.
(Out of the blue)
(Saying a Chinese idiom
is for mission number 1.)
(We haven't begun
mission number one yet.)
- Why?
- Hyeongseoljigong?
- Seriously?
- Does it not make sense?
- Don't push it.
- How delicious.
Is it that good?
There's a gym ball here.
Where?
A gym ball.
A gym ball?
This...
Who would use a gym ball?
(Who would use a gym ball?)
(The cameraman was hit
by the bouncing gym ball.)
Are you all right?
- Are you all right?
- Hold on.
I saw you lose your balance.
He was hit in the back of his head.
The ball got him twice.
Whoever placed a sticker on there
wasn't taking this seriously.
Don't you find it appalling that
someone would put a sticker there?
- This...
- Right?
Just think about it.
Whoever this is
didn't want to be on my team.
Just look.
The ball is the smaller one too.
- That's...
- I find this disgraceful.
Right? That's someone being cheeky.
It sure is.
- I agree.
- Right?
Jong Kook, you want to see
who the cheekiest is?
What do you think about this?
Isn't this despicable?
- But that...
- This,
- this, and the gym ball.
- The gym ball.
Bring that over here.
- The problematic trio.
- The despicable three.
They clearly didn't want
to be on your team.
- You're right.
- Right?
They must've been chosen
by those who know me well.
- They're all awful choices.
- They know what I hate.
You must catch
the three who chose these.
- My gosh.
- The rubber equipment.
- You must sniff them out.
- Right.
- How funny.
- They must be caught.
(Jong Kook hasn't been
this serious before.)
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Think about the rule of this game.
- Why are you speaking up?
- What?
You must be one of them.
You must've chosen 1 out of these 3.
You're better off choosing
the equipment you like.
- He must've chosen one of them.
- Right?
Whoever chose the resistance band
is more despicable.
- Why?
- Do you work out with that?
What's wrong with a resistance band?
(Why?)
What?
I mean...
I'm sure Jong Kook stretches.
Would Jong Kook work out
with a resistance band?
- You saw me using this?
- That's far-fetched.
This lame thing?
(He's close to arresting
rubber offender number 2.)
The ball is used
to work your back at least.
Exactly. I have no business
using a resistance band.
- It can be used for other things.
- Like what?
Like this. It can be used this way.
- Is that so?
- That's one of the functions.
To be honest though,
what I find most
despicable and shady...
is the fact that someone chose
this lighter ball.
- Right.
- Why?
That choice seems shady to you?
Imagine the thought process
behind that.
Jong Kook must be in shock.
What was the intention behind it?
Is that so?
- Really?
- Look at his expression.
- Is that how it is?
- No way.
By that rat?
(That rat chose this ball?)
- I wonder why.
- That's not it.
- But...
- I agree.
It truly is despicable.
- That rat?
- Just think about it.
That's why this rat chose this ball?
Whoever it is...
- But...
- Let me say one more thing.
- This is bad.
- The number was facing the back,
but I turned it around
for you to see.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
(And like that...)
Okay, all right.
- Then...
- Yes.
I choose this one.
You chose numbers 2 and 8.
(Jong Kook chooses number 2 and 8.)
Joining Team Jong Kook
is Se Chan who chose...
the medicine ball.
- Unbelievable.
- I chose that...
because I foresaw this.
- I doubt it.
- How cool is this, right?
I knew you'd choose
one you like and one you hate.
It wasn't easy
choosing the right one.
Jong Kook's second teammate...
is Mingyu.
(Mingyu from Anyang
joins Team Jong Kook.)
Was it you, Mingyu? Gosh.
- How sweet of him.
- You chose a good one.
The others must be
split into teams too,
so how will you do this?
Hyosung and Ji Hyo
can choose their teams.
Play rock-paper-scissors
to choose members.
(The teams:
Jong Kook, Se Chan, Mingyu)
(Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, Hyosung)
(Suk Jin, Haha, Ji Hyo)
- We should stand in our teams.
- Right.
Are you happy with your teams?
- Yes.
- It's perfect.
- Let's do this.
- Let's win today.
- It's too annoying to let him win.
- Exactly.
- The others...
- Hold on a second.
Haha and Suk Jin...
are enthusiastic about today's game,
- but Ji Hyo is silent.
- Where's your enthusiasm?
Better luck next week then.
- Take a pass on this week.
- Right.
We always have
next week to look forward to.
Of course.
This next mission
is perfect for Jong Kook...
since he's a man with keen insight.
The game is called
Do You See What I'm Eating?
(Round 1:
Do You See What I'm Eating?)
- I see it.
- Sound must be involved.
One team will sit behind
a divider...
and will get three minutes each...
to eat the chosen dish.
The other teams will win a point...
if they guess what dish is it
without smelling it.
So we have to rely
on our eyes and the sound.
Two teams will get to guess
what the dish is.
The team eating the dish
will win a point...
if the other teams...
don't manage to guess right
during those three minutes.
(That's how the team eating
can win a point.)
- Okay.
- Got it.
- What a hyeongseoljigong situation.
- Yes.
(Jae Suk fit in hyeongseoljigong
within his conversation.)
(Hidden mission)
(Talk using Chinese idioms.)
(It must be correct
and only used once.)
(Jae Suk successfully
squeezes in a Chinese idiom.)
Hyeongseoljigong is mine, you know.
That's my catchphrase from now on.
- Hyeongseoljigong.
- Gosh.
What was that idiom
with the black and...
- Geunmukjaheuk?
- What...
Geunmukjaheuk?
I was clueless, wasn't I?
Right, geunmukjaheuk.
What does geunmukjaheuk mean?
It means you turn black too...
if you dive yourself
into black colors.
So it's not something good.
You "geunmukjadeuk".
(Geunmukjadeuk?)
- Unbelievable.
- It's "heuk" not deuk.
- It's geunmukjaheuk.
- Deuk?
You got confused with jaupjadeuk.
- Right, jaupjadeuk.
- Jaupjadeuk.
It's confusing.
- How beeilbeejae.
- How iljamusik.
Iltassangpi.
(This one doesn't count.)
- Team Jae Suk will go first.
- Sure.
Okay.
(Team Jae Suk
randomly chose a dish.)
- Unbelievable.
- It'll be easy to guess.
This is too small for my nose.
Hey, it's Inspector Gadget.
Go, go, Gadget Arms.
Here comes the food.
My gosh.
Do you think
we can guess this right?
(They can only rely
on what they hear.)
- No way.
- This will be too obvious.
We need to duck while eating.
Ready, set, go.
(They eat the first dish.)
Go.
(The viewers at home
should try and guess too.)
- Wait, that...
- Unbelievable.
(They all prick up their ears.)
He took a bite.
(They keep hearing crunchy sounds.)
What could be that crunchy?
It's young radish kimchi.
(Whispering)
- I'm sure of it.
- What could be that crunchy?
You should be trying to mask
what we're eating.
Don't just enjoy the dish.
We're not trying
to make it sound delicious.
- I think you're right.
- Right?
- Yes, what you said.
- Go ahead then.
- Young radish kimchi.
- Don't make it sound delicious.
(Young radish kimchi?)
- Shall we make a guess?
- I'm sure of it.
Let's do it. Say what you told us.
Let me answer!
Young radish kimchi.
(Team Jong Kook guesses
young radish kimchi.)
(The first dish sounded crunchy
when Jae Suk ate it.)
(Is it young radish kimchi?)
(That is incorrect.)
- That's not it?
- It must be something similar.
- Jae Suk knows what he's doing.
- Exactly.
Anyway, Jae Suk's done.
I'm worried.
- Let's see how Hyosung does.
- Hyosung, go ahead.
(Hyosung takes a bite
out of the dish too.)
It could have a different name.
- It's a fritter.
- Yes, I agree.
- Right?
- It's a fritter.
- A fritter.
- Deep-fried crab?
It doesn't have an easy name.
(Just then,)
(they hear a clear crunchy sound.)
- I'm sure it's a fritter.
- She took a bite.
How about deep-fried shrimp?
(He's not sure.)
- Let's answer.
- Let's do this.
- Let me answer.
- Deep-fried shrimp.
(Team Suk Jin
thinks it's deep-fried shrimp.)
(That is incorrect.)
Isn't it a fritter?
(She makes sure it looks crunchy.)
- She's not making a mess.
- Good job, Hyosung.
It's our turn to guess now.
- You have 20 seconds.
- Got it.
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo...
(Banging)
(Thudding)
(Bumping)
(The additional noise
of the plate thumping)
Don't tap on the table.
You shouldn't touch the plate.
I know he's my teammate,
but he sure plays dirty.
(The dirtiest player ever
does his very best.)
- So...
- From what I can tell,
he's only eating...
the surrounding pieces
and not what's in the center.
He's not touching
those that give off a crunchy sound.
It has to be a dish...
that gives off a lot of noise
when you eat it.
- Crunchy...
- I love this dish.
- Isn't it salty?
- Hold on.
I saw bits of cucumber.
(Kwang Soo made the mistake
of showing what he's eating.)
- Cucumber?
- I saw something white.
I saw something
when he opened his mouth.
It's white.
(They saw something white
in his mouth. What is it?)
- Cucumber?
- Yes.
- That's not a dish.
- One.
Pickled cucumber.
(Team Jong Kook's answer:
pickled cucumber)
(Incorrect)
It'd be a shame
if you don't get it.
Tonkatsu
- Let's go with tonkatsu.
- 1, 2, 3.
- I don't think so.
- Tonkatsu.
(Team Suk Jin's answer:
tonkatsu)
(Is tonkatsu correct?)
(Incorrect)
- Okay!
- That's not what I heard.
Okay!
- What was it?
- What is it?
It was fried dumplings.
Fried dumplings.
See? It was something fried.
That was so hot.
(Crunchy fried dumplings ASMR)
It could have a different name.
I didn't hear it.
It's crunchy around the border
and soft in the center.
- That's what I thought.
- You were right.
That's what made it tough.
(Team Suk Jin is next.)
(What will they get to eat?)
All right.
Who knows why
Suk Jin is sitting over here?
- He wants to eat.
- He's hungry.
Correct. He wants to eat.
- I might not get to eat at the end.
- That's right.
- Suk Jin can't hide it.
- No, he can't.
He can't be on an eating show
because he's a picky eater.
Oh, my. I'm a meticulous person,
so it won't be easy.
(Boasting)
Nobody is listening.
It's okay. I can talk to myself.
It's okay.
You live alone. It's all right.
Keep going. It's okay.
- Are you really okay?
- I talk to myself frequently.
It's okay.
I talk to myself at home too.
It's sadder because he pretends
he's cool about it.
It's okay.
Don't show it.
I hope we get it
as soon as he takes a bite.
That's not possible.
This is... What is this?
Suk Jin, I'll guess
as soon as you take one bite.
Ready, set, go.
(What will they get to eat?)
- Just start.
- This is overwhelming.
(He's careful.)
- It's guksu.
- It's noodles.
Right?
(It's guksu. It's noodles.)
(They guess on his first bite.)
Oh, gosh.
Gosh, Suk Jin.
It's guksu for sure.
(He tries to make up for it
with his poor acting.)
He won't be able to do an
eating show on Ji Suk Jin World.
(Ji Suk Jin World can't be
an eating show.)
He was reviewing cars last time.
(You must be a subscriber.)
- You must be a subscriber.
- Yes.
(Kim Jong Kook,
1 of 72.5 thousand subscribers)
That's great.
I want to see how far he gets.
Do you watch him?
I guess he really likes Suk Jin.
He doesn't know a thing about cars,
but he was doing a review on them.
You start as a hater
and become a fan.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
You realize what's on their heart.
Great strategy.
Give a hint to your subscriber.
(He doesn't give preference,
but he's giving out hints.)
- It's udon.
- Udon.
- Let me answer. Udon.
(Team Jae Suk's answer: udon)
That's too bad.
It's a type of noodle.
Kimchi guksu or janchi guksu.
Janchi guksu is a good guess.
Should we go with that?
(Black shell?)
- Be careful.
- Hey.
I see a clam.
- Suk Jin.
I don't think that's good.
- Hold back. We have to win.
- Suk Jin.
- It's a clam, right?
- Kalguksu.
- Kalguksu with Manila clams.
- It's clam.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Kalguksu with Manila clams.
(Team Jong Kook's answer:
Kalguksu with Manila clams)
(Incorrect)
- He's not chewing on the clam.
- He's not.
- He made the sound on purpose.
- You can suck it.
If you're done,
the next person can start.
(It's Haha's turn.)
Watch him carefully.
Dong Hoon will savor the food.
Okay.
I'm going to eat now.
(This is the standard
eating show ASMR.)
- It's hot.
- He's good at this.
(This is the standard
eating show ASMR.)
(Haha's ASMR, live streaming)
(That looks good.
What are you eating?)
I'm sure it's noodles.
This is so hard.
(Slurping)
I'm getting hungry now. What is it?
(Swallowing)
What's that? It sounds so good.
Is it hot? What's the matter?
- What is it?
- He's good. He's good at ASMR.
(So this is how you do it.)
Are you eating the plate too?
This is good.
Is he done?
- Is he done?
- I'll eat one more time.
He's good.
(He's practically
giving it to them,)
(but they still have no clue.)
What can it be?
- It's a type of noodle.
- It is.
It doesn't have to be noodles
to sound like this.
- That's true.
- I heard this earlier.
Good job. Good job, Haha.
- Ji Hyo's next.
- It's Ji Hyo.
This is her first time
conducting an eating show.
This is my first time.
I'll eat without trying
to trick you.
(It's a mystery again.)
This is driving me insane.
I have no clue.
- What is that?
- She's good.
- Good luck, Ji Hyo.
- No wonder she's an actress.
I'm sure it has soup.
- What?
- It has soup.
Is it hot? Hot soup?
(Watching closely)
Ji Hyo ate...
- I think so.
- She exhaled.
That means it's hot soup.
What is it?
- I don't know.
- Jjamppong?
(Is it jjamppong?)
Is it mala soup?
1, 2, 3.
- Jjamppong.
(Team Jae Suk's answer: jjamppong)
(He saw her breath.
Is it jjamppong?)
Okay!
(Correct)
- At the end.
- We almost had it.
(Team Jae Suk earns 1 point
and leads with 2 points.)
That was great reasoning.
- Because...
- See?
How did you know?
- Ji Hyo...
- Right.
At the end,
she did this with her lips.
- Right.
- How did you know?
(Detective Yu realized that
she was eating something spicy.)
This is...
(She drank the spicy soup.)
(Exhaling)
It looked spicy and hot.
Right?
How did you get jjamppong?
Don't relax too much.
Block your nose properly.
- I know.
- I can't see at all.
Jong Kook has to duck a little more.
- They're getting something.
- Let's see.
Oh, dear.
- Here?
- Mingyu.
- Yes.
- Are you doing good?
It's something
Jong Kook doesn't like.
- It's something he doesn't like.
- It's something fried.
- I bet it is.
- He doesn't look too happy.
- No.
I don't think you'll ever get it.
Let's get started. Ready, set, go.
(He's being noisy.)
- Is it noodles?
- What is that?
It's ramyeon.
- It's not.
- It's not ramyeon.
He's making that sound on purpose.
- I agree. It's not guksu.
- It's not guksu.
It's something other than guksu.
That's true.
It doesn't sound like noodles.
- Is it tonkatsu?
- It's like wheat noodles.
I'm done.
- You're done?
- There's not much.
- There's nothing on his lips.
- Really?
You didn't eat.
- What?
- You didn't eat.
- I did.
- It's red.
I have a good feeling.
(Jong Kook is being noisy too.)
(What is it?)
That sounds the same as before.
They make nice sounds.
- It sounds tasty.
- We're good at this.
(Sucking)
It's something hard.
Hey, I know what it is.
He's sucking the crab meat.
It's kind of like that.
It's like that, right?
He's sucking something.
- In gochujang.
- Can we answer?
- Let me answer.
- Spicy marinated crab.
(Team Suk Jin's answer:
spicy marinated crab)
(Was he sucking something hard?
Is it spicy marinated crab?)
(Correct)
That was amazing.
From Jong Kook's sucking.
He got caught.
(That's too bad!)
I said he was sucking the crab meat.
- How did you know?
- That was amazing.
- We're the smart ones.
- How did he know?
- That was amazing.
- The winner of this mission is...
Team Jae Suk with two points.
(Team Jae Suk scores 1st place
for this mission.)
Great. Good job.
Sure, guys.
Hyosung is a singer
and a good daughter.
(The first mission of
Tiger's Birthday Party is over.)
On one of the spaces
Jong Kook wrote the prizes,
Team Jae Suk's sticker
will be placed.
The first mission is a freebie.
Right, there are many missions left.
We have to give them one
to make this exciting.
We shouldn't win everything.
Here.
- Did you hurt your right leg?
- Yes.
Your right butt cheek is
much smaller.
That's not true.
- What?
- My pants got stretched.
Is that so?
Team Jong Kook came in last,
so change one prize into a dud.
(Team Jong Kook lost, so they must
change a prize into a dud.)
When we lose once,
- we take two blows.
- Yang Saeroyi.
Cover VR gaming console.
- He doesn't play games.
- Cover VR gaming console.
I don't like VR.
I covered VR.
- Okay.
(The roulette changes to this
after Round 1.)
Is everybody still hungry?
- Yes.
Before we move onto
the next mission,
we'll take lunch orders.
- That's great.
- Today is Jong Kook's birthday,
so we'll have
a special birthday meal.
- Birthday meal?
- That sounds good.
This is uncomfortable.
Birthday parties don't last long.
I had no idea
we'd be doing this for this long.
What if we write a card for him,
and he reads it at the end?
- This is insane.
- That's the worst.
But if he cries, he gets a penalty.
"Jong Kook, it's Dong Hoon."
(They would hate that
more than penalties.)
It makes me feel weird hearing that.
You will be drawing an item
you want to see...
for Jong Kook's birthday meal.
What's that?
We'll look up the completed image
on an app,
and if the picture is
within the top five...
pictures or images that come up,
we'll order that food immediately.
- We'll order that food immediately.
- Is that possible?
- It has to come up?
- One at a time.
We tried it. If you draw well,
the food actually comes up.
- That's crazy.
- Really?
If you draw poorly,
something random comes up.
We should draw something easy.
Something simple.
- What should I draw?
- Drumsticks are easy.
Chicken is easy.
- I'm going to draw a burger.
- I'll do ramyeon.
I'm craving for
jjamppong and tangsuyuk.
Jjamppong is difficult.
Right? Jjamppong
and tangsuyuk are difficult.
We could draw
the Great Wall of China.
If we draw that,
a Chinese restaurant will pop up.
You will have five minutes.
You will give us the food, right?
I will give you the food
after the mission.
We can only draw one thing, right?
- What?
- I can't draw.
- Does it look like LA galbi?
- It looks like LA galbi.
(Is that LA galbi?)
How is that LA galbi?
- It's LA galbi.
- That's funny.
- LA galbi has these bones.
- Maybe I should draw a steak.
(Mingyu draws without hesitation.)
Is that chicken?
It looks like poop, not chicken.
- It's chicken.
- Really?
Haha, you are doing great.
- Haha.
- Is that naengmyeon?
- It's jjajangmyeon.
- I need to draw the sauce now.
Draw two peas.
Drawing two peas is a great idea.
It really looks like jjajangmyeon.
There is even pickled radish.
Haha, you should have studied art.
- I did study art.
- How about a cake?
I drew a cake.
(I see.)
I am done.
- Already?
- You are done?
- What did you draw? A burger?
- It looks similar.
- It looks like a burger.
- What is that blue thing?
- The blue thing?
I made a mistake.
I am sure I will get a burger.
I am sure of it.
- Suk Jin, what is that?
- Tonkatsu.
Tonkatsu doesn't look like that.
I need to draw vegetables
like cabbage, but...
I am sorry, but I want to see
Mingyu's drawing.
(Jae Suk cuts him off.)
I am sorry, but I want to see
Mingyu's drawing.
(Laughing)
- I was talking to myself.
- Really?
You don't need to be sorry.
- I was talking to myself.
- Okay.
- You don't need to be sorry.
(I won't accept an apology.)
I have no idea what Ji Hyo drew.
What is that?
- It's LA galbi.
- Don't you know what LA galbi is?
- I had no idea.
Gosh, what is that?
You have 10 seconds now.
- Subway.
- Seven,
- 6, 5,
- What?
(As everyone colors the drawing,
Jong Kook's feast becomes complete.)
- 2, 1.
- What is Jong Kook's drawing?
- Put the markers down.
- Okay.
Please show us your drawing in turn.
I will go first. I drew ramyeon.
While I couldn't draw the details,
- I hope I get some kind of noodles.
- Okay.
- I drew noodles.
Jong Kook.
- What is that? Soup?
- It's a sandwich.
I hope I get a sandwich
or a hot dog.
A hot dog.
- You didn't have much time.
- You got the details.
- I know.
- There are olives.
I drew it quickly.
- Mingyu will succeed.
- I drew fried chicken.
- It looks like fried chicken.
- He can draw well.
- I drew jjajangmyeon.
- Okay.
Haha drew jjajangmyeon well.
(Suk Jin is the next presenter.)
It looks like fried chicken.
He can draw well.
It's incredible.
Tonkatsu.
(Is that tonkatsu?)
(The atmosphere turns frigid.)
Suk Jin.
My goodness. That's...
- That's...
- What? It's tonkatsu.
I drew pickled radish
and vegetables.
I wonder what he will get.
- I am sure he will get something.
- I drew a knife and a fork too.
Ji Hyo.
I drew LA galbi.
- Isn't that a train?
- It's LA galbi.
- You need to erase the words.
- I will do that.
- We will never get LA galbi.
- These are the bones.
I drew a birthday must-have, cake.
I drew a pizza
with the sweet potato mousse.
- I drew a burger.
- He will surely get a burger.
A burger.
(Which drawing will succeed
the image search mission?)
- I will take a photo.
- It's ramyeon.
Because the bread is white...
(It's a success if there is ramyeon
in the top five search results.)
- Ramyeon.
- Top five search results.
- Hold on.
- What?
- Did you get ramyeon?
- What did you get?
The first result is
some kind of a monster.
- It's some kind of a monster.
- Try again.
- What is that? Why did that pop up?
- This is the first image.
This is fascinating.
- Is that it?
- It's the image.
What is this?
You got ramyeon as the fourth image.
You succeeded.
(The first dish, ramyeon,
is a success.)
It's a drawing.
I don't know whose work it is,
but it's a lousy drawing.
- Is this ramyeon?
- It could be a famous artwork.
That's incredible.
Jong Kook, I improved.
- Good job.
- Yang Saeroyi.
(Link your arms with Jong Kook.)
(Se Chan succeeds to link arms
with Jong Kook.)
(Linking arms)
(He succeeded.)
- Next is Jong Kook's drawing.
- Mine?
Jong Kook will surely succeed.
Do a good job.
(Will they succeed to get a sandwich
after ramyeon?)
- Jong Kook, you got it.
- You got it.
- It's the second image.
- What happened?
- What?
- This is exactly what you got.
- Subway.
Someone drew
the exact same sandwich.
- That's incredible.
- Let's see.
That's incredible.
- Is this the search result?
- Yes.
- The sandwich is a success.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook.
- This is good.
- This is insane.
(Jong Kook, let's link arms.)
(Kwang Soo succeeds
to link arms with him too.)
(Jong Kook
hasn't figured anything out yet.)
What should I do
if I don't get fried chicken?
This is a good vibe.
- Let's try it.
- You'll get it.
What is this?
Why is there spilled ramyeon?
(Confused)
There is a photo of spilled ramyeon.
Fried chicken failed.
I thought it would surely succeed.
Tonkatsu is a fail.
The burger is a fail.
LA galbi is a fail.
- Pizza.
- Let's stay hopeful.
- It might work.
- We got it!
- Did you get it?
(They get pizza!)
All the images are of pizza.
That's incredible.
- Okay!
- I did it!
We have ramyeon.
It comes with soup.
The dishes you secured are
ramyeon, sandwich, and pizza.
Pizza.
Pizza is perfect
for a birthday feast.
(Jong Kook's birthday feast
is coming up.)
While lunch gets prepared,
we will play...
Speed Picasso for Jong Kook,
the man with artistic skills.
That's good.
After the whistle, the person
who gives the problem...
will copy a famous scene
from a movie...
in the calendar for 20 seconds.
A famous scene from a movie.
If the team members
correctly guess the movie title.
the team will receive a point.
It's a foul to write words
or provide an unrelated hint.
Please clear the table.
- Shall we cut the slate?
- No, no. We will keep going.
(Oh, okay.)
I showed my passion.
- It's okay. Good job.
- Okay.
(Se Chan is full of passion.)
Start when you hear the whistle.
- If you write words, you are out.
- Of course.
- Turn the page.
- Okay.
A famous scene
that comes to your mind...
Hey, why...
(A sudden hit on the head)
- Did you do that?
- No!
Me?
(What is up with Suk Jin?)
Why would he do that?
That was a funny skit.
- He hasn't hit me yet.
- "Did you do that?"
(Slapstick comedy
from the "Humor No. 1" days)
- Mingyu was unfazed. "No."
- "No."
(Stern)
He hasn't hit me yet.
Did you take out your bang
on purpose?
No. Did it come out?
Suk Jin, you look so cute.
You look so cute.
- I don't believe you.
- You look so cute.
Since the day you were like,
"You can do it"...
(Whistling)
(The buttcrack whistle)
(A clear sound from the deep valley)
- It was a nice skit.
- I will subscribe.
- That was funny.
I will like and subscribe.
- Did you do that?
- No!
- "Did you do that?"
- I will like and subscribe.
Are you sure?
My stomach is full.
I mean, my stomach hurts.
(Everyone is going crazy
from laughing so much.)
It has been a while
since we heard Suk Jin fart loudly.
Seriously.
- That was nice.
- I know.
Start when you hear the whistle.
Each person has 20 seconds.
Get ready.
Set.
(Start.)
I bet it's hard.
(How will I draw this?)
- It's hard to draw in 20 seconds.
- Get the important bits.
(He draws diligently.)
- 20 seconds isn't very long.
- You are right.
10 seconds.
(Mysterious droplets)
Haha can draw well.
- Wrap it up.
- Five seconds.
- Gosh, I made a mistake.
- What?
2, 1. Show them.
- Show them.
- Show us.
- Time's up. Show us.
- Show them.
- We guess the movie title, right?
- Yes.
(What is that?)
It's...
- I think I know.
- It's...
- "Welcome To Dongmakgol".
- That's right.
- You guys don't disappoint!
- You are good.
(It's a popcorn scene
from "Welcome To Dongmakgol".)
- You guys don't disappoint!
- You are good.
- Haha drew well.
- Good job.
He really drew well.
- That's incredible.
- Good job.
- Haha.
- Time is ticking.
- Hurry up.
- You are in the best condition.
- Time is ticking.
- What?
- The time is ticking.
You are almost out of time.
(Time dissipates
even before he sees the problem.)
- Time is ticking.
- Show us.
- 2, 1. Show them.
- 2, 1.
All right. Here you go.
- What?
- You can get it right.
(What is that?)
- What is that?
- Are those dumplings?
Is it a kiss?
What is that?
(Blinking)
- "Dumb and Dumber".
- No, no.
- Hurry up.
- Are those tongues stuck together?
- I can't explain.
- You can pass.
I had to draw in a hurry.
- I know what it is.
- Five,
(The game is ongoing,)
- It's the answer, right?
- My goodness.
- How did you know?
- I knew right away.
(but the 2 of them are busy
with the hidden mission.)
- These aren't tongues.
- Are those noses?
- "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial".
- What?
"E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial".
Correct!
- Correct!
- Are those fingers?
(A signature touch
from "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial")
Are those fingers?
These are fingers.
- Suk Jin.
- I didn't hear that.
What's wrong with telling them
that they aren't tongues?
(Beeping)
(Laughing)
(It's the artistic Ji Hyo's turn.)
(Which movie did Ji Hyo get?)
- Is it a scene?
- It's a famous scene.
Five seconds remain.
- Are you done?
(She finishes the drawing
with 5 seconds remaining.)
- What?
- What is that?
(A square and a circle?)
- What?
- What is that?
- Let me answer.
(He takes a good look.)
Let me answer.
- "The Man from Nowhere".
- That's right!
(Correct)
My goodness.
(How is that
"The Man from Nowhere"?)
- I mean...
- How did he get it right?
- A hair clipper.
A hair clipper.
He is shaving his hair.
(Hair clipper, Won Bin)
- That's Won Bin?
- The hair.
- Is it that scene?
- It's this scene.
- Good job.
- How could this be...
- "The Man from Nowhere"?
- That was incredible.
She even left some time
on the clock.
This game is all about quick wits.
- It's all about quick wits.
- Hey.
- Where did it go?
- Draw with anything.
Time's running out.
He is wasting so much time.
Why can't you take out a marker?
It took him 20 seconds
to find a marker.
Seriously. He wasted so much time.
- For goodness' sake.
- I know what it is.
10 seconds.
(Se Chan continues to do
the hidden mission.)
- It's the answer, right?
- Jong Kook.
- I figured it out right away.
- Five...
(The 2 of them
monopolize the arm-linking.)
Let me answer!
- Five...
- I drew this.
Let me answer!
"Tazza".
Okay!
(How are they so good?)
(They complete the mission
after a buzzer-beater.)
- Haha. You are so good.
- I figured it out.
We are so good at this game.
Kwang Soo, let's go.
- Okay.
- We are so good at this game.
- This is bad.
- Stand behind us.
Let's do a good job.
I will hit him.
If he gets it wrong, I will end him.
(Suk Jin wants revenge
for what he suffered earlier.)
Can I hit like this?
- Of course. That's fine.
- Okay.
- Is this fine?
- Yes.
Can I move in like this
and hit you with the handle?
Yes, you can.
In that case,
- can I poke you with the handle?
- Don't draw blood.
(I will draw with care.)
You have five minutes. Get ready.
(Team Jae Suk starts.)
What?
(Which movie surprised Hyosung?)
Gosh, what should I do?
This is... Oh.
There you go! That's it!
How many seconds remain?
- Let's go!
- 10 seconds remain.
- She doesn't hesitate.
- Let's go.
I will hit like this.
Five,
four...
- I get it.
- Good job.
- What is that?
- I don't know.
- Be quiet.
- I get it.
- Keep your mouth shut.
- What is that?
Do you shake that thing?
- This movie was a big hit.
- She drew well.
This movie was a big hit.
I get it.
(The hidden mission is going well.)
- My goodness, that's...
- I know.
That one is hard.
If you don't know, pass.
- Pass.
Pass.
- It's "Inside Men".
- The answer is "Inside Men".
- Gosh.
That's right.
Was it this scene?
(Was it this scene?)
(Which scene will Kwang Soo draw?)
This is hard.
(It's "Nowhere to Hide.")
Keep the drawing simple.
10 seconds remain.
(He seems to be drawing the scene
similarly.)
3, 2, 1.
- I have an idea.
- Show them.
(Pow!)
(What?)
- He wrote a word.
(Writing words is a foul.)
You wrote a word.
- You can't write words.
- Why did you do that?
That's...
(What do you think you are doing?)
Why did you do that?
Why didn't you write the title?
- Why didn't you write the title?
- I wasn't thinking.
You don't have time.
- I was pressed for time.
- "Nowhere to Hide".
That's right.
It's "Nowhere to Hide."
- Why did you write a word?
- You drew well.
- I was pressed for time.
- Hold on.
How do I draw this?
You should have drawn
something else.
Seriously.
- He didn't need "Pow!"
- 10 seconds remain.
- They would have gotten it.
- I know.
(How will he draw this masterpiece?)
It's well-known
that Jae Suk can't draw at all.
Get ready to have a laugh.
I can't wait.
(A mental breakdown)
Fish?
(He really drew a parasite.)
- What is that?
- Fish?
Let me answer.
"Collective Invention".
What was it called?
- What was it called?
- What is that?
- Don't mouth words.
- It's...
- It's an anchovy.
- What is that?
Salmon!
Don't mouth words.
- Who did that?
- Stop mouthing words.
What is that?
- What was it called?
- Pass.
Isn't that poop?
- An alien.
- Pass.
- Pass. Pass.
- That's too bad.
- It's "Parasite".
- "Parasite".
(You're not thinking.)
- For goodness' sake.
- This is hard.
You didn't get
a single question right.
This is...
The movies are hard.
(I will succeed this time!)
You have 10 seconds left to draw.
This is so hard.
This one is easy. This one is easy.
3, 2, 1.
(However,)
(there is another word.)
He wrote something again.
Why did you write a word?
Hold on.
- He wrote a word again.
- He wrote a word.
- I didn't see it!
- Why did you write a word?
I didn't see it!
- Why did you write "Wham"?
- I didn't see it!
For goodness' sake.
- Forget it.
- Go and sit down.
- Go.
- It was "Shaolin Soccer"!
- Why did you write "Wham"?
- "Shaolin Soccer".
Anyone would have known
that it's "Shaolin Soccer."
- Why did you write a word?
- I was pressed for time.
This is...
(Which movie did Jae Suk get?)
All right. With this one,
I will draw the scene
exactly as it is.
- He can't do draw it.
- He did draw a parasite earlier.
- That's right.
- Right?
- 2, 1.
- Let's get one right.
- Show them.
- Time's up.
- Stop drawing.
- Okay.
(An alien creature appears.)
(What is that?)
- What?
- I think I know.
Let me answer. Pringles.
What is that?
- Isn't that Pringles?
- What is that?
"Edward Scissorhands"!
(Incorrect)
I know because Jae Suk is
on my level.
If we play this game together,
we would get everything right.
"The Terminator".
- What is that?
- No!
- "Inspector Gadget"!
- No.
- This is driving me crazy.
- What is going on with the arms?
- Pass. Pass.
- What's the movie?
- It's over.
- Lee Jung Jae.
"Assassination".
He has two bullet wounds.
- He has 2 bullet wounds.
- Look.
- How is this...
I got these wounds
from an assassination attempt.
I have two wounds.
(Are these Lee Jung Jae's fingers?)
"Assassination".
He has two bullet wounds.
- He has 2 bullet wounds.
That's ridiculous.
- How is this...
- My goodness.
- Jae Suk.
- How is this...
- I did my best.
- You didn't draw the bullet holes.
- You should have drawn the wounds.
- These two look the same.
That's either Pringles or a snowman.
These two look the same.
For goodness' sake.
Team Jae Suk has zero points.
"I have two wounds."
(Jae Suk left 2 masterpieces.)
- For goodness' sake.
- Get ready.
Set...
(Team Jong Kook starts.)
My goodness.
(The first question is
"The Lord of the Rings.")
This should be enough.
(Peeking)
Give Suk Jin a warning
for his flippant behavior.
Oh, that movie.
It isn't a flippant behavior.
I am simply curious.
(Members of other teams have
a war of nerves.)
- Is the time up?
- 3, 2,
- 1.
- He got done 1st.
I think they will know.
(The One Ring and Gollum)
- An alien?
- "Sonic the Hedgehog".
- "Sonic the Hedgehog"?
- "Men in Black".
(They don't have a clue.)
It's a person on a bicycle.
- How do you not know this?
- As soon as I saw the drawing,
I thought he drew really well.
"The Avengers"?
What is that round thing?
- Oh, it's "The Lord of the Rings."
- That's right.
- It was a ring.
What?
It was hard.
I don't know this movie.
It's okay. Just draw what you see.
- Just...
- Hey.
Okay.
(His enthusiasm is at its max.)
- That's incredible.
- It looks similar.
- 2, 1.
- They will surely get it right.
Show them.
- "Leon: The Professional".
- No.
- "A Better Tomorrow".
- Yes!
"A Better Tomorrow".
Anyone would have gotten it right.
The details.
- Mingyu can draw well.
- The details.
I don't know the movie.
- What?
- Mingyu is good at this game.
What? What is this?
Just do what you can. It's okay.
- He is drawing really fast.
- Five,
four,
- three,
- You are drawing so fast.
two,
one. Show them.
Let's see it.
What is that?
I get it.
- What is he, a kindergartener?
- Show them.
What is that?
I get it.
(His teammates are flustered.)
"Friend"?
(Correct)
(Jong Kook channeled
the spirit of guessing.)
You did it!
It's "Friend."
They have arms around the shoulders.
How is that "Friend"?
It's "Friend."
They have arms around the shoulders.
- How is that "Friend"?
How did he get it right?
This is ridiculous.
How is that "Friend"?
Is there a secret mission?
(That drawing doesn't depict
friends.)
- "Friend".
- This is ridiculous.
Do they know the answers?
Did you tell them the answers?
I get that they have arms
around the shoulders.
But how could he know it's "Friend"?
I didn't draw it right.
It's okay though. It's easy.
- "Joker".
- Okay.
(They answered "Joker" right.)
One.
(It looks like
a mathematical formula.)
"Miracle in Cell No. 7".
(But they get it right immediately.)
Look at it carefully.
- "The Host"?
- Correct.
- Is it right?
- You got it right.
Jong Kook!
(The game is over
with their great teamwork.)
- What's that?
- This one was difficult.
- It's good enough.
- Well done.
- We did a good job.
- Look.
They would've
answered "Assassination".
What are you talking about?
- This is disappointing.
- How would we answer this?
"I have two."
Let me announce
the results of Speed Picasso.
First place is Team Jong Kook.
Well done, guys.
- We won.
- Jong Kook answered them all.
Team Suk Jin is second place.
Gosh, we're in second place again.
And Team Jae Suk is
in third place with zero points.
We didn't get anything right.
Please bring in the roulette.
Should I put something on the dud?
Yes.
- I think this one is good.
- Here?
This one looks good.
(They wrote a laptop computer.)
Let's go have a meal.
Okay.
(They go to eat
after the second mission.)
(The dishes on their bucket lists
have arrived.)
It's ramyeon and pizza.
- My gosh.
- Sandwich.
- Try this.
- Okay.
This is what Hyosung drew.
- Right.
- That's true.
We're eating this
thanks to Hyosung.
And we're eating ramyeon
thanks to Se Chan.
The ramyeon is really good.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
If that's not true,
I'll slap you in the face.
What?
What did I do?
I like it though.
Slap him in the face?
I should eat more pizza.
It's good.
(While they enjoy the food...)
(I should complete the mission.)
Is it because of your shirt?
Why do you look so big?
- What?
- This.
- Your arm.
- I've been working out my arms.
It's good, isn't it?
(What is he doing?)
They got big, right?
I didn't do it for a while.
- They are firm, right?
- Gosh, look at this.
They are amazing.
Is it because of your shirt?
(All right. That was natural!)
(After hesitating for a moment,)
(Kwang Soo approaches Jong Kook.)
(He sneaks up to Jong Kook.)
(By the way...)
By the way...
(What?)
What is it?
- Nothing.
- What?
(Why is he smiling?)
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
- Do you like the food?
- It's really good.
Enjoy.
(Kwang Soo looks nervous.)
(And Joon Kook
watches him feel that way.)
(Humming)
Why is he humming?
What's with him?
What's with the humming, Kwang Soo?
- Why are you humming?
- What did I do?
You just seem so relaxed.
- Why do you even care?
- What makes you...
feel so relaxed?
I really enjoyed the food.
Kwang Soo, eat a lot.
- What?
- Eat a lot.
(A counterattack)
What are you guys doing?
Eat a lot.
(He got it. We're doomed.)
I don't know.
- Are they fighting?
- Eat a lot.
(There you go, Ji Hyo.)
(He knows what's going on.)
Darn it.
I hate this. What's all this?
Let's just sing
a birthday song to him.
Let's do that.
(Happy birthday to you)
My friend, Jong Kook.
(They are doomed already,
so they just sing to him.)
I love you, Jong Kook.
(They all take Jong Kook's arms.)
(Nice try.)
(It's completely failed.)
Happy birthday!
Now it feels like a birthday.
(Let's enjoy it together.)
Why were you guys hesitating?
You can just celebrate it.
My gosh.
All right. 1, 2, and 3.
(He claps in desperation.)
(Jong Kook found out about the
mission. What about the next one?)
It was fun.
What is this?
There's a blindfold.
- A blindfold?
- A blindfold.
- And there are cookies.
- There are cookies?
- What are they for?
- We should...
bring something
before someone else moves.
I see.
Jong Kook already knows what to do.
How did you know?
We should bring it.
This is the last mission.
It's the last one already.
After this mission, you will
spin the roulette.
Let's do this!
Okay.
- All right.
- Let's do this right.
- Let's do this.
- Congratulations.
- This is the last mission.
- Good luck.
- The last one.
- The last mission...
is perfect for Jong Kook.
It requires physical strength and
quick wit. It's Defend Your Cookies.
- Defend Your Cookies?
- Okay!
It's a game
of attacking and defending.
Team Offense will decide
one person to defend cookies...
and two people to move cookies.
The eight members
except for the guard...
can move around while music plays.
Two members from
Team Offense should put...
as many cookies in their basket
in front of the guard...
as they can.
Meanwhile, members
from Team Defense should...
eat as many cookies as they can.
- Should we eat them?
- Are we eating the cookies?
The guard sitting here...
should wear
a blindfold during the game.
And he can squirt a water pistol
at one person when the music stops.
The person who's shot
should go back to the starting line.
(The member who's shot should
go back to the starting line.)
- It's hard.
- You're given five minutes.
After three rounds,
the team with most cookies
will win the game.
- I see.
All right.
Can we simulate the game once?
Why did he even answer?
He just said he understood.
- Did you not understand it?
- Why would he want to simulate it?
You should get him
a tutor or something.
Wait. Did you understand?
Of course I did.
(Surprised)
(He sounds embarrassed again.)
- I see.
- How could he say that?
Okay.
(Who will get more cookies
and win the game?)
- Team Suk Jin will go first.
- Okay.
You can't move
when there's no music playing.
- Ji Hyo. You can't see, can you?
- No.
What should we do there?
We should put these in the basket.
We should put...
as many cookies in there as we can.
It's not easy to eat them.
It's not easy.
- Let's begin.
- Watch out for the squirt gun.
Start.
(Music starts.)
(They can move around
only when music plays.)
(Once the music stops,
the guard can quirt the gun.)
Haha is my team.
(I sensed someone's
presence around here.)
(She hit Kwang Soo right away.)
(He's denying it.)
You should go back.
(It's been only 5 seconds.)
Did someone get hit?
Was it Mingyu?
(They move forward quickly
while music plays.)
(They all stop.)
(She squirts the water gun.)
(Jae Suk is right in front of her,
but she shoots at the floor.)
(Haha puts cookies in the basket.)
(And Jae Suk steals them.)
(Giggling)
(They burst into laughter
all of a sudden.)
(Sneaking down)
(She shoots him in the back.)
(He's really bad at games.)
Go back to the starting line.
(He goes back without
showing good performances.)
(While Mingyu goes back,
they all come up to Ji Hyo.)
(Gobbling up)
(They are busy
bringing more cookies.)
(The music stops.)
(Rustling)
(Stumbling)
(She squirts the water gun at him.)
(It's Kwang Soo again.)
- I think someone's right here.
- Go back.
(She keeps shooting at me.)
(Suk Jin is here again
to deliver more cookies.)
(Turning)
(Squirting)
(She shoots at her team member.)
- Hey.
- My gosh.
It was Suk Jin.
I can't see.
I can't see anything.
Gosh.
(I should eat it all up.)
(Rustling)
(Kwang Soo is
right in front of her again.)
(Fortunately, Ji Hyo makes a turn.)
(He managed to escape the crisis.)
(Meow)
(I heard a cat around here.)
(She shoots at Kwang Soo again.)
(Frustrated)
I can't see.
(Pinching)
(Groaning)
(She heard something around here.)
(She shoots straight at his lips.)
(How could she shoot him
right in the lips like that?)
It got into my mouth.
(Jae Suk is still alive.)
Stop eating my cookies.
(He's even savoring the cookies.)
(I can't let him do that!)
(How could you pinch me?)
(Pinching)
(Groaning)
(She looks in the direction
of the sound.)
(Squirting)
(He got even with Jae Suk.)
(You wait and see, Se Chan.)
What is happening here?
They are going to finish
my cookies at this rate.
(The given time is almost up.)
(The music stops.)
(Pinching)
I got you.
(I got you.)
(Prince with squid ink)
(He has an ink-and-wash
painting on his face.)
(Round 1 is over.)
Gosh. What happened
to you, Kwang Soo?
Now I know how to play this game.
It's really easy.
Okay.
My gosh. What happened
to you, Jae Suk?
What's wrong with you?
- You did this to me.
- My gosh.
- I couldn't see anything.
- You were...
- You did a good job.
- I couldn't see.
Well done.
We will collect the cookies
on the floor and measure the weight.
- Really?
- Those who will be shot...
have already been decided.
- It's strange, isn't it?
- It's strange.
- Who's next?
- Jong Kook.
Let's do this right.
- Okay?
- It's his birthday.
He's volunteering.
- I think it'll be hard.
- It's not easy.
Ready.
(Round 2 starts.)
(Focusing)
(Silent)
Nice!
(Suk Jin is hit.)
(Suk Jin is sent back
to the starting line.)
(Haha, a member of Team Defense
has to eat cookies.)
(He goes behind Jong Kook.)
(No one is even touching
the cookies?)
(Everyone surrounds Jong Kook...)
(and starts putting stickers
on his body.)
(The hidden mission
for Mission 3 is...)
(putting stickers
on Jong Kook's body.)
(Everyone expected this mission
to be the hardest.)
(How are we going to put
stickers on Jong Kook?)
(No one dared to carry out
this mission.)
(This is our chance!)
(Someone is behind me.)
(Crowded)
(Everyone focuses on the hidden
mission instead of the cookies.)
(The newbie, Mingyu, is the only one
playing the game.)
(Careful)
Someone is carrying out
a mission behind me.
(Jong Kook finds out.)
(We're doomed.)
Why do you keep
carrying out missions?
That's enough.
(What do we do now?)
I said, that's enough.
(This hidden mission failed too.)
(Just then)
(Kwang Soo's eyes suddenly
look completely different.)
(Memories of being humiliated by
Jong Kook flash through his mind.)
(Irritated)
(With angry eyes,
Kwang Soo approaches Jong Kook.)
(His opponent is
a blindfolded tiger.)
(Kwang Soo carefully approaches
Jong Kook...)
(and attacks the top of his head.)
(You didn't expect this, did you?)
I shouldn't just sit still.
Gosh, I can't believe you guys.
(The top of the head is
the only part without muscles.)
(Everyone is busy putting stickers
on Jong Kook.)
Everyone, please focus on the game.
I can't believe you guys.
(Jong Kook is about to explode.)
(The angrier the tiger gets,)
(the more aggressive
Kwang Soo gets.)
This isn't what the game is about.
This isn't...
Seriously.
(You ruined everything for us.
Do something about it!)
Stay still.
(Is it really okay to do this?)
Kwang Soo, please go back.
Kwang Soo, go back.
(Haha puts more stickers
on Jong Kook.)
Kwang Soo.
(Here's my hidden mission!)
- Eat the cookies.
- Time-out.
- This isn't how you play this game.
- Hold on. You punk.
You punk.
Gosh, the stickers are
all over my hair.
- Kwang Soo ignores the rules.
- What's with you?
- Kwang Soo.
- You ignore the rules.
I knew there was a mission,
but how could you do it so openly?
We did it openly
because you found out.
(Why did you have to find out
so fast?)
Well said.
He means it.
Please take the basket away.
Here it is.
They're catching up with us.
(No one paid attention
to the cookies.)
It's our turn now.
- It's our turn.
- I'll be the guard.
- All right.
(Jae Suk volunteers
to be the guard.)
- Can we start?
- Let's start.
(Round 3 starts.)
(Hyosung is carrying
a lot of cookies.)
(Hyosung's hands are
full of cookies.)
(Se Chan stops her.)
(Kwang Soo is delivering
cookies too.)
(You can't put those cookies
in the basket.)
Please.
(Jae Suk shoots
at his own team member.)
(Kwang Soo is
the race starter of 2020.)
(Annoyed)
(After killing his own team member,)
(Jae Suk enjoys
playing James Bond.)
(He pretends to be sharp.)
(While Jae Suk plays with his gun,
his cookies are taken.)
(Hyosung is the only one
filling the basket with cookies.)
(Busted!)
(Jae Suk kills
his own team member again!)
It was me!
- Was it you, Hyosung?
- Yes.
(What were you doing there?)
(The tiger is on the move.)
(Kwang Soo puts stickers on him.)
(Let me join you.)
(Kwang Soo pretends
he didn't do anything.)
(Kwang Soo gets punished
right away.)
(Haha punishes himself.)
(I can't believe these guys.)
(While everyone is distracted,
Suk Jin moves forward.)
(Not knowing when to stop,)
(he ends up right in front of
Jae Suk.)
Who are you?
(Suk Jin's nose is covered in ink.)
(Jae Suk is hooked on
playing James Bond.)
Who are you?
(He grabs Ji Hyo's cap...)
(and shoots his water gun
ruthlessly.)
(Ji Hyo tries to steal cookies
instead of going back.)
Who are you?
(Ji Hyo is shot right in her face.)
(Se Chan screams
with his mouth full of cookies.)
(Worried Se Chan will choke,)
(Jae Suk shoots ink
into his mouth.)
(Jae Suk is out of control.)
It's mine.
(There's only 1 minute left.)
Suk Jin.
Here he is.
To the right.
- Here?
- Hold on.
(Jae Suk takes aim.)
- Is he here?
- A little lower.
- Here?
- Even lower.
(I'll shoot you wherever you are.)
- Here he is.
- Wait.
(Bull's eye)
- Give me a new gun, please.
- How many guns are you using?
Why did you give him a machine gun?
(James Bond with a machine gun)
(Who is his next target?)
(Ji Hyo is caught stealing cookies.)
(She's wearing black lipstick now.)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo
are out of control.)
I'm scared.
(Kwang Soo comes back
after sending Ji Hyo away.)
It's me.
(Desperate)
(I'll teach you a lesson.)
This isn't what the game is about.
Everyone.
(After seeing this mess, the staff
decided never to play this again.)
You have 20 seconds left.
(There are only 20 seconds left.)
(Jae Suk is still enjoying
playing James Bond.)
(The players gobble up the cookies.)
(Round 3 is over.)
Okay!
Please pick up everything
on the floor.
We have more cookies
than I expected.
- That's a relief.
- Okay.
- Unbelievable.
- That was hilarious.
- Okay.
- That was fun.
(That was fun.)
- We're weighing the cookies now.
- Okay.
Everyone, let me announce
the final mission result.
- What's the result?
- It's over.
With 0.648kg,
Team Jong Kook is in first place.
(Team Jong Kook wins first place
with 0.648kg.)
We worked hard.
With 540g, Team Suk Jin is
in second place.
- No way.
- Really?
- We're in 2nd place again.
- We keep coming in 2nd place.
With 292g, Team Jae Suk is
in third place.
According to the result, let's make
changes to the roulette wheel.
Please bring it in.
- We're in first place again.
- I know.
(A dud is replaced
with a Korean beef set.)
We'll definitely win a gift.
There are too many gifts.
(This is not good.)
Before Jong Kook spins
the roulette wheel,
I'll reveal the hidden missions,
which Jong Kook didn't know about.
- He didn't know about them?
There were missions
that he didn't know about?
Today's hidden missions
were carried out...
to decide who will pay
for Jong Kook's birthday gift.
- Surprise!
- Yes!
- Happy birthday!
One of us will pay for the gift
you pick.
I see.
If Jong Kook...
manages to guess
all five hidden missions...
carried out by the other members,
he can spin the roulette wheel
three times.
If he guesses 3 or 4,
he gets to spin it 2 times.
If he guesses two or less,
he gets to spin it only once.
It's not easy to guess
all five of them.
- It's not easy.
- Take a guess.
First, linking their arms with me.
(Confident)
And then putting stickers on me.
Putting stickers on you.
Let me see.
What else?
Making me say, "Here I am"?
(Kim Jong Kook, Tiger,
Extremely good at guessing)
Making you say, "Here I am."
(How did he know?)
And?
(Jong Kook has already guessed
3 missions right.)
What else, you punk?
(Out of frustration,
Suk Jin snaps at Jong Kook.)
Gosh.
(It makes everyone feel better.)
(Disappointed)
Let's see how many you get right.
- What did we do all day?
- It's the worst.
Hold on.
I'm not sure about the other things.
Making me eat something?
- Jong Kook got three right.
- It's too hard.
You can spin the roulette wheel
two times.
(Jong Kook gets to spin
the roulette wheel 2 times.)
- We'd love to get him a present.
- Of course.
- All right.
(The Running Balls have been
distributed.)
(Ji Hyo: 56, Haha: 43,
Se Chan and Kwang Soo: 27)
(They can transfer their
Running Balls to someone else.)
Decide who you want to transfer
your Running Balls to.
- Shall we decide?
- Yes.
(They write down who will receive
their Running Balls.)
We're a team.
- You and I are a team.
- I know.
We've been through so much together.
(Whispering)
Why...
- Why are you listening to him?
- That's not it.
- Let me just hear him out.
- Whose side are you on?
You and I are a team.
Your teams don't matter anymore.
Write Jae Suk's name.
Everyone should write
Jae Suk's name.
- I...
- Write Jae Suk's name.
(Suk Jin wants all the
Running Balls to go to Jae Suk.)
I'm giving five to Jae Suk.
- This is not...
- Write, "Yu Suk Jin."
"Yu Suk Jin."
"Yu Suk Jin"?
He wants me to write, "Yu Suk Jin."
(What are you talking about?)
"Yu Suk Jin"?
Let's see what happens.
Please spin it.
It'd be unbelievable
if he picks Team Jae Suk.
- Here we go.
- That'd be incredible.
- Spin it hard.
- A laptop.
Please.
- Let's go!
- Please.
Look at the dust.
- Let's see.
Pick a dud!
It's almost there.
- Here it comes.
- This is dangerous.
- Why?
- It's coming back.
Keep going. This is dangerous.
- Jong Kook.
- It's coming back.
("Sports massage pass")
(What will be the first gift for
Jong Kook's birthday party?)
- Stop.
- Keep going.
"Tonic".
- Tonic.
- It's worth 300 dollars.
- That's not too expensive.
- Tonic.
- That's not expensive.
- It's fine.
- Tonic.
- Sure.
- Should we keep going?
Tonic.
- Korean beef set is good.
- Is this his last chance?
It is.
Please. Please.
This is...
- making me nervous.
- It makes you tense up.
- It's getting there.
- It's going.
(Is the last one a dud?)
- You never know, Jae Suk.
- It's coming.
- Jae Suk!
- Team Jae Suk!
- It's coming!
(Will it land on
Team Jae Suk's "laptop"?)
- Laptop!
- What is it?
(Laptop?)
- Laptop!
It's a laptop.
Really?
- This is insane.
- It's a laptop.
- Why did you suggest it?
- He's so lucky.
- Who?
- He's lucky.
- Who's going to pay for it?
- I got a laptop.
- Tonic.
- This is insane.
Okay!
He got the tonic and the laptop.
We'll draw two balls later.
The 1st will pay for the tonic,
and the 2nd will pay for the laptop.
- Look at that.
- What's wrong with Suk Jin's?
I have fewer balls than expected.
- Suk Jin...
- I have more than I thought.
It would be strange
if Suk Jin doesn't get picked.
I didn't know
you all loved me so much.
It would be strange
if Suk Jin doesn't get picked.
Close it.
The one who deserves
it will get picked.
I can get tonic for Jong Kook.
- The first person...
- Can't you?
is for the tonic.
Please give a round of applause.
Happy birthday, Jong Kook!
I hope you feel energized
after drinking the tonic.
I wish you good health.
Here we go. This is for the tonic.
This is so much fun.
Is one coming out? There is.
- Don't look.
- Is there one?
There's one person.
This is for the tonic.
Tonic is good for your health.
This is our chance
to give him a gift.
It's our chance. Who is it?
(Who is the lucky person
that gets to pay?)
Tonic is good for your health.
Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin is the lucky one.)
This is nerve-racking, right?
- Let's laugh. Laugh.
- I had no clue.
I didn't think
it was going to be him.
I'm happy.
I'm happy because instead of him,
I want to get it for his mother.
You're blushing too much
to be happy.
- Next person.
- Laptop.
- This is for the laptop.
This is the real deal.
This is more expensive.
I wonder
who the lucky person will be.
1, 2, 3. Here we go.
What are the odds?
- Is one coming?
- There is.
Who will be paying for the laptop?
1, 2, 3.
Se Chan.
(It's Se Chan,
Jong Kook's favorite.)
(Gosh...)
(He's so happy
that his legs give out.)
Suk Jin.
I am the poorest here.
- How did this happen?
- It never works out.
A laptop?
I thought
it was going to be Suk Jin.
(Admirable Se Chan)
There are 100 dollar laptops.
- We'll sign it.
- They like gifts.
I know.
- We'll present the gifts.
- Sure.
- There you go.
- Jong Kook.
- Happy birthday.
- Congratulations.
Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday, Jong Kook.
- Yes!
Happy birthday.
(May is the month of festivals.
5 Almighty of Festivals are here!)
(Ahn Ji Young of BOL4)
(Jin Hyuk of UP10TION,
Hyojung of OH MY GIRL)
(BewhY, Jessi)
(Whoever gets more money wins!)
(Team Idol Stars?
More like stars in my heart.)
(Team Idol Stars, Team Hip-Hop,
and Team Indie compete...)
(with pride for
the title Almighty of Festivals.)
Don't get mad unnecessarily.
(It was peaceful in the beginning,)
(but that changed all of a sudden.)
(The festival is over.)
(It's not about teams anymore.)
(It's a brutal festival
with rivalry.)
(Monopoly, Share)
(The temptation to take it all
is uncontrollable.)
(Share and monopoly,)
(betrayal and deals continue
between these options.)
(Who will protect their money
and monopolize the festival?)
(Festival Money Securing Race:
"A World of the Festival")