(To the refreshing blue ocean
of Jeju Island)
This is my first time here
since shooting Running Man.
This is nice.
Ji Hyo, why did you
get here yesterday, by the way?
- I just...
- Did you get here yesterday?
This looks fake. Hello.
- Hello.
- Isn't this computer graphics?
- This is amazing.
Jeju Island!
It's so nice to be outside.
Welcome.
The ocean looks beautiful.
It's been a long time
since we did this last time.
- It's beautiful.
- This is so nice.
I couldn't go anywhere this year.
I took an airplane
after a long time.
This feels different.
It felt strange to fly in a plane.
- I know.
- Because it's been so long.
Look at the stylists. They're
taking pictures of the scenery.
- There's Jong Kook's stylist.
- They're on a vacation.
They will upload the pictures
on their social media.
I was excited last night.
You've got some blusher
on your face to look lively.
- Because I'm in Jeju Island.
- Really?
She woke up at four to go to
a beauty salon this morning.
- Really?
- Yes.
I wanted to look pretty.
I want to look nice.
We've come to Jeju Island
after a really long time.
And we have four actresses
who are perfect for the scenery...
- of Jeju Island.
- My gosh.
- Really?
- Here come the actresses.
Welcome.
- Then...
- They've come a long way.
I decided to come here
because I heard you'd come.
That's not important.
It's just good to be on TV.
There they are.
- That's Choi Yeo Jin.
- I haven't seen Yeo Jin for long.
Yeo Jin.
Hello.
- E Hyun.
- Hello.
There's E Hyun.
And who else?
Can we go there? I'm nervous.
- It's Ju Bin.
- There's Ju Bin.
And Ji Eun is here too.
Nice to meet you.
She's from "Be Melodramatic".
(Han Ji Eun played a single
working mom in "Be Melodramatic".)
(She's a rising star who shows her
distinctive acting in many dramas.)
(She played an actress with a unique
personality in "Be Melodramatic".)
(Lee Ju Bin showed her impressive
acting in "Mister Sunshine".)
They've come a long way.
- I'm glad you're here.
- They've come a long way.
Let's talk to them one by one then.
We have So E Hyun here.
Your real name is Jo Woo Jung.
- Right.
- I didn't know.
- It's a pretty name.
- I like your name.
Why are you using a stage name?
My agency consulted a fortune-teller
and said it would be successful.
- A fortune-teller?
- So E Hyun?
- You're honest.
- Right.
I had nothing to do with it.
I like the name, Woo Jung.
I know. It's like Jo Friendship.
Jo Friendship?
(Jo Friendship)
What? Jo Friendship?
- Is it her English name?
- Yes.
That sounds great.
And we have Choi Yeo Jin here.
It's been a long time.
- It's been years.
- You've met Ji Hyo before.
In "Lovely Horribly".
- Right.
- We met in "Emergency Couple".
I see. "Emergency Couple".
What was Ji Hyo like
when you worked with her?
She's a sleepyhead.
- She was the same.
- It's the same.
She's consistent all the time.
It was surprising that
she could act so well right away.
- That's surprising, right?
- Yes.
We're also surprised by that.
She's good here as well.
She just plays games
as soon as she wakes up.
- And she doesn't get puffy.
- She claps her hands getting up.
I'm serious.
- She's like a machine.
- That's amazing.
All right.
Next, we have Han Ji Eun here.
- Hello.
- When I saw her coming,
I wondered where I knew her from.
- It's "Be Melodramatic".
- She was in "Be Melodramatic".
- Right. It's "Be Melodramatic".
- I love the drama.
She went to the same college
as So Min.
- Really?
- Yes.
- We went to the same school.
- Tell us about So Min.
Ji Eun, what was
So Min like back in school?
So Min?
I don't know much about her.
(I don't know much about her.)
- She was...
- They weren't so close.
I worked really hard in school.
That's strange.
So Min, do you remember
anything about Ji Eun?
- Of course, I do.
- Okay.
But I don't remember it clearly.
Did you two fight or something?
(It's more awkward
when they're not close enough.)
- It's so strange.
- You two had a fight, right?
- So Min, did you fight with her?
- You should make up.
So Min won't start talking
before she hears anything.
Anyway, it wasn't...
Something wasn't so clean.
You mean your relationship?
- Me?
- I mean, it was clean...
- Ji Eun is upset now. "Me?"
- I mean our feelings...
- No.
- They might fight.
There wasn't a man involved, but
her friend was involved with a man.
- Me?
- I mean...
- She said, "Me?"
- No.
- "Me?"
- So Min.
You two weren't so close, right?
- It's not like that.
- What's going on?
I'm not saying Ji Eun was
involved with a man.
- Ji Eun is upset.
- Hang on. Let me correct this.
It's not that there was a man
between Ji Eun and me.
- I see.
- I meant Ji Eun's friend.
- We have plenty of time today.
You should think about it.
Ji Eun said she had something
to say. Please tell us.
Well...
She's glaring at So Min now.
This is my first time in a variety
show, so I'm not sure...
- how much I should talk.
- Tell us about the whole thing.
- Just be honest.
- Tell us everything about So Min.
- It's okay.
- You remember something about her.
I remember that she was
in the group dating dream team.
The group dating dream team.
- She went on a lot of dates.
- That's right.
- And Ji Eun was there.
- Right.
- I remembered something.
- What?
(I remembered something.)
- I can't say that.
- No. What is it? Tell me first.
(No. What is it? Tell me first.)
What?
- What? She can say anything.
- I remember what she was like.
(So Min starts to recall the past,
and Ji Eun is nervous about it.)
- Tell us what it is.
- I remember it now.
- You're making me nervous.
- Tell us.
I once said that I went on
a lot of group dates back in school.
I tried hard to lighten up the mood,
but the boys asked someone else out.
- Do you remember I said that?
- You did.
It was Han Ji Eun.
(Their past has finally
been revealed.)
It was Han Ji Eun, everyone.
I lightened up the mood...
- and thought things would go well.
- You had a good chance.
I just remembered
that I was close to her.
- You know that So Min...
- She lightened up the mood.
- is good with words, right?
- Indeed.
- I led them while playing games.
- We've been there too.
In short, you were in the same
position as Jae Suk's.
- Yes, that's right.
- The female version of Jae Suk.
- She was in my position.
- She was the ice breaker.
You weren't asked out by anyone
because you led everyone.
The atmosphere was so good
that day, Suk Jin.
- Jae Suk was always like you.
- Suk Jin, don't...
Don't act like you know much
about a group blind date.
- We did it when I was younger too.
- I know.
Next up is Lee Ju Bin.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- I'm so excited to see her here.
- Hello.
I'd like to tell you something
right now.
- She said she wanted to be here,
- What's the reason?
and the person she wanted to
team up with was...
Se Chan.
Why?
- Exactly.
- Ask her. We're in Jeju Island.
- Why?
- Oh, my.
- No one has picked me before.
- Let's ask her.
(His comment made her laugh.)
- Let's hear the reason.
- You have a chance.
- Let's let her explain.
- Why did you pick him?
Let's forget why you wanted to
be on this show.
Why did you pick Se Chan?
I've been a big fan
since he appeared...
- on "People Looking for a Laugh".
- "Woong's Father"?
- Yes, I liked "Woong's Father",
- My goodness.
"The Invisible Man", and "The Best".
Se Chan is even more charming
in person.
- He has such a kind heart.
- But I'm sure...
- I'm counting on you.
- She's counting on me.
- Really?
(She's counting on me.)
Will you go back to Seoul today?
- Yes, I'll leave today.
- Oh, I see.
- What a shame.
- I'm sorry.
- You see...
- She drew the line.
- People like her...
- Yes.
usually leave hastily
as soon as the shoot ends.
- They just run away.
- We don't even get to say goodbye.
She said she'll leave later today,
but you might see her
on the plane tomorrow.
(My schedule has been changed.)
That would be the worst.
- Se Chan's heart is wide open.
- Yes, my heart is open.
I'm sorry to say this
from the beginning,
but I don't think you have a chance
with her.
- Jae Suk, come on.
- Listen.
- We all must...
- Don't be so negative.
- We must face the reality.
- I understand.
- I agree.
- Yes.
- Gosh, seriously.
- He's right about that.
Let's welcome our four guests.
(Welcome to Jeju Island.)
Today,
- you'll be divided into four teams.
- I see.
Our guests will be the team leaders,
and choose their team members.
We asked the guests to choose...
the best four members
to be on their teams,
- Okay.
- and ranked you by popularity.
A popularity ranking again?
But you won't reveal
who picked who, right?
- It makes us disappointed somehow.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
- We get our hopes up.
Don't take it to heart.
- Also, some of you...
- Yes.
get the wrong idea.
It doesn't mean they like you.
- They just want you on their teams.
- Just as a team member.
- Just as a team member. That's all.
- Exactly.
- But it means a lot to us.
- That's true.
- The person in fourth place.
- Is that the last place?
Let's find out
who's in fourth place.
The fourth place is not bad.
It's Se Chan.
- Is it a good thing?
- Of course.
- He must've been her best choice.
- I guess only Ju Bin picked him.
Only Ju Bin? I don't think so.
- You can say that Se Chan is...
- It's not bad.
- high on the ranking.
- It's good.
- I'm high on the ranking.
- It's not bad at all.
Let's find out who's in third place.
(The person in third place)
- Oh, my. It's Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin? Hang on.
(What?)
- Really?
- It's strange.
- You manipulated the result, right?
- What's going on?
It's because they would feel
comfortable around him.
I can't believe this.
Are you serious?
They know who is
the most popular member among us.
Let's move on to the person
in second place.
- What?
- It's Jong Kook.
My gosh. I didn't expect that.
- What?
- It's Jong Kook.
My gosh. I didn't expect that.
- Jong Kook is in second place?
- I'm surprised.
- Then who's in first place?
- It must be Jae Suk.
That person won
by an overwhelming majority.
I'm sure it's Jae Suk.
(I'm sure it's Jae Suk.)
- By an overwhelming majority?
- What?
(Who won overwhelming support
from the guests and came in first?)
- By an overwhelming majority?
- It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo seems more surprised
than the others.)
- What?
- It wasn't Jae Suk?
Then what about us?
Jae Suk is not in the top four?
- Then what about us?
- Hey, Jae Suk.
- What could be our rankings?
- Oh, no.
- Kwang Soo is in first place?
- This is ridiculous.
(Kwang Soo is Yeo Jin's 1st,
Ji Eun's 1st,)
(E Hyun's 2nd,
and Ju Bin's 4th choices.)
- Did you mix up the order?
- What's going on?
- I think that's the case.
- We didn't mix up the order.
- Isn't he in last place?
- But we...
- I'm already upset from the start.
Kwang Soo is in first place.
Let us vote
for our best choices too!
Check the rest rankings.
- All right.
- Let's leave, Ji Hyo.
I knew this would happen when I
heard female guests would come.
Let's go, Ji Hyo. Let's go.
- Why did you throw sand?
- Hey, get the car ready.
- So Min.
- Why did you throw sand?
You two might be
in 5th and 6th places.
- Seriously.
- Wait and see.
Do you think I went to the beauty
salon to be humiliated like this?
- At 4 a.m.?
- Actually,
I understand why you're upset.
One of our guests is your friend.
- Your friend didn't pick you.
- No, she didn't.
- We went to the same school.
- The person in fifth place.
- I'm in fifth place.
- Gosh.
I'm starting to feel upset.
- Haha sounds like my dad.
- This is so annoying.
- Haha hasn't been called yet.
- He hasn't been called yet.
Let's find out who's in sixth place.
- Haha must be...
- I'm so relieved.
- I almost threw sand.
- Haha is in sixth place.
However, you know...
- I almost threw sand.
- If you'll keep going like this,
- You see,
- invite male guests for us too.
- Why invite only female guests?
- although we have female guests,
I didn't expect Ji Hyo and So Min...
- to be in the bottom two.
- It's not fair.
This is how yin and yang works.
- They must be disappointed.
- I'm disappointed.
- Yeo Jin, I'm disappointed.
- They must be disappointed.
- So Min, you must be in last place.
- 1 of them won by 1 vote.
- Although your friend is here.
- I'm sure I'm in last place.
(She's predicting
she's in last place.)
I must be in last place.
Ji Hyo is in seventh place.
(Song Ji Hyo in seventh place)
(Ji Hyo is Ju Bin's
third best choice.)
My, your friend is so harsh.
You have a good friend, So Min.
You have such a good friend.
Your friend is very honest.
- You hate her that much?
- I mean...
- Her friend...
- "You hate her that much?"
- You hate So Min that much?
- Her friend...
- I'm sorry.
- She absolutely...
I bet you hate her.
- I think I should remove my makeup.
I'm going to remove my makeup.
- I'm sorry.
- I can't believe this.
- She hates you. Right.
- This is so disappointing.
I'll tell you how the guests will
choose their team members.
- You see the water bottle, right?
- Yes.
We'll put flags with numbers
from 1 to 4 on them...
around the water bottle
in the order of rankings.
The guests will dance
to the music at the starting line,
and when Jae Suk blows the whistle,
run and pick one of the flags.
- Pick one flag.
- Oh, I see.
People in the top four,
please put your flags in the sand.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
- We can pick who we want, right?
- The top four.
Yes, you can pick who you want
to be on your team.
(Kwang Soo, 1st, Jong Kook, 2nd,
Suk Jin, 3rd, Se Chan, 4th)
You know, I am sure...
that Yeo Jin will run like crazy.
- No, I won't.
- Really?
Wait. Let me just put this down.
Are you all ready?
- We'll play music for them.
- Okay.
Yeo Jin must be a fast runner.
Run when the whistle is blown
while dancing to the music.
- They'll pass by so quickly, right?
- E Hyun is also good at running.
(The top four are excited.)
(Her long arms and legs reacted
to the excited melody instantly.)
She's dancing on the beach.
All right. Come on.
- She must've prepared for this.
- Yeo Jin.
Yeo Jin, you're so cool.
(Taken aback)
- She hates it.
- We want to see your dance.
- Awesome. She's so cool.
- Oh, my.
- Yeo Jin is still good at dancing.
- That's awesome.
(Her stage presence is
on another level.)
(While only Yeo Jin was
doing her powerful warm-up,)
(the whistle was blown!)
Run!
(Running at full speed)
(She started running
while tying her hair.)
(She's running as fast as she can
among the tall and lean girls.)
(Screaming)
(She fell down
and went out of the frame.)
- Are you okay?
- Hey, Ju Bin.
(What was that?)
Oh, dear.
- Are you okay?
- Hey, Ju Bin.
(Please leave me alone.)
(Meanwhile,
E Hyun picked Jong Kook.)
(Yeo Jin picked Kwang Soo.)
(Ji Eun picked Suk Jin.)
- Wait.
- Ju Bin.
(Ju Bin successfully picked
her best choice Se Chan.)
- Did you see that?
- Oh, yes.
(Please pretend you didn't
see anything.)
- She used the falling technique.
- I've never seen that before.
It's as if she died on the street.
Ju Bin, are you...
- Are you okay?
- I've never seen anyone who fell...
She's not athletic at all.
- Why did that happen?
- I don't know. She fell like this.
(She's not athletic at all.)
Did you all pick the person
you wanted?
- Ji Eun, what about you?
- No.
- Did you pick the one you wanted?
- She's too honest.
(As Ji Eun answered firmly,
Suk Jin is disappointed.)
Did you pick the one you wanted?
- Fortunately, I did.
- Did you?
- Okay.
- You picked the one you wanted?
(She sounded happy to pick me.
I'm so excited.)
- Se Chan...
- You picked the one you wanted?
- Yes, I did.
- E Hyun, what about you?
- I picked the one I wanted.
- Okay.
All right. It's my turn.
I have never seen anyone...
- She fell really hard.
- I've been doing this for 10 years,
- I've never seen anyone like her.
- Exactly.
I've never seen that kind of
reaction before.
It must be a memorable moment
for her.
I have made my decision.
I'll join Ju Bin's team.
(What did you say?)
Ju Bin, please pick me.
- Why?
- You're dead meat.
Go away!
- Pick me, Ju Bin.
- She's going to come between them.
- Don't do that.
- Oh, to come between them?
All right. Are you ready?
(Now, it's time for the race
for the last four.)
- Dance.
- Oh, yes!
(As the dance time began again,)
(the predator of the dance world
started dancing.)
Dance together.
(E Hyun feels uncomfortable.)
(Even Yeo Jin's friend feels
uncomfortable to dance with her.)
- They should dance individually...
- We can't do it that way.
because the others are
intimidated by Yeo Jin.
- I won't dance this time.
- That's okay. You can dance.
- Let's start with E Hyun.
- Each of you will dance alone.
- Play some music.
- Woo Jung as in friendship.
Here goes Woo Jung.
- Here we go!
- That's great.
I haven't danced in a long time.
(She started dancing
the old-fashioned dance move.)
- Really?
- What's that move?
That's an old-fashioned dance move.
Next up is Yeo Jin.
- She's an instructor.
- Yes, she is.
She's a great dancer.
- She's like Poseidon.
- She's amazing.
- Poseidon?
- She's just like Poseidon.
- She's scary.
- Next up is Ji Eun.
That's an old-fashioned way
of dancing.
(This dance move can make
your blind date a success.)
What's that?
(The whistle was blown
right that moment.)
(She started running while dancing.)
Here we go.
Ju Bin is running fast.
(Ju Bin is leading
the race unexpectedly.)
(She redeemed herself
and picked up a flag.)
(She picked up the flag
of the eighth place?)
(So Min is on Ju Bin's team.)
Yes, she picked me as I asked.
- Finally.
- I'm surprised that Ju Bin...
- She picked So Min.
- picked So Min.
Why did you pick
the worst member to team up with?
She asked me to pick her.
Se Chan. Se Chan.
(Yeo Jin picked Jae Suk.
E Hyun picked Haha.)
(Ji Eun picked Ji Hyo.
Ju Bin picked So Min.)
- Why did you pick So Min?
- Yang Se Chan!
- I'm so tired.
- We're in trouble.
- I can't swear at her.
It's over here.
I only trust you.
- Okay, good.
- I only trust you.
I only trust you.
- I'm Ju Bin's avatar today.
- Okay. Let's see it.
We're in trouble if Yeo Jin is...
- the team leader.
- This is it?
- We're in trouble.
- My team is just perfect.
Are you all satisfied
with your team?
- Yes.
Today is episode one of...
the Jeju Island Special:
Wind, Woman, Rock, and Bomb.
What is that again?
Everyone will choose
one card each in secret.
The team that collects
one card each of the three things...
that represent Jeju Island,
wind, women, and rocks will win.
- We must collect one card each.
- Is that so?
The team that has the bomb card
will receive a penalty.
- We need to remove it.
- After a moment,
you will choose one card each.
There are two cards each
of the wind, a woman, and a rock.
5 cards are blank,
and 1 card is the bomb.
- One card?
- Yes.
Ultimately, a team will win
if they collect...
one card each
of the wind, a woman, and a rock.
If there aren't any teams
who accomplish that,
the team that collects the most
cards regardless what card will win.
We will give you the chance to
exchange cards through missions.
- We'll start drawing cards.
- Okay.
- We can start with this team.
- Let's go.
We have a better chance.
Gosh, Se Chan!
- He's leading.
- Okay, choose one each.
Se Chan is all the rage these days.
Try choosing one each.
Everyone, come this way.
Didn't Se Chan choose the same card?
(Se Chan, Wind)
Keep a straight face.
Okay, wait a minute.
Pretend that it's the bomb.
Okay? You should pretend
that it's the bomb.
(So Min, Woman)
I know.
We don't have the bomb, right?
- I'll start first.
- Se Chan.
(Suk Jin, Rock.
Ji Hyo and Ji Eun, Unrevealed)"
(The other teams also continue
to choose cards.)
- You're okay, right?
- Yes.
(Kwang Soo, Woman.
Jae Suk and Yeo Jin, Unrevealed)
(Haha, Rock.
Jong Kook and E Hyun, Unrevealed)
We'll move to the first mission
location now.
3 people will move at once,
and the spots are divided into 2.
- Really?
- The first keyword is "meat".
The second keyword is "seafood".
- We should go to "seafood".
- It's Jeju Island.
Jeju Island is famous for its
seafood. Meat is also famous, but...
- We'll choose "meat".
- It's obviously famous for meat.
- It's meat.
- It's meat unconditionally.
- It's Korean pork.
- If so,
we'll move
to the first mission location.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Nice!
I'll put it in my bag for you.
Honestly, it's likely
that our team won't lose.
- Of course not.
- I'll tilt my seat back a little.
- Yes, there's a lot of space.
Just tilt it a little!
- You said you would tilt a little!
- Gosh, this is...
You told me to tilt it back!
I just split my legs straight now.
Why is the tallest person
sitting in the back?
Why are you making me uncomfortable
by sitting in the back?
Everything will be over
if we eat perch today.
- Isn't perch expensive?
- They're expensive.
- Okay.
- They're the most expensive fish.
- I don't think that's true.
I just said one word.
Did the two of you take sides
to bully Kwang Soo again?
Kwang Soo isn't a fool.
Gosh.
I'm telling you one more time.
Kwang Soo isn't a fool.
- There's no need. It's obvious.
- That's right.
Doesn't his face look like
a type of fish?
Yes, he looks like a type of fish.
- You also look like fish.
- Isn't that right?
You kind of look like a rockfish.
A rockfish?
- We look like fish.
- Jae Suk looks like an anchovy.
- Anchovy.
That's perfect.
He looks like an anchovy.
How could you say I look like
an anchovy?
- Kwang Soo is...
- Yeo Jin kind of looks like...
- a halibut.
- A halibut is...
- That's not it.
- Do you want to...
- I'm just asking you.
- You're making a lot of mistakes.
You kind of look like one.
- Say something that looks pretty.
- Se Chan.
You could say mermaids.
- That's right.
- How could you call her a halibut?
Mermaids?
- Poseidon.
- I said, "Poseidon".
- Poseidon is cool at least.
- Yes, Poseidon.
- Poseidon is human.
- There are so many cool things...
- in the sea.
- That's right.
Please don't try to grab
me by the collar, Yeo Jin.
So Min kind of looks like
a kissing gourami.
- A kissing gourami.
- A kissing gourami without a mate.
She's lonely.
- No, I'm a doctor fish.
- Yes.
- A doctor fish?
- I will gnaw everything off.
- She will gnaw everything off.
- A doctor fish suits you.
What suits Ju Bin? Ju Bin is...
What do I look like?
- Nemo.
- Nemo?
- Why am I the only cute one?
- Is she Nemo?
- Really?
- That's fortunate.
- I thought she looked like a carp.
- A carp?
Nemo suits her well.
- Yes.
- If so...
Say things like that out loud.
- No, it's okay.
- What did you say?
Se Chan just said this shyly.
"Nemo? That suits her well."
- I told him to say that out loud.
- Don't say that out loud.
(She suddenly turns around.)
Hey, Yeo Jin.
- Why are you so angry?
- No...
- Why are you angry?
- You're treating us differently.
- That's not it.
- Yeo Jin, please scold him.
I'm already hot as it is
after coming to Jeju Island.
- Stop that.
- Yeo Jin.
- So Min was just teasing me.
- Today's team atmosphere is...
Your responses for us are like
a hot and cold tub.
It's nice that Yeo Jin is
fighting about everything for us.
I'm not afraid of Jong Kook today.
Okay, I will protect you.
We might beat Jong Kook
with Yeo Jin.
I think she will beat him.
They must be giving us seafood
right next to the sea.
This must be it.
"Jeju's seafood rice"
Is there something called
"seafood rice"?
- It sounds good.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- Cold raw fish soup.
- Gosh.
- It's really windy.
- Hello.
- We should sit by teams.
General Yeo Jin, sit there.
- You should sit at the end.
- Sit in the middle.
- Will Ju Bin sit there?
- Yes.
Sit there.
Am I the only man today?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(His cheeks are rising
since he's treated as the center.)
I'll tell you the menu that will be
the prize of the first mission.
- What is it?
- First,
there will be all kinds of
fresh raw fish.
(We will start with all kinds of
fresh raw fish.)
- We must eat raw fish.
- Assorted raw fish.
(You can smell the sea
from the assorted raw fish dish.)
Sea urchin roe.
(Savory sea urchin roe)
- It's my favorite.
- I really like sea urchin roe.
- I really like it.
- Grilled abalones.
(Tender grilled abalones)
Grilled tile fish.
(Grilled tile fish that will wind up
in your mouth quickly)
- Sea urchin rice.
- Sea urchin rice?
Cold raw fish soup,
abalone sea urchin seaweed soup,
and top shell kalguksu.
Top shell kalguksu is good.
There is top shell kalguksu.
Do they have
all of those menus here?
- It's my favorite.
- Top shell kalguksu?
I don't know about the others,
but I'm going to eat
top shell kalguksu.
Are you going to give us everything?
- It's the winning team's advantage.
- Will we eat everything?
- The winning...
- Only the winning team can eat?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- This is too harsh.
- We're going to be in trouble.
- Let's win.
- I want to eat sea urchin roe.
The losing team will receive some,
but there won't be as many as this.
- The first mission is...
- Yes?
important to keep your cool.
It's Is Jenga the Reason
Why My Hands are Shaking?
Representatives of each team
will play Jenga 1 on 1.
You will attach a low-frequency
therapeutic apparatus...
on your wrist and hand.
You will pile Jenga blocks in turn,
and the team that makes it
fall down first will lose.
The team that gets two wins
first will win.
We won't be able to do it because
our hands are shaking.
My hands are already shaking
without the apparatus.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- I don't like that. I'm afraid.
- What am I going to do?
Okay. The winning team can check
the cards of their opposing team.
- What?
- We can check the cards.
Next, they can exchange
up to two cards if they want.
- Okay.
- We can also exchange cards.
- Up to two cards?
- Yes.
- Yes, up to 2 cards.
- 2 cards.
Who will be the first representative
of each team?
(Round 1 of Jenga
Kwang Soo versus Ju Bin)
We can't sit down.
- Ju Bin, you must win.
- Okay.
Ju Bin, do you usually
like to drink alcohol?
- Yes.
- Do you like to?
We're in trouble. She's going
to shake her hands a lot then.
What am I going to do?
(She's shaking a lot.)
Look at this!
- What is going on?
- Wait a minute.
This is too harsh.
(His pupils are expanded.)
But this makes you healthy.
- Isn't it right?
- Doesn't it hurt?
- It's therapy.
- It doesn't hurt.
I think this is kind of strange.
It feels refreshing in the end.
You should pile Jenga blocks
like that.
- I'm in trouble.
- Who starts first?
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
You can do it!
- What is that?
- Rock-paper-scissors
You can do it!
What is that?
- No...
- That's good.
- Ju Bin, you should start first.
- Should I?
You can do it.
- Wait a minute.
- We have to win.
- It won't last long.
- Wait a minute.
It's over the minute
you make it all down.
Are you going to take
the middle one out, Ju Bin?
- No.
- Take the one in the end out.
- You touched the one in the end.
- What?
- Can't you pick another block?
- It's over if you touch a block.
Take it out.
I think it will be safe.
But...
- But this is...
- No...
- There's a time limit.
- It's over.
- Nice.
Pile it up strangely.
(She succeeds at taking
a block out safely.)
Hey...
- Hey...
- Be careful.
- Is it possible to do this?
- Of course, it's possible.
- It's possible.
- Is it possible?
- It's possible in Jenga.
- Yes.
Okay.
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, your hand won't shake
if you concentrate.
Kwang Soo, concentrate.
You can do it!
Just take it out, Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo, just take it out.
- Oh, my.
- Just take it out.
- Pile it on top.
My hands keep shaking.
You know what will happen
if you drop it, right?
You're really frustrating.
- Kwang Soo.
- Oh, my.
(He succeeded at taking a block
out after many twists and turns.)
Will you pile it like that?
- Will you pile it like that?
- No.
- Kwang Soo...
- Are you going to quit?
Kwang Soo,
look into my eyes clearly.
(Emergency eye contact time)
- She grabbed him by his collar.
- I will pile it properly this time.
Kwang Soo, why can't you do that?
I will pile it properly.
Wait a minute,
what is your left hand doing?
- Gosh.
- Okay.
I will pile it quickly.
(What is your left hand doing?)
(The apparatus is on his right hand.
He's playing with his left hand.)
Wait a minute,
what is your left hand doing?
(He got caught by doing
tricks with his hands.)
- Okay.
- Using your left hand is cheating.
- I'm sorry.
- His left hand is even shaking!
- Hey...
- He's tricking our eyes.
Don't try to fool our eyes.
(The Jenga shark is even acting
out low-frequency now.)
(I can't believe him!)
I fell for it.
You shouldn't trick our eyes.
(He does it this time
without tricking their eyes.)
Go.
(He succeeds.)
- Good.
- Right now...
- Okay.
- Take number 38 out.
- You should take that out.
- We don't have any time left.
- Ju Bin.
- Ju Bin, your hands are shaking.
- That's it!
- Yes!
Ju Bin, piling it on top is
important.
- We don't have any time left.
- Just pile it.
You can do it.
Let's just end it the next round.
Let's just end it here.
- There's no need to shake. Just go.
- Okay.
- That's it. Good job.
- Ju Bin, you can't do that.
Do it gently.
- You can do it.
- You can't do that.
If number 38 falls down,
it will be over.
- It really will be over.
- That's right.
- Ju Bin, that will be the end.
- Concentrate.
- You can do it.
- Ju Bin.
The problem won't be solved
just because you concentrate.
- He just won't stop.
- Concentrate.
It's not all about concentration.
- Don't pay attention to him.
- That's...
- He's so annoying.
- Oh, my.
- Good job.
- Stay still.
- That's it.
- Okay.
- It's over now.
- It's over.
- Please end it.
- Kwang Soo.
- I want to stop.
- It's over now.
- Kwang Soo.
But this is dangerous
because this block is...
- supporting everything up.
- You should start from the bottom.
That's right.
Kwang Soo also knows that.
He's not a fool.
Wait a minute, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, I told you to
do it with your right hand.
- Is he doing that again?
- Don't do that!
(His bad hand trick relapsed.)
(So Min didn't even know it.)
Kwang Soo, I told you to
do it with your right hand.
(Is he doing that again?)
- I almost fell for that.
- You should stop it.
- Kwang Soo, your acting is so good.
- Jae Suk.
- Thank you.
- We keep falling for that.
- I had no idea.
- He shook his hand.
I didn't know.
He shook his left hand so well.
- It just seemed right.
- He acts really well.
Kwang Soo, you can do this
if you stay focused.
- You can do it.
- Okay.
Good. You should stop
pulling pranks now.
Kwang Soo has got the hang of it.
It's not easy.
Kwang Soo, if you put it
on there, you'll win.
(She stays close to him
to distract him.)
So Min. Stay still unless you want
Yeo Jin to slap you in the face.
Yeo Jin can slap you.
Look at her. She raised her hand.
Hey!
Don't hold it. If you touch
the block at the bottom,
(Will Kwang Soo be able
to put the block on it?)
- you will lose.
- It's done. Kwang Soo did it.
- Kwang Soo did it.
- Oh no.
(Kwang Soo failed.)
- Fail.
Okay.
- It's 1 to 0.
- Yes.
- Ju Bin, good job.
- Thank you.
- We have to win this time.
- Let's move on.
If you win the next round,
you will be the winner.
- That's great.
- All right, Yeo Jin.
- Yes.
- You have to win.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Poseidon.
Get into the sea
after winning this game, okay?
- You can't lose.
- Good luck.
- She's so charismatic.
- Okay. I'll go first.
- Hang on, Yeo Jin.
- Why?
(Hang on, Yeo Jin.)
(Time out)
Why?
What?
- He turned it off, right?
- It's turned off.
(He turned off the device secretly.)
It's not turned on.
- You punk. Come here.
- You know what?
- I can't believe this.
- They were shaking differently.
Don't make it too strong.
As a penalty,
make it one level higher.
- Increase it.
- Gosh, it's too strong. Lower it.
A little more.
This is off.
Jae Suk, it's too strong.
It's just too strong.
- It's too much.
- Okay.
- It's too powerful.
- I'm sorry. Okay.
- Okay.
- Will you be nice then?
I'll be nice. I swear.
- You should be nice.
- I'll be loyal.
- Be nice. Behave yourself.
- I will. Okay.
- It's done.
- I guess it's strong.
Will you date So Min or not?
- Will you date her or not?
- I'll just do as you say.
- I'll do as I'm told.
- Will you date So Min?
I'll do whatever you say.
- Say sorry to So Min.
- I'm sorry.
It's all my fault. I'm so sorry.
Behave yourself, okay?
- I want to keep this.
- It's level four.
I want this.
It was strong.
(They want to have an instrument
of power like this.)
Yeo Jin isn't shaking
her hand a lot. She seems fine.
I know how to do this.
This is fun.
- Good.
- What do I do?
You can't pick it up like that.
(A delinquent hand)
- Yeo Jin.
- You should pick it up like this.
Don't do that.
- Yeo Jin.
- You can just pick it like this.
- But this is too...
- Do whatever you want.
You can do whatever you want.
(She cups her hand
and tries it again.)
(Petty)
(Her fingers look petty
when they're put together.)
This is quite unique.
It looks like a duck.
This is really strong.
- She overcame it.
- I did it.
- She did it.
- Se Chan, show us what you can do.
- I will.
- Okay.
- Let's eat.
- Se Chan.
This will end soon.
Once he fails, it's over.
- Once he fails, it's over.
- Okay.
What? It will be over.
- So Min.
- Be careful.
Do it right.
- It might collapse.
- Gosh, this is...
Se Chan, you're really bad at this.
Touch it lightly.
(Groaning)
- That's for Yeo Jin.
- I'm sorry, Yeo Jin.
- I'm really sorry.
- Hey!
- That's for Yeo Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm really sorry.
- I can't believe this.
Hey, you did it to Yeo Jin.
- Hey!
- I really didn't know.
(She felt a twinge
at an unexpected moment.)
- It hurt so much.
- I really didn't know.
Just hurry.
I will overpower
the high-frequency waves.
- I should overpower it.
- It's low frequency.
Is it low frequency?
- High frequency?
- Why did you point that out?
- I didn't know.
- Hey, Se Chan.
If it were high frequency,
you would've died.
Ju Bin is surprised.
Se Chan.
It's over.
It's almost over.
Oh no.
(Se Chan failed.)
Fail.
It's done. It's over.
- I can't do this.
- I can beat So Min.
- Okay.
- We can still win.
Watch me. I'll win with my
mental and physical strength.
Show us.
This is stronger than you think.
Don't worry, Yeo Jin.
This is the final round.
So Min, let's eat.
- This is hard.
- Good luck.
It's okay. You can do this.
Jae Suk, you can eat
top shell kalguksu.
Right. There's also sea urchin roe
and grilled abalone.
- You can do this.
- That's my favorite.
Above all things,
- I'll eat top shell kalguksu.
- Jae Suk, let's just do this.
- Watch me.
- Are you holding out?
- Sure.
- It's not turned off yet.
(He was bluffing
while the device was off.)
This hurts a lot. It really hurts.
- Is this right?
- It hurts when it's strong.
It will hurt if I do this.
But this is fine. This is okay.
- This is okay.
- This is fine, right?
- It hurts when it's stronger.
- It will be about this.
Stretch out your hand. Okay.
It will be like this.
- Gosh.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
It just happened before I knew it.
- I accept that.
- You know what it is.
It doesn't feel like your hand
because of the low frequency.
- It hurts.
- Just do it, So Min.
Why does it hurt so much?
It's really painful.
That's right. So Min, well done.
- Slow down.
- It hurts so much.
- Good.
- She's really good.
Nice. This is good enough
for the final round.
It hurts so much.
He's holding out.
(It's the low frequency
boaster's turn.)
- Put it on.
- It's hard to put it on.
This is all about mental strength.
It's no big deal to me.
It's hard now. Look.
He can't put it on there.
He overcame the low frequency,
but he's shaking out of fear.
- That's the only explanation.
- He's shaking his hand.
- Because of the cameras.
- See?
- I'm sure we're going to eat.
- We have to eat.
That's right. Good.
Good. So Min, well done.
Once you get through this...
- You'll overcome it.
- Watch me.
I'll overcome it.
- I'll do it right away.
- He can't overcome it.
It's shaking.
We don't know it yet.
Okay. It's done.
So Min, what's hard
is to put the block on it.
It feels horrible.
(He should put the block
on the Jenga tower.)
I think it's hard.
Jae Suk doesn't shake
his hand a lot. He overcame it.
He's shaking. Bounce.
(If Jae Suk fails,
Team Ju Bin wins right away.)
- He's focused.
- Gosh.
Gosh, he has good concentration.
(It's breathtaking.)
It's almost time.
Let's move on to Part Two.
- Already?
- Is it too early?
No? Isn't it time yet?
- What?
- It's too early.
(Running Man Part 2
will start a while later.)
Drop it.
(After taking a break,)
(he manages to put
the block on the tower.)
It's done.
- So Min. This is it.
- It's over.
It's taking a long time
because it's the final round.
- You can do this.
- Just do it.
- I want sea urchin roe.
- Make it short.
- She better fail.
- Keep the balance.
It's falling down.
- It's falling down.
(She put it vertically again.)
Stay still. We did it.
(They are getting extremely excited
with the unstable Jenga tower.)
Look at you. You must be nervous.
(Extremely nervous)
Kwang Soo is shaking
his hands. Good.
Hey. It shouldn't be so easy anyway.
Let's do this.
I'm so distressed.
It's really painful.
Hang on. Wait, Jae Suk.
(Hang on. Wait, Jae Suk.)
Hang on a second.
- What is this?
- What?
(A toothbrush case?)
Why did you put it in here?
- My hand was shaking.
- This is...
(A while ago)
so easy anyway.
(He took the wire
off the device...)
(and connected it
to his toothbrush case.)
(Then he shook his hand himself.)
I can do it this way.
This isn't the device.
This is a toothbrush case.
Why did you do that?
Jae Suk, when I unplugged it,
you started shaking your hand.
That's teamwork. It's good teamwork.
He says it's teamwork.
They are unbelievable.
Jae Suk is so good at this.
Good.
It will be over
once he puts it on the tower.
This is the hard part.
Wait. Are you sure
the device is working?
- It is.
- He's overcoming it.
Okay. It's working.
He overcame it.
(Groaning)
- What was that?
- He shows off his strength.
He's showing it off
against the low frequency.
(He fights against
the low frequency.)
It will be over once he places it.
You should pray, Se Chan.
It's over.
You can't use your body like that.
Leave him be.
You know how it will turn out.
- He might push it.
- It will collapse anyway.
- It will crumble away.
- Hang on.
I should do it as slow as I can.
- Gosh.
- Yes!
(Jae Suk failed.)
Fail.
We will enjoy the food.
(So Min wins the final round.)
(Team Ju Bin gets to eat
the Jeju Island seafood.)
- Team Ju Bin wins.
- Okay.
- Bring in the food.
- You're the best.
Well done. So Min, you were amazing.
She's been playing
board games a lot.
What?
- This is beautiful.
- My goodness.
I have a question.
Should I carry this around?
- Yes.
- But don't show it to others.
- Okay.
- Be careful around Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo? Why?
- And be careful around So Min.
So Min is dangerous.
Tell us about So Min.
I bet she's talking about you now.
I'm sure she talked
behind your back, Ji Eun.
- Really?
- Did you have...
- any problems with her back then?
- Me?
You two were friends, but you
weren't so excited to see her.
I know.
I think there's a secret
between you two.
I'm sure there's something.
She holds a grudge.
Earlier today,
she said I was dirty, right?
- No. She didn't say that.
- What did she say?
(Earlier today, she said
I was dirty, right?)
(Her memory is distorted.)
What did she say?
- It wasn't clean.
- Our relationship wasn't clean?
She said it wasn't clean,
but it's become dirty.
"Ji Eun is dirty."
This is what she remembers.
It's not easy to say such a thing
about your friend.
- It's not easy.
- Gosh, this is hard.
I'm serious.
Actually, when there was
a group date,
our seniors decided
who should go on the date.
They were like, "You, you,
and you will go on the date."
- Really?
- And So Min and I got picked a lot.
- Your seniors decided it.
- They picked the best ones.
If I did something on the date,
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't mean to be like that.
What can I do...
- when that's what they said?
- Right.
(She does a 180.)
(It's her fault for being
too popular.)
Right? It's not like...
I told them to choose me.
- No, right?
- But So Min could think that...
you flirted in a way.
To be honest,
this is how I remember it.
My relationship with So Min
boils down...
to her having...
a victim mentality.
(So Min has a victim mentality.)
(Victim mentality?)
(The bait caught
the biggest fish yet.)
Gosh, that's harsh.
That's what I believe.
Also, there's something...
quite complicated
between So Min and me...
regarding a good friend of mine.
(She took the bait.)
Is that friend a man or a woman?
- A man, no, a woman.
- It's a woman.
- So a woman...
- A man got in between them.
That's right.
And I was kind of stuck in between.
- You couldn't take one's side.
- Right.
When splitting into groups...
- Was that too mean?
- Who?
- Was I too mean?
- Of course not.
- So Min thinks she's a victim.
- It could happen.
Yes, exactly.
(No, that's not what I meant.)
Guys, seriously?
Gosh, this is hilarious.
- This isn't how it should be.
- An old friend of mine...
- Is this the place? Looks tasty.
- I bet it's delicious.
This is what you'd expect
at Jeju Island.
Check out the names
of the buildings.
(Where local food of Jeju
is served!)
(A place where you can
experience the old Jeju)
We're here at the Commission
Agency Site of Kim Man Deok.
- The first mission...
- Yes?
Teamwork will be key...
in this game
of I Can't Hear Your Voice.
I Can't Hear Your Voice?
You'll be given 100 seconds each.
Two chosen members
will put on headphones.
One will describe the word
while one answers.
A total of four rounds
will be played.
The team with the most
correct answers will win.
Please note that
you can't directly name the word.
- The winning team...
- Yes?
will be able to see
a card of their choice...
and receive a chance
to swap their cards twice.
- Twice?
- Twice.
Three servings of a meal
will be served...
while the losing team...
- only gets one.
- A single serving?
- That's mean of you.
- No way.
The name of our team...
- is 1, 2, 3.
- Why?
- He has 1 child, she has 2,
- I have 2.
- while I have 3.
- 3.
- 1, 2, 3.
(He just accepts it.)
We'll call ourselves
Victim Mentality.
That's our team name.
No way.
- Victim Mentality.
- Mentality!
(Victim Mentality!)
How hilarious.
Let's do this!
I'll try and guess the word.
Ji Hyo, you should stand over here.
- Okay.
- That's a good one.
You can't point out
the number of syllables.
How about this then?
(Nod your head instead.)
(Okay.)
I bet it's loud.
- It's really loud.
- Here we go.
Ready, get set, go.
(Macaron)
The most expensive item...
at coffee shops.
- Expensive?
- You're insane?
- A dessert...
- A sort of cake.
The most expensive dessert!
The most expensive cake.
- A snack.
- What?
A...
A snack.
- A snack!
- An expensive one.
- An expensive one?
- Yes.
Squid-peanut Balls!
No, it's round.
(Squid-peanut Balls
are most expensive to Jong Kook.)
- What...
- How is that expensive?
It's a round-shaped snack.
Homerun Balls?
An expensive snack.
- Homerun Balls?
- A snack?
- He must really not eat snacks.
- An expensive one?
Is it round? Onion Rings?
- Pass.
- I'll pass.
Pass.
- I like how frugal he is.
- Snacks that women like?
- Pass!
- This is a tricky one.
When driving...
When joining the military?
The military?
- This is fun.
- A car!
A car.
The Let's Play app?
(The Let's Play app)
(The GPS system led him
to a lodging establishment.)
- The Let's Play app?
- Are we advertising it?
- That's what she said.
- What?
The Let's Play app.
(The Let's Play app)
When you're driving a car...
You're driving.
- A towel?
- Yes, that.
- When driving...
- Right, a towel.
It shows you the way.
On our cellphones.
- Cellphones.
- Cellphones!
The T Map app.
- The T Map app?
- The T Map app!
(Welcome to the world
of indirect advertisements.)
- What was that?
- A map. A map!
- A see-saw?
- Yes, a map.
A map you need when driving.
Driving, see-saw...
- A map you need when driving.
- Yes, while driving.
- Tell him the number of syllables.
- That's not allowed.
You'll pass.
- This...
- Hey!
You'll probably get this one.
Pyongyang or Hamhung?
(Naengmyeon)
- Park Myung Soo.
- After eating!
Park Myung Soo.
Park Myung Soo!
After eating.
Jessica.
(Pondering)
What you eat in the summer.
- What you eat.
- Yes.
- Noodles.
- Patbingsu?
Noodles.
- What?
- In the summer.
- The summer.
- That's right.
- What you eat.
- What you eat!
- Naengmyeon.
- Naengmyeon!
(She said it loud and clear.)
(She was so frustrated
that she said it out loud.)
You can't just say it!
Your time is up.
- This...
- Hold on.
Is it over?
- I mean...
- I was completely clueless.
- Just the words...
- Not without any gestures.
- Especially without any gestures.
- I see.
It's impossible to know.
- Naengmyeon.
- Hold on though.
Jong Kook, have you never
had any snacks before?
How can an expensive snack...
- be Squid-peanut Balls?
- But...
Squid-peanut Balls
and Homerun Balls.
I couldn't make any of it out.
I'll describe the word.
Ready, get set,
go!
(Ceiling price)
Shares. Stocks!
Army doctor.
Stocks.
- That's right.
- Shares.
- Soldier.
- Nice!
The stock price...
is going up.
- Going up!
- Don't.
- You can't do that.
- The frustration gets to you.
- A soldier goes up.
- Yes, the stock price goes up.
Say that in another way.
A soldier goes up.
- An airplane.
- An airplane...
- An airplane?
- She's very one-dimensional.
The opposite of floor price.
- A soldier.
- Shares!
- From what I can tell...
- The price goes up!
- Say it again.
- She doesn't know much.
The stock price goes up.
What do you call that?
I doubt she knows what this is.
- Hey!
- Just move on to the next one.
- Pass.
- This is probably new to her.
Pass.
- Pass.
- This is an easy one.
Hang glider...
It's over. We're moving on.
- The next one.
- We're moving on.
- Look at her expression.
- What?
- We're moving on.
(Why can't you move on?)
- We're... Yes, we'll pass.
- Pass!
- It's already been done.
- Pass...
It's been done.
Gosh, this is frustrating.
At the sea...
- Pass.
- In the sea...
Can't we pass?
We already did!
- In the sea...
- Can't we pass?
(It's impossible to
communicate with her.)
(She's the only one
that hasn't moved on.)
We already moved on.
- Got it.
- We're on to the next one!
Okay.
They go into the sea...
Abalones...
What? Jjamppong?
Abalones.
- Abalones.
- Abalones!
- Oh, I know.
Haenyeo!
(She answers haenyeo correctly.)
That's right.
(Tattoo)
(Tattoo?)
The people of Hongdae area.
(The people of Hongdae area)
(The people of Hongdae area
are attacked.)
(Choking)
- Rooftop?
- The people of Hongdae area.
- What?
Why not just say
the Korean word "munshin"?
Alone?
A dragon on one's back.
- A dragon?
- Yes, dragon.
A dragon that's drawn on the body.
- A dragon?
- A dragon that's drawn on the body.
(Buffering)
- A dragon.
- Swearing?
- Yes, a dragon.
- She thinks it's swearing.
- Your time's up.
- Swearing?
- Gosh.
- What a relief.
- I'm so glad.
- Just you wait.
We'll end it for sure in this round.
(Haha and Jong Kook are up next.)
Why else would I
have chosen these two?
- Okay, good.
- They're the best.
- All right.
- Hold on.
Are you ready?
- And go.
- They'll dominate for sure.
(Pork cutlet)
- Our restaurant!
- Yes?
You and I.
- Yes, you and I.
- What do we sell?
What do we sell?
- Pork cutlet.
- Yes!
(They easily get one right.)
I didn't expect them to
get it right.
Pororo.
(Penguin)
Pororo. The animal.
What am I?
Two syllables.
Haha? Haroro.
- Haroro.
The animal? Penguin!
(Penguin is correct.)
(They take the lead
with two correct answers.)
This one seems tricky.
(Ilchwiweoljang)
(He's weak when it comes
to four-syllable idioms.)
- I...
- You?
(4 syllables)
I've improved.
A four-syllable idiom.
I've suddenly...
He has suddenly improved.
I've, you know...
I'm the bomb now.
(He's trying to explain
what ilchwiweoljang means.)
I didn't expect this either,
- but I'm the bomb now.
- A superpower?
Four syllables.
- A four-syllable word?
- Your time's up.
(Time over)
He almost understood
"ilchwiweoljang" though.
Why don't you two give it a shot?
Was "ilchwiweoljang"
a word I needed to guess?
Ilchwiweoljang? Seriously?
You have to do well
in order to eat lunch.
It won't be easy though.
Ready,
get set, go.
(Nucksal)
- Goodness.
- Oh, dear.
A rapper!
- He's a rapper.
- A rapper.
He has thick skin.
(Nucksal means to have thick skin?)
- A rapper?
- He has thick skin.
- What on earth?
- Thick legs?
- His skin.
- His foot.
(He's fascinated)
- Look at her expression.
- Horse?
Moon.
(Pondering)
- Horse?
- What's with her expression?
(Two syllables)
- Horse?
- Look at her expression.
(She takes a note
out of Haha's book.)
What on earth is she doing?
A rapper who talks well?
- Two syllables!
- She's copying Haha's strategy.
(Copying Haha's strategy
results in...)
- Two syllables?
- Yes.
(She was able to tell Ji Hyo
that it's a two-syllable word.)
This is what I like.
(This is what I like.)
(This is what she likes?)
- This is what she likes.
- She must like Nucksal.
(They finally understand
what she's saying.)
- The rapper!
- Rapper.
It's a name.
- Name.
- "It's a name."
- A name. A rapper's name.
- Name?
- "It's a name."
- A rapper's name.
A rapper is what?
- No, it's a rapper and...
- A rapper and...
She's so desperate.
- This is crazy.
- She's so funny.
- She's...
- Sit down when you talk.
- This is good.
- Good?
(Frustrating)
Just pass.
- Move on.
- The next one.
(Pass!)
(Repayment of a kindness
even after one's death.)
(It's an old saying.)
- Moving on to the next.
- She doesn't know what it means.
You know this one, right?
Don't know this one either?
- Jeju Island.
Famous rice cake!
(Jeju Island! Famous! Rice cake!)
Just talk slowly.
- She doesn't know what it is.
- Jeju Island's...
- She doesn't know.
- Jeju Island? Say it again.
1, 2...
(How many syllables?
Four syllables.)
- Rice cake!
- We won't be able to have dinner.
Say goodbye to the food.
Jeju Island's rice cake.
Jeju Island's rice cake?
Omegi rice cake!
(Correct. Omegi rice cake)
(Now it's a tie!)
- Come on. You're doing great.
- I'm sure she knows this one.
Just get one more correct answer.
(Olle Trail)
- 1, 2, 3.
- Olle Trail. Her face is red.
It's on Jeju Island.
- It's on Jeju Island.
- This one is easy.
It's a trail!
It's a rail on Jeju Island?
KT!
- Gosh, KT?
- KT.
- Why? Did you hear it?
- She won't get it.
- KT!
- She won't understand.
- Don't do that. Don't do that.
- A famous trail in Jeju.
- On Jeju Island.
It's famous in Jeju. It's KT!
- KT is famous in Jeju?
- In Jeju Island!
Three syllables!
A taxi is what?
- Jeju Island!
- Taxi fare?
You should move on to the next.
- Pass.
- All right.
(Acting cute)
(Aing!)
(Using her whole body
to express what it is.)
What do you call this?
(Ang!)
- This is weird.
- It's weird that she got that.
- You don't know this?
- What is this called?
Acting cute.
(The whole explanation
is one-dimensional.)
- It's about how you act.
- Action?
- Action.
(Just trying to act cute
as much as she can.)
Acting cute.
(That is correct.
Act charming)
(Finally got the correct answer)
(Turned the table but 3 to 2)
Okay, time's up.
- You are...
- One day?
- Right now.
You're wearing it.
- You should stop.
- You're wearing it.
- She's good.
- It took longer than I expected.
- Good, good, good.
- Excuse me?
He said we won. We won.
(Now she finds out they won.)
- She turned it around at the end.
- Ji Eun.
When this episode is released,
- other variety shows will want you.
- Great.
- Too bad you lost.
- Gosh.
Here is the result
of the first mission.
Ji Eun's team can choose a member
to check a card.
You should decide
which one's card you want to check.
Do we swap cards
with the one they pick?
It's up to them.
- They'll take it if they like it.
- They can choose not to take it?
- They won't if they don't like it.
- Oh, I get it.
- Then we will...
- What card are you holding?
- Your card.
- If you want to know,
you have to pick mine.
She's unusual.
Did you really think
he would tell you that?
E Hyun, are you holding
a useful card?
- Your card.
- Mine is a bomb.
- It's a bomb?
- Yes.
She doesn't mean that
it's literally a bomb, right?
Shall we check E Hyun's card?
We'll check So E Hyun's card!
- We'll check So E Hyun's card.
- So E Hyun.
- Show us.
- So E Hyun, show them your card.
They can check your card
just like that?
I guess they can.
Mine really is a bomb.
(What kind of card
would So E Hyun have?)
(It's empty!)
I will make an exchange.
Yes, let's do that.
I'll make an exchange with Haha.
Song Ji Hyo wants to make
an exchange with Haha.
(Ji Hyo got Haha's rock card.)
(Suk Jin, Rock.
Ji Hyo and Ji Eun, Unrevealed)
(Ji Hyo, Rock.)
(What is on the card
that Haha received from Ji Hyo?)
(Jong Kook, Unrevealed.
E Hyun, Blank. Haha, Rock.)
(Haha, Unrevealed)
Now your meal will be served.
The winners get three servings.
The losers
will only get one serving.
Please serve the food.
(It's a feast of appetizing meat!)
Okay, this is why we're in Jeju.
- This looks really good.
- It's amazing.
- I'm so hungry.
- It looks delicious.
- My goodness.
- This is why it's called "Meat"?
The yukgaejang
is unbelievably delicious.
Yes, it's good.
(Sweet bracken yukgaejang,
dombe meat...)
(and noodle soup with pork)
This is dombe meat.
This one is dombe meat?
Before we serve you your meal,
you should exchange cards.
- Exchange cards.
- Should we pick one?
- Let's...
- Hey, it's obvious that...
Kwang Soo or Jae Suk has a bomb.
So we should make sure who that is.
Then should we pick Jae Suk's card?
Jae Suk's? Okay.
We made a decision.
- We'll check Jae Suk's card.
- Okay.
- Show us your card.
- Show them your card.
This goes very well
with Jeju Island.
- Oh, gosh.
- It's empty.
- Nothing's in it.
- No.
It's blank.
- It's blank.
- Nothing's in it.
Kwang Soo, what's yours? A rock?
A woman.
Did you just call Kwang Soo a rock?
Hey!
- No, I didn't mean it like that.
- What's wrong with that?
- You deliberately said that.
- What's wrong with saying "rock"?
He asked if I have a rock,
so what's wrong?
Let me get this straight.
- I'm okay. Don't make a big deal.
- Hey, you.
Don't you dare call Kwang Soo
a rock again.
- You just stay quiet.
- I don't care what he calls me.
- You watch your mouth.
- What wrong with that?
I straightened it out.
It was also funny
when he said he has a woman.
Since he has long hair.
A woman.
He's lying.
- Shall we?
- Tell us how your picks.
Well, we should try it.
- This is the first game.
- All right.
- We will make an exchange.
- Yes, we will.
Who will exchange with whom?
I will exchange with Kwang soo.
- Making one exchange?
- Yes.
- Please change your cards.
- Open it.
Gosh, it's wind.
(Not bad)
- Wait, it's a woman.
- It's a woman.
We told you honestly.
- Wait a minute.
- We knew you were being honest.
- This is good for both.
- Yes.
- Well, for us...
- Right? For her too.
Yes, you're right.
- It was a good exchange.
- I'm happy for both.
Now we will serve you your meal.
- It's hard to have a meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
- This is the meal?
- Gosh, it's abalone.
(A plate of assorted fresh sashimi)
It's amazing.
(Various kinds of seafood)
Look at the abalone.
It looks really delicious.
It looks really good.
- The smell.
- Smells good.
How is it?
- Is it good?
- Yes, it is.
The rice and sea urchin bowl is
nicely scorched at the bottom.
(Various kinds of seafood is making
him forget what to say.)
- Amazing.
- Can they have some too?
I don't think so.
Jae Suk.
- This is so good.
- It's rice with sea urchin roe.
It's really good.
Who can imitate an abalone?
(Imitate an abalone?)
What do we do about her?
- This is humiliating.
- How could she do this?
- This is ridiculous.
- Why aren't you giving us food?
- It's urchin and abalone.
- Come on. Imitate an abalone.
Cue!
- Here he goes.
- Imitate an abalone. Cue!
(Here's a wild abalone.)
There's an abalone.
Taste this. It's so good.
It's scorched nicely.
I won't let you humiliate me,
Jeon So Min.
The rice with sea urchin roe
is so good.
You think so?
It's time to choose the keywords
for the second mission.
The first word is "steal".
The second word is "take off".
(Which member will move
to which team?)
What is this?
- What is it?
- What's this?
Why is this "take off"?
Are we doing taekwondo?
They're taekwondo uniforms.
There are socks. Maybe we're
taking each other's socks off.
(An airplane zooms by
over their heads.)
(It's noisy because there's
an airport nearby.)
There are airplanes flying by
because there's an airport nearby.
An airplane flies by
every four minutes.
Really?
My goodness.
Jong Kook shouldn't be here.
- Who is it?
- Please let it be Suk Jin.
(They're all waiting for
Suk Jin to arrive.)
- Okay!
- That's it!
It's Jong Kook.
Can't you hear Haha?
Haha's here too.
Come on! You're all dead!
(Jong Kook, Haha, and E Hyun
have arrived!)
- So E Hyun.
- E Hyun's here.
- Jong Kook, gosh.
- I'm scared of her.
It's Jong Kook.
Gosh, it's Yeo Jin.
Yes, there she is.
(Hi, Yeo Jin.)
Gosh, I'm scared of her.
Hello.
Gosh, this sucks.
We're so dead.
- I'm so scared.
- Hey, you're here.
Gosh, what's with the uniform?
All of you chose
the word "take off".
Here's the second mission.
You have to take off
your opponent's clothes...
in order to gain points.
- Take off clothes?
- What?
(You have to take off your
opponent's clothes to win.)
(Take off their clothes?)
- Take off clothes?
- What?
- Are you serious?
- This is so one-dimensional.
- Seriously?
- It's so one-dimensional.
The second mission is called
Stake Your Life on a Single Match.
One member from each team
will fight one-on-one.
We're adopting the rules of judo.
If you take off your opponent's
pair of socks, you get a Yuko.
If you take the top uniform or
the bottom, you get a half-point.
If you get the name tag
under the uniform, you get a point.
(Full point)
(Two Yukos equals a half-point,
two half points equals a full point)
Two Yukos equals a half-point.
So if you get their socks
and a top, you get a full point.
Which male member
will go for the first round?
It depends on who
you're fighting against.
I'm sure anyone can win you.
So it doesn't matter who fights,
Kwang soo or me.
(Anyone can win me?)
You're the one who should
choose carefully.
I pick you.
(I pick you.)
(Jae Suk ignores him,
so he decides to be rude too.)
- He wants you.
- Just this once.
"I pick you."
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
- I'll fight Haha, you fight him.
- All right.
- Haha chose me, so I'll fight him.
- Okay, okay.
Let's go.
Of course, I'd be better for Haha.
My back hurts today.
Your back hurts?
- Yes, a little.
- Where?
Which part?
- Hey.
- Just let me see.
My goodness.
- This part?
- Go away.
This part?
(Punching)
(He really punched his back
when he said it hurt!)
How dare you!
- What's wrong with him?
- He says his back hurts.
Then should we focus on
punching him in the back?
I knew he wouldn't worry about me
but this is unbelievable.
I can't believe this.
Kwang Soo, what is that?
- I tied a knot.
- Gosh, that's really...
- unattractive.
- What?
Then how should I do it?
- Is it called "untie your knot"?
- He said it's unattractive.
Then should I tie this?
We're on the same team,
but you really are pathetic.
(Even his team members
think he's pathetic.)
Aren't you tired of it?
- It's really fun.
- It's really fun?
(He says it's fun.)
I thought you would be
really tired of yourself.
- Seriously.
- It's therapeutic.
Thank goodness.
Is it therapeutic for you?
I am glad that it's therapeutic.
You know the rules, right?
Let's begin.
(The first round)
Get ready.
Let's go!
We need to win no matter what.
(Jae Suk needs to win this round
no matter what.)
(Let's begin!)
(It's a match
between the weakest members.)
(They look weak from the start.)
(Who will be the weaker one?)
Is Haha drunk?
Seriously.
You didn't even budge.
(Whirring)
(An airplane passes over the arena.)
- You little...
- You...
(They swear at each other
while the audio gets drowned out.)
I can't hear you
over the sound of the airplane!
(What are they saying?)
(They continue to have
a private conversation.)
(They are fighters
who use their mouths, not bodies.)
(The airplane passes by...)
(and Haha aims for Jae Suk's sock.)
You got it!
(His back is wide open
as he reaches for Jae Suk's sock.)
Okay. You got it!
No! Guard your name tag!
(Jae Suk will get one full point
if he rips off the name tag.)
- No! Guard your name tag!
- Guard your name tag, Haha!
One full point!
(Jae Suk wins with one full point!)
(The weakest members' match ends
so fast...)
One full point!
(that it's embarrassing.)
He won with one full point!
(Dazed)
Does the game end
if the name tag gets removed?
(Incredulous)
(Their teammate is weaker
than they expected.)
- Isn't it about the socks?
- He didn't know.
- I didn't know.
This is about taking off clothes.
- One full point!
- Good!
- The man with one full point!
- Okay!
I had a really cool plan.
- Haha looked so stupid.
- Hold on.
- This match shouldn't count.
- He tried to lift me up.
This match shouldn't count.
I had a really cool plan.
- Okay.
- Haha loses with one full point.
- Hey!
- Okay!
- I was going to...
- All right!
I even swore
when the airplane flew by.
It took me more time
to change into these clothes.
- He didn't understand the rules.
- Seriously.
- Kwang Soo!
- All right.
I will do my best.
- Just do some damage to him.
- I might beat him.
For goodness' sake.
I am in a bad condition.
Jong Kook has a bad back today.
(He pretends to be worried.)
Don't overexert yourself.
This is bad.
Kwang Soo,
just do some damage to him.
Do your absolute best...
so that he is humiliated
even if you don't win.
- Okay?
- Okay, okay.
Just fold him in half.
Kwang Soo, that's your specialty.
(He will aim for Jong Kook's back.)
Jong Kook's back is hurting!
And you're aiming for his back?
(He will hit where it hurts!)
There you go!
- He is the worst.
- Kwang Soo.
- He is flippant.
Kwang Soo, know this.
Kwang Soo.
Remember that the airplane passes by
every four minutes.
Why did I pick him?
- What?
- Why did I pick him?
Isn't it great that he is
on our team?
- He is insane.
- Had he been on another team...
I really don't want to do this.
(Picking up)
Hold on. You can't use that.
(He picks up a rock from
the corner of the park.)
(It's a rock for therapy.)
You can't use that.
(He acts like
he doesn't know anything.)
Hey! You jerk!
(He stopped playing fair
10 years ago.)
He is absolutely ridiculous.
He has a license.
A license?
- The viewers...
- They forgive Kwang Soo.
(The viewers go,
"He is always like that.")
Kwang Soo.
Remember that the airplane passes by
every four minutes.
Okay, okay.
Get ready. Set...
(Round 2 begins!)
He is ridiculous.
- Five minutes, right?
- Yes.
There is a tie, right?
- Just take off his socks.
- Okay.
Think of it as skinning him.
(Jong Kook,
think of it as skinning him.)
Skin!
Kwang Soo, that's good.
- Kwang Soo, save up your energy.
- Jong Kook,
he is getting tired.
(He exhausts his energy
by being flippant.)
- Hey!
- He is breathing with his mouth.
(Panting)
- He is exhausted.
- Let's go!
Kwang Soo, why are you taking off
your clothes?
- Kwang Soo, fasten your belt!
- Okay!
Why are you taking off your clothes?
- Hey!
- It came undone.
What is going on?
(What is going on?)
(It's time to stop playing dirty!)
Kwang Soo!
(Jong Kook begins to strike back.)
Jong Kook, he is intimidated.
Look at his face.
(Kwang Soo is intimidated.)
He is totally intimidated.
He is aiming for a tie game.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo. Hang in there.
Here it comes.
Kwang Soo!
(Collapsing)
(Jong Kook uses brute strength
to throw him down.)
Kwang Soo!
- My goodness.
- Oh, no.
- He is putting on a show.
- This is...
(Kwang Soo gets folded up.)
- You jerk.
- Wait. Stop!
(Kwang Soo gets folded up.)
You jerk.
It's an airplane! It's an airplane!
(An airplane flies by
while Kwang Soo gets folded up.)
It's an airplane! It's an airplane!
(He swore so loudly
that they could hear it clearly.)
(He is saying everything
he wants to say.)
You little punk. Come here.
- My goodness.
- That's so funny.
Good job.
That's so funny.
- Come on.
- Okay.
(He attacks the lumbar spine.)
He is kicking.
I don't want to play
against this jerk!
"I don't want to play
against this jerk."
(There is nothing to be gained
by playing a game with Kwang Soo.)
He is a lunatic!
(He plays dirty
and kicks repeatedly.)
- Oh, no!
- Kwang Soo, hang in there.
- That's good.
- He keeps hitting Jong Kook's back.
(Jong Kook finally manages to remove
Kwang Soo's name tag!)
He wins with one full point!
(Jong Kook wins
with one full point!)
- Gosh.
- Good job.
Why is it the winner
who always gets hurt?
Kwang Soo, LFW. LFW.
- LFW?
- Yes, LFW.
Why is it the winner
who always gets hurt?
What does LFW mean?
"Lost but fought well."
- LFW.
- I did my best.
Say something to Kwang Soo!
No one else would put up
with his behavior.
(Punching)
No one else would put up
with his behavior.
(It's not over until it is.)
- That crazy...
- He is full of energy.
- That crazy jerk.
- LFW.
He hit me for real.
Hey, LFW.
- He hit me for real.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
- LFW.
That phrase suits him very well.
- Did you play Jenga?
- We destroyed Jae Suk.
Did Jae Suk get shaky hands?
We played it with this.
I see.
We will win this round easily.
- Thank you for the food.
- They are no match for us.
Thank you for letting us
play against Suk Jin,
- the weakest member.
- But there is Ji Hyo.
- So Min, I...
- You guys don't look so strong.
The second mission is...
Tubes on a Tangerine Tree.
Pick a member
who will protect the tubes...
as the tangerine tree.
The two other members
need to steal the tubes...
and put as many of them as they can
on the tangerine tree.
You can steal tubes
from the other team's tree.
The team with more tubes
on the tangerine tree wins.
The winning team will get a chance
to check one member's card...
and exchange the cards.
Who won earlier?
- We won.
Ji Eun, did you get to eat?
Did you win?
- It was no joke.
- You are still...
thinking about it, right?
What? Did something happen
between her and So Min?
- Nothing happened!
- We heard a lot about So Min.
- We heard good things.
- I didn't do anything.
Then why aren't you looking
at So Min once?
- I am looking at her.
- She is looking at me. Come on.
I heard there is bad blood
between them.
- There is nothing.
- Check it when the episode airs.
There must be a story.
So Min, let go of your grudges.
We are on Jeju Island.
- She has grudges.
- This is my first variety show,
so I did as they asked.
Don't do that, Ji Eun.
I did it to give you
more screen time.
Thank you.
I don't know what's happening,
but thank you.
Please pick a member who will be
the persimmon tree.
Get ready.
Set...
You can go slow.
You can take your time
in the beginning.
- Ji Eun working so hard.
- Put the tubes on her.
Go ahead.
- I will throw the tubes.
- That's good.
That's good. That's good.
We got as many as we can.
We got as many as we can. Wait.
Knock out their tubes!
(The awkward alumni meet
in front of a tangerine tree.)
We just need to keep those tubes.
(She gets past Ji Eun.)
(So Min kicks.)
We just need to keep those tubes.
Hey!
Don't kick!
What?
My goodness. My goodness.
That was no joke.
All right. Stop.
- All right. Stop.
- Hey.
(Ji Hyo runs somewhere.)
(What?)
(Why is she attacking Ju Bin?)
Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo!
- Hey.
(Ji Hyo the delinquent
attacks the wrong person.)
locks her head and throws her down.)
- For goodness' sake.
- Hold on.
Ten seconds remain.
She is heavy!
She is grabbing me by the neck.
(Se Chan currently has 0 tubes
because of Ji Eun.)
- Hurry up.
(Ji Hyo is also struggling
because of Ju Bin.)
Hurry up.
- Hey!
- I will hold on to her.
(Ju Bin is in Ji Hyo's clutches!)
- Oh, no.
- Get your feet up.
- 5, 4,
- three,
- Hurry up and stick them in.
- two,
- Ji Hyo.
- one.
- Let's go down together.
Let's go down together. Come here.
Come here.
- Okay. Ji Hyo has five tubes...
- What is this?
- and Se Chan has two tubes.
- How many does he have?
I am exhausted.
She cheated too much!
- Seriously.
- Excuse me.
Ju Bin...
cheated much more.
I... I...
- She is so strong.
- You know,
Ji Eun is so strong.
She is really strong.
She must be angry at someone.
- Guys.
- It's So Min, right?
- You should make up here.
- You want to attack her, right?
- She attacked me.
- Okay.
- You must be angry.
- She attacked me already.
"I haven't met my enemy in a while!"
"I will show her!"
(He adds a skit
to his made-up story.)
- I understand, Ji Eun.
- She is so strong.
Ji Eun's team can pick a member
and check his or her card.
We will check Ju Bin's card.
- Ju Bin.
- We will give you another chance.
- No, thank you.
- Okay.
(They decide to check
Ju Bin's card.)
All right.
(What's Ju Bin's card?)
(They check
that it's the wind card!)
For goodness' sake.
They must have the same card.
(Team Ji Eun members
school their faces.)
We figured it out.
You must have the same card.
(They fall for the poker face.)
It's the wind card.
Then we will exchange two cards.
Se Chan.
Will you exchange cards?
- We will switch Ju Bin's card...
- And Ji Eun's card, right?
(Ju Bin and Ji Eun exchange cards.)
Exchange cards.
Then...
Let's check it later.
(Ji Eun originally hard...)
(a blank card!)
We don't know what will happen.
- The rock card.
- The discussion is taking forever.
- We have 2.
- We have 2,
- so we need to give one to them.
- It's a technique.
I will switch my card.
Let's take our chances.
That means...
- I will switch mine with Se Chan's.
- Okay.
(Suk Jin and Se Chan
exchange cards.)
(Se Chan has...)
(the woman card.)
For a second...
- I was about to take that.
- Okay.
Let's check the cards. Come here.
(Wind, woman, rock)
(Team Ji Eun collected
all three cards.)
Gosh, what is this?
(Team Ji Eun collected
all three cards.)
Are you satisfied?
I guess this is a bit better.
Let's move to the location
of the last mission.
(Team Ji Eun completed their deck.)
(The supermodels
are having the final match.)
The strap is too...
Come here.
(Poseidon's tornado!)
That's too...
This match is too one-sided.
- Help me!
- It won't take long.
Yeo Jin is smiling.
Yeo Jin!
- Yeo Jin!
- I will take this.
(Poseidon goes for the socks.)
Yeo Jin! Yeo Jin!
What is going on?
- She ripped it.
- What?
- Did she rip it?
- Don't rip it.
- What is going on?
Yeo Jin! Yeo Jin!
- What?
- She ripped it.
(She ripped the sock
with brute strength.)
What is going on?
Hey. Hey.
(E Hyun's sock passed away
on Jeju Island.)
She ripped it.
(After ripping a sock,)
Yeo Jin.
(Yeo Jin takes the name tag
for one full point!)
I got it!
You won with one full point!
- Okay. E Hyun, you worked hard.
- I am exhausted.
Team Yeo Jin won.
- You fought well.
- Okay. Whose card shall we check?
- Well...
Shall we check Jong Kook's?
- Sure.
- We will check Jong Kook's.
He looked a bit...
(Jong Kook's card is...)
(blank.)
- His card is blank.
- My card is blank.
I will exchange mine with Haha's.
- And...
- Mine with E Hyun's.
(Jae Suk and E Hyun have
a blank card.)
- Haha.
- Okay.
Check the cards.
(Jae Suk received Haha's card.)
(What was Haha's card?)
(A blank card!)
- Here you go.
(Yeo Jin and E Hyun
switch cards as well.)
(Yeo Jin got E Hyun's blank card.)
It can't be helped.
(Blank, blank, wind)
- Here you go.
(What did E Hyun get
from Yeo Jin?)
(Blank, blank, blank)
(She got the bomb.)
What is it?
(E Hyun got the bomb from Yeo Jin.)
I see.
Okay, okay, okay. I see.
- This isn't half bad.
- I get it now.
I get it now.
Please gather around in the center.
You know,
- So Min.
- Yes?
I heard the news.
Did it travel that far?
Ji Eun said something about you.
Ji Eun just thinks...
that she didn't do anything wrong.
She just thinks
that you have the victim mentality.
Look at her facial expression.
- We asked.
She said it wasn't so clean.
Something wasn't so clean.
Ji Eun is clean.
She is clean.
Her friend is the problem.
- Her friend?
- Her friend is the problem.
The puzzle pieces
are coming together.
- Later on,
- That's the problem.
you should sort things out
with Ji Eun.
An airplane passes by
every four minutes.
You can swear as much as you want.
- Sort things out then.
- Okay.
That's how it is.
When your acquaintances visit
the show,
- it's the most exhausting.
- That's right.
- You know what it's like.
- You get older.
- I am getting older.
- They know you too much.
(An airplane approaches
and drowns out the audio.)
So Min, now is your chance to speak.
(She finally gets freedom.)
(She brings up a real name.)
(She gives the back story.)
Don't speak ill of my friend!
(Ji Eun counterattacks!)
"Don't speak ill of my friend!"
(This is interesting.)
(A childish fight
between real friends)
"Don't speak ill of my friend!"
Hey!
- Are you living well?
- The airplane is gone!
- She is my friend!
The audio is working.
The airplane is gone.
Their fight is interesting.
That was hilarious.
I hope another airplane will fly by.
Why don't we go to an airport
for the next location?
I can't help but wait
for the airplanes.
Please.
That was so funny.
- It's time for the final mission.
- It's the final one.
One team has the bomb...
and other teams are collecting
the cards.
The last mission that will give you
a chance to switch the cards is...
I Got Fooled
in an Attempt to Find What's Real.
The game names are long today.
It's the random game
in three stages.
Every time you get past a stage,
you will win a point.
One member from each team
will begin at the starting line.
Stage one involves boxes.
Out of the four boxes,
one has a water bucket.
One person will be eliminated.
The next stage involves
the vaulting boxes.
Two are real vaulting boxes
and one is made of polystyrene.
That leaves behind two people.
One will get a water-filled ball
and the other will get a real ball.
If you kick the real ball,
you get a point.
If you score a goal,
you get two additional points.
(If you score a goal,
you get 2 additional points.)
You need to kick gently.
- Yes.
- If it's the fake ball...
- It won't go far.
The team that places 1st
can exchange 2 cards.
The team that places 2nd
can exchange 1 card,
but they won't be able to exchange
with the winning team.
(The team that places 2nd
can exchange 1 card.)
- One member's card.
- We need to avoid last place.
This is hard. This is hard.
Who will participate
in the first round?
I will go.
Okay. I will survive until the end.
Jae Suk, just avoid the ones
you want to choose.
I want to choose this one,
- so I will avoid it.
- Avoid it.
Choose well.
Ji Hyo, it doesn't matter.
I choose...
number one.
Is that your choice?
- Yes.
- No!
I chose number 1 although
I wanted to choose number 2.
- Okay.
- You know what I mean.
We need to do this.
- I choose number three.
- Let's go!
- I choose two.
- I will advance.
- Okay.
- Let's advance.
- Go, go.
- Jump!
- Show us your jump!
- I will jump high.
- Let's go.
- One,
(Will Jae Suk avoid being unlucky
this time?)
two,
(In one of the boxes is
a water bucket.)
three.
(Who will get eliminated first?)
- Let's go!
- Okay!
(Ji Hyo is out.)
- Three.
- Let's go!
(She gets a foot bath.)
Let's go!
(Oh, no!)
(Our team survived!)
(Ji Hyo got eliminated in Stage 1.)
That serves you right!
I told you.
Kwang Soo, I told you
that I wanted to choose number two.
That's a good strategy.
- I really wanted to choose it.
- You wanted to choose number two.
Let's go. Let's go!
Jae Suk, just go for it.
- Okay. I'll go with number one.
- Oh, wow.
I'm on a roll.
You seem so confident.
A man must be in the center.
I'll go with number two.
Okay.
Then I'll go with number three.
- I'll show you how high I can jump.
- Okay.
- Okay. I'll show you.
- That's good.
All right.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Just go for it.
- Let's go at once.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- 1, 2,
- three.
- Jump.
(1 of the 3 is made of polystyrene.)
(Will Jae Suk be able to avoid
the bad one again?)
- Jump.
- What could be the result?
(Jae Suk failed.)
Jump.
(He picked the bad one again.)
Nice!
(I was a fool to get my hopes up.)
Jae Suk.
(Getting this far is a miracle
for Jae Suk.)
I told you not to follow your hunch.
- You can do whatever you want.
- You should've avoided it.
I really wanted to pick that one.
- Exactly. You should've avoided it.
- I told you not to do that.
Nice.
Nice. Good job.
Oh, gosh. I have no idea
how to tell the difference.
Pull this off.
How do we tell the difference?
- This time...
- Haha, did you pick that one?
- Yes, I'll go with this one.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Good luck.
- Go ahead.
All right. Ready.
Get set. Go.
(Who will kick
the water-filled soccer ball?)
(Haha picked the water-filled ball.)
(That means Se Chan picked
the real ball.)
(If he scores a goal,
he gets extra two points.)
Okay.
(Se Chan scored a goal.)
The ball went into the goal.
(He made a clean shot.)
- Okay. Okay.
- All right.
(Se Chan is the best.)
- Good job.
- So Min, I think I did well.
- You did well.
- Was it a real ball?
- It was a real ball.
- That's awesome.
(What a shame.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- Let's go.
- You're our last hope.
Let's go.
- Ju Bin, you can do this. Let's go.
- Ju Bin.
- I don't know what to choose.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
- I don't know!
Which one should I choose?
- This is the last round.
- This one was...
- The box at the end.
- At the end?
It was number two
in the previous round.
I'm sure it's not the same box.
- Okay!
- I'll go with...
I pick the box that was the bad one.
(Jong Kook picked the same box.)
(But I already picked that box.)
You picked the box
that was the bad one earlier?
Sure. Go ahead.
I can pick something else.
- We have as many as four boxes.
- Just do as you always do.
Okay. This one?
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- Go, go, go.
- Okay.
1, 2, 3.
(Who will be eliminated
in the first round?)
(Big Nose fell into water.)
(Groaning)
You failed.
(Team Ji Eun failed in the 1st
round 2nd time in a row.)
- This is ridiculous.
- I told you...
I told you to choose that box.
- No way.
- I told you to pick that one.
I was worried.
- It's hard to tell the difference.
- This is...
- But...
- I'll go with this one.
- I'll go with that.
- Okay.
Good.
Ju Bin, do you want to
switch places with Kwang Soo?
No, don't do that.
Give him a chance.
Ask him if he wants to do that.
Just in case.
How about we play
rock-paper-scissors?
Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay.
- Switch with him. Good.
- Do you think that's the bad one?
- This is a great chance for us.
- Go, go, go.
- I don't think it is.
- I think this is the bad one.
- Kwang Soo, go.
- I think this is it.
- No.
- Go, Kwang Soo.
- I think this is it.
1, 2...
- I think it's made of polystyrene.
- You should sit on it.
Three.
(Kwang Soo never gets lucky.)
(Ju Bin switched places with him.
What could be their fate?)
(Ju Bin fell.)
Three.
(The terrifying curse
of the unlucky man)
(Nice!)
- I knew it.
- She should've stayed there.
- I'm sorry, Ju Bin.
- Se Chan.
- You're a spy, aren't you?
- No, I'm not.
- You did well.
- Thank you, Ju Bin.
- Ju Bin.
She shouldn't have switched
places with him.
I knew it. I had a feeling
that it was the bad one.
I didn't know. You did a good job.
- Kwang Soo will fail in this round.
- Kwang Soo.
This is the most difficult round.
It's confusing.
I think this one is it.
This is the most difficult round.
(Looking closely)
(Looking at it won't make
any difference.)
(Jong Kook chooses carefully
as if he chooses a protein shake.)
I'll go with this one.
- Go, Kwang Soo.
- Just kick it into the goal.
1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo didn't expect
he would make it this far.)
(Will his luck last until the end?)
(No way. He picked
the water-filled ball.)
(Now, what's important is whether
Jong Kook will score a goal or not.)
(If he scores a goal too,
his team will win the race.)
(Will he scare a goal?)
- They both missed.
- You unlucky man.
(He missed a goal!)
I got scared before I kicked it.
I thought it was
the water-filled ball.
Both of them failed.
How could you miss that?
I thought it was
the water-filled ball.
- How could you miss that?
- I thought it was the fake ball.
I got scared
and pulled my foot back.
Each team won one point
every time they pass each round.
The winning team is...
(Which team will win the chance
to exchange two cards?)
Team Ju Bin.
(Team Ju Bin won.)
- Oh, yes!
- Let's go around in a circle.
(That's a shame.
If only I had scored a goal.)
(Gosh. They're annoying.)
(They're trying hard
not to show their emotions.)
This is your last chance
to exchange your cards.
The winning team, please tell us
which cards you want to exchange.
- We will...
- We'll exchange...
(They only need the wind card.)
- exchange only 1 card.
- only 1 card.
Whose card will you exchange?
Mine.
- We'll exchange hers for Ji Eun's.
- For Ji Eun's.
- Mine?
- Yes.
Whose for whose?
(They picked the wind card
that Ji Eun has.)
(They gave Ji Eun the wind card
at the second mission.)
(And they received the blank card
from Ji Eun.)
(So they knew that Ji Eun had
the wind card.)
(They focused on Ji Eun's wind card
strategically.)
(Ju Bin's blank card)
(They picked Ji Eun's card
as they planned.)
Give us your card, Ji Eun.
- Give it to us.
- It's okay.
That's not it.
(Ju Bin had the blank card.)
(So Team Ju Bin collected
all three cards.)
- Here you go.
- Okay.
(She's maintaining her poker face
just in case.)
I can hear you.
Everything went well for us.
- This is hard to believe.
- Exactly.
(Their strategy
worked out perfectly.)
- It's unbelievable.
- Later...
The team in second place, tell us
the card you want to exchange.
We'll exchange mine...
(Will E Hyun's bomb card...)
(go to Team Yeo Jin
or to Team Ji Eun?)
(We'll exchange mine...)
for Ji Hyo's card.
(They'll exchange E Hyun's bomb card
for Ji Hyo's rock card.)
Okay.
Can they exchange another card?
They can exchange
only one card, right?
(We're done for.)
(Maintaining his poker face
is pointless.)
- Why did they all take our cards?
- Why did you do that?
Our team...
- Did we do something wrong?
- You know...
All right.
The card exchange is over.
Reveal your cards
starting with Team Ju Bin.
- You go first.
- Let's do it.
- We go first?
- Yes.
- Must we do this?
- Se Chan nagged us to do this.
- Just this once.
Let's give it a try.
The hilarious Rock.
The best in the universe, Woman.
The fist beauty, Wind.
- We succeeded.
(They look cheerful like the cast
of "TV Kindergarten".)
We did a perfect job.
It's awesome.
(This is so annoying.)
What?
(The three of them worked hard
but only helped another team win.)
We got lucky only in the beginning.
- Awesome.
- See?
Those comments were so neat.
Look how they're whispering
to each other.
They all look upset.
They're just jealous.
They're jealous.
The next team,
please reveal your cards.
- I have the bomb card.
- Okay.
- They'll get the penalty.
- We lost our cards.
They took our cards.
They were the first team we met.
The winning team
of the first part...
of The Jeju Island Special is
Team Ju Bin.
(Team Ju Bin won.)
- The winning team will receive...
- We won!
top quality Jeju Island's black pork
gift sets.
(Jeju Island's black pork gift sets)
Oh, my. That's amazing.
I bet the meat has gone bad.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Oh, my.
It's heavy.
I've never won before.
Now, I'll reveal today's penalty.
Okay. What is it?
- The penalty is...
- Yes.
You will be slapped on the forehead
with a wet hand.
- That's easy.
- It's not a harsh one.
It's time for Suk Jin...
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, no.
I need to temper my hand...
- by repeating wetting and drying.
- Tempering your hand?
- Like this.
- Jae Suk.
- Dry it in Jeju Island's breeze.
- Of course.
Of course, I use the breeze.
You must know
what you've done wrong.
(Welcome, wet hand slap.)
(It's as refreshing
as Jeju Island's scenery.)
Let's hear how they feel
about being on the show.
It was nice to get some fresh air
since it's been a while.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for your help.
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
(The Jeju Island Special Part Two:
Welcome To Running Group Tour)
(Jae Suk is a human cultural asset,
and Suk Jin is his student.)
(Se Chan and So Min are
a newlywed couple.)
(Haha is an assistant manager,
and Jong Kook is a new employee.)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are
a math contest winners.)
(Running Tour begins
with many tourists.)
(The highlight of a group tour,
shopping)
(Having the best photo in life
taken)
(The feast that you can enjoy
only on Jeju Island)
(Can I really enjoy shopping
like this?)
(Some of them enjoy themselves...)
(while the others pay the bills
for them.)
(If you get caught,
you have to pay!)
(You will be the one who pays for
everything the others enjoy.)
(This never has a peaceful day.)
(My family never has
a peaceful day.)
(What could this strange
loser-pays-all group tour be?)
(The Jeju Island Special Part Two:
Loser-Pays-All Group Tour)