(Last week)
- Hello. This is Kang Sora. - What?
(Superstars visited Running Man last week!)
- Hello, So Min. - What's happening?
(Hello, So Min.)
(Happily screaming)
(4 cast members from "Secret Zoo")
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Ahn Jae Hong, Kang Sora, Jeon Yeo Been, Kim Sung Oh)
(The captains must arrive first with their team members.)
- We're on the same team. - Jae Hong. I'll go to you.
(She's not on his Jae Hong's team.)
I can tell from Sora's face. Get out of my way.
(All sorts of scamming and tricks unfolded to obstruct one another.)
(Kwang Soo stole Se Chan's phone.)
- Don't go. - It's you two.
(The two of you are on my team.)
Are you sure?
- Come on, don't lie. - Jae Hong.
(Come on, don't lie.)
Hey, let's not do this.
(Hey, let's not do this.)
- Come here. Goodness. - Hurry.
(At the end of many hardships,)
- We must hurry. - Gosh, Se Chan.
(they finally formed their teams.)
(Team Sora, Team Jae Hong, Team Sung Oh, Team Yeo Been)
- Are we on the same team? - Let's go.
I thought I was on Jae Hong's team.
(Which team will arrive first for the opening segment?)
He fooled you. Why didn't you answer your phone?
(The place of their opening segment is the SBS building in Mok-dong.)
(The first two teams to arrive will get a benefit for the race.)
(At that time, the first team arrives.)
- It's Kwang Soo's team. - Okay.
(Which team arrived first?)
- Be careful. - Thank you.
- Be careful. - Goodness.
(The first person to arrive is...)
(Sora.)
(Team Sora is the 1st one to arrive.)
(Team Sora gets a benefit.)
- We pull out the flag, right? - All right.
(They easily take the flag.)
- This does make me happy. - Okay.
- I see a flag. - Oh, no.
(The 2nd team arrives next.)
It's still there.
(Team Yeo Been is the 2nd to arrive.)
- Suk Jin. - Gosh.
- Hello. - Gosh.
(The 1st and 2nd teams to arrive get the benefits.)
- Hello, Yeo Been. - Hi.
- Hello. Jae Hong. - Hi.
(Team Jae Hong arrives next.)
- They are on your team? - So Min wasn't on your team.
- My goodness. - Hello. Hi.
(And after a while, Team Sung Oh lastly arrives.)
She totally got seduced by Jae Hong.
(So Min definitely was a big help for Team Jae Hong.)
Didn't I tell you?
You can't trust people with faces like his.
(Keep in mind)
Come on.
You need to get a grip, So Min.
(He scans Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin.
You're wearing shoes a prime minister in Joseon wore.
(A prime minister would wear those shoes in Joseon Dynasty.)
- Are those UGG boots? - I thought...
- The UGGs Lim Soo Jung wore? - I mean,
(No way!)
- Hey, didn't she wear those? - "I'm Sorry, I Love You".
(Lim Soo Jung's UGGs)
- That's the ones Soo Jung wore. - I couldn't believe my eyes.
- I was so surprised. - The prime minister wears them.
(His fashion encompasses from the 15th to 20th centuries.)
- I thought you were wearing a cast. - My goodness.
- Why are you wearing those? - What are you talking about?
(Suk Jin, the trendy hipster)
- Hey, these are warm. - The prime ministers wore them.
(Calm down.)
- Prime minister's shoes? - All right.
(The mission that made him wear the prime minister's shoes has ended.)
Well, actually,
- because of the morning mission, - Right.
(Let's officially introduce the 4 actors of "Secret Zoo".)
so we didn't get to say hello properly.
- They filmed a movie together. - A film.
- "They Don't Bite". - It's called...
It's not "They Don't Bite."
(Cough)
- Suk Jin. - What?
If you don't know the title, just be quiet.
("They Don't Bite")
Come on.
- Come on, Prime Minister. - My apologies.
(I apologize on the prime minister's behalf.)
- It's "Don't Harm Me." - No.
- It's "Don't Harm Me." - Seriously.
(He gets it wrong again.)
It's "Secret Zoo."
- This movie takes place at a zoo. - Right.
("Secret Zoo" takes place in a zoo.)
- What is this movie about? - There are no animals at the zoo.
So the zoo is about to close down.
(What kind of story is it?)
And the employees of the zoo put on costumes...
- and pretend... - You put on costumes.
- to be animals. - You become fake animals.
(I see.)
- You'll be fake animals? - Yes.
Do you really think this is possible?
(Transformation into animals)
One of the costumes seems off.
- Let me ask Jae Hong this. - Okay.
- You have a history with Suk Jin. - Jae Hong.
(He has a history with Suk Jin.)
- "Candy in My Ears". - Actually, Jae Hong and I...
(They were phone call partners in a program 3 years ago,)
talked a lot on the phone three years ago.
- You were on a TV program, right? - Yes.
(and they were on the phone with each other the whole day.)
How did you feel after finding out that Suk Jin was your partner?
(How did you feel when you heard your partner was Suk Jin?)
The thing is when the batteries ran out,
(Surprised)
- the call ended. - Right.
- That was what the TV show about. - Right.
When the batteries ran out, the call ends.
So I kept the flashlight on with the phone.
(Bursting into laughter)
(I knew it. The calls ended too quickly.)
- So... - He wanted the call to end fast.
(Laughing)
I really liked him.
- So the battery runs out fast. - That was funny.
(He kept it on hoping the battery ran out fast.)
That's so funny.
Everyone here is entertaining.
(These actors are great on variety shows.)
- Jae Hong has entertaining stories. - That's funny.
- You can split your legs? - He's flexible.
(Hard to believe)
Yes, I can do the splits.
- Can you show us? - I would've never guessed.
I can also split legs.
- Someone else's legs. - Right.
- That's your area of expertise. - He won't stop there.
(I think you can split more than a person's legs.)
- He'll split everything. - Everything.
- Why would you do that? - I mean,
- I was just saying. - Well, for legs...
- Can you show us? - The leg split?
(Jae Hong will try splitting his legs.)
If you can't, he'll help you.
- The side split or the front split? - Either one is fine.
(The side split or the front split?)
He can do the front and back.
- The front split might be better. - The front split.
(Interfering)
- The side split is harder. - The side split is really hard.
(Interfering too)
- I'll do the side split. - Yes.
- Really? - You can really do that?
(Will he be able to do the difficult side split?)
- That's the hard one. - You can do it?
- You can do it in those pants? - Don't overdo yourself.
- I'll go easy on myself. - Okay.
(Hesitating)
- It's hard in those pants. - Wait.
- It's hard in the morning. - Do the front split.
(If it's tough...)
- The front split? - Yes.
I don't care which one. Can't you just do it?
(Struggling)
I don't think he can do it.
(Surprised)
(Wide leg split)
I don't think he can do it.
(Surprised)
Gosh, he can do it.
(He's very flexible unlike how he looks.)
- I didn't think he could. - He's really good.
- Doesn't that hurt? - Yes, I'm fine.
(He's very flexible.)
- Are those your legs? - By the way,
- Hung Kam Bo was really flexible. - Right.
- Why did you bring him up now? - Why would you say that now?
- Hung Kam Bo was really flexible. - Why did you bring him up now?
(Jong Kook suddenly mentions Hung Kam Bo.)
- Why are we talking about him? - All of a sudden?
(He just crossed my mind.)
I'm saying that some people are flexible...
(They're the people who are more flexible than they look.)
- although they don't look flexible. - Right.
Other people can do the splits. Why did you bring him up?
That's amazing.
(After Jae Hong showed off his flexibility,)
- And Sora is here today. - All right.
(Sora will officially introduce herself.)
- Pine trees, green pine trees. - All right.
Sora, how was it today? You briefly did a mission.
(How do you feel about appearing on Running Man for the first time?)
It was brief, but you said something was shocking.
The betrayals among the members.
(She sounds cheerful.)
(She points out the distrust in Running Man.)
- She... - That was shocking?
- She was so shocked in the car. - She couldn't do it.
(It was really shocking.)
By the way, Sora...
- is famous for her selfies. - She takes a lot? She likes it?
(Sora is famous for posting selfies on her social media.)
Her fans have a nickname for it.
- Selfie Fool. - SF.
Gosh, here it is. There.
(Gasping)
- That kind of selfie... - Did you take that photo?
- That... - Did someone take it for you?
People take that kind of photos for advertisements.
(She's well-known for wasting her beauty.)
People don't usually use these photos.
- You took them and uploaded them? - Is this how you take photos?
- Yes, I posted it a long time ago. - You posted it online?
(Her eyes are brought to the center.)
- She's good now. - Well, that's not too bad.
- I'm good at taking selfies now. - You took them recently.
(Now she's promoted to the deity of selfies.)
She can take these photos now.
Now, we have Kim Sung Oh.
(The third guest is Kim Sung Oh.)
In a way, people are reminded...
(He's an actor who takes the roles of villains and a scene-stealer...)
- of his intense villain roles. - "The Man from Nowhere".
(with his intense looks,)
He showed us a lot of intense performances.
(for example, his role in "The Man from Nowhere".)
- You kidnapped Ji Hyo a while back. - Yes.
- Yes. - What?
- He did that in a movie. - What? In a movie?
(In a film?)
- You scared me. - You should mention that first...
(You should have said it was in a film first.)
- and say that next. - I thought he did it in real life.
- Come on, be clear. - No.
- I should've mentioned that first. - You can't say it like that.
(He kidnapped Ji Hyo in "Unstoppable".)
- He did that in a movie. - But...
By the way, what kind of person is Ji Hyo in your opinion?
(What does he think of Ji Hyo?)
She's the best.
(She's the best.)
- In what ways? - What?
We want to know too.
Why is she the best? Why?
(Please be more specific.)
Can you tell us in what ways she's the best?
I said it because we're on TV.
(I said it because we're on TV.)
If you think what I say on TV is valid in real life,
I can't be on TV then.
Should I be myself then?
(Losing his temper)
- He has a lot of anger inside him. - Listen.
- You need to be yourself on TV. - He's angry.
(He easily loses his temper since last week.)
You need to give me some breathing room.
(The angry side of him comes out when he's provoked.)
- You can't corner me like that. - Listen.
- What did I do wrong? - Why would you say that?
(Victimized)
- I can ask him a question. - Right.
Yes. You're not supposed to ask that.
(Sung Oh is the best.)
- He's making stuff up. - You know...
- I can't say only nice things. - That's not it.
(Which animal did this short-tempered Sung Oh...)
In your movie, "Secret Zoo,"
(play in "Secret Zoo"?)
which animal are you?
I'm a gorilla.
(Sung Oh played the gorilla.)
- I can see the gorilla inside him. - It suits him.
- What about you, Yeo Been? - I'm a sloth.
- It suits her. - I can see it.
- It suits you. - You do resemble a sloth.
(There's a sloth on her face.)
- Did you put on makeup for that? - Your face...
- The director did a great job. - Me?
(Is that a compliment?)
- He cast the right people. - He did an awesome job.
You can totally be the sloth.
(Making it sure)
You've never seen a sloth in person.
- No. - We're looking at one now.
- I've never seen it in person. - We're looking at one now.
(We're looking at one right now.)
- We're looking at it now. - When I see you,
(Now we only see you as a sloth.)
- I can totally picture it. - You totally fit the role.
(The director had a discerning eye.)
- He cast the right person. - He did a great job.
- She reminds me of a sloth. - That's amazing.
(Today's race that these diverse actors will run is...)
Today's race is called Reincarnated: We Won't Harm You.
(The Reincarnated Won't Harm You)
Among you, two members who were eliminated...
- Again? - There's another twist?
(They get the feeling there will be a spy.)
- There are spies again? - Gosh, this is crazy.
- Gosh. - Come on.
Among you, two members who were eliminated are back...
(Among the 12 members,)
(there are 2 reincarnated members who were eliminated,)
by reincarnation.
And two deities of death are trying to catch them.
(and the 2 deities of death who are after the reincarnated members.)
I think Sung Oh probably got reincarnated.
(Jae Suk thinks Sung Oh is a reincarnated member.)
- You got a mission, didn't you? - Yes.
- He came here early today. - My gosh.
- It's obvious he's the deity. - Gosh. Look at his face.
(She can tell by his face.)
I get it now.
(So you would push me into a corner with no reason?)
- He's the deity of death. - I know what to do now.
Okay.
There will be three rounds in the mission.
(If a reincarnated member survives after 3 rounds, they win.)
If even 1 of the 2 reincarnated members survives,
they will win.
(If both the reincarnated members are eliminated,)
And if both members are eliminated, the deities of death will win.
(the deities of death win,)
- The losers get the water bomb. - The water bomb?
(and the losing team will get the water bombs.)
- Yes. - It's really cold today.
The deities can eliminate members by ripping off their name tags.
(The deities of death can eliminate the reincarnated members...)
(by tearing their name tags.)
Only the deities will have 10 minutes to remove...
(For 10 minutes after every round,)
(only the deities of death can eliminate the reincarnated members.)
the name tags after each mission when the light is turned on.
If the reincarnated members aren't eliminated,
(If any of the reincarnated members survives,)
the staff members will draw two balls randomly after each round,
(2 more deities of death will be drawn after every round.)
and the chosen members will join the deities.
(The chosen members will join the deities of death.)
The chosen members will join the deities.
(The deities of death will be informed of their teammates.)
And the deities will be informed about the members on their team.
That can't happen. There can't be more deities.
- Are you the deity of death? - Why not?
(Why not?)
Why can't that happen?
- If I was, I wouldn't say that. - Right.
(I said that there can't be more, so I'm not a deity of death.)
- He'd be the reincarnated member. - The reincarnated member.
- Suk Jin, you should focus. - You reincarnated, didn't you?
(You don't know the rules.)
He whispered this to me.
"I don't get it."
(Suk Jin says, "I don't get it.")
(He wants to be sharp, but he can't understand the rules.)
So the members who weren't chosen as the deities of death...
(A regular member that doesn't become a deity of death...)
will be on the reincarnated members' team.
(until the final mission will join the reincarnated members.)
If they are eliminated, they'll face the penalty together.
(Therefore, the ordinary members must protect...)
Protecting them to survive in the race will be important.
(the 2 reincarnated members from the deities of death.)
I'll draw two members for the deities of death.
- You'll draw them? - I see.
(It's time to draw the first 2 deities of death.)
- So no one was informed? - The first two will be chosen now.
The first two deities of death will be chosen now.
(2 deities of death...)
(who have to eliminate the reincarnated members...)
We're done with the draw.
(have been chosen.)
(Those who are chosen as the deities of death...)
- Did you send the text messages? - Yes. I did.
(will receive a text message.)
(From now on, the deities of death...)
The deities of death must go after the reincarnated members.
(must find and eliminate the reincarnated members.)
First, I'll give out the advantage to the two winning teams.
(The winners of the preliminary mission will be given the benefits.)
- Okay. - It's an advantage.
(Team Sora and Team Yeo Been can give a penalty badge...)
You can put it on any member of your choice.
(to a member of their choice.)
It's the penalty badge.
If we get a lot of penalty badges...
If you have a lot of the badges, regardless of the outcome,
(The member with the most number of penalty badges will get hit...)
you'll get the stick as the penalty.
(by the stick regardless of the victory or defeat of one's team.)
Whom should we give this to?
(Jae Suk thinks.)
- Kwang Soo. - What?
I see. Someone on our team?
- No. - So we'll discuss who'll get it?
(You wanted to discuss it with me, right?)
- Our team has to choose one? - For a second...
- They are on the same team. - Were you trying to give it to me?
(Were you trying to give it to me?)
(Kicking)
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo are on the same team.
(Kicking twice)
- He tried to give it to Kwang Soo. - You tried to give that to me?
(The gate to the world of betrayal has opened.)
- Kwang Soo. - What's happening?
You have no faith in me.
(He tries to back out of it.)
- He really kicked you. - Right?
(Shocked)
He really kicked Jae Suk.
- Of course. We don't fake it. - Right.
(Of course, Jae Hong. We keep it real.)
- Jae Hong, this is real. - We don't fake it.
(Team Sora starts discussion.)
- We should discuss to pick someone. - Today...
- You should pick someone. - Yes.
(You should choose, Sora.)
No, don't make me do it.
Why not? It's all right.
Should we vote? Should we all vote?
(Then...)
Since he looks the healthiest, we should pick Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook?)
Jong Kook?
- Is that a dangerous move? - It's okay.
- Just now, - What?
you've been chosen by Sora.
- Me? - Yes.
- We've never met. Why me? - Right.
I mean... Have we met?
(Do you know me, Sora?)
- You don't know me. - No, listen.
(Tying)
- Jong Kook. He hates... - We've never met before.
(He hates doing things without any reason or probable cause.)
- this the most. - Right.
- There's no probable cause. - Did I offend her in any way?
She said you looked healthy.
(Jong Kook is convinced.)
- Yes, she has a point. - Yes.
Just give it to anyone you want, Actress Jeon.
(It's time for Team Yeo Been to give out the badge.)
- At least, you met her before. - Relax. There's no pressure.
(This team lets Yeo Been choose.)
You won't listen to me.
(Surprised)
(Jong Kook gets 2 penalty badges.)
- What's happening? - That was bold.
(Her own teammates are taken aback.)
What just happened?
- Me? - She's trying to undermine him.
(Repeating)
We've never met before.
Giving you the stick is better...
(They give all the badges to Jong Kook as he seems powerful.)
- than getting one from you. - Me?
I won't watch your movie even through VOD.
(Bombshell)
I won't watch this movie even if it comes out as VOD.
Come on.
(Jong Kook is being a sore loser for a choice he can't accept.)
You didn't have to say that.
What is this?
(Everyone is really flustered at his boycott in front of them.)
She suddenly gave it to me.
- What is this? - How shocking.
(Jong Kook gets 2 penalty badges.)
- What is this? - Change your outfits,
(Today's race to protect the reincarnated members begins now.)
and let's get started.
- Let's go. - All right.
You'll be given a hint regarding those who have been reborn.
(The first mission to reveal a hint on the reincarnated members.)
Okay.
(The Reincarnated Won't Harm You, The First Mission)
For this first mission, all of you need to succeed.
It's called Rodeo and Juliet.
(Rodeo and Juliet)
- Rodeo and Juliet? - Rodeo and Juliet?
The teams will take turns.
(All teams will take turns.)
If you don't pass 3 out of 5 rounds,
(If they don't pass 3 of the 5 rounds,)
the hint will be revealed.
(the hint on the reincarnated members will be revealed to all.)
The deities of death will try to fail intentionally.
(Those who try to fail intentionally could be the deities of death.)
That's right.
One of you will get on the horse and try to hold out.
(A member from each team will sit on the horse and try to hold out.)
One of the other members...
(The remaining team members will either eat jjajangmyeon...)
must eat jjajangmyeon or do the water bottle flip...
(or make a water bottle stand to pass the mission.)
in the amount of time the person lasted on the horse to pass.
- Flip a water bottle? - Yes, you flip it upright.
(No hint will be given if they succeed more than 3 times.)
(By doing so, they can protect the reincarnated members.)
- Let's have jjajangmyeon. - Okay.
(They decide to have jjajangmyeon.)
(They're excited.)
Haha, let's work.
- What? - Don't goof around.
(Haha is caught on Jong Kook's radar.)
He wants you to stop goofing around and work.
- I am. What's wrong with him? - Did you hear him?
(He's sullen.)
(Se Chan is a tattletale.)
He said, "I am. What's wrong with him?"
That's what he said.
(What did you say, Haha?)
He said that. Right?
(He won't give in.)
- I'm just reacting. - Right.
You're working.
(Haha is in trouble.)
Okay. I got it.
(Jong Kook made up his mind on his target today.)
Take your hands out of your pockets when working.
(He's still being stubborn.)
- Work, will you? - What?
(The day I take out my hands is your last day.)
- Be sincere. - Okay.
- Let me fix your clothes. - You should wear this.
(They are about to begin the mission.)
You should wear this and give that to me.
(Bickering)
- They're the same size. - Yeo Been.
I know you haven't gotten to know him yet,
(What does Yeo Been think about Suk Jin?)
but what do you think about Suk Jin?
He promised to make me into a star.
(It's an ambitious promise made by the prime minister of Joseon.)
- Why would you promise her that? - I told her so.
- I did. - What's wrong with him?
I am the star-maker of this show.
- Why would you promise her that? - Look.
(Suk Jin will make Yeo Been a star.)
I know she's already famous,
I'm going to make her name the most-searched word online.
(Please enter "Jeon Yeo Been" on the search box.)
- Which team will go first? - Let's see.
Let's play a Race of Wits.
(Should we start the Race of Wits?)
- The 1st person to... - 1!
(The staff didn't say go.)
You need to sit down.
(Then I'll sit down.)
She plays so dirty.
- She's so reckless. - Two!
(She says 2.)
- Hold on. - We haven't started yet.
- Two! - We haven't started yet.
- What's wrong with them? - What's wrong with them?
(Isn't this how you do it?)
- They do whatever they want! - What's wrong with them?
(They play dirtier than they look.)
Like I said, Sora is very straightforward.
- She's very determined. - She's reckless.
(Sora is straightforward.)
- She only does what she's told. - She just wants to win.
(The Race of Wits resumes...)
- Whoever loses... - Goes first?
(after they curb their enthusiasm.)
- Yes. - Okay.
If we don't do anything, we'll win.
(We will win the game if we don't do anything.)
I'm sure.
Get ready, set, go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
- 5. - 6.
Okay!
(Sung Oh and Suk Jin are out.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - You should've waited.
(Jong Kook starts to nag.)
- Sung Oh, do better. - He's being scolded.
(Even guests aren't exempted from Jong Kook's nagging.)
- Let's go! - We overlapped.
We overlapped.
(That was close.)
You told us to wait.
- You said we should be quiet. - What have you done?
- What have you done? - What?
You told us not to do anything, but you did instead.
(A 55-year-old man may not remember what he said.)
He got too excited.
(He even betrays his own words.)
That's what this show is all about.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
(Team Sung Oh lost from the rock-paper-scissors.)
- Let's do it. Come here. - Okay.
(Sung Oh will ride the rodeo on behalf of Team Sung Oh.)
- Good luck. - Kwang Soo, come here.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
I bet he'll be good.
(Look at his posture!)
You look quite stable.
(Very stable)
There's a 75-percent chance he's a deity of death.
I can see the words next to him.
(The deity of death?)
He's not that talkative anymore.
Doesn't he need a helmet?
(He needs to wear the helmet for safety.)
- Helmet? - Yes, let's give him one.
(I'll bring it.)
He should wear one.
(Do I need a helmet?)
Is it that intense?
- If you hold out for too long... - It's cold.
Don't use both hands.
(Goodness.)
Jae Suk!
Don't use both hands.
(Jae Suk slips and falls.)
Jae Suk!
Don't use both hands.
- What's wrong with him? - What's wrong with him?
Jae Suk!
(The others fall as well.)
- What's wrong with him? - What's wrong with him?
- What's wrong with you? - Come on.
(What's wrong with you, you troublemaker?)
What's wrong with you?
- You almost got hurt. - Why did this move?
(Embarrassed)
It is quite slippery.
(This troublemaker has priors.)
- You almost got injured. - Why is this slippery?
- You try to be so funny. - He tries to be so funny.
(He is the oldest troublemaker.)
- I can't believe you. - Why was that slippery?
- Be careful, will you? - Did you get that?
(Abruptly)
- They got it. - What?
(Brazen)
Don't act like it was intentional.
(Stop being rediculous.)
- They got it. - You got it, right?
(Is my slapstick comedy recorded on camera?)
- It's slapstick. - He acts like everything's planned.
(Yoo Jae Suk is a comedian...)
(who doesn't waste a single chance of comedy.)
- "That's a highlight." - All right.
(With the helmet Jae Suk gave, Sung Oh starts.)
- We'll start the timer now. - I have a good feeling about this.
(Depending how long Sung Oh can last,)
- Me too. - Get ready, set, go.
(they can either eat jjajangmyeon or make a water bottle stand.)
Hang in there.
That's quick.
Look at the angles.
(He bounces up and down calmly.)
- Look at his gaze. - You shouldn't be stiff.
- Your body needs to be... - It needs to be flexible.
(Moving limply)
Good. Great job.
He looks so sexy.
Good.
(He looks seductive.)
You're looking sexy!
(Sung Oh continues to bounce his waist...)
You're doing well.
- He's good. - He is.
(even after the horse speeds up.)
Why does he look so sexy?
He looks sexy.
(She is embarrassed for him.)
Good. Nice hips.
What if this doesn't get aired?
That's okay.
(With a little embarrassing groove,)
You're doing well.
(Sung Oh lasts for 55 seconds.)
- You're doing well. - You are.
(He clenches his teeth.)
- He's hanging on. - He is.
(This isn't how it's supposed to be.)
I think they could finish a bowl of jjajangmyeon.
(It's enough to get a bowl of jjajangmyeon.)
He may make it look easy, but that's not the case.
- It's really hard. - He's the best one I've seen.
(Team Sung Oh is more relaxed with enough time.)
You're doing well.
You're doing a great job.
- You're doing well. - What is this?
(When is he going to fall?)
If he's going to take this long, let us stop by at home.
(Right then,)
He's really good.
(he finally falls.)
- Okay, okay. - Are you okay?
(What is Sung Oh's record who lasted longer than expected?)
How many seconds? Or were they minutes?
1 minute and 40 seconds.
(Incredible record)
(This sexy man breathes heavily.)
He's obviously not a deity of death.
(Sung Oh is no longer suspected of being the deity of death.)
You're right.
It didn't matter whether I was reincarnated or a deity.
- I just wanted to ride it well. - Exactly.
(It didn't matter that it was a mission.)
I watched rodeos often.
- You did well. - Every time I saw it on TV,
("I think I can do a good job.")
- You wanted to try it? - I felt like I could ride it well.
(He finally got an answer to his curiosity on variety shows.)
- He's flexible. - He is.
He's good.
(Within 1 minute and 40 seconds,)
So Min and Jong Kook,
(So Min or Jong Kook has to try a mission.)
please decide whether to do the water bottle flip...
(1. Eat jjajangmyeon)
or eat jjajangmyeon in the given time.
(2. Make a water bottle stand)
They could do both in that given time.
(1 minute and 40 seconds should be more than enough.)
You could have jjajangmyeon and jjamppong.
(Bluffing)
- Please make your decision. - We choose jjajangmyeon.
(Confident)
You have 1 minute and 40 seconds.
(He tries to tell them what to do.)
- You can have fried dumplings too. - This is...
- This is too easy. - You could order them right now.
(Bluffing)
- You can stop by at home too. - You may begin once I tell you to.
(But the person who is trying the challenge...)
(is So Min.)
- Will you eat? - So Min will eat?
- Yes. - I doubt...
(If So Min is the deity of death, she'll try to fail.)
she will finish it. I really doubt it.
I have a small mouth.
(Challenge of eating jjajangmyeon in 1 minute and 40 seconds begins.)
You shouldn't eat it like that.
(Trying to coach again)
She can't do it. She can't.
(Amid many criticisms,)
(a man approaches her to hold her hair.)
(That's Se Chan.)
(Goodness!)
(Being sweet)
(He approaches her without a warning.)
Work, will you?
(Stop doing sketches!)
(She focuses on eating again.)
I don't think she can do it.
(It's getting clearer that she will fail.)
- She won't be able to finish it. - She can't.
She won't finish it.
(There's still a lot left.)
She only has a minute and 40 seconds.
(Mumbling)
It's too much.
She needs to do it again.
They didn't give her pickled radish. She needs to eat that.
Why can't she finish it?
(Is that an excuse?)
She's not even having double servings.
(So Min gave up on her mission and is now focusing on getting full.)
I could finish jjamppong and jjajangmyeon.
- She's a deity of death. - I think she's a deity of death.
Yes, it feels like it. She's really eating slowly.
(She couldn't even finish half after 1 minute and 40 seconds.)
I agree.
A minute and 40 seconds is a long time.
(Mumbling)
I'm really doing my best.
(Sung Oh's 1 minute and 40 seconds is about to come to nothing.)
- Five, - She can't finish this?
- four, - She's so suspicious.
- three, - I could've eaten...
- two, - another dish.
- one. - I'm serious.
(Mission failed)
- She failed. - You've failed.
She's not giving it her best.
(For variety show experts, 1 minute and 40 seconds...)
You should've told me in advance if you were going to eat like this.
(is enough to finish both jjajangmyeon and jjamppong.)
It's because she didn't have any pickled radish.
(Obsessed)
(Now they need to succeed in 3 out of 4 missions.)
This is way too much.
Is anyone confident...
(Who can ride the rodeo confidently right now?)
- to do better than Sung Oh? - I know, right?
I think I can.
(Confident)
- Jae Hong wants to try. - Go on.
- Go, Jae Hong. - I'm flexible.
(He is proud of his flexibility.)
- Okay. - Okay. I have high hopes for you.
(It's Jae Hong's turn from Team Jae Hong.)
Good luck.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
(How much time can he earn using his flexibility?)
- Ready, get set... - This will be interesting.
Go slowly. Okay.
- That's good. - Loosen up your hips like he did.
(He's off...)
(to a very good start.)
- Use your hips. - Loosen them.
- You look sexy. - You're doing well.
- Hang in there. - Here he goes.
(The rodeo speeds up after 7 seconds.)
It's going fast all of a sudden.
- Sir... - This is only the beginning.
- Your arms are... - Hold on.
(The crisis came earlier than expected...)
(considering how he was proud of his flexibility.)
- No. - Hang in there.
He's already tired.
(He is about to fall already.)
He's exhausted.
Sir!
(Urgently)
It's too fast.
(It feels different from the last time.)
- It's faster than before. - Don't give up.
(The speed is exactly the same as the last time.)
Don't give up.
- Use your hips. - Use your hips.
He's going to fall soon.
- No, no. - Jae Hong.
(After flapping his body,)
- He's done. - No!
(he falls to the ground.)
- See? It's not easy. - Sung Oh was good.
(Jae Hong proved Sung Oh's greatness.)
- This is how most of us are. - Sung Oh.
How many seconds was that?
(Jae Hong's record was 35 seconds.)
- 35 seconds. - What?
That's not bad.
It wasn't this intense before.
35 seconds.
(Now they have to decide whether to eat jjajangmyeon...)
We need to finish it.
(or make a water bottle stand within 35 seconds.)
We can do it, right?
(Thinking hard)
Come on. Jung Jun Ha finished one in eight seconds.
(You need to go for the water bottle if you have 35 seconds.)
- Just go with the water bottle. - It's impossible to finish that.
No, it's possible.
(He is the only one rebutting.)
- No. - No. Try it then.
- He can do it. - Let me check the amount.
(Thinking)
He must be full because he had gimbap by himself.
(Why are you hesitant?)
Right, he must be full.
(He had a roll of kimbap when everyone else was changing.)
He must be full. He ate something while the others were starving.
(Are you full after eating kimbap?)
Is that why?
- Jong Kook, are you being serious? - How long will this grudge last?
(Jong Kook is picking a fight again.)
(Are you doing this for a show?)
Are you being serious or what?
- He ate by himself. - He must be full.
(It's understandable that you are feeling full.)
We were all starving.
You need to overcome his scolding.
You're only saying that to make the viewers laugh, right?
(Intimidated)
(Of course!)
Of course.
- That's a given. - Ready,
(Haha is trying to eat jjajangmyeon within 35 seconds.)
set...
(Demotivating)
35 seconds? I doubt you can finish it.
Why would you say that already?
- You're on the same team. - Don't demotivate him like that.
(Jae Suk ruins the mood after 2 seconds.)
- Should I not? - You shouldn't be like that.
10 seconds have passed.
(Haha speeds up...)
- You can do it. - He can.
(after the members nagged him.)
- He'll succeed. - It's only been 10 seconds.
(How can he eat all of that?)
- It's going to work. - You can do it.
- Let your stomach do all the work. - He's going to succeed.
(Trying to coach again)
- 20 seconds have passed. - Haha, you're almost there.
(He has 15 seconds left.)
- You can do it! - One more bite.
- You're almost there. - One more time.
(Noodles are almost gone.)
You have five seconds!
Haha, you're almost there.
- You're almost there. - You can do it!
- 30 seconds have passed. - You have five seconds!
(He has 5 seconds left.)
(It's a success if both of his mouth and the bowl have no noodles.)
- 1 more bite. - You have 5 seconds left!
You're almost there.
(What's the result?)
- 3, 4, - He did it.
- five. - He did it.
(35 seconds is over.)
(It's time for judgement.)
- five. - He did it.
He passed, right?
(Sneaky)
- He finished it. - You've failed.
(He has some in his mouth.)
- He's failed? - The food isn't inside his mouth.
(His mouth is full.)
You've failed.
So why in the world did you have to eat that gimbap?
Why did you?
I knew we had to eat jjajangmyeon. That's why I told you not to eat.
(It's time for Jong Kook's nagging.)
- You're just too full right now. - My goodness.
I saw this coming ever since he ate that gimbap.
(Kwang Soo is adding on.)
(Are you doing this to me too?)
He had an entire roll.
- And it was tuna, at that. - You're right.
(It was tuna kimbap.)
- He gobbled it up. - You're right.
(Eating normal kimbap is okay, but tuna kimbap is unforgivable.)
We should do it.
Okay.
(It's now competitive Sora's turn.)
- Sora, you must succeed. - Good luck.
- Good luck. - Let's go, Sora!
(Sora seems overly determined.)
You can do this!
At least stay on there for 35 seconds.
(At least, last for 35 seconds.)
We can finish the bowl then.
- Don't let it speed up too fast. - Right.
(Abruptly)
You said it like you have authority over it.
(Flustered)
He always becomes haughty when we have guests.
(Suk Jin always becomes haughty when they have guests.)
- What authority do you have? - I just asked.
(He acts like he's in power.)
"Don't let it speed up too fast."
(Cut them some slack.)
- I'm asking you. - The guy looked at you...
looking completely annoyed.
(Everything the star maker does looks edgy.)
Gosh.
- Good luck. - Just give us 30 seconds.
(Sora still doesn't hear others talking.)
- Okay. - Is that enough?
(Serious)
- Of course. - Ready,
- Good luck! - The longer the better though.
- Okay, good. - Looking good.
(Thanks to her horseback riding experience,)
Sora, you've got this.
(she looks relaxed.)
- She's good. - She's rocking to the rhythm.
It's speeding up. Stay on it.
(Then it speeds up.)
- Sora, you're doing great. - It's faster now.
Wait, she's swaying too much.
(Getting nervous)
- You're doing great. - But...
- She's quite flexible. - She's doing great.
(She's doing well on level 2.)
- Good. - What's with that speed?
(Level 3 begins. It will be 20 seconds.)
(She falls off right after level 3 begins.)
(That's too bad!)
- How long was that? - 23 seconds.
(23 seconds is the shortest record.)
- It's not much. - You did well though.
- Right. - You did a good job.
(23 seconds)
- The jjajangmyeon. - In 23 seconds?
(What? Finish jjajangmyeon within 23 seconds?)
- 23 seconds? - As you know, Jae Suk...
loves noodles.
(It might be possible since Jae Suk loves noodles.)
- He could do it. - I know he can.
It's completely possible.
He loves noodles...
(It's possible for him.)
and didn't eat any gimbap.
He loves noodles and didn't eat any gimbap.
- Right. - Right?
(It's possible if he's hungry.)
- The gimbap... - Seriously?
That's enough!
Jae Suk can do it.
(So why did you eat gimbap alone?)
Why did you eat it then? It prevented you from succeeding.
- Because of you... - Unbelievable.
(It's the curse of tuna gimbap.)
Gosh.
In 23 seconds?
(Anyway, can Jae Suk finish jjajangmyeon within 23 seconds?)
Hold on. Does he only have to eat the noodles?
(He succeeds if his mouth is empty.)
- Must he swallow everything? - His mouth must be empty.
- He must swallow it all? - Okay.
- No way. - That seems tricky.
(This will be hard.)
- It doesn't seem easy. - Ready,
- Here I go. - It hasn't gone mushy yet.
(Giving an excuse)
- get set... - Jae Suk, please.
- It's a lot though. - This is our last chance.
(Jae Suk starts eating jjajangmyeon.)
- See? It's not easy. - Just wait.
- Count the time for us. - He may be able to do it.
(His strategy is to have a big bite and chew.)
- He's almost done. - Just swallow it.
- 8, 9... - There's still a lot of time.
- He's already half done. - 10 seconds have passed.
(10 seconds left, and he already ate more than half.)
- 10 seconds? - He might be able to do it.
- He might do it. - He's swallowing as he goes.
(He continues to have big bites.)
No wonder you're like a llama.
- 18, 19, 20, 21... - No wonder you're like a llama.
(He swallows as he eats like a lama that loves noodles.)
(Exclaiming)
- 22. - He ate all the noodles.
- 23. - Time over.
(There are no noodles left in the dish.)
(They only have to check inside his mouth now.)
He ate it all.
(They cover him up.)
Here. Swallow it.
(Hurry up and swallow it.)
Go on.
Jae Suk...
(10 years of teamwork shines at times like this.)
Hey, look!
- He ate it all. - See?
(Shameless)
Please open your mouth.
- There's nothing in there. - See?
(Jae Suk's success is reluctantly approved.)
- Okay, you pass. - Yes!
(The miracle of 23 seconds)
Let's go.
- No way. - All right.
(It's unbelievable that Jae Suk did it.)
(Jae Suk is proud with the sauce all over his mouth.)
- Okay! - I can't believe it.
This is because he didn't eat any gimbap.
(Haha has nothing to say.)
- Right? - He didn't eat any gimbap.
- Don't you agree? - If he had the gimbap too...
(It's possible because he was on an empty stomach.)
It's because he was on an empty stomach.
- That's why. - I could suck it all in.
(Jong Kook's gimbap theory is supported thanks to Jae Suk.)
I can't believe he did it in 23 seconds.
- Okay. - Yeo Been, you're next.
(The fourth player is...)
Go, Yeo Been!
(Yeo Been.)
- Yeo Been. - Good luck.
- So she has to succeed? - Yes.
I'm sure you're aware of the importance.
We won't succeed unless you ride this well.
- Okay. - Good luck!
(Isn't that obvious?)
(What Suk Jin said makes Yeo Been more nervous.)
- Oh, no. - You can do this. Who knows?
This could reveal a hidden talent of yours.
(Good luck.)
I hope it doesn't go too fast.
- What... - What was that?
(What?)
(What are you doing?)
- What was that? - Seriously?
- I mean... - Are you kidding me?
(She demonstrates...)
- I didn't expect that. - What was that?
- We're doomed. - A slapstick comedy?
(old slapstick comedy unexpectedly.)
She has what it takes to thrive on variety shows.
(She tries again.)
In through the front door, out through the back door.
(What?)
- What? - What's wrong with you?
- What is this? - What are you doing?
(What's wrong with you?)
- Isn't that a typical... - This is a slapstick comedy.
(She found her hidden talent for slapstick comedy.)
This is what the old comedians used to do.
That's what Kim Yong Man is good at.
- What... - Look at Yeo Been.
(Still?)
- What's wrong with you? - Are you kidding me?
- Are you doing this on purpose? - Of course not.
(I'm not doing this on purpose.)
- What's wrong with you? - I don't think I can do this.
- Come over here. - I can't do this.
- I'm not wearing the right pants. - I'm loving her character!
(They've found a new rising star for slapstick comedy.)
Me too.
- I can't do this. - She's a great fit...
- in terms of variety shows. - What's wrong with her?
(What?)
in terms of variety shows.
- What? - What's wrong with her?
(Again?)
(Her athletic ability is perfect for variety shows.)
I don't think I can do this.
- What is this? - What's wrong?
I don't have the right pants for this.
(She's about to cry.)
Her pants are too slippery.
(Yeo Been's 1st slapstick comedy in 2020 wakes comedians up.)
I'm wearing the wrong pants.
Yeo Been, you're full of surprises.
- There. - She's good.
(She finally sit on the rodeo after five tries.)
- You're set. - There you go.
Isn't she a deity of death?
(They'd rather believe that she's the deity of death.)
- Unbelievable. - No way.
This type of comedy was forgotten even among comedians.
- In the past... - It brought back memories.
(Touched)
- Remember Shim Hyung Rae? - My pants are slippery.
(My pants are slippery.)
Your pants must really be slippery.
(Her pants are the star maker.)
- It's good though. - It could serve as an advantage.
- Okay. - It could benefit her.
(The slippery pants might be advantageous.)
Right, it could help her sway easily to the rhythm.
- That's right. - Let's go.
(Yeo Been's challenge appears to be unsure for many reasons.)
- Ready, - Yeo Been, you can do this.
- Please take it easy. - get set...
- I'm not sure about this. - She'll easily fall off.
(The rodeo starts lightly with level 1.)
Gosh.
- It's easy at first. - Right.
(This is not bad.)
But when it starts to swirl...
(After 7 seconds, it speeds up to level 2.)
Keep your back strong.
- Your back! - There's no rhythm whatsoever.
- Hold on. - She's not swaying to a rhythm.
(Flapping)
(She's bad at moving to the rhythm.)
- No way. - How can one be like this?
(It looks obvious that she's reached her limit.)
- Hey! - Hang on a little longer.
Please, just a while longer...
(Screaming)
- Oh, no. - Please, just a while longer...
(She drops as soon as level 3 begins.)
No!
(The star maker is frustrated.)
No! How long was that?
- How long was it? - 18 seconds.
(She set the poorest record of 18 seconds.)
- Gosh. - That's only enough time...
- for the bottle. - Exactly.
- There's no other option. - We have to go for the bottle.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
(She's out after performing impressive slapstick comedy.)
- No, you did great. - It was hilarious.
(Suk Jin tries to made the bottle stand.)
(What?)
(He succeeds on his first try.)
(Startled)
- What now? - Did he do it?
(Acting haughty)
Call me crazy because I did it on my first try.
(I'm so good.)
- Okay, good. - What's gotten into me?
- The timer wasn't set. - It must be my lucky year.
(2020 must be his lucky year.)
Unbelievable.
(Suk Jin is being too positive...)
He called it his lucky year.
(after succeeding in a practice game.)
Ready, get set...
(How will he do in the actual game?)
(What?)
(He succeeds on his first try!)
What?
(It only took him a second.)
(Staggering)
Gosh.
(His lower body isn't as strong as his luck.)
No way.
- My gosh. - Suk Jin!
(That was awesome, Suk Jin.)
No way.
- I can't believe it. - Seriously?
(No one expected Suk Jin to succeed.)
I thought Suk Jin was going to collapse from high blood pressure.
(Shocked)
- Me too. - Insane, right?
How I'm on a roll is insane!
(Overreacting)
Jae Suk, we should have an ambulance ready just in case.
(I was shocked too.)
I thought Suk Jin was going to collapse.
(They thought Suk Jin would collapse after making it happen.)
- Unbelievable. - He won the game...
(Laughing)
at the expense of his health.
(Thanks to Suk Jin, it's the last round.)
Please pick a person to go from the last team.
(The last player is Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo, are you up for it?
- Sure thing. - Good.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Make it at least 30 seconds. - Sure thing.
Can you eat another bowl of jjajangmyeon?
(For 30 seconds)
- Well, Sora... - He can eat it instead.
(This time, Sora will make the bottle stand.)
Sora practiced the bottle flip.
(While others took a break, Sora practiced by herself.)
- Kwang Soo, here you go. - He'll be good at this.
(Se Chan helps Kwang Soo put on the headgear.)
- Well, Sora... - He can eat it instead.
- Sora practiced the bottle flip. - He has it on backward.
(What?)
Kwang Soo, it's on the other way around.
Just keep it like that.
(Kwang Soo is not an idiot!)
- It's not so bad though. - It suits you.
- Really? - You look like a fish.
(Tempted)
- That's better. - It looks better that way.
(As people say he looks good,)
Doesn't he look like a fish?
(he smiles.)
- Is it all right? - Yes.
- It suits you. - Kwang Soo, you're looking good.
(Kwang Soo confidently walks over with his headgear on backwards.)
- It suits you. - Nice.
Make sure you stay on for at least 30 seconds.
(Wriggling)
Don't do that.
(Kwang Soo's waist is always being weird.)
- Ready, - Giddy-up!
(The last challenge to obtain the hint starts.)
- get set... - He's too tall for this.
He's at an advantage with his long arms.
- See? - Keep it steady.
(Arrogant)
- Nice. - Good job.
(Confident)
- Nice. - That's it.
- You're looking good. - Good job.
(Kwang Soo is doing well,)
- Nice. - Go for it.
(but he doesn't look good.)
Okay.
- You have a good rhythm. - Kwang Soo...
- My gosh. - You're like a machine.
(Bouncing)
You were made for this.
- You've got this. - You'll do better than Sung Oh.
(Kwang Soo's likely to break Sung Oh's record with his long arms.)
- No way. - Good job.
- Kwang Soo, you're doing great. - You were made for this.
- He's good at this. - Way to go!
(It looks weird, but he's doing well.)
- He's like a machine. - He'll have the top record.
- He's really good. - He's a machine.
The operator seems flustered.
- You're a machine. - He's making it angry.
(Even the rodeo expert has never seen...)
- This was a game for Kwang Soo. - He was made for this.
(such a long arm bounce like Kwang Soo's.)
(Giddy-up!)
Giddy-up!
(Falling)
- Okay. - Nice.
(He provokes the horse too much and ends up falling off.)
Giddy-up!
- Okay! - Good job.
- A minute. - A minute?
(Kwang Soo's record is 1 minute.)
- Kwang Soo... - My gosh.
Sora will attempt the bottle flip.
(It's finally time for her to step up.)
(Sora practiced hard in the corner.)
Nice, she has a minute.
- Bring the bottle. - All right.
(Serious)
I see she's the serious type.
(Kwang Soo sacrificed himself to give her a minute.)
(She's practicing again.)
You have one minute.
Ready... Wait, no more practicing.
(If she makes the bottle stand within 1 minute,)
- Ready, - Please.
(she can stop the hint from getting revealed.)
get set...
You have enough time.
- Gosh. - You're using too much force.
Yes, that's about it.
- Gosh. - What was that?
(Did something just fly by?)
(Falling)
- What was that? - Hold on.
(Sung Oh, the scene-stealer)
- Wait. - Are you all right?
(What's wrong with him?)
What's wrong with you?
(Puzzled)
(He's flustered.)
- Gosh. - What's wrong with you?
(Whatever happens next to her,)
You can't let it be that obvious.
(Sora doesn't even look at it.)
- Are you kidding me? - I mean...
- I wanted to watch from this side. - He laid out flat.
(Clumsy)
I wanted to watch from this side.
(Sung Oh needs the guardian's attention.)
It's slippery.
- What on earth is wrong with you? - It's slippery.
(While everyone is laughing,)
Hold on.
(Sora's completely focused.)
30 seconds.
It's all right. You have enough time.
(She's trying so hard.)
She's not the deity of death. Look at how focused she is.
Just a little bit more.
That's it. You're almost there now.
(It looks like the bottle would stand, but it falls.)
Flip it a little harder.
You're almost there.
(Just then...)
(She barely succeeds.)
Nice!
It stood right at the edge of the table.
(Luckily, the bottle is stopped just before falling.)
- Good job. - Nice.
(Now she sees people around her.)
You will not receive any hints about the reincarnated members.
(As they succeeded in 3 rounds out of 5,)
(they will not receive any hints about the reincarnated members.)
- Okay. - Nice!
- All right. - Good job.
(The deities of death must be frustrated.)
Some of the members are good at slapstick comedy.
We should call them Team Slapstick.
(Team "Secret Zoo" is good at slapstick comedy.)
Especially Yeo Been and Sung Oh.
The guests today are hilarious.
Everyone including Yeo Been.
The guests are fun but our members aren't.
Right.
Who was that directed at?
(Jae Suk is now looking...)
- Who did you say that to? - Hang in there.
(at the star maker.)
- Who? - Hang in there.
- I'm taking a break this week. - Stay strong, Suk Jin.
(A pathetic excuse)
(Suk Jin's been taking a break for 10 years.)
- He's taking a break. - A break.
- Suk Jin, hang in there. - Sure.
Right now, for 10 minutes, the deities of death...
(For 10 minutes,)
will try and rip off your name tags.
(the deities of death will try and rip off the name tags.)
(Name tag elimination out of the blue?)
- That's out of the blue. - Why?
But we didn't receive any hints.
(Only the deities of death may eliminate the others.)
Only the deities of death may eliminate anyone.
Over the course of three rounds,
the deities of death can eliminate two people each.
(Over the course of three rounds,)
(the deities of death will only be allowed...)
(to eliminate two people each.)
The race is over If the reincarnated members are eliminated.
(When both reincarnated members are eliminated,)
But if a regular member gets eliminated,
(the deities of death win.)
(If a deity of death rips off the name tag of a regular member,)
both the deity of death and the eliminated member...
(both the deity of death and the regular member...)
will receive a penalty badge each.
(get the penalty badge.)
Even if you're not reincarnated, be careful not to get eliminated.
(The ordinary members must also protect their name tags.)
It'll become obvious.
Let's start...
(With two deities of death present,)
- the name tag elimination. - Right now?
(the 1st round will begin.)
Right here?
(The siren goes off to notify them of the beginning of the race.)
- Are we supposed to run? - What?
Ordinary members can't rip off name tags, right?
- Are you a deity of death? - She must be a deity of death.
I'm not.
Are you a deity of death?
(They can't move hastily...)
- What are you doing? - What's with Yeo Been?
(as only the deities of death can remove the name tags.)
So Min, what are you doing there?
You want to make it so obvious?
(So Min starts behaving unusually.)
- I'm nothing. - She's acting strange today.
I'm just sick.
Are you pretending to be sick because you're a deity of death?
(While Se Chan is doubting her,)
(Yeo Been gets close from behind.)
- What is she doing? - Gosh, you startled me.
Gosh.
(Is Yeo Been going after the name tags...)
(because she is a deity of death?)
I know you're not a deity of death.
(An important role)
They wouldn't give you such a role.
You're too weak.
I'm not as weak as you are.
(The weak middle-aged men are squabbling.)
I'll rip off your name tag.
You're not a deity of death, are you?
- I'm not. - I knew it.
If I was, your name tag would have come off.
I wouldn't let that happen.
(Being childish)
(The weakest members keep squabbling.)
What are you doing? Gosh.
(Startled)
(Is Jae Suk going after him?)
I will not...
(Stuttering)
What?
(Suk Jin is startled and slurs his words.)
Go away!
What did you say?
(What are you saying?)
What does that mean?
(He continues teasing Suk Jin in the new year.)
- I don't understand. - Go away!
Let's go upstairs.
(Quietly)
In the elevator?
(Se Chan suggests to Kwang Soo they go upstairs.)
(What's on his mind?)
You're not a deity of death‚ are you?
I'm not.
(A deity of death?)
(Kwang Soo follows him carefully.)
(Suddenly...)
(Se Chan grabs Kwang Soo's name tag.)
I'm not a deity of death. What's with you?
Why do you look so nervous?
If you're a deity of death, rip off my name tag now.
(Provoking boldly)
I'm serious.
You're not a deity of death, are you?
I'm not. If you are, rip off name tag now.
Do you want to be a deity of death?
- I think that'd be easier. - Okay.
(If it's a mistake,)
(both the deity of death and the regular member...)
(receive a penalty badge each.)
You're not?
(Is either of them a deity of death?)
Hey!
(Kwang Soo screams.)
(Why did Kwang Soo scream?)
What happened?
Did you get eliminated?
- Gosh, this is annoying. - Who eliminated who?
(What's going on?)
Who eliminated who?
Gosh. This is...
(Both their name tags are barely attached.)
- Did you see that? - Unbelievable.
- Gosh. - I didn't see it.
(They're both claiming that their name tags got removed.)
This is crazy.
(One of them is a deity of death.)
So one of you is a deity of death?
- Hey. - Unbelievable.
(Who is a deity of death, Se Chan or Kwang Soo?)
Unbelievable.
(The race is over.)
I can't believe it. I was at the scene.
(Although Haha didn't see who ripped off the name tag,)
- Who is it? - I'm not sure.
It's one of the two.
(he was on the scene right after the incident.)
- It's driving me crazy. - Who are they? Tell me.
Guys, listen to me.
Look. They both got a penalty badge.
I saw it.
(Both of them are wearing a penalty badge on their chest.)
- One of them is a deity of death? - Unbelievable.
(They have the penalty badges.)
(One of them is a deity of death, and the other is a regular member.)
Let me tell you one thing.
One of them is a deity of death.
Se Chan is.
(Out of the blue)
- Jong Kook. - I'm not.
- Didn't you see me do the rodeo? - I did.
What about me?
- Se Chan. - Yes?
It's okay to say that you're a deity of death.
(Se Chan is already on Jong Kook's radar.)
It's not like I can eliminate you.
(Denying)
What if I'm not?
I can say that too, right? I'm not.
Is it you then?
I did the rodeo for more than a minute.
- He couldn't be a deity of death. - For more than a minute.
(Kwang Soo worked too hard during the mission to be a deity of death.)
- He did his best. - Also,
I would have volunteered to eat jjajangmyeon.
(He makes an impassioned speech.)
- Jong Kook, but... - Se Chan, it's okay to say it.
(Jong Kook is already convinced.)
Jong Kook is doing it again.
(One of them must be lying.)
- I'm on his radar again. - Say it.
- It's okay to say it. - Say who the other is.
(Which of them is a deity of death?)
- Seriously... - I mean...
- You're so mean. - What's wrong?
What happens now?
(The 1st round of the race ends...)
More penalty badges have been distributed.
(with the fact that either Kwang Soo or Se Chan is a deity of death.)
The deity of death race for the first round is over.
I will pick two more deities of death now.
If the same person from the first round...
(If the name of a deity of death is drawn again, that doesn't count.)
is picked again,
that chance is gone.
Therefore, there may not be four deities of death.
I'd rather be a deity of death.
Can you turn around for a second?
(Two more deities of death are picked.)
(The deities of death in Round 1)
(The deities of death in Round 2)
(One person stays a deity of death.)
- All right. I'm done. - Okay.
(Current number of deities of death)
(There are 3 deities of death in total.)
- Sung Oh. - Come on.
(The result is texted to them.)
I want to be a deity of death.
- They're chosen randomly. - I've never been chosen.
(The deities of death are notified of the new deity of death.)
- I wasn't chosen. - Me neither.
They're not giving me the role.
The first round is over.
(Who are the 3 deities of death who are after the reincarnated members?)
Let's move to another place for the second round.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's go. - I can't believe Kwang Soo.
(They move on to the second round with the curiosity of the deities.)
Se Chan!
- What is this? - What is this?
(They are at the location for the second round.)
Here is the second mission for all members.
(The Reincarnated Won't Harm You, The Second Mission)
- It's called Rumor Has It. - Rumor Has It?
(Rumor Has It)
Each round will be played by six members.
(6 members will stand in a line to deliver a sentence...)
You'll put on headphones and deliver a sentence...
(given by the staff to the next person.)
to the next player.
(If the main contents of the sentence are delivered...)
To win, get the correct sentence delivered to the last player.
(to the last person, they succeed.)
If you get 2 out of 3 sentences correct, you succeed.
(If they get 2 out of 3 questions correct, they pass the mission.)
If the mission fails,
(If they fail,)
all members will receive a hint about the reincarnated members.
(all members will receive the hint on the reincarnated members.)
I'm afraid too many members will act like deities of death.
(He starts doubting.)
- Right. - Right.
(Suk Jin, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo)
There are many suspicious members.
There are too many. It's so hard today.
(Who would be the deities of death?)
Please choose six representatives.
(6 members will participate in the 1st quiz)
(Jong Kook, Se Chan, So Min, Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, and Haha)
- Try to deliver the main idea. - Exactly.
(The key to this mission)
- That's right. - That's right.
The first player should summarize the sentence well...
- deliver it correctly. - Right.
I'll do my best.
(The first player has a critical role.)
- Let's show them. - Seriously.
(They'll be given a hint on the reincarnated members if they fail.)
Let's win a hint.
Let's watch carefully.
Some of them may be deities of death.
(They must succeed to protect the reincarnated members.)
- I'm sure. - Definitely.
(If someone deliberately makes a mistake,)
(there's a high chance that the member is a deity of death.)
Either Se Chan or Kwang Soo is a deity of death.
(And one of these two members is a deity of death.)
Right. We should watch them.
Here we go. Ready, get set, go.
(What sentence will the staff give them?)
This is impossible.
- I can't even remember the names. - I don't understand a thing.
(They have to deliver such a long sentence?)
- That's hard. - That's impossible to remember.
(He's about to give up already.)
- Gosh. - This won't work.
(Listen, guys. In the Champions League,)
It's just impossible.
(Sadio Mane scored a hat trick. I want autographs of...)
- I couldn't memorize half of it. - I've lost all my will.
(They are demotivated already.)
You'd have to already know the names...
(It's only possible if one is familiar...)
of the players and coaches to memorize it.
(with the names of the soccer players and the coaches.)
This is too hard.
(The answer will be admitted if they deliver the main contents.)
Just make it as close to the original sentence as you can.
(While Jong Kook is memorizing the sentence,)
(the others are dancing.)
(They're dancing to one of BTS' songs.)
I know this dance.
(They're dancing pretty much in sync.)
(Jong Kook is serious, but the others are having fun.)
It's that song.
(She finds it interesting.)
Let's start.
(Jong Kook delivers what he memorized to Se Chan.)
- Listen, guys. - "Listen, guys."
(It's a good start.)
(Listen, guys.)
- In the Champions League... - "In the Champions League..."
(In the Champions League,)
Sadio Mane scored a hat trick.
(Sadio Mane scored...)
- Who? - Sadio Mane.
(a hat trick.)
- Sadio Mane. - You don't know who he is?
(A winger for Liverpool)
- "Sadio Mane"? - Yes, Sadio Mane.
(It's a shaky start.)
- Sadio Mane and... - "Sadio Mane".
(I want autographs of Sadio Mane and the manager, Klopp.)
Jurgen Klopp, the manager of Liverpool...
(The player who became a free agent according to the Bosman ruling...)
- That's English. - Yes.
(My goodness.)
(The English names put Se Chan in trouble.)
- Jurgen Klopp is the manager. - What was the other name?
(He's already confused.)
Sadro Malen?
- It's Sadio Mane. - "Sadio Mane".
(Pull yourself together!)
I want autographs of Sadio Mane and the manager, Klopp.
(I want autographs of Sadio Mane and the manager, Klopp.)
The player who became a free agent according to the Bosman ruling...
(The player who became a free agent according to the Bosman ruling...)
What? The Bosman ruling?
(It's perfect so far.)
- Samuel Umtiti... - Oh, my.
(Difficult name)
Samuel Umtiti...
(Jong Kook is incredible.)
Bring him to Camp Nou.
(Home stadium of FC Barcelona)
Do you know it?
- Camp Nou. - I don't.
(Se Chan is about to cry.)
(How can you not know it when you play soccer with me?)
(I'll make you remember it.)
- Camp Nou. - "Camp Nou".
Se Chan, hurry up.
(It's already more than what Se Chan can remember.)
Bring him to Camp Nou.
I want him in the back seat of my six-seater SUV.
(Perfect)
(Jong Kook delivered the 100-letter sentence perfectly.)
(Jong Kook is amazing.)
(This is incredible.)
- He's incredible. - All right.
- Listen, guys. - "Listen, guys."
(Se Chan delivers the sentence to So Min.)
- Listen carefully, guys. - "Listen carefully, guys."
- Listen carefully, guys. - The Champions League.
(1st term related to soccer, the Champions League)
"The Champions League".
- In the Champions League... - "In the Champions League..."
- A player scored a hat trick. - "A player scored a hat trick."
(2nd term related to soccer, a hat trick)
A hat trick. It means scoring more than three goals.
(He adds an explanation.)
What? A hat trick?
Cut that out.
(Don't explain it. It'll only confuse her.)
"Listen, guys. A hat trick in the Champions League..."
(Listen, guys. In the Champions League...)
Okay.
(The next word is Sadio Mane.)
Sadio Mane.
(You have to remember it. It's Sadio Mane.)
Okay. Simon Murphy. No, that's not it.
Simon Murphy.
(He gets every letter wrong except for "S".)
No, that's not it.
- Just keep going. - Simon Murphy...
(He changes the name of Sadio Mane.)
- Simon Murphy. - "Simon Murphy".
- There's a guy called Simon Murphy. - Simon Murphy?
(Yang Se Chan, not good at English)
- He is called Simon Murphy. - Simon Murphy?
(Jong Kook's effort has come to nothing.)
And then...
- there is the manager of Liverpool. - "The manager of Liverpool".
(He remembers the manager of Liverpool.)
- His name is Club. - "Club".
His name is Club.
"Club"?
In addition to him,
(Klopp's name is also changed by Se Chan.)
there is another manager.
(He adds an unknown manager.)
- Another manager? - I mean...
It's an English name again.
What did Jong Kook say?
(It was clearly an English name.)
(All the English names paralyze Se Chan's brain.)
Si... Siranman?
- "Siranman"? - The manager is called Siranman.
(It's Samuel Umtiti!)
He is transferring.
And he is getting in a six-seater SUV.
(He forgot about Camp Nou.)
- An SUV? - Yes.
Who gets in it? Simon Murphy?
(She tries to put the sentence together.)
Or the manager of Liverpool, who is transferring?
All of them.
Okay. Liverpool...
(He turns it into a test drive.)
A person called Simon Murphy...
and he will get in a six-seater SUV...
(Se Chan's sentence: Simon Murphy, Coach Club, and Siranman,)
- and leave. - A six-seater SUV...
(they all got in a 6-seater SUV and left.)
- A hat trick? - A hat trick.
(His brain stops functioning.)
- It's hard. - This is bad.
(So Min delivers the sentence to Kwang Soo.)
Listen carefully, guys.
- The Champion League. - "The Champion League".
(The "Champion" League, hat trick)
- A hat trick. - "A hat trick".
(She successfully delivers the two words.)
- Hat trick. - That's three goals.
Someone scored a hat trick.
And the Liverpool Club...
(She starts saying it wrong.)
- What? - Liverpool.
Simon Murphy and...
(Simon Murphy appears again instead of Sadio Mane.)
- "Simon Murphy"? - Yes, Simon Murphy.
And a side trick?
Sidopick?
Is that a name?
Well... Si...
(The sentence starts going nowhere.)
Simon Murphy of Liverpool...
(Sadio Mane to Simon Murphy)
and another man with an English name...
(Jurgen Klopp to "another man with an English name".)
(Samuel Umtiti to Side Trick)
and Side Trick...
were put in a six-seater SUV and sent away.
She is a deity of death.
She is definitely a deity of death.
(Doubting strongly)
- Why? - It wasn't that bad.
(I just delivered the sentence as I heard it.)
- Keep going, Kwang Soo. - Keep going.
- That's what Se Chan said. - Keep going.
(Both Se Chan and So Min are suspicious.)
- You'll hear it later. - The English names...
- Listen carefully, guys. - "Listen carefully, guys."
(Kwang Soo delivers the sentence to Ji Hyo.)
Liverpool in the Champions League...
"Liverpool in the Champions League..."
(Sadio Mane scored...)
A hat trick was scored by...
Simon Dominic?
(a hat trick.)
(Simon Dominc Becomes a Soccer Player)
(Simon Dominic Scores a Hat Trick in the Champions League)
Simon, Simon Dominic
And Simon...
(It gets more interesting.)
Diva.
- "Simon Diva"? - They...
were sent away in a six-seater SUV.
- Keep going. - I want to send you away.
(Seething)
You want to send me away?
- Listen, guys. - "Listen, guys."
Is it a will?
It's a will.
(It has suddenly turned into a will.)
This man is dividing his property on his deathbed.
(It's his first time hearing about it.)
(Dozing off)
- Look at Ji Hyo. - This man is dividing the property.
That's the only thing that comes out of a will.
(It's a rumor started by Ji Hyo.)
- I can't believe Ji Hyo. - Listen, guys.
It's a will.
(What is the content of the will?)
In the Champions League,
(Champions League, Liverpool)
Liverpool...
is it.
(The will that Ji Hyo heard: it's Liverpool of the Champions League.)
So that's the will?
The will!
(A very short will.)
"In the Champions League, Liverpool is it."
(Something isn't right, but he's focusing again.)
- A hat trick... - "A hat trick".
(The content of the will is totally erased.)
Then there was some kind of a league.
It's a six-seater.
(It's someone's will who really wanted to ride a 6-person car.)
The diva of a six-seater.
The diva of a six-seater?
(What is she talking about?)
Ji Hyo, that's good.
Ji Hyo got all the key points.
(Unexpectedly)
The diva of a six-seater?
- It isn't a will, is it? - Don't add things!
(She still passed on Champions League, hat-trick,)
(Liverpool, and 6-person car.)
Listen carefully, guys.
(He is trying to come up with a sentence from what he heard.)
Europe... The UK...
- The Champions League. - He doesn't know much about soccer.
(Jong Kook is being frustrated.)
Liverpool...
I sincerely congratulate you on six consecutive victories.
(Not a 6-person car)
I sincerely congratulate you...
(He can summarize 100 words in just one sentence.)
(This is how scary a wrong message delivery can be.)
Did I get it wrong? It can't be a six-seater.
Did I get it wrong?
(First sentence failed.)
- I heard a six-seater. - What?
- Jong Kook memorized it perfectly. - Really?
(Jong Kook memorized the entire sentence.)
- Ji Hyo said, "It's a will." - I was so taken aback.
(It's funny when he thinks about it agin.)
Ji Hyo, it was funny.
(She is the creator of rumors.)
- This is your last chance. - The last chance.
(They need to guess more than two questions correctly.)
(They'll fail if they get it wrong this time.)
Let's change two players.
(A proposal to change players)
- Let's do that. - I will give it a try.
(Suk Jin wants to take part.)
Suk Jin, I am sorry, but...
- I will give it a try. I can do it. - Suk Jin.
(Calm down)
If you want to make Yeo Been a star,
- you should give her a chance. - Yeo Been.
(The star maker wants to be more successful than the actress.)
Suk Jin, we need to succeed.
Let's begin. Here we go.
(The second question)
(Listen, children. The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment at Seocho-gu...)
- My goodness. - Listen, guys.
(should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.)
(Give the pet armadillo and kissing gourami to my nephew, Jae Hong.)
(Donate the mandrill monkey to the Nairobi National Park of Kenya.)
That one is hard too.
(That's too difficult.)
- Seriously. - It must be hard.
It's hard. It isn't easy.
(Can Jong Kook memorize the entire sentence again?)
(Jong Kook delivers the sentence to Sora.)
- Listen, guys. - It's "Listen, guys" again.
(The first sentence)
(A bad memory)
Listen, guys.
The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment at Seocho-gu...
should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.
Give the pet armadillo...
and kissing gourami...
to my nephew, Jae Hong.
(He's perfect until now.)
And...
the monkey...
(First of all)
What kind of monkey was it?
(Facing the first obstacle)
Donate the monkey...
(Jong Kook couldn't remember it's mandrill monkey.)
to the Nairobi National Park of Kenya.
(Everything was perfect except for the mandrill part.)
(Sora delivers the sentence to Jae Hong.)
- It's a will. - A will.
(Abruptly)
Listen, guys. The Hanmaeum Apartment at Seocho-gu...
(The will is back.)
- The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment... - 142m²?
should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.
Give the pet armadillo...
and kissing gourami to my nephew, Jae Hong.
(To me?)
And... What was the last one? What was the last one?
(She only needs to remember the word, "mandrill".)
Remember the last one.
(It's at the tip of her tongue.)
The pet elephant...
(A mandrill monkey has turned into an elephant?)
No, no.
Donate something to the Nairobi National Park of Kenya.
(What was she supposed to donate to Nairobi in Kenya?)
What was it?
(She donated an elephant instead of the mandrill monkey.)
(Jae Hong delivers the sentence to Yeo Been.)
What was it?
- It's a will. - "It's a will."
- Listen, guys. - "Listen, guys."
The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment at Seocho-gu...
should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.
Give the pet armadillo...
(He was perfect until now.)
and kissing gourami...
- to my nephew, Jae Hong. - My nephew, Jae Hong.
(What was it?)
- The rhino... - The rhino.
- The rhino... - "The rhino..."
(The mandrill monkey has turned into an elephant,)
(then into a rhinoceros.)
Keep going.
(He's already having a meltdown.)
Give it to someone.
Give the rhino to someone.
(You are supposed to donate it to Nairobi National Park.)
(Yeo Been delivers the sentence to Kwang Soo.)
Listen, guys. It's a will.
(It's now widely spread.)
Again?
(A will again?)
Is it a will again?
(Now they are confused if it's actually a will.)
The 142m² apartment at Seocho-gu...
should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.
The pet armandidorang...
(Confused)
(We are doomed.)
The pet armandidorang...
and kissing gourami...
(Everything's perfect except for the armadillo.)
- should go to my nephew. - What?
The nephew.
Yeo Been, you are acting strange.
Send them to my nephew.
(She forgot Jae Hong.)
Send the armandi and kissing gourami?
(He didn't understand correctly.)
And...
the rhino... Wait, that can't be right.
(Raising a rhinoceros?)
What was it? The rhino...
(What was I supposed to do with the rhinoceros?)
Well, the rhino...
(Throwing a bait)
It should be released.
- It should be released. - Release it.
(She took the bait.)
What kind of nonsense is that?
- I don't know... - Release the rhino?
(How did we get this far?)
how this happened.
- What else can you do? - That's right.
(Rhinoceros freedom)
- But why would you release it? - What else can you do with a rhino?
(What is she talking about?)
- That's the only choice. - That's right.
(Jong Kook gave up too.)
- It's not like you can eat it. - But...
(Kwang Soo delivers the sentence to Haha.)
Listen, guys.
- Is it a will again? - How did you know?
(A deja vu?)
(Goodness)
- Is it a will again? - How did you know?
- How did you know? - How did you know?
(She has nothing to say.)
(Is it really a will?)
Are you serious?
It's a will.
(Kwang Soo delivers the content of the will.)
- The 142m² apartment... - Listen, guys. It's a will.
(He starts off smoothly.)
The 142m² apartment at Seocho-gu...
- 23. - What?
There was something about 23. I am sure of it. 23.
(He memorized the second and the third child as 2 and 3.)
- The 142m² apartment... - "The 142m² apartment."
(It's not a 142m² apartment.)
- is on the 43rd floor. - "It's on the 43rd floor."
(It gets worse.)
Okay.
(The will is going nowhere again.)
The pet armand...
Armand?
Isn't that the name of champagne?
- Champagne? - I am sure it's a brand name.
(Kwang Soo suddenly spit out a brand for champagne.)
Armandor.
(He changes on the spot.)
Send the pet armandor to my nephew.
(What is that?)
(We are going to fail this time too.)
- My nephew. - Release the rhino.
(The last will?)
- What? - Release the rhino.
What?
(The last sentence of the will is the freedom of the rhinoceros.)
- This is crazy. - That's exactly what I heard.
(I swear)
Listen, guys. It's a will.
(It's time to guess the answer.)
- A will. - I give you...
(Sora is the source of the rumor that it's a will.)
the 142m² apartment...
(It's not 43rd floor.)
(Haha guesses it right.)
(This feels good.)
I don't think it's on the 43rd floor.
I give you 23 142m² apartments...
(Now they know their father's secret.)
Our father was a rich man!
- Seriously. - Our father...
(The father was rich!)
- Our father was a rich man! - 23 142m² apartments?
(In Seocho-dong?)
That's insanely rich.
(They once again understand the power of rumors.)
I will give the 23 apartments to you.
Inside them were...
a cat named Armand...
and kissing gourami.
Give them to the rhino.
(The rhinoceros earns Armangdi and kissing gourami.)
Then the family will be successful for generations.
I will reveal the answer.
(It's time to reveal the answer.)
What's the answer?
- The rhino... - Is there a part about a rhino?
(The source of the rhinoceros rumor)
I talked about a monkey, but Sora changed it to an elephant.
(The mandrill monkey has turned into an elephant,)
(then into a rhinoceros.)
Then Jae Hong changed it to a rhino.
All right. Since you failed the mission,
(They failed.)
I will reveal a hint on the reincarnated members.
(The hint on the reincarnated members are revealed.)
If you are a deity of death, take note.
(What hint will be given?)
The reincarnated members don't have the AB blood type.
(The reincarnated member's blood type is not AB.)
- It's not me. - Don't have the AB blood type.
(Jeon So Min is excluded.)
It's not me.
- That eliminated one member. - Seriously.
(Just one)
For 10 minutes, we will play the name tag elimination again.
(It's time to play the name tag elimination...)
(for the next 10 minutes.)
A hint on the deities of death is hidden somewhere in here.
(There are hints on the deities of death throughout this building.)
- Okay. - We have to find it.
Where is it?
You have to look for it.
- Where is it? - You have to look for it.
(He blatantly wants to know the location of the hints.)
- "Where is it?" - Why would they tell you?
(Why would they hide them if they'll just tell you?)
- You have to look for it. - Are you okay?
- I feel dizzy. - "Where is it?"
(Dizzy)
That was hilarious.
- Jae Hong, that was original. - I feel dizzy.
(Jae Hong is cute.)
"Where is it?" That was original.
(It's an unprecedented character in variety shows.)
He must be the first person to ask that outright.
(Amazed)
Let's go.
(The siren that signals the start of the race goes off.)
For goodness' sake.
(Name Tag Elimination Starts)
- Let's look for the hint. - Let's look for the hint.
- You are a deity of death. - No, I am not.
(Suk Jin is trying to sound Se Chan out.)
(Denying fervently)
- No? - No.
(Suk Jin is trying to sound Se Chan out again.)
- Is Kwang Soo a deity of death? - Yes, he is.
(Se Chan claims his innocence.)
He ripped off my name tag.
- For goodness' sake. - I am serious.
(He is confused.)
- This is driving me crazy. - Kwang Soo ripped off my name tag.
I am serious.
(What Se Chan claims is true?)
- Whatever. - Don't get fooled.
(He finds something.)
What is it?
Hold on. Why is the moving camera on me?
(Wait a minute.)
This is too much.
(The moving camera is following Se Chan.)
Why are there three cameras on me?
(They are all going to suspect him...)
Everyone will be out to get me.
(if the moving cameras are following him.)
Kwang Soo, hold on.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan gather together.)
I...
(Screaming)
(There's a sudden scream.)
What was that?
(It's a woman's scream.)
(Who?)
- I heard someone scream. - Hey.
(Why?)
(What just happened?)
What was that?
The scream stopped abruptly.
(They run to the location where they just heard the scream.)
Where did that come from?
- No way. - Did you get eliminated?
(The person who screamed was...)
(Sora.)
Did you get eliminated?
(But...)
(she's holding a name tag.)
- My gosh, seriously. - This is crazy.
(Sora was in the lecture room alone with Jae Suk,)
- Hey. - I guess I was wrong.
- Jae Suk eliminated her. - He's the deity of death.
(and her name tag got ripped off.)
That means he's the deity of death.
(Then is Jae Suk the deity of death?)
I'm only holding my name tag.
- He's the deity of death. - Sora is unbelievable.
(But Jae Suk appeals.)
- He's the deity of death. - Everything happened so quickly.
- She took off her own name tag? - Yes.
(She took off her own name tag?)
You're saying she took off her own name tag?
(It's all Sora's scenario?)
But we ran over here because we heard a woman scream.
What's going on?
(Sora argues Jae Suk ripped off her name tag.)
- What's going on? - My gosh, Sora is unbelievable.
(Jae Suk argues Sora's putting on a show.)
You're the deity of death.
I'm sure that a woman screamed.
(Who's telling the truth?)
(One of them is acting.)
- Yes. - Yes, it was.
- But... - But seriously...
My gosh, I'm lost for words.
(Jae Suk appeals.)
Whoever screamed sounded really urgent.
But if Sora's faking this, it's actually really creepy.
- No, wait. - Seriously.
I bet she screamed because it wasn't Jae Suk.
(In the end,)
(she pleads her innocence with all her body.)
- I swear. - What's the matter?
- What's wrong? - This is what people do...
(Listen to me.)
- when they feel upset. - Who was it?
- Why are you lying down? - Let me tell you...
(Then Jong Kook joins them.)
- what I think. - It's not her.
(Abruptly)
- It's not her. - Why?
I read the hint. It's not her.
Really?
(Jong Kook read the hint?)
- Really? - What did it say?
- You saw the hint? - I read the hint.
(What did the hint say?)
- What was it? - The deities of death...
(He shares the hint he saw.)
My gosh, what's this?
(A moment ago)
(Jong Kook finds a hint about the deities of death.)
"The deities of death aren't any of the female guests."
(The deities of death aren't any of the female guests.)
None of the female guests are the deity of death.
(That means Sora and Yeo Been aren't the deities of death.)
It's not any of our female guests.
(He shares the hint.)
(Then...)
Really?
- That means it's me. - I knew it.
(Jae Suk admits.)
(I caught you, you darn deity of death!)
- Look at him. - I'm sorry.
(She almost got framed.)
What's the matter with you?
- It's these two. - I'm sorry.
(So far, there are 3 deities of death.)
Stop it.
(Deities of death: 1. Jae Suk,)
(2. Kwang Soo or Se Chan,)
- It's these two. - I'm sorry.
- My gosh. - There are two...
(3. And someone yet unknown)
- Get lost. - out of these three.
(Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, Se Chan)
I swear it's not me.
- This is a misunderstanding. - It's 2 out of these 3.
You guys are unbelievable.
(Shameless)
That was such an obvious hint.
Jae Suk was...
We're going to pick the second deity of death.
(Earlier, they picked two more deities of death.)
(The result of the draw)
(Jae Suk got picked as the deity of death.)
We'll let you know via text.
(They picked another deity of death.)
(Who are the other 2 deities of death?)
- The actual shoot... - No, it's not me.
(Jae Suk's identity is revealed.)
might be over already.
(Maybe)
(Shush!)
(The deity of death gets angry.)
Why did you hit me?
(If Jae Suk is a deity of death,)
Are you kidding me?
(then is the other deity of death Kwang Soo or Se Chan?)
The race is over.
My gosh, I can't believe he was the deity of death.
(One of the deities of death is revealed.)
Before we move on to Round Three, let's pick two more people.
(They draw the deities of death before the next mission.)
We're picking two more deities of death?
(Who will be my colleague?)
I need more allies.
Because the same person might get picked?
(There's a possibility of overlapping.)
Yes, if the same person gets picked, it won't count.
(They pick two more deities of death who don't overlap.)
(With 2 more of them, now there are 5 deities of death in total.)
4 teams will compete in a team of 3 for the final mission,
(The final mission of today)
"I'm Scared You Might Burst If I Touch You."
(I'm Scared You Might Burst If I Touch You.)
Each team will take turns.
(3 people form a group, and 2 people will wear an air suit,)
Two people will wear an air suit...
and explain a word to their member using only their bodies.
(and explain a word to their member using only their bodies.)
And that member needs to get it right.
(And that member needs to get it right.)
Whoever gets more right will get a hint on the reincarnated members.
- The reincarnated members? - I see.
Please discuss which team you're all going to be in.
(They need to form a team to do the mission.)
Can't we just stick to our old teams?
- Yes, good idea. - That's a good idea.
(If they stick to the old teams,)
But if we get something right,
(Jae Suk and Sora are on the same team.)
Jae Suk will also find out about the reincarnated members.
Yes, he'll end up knowing.
(That's a no.)
Can't we just leave him out of the game?
(We already know Jae Suk is a deity of death.)
Let's just leave him out.
(Jae Suk can't say anything because he's already revealed.)
- That's nonsense. - You're going to tell us who it is?
How about this?
Let's put Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan in one team.
(Jong Kook wants to put Jae Suk, Kwang Soo and Se Chan on one team.)
- Yes, let's do that. - Come here.
(They're putting the candidates on the same team with Jae Suk.)
- Let's put them in one team. - Then we'll know.
- What's going on? - You're all in one team.
Why should I be on this team?
(He realizes it now.)
- I'm not it. - Why are you...
- doing this to me? - Good idea.
(Now I'm relieved.)
- I'm not it. - How about we put Sora...
One of them is a deity of death.
(At least, one of them is a deity of death.)
- Yes. - Yes.
I see you have your arm around Se Chan's shoulder.
(Does that mean Se Chan is the deity of death?)
What is the matter with you? Seriously!
(What is the matter with you?)
What's wrong with you?
You guys look so close.
(Is Se Chan the deity of death?)
I feel so close to you.
(Or is Jae Suk trying to confuse them?)
My gosh.
(The teams are formed.)
Don't let him fool you guys.
(Teams)
His face is red.
I really think it's Se Chan.
This is cute.
(Se Chan is the gorilla. Kwang Soo is the polar bear.)
(Hugging)
Who is this?
(Why is she suddenly hugging him?)
- Who is it? - What's wrong with you, So Min?
The gorilla is so cute.
(The gorilla is cute.)
- What's with you? - He's so cute.
(Is it the gorilla that's cute or is it Se Chan?)
I thought we were just friends.
(Kissing)
- What's this? - What are you doing?
(She suddenly kisses him.)
- You're so cute. - Who was that?
- Will you cut it out? - That was So Min.
(What's up with them?)
- Hey. - I'm just playing.
The gorilla costume looks so cute.
(Everyone's puzzled by So Min expressing affection.)
What's with you?
The bear is really cute too.
(She slaps him.)
(They're both cute, but she treats them differently.)
Hey!
- Why are you hitting him? - Why are you hitting me?
(You said I'm cute. Why did you slap me?)
- The costumes look so cute. - Kwang Soo, you're done.
(So Min's tough expression brings the polar bear to his senses.)
- I'll get it right. - You guys look so cute.
- They're cute. - Okay.
(The game begins.)
Okay, go.
Ready, get set...
(With two cute animals,)
(how will Jae Suk do as a team?)
Go!
(First quiz: Heat pack)
(They think carefully.)
(The bear and gorilla try to explain in their own unique ways.)
What are they doing?
- What? - He is a deity of death.
(They try so hard to communicate with Jae Suk.)
It's cold? It's cold?
(Jae Suk, the animal communicator, slowly understands them.)
- Kwang Soo's pretty good. - It's cold?
(Kwang Soo is proud.)
His hands are saying so much.
It's cold?
(He uses his cute polar bear paws to explain the word.)
A heat pack?
(He gets it right.)
(Second quiz: Rice cooker)
(The bear makes small movements.)
(The gorilla makes big movements.)
What? I don't get it.
- Rice? - He's almost there.
- Stew? Is it stew? - He's explaining.
(No!)
A stew?
(The body language of a polar bear)
- That's a no. - He just crossed his hands.
He's so cute.
(He's so cute.)
The bear says no.
A stew? A meal?
(The polar bear knows how to express himself.)
A meal? No?
(While the polar bear struggles...)
A pot?
Hey, gorilla. Will you do a better job?
(Se Chan)
Hey, you need to do better.
(Unlike the shy bear,)
(the gorilla is dancing.)
Hey, what is he doing?
(Regardless of the mission,)
My gosh, are you serious?
(the gorilla is excited.)
- He's so cute. - Hey, polar bear!
- He's so cute. - Explain!
(The ape's swag)
Polar bear, explain!
(He can only count on the polar bear.)
The polar bear is so shy.
(He's huge, but he's very shy.)
- Why is he so shy? - Hey!
Will you please explain properly?
He's so timid and kind.
- That's not the polar bear I know. - He's so cute.
Why are his arms so short?
Hey, polar bear!
(The polar bear struggles outside of home.)
Move on to the next one.
(They move on to the next question.)
You need to explain properly.
(The next quiz: Bidet)
You guys can work together to explain the word.
Toilet seat!
(He guesses it wrong.)
Jae Suk is having a hard time getting it right.
(Describe properly!)
What is it? I don't get it.
(As Jae Suk scolds them,)
- Your costume is getting deflated. - It's losing air.
(the polar bear looks very discouraged.)
- It's losing air. - Look at him.
Jae Suk, you just discouraged him.
It's okay again.
(He seems okay, but at the same time,)
Jae Suk, you just discouraged him. It's okay again.
Look. He's looking down.
(the polar bear is discouraged again.)
Hey! Chin up! Hold your head up high!
(Sparta)
Look at him listening to you.
He's trying really hard. He's very kind.
(He's trying really hard. He's very kind.)
- He's so cute. - He's just a little shy.
(The polar bear is working hard in a foreign country.)
What?
Hey, polar bear. You need to do better.
(And today, he really misses his family in the North Pole.)
Jae Suk, you just discouraged him. It's okay again.
Hey! Are you dying?
- Are you dying? - It's okay now.
(Your compliment saves the polar bear.)
Hurry up.
(The bidet is too hard for animals.)
What is it?
That's not it.
(How will they cooperate to describe the bidet?)
- Why are you guys kissing? - Waist!
(Surprised)
Waist! Hey, wait...
(It becomes the animal kingdom while working on a quiz.)
What are you guys doing? Are you serious?
(They suddenly start showing too much affection.)
What are you guys doing?
(He punishes them for being too sexual.)
Come to your senses!
(Don't go against the way of nature.)
(We were too focused.)
- What do you think you're doing? - This is so funny.
(I love it.)
- Just move on. - Next!
(It was hot, but they had to pass it.)
- This one is so hard. - How is he going to get this one?
This one is so hard.
(The next quiz: Instant glue)
- This one is so hard. - How is he going to get this one?
(How will the animals describe the word?)
My gosh.
(Sticking)
What's this?
- What? - What are they doing?
(The polar bear and gorilla stick together and stay still.)
What's this?
(The polar bear is looking far away,)
(and the gorilla has his face buried in the polar bear's chest.)
What is this?
(They're glued together.)
- He really can't get this one. - This is so funny.
- He can't get it right. - Next.
(They pass this question too.)
This one is hard as well.
(Contact lens)
What is it?
Look at him.
(Looking for something)
(He uses his paws to explain the details.)
(He tries his best to use his paws.)
- Eyes! - My gosh.
- Eyes! - This is so funny.
Glasses! Contact lenses!
- Contact lenses! - Yes, he got it right.
(Contact lens is correct.)
- Great. - That's it.
You guys got five right.
(Team Jae Suk answered 5 questions within 5 minutes.)
- That's a lot. - We did very well.
(Good job.)
Great job.
Next team, please choose one person.
(Next)
What's that?
(Jae Hong is the bear. Sora is the dinosaur.)
Tent!
(Team Haha guessed 6 quizzes right.)
- Car! - No.
(Yeo Been is the bear. Ji Hyo is the dinosaur.)
Motorcycle!
(Team Suk Jin guessed 7 quizzes right.)
(So Min puts on the gorilla costume and explains very passionately.)
Look at So Min.
(Sung Oh is in a dinosaur costume.)
(Thanks to So Min's effort to help him get the answers,)
Is she running?
Fire extinguisher!
(Team Jong Kook answered all 10 quizzes within 5 minutes.)
You got all 10 questions right.
- So Min did a great job. - Nice.
(He loved the gorilla.)
Great job.
Will the winning team please come forward?
(Team Jong Kook will get a hint on the reincarnated members.)
- We'll give you a hint. - Should we keep it from Sung Oh?
(He's suspicious of Sung Oh.)
- Why? - Never mind. Come on.
(Scary)
You can see it too. Great job.
This is a hint about the reincarnated members?
(What kind of hint will they get?)
Yes, the reincarnated members.
You're going to tell us?
Reincarnated members...
aren't among any of the younger members of Running Man.
(The reincarnated members aren't the younger members of Running Man.)
(Then Se Chan and So Min aren't the reincarnated members.)
This is confusing.
The hint was given.
For 30 minutes, we will have the final name tag elimination.
- 30 minutes? - If you don't come to a conclusion,
(If you don't come to a conclusion in 30 minutes,)
we will open the stage where the identities will be revealed.
(there will be a stage where the real identities are revealed.)
Three members can go up the stage at the same time.
(3 members can go up the stage at the same time.)
If all three of them are regular members,
(If all three of them are the ordinary members,)
the reincarnated members and regular members win.
(the reincarnated members and ordinary members win.)
(If even one of them is a deity of death,)
If even one of them is a deity of death,
(the deities of death win.)
the deities of death win.
The reincarnated members can use a special method...
(The reincarnated members can use a special method...)
to check the members' identities.
(to check the members' identities.)
Each of them can rip off one name tag...
(Each of them can remove one name tag to eliminate a deity of death.)
to eliminate a deity of death.
If all reincarnated members are out before the stage opens,
(If all reincarnated members are out before the platform opens,)
the race will end immediately.
(the race will end immediately.)
Please go to your designated spots...
(They go to their designated spots.)
before the race begins.
(Who are the reincarnated members and deities of death?)
I don't know if it's Se Chan or Kwang Soo.
Who could it be?
(Who's the deity of death between the two?)
Maybe both of them are the deities of death.
(Both of them could be the deities of death.)
I need to know who the reincarnated members are.
(To protect them or to eliminate them?)
Who are they?
The one I think is a reincarnated member...
is Sung Oh.
Sung Oh and Jae Hong.
(Suk Jin thinks Sung Oh and Jae Hong are the reincarnated members.)
(Walking around)
(Jae Hong is walking around.)
Sung Oh.
(Sung Oh enters the room.)
(Are Sung Oh and Jae Hong meeting in secret?)
Sung Oh.
I should pretend to be a regular member, right?
That's right.
(The two come up with a strategy.)
No one is suspecting you.
Whose name tag should I rip off?
(Are they the reincarnated members or deities of death?)
Then people will know...
that both of us are the reincarnated members.
(Are both of them the reincarnated members?)
Find and go to the location of the members.
(They had a preliminary mission on the last week's episode.)
(Sung Oh's van)
(Ripping off)
Sung Oh,
(What's going on?)
you are out.
(But I haven't even gotten started.)
I was outside the van.
(He talks nonsense.)
(Jae Hong's name tag gets ripped off too.)
(What are you doing?)
I will put it back on.
(Is this a prank? What's going on?)
What was that?
Am I out?
(Puzzled)
- What... - You are a reincarnated member...
(You are a reincarnated member who came back to life.)
who came back to life.
Another reincarnated member is...
(Sung Oh and Jae Hong found out about each other's identity.)
Sung Oh.
Jae Hong.
There are more deities of death.
(That's how Sung Oh and Jae Hong were reincarnated.)
I will tell you how you can check other members' identities.
(The bigger number of the deities of death is disadvantageous to them.)
Find the name tags that are hidden...
(They have to find name tags hidden in the building.)
in the building.
If you collect three name tags, we will give you...
(If they collect 3 name tags, they'll get...)
the number of the deities of death out of the three.
(the number of the deities of death out of the three.)
- Out of the three? - Yes.
We need three name tags.
From the number,
we can ascertain our guesses and eliminate the deities of death.
I will rip off Se Chan's name tag.
(Jae Hong is sure Se Chan is a deity of death.)
- Really? - Yes. I am sure it's him.
Then you should do it.
Let's begin.
This is too hard.
(The race is too hard for the reincarnated members.)
(He doesn't hide that he is a deity of death.)
5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
(The deity of death candidates are after the reincarnated members.)
The race starts.
The deities of death need to work.
(The official deity of death)
(The official deity of death goes to the members.)
- Tell me if you are reincarnated... - Suk Jin.
- Go away. - Please go someplace else.
(Go away, the deity of death.)
Go away.
We don't want to talk to a deity of death.
(The deity of death is not welcomed anywhere.)
Jae Hong, are you a reincarnated member?
(He's straightforward.)
I am a regular member.
- Go away. - I am serious.
Do we agree...
(Is everyone here ordinary members?)
everyone else except for Jae Suk is a regular member?
Suk Jin is the one...
- who is the closest to death. - What? Why?
- His age... - Don't talk about reality.
Why did you suddenly bring up death?
(Why is she suddenly talking about real death?)
He could be a deity of death.
What are you playing at?
- He could be a deity of death. - You could die at any age.
- You can't... - You could die at any age.
You can't make a guess that way.
(After exchanging curses,)
(Jae Hong is busy looking for name tags.)
(He finds the first name tag!)
(It's Se Chan, the member Jae Hong suspects the most!)
I want to find another one.
(He needs to find 2 more name tags.)
Would it be in here?
Keep looking.
(The crew wouldn't hide it by the switchboard.)
There it is!
(There it is!)
No, that's a prop.
Really?
(Sung Oh is bad at finding the name tags.)
(But he doesn't give up and continues to look for name tags.)
They hid them too well.
Sung Oh.
(What is he doing there?)
(Did she see me looking for name tags?)
- Sung Oh, what exactly are you? - What?
You could be a deity of death. I'm confused.
(He looks suspicious.)
- You are a deity of death, right? - I...
(He's approaching cheerfully.)
How could you ask me that so suddenly?
- Seriously. - I am a regular member.
- Me too. - Really?
(Everyone claims to be a regular member.)
What are you?
Here is what I figured out.
(He's very serious.)
The production crew assigned...
the reincarnated members, deities of death,
and something else.
(Something else?)
We need to find the being between the first two,
(Serious)
Young Gu.
(He brings up Young Gu in haste.)
There is Young Gu among the regular members?
(Watching Ji Hyo)
(There is no way Ji Hyo would fall for this lie.)
(She falls for it.)
That's what I figured out.
(Okay, I got her.)
(He holds his laughter.)
If one of us is a deity of death...
So we need to find the link.
(She has no doubt about Young Gu.)
Let's hide first.
There are cameramen. We can't hide by ourselves.
(Will you have a meeting without the cameras?)
(Reincarnation of Young Gu?)
My kids do that.
(I thought I could hide by myself.)
My kids hide their faces and tell me to look for them.
So Min!
- Listen to me for a second. - Did you figure something out?
Be suspicious of Jong Kook.
(For a deity of death)
- Be suspicious Jong Kook? Why? - Be suspicious of Jong Kook.
(Se Chan tells So Min to be suspicious of Jong Kook.)
- A deity of death? - I think he corners me...
- because he is a deity of death. - What do you mean?
- Why? - He corners me too much.
(He suspects Jong Kook and pleads his innocence.)
The deities of death know each other.
What did you say?
(Say that again.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - I am recording. What did you say?
(Why did she turn the camera on...)
Why are you recording when there are cameras everywhere?
(when there are so many cameras?)
Come on. What about Jong Kook?
There is a chance Jong Kook is a deity of death.
(Still, Se Chan doesn't refuse to do it.)
That must be why he corners me.
You recorded it...
(You recorded it to see Se Chan when you miss him, right?)
to see Se Chan when you miss him, right?
(Is it for personal use?)
Right?
(Stop making it so obvious.)
- So Min. - So Min.
You are so weird on the show.
(That's not it.)
(Don't do the show for personal use.)
- A deity of death said this. - What?
(Everyone, get this.)
- He is a deity of death. - He is.
(She shares the video of Se Chan with everyone.)
- He is a deity of death. - It's highly likely.
- He is a deity of death. - Just look at him.
That's it.
Did you film this video because you like him?
- Hey. - Stop it.
There is no other reason to film it.
(Everyone shows the same response.)
Why did you film it when there are so many cameras?
(It's a rational suspicion.)
- It's not like that. - It's for personal use, right?
- She will watch it every night. - She did it...
(We've been in love too.)
because she was embarrassed.
(Leave the personal agenda out of this race.)
Hey, earlier...
(Jae Hong is looking for name tags.)
There it is!
(He finds the second name tag!)
(Jeon Yeo Been)
(He obtains Yeo Been's name tag!)
(He continues to look for the hint.)
(He finds the third name tag!)
(Ji Suk Jin)
I collected three name tags.
If you collect three name tags, we will give you...
(Jeon Yeo Been)
(When they collect 3 name tags,)
the number of the deities of death out of the three.
(they can check the number of deities of death among the three.)
How many deities of death...
(Careful)
- The number is... - Yes.
(Among the three of them,)
- How many deities of death... - The number is...
(how many deities of death exist?)
- 1. - 1?
(Among the 3 of them, 1 deity of death exists.)
(There's a deity of death among Suk Jin, Yeo Been and Se Chan.)
I will rip off Se Chan's name tag.
- Really? - Yes. I am sure it's him.
(Jae Hong was sure Se Chan is a deity of death.)
Then you should do it.
You must know.
- Know what? - My identity.
Of course, I do.
(Certain)
You are a deity of death.
This is driving me crazy.
(Everyone's suspicious of Se Chan.)
You are scaring me.
Go rip off someone's name tag.
(While Se Chan is accused of being a deity of death...)
- Seriously. - If you are wrong...
Right now, I should be...
(Ripping)
- What was that? - Why did you rip off my name tag?
- Seriously. - Right now,
(Jong Kook's name tag...)
(gets ripped off!)
I should be...
- What was that? - Why did you rip off my name tag?
(What is going on?)
Why did you rip off my name tag?
(Sora suddenly ripped off Jong Kook's name tag.)
(He hasn't figured out what's going on.)
I will get...
- What? - I will get another badge.
- Why did you rip off my name tag? - I will get another badge.
(And)
(Ripping)
(She rips off Se Chan's name tag as well.)
You can only rip off one name tag.
(Only the reincarnated members and...)
What was that?
(the deities of death can rip off name tags.)
You can't rip off two name tags.
(If she's a reincarnated member...)
What is going on?
(Sora ripped off two name tags in an instant.)
Sora.
What is going on? Did someone rip off a name tag?
(And the members are gathering to check what's going on.)
- What is going on? - I don't know!
I thought she was a ghost!
(What's going on?)
I peed my pants a little!
(Only the deity of death can rip name tags off twice.)
- What is going on? - What did you do?
I was getting a bit bored.
- What does that mean? - Are you a deity of death?
(What is Sora's identity?)
It's not any of our female guests.
(Sora was a regular member at this point.)
(Before Round 3, more deities of death were picked.)
(Kang Sora)
(Sora became a deity of death.)
I might as well rip off name tags. There isn't much time.
(If anyone is suspicious...)
(As she couldn't narrow down the reincarnated members,)
- This has never happened before. - This is insane.
(she ripped off the name tags.)
I was just standing still.
(Se Chan is upset.)
- This is crazy! So you know now! - Who eliminated them?
Who eliminated them?
(If Sora, the deity of death, ripped off Se Chan's name tag...)
- Sora ripped off my name tag. - That means he is a regular member.
(Se Chan is a regular member.)
- Kwang Soo. - That means he is a deity of death.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan are proven to be the ordinary members.)
- Kwang Soo is it. - He is a deity of death.
He is a deity of death.
(Kwang Soo is a deity of death.)
Hey, you!
- Hey, you! - For goodness' sake!
- Hey! - That's not how you play!
- Why did you do that? - That's not how you play!
(I made so much effort.)
Sora!
Do you want to be a deity of death?
(Do you want to be a deity of death?)
- I would feel more comfortable. - Okay.
(Acting)
(Testing)
- What are you? - I am a reincarnated member.
(He sounds Kwang Soo out.)
(Kwang Soo was sure Se Chan was a reincarnated member.)
Really?
Hold on.
Hold on. I was lying.
(He runs to Se Chan.)
I was lying.
(Ripping)
I am...
(Kwang Soo thought Se Chan was a reincarnated member.)
(He put the name tag back on.)
- Hey! - Things were going too slow!
Why did you rip off Se Chan's name tag?
(Sora made the deity of death to confess.)
What were you thinking?
Sora. For goodness' sake.
(She unintentionally attacked Team Deities of Death.)
I mean...
Jong Kook, I hate you.
(Sorry for doubting you, Se Chan.)
Jong Kook.
Where are Sung Oh and Jae Hong?
(Where are Sung Oh and Jae Hong?)
I mean...
(Sung Oh and Jae Hong are looking for hints.)
Where are they?
(The rest of the members starts looking for the two.)
Jae Hong isn't here either. Where did he go?
Anyone who isn't here is either a deity of death...
or a reincarnated member.
- I'm right here. - I'm sure of it.
- Those who aren't here... - I'm right here.
(They begin to suspect Sung Oh and Jae Hong.)
- are definitely... - Jae Hong isn't here.
either a deity of death...
(I think Sung Oh and Jae Hong are acting suspiciously.)
- Or a reincarnated member. - or a reincarnated member.
I'm sure they're here.
- Jae Suk. - We need to get Jae Hong.
(We need to rip off their name tags.)
We need to eliminate Jae Hong and Sung Oh.
- Hurry. - Where are they going?
- Hurry. - If we don't do it, we'll die.
(They begin to search for the reincarnated members.)
We'll die.
- Let's go. - We need to go together.
(A deity of death can rip off up to 2 name tags.)
- We have to eliminate them. - This is crazy.
Over there.
Someone's there.
(They've found someone.)
This is crazy.
(Jae Hong is looking for a hint.)
Someone's there.
(And they run toward him.)
They're running!
(As soon as the deities of death are on the move,)
- We need to catch them! - We need to catch them!
(the remaining members go after the deities of death.)
They're running! We need to catch them.
Look!
(Jae Hong runs away after he sees them come after him.)
(Jong Kook tries to help the reincarnated members.)
Kwang Soo! Hey!
(Jae Suk blocks Jong Kook.)
- Kwang Soo, eliminate him! - Hey!
- Catch him! - Kwang Soo, eliminate him!
(Jae Suk's defense)
You need to catch him!
Eliminate him!
(The deities of death will win the race...)
(if they eliminate all the reincarnated members.)
(The distance between them keeps getting closer.)
Go!
(Of the 2 reincarnated members,)
Jae Hong, run!
(1 could now get eliminated.)
(Jae Hong is in trouble,)
Jae Hong!
(and Se Chan, a regular member, comes to the rescue.)
Jae Suk!
(Se Chan protects Jae Hong.)
You darn deity of death.
- Come here. - Jae Suk!
(Jae Hong approaches Kwang Soo after seeing Se Chan.)
You darn punk!
Wait.
(Now, Kwang Soo is outnumbered.)
- Be careful. - I'll hold him.
Hurry. Do it.
(He quickly approaches Kwang Soo's name tag.)
(Ripping)
- Okay! - Nice!
(Swift)
(Kwang Soo, the deity of death, gets eliminated!)
Jae Hong!
Kwang Soo, the deity of death, is now eliminated.
He was the deity of death?
(They finally introduce themselves.)
- Yes. - I'm so angry.
(We are on the same team!)
I almost had him!
Kang Sora!
(He's angry at Sora for ruining everything.)
(Jae Hong and Se Chan succeed in eliminating Kwang Soo.)
(Reincarnated Members, Deities of Death)
(Kwang Soo is eliminated)
My gosh, it must've been hard.
(Now the ordinary members know who the reincarnated members are.)
Seriously. How did you two manage?
(Jae Suk sees Kwang Soo who's on his way to the jail.)
- Kwang Soo. - Jae Suk.
What happened? You didn't catch them?
- I got eliminated. - You didn't get Jae Hong?
(He doesn't know what to say.)
(I can't believe you didn't get Jae Hong's name tag.)
There's something I didn't tell you.
I could ask about three people.
(Something he didn't say?)
And I asked about Se Chan, Yeo Been,
(Jae Hong shares the hidden mission hint with the members.)
- and Suk Jin. - How many are there?
Out of those 3 people, 1 of them is a deity of death.
(One of Suk Jin, Yeo Been, and Se Chan is the deity of death.)
So two people are innocent.
- It's either Yeo Been or Suk Jin. - One of them is innocent.
(Other than Se Chan, who proved himself a regular member,)
- Yeo Been, what are you? - Yes?
- What are you? - What about you?
(Either Suk Jin or Yeo Been is the deity of death!)
- What are you? - You tell me first.
What are you, Suk Jin?
(One of them is acting.)
I'm just a normal person.
- Really? - Yes.
Should we go together?
(Which one is the hidden deity of death?)
Sure.
(Ripping)
I can't believe you attacked me from behind.
Suk Jin ripped off my name tag!
Here's a penalty badge for you.
(Suk Jin's name tag is ripped off.)
- Yeo Been is a deity of death! - Suk Jin tried to eliminate me!
(They accuse each other of ripping off their name tags.)
- Yeo Been took off my name tag! - Suk Jin ripped off my nametag!
- I'm serious. Stay away from him. - Who did it?
- Yeo Been attacked me from behind. - Stay away from Suk Jin.
- Stay away from him. - You're lying.
Yeo Been obviously tried to take off his name tag.
(Chaotic)
She took my name tag off.
- She's a deity of death. - I'm serious.
- She's a deity of death. - Stay away from her.
Yeo Been is a deity of death.
- Yeo Been did this to him. - Look.
(They suspect Yeo Been after seeing Suk Jin's name tag.)
- She did it. - Take a look at this.
- He's putting on an act. - Yeo Been is a deity of death.
(Is she telling the truth? Or is she lying?)
- She's a deity of death. - Yeo Been is a deity of death.
(The identity of the deity of death remains a mystery.)
You're a deity of death.
- What? - Yeo Been is a deity of death.
(Even the members passing by join.)
- She took my name tag off. Look. - Really?
- It's Yeo Been? - She attacked me from behind.
(One of them is the deity of death.)
These three are all deities of death.
(They both argue that the other person is the deity of death.)
- She took it off from behind. - I'm just a normal person.
You saw that, right?
Right now... Gosh, this is hard to tell.
(Jae Hong is watching the situation in a distance.)
Don't go near Jae Suk. Come here.
Sora... Sora's okay for now.
(Sora is also watching.)
She can't take off any name tags.
- Suk Jin. - I don't need anything.
(Everyone's identity is still not confirmed.)
- Stay right there. - I'm totally fine.
- You stay there as well. - Me too.
Stay there.
(They strengthen their guard.)
Wait.
(At that moment,)
- Is it him? - Look at her.
- Wait, is it him? - Look at her.
(Yeo Been suddenly starts running towards Jae Hong.)
- What are you doing? - Let me see.
- What are you doing? - Show me.
(Why is she running towards him?)
What's wrong with her?
- Hold her still. - She's a deity of death.
(From a distance)
Hold her still.
- Stay away. - Stand back.
(Which one of you is the deity of death?)
She's being weird. Look.
(A complete chaos)
What is she doing?
I'm telling you! She tore my name tag off!
(He is pleading his innocence.)
- Exactly. - So get over here.
(His facial expressions speak the truth.)
- You're really scary. - Stay there.
Suk Jin isn't a good actor.
- Hold her still. - I'm so upset.
(Absolutely confident)
He really means it.
- Suk Jin is really angry. - I'm so angry.
(Just like Suk Jin said, is Yeo Been the deity of death?)
Yeo Been is the deity.
- We can't trust Haha either. - We can't trust him.
Are you kidding me? You're unbelievable.
(Haha could be the deity of death.)
So Min isn't safe either.
(Which two of these five are the deities of death?)
- I'm sorry. It's just for now. - Let's go.
- The deities of death... - Let's check.
(Team Reincarnation holds an emergency meeting.)
- There's Haha, So Min, - So Min...
- and Ji Hyo. - and Ji Hyo.
- Go away, reincarnated members! - Go away, reincarnated members!
- Go away, go away! - Go away!
- We want to be treated fairly! - Treat us like humans!
You guys get all the camera time!
We're working too!
(The deities of death and the candidates are approaching.)
Let us work!
- Let's go... - That's the deity of death.
Don't come near him. Run away.
Yeo Been, we just got a hint.
(Throwing a bait)
(You found a hint?)
Right?
We already know that you're the deity of death.
(He lies to her.)
(Is she upset because they're wrong?)
- Right? I'm a normal person. - Yes.
- No way. You can't go. - Can I go there now?
(He is trying to understand the situation.)
- Yeo Been, we already know. - Let me go there now.
- No! - Let me go!
(One of them is acting until the end.)
- I'm going to go, okay? - No way!
My gosh, what's with her?
- They trust me. - No!
(Confident)
No, wait.
(At that moment,)
- No, wait. - Suk Jin can't be here.
(Yeo Been runs towards them.)
- Hey, be careful. - Watch out.
(Yeo Been is the deity of death.)
- Be careful. She's scary. - Suk Jin can't be here.
(Suk Jin and Yeo Been are confronting each other.)
Hold her tight.
(Ripping)
(Yeo Been's name tag gets ripped off.)
Hold her tight.
(Sung Oh rips off Yeo Been's name tag.)
We got fooled.
I'm not the deity of death. It's not me.
Now, we know for sure.
(The identity of the deity of death)
- It's okay. - That was a good guess.
(Is Yeo Been really the deity of death?)
(Or is she just a regular member who got framed?)
- Are you out, Kwang Soo? - Yes.
- Me too. - What?
(Yeo Been moves to the jail.)
Normal people can also get eliminated?
(What?)
(Yeo Been is a regular member?)
A reincarnated member tore off my name tag.
- She's a normal person? - We know the answer now.
(Yeo Been is a regular member!)
Okay, we got it. Hey, Sung Oh.
- We got it. - She's a normal person?
(If Yeo Been is a regular member,)
- Good. - She's a normal person.
That means Suk Jin is a deity of death.
(then Suk Jin is the deity of death!)
- Suk Jin is a deity of death. - It's him.
It happened a while ago.
(Ripping)
(Suk Jin ripped off her name tag when no one was looking.)
What are you? A reincarnated member?
- I'm a normal person. - Be quiet.
(Feeling wronged)
Suk Jin just ripped off my name tag!
(Look here!)
(Sora and Suk Jin come up with a lie.)
I can't believe you attacked me from behind.
(They make it look like his name tag was ripped off.)
Yeo Been took off my name tag! Look!
(Suk Jin acted like he was the one who got attacked.)
The race is over. Please gather around in front of the platform.
(The time is up.)
You thought I was a normal person, didn't you?
(Satisfied)
- Yes, totally. - Right?
(Completely fooled)
Everyone's gotten so good at this.
Suk Jin is a great actor.
(Suk Jin is getting better at conning members.)
He was a deity of death?
Seriously.
(Even the actor admits it.)
The race is finally over.
However, the reincarnated members are still alive.
The reincarnated members can discuss with each other...
(The reincarnated members will win if they pick 3 ordinary members.)
and put three people on the platform.
- Three people? - Reincarnated members will lose...
(They will lose if one of them is the deity of death.)
if they pick a deity of death.
If not, they'll win.
(They will win if they only pick the ordinary members.)
We know for sure that Suk Jin,
(Suk Jin, Jae Suk, and Sora are definitely deities of death.)
Jae Suk, and Sora are deities of death.
Now, we need to choose between Haha, So Min, and Ji Hyo.
(The remaining deity of death is among these three.)
- Who do we know for sure? - But...
(Who is the deity of death?)
It's really not me.
(All 3 of them are pleading their innocence.)
- I swear it's not me. - If you don't pick me,
you'll really regret it.
I don't care.
(Firm)
I want him to bet his entire fortune.
(What is the real identity of So Min...)
(who is angry enough to bet her wealth?)
We're going to draw two deities of death.
(In the first draw,)
(her name didn't get picked.)
(In the end, her name never got picked.)
Why can't I be the deity of death as well?
(So Min is a normal person.)
(She shows how upset she is that he won't believe her.)
I want him to bet his entire fortune.
- So Min is a deity of death. - I'm so upset.
So Min is a deity of death.
(He starts accusing innocent people again.)
- What? - That came out of nowhere.
- He's doing it again. - So Min...
(Here he goes again accusing random people.)
- What's wrong with you? - I'm really not it.
(The first victim)
- So Min, stop lying. - It really isn't me.
- It's really not me. - You've done enough.
(I really am not the one.)
- I promise it's not me. - This is so upsetting.
This is so upsetting.
(Now it's narrowed down to these two.)
I'm so upset.
Ji Hyo came downstairs and asked me...
(A while ago...)
why I was all alone.
(What did Ji Hyo say?)
Then she told me what was happening and warned me to run away.
Sung Oh, everyone's gathered together right now.
(Ji Hyo ran into Sung Oh.)
If you're really a reincarnated member,
you need to be careful. They're all targeting you.
(Ji Hyo advised Sung Oh to hide.)
They're all targeting you.
(Suspicious)
- Why are you smiling? - What?
- I smiled? No, I didn't. - Yes.
- You did. - I didn't smile.
(He found Ji Hyo suspicious when she warned him with a smile.)
I feel like she lied to me.
(Something's strange.)
I didn't lie to you.
And I didn't smile, Sung Oh.
(Ji Hyo has a strange smile until the end.)
My gosh, this is crazy.
- Are you done now? - Yes.
(Which one of the two is a deity of death?)
We'll choose after we hear your last words.
(It's time for their final defense.)
- I'm human. - Why?
Because I'm human!
(He has no proper reasons.)
- That's it? - Did you treat me like a human?
- Did you act like a human? - You!
I stood by you when you were being accused as a deity of death!
(Don't you remember?)
He's right. He stood by me.
(Haha was the only person who defended Se Chan...)
(when everyone else was suspecting Se Chan.)
I was the only one who kept saying you're innocent.
(I am now more confused.)
I feel so upset.
(Both of them argue that they are innocent.)
- It really isn't me. I swear. - I feel really upset.
- I'd rather have humans lose. - I'm really human.
(Frustrated)
I don't care if humans lose even though I am one.
(She is outbursting with frustration.)
The reincarnated members can have their final discussion...
(It's time to make the final decision.)
and put three people on the platform.
(If 1 of the 3 people is a deity of death,)
(Team Reincarnation will lose!)
- Go ahead. - Se Chan.
(Team Reincarnation chooses Se Chan.)
Okay, please step up.
- Jong Kook. - Finally.
(Jong Kook)
Finally.
I can't get soaked today.
(The last person...)
- Me neither. - Let's be a decent human being.
(holds the key to victory.)
- You need to make... - I'll just be a deity of death.
- the right choice as a human being! - They've begun.
(Who will be the final choice of Team Reincarnation?)
- Ji Hyo. - Okay, step up the platform.
(Team Reincarnation chooses Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo.)
I swear I'm not a deity of death. How many times have I told you?
(Haha claims that he is innocent until the end.)
- Okay, then. - You're mistaken.
(If one of them is a deity of death, Team Deities of Death will win!)
Among these three people...
You still have time to cancel.
The deity of death...
Please! You still have time to change your mind!
You still have time!
Among the three of you...
(They weren't certain who the deity of death was until the end.)
(What is the result?)
Among the three of you,
there's no deity of death.
There's no deity of death.
(They made it! The reincarnated members win the race.)
- See? Exactly. - I'm sorry. I suspected you.
- No. - I'm sorry.
(That was close.)
And for your information, So Min wasn't the deity of death either.
See?
Say that louder! Tell them I'm a human!
Say that louder. Tell them I'm a human. Please.
(They're enjoying the victory. They're not interested in So Min.)
(Guys. Human comes first.)
Please. Say that louder.
The reincarnated members were Jae Hong and Sung Oh.
(The reincarnated members are Jae Hong and Sung Oh.)
They were eliminated during the preliminary round this morning.
As for the deities of death who were chosen after each round,
(Then the deities of death are revealed.)
Kwang Soo and Haha were chosen after the first round.
(Kwang Soo and Haha were chosen in the 1st round.)
- Jae Suk and Haha were next. - Come on.
(Jae Suk and Haha were chosen in the 2nd round.)
(Suk Jin and Sora were chosen in the 3rd round.)
- You were chosen. - Suk Jin and Sora were chosen...
after the third round.
I see. So you were a human too.
(Out of the blue)
How many times must I tell you? He just said that too.
(I told you many times.)
- I'm sorry, So Min. - Hold on.
(Heartbroken)
It's so weird. Whenever we get the water bomb, it gets cold.
(Among the 5 deities of death,)
(Jae Suk is exempted from the penalty.)
Is it frozen?
Suk Jin should give the stick on our behalf.
(Jong Kook who had the most number of penalty badges...)
- Me? - Yes.
(will face the penalty.)
I'm sure you have a lot of grudges against him.
(Suk Jin will be the executioner.)
Can I use the side to hit him?
(Can I use the side to hit him?)
- The side of the stick? - Go ahead.
(Do it if you can.)
Is it today?
You, punk.
(He doesn't sound scary at all.)
Do it right!
It's about time Suk Jin taught you a lesson.
(Vicarious satisfaction)
- You need a good beating. - How many?
You need a good beating.
I need an excuse to hit him hard next time.
(Scary)
(Starting today, it's self-defense.)
(Suk Jin's a little intimidated.)
You, punk.
(Repeating himself)
Do it right.
Hey, Suk Jin can be pretty strong.
(I dare you to do it.)
(Striking hard)
(A loud striking sound)
That sounded like it hurt. That was strong.
(He's hitting for real.)
(But Jong Kook is not affected.)
Come on, hit me harder.
It only offended Suk Jin.
Gosh. That was my full swing.
(Flustered)
That wasn't so bad.
Anyway, I'd like to thank the cast of "Secret Zoo."
(The deities of death will face the water canon penalty.)
I hope that your movie will be well-received at the box office.
(Wishing ""Secret Zoo" to be a hit,)
Thank you. I hope your movie is a big hit.
(they finish up with the water canon penalty.)
I hope it's a big hit.
All right. In 1, 2, 3.
(Splashing)
Good job.
(Thanks to Kang Sora, Kim Sung Oh, Ahn Jae Hong, and Jeon Yeo Been...)
Good work.
(for joining us.)
(Running Martial Arts School opens!)
This is new.
Everyone, block it.
(To become the masters of martial arts,)
We did it.
(four masters came to attend the school.)
- Come on! - That was amazing.
(The master of wind, Park Cho Rong)
(The master of water, Kang Han Na)
Han Na.
(But...)
I want to pair up with you.
(is there a possibility of romance at school?)
What's happening? Is this a green light?
I'll follow my heart.
(Did the students follow their hearts...)
(and choose romance over martial arts?)
- I didn't see it coming. - This is how you do it.
(There's no time for that!)
(A secret trade of cards in the back of the school)
This is really important.
- She came determined. - She's really good.
(The master of fire, Keum Sae Rok)
(The master of tree, Lee Joo Young)
- There's the posture. - She seems experienced.
(Which one of them will become the master of martial arts?)
She seems good at this.
(Running Martial Arts School: Trade the Cards)