- Hello. - Hello.
(One cold winter day)
So Min dressed up today.
I'm wearing dress shoes in a long while.
(It's for a new look.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Everyone dressed up for the new start in the new year.)
I'm wearing dress shoes in a long while.
Actually, Jong Kook is on a new show. I saw it.
(Jong Kook's starting a new show.)
- "Fly Shootdori". - Things have gotten friendly now.
- You're promoting other shows. - Right.
- We're a real family. - Right.
(They feel like a family.)
- I started filming "Fly Shootdori." - Yes.
(Se Chan is on Jong Kook's new show.)
Se Chan is on the show with you.
- Se Chan. - Jong Kook,
(Is that a connection?)
- didn't you help him get cast? - Yes, he practically hired me.
I found out that we're filming in Taebaek.
We have to film for two days when I go down there.
I thought I would be really bored there,
(He thought he'll be bored alone in the mountains.)
so I decided to take one of my sidekicks.
Jong Kook, is that why you picked me?
(Now he can say why Se Chan's on his new show.)
That's why you brought me there.
It will be so boring if I go there alone. Don't you agree?
(I can't stand boredom.)
Right.
- I feel comfortable around him. - In a nutshell, he's your doll.
- Right. - Yes.
He keeps me in his pocket.
(Pocket doll Se Chan)
When he tells me to come out, I come out.
He's a doll you keep next to you when going to sleep.
(Jong Kook feels anxious to be away from Doll Chan.)
I knew it.
Doll Chan, you're something else.
(It's a combination of doll and Se Chan.)
- Doll Chan. - Doll Chan.
(Doll Chan)
It's a combination of "doll" and "Se Chan."
- Seriously. - My gosh.
(Doll Chan sounds cute.)
That's crazy.
So Min was bored either at the end or in the beginning...
(So Min was bored, so she called Se Chan.)
of the year, so she called Se Chan.
Se Chan told her that he was on his way to Taebaek.
- She said she was very lonely... - Really?
(So Min felt lonely this winter without Se Chan.)
- at the beginning of the year. - I'm sorry.
I took away the doll you're attached to.
Gosh, the doll she's attached to?
(The conflict of the custody around the doll)
I took away the doll you're attached to.
Gosh, the doll she's attached to?
- I'm a doll? - Hey, let's share him.
(Everyone wants Doll Chan.)
Let's share him.
- He's a doll I cannot touch. - Is that so?
- I see. - When it snowed earlier,
(So Min was looking at the snow outside...)
So Min was standing by the window and was watching the snow...
(and felt sentimental.)
by herself. I thought to myself, "My gosh, So Min."
But the automatic door opened, and she got squashed.
(The unexpected automatic door)
- She's a true TV entertainer. - I'm serious.
- She's a real TV entertainer. - I missed that.
(It breaks the mood.)
- I should have seen that. - So Min, what were you doing?
- I was so embarrassed. - Her life is entertaining.
(Whispering)
(When did Jong Kook see that?)
Before you start your race, only one guest will join you today.
- We only invited one. - Really?
- There's only one guest. - Really?
(The only guest?)
Please come on in.
- Gosh, it's the only guest today. - Who is it?
(Anticipating)
- The only guest of the day. - The stairs?
- It's been a while. - The guest is coming. Who is it?
She's wearing a pink jacket and boots.
(Catchy pink winter jacket...)
It's been a while since I saw those long boots.
(with long boots for horseback riding)
People usually wear them when they go horseback riding.
I think she's been on variety shows.
(Who's the guest in the extraordinary look?)
- She's... - She's very... Is that Jin Young?
- Who is it? - Who is it?
(Shy)
- It's not Jin Young. - Han Na?
- Is she... - Hello.
(The most lovely, Park Ha Na)
- It's Ha Na. - It's Ha Na.
(The actress won over the viewers with her countless charms.)
Fine. Keep living like that!
- It's Ha Na. - It's Ha Na.
(Nice to meet you.)
- My goodness. - Please stand in the middle.
- How are you? It's been a while. - Park Ha Na.
We were told we'd have only one guest, and Ha Na came.
(It's her 4th time to be on the show.)
(Now it feels like she's a member of the Running Man family now.)
Ha Na... I think you were on our show quite recently.
(It's been a year, but it's never awkward to see her.)
- It's been a year. - Really?
- It's already been a year? - I saw a rerun of the episode.
- Right. - Yes.
Well, today... My goodness.
(She even watches reruns.)
(Jae Suk goes straight down to the point.)
This is the first one on the list. It's underlined in blue.
The writer added three stars on this.
- You'll show us your EDM dance. - All of a sudden?
(She'll show them her EDM dance.)
- Jae Suk, are you serious? - Before saying hi to the viewers?
(We didn't even say hi properly.)
- My gosh. - That's all right.
(EDM dance comes before the greeting.)
- That's so 2020. - You can do it.
These days, we don't build up to reach the climax.
(The Grand Award winner says that...)
We cut to the chase right away.
(the trend is to cut to the chase right away.)
- Let's go. - Ha Na, can you show us the dance?
(It changed a lot in a year.)
- Of course. - Great.
It's embarrassing to dance by myself.
- I brought friends. - Where?
- What? - What friends?
(Friends?)
Did you bring dancers?
(Are they dancers?)
- Yes. - She brought dancers.
She came determined.
(Since it's been a year)
- Buddies! - What?
My gosh. Goodness.
What's that?
(Ha Na's friends shock everyone.)
- They are real parrots. - What's going on?
(Ha Na's friends, 2 parrots)
Really?
(She brought birds?)
Are they shy?
My friends!
(Good to see you, buddies.)
- So Min's nickname is Parrot. - They are my friends too.
By the way, they are beautiful.
(Nice to meet you.)
- Ha Na, how old are they? - Yes?
(Introduce your friends, Ha Na.)
So this one is Nana.
(Nana, 5)
I think it's five years old. I adopted Nana.
- You adopted Nana. - Gguggu is...
(Gguggu, 8 months)
- eight months old. - It sat on your finger.
(He feels comfortable on his mom's hand.)
- They are beautiful. - That's fascinating.
It went to Ha Na.
(Fascinated)
Will it come if I put my finger here? It came to me too.
Hello.
(He keeps a distance.)
- How interesting. - That one...
- easily makes friends. - Don't come. You won't come? Don't.
I think Nana is going to dig out Suk Jin's earwax.
- He's about to cry. - My gosh.
(Nana's sociability flusters Suk Jin.)
- Nana is friendly. - What's going on?
It's eating your shirt.
- No, he doesn't have a lot of hair. - Do they bite?
(Don't eat his hair.)
- Suk Jin. - No.
- It's so loud. - He doesn't have a lot of hair.
(Every strand of hair is so precious to him.)
- Suk Jin. - No.
It's eating lice from Suk Jin's hair.
(The early bird?)
It was eating lice.
He should put it on his shoulder.
Jong Kook, try it on Se Chan. Let's see he'll come to you.
(We have a bird too.)
(Is Se Chan a bird?)
Can it talk?
(Nana and Gguggu)
That depends on the species. They can't talk.
(They can't talk, but they can dance.)
- But they can dance. - What?
- You'll dance with them? - Yes.
- Nana can dance. - Really?
- Really? - She can dance.
(Nana can dance to EDM songs?)
Let's watch Ha Na's EDM dance with Nana.
- Let's start with that. - I need Gguggu.
- It doesn't look like it'll dance. - Gguggu needs to help us.
That's intriguing. It's so calm.
I've only seen this on "How Is That Possible?"
I've never seen this in person.
(A parrot that likes to dance)
- A dancing parrot. - Right.
You can do it, right? Please help me.
(You can do it, right?)
(It's been a year. Help your mom out here.)
- Help me out. - Let's watch Nana's dance.
- Nana. - Nana.
(Don't worry, Mom.)
- Let's watch Nana's dance. - Nana.
(Their eyes are on the parrot.)
What is it?
(EDM music plays.)
Look at the wings. They are moving.
(They're moving.)
What?
(At first, they are enjoying to the rhythm.)
- It's dancing. - The wings are moving.
(Dancing)
- Seriously? - My gosh.
(What on earth is this?)
- Look at the body roll. - It's dancing to the rhythm.
(The dancing bird king)
It's really dancing.
(It even dances on the beat!)
It's coming down. It's on the stage now.
- Okay. - It's on the stage.
Nana needs a partner to dance.
(Copying the parrot)
Nana needs a partner.
(Suk Jin is having a blast with Nana's trick.)
In my opinion, Nana danced really well.
(Good job, guys.)
Right.
(Nana dances better at home.)
It was better than I expected.
- Nana. Gguggu. Thank you. - Thank you.
(See you next time.)
That was so much fun.
When they played the EDM track, I was really surprised to see...
So Min doing the outdated dance move.
With the EDM music?
(The female warrior of techno music is summoned.)
That's for techno music.
(She can't forget the old trend.)
She did a move for techno music when they played the EDM music.
All right. Let's wrap up here.
Wait, Ha Na. Did you prepare another dance performance?
- She prepared a lot. - I prepared a lot.
(She prepared a lot.)
Earlier, her pets danced.
(She's enthusiastic. She'll dance this time.)
Will you dance this time?
Yes, I prepared to dance to Jong Kook's song.
- My song? - Which song?
My songs are oldies of old songs.
(Oldies of old songs)
It's "Black Cat."
("Black Cat Nero" by Turbo)
- That's an old song. - I'll show you a snippet.
- All right. Ha Na. - "Black Cat Nero".
(How's Ha Na's "Black Cat Nero" who is enthusiastic?)
- Dance to "Black Cat Nero." - I'll show you a snippet.
I feel shy now.
(As soon as the intro begins, she bounces like a cat.)
Is this how you dance to the song?
- That's correct. - Is this how it goes?
(Thumbs up from the three men who know Turbo's dance very well)
- Just like that. - She's got swagger.
(She's good.)
- Yes. - Is this it?
(She acts like a cat.)
She should come to your concert.
- She's a cat. - That move.
(Let's go back to the 1990s!)
- In 1, 2. - Go.
(She transforms into a powerful cat from a gentle cat.)
(The original singer is happy.)
What? What was that all of a sudden?
(Fluttering away her pink jacket)
- She's amazing. - Is that the right move?
That's right. That's one of the moves.
(She flails her leather boots.)
That's the dance for the bridge.
(She finishes with a cute kitty act.)
- Ha Na. - Thank you.
(Doll Chan dances to the music automatically.)
I'm sorry to ask you this, but what was the last move?
(She rushed to finish up with a cute act.)
- I didn't memorize that part. - I see.
- Is that why? - I felt shy.
But she works hard.
(We appreciate her effort.)
- Yes. - She works hard.
The dance moves were really funny.
(She tries to fix the situation.)
(It's funny?)
Funny? Did you say it's funny?
- Why are you leading the show? - Jong Kook's life...
- is in that song. - No, it's not that.
But it's funny?
(That's not what I meant.)
Jong Kook, why don't you demonstrate for us?
(Enthusiastic)
- Why are you leading the show? - Why would I do that?
- Why would I do that? - Shall we do it together?
(She even summons the original singer.)
To be honest, you didn't even memorize the routine properly.
(Whatever)
I would've done it if you memorized it properly.
(Embarrassed)
To tell you the truth, I couldn't make big reactions.
(Jong Kook has a reason to act that way.)
- Well, she worked hard. - I want to see the original dance.
(The pink cat wants to see the original cat.)
- She didn't have much time. - Right.
- We should see the original dance. - Right.
(It's never easy to make Jong Kook dance.)
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Dance for us.
(Dance for us.)
- Do you want me in the back? - It's been so long.
(Doll Chan volunteers.)
- Should I join too? - You should do it too.
(Haha, join us.)
- By the way, - You guys, stand in the back.
when he was active as Turbo, he didn't dance zealously.
(Haha and Se Chan know where to stand.)
Right. By the way, both of them...
(They're pretty much members of Turbo.)
- rapped at my concerts. - Really?
- So he can... - I'm the first Kim Jung Nam.
- He's the second Kim Jung Nam. - Right.
I can even do Mikey's part.
- Haha is Jong Kook's first doll. - Right.
(The 1st and 2nd dolls)
- He's the 2nd doll. - I'm the 2nd one.
(Doll Chan and Doll Ha)
- Kwang Soo is a temporary one. - It goes like this.
(The 1st and 2nd Kim Jung Nams try to get in sync.)
- Do we just repeat this? - He threw Kwang Soo out.
(Jong Kook's ready.)
All right. Play the music.
(I can't wait to see it.)
(The music plays.)
- My gosh. - Great.
(Dancing in sync)
- They look cute. - Don't you dare...
- go in front of Jong Kook. - You should join them.
(Warning from the 1st Kim Jung Nam)
Ha Na. Why did you go in front of him?
(The passionate pink cat joins.)
(At a glance, it looks like Turbo has united.)
- Stand behind Jong Kook. - You're doing great.
- You're doing great. - Make Jong Kook stand out.
(With the honor of 1st and 2nd Kim Jung Nams)
All right.
(As if Turbo is back)
(I can't believe I'm seeing this in person.)
- That's so cool. - Right. That was the move.
This move.
(The old man dances.)
Gosh, they are so in sync.
This is the part.
(This is the part for Jung Nams.)
(The leader shouts.)
- Go. - It's war.
(The competition heats up as they're finished talking.)
Great job. Nice.
- Great. - You're too young for it
(You're too young for it)
(Greatly satisfied)
- Cut it. That's enough. - Nice.
- That's it. - Great job.
(They immerse so much that they can't hear the others.)
Great job!
- You know what? - I knew it.
- You are my dolls. - Jong Kook.
(Full of love)
- My dolls. - Dolls.
(They're Jong Kook and his dolls.)
I felt so bad for them.
- Why? I do it because I want to. - Two of them did the same part.
(Doll Chan)
Goodness.
(A tear-jerking scene of sharing the same part)
After the intro, Jong Kook was resting in the back.
(While the 1st and 2nd Kim Jung Nams were competing, )
I rest up here and get ready.
(Jong Kook seemed pleased standing a step behind them.)
- I catch my breath. - Right.
(We're looking for the 3rd Kim Jung Nam.)
Thanks to Ha Na,
- Jong Kook performed. - Right.
(It was a performance from the old days thanks to Ha Na.)
- I suddenly danced to an old song. - Right. All of a sudden.
(Thank you.)
If this is all you can do,
don't say that you prepared a dance performance.
Don't say that you prepared a dance performance.
- It didn't deserve three stars. - You know this wasn't...
(The specialty with 3 stars wasn't that big of a deal.)
There were three stars next to it.
- It didn't deserve three stars. - Right.
I'm not sure if you know this,
but we wrapped up the mess you created.
- We wrapped it up. - We cleaned it up.
(We resuscitate dead specialties.)
- We did all the finishing touches. - Okay.
- You guys are brutal. - It was somewhat lacking.
(Thank you.)
I'll explain the rules now.
Today's race is called Empty House: Oh, My Thieves.
(Empty House: Oh, My Thieves)
You are nine thieves who are eyeing the valuables in a mansion.
(They are 9 thieves, looking for the valuables.)
We are thieves?
There will be three per team.
(3 people will form a team.)
The mansion owner will go out from 3pm to 5pm.
(The mansion owner will leave the mansion from 3pm to 5pm.)
There's the mansion owner.
You must steal valuables when the mansion is empty.
(You must steal the valuables in the mansion while it's empty.)
The team with the most money will win and receive a prize.
(The team with the most amount of money will win the race.)
And the losing team will face a penalty.
(The losing team will face a penalty.)
However, in the mansion,
(There's a gem that's more expensive than...)
there is the Tear of Yondu necklace. It costs 30 million dollars...
(all the other valuables combined.)
which is more expensive than all the valuables combined.
(It's called Tear of Yondu which costs 30 million dollars.)
- Tear of Yondu? - Tear of Yondu?
Tear of Yondu?
- Tear of Yondu. That's her. - There's another one here.
(But So Min is Yondu.)
I can cry as much as you want me to.
(For 30 million dollars...)
Obtaining the gem will guarantee a victory for your team.
(The team that obtains Tear of Yondu will win the race.)
Please look for it thoroughly.
The team of three thieves consists of...
(A team of three thieves consists...)
a firearms expert, hacker, and appraiser.
(of a firearms expert, hacker, and appraiser.)
A firearms expert who will be the captain...
will get a water gun that allows them to eliminate a member.
(The captain, who is the firearms expert, )
And an appraiser will get a tool that distinguishes valuables...
(will be given a water gun that can eliminate a member.)
(The appraiser will be given a tool that tells the prices of valuables.)
between expensive and cheap ones.
And for hackers,
it's advantageous to select the smartest member.
(It's advantageous for hackers to choose smart members.)
I'm probably a hacker.
(Quietly)
Some of you can't be.
Before you start, you'll select your teams first.
We appointed the captain of each team.
Captain Yoo Jae Suk.
(Captain Yoo Jae Suk, firearms expert)
Captain Kim Jong Kook.
(Captain Kim Jong Kook, firearms expert)
And Captain Haha.
(Captain Haha, firearms expert)
I'm sorry to interrupt,
(Wait.)
- but shouldn't it be Suk Jin? - What about Suk Jin?
(What about Suk Jin?)
One of them should be Suk Jin.
(No one knows why he was not called.)
- Aren't you being too cruel? - By the way...
- He was waiting for his name. - Listen.
(He thought his name would be called, )
As soon as he talked about captains...
(so he was trying to keep a straight face.)
I was trying hard to keep a straight face.
His face turned dark.
- You should let him be a captain. - My gosh, seriously.
(He can't accept it.)
Gosh, this is so weird.
Team Member Ji, join me.
Join me.
(Since you're smart, be a hacker.)
The three of you will play rock-paper-scissors.
(The three captains will play rock-paper-scissors to choose...)
The winner will get to choose their members first.
(their numbers by the order of winning.)
Really? Will we play rock-paper-scissors?
(They'll select their hackers first.)
- Play it and pick one member. - Let's do it.
- I'm a hacker. - We should step back.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Suk gets to choose first.)
- Okay! - What are you talking about?
(I'm a perfect hacker.)
Come on, Kwang Soo.
Suk Jin is the smartest one.
(No, I'm the hacker.)
- Hold on. Do I choose a hacker? - Yes.
- Pick a smart member. - Class president in sixth grade.
(Abruptly)
I was the class president in the 7th grade...
and vice president in the 8th grade.
- Go back to your spot. - Hey.
(Listing her achievements to be a hacker doesn't work.)
Can't you tell just by looking at me?
(Do I have the face of a hacker?)
Right. I can see that you're old.
(He's not a hacker. He's just old.)
- It wasn't "aged." He said "old." - Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, it's your face. - You look very tired.
(The make-up couldn't cover the fatigue of the middle-aged man.)
My gosh, you punk.
I'm good at the acrostic poems.
(Ha Na raises her hand.)
(She gets enthusiastic again.)
- You're good at acrostic poems? - Yes.
- You must be smart for that. - Give it a try.
(Enthusiastic)
- Give it a try. - Hold on.
You keep starting things, but you can't finish them.
- Do we have to finish this too? - No.
(We like your enthusiasm, but...)
- Stop making us clean up your mess. - Where are you going?
- Hold on. - Where are you going?
(Where is she going when she has to make an acrostic poem?)
Don't make a mess here.
I shouldn't have asked her to do it.
Why did you say that?
- Why did you do that? - Goodness.
- She likes to show off. - My goodness.
- Will she do it with her parrots? - For acrostic poems?
(Is she going to bring the parrots again?)
- She should... - Will the parrots recite the poems?
(The more enthusiastic she gets, the more anxious they are.)
Her poem must be really good.
(Ha Na comes out of the bathroom.)
- She's coming. - Here she comes.
(I'll show you.)
- She's coming? - Where did she go?
Where did she go to prepare for her acrostic poem?
(Why did she go to the bathroom?)
- What did you do? - What was that?
- Where did you go? - Did you go to the bathroom?
I prepared acrostic poems for all eight of you.
(Too enthusiastic)
- Eight poems? - I know I can't...
We don't have that much time.
(Pretending to be the one in charge)
- I only brought the best one. - That's great.
(She'll only do the best acrostic poem.)
- Whose name will you use? - So Min's.
(She'll try with So Min's name.)
- So Min's name. - My name is hard to do a poem with.
- You should do one with her name. - First line.
I came here by myself.
- Second line. - So Min, please help me a lot.
Third line.
When it comes to embarrassing acts,
we should do them together!
We should do them together!
(Raising her hands high)
(In fact, everyone did join her embarrassing moment.)
We can't even make this work.
(Unrecoverable)
- Don't you get this? - No, we get it.
(So Min cries, )
- My gosh. - So Min.
(and Ha Na also cries.)
- She went to the restroom. - She went to the restroom.
(Now that we think about it...)
- She wet her armpits. - She looked in the mirror.
(In the bathroom...)
- She did this with the water. - She put water on her armpits
- Come on. - Right now...
(She shudders out of embarrassment.)
My gosh.
So Min's armpits.
- She brought the incident back. - The water park.
(So Min's armpits were called again as they were about to forget.)
- She reminded us. - It's not that.
Am I that famous?
(She realizes how popular her armpits are.)
Hey, that meme went viral.
- By the way, - This...
- I... - So Min and her armpits.
I went there to splash water on me,
But I was already sweating.
- There's no need for water? - You were already sweating?
(That wasn't water?)
You didn't have to tell us that.
(You didn't have to tell us that.)
All right. Ha Na.
- I'll choose Ha Na. - Okay.
- Ha Na. - She's amazing.
(Team Jae Suk recruits Ha Na as the hacker...)
How could I not choose her? I chose her for her enthusiasm.
(for her enthusiasm and information sharing.)
- Are we going in order? - Yes.
I'll choose So Min who will publish a book soon.
(Team Members)
Ji Hyo!
- I'll choose my doll. - Kwang Soo.
(Team Jae Suk, Team Jong Kook, and Team Haha)
We'll distribute the tool to each team.
(Pen for the appraisers)
- The pen is for the appraiser. - The pen?
(Water gun for the firearms experts)
- This doesn't suit me. - Is that your role?
- Yes, that's my role. - My gosh.
- That's yours, Jong Kook. - Use the light on the pen.
You'll see what's written.
Write it with the pen first.
(Scribbling something)
- Shine it. - Write it with the pen first.
(Laughing)
- She's driving me crazy. - What is it?
(What did she write?)
What?
Why?
"Se Chan."
- She drew a heart and signed it. - "From So Min."
(Only the appraiser can read the love letter.)
- So Min got a good team today. - Exactly.
- Why do you keep... - My gosh.
- following me around lately? - Right.
(Why do you keep following me these days, Se Chan?)
(The mission tools are provided.)
- What is that? - What is it?
- There are three cars. - That's going to be really cold.
(Why are there 3 cars here?)
- What is this? - It'll be really cold.
(A luxurious sedan with the best ride quality)
- Which one? - I want to ride that one.
(A van with spacious room that can go a long way)
No, I don't want that one. It'll be cold.
It's a convertible.
(And a convertible car in this weather!)
Gosh, it'll be freezing.
- In this weather? - It will be so cold.
(No way.)
But riding a convertible now...
(That's almost a penalty.)
- It's too cold. - doesn't sound good.
- Isn't that a penalty? - A convertible...
I don't like it even when it's sunny because of the micro-dust.
(What are these cars for?)
I like convertibles.
You don't know the address of the mansion you need to rob.
(The thieves have no information on the mansion such as the address.)
You need to complete missions...
to obtain the address and passcode of the mansion,
locations of surveillance cameras, and the patrol schedule.
Arriving at the mansion quickly will be advantageous.
(It's advantageous to get to the empty mansion first.)
The mansion will open from 3pm to 5pm.
(It will stay open only for 2 hours.)
You have three options for transportation to get there.
(There are 3 vehicles to get to the mission spots.)
Team Ocean's will drive...
(Team Ocean's with the luxurious sedan)
- the luxurious sedan. - Team Ocean's.
Team Home Alone will drive the van.
(Team Home Alone with the van)
Team Home Alone.
Team Les Miserables will put on a wig and ride the convertible.
(Team Les Miserables with a convertible and long wigs)
- These are the teams. - Let's avoid that one.
Don't we look like the thieves in "Home Alone"?
(Kwang Soo and Haha)
- It's "Home Alone." - Right?
(They're the thieves that go through a hard time every Christmas.)
It totally suits you. The hat helps too.
- Let's go for that one. - It's on fire.
(The hat and his facial expression look exactly the same.)
- Macaulay Culkin. - You're wearing the same hat.
(Decalcomania)
- You have to scream like this. - This?
(Ji Hyo looks like Kevin.)
He has the same hat.
Only 1 of the 3 silver trays has cherries from Chile.
(Mission: Cherry Game)
(Only 1 of the 3 silver trays has cherries on it.)
The team that picks the tray with the cherries from Chile wins.
(The team to choose the one with cherries...)
The winning team will assign the cars to all of the teams.
(will decide all the vehicles.)
The winning team will decide.
Hey, riding that car is a penalty.
(Boycotting the convertible)
- I want to ride the sedan. - I want this one.
(His preference)
I don't care which car I get as long as it's not the last one.
(As long as it's not the convertible...)
Discuss among yourselves to pick a tray.
Ha Na, you should choose.
(Enthusiastic Ha Na will choose first.)
When I observed Ha Na,
I could tell she gets unlucky too.
Let me feel the energy of cherries.
(She makes a fuss when she can't get the job done.)
- She's enthusiastic. - Indeed.
(She listens to feel the inside.)
She's enthusiastic.
I need enough airtime for myself.
- What is it? Did you decide? - I have a good feeling about that.
- Do it. Get whatever you want. - Open it.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(The cherries will be on only one of the trays.)
(What is on the tray Ha Na chose?)
(Full of cherries)
(Team Jae Suk will decide the vehicles for every team.)
That was amazing.
- How did you know that? - That was amazing.
You called it.
(Ease your disappointment...)
Try it.
(with sweet cherries.)
- Okay. - Cherries are good in snowy winter.
(Sweet and sour cherries eaten in a warm room during winter)
- These are good. - Yes.
These are great.
(And...)
- I like cherries. - Me too.
(Suk Jin is eating cherries in a unique way.)
(Eating it in one go)
I heard your teeth crack. Are you okay?
(The insurance doesn't cover dental implants.)
- I heard a crack. - I think it hit your tooth.
- No. - What's wrong?
You know what?
(Suk Jin feels good after eating a cherry in one go.)
Everything is going my way this year.
He uses up his luck on useless things.
(It was great luck.)
He uses it on the bottle flip.
(He mainly uses his great luck when doing a mission.)
You're right. You have a boint.
I have a "boint"?
- You have a boint. - I have a "boint"?
(The younger members have a "boint".)
I have a "boint"?
- "Boint"? - "Boint"?
He needs to "cherry" up, you know.
(Eat some cherries.)
He needs to "cherry" up.
(Suk Jin, please "cherry up" this year.)
- Can we start? - This is fun.
- Which team will get that car? - You must decide.
(Now Team Jae Suk can designate the vehicles.)
- You can choose however you want. - Let us play rock-paper-scissors.
To make it entertaining, they should...
- They're Team Les Miserables. - He can drive.
So they are Team Les Miserables.
- Even if we make them drive it... - Jae Suk, they can be newlyweds.
(Se Chan and So Min)
- Right. - Jong Kook won't say a thing.
(While Haha is trying dump the convertible on others...)
(Wearing)
Jong Kook can drive the car. And they can sit in the back.
(Kwang Ja, the tragic heroine appears.)
- Right. - That will be so fun.
- Take that off. - I can't.
- Take it off. - I can't give it up.
- The wig looks great on you. - You look beautiful.
(The long straight hair suits her perfectly.)
- Take it off. - I can't give it up.
(She realizes her fate that's approaching.)
- Jae Suk won't even listen. - We can change his mind.
- Kwang Ja will take it. - It's settled.
(Team Haha will get the long wigs and the convertible.)
- It's settled. - Which team gets the convertible?
We'll take the Maserati.
(Sedan: Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and Ha Na)
I'd rather see Kwang Soo with the wig than Jong Kook.
(Van: Jong Kook, Se Chan, and So Min)
- We'll have a comfortable ride. - We'll take...
(Convertible: Haha, Kwang Soo, and Ji Hyo)
I'll give you the address of each spot.
(Locations of mission spots)
- Se Chan. - Hello.
- Honey, let's go. - Okay.
(The role-playing of newlyweds begin.)
- What's Jong Kook's role? Our son? - Yes.
- My son. - Son?
My son.
(A frightening son)
- I have a great son. - You raised a nice son.
- He's reliable. - I gave birth to a great son.
How did I give birth to a handsome son with you?
You have a great son.
(The best combination of DNA from Se Chan)
This is the mission card.
There are three places.
(The three locations have different hints.)
Even if we go to one of these, we need to know the passcode.
Then we should go here first.
(To the mission spot where they can obtain the password and address)
We need to know the passcode first.
(This team too.)
Don't you think everyone will go...
(Team Jae Suk go to obtain the password and address too.)
- to this spot? - I'm not sure.
(Both Team Jae Suk and Jong Kook are heading to the same spot.)
It's snowing a lot today.
This is pricking my head.
- Darn it. - It's so prickly.
(Team Les Miserables is struggling with the long wigs.)
It's pricking my head.
It keeps going into my mouth.
(Riding a convertible with the long-haired wigs...)
This is so irritating. It is!
Let's turn on the heater.
(Let's at least turn on the heater.)
(Is this the heater?)
- Where's the heater? - You opened the trunk.
You opened the trunk.
(Opened)
How do I close it?
Please close the trunk.
(A total disaster)
Let me punch in the address.
(They finally take off after many struggles.)
- I'm on the wrong team. - Hey, we just have to win.
(Laughing)
- Yongmun... - Yangpyeong-gu.
(A beauty from behind)
Everyone's staring at us.
- I saw Yongmun just now. - Really?
(They try to leave after putting in the mission address.)
(Sighing)
You can't even use the navigation properly.
Then you try it. This isn't easy.
- Hold on. - Let's go there.
(Whatever.)
- It's snowing a lot. - Let's just go there.
(Meanwhile...)
(They set out in a convertible, wearing wigs while it's snowing.)
Let's go.
(They do look cool.)
(I got a new car)
Everyone's staring at us.
(Everyone is looking at my car.)
- I'm so embarrassed. - This is so embarrassing.
My hair's a mess.
- This wig is... - Haha.
(What is that?)
It's so freezing!
(It just happened to snow today.)
This car is fast.
- Haha. - Haha.
(Haha likes to drive fast.)
The faster you drive, the messier Kwang Soo's hair gets!
(Driving fast)
It's so fast, though.
- Haha! - I can't hear you.
(Messy hair)
Okay, I'll slow down.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
(Laughing)
My goodness.
(He is the reason why we are riding this convertible.)
Let's eliminate Jae Suk's team first.
- Of course. - Do you have the water gun?
Okay!
See? He can't hear me. He's making no sense.
(See? He can't hear me. He's making no sense.)
He can't hear a thing.
(Broken communication)
Let's not talk.
I'm freezing.
(Team Jong Kook is going to obtain the password and address.)
Anyway, we should go to the mansion and...
(The final mission today is to steal from the mansion.)
Aren't we supposed to steal as much as possible?
You're right.
This mission is perfect for Kwang Soo.
(One person comes to mind during this thief mission.)
It suits Se Chan too.
(Se Chan's face)
- Am I a petty thief? - Yes.
I'm awful at stealing. I get caught...
- because I can't lie. - You stole my heart, didn't you?
I never did.
(A petty thief that stole my heart?)
- Are you sure you didn't offer it? - She offered it?
(I didn't steal it.)
- I think you offered it. - Is it out on the market?
No.
- We're here. - Are we?
- Are you sure? Let's go inside. - Yes.
Are we the only ones here?
(Team Jong Kook arrives first to the spot.)
I think so.
This would be a great place to come and relax.
(It'd be nice if we came here for fun.)
Wouldn't it be great to spend a night here?
(He agrees.)
- It'd be wonderful. - It'd be great.
- Let's come here again. - Se Chan.
(You and me)
Where?
- Us three should come here. - And spend the night?
(Three of us for one night?)
Sure, as long as he doesn't leave midway.
(Don't leave me and So Min alone.)
- You better not leave. - Hey.
- You better not. - Why would you say that?
(It's safe when Jong Kook is with us.)
Just in case. I don't want him to disappear.
I'm done. This is hurting my pride.
(This attempt of creating a sweet atmosphere)
- Don't be ridiculous. - I'm done.
(I am so done.)
- I was only joking. - Get out.
(Mission spot for the password and address)
- I think this is it. - It's so pretty.
- The flowers are swaying - The flowers are swaying
(This is the mission spot for the address and password.)
I think we'll be playing a game.
If you win this mission, you'll get the mansion's address...
(A mission over the mansion address and the password)
- and its passcode. - Okay.
The mission is called Strawberry, St-raw-berry.
(Mission: Strawberry, st-raw-berry)
- "Strawberry, St-raw-berry"? - "Strawberry, St-raw-berry"?
This is a popular game these days.
(It's a very popular game these days.)
Really?
(According to the beat, you either say "strawberry" or "st-raw-berry.")
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry - St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(Beat 1, strawberry. Beat 2, st-raw-berry.)
- Strawberry - St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(If the three of them reach the 8th beat, they succeed.)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- What is this? - What is this?
(They are all confused.)
- What? - St-raw-berry counts as two beats.
(Strawberry is beat 1, St-raw-berry is beat 2.)
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry - This is a famous game?
- This is the third beat. - Strawberry
- Darn it. - We came first.
- Strawberry - We came first.
(Team Jae Suk arrives.)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - This is really hard.
- How do you do the eighth beat? - Do you know this game?
- St-raw-berry - Do you know this?
(These middle-aged men have never heard of the game.)
No, this is my first time.
- Watch us. - Let's begin.
Ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Strawberry
(Beat 1)
- Straw-berry - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Beat 2)
- It's st-raw-berry. - St-raw-berry.
Straw-berry
(Straw-berry)
(He fails due to his wrong pronunciation.)
Do you have to be that strict?
- Get out. - Get out!
- Give us one more chance. - St-raw-berry
(Please calm down.)
- Goodness. - Hold on.
You should give us at least three tries.
(We got it wrong so fast.)
- Do we get 3 tries? - Give us 3 tries.
(Confident)
- Gosh. - We just sat down.
- Gosh, this is frustrating. - We'll start once again.
(You can do it again.)
- We say straw-berry in my area. - Wake up.
(He claims that it's his dialect.)
All right.
- Ready, set, go. - Let's go.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
(He gets it right this time.)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Beat 3)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry and st-raw-berry
(Beat 5)
Hold on.
Strawberry and st-raw-berry
(Strawberry and st-raw-berry)
Hold on.
(He gets it wrong.)
- Get out. - Hold on.
Please leave, Se Chan's girlfriend.
(That man who doesn't know the rules)
- Explain the rules. - Please leave.
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry - St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(Se Chan undergoes an intense training.)
- Say it again. And then she says... - Strawberry
- Strawberry - St-raw-berry
Let's practice.
(We should practice too.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(Team Jae Suk starts a practice game.)
(Beat 1: strawberry Beat 2: st-raw-berry)
- Strawberry - St-raw-berry
(Beat 3: Strawberry, st-raw-berry)
Strawberry and st-raw-berry
(He misses the beat.)
- The beat was wrong. - What was that?
Strawberry and st-raw-berry
- What was I supposed to do? - Show us.
(He should have started a beat faster.)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - Right.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(He gets it wrong again.)
- No. It's strawberry, st-raw-berry - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Say it while you clap.)
- No. It's strawberry, st-raw-berry - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Look. Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(They start as Suk Jin explains the game rule.)
- Let's start. - Strawberry
- You go first. - No, you should go first.
- Let's change. I'll go first. - I like strawberries
(Disorganized)
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
(He gets it wrong again.)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - Hey!
- Goodness. - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Suk Jin is angry.)
- Get out. - Give us one more chance.
(I'll give you one more chance.)
- Okay. - Come on.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(You need to do it from the 2nd beat.)
(Okay, understood.)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - That's it.
- Let's start. - Let's change seats.
(Prevent any memorization)
You two should change seats.
(They will be randomly seated if they try again.)
- All right. Ready, set, go. - Is this right?
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(He finally gets it right.)
- Is it my turn? - St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(Suk Jin is infuriated.)
- Aren't we going this way? - Get out.
(Team Jae Suk fails.)
- Get out. - St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Let's change seats. So Min will go first.
(Team Jong Kook gets randomly seated as well.)
Okay. We can do it.
- Jong Kook will come next. - All right.
- We can do this. - Get ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Strawberry
- St-raw-berry - St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry... What is it?
(He's supposed to say "strawberry, st-raw-berry".)
- What is it? - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Beat 3)
(It was clearly a wrong answer.)
- Get out. - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- It's not st-raw-berry? - No.
(It's "strawberry, st-raw-berry", okay?)
- Is he stupid or what? - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- All right. - I'm sorry,
- but So Min. - So Min.
Are you the class president or something?
Why are you so hyper?
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(She looked very excited.)
(She stood up.)
Strawberry
(She seemed like a friendly class president.)
Guys, I'm the brain of our group. I'm the hacker.
(I am the brain of the group.)
She's so confident.
- St-raw-berry, strawberry - Jae Suk will sit in the middle.
(It's Team Jae Suk's turn.)
- Ha Na will be the last one. - Hold on.
This isn't good.
- Ready, set, go. - Ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(He's supposed to say "st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry".)
- St-raw-berry - Get out.
(Please give us one more chance.)
- Give us 1 more chance. - We'll give you 2 more.
(We'll let you go this once.)
St-raw-berry
You have two tries.
Right?
- Ready, set, go. - What's the seventh beat?
(Wait a minute.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
- St-raw-berry - Come on.
(Why did he ask about beat 7?)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - Okay!
What's the seating arrangement this time?
(Is he the spy?)
- Why do we have to change seats? - Jong Kook will start first.
(He blames his seat.)
(Suk Jin is no longer confident.)
- What's wrong with you? - Hey.
He keeps changing our seats, and it's confusing me.
(Suk Jin once again doesn't understand the rules.)
Is this right?
Get ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, straw-berry
- St-raw-berry - You can't say straw-berry.
- St-raw-berry - Can't you just let him be?
That's how they say it in my area!
(That's how we say in Dongducheon!)
Can't you just turn a blind eye?
They're the same.
Get out.
(Get out of there.)
(He is eliminated.)
- Straw-berry, straw-berry - Get out.
- Get out. - Isn't this right?
(We would have succeeded if it weren't for Se Chan.)
If it wasn't for Se Chan...
I'm so distracted by the pronunciation.
(He is feeling frustrated.)
It's so confusing.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(This team has yet to understand the game rules.)
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Straw-berry
(Suk Jin repeats Se Chan's pronunciation mistake.)
That's not right.
- It's st-raw-berry. - Isn't that what he said?
Is that what I said?
(Suk Jin pretends he doesn't know about it.)
Why can't you do it properly?
(They are practicing. Let's start.)
- I like strawberries - You're done!
I like strawberries
(Let's hurry up and start.)
You're done!
- You're done. Don't be sly. - Get out.
- It's our turn. - Wait.
- Come on, Suk Jin. - Hold on.
(Suk Jin is an unprecedented character with unexpected answers.)
- Did I really say that? - It's st-raw-berry.
- That's what I said. - St-raw-berry
(It's Team Jong Kook's turn again.)
Get ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(Nervous)
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(They pass the beat 4.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, strawberry
(It's the beat 5.)
(He finally gets it right.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(They pass the beat 6.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(They even pass the beat 7.)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(It's the final beat 8.)
(Se Chan just needs to say st-raw-berry 4 times.)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
We did it!
(Team Jong Kook succeeds.)
I think he mispronounced it.
- No, he didn't. - I think he did.
(I don't think he said it right.)
- I think he mispronounced it. - No, I didn't.
- We're good. - We're pretty good.
(Se Chan did it!)
- Good work. - Great job.
(Yang Se Chan is a fighter from Dongducheon!)
- I think he mispronounced it. - Se Chan did it.
- I did it. - I thought it'd never end.
Since you've succeeded, we'll give you the address...
(Team Jong Kook acquires the password and address.)
and the hint for the passcode.
- Okay. - Okay.
You must read this outside.
(To prevent Team Jae Suk from cheating)
- All right. - You must go outside first.
- Let's pack. - All right.
- St-raw-berry - St-raw-berry
(This team is stuck in the strawberry and st-raw-berry loop.)
I have a feeling they won't end soon.
(Picking a fight)
- You're wrong. - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Frustrated)
During the last part, shout, "Lee Man Ki!"
(Is he giving advice?)
Be quiet.
- Please do that. - Shut it and leave.
Here we go.
I'm curious about the hint.
(They check the hint.)
Let's see.
The passcode is...
- It's 200202. - 200202.
- 200 and 202. - 200202. I get it.
(If they enter the password, they can enter the mansion.)
We should retrieve all the hints and then head to the house, right?
(Hint on the mansion)
Right.
Haha, to the right.
- The right? - Yes, make a right.
(Team No Brain with long hair is still struggling with the map.)
- Are you looking at the map? - Make a right.
- Are you sure? - I'm sure.
(Kwang Soo checks the map on Ji Hyo's phone.)
Gosh, it's freezing!
- What's this? - Let me see.
I lowered the map and...
(He's lost for words.)
- What is it? - The names of the months...
- are in English. - How is that important?
The names of the months are in English.
(The screen is filled with basic English words.)
How is that important? Give me that.
We need to check the map.
- Have you been studying? - Of course not.
(Flustered)
- Are you studying English? - You've been studying.
(Ji Hyo's studying English.)
This is for real. There's no doubt about it.
- I just put them on the screen. - You're trying hard.
Good job.
November and December...
I'm always confused by those two as well.
(Me too.)
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
(She's learning basic English at the age of 40.)
- Exactly. You're just studying. - Haha, make a right over there.
- It's never too late to study. - Of course.
(It's never too late to study.)
- Is this the place? - I'm inspired, Ji Hyo.
(Respect for Ji Hyo)
Stop talking about it!
- Over here? - On our way...
(When will they arrive at the mission spot?)
Hold on. Make a left.
What's the fourth month of the year?
(Meanwhile, in Team Jong Kook's car)
Se Chan, do you want some water?
- Sounds good. - Water?
(Sweet and loving)
Here you go.
- Are you done? - Thanks.
(Hang on. Look at them.)
- You have the lid. - Right.
It's nice to have So Min take care of me.
Just so you know, it's better to have...
(Jong Kook gives advice as an older person.)
a talkative wife or a girlfriend.
- They respond well. - You'll get bored.
I like women who respond well and laugh a lot.
(He agrees.)
- Someone who responds well? - Yes.
(Perking up)
No way! Really?
(She gives him the top 3 responses.)
(Yes, that's what I'm talking about.)
(Exploding with exclamations)
Gosh, look at you steering the wheel.
(Random...)
That's so cool.
(reaction)
I've never seen anyone who does it with two hands.
(He must be a beginner!)
Gosh, look at his gums.
Look.
(He never smiled that brightly before.)
- His gums? - No way.
It'll be fun to go on a trip with So Min.
(The queen of reaction)
- Being talkative is better. - Of course.
(A talkative girlfriend is the best.)
It's the best.
I love it too.
Don't you prefer someone like Park Na Rae?
(Your type)
Na Rae isn't exactly my type.
(Na Rae isn't exactly my type.)
What about Do Yeon?
Yes, Do Yeon's amazing.
(It's more like Do Yeon.)
Do Yeon's great.
Is it me or Do Yeon?
(The punch comes out of nowhere.)
(He's suddenly forced to choose his type.)
Is it me or Do Yeon?
(Is it the talkative So Min or the funny Do Yeon?)
Unbelievable. Of course, it's you.
Must I even say it?
(Jeon So Min is my type.)
- Are you sure? - Of course.
(His business partner is touched.)
This will air on TV, you know.
She says it'll air on TV.
(He can't take back what he said.)
- But... - It'll be written in an article.
(Keep what he said forever.)
- I'm sure of it. - No way.
I wish we'd get there soon. Oh, we're here.
- Are we? That was are. - Right.
Strawberry, St-raw-berry
(Team Jong Kook arrives at the surveillance camera mission.)
St-raw-berry and strawberry Strawberry and St-raw-berry
(If they complete the mission, they will be given a hint...)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, strawberry, st-raw-berry
(on the locations of the surveillance cameras.)
- What's that? - I'm nervous for some reason.
(What kind of mission will they do here?)
I see the ropes. Are we supposed to tie up or drag someone?
Let me inform you of the rules.
This is to find out the locations of the surveillance cameras.
(To find out the locations of the surveillance cameras)
Endure the Weight of the Paper.
(Mission: Endure the Weight of the Paper.)
- The weight of the paper? - Its weight?
One person will have a piece of paper laid on his or her head.
(1 person will have a piece of paper laid on his or her head.)
(3 members' legs will be tied.)
You will then compete in a four-legged race.
(They will then compete in a 4-legged race.)
Your goal is to place the paper in the basket...
(Their goal is to place the paper in the basket within 60 seconds.)
within 60 seconds.
(Those who complete the mission will be given hints...)
(on the locations of the surveillance cameras.)
What if we made his hair pointy...
(The head should be flat to lay a piece of paper.)
- and stick the paper there. - Should I?
(Make my hair pointy?)
No, you're adorable enough.
- I'll flatten it then. - He's cute.
(Doll Chan looks cute like this.)
Let's make it flat and put the paper on it.
From what I can tell, they're the couple in love.
(They're the true couple on this team.)
(Bromance between Jong Kook and Doll Chan)
No matter how I think about it...
It's called bromance!
(Glaring)
They seem inseparable.
(Isolated)
- So Min, please don't sulk. - He's right.
(A love triangle with Se Chan in the center?)
- Come on. - This way.
Let's get on with the game.
(The three in a love triangle will give the game a shot.)
Wait, this is too easy.
(Confident)
- Big strides. - Don't turn your head.
- Gosh. - Why did you turn your head?
(Falling)
- I get it now. - Good.
- Do something funny. - We can do it.
(Falling)
- It wasn't even funny. - Exactly.
(Failing like this isn't funny.)
It wasn't funny. We should do better.
Are you failing on purpose just to keep holding my hand?
(He keeps making boring mistakes.)
(Is that why he's been failing?)
- Wait... - It sounds like it.
- Is his palm sweaty? - You see...
(Holding tight)
It is sweaty, and he's holding my hand really tight.
I'm startled.
(My Doll Chan looks happy with his girlfriend.)
- I didn't lock fingers though. - Stick your tummy out.
(Stick your tummy out.)
Jong Kook, must you do that?
- Stick your tummy out. - Let's lock fingers.
(The two men start acting like a couple again.)
Jong Kook, must you do that?
(Frowning)
Something's definitely going on between them.
(They lead a dangerous relationship with him having a fake girlfriend.)
- So Min. - Okay, we're ready.
(After numerous attempts, they change the courier.)
(Sticking)
- All right. Let's go. - It's the magnet lady.
(The magnet lady returns.)
- Tell me about it. - It's the magnet lady!
Gosh.
- Let's go. - All right.
(How does it stay on?)
We can do this. It won't fly off.
- Let's go. - This won't fall off me.
We can even walk at a fast pace to make sure it won't fall off me.
- Sure. - It won't come off.
(It never falls.)
It won't come off.
- She's the magnet lady! - It won't come off.
Here comes the magnet lady. Okay, we're almost there.
(They succeed only if they drop the paper in the basket.)
Magnet lady, do your thing.
(Will the legend of magnet lady continue?)
- Gently... - Stick your head in there.
(They succeed.)
- We did it! - Nice!
- Magnet lady. - You succeeded in the mission.
(Team Jong Kook got the locations of surveillance cameras.)
- Hold on. - Okay, we did it. It was fun.
- It's fine. - Here you go. It's a hint.
(I'll give you the hint.)
- What's this? - You may read it here.
(No one's around, so you may read it here.)
(Locations of Surveillance Cameras)
In sub-basement level 1, there are two near the stairs...
(Sub-basement level 1)
(Level 1, level 2)
This doesn't seem easy. We should go down...
(Locations of surveillance cameras in the mansion)
That's a lot of cameras.
(Sub-basement level 1)
- There are three. - Right.
(If they're exposed to surveillance cameras for more than 5 seconds, )
Inside Room 1...
We need to turn all three of them off first.
(the patrol guards will be sent. once they get caught, they're out.)
Where exactly are they?
(They have 5 seconds to turn each of them off.)
- Right. - There are a lot.
(Meanwhile, Team Jae Suk moved to obtain the patrol schedule.)
Before 3pm?
- We're running out of time. - Oh, dear.
(What game will they play here?)
Unbelievable.
What are these for?
- Here are the rules. - Sure.
(Mysterious tights with gloves attached)
What are we supposed to do?
The patrol schedule is what you'll obtain if you succeed.
(This mission is for the patrol schedule.)
The game is called Clap Your Hands.
(Mission: Clap Your Hands)
You will choose two members to compete.
(2 members will put on tights...)
(with a glove attached to it on their head...)
The two will put on...
(and move toward each other while making the tights swirl.)
tights with a glove attached to it on their head...
and move toward each other while making the tights swirl.
(They have 100 seconds to make the gloves...)
You have 100 seconds to make the gloves...
(clap each other three times.)
clap each other three times.
(What hint will be provided if they succeed?)
(They will be given the patrol schedule...)
(which contains the time and location for the patrol guards.)
(It will help them stay clear of the patrol guards!)
Let's get going.
(2 players of Team Jae Suk)
All right, here we go.
All right.
- All right. - Hold on.
(Park Ha Na and Ji Suk Jin, )
(most likely)
Suk Jin, you should go down.
(One person has to get lower to make the gloves clap each other.)
Go down. Get closer.
Wait, this is too low.
(Oh, no!)
(The tights give her a nose lift.)
You were wearing it too low. It wasn't spinning well.
(She smiles brightly after getting a nose lift.)
It was on your forehead.
(Laughing)
Ha Na.
(She gets a facelift too.)
Try to do better.
(Lifting)
You have to do better.
You don't have time for that.
(Dumbfounded)
Seriously.
(Suk Jin tries to add it to his collection.)
What are you doing?
(Let's take a photo together.)
We don't have time for this.
(The most hilarious shot of the first half of 2020)
I can't see anything.
(I'll show you how it's done.)
Ha Na, move. Suk Jin and I will play.
(As soon as they begin, )
(they manage to clap.)
- There you go. - You clapped.
(The 2nd clap)
- Okay. - Two.
(The 3rd clap)
- We're done. - You clapped again.
(They accomplish the mission so fast.)
Since you've completed the mission,
(Team Jae Suk obtains the patrol schedule.)
- I'll give you the patrol schedule. - Thank you.
(The patrol time and route are revealed.)
What's this?
(Patrol Schedule)
(Meeting Room 1 and 2, Hacker's Room 2, and Dining Room at 3:30pm)
(Hacker's Room 1 and Reception Room on the 1st floor, )
(Hacker's Room 3 and Meeting Room 3 on the 2nd floor at 4:30pm)
(1st Floor, 2nd Floor)
(In order not to be eliminated, )
(they shouldn't be seen by the patrol guards.)
We've been doing well so far.
(Team Haha arrives at Strawberry, St-raw-berry mission spot.)
- Let's succeed at once. - Okay.
(Enthusiastic)
I'll go first.
You say, "st-raw-berry".
(Captain Haha orders them with confidence.)
I say, "st-raw-berry, strawberry," right?
- Okay. - Let's start.
(Okay, let's go.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(Confident Team Haha's first attempt begins.)
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, strawberry
(She misses the beat.)
(Loss for words)
You can continue until you succeed.
(She didn't understand the rules, and she's off the beat.)
- The first one is "strawberry." - Do you get it?
- The third one is... - St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(She's practicing with "St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry", )
(when it's "Strawberry, st-raw-berry".)
- You're pronouncing it wrong. - St-raw-berry
It seems like...
Ji Hyo doesn't know the beat. Do you?
She's smart, but she has no sense of rhythm.
(Don't look down on her.)
That's why.
- Please understand her. - Strawberry
(She's smart. She only has no sense of rhythm.)
- No. - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Can we just give up?
- Hold on. - We know the rules now.
(We'll find our way to the mansion.)
It's not that she doesn't know. Should we give it a try?
Let's try.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Precise)
Say "strawberry" when you clap your hands.
(Clenching his teeth)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - St-raw-berry
- Okay. - Repeat after me.
(Pretending to understand the rule)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - Pronounce it properly.
(Pronounce it properly.)
Start saying, "st-raw-berry," when you point to the right.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - There you go.
(She manages to say it once.)
- Okay. - Pronounce it right.
Let's give it a try.
(Let's calm down and try again.)
If we fail, we can try again.
Ready, start.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
- Strawberry - St-raw-berry
(Success)
(She misses the beat again.)
St-raw-berry
(Is this wrong?)
- I said it. - You pronounced it wrong.
- St-raw-berry - And the rhythm...
(I can control myself, I can control myself.)
How should I explain it?
- It's hard to explain. - Strawberry
(How should we explain such an easy mission?)
St-raw-berry
- I get it now. - Okay.
(She suddenly realized.)
Switch seats first.
(They'll switch their seats.)
We'll start with the person on the far right.
(They always have to start with the person in this seat.)
Ji Hyo and Haha, please switch seats.
(What she memorized is now useless.)
- You say... - You'll go first.
Strawberry.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Feeling uneasy all of a sudden)
- Okay. - Let's start.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(How will their third attempt turn out?)
Strawberry
(Success)
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(He misses the beat.)
Haha.
(Even Haha misses the beat.)
- What did I do? - Hold on.
- I think it's the stool's fault. - What's wrong?
(Enraging)
It's the stool's fault.
(It's a magic chair that turns anyone seated on it into Ji Hyo.)
- Did I do it wrong? - You were doing so well.
Hold on.
- The first one was correct, right? - I'll sit here.
(We have to do something.)
Okay, let's try. This is strange.
(Kwang Soo moves to the evil stool as he's the best among them.)
- Is it "Strawberry, st-raw-berry"? - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Frustrated)
Ready, start.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(It's the fourth attempt already.)
Strawberry
(Success)
St-raw-berry
(He was late.)
(Shocked)
What's wrong with me?
(Embarrassed)
Do we have to do this?
(Do we have to do this mission?)
- Do we have to get it? - Isn't this correct?
(Isn't this right?)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Okay, I get it perfectly now.
We can't fall behind because of this stupid game.
(How are we unable to even begin the game?)
(From the captain to the hacker, everything is a mess.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
Ready, start.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(They're always so zealous with the introduction.)
- Strawberry - St-raw-berry
(They finally got the second one right.)
(What about Kwang Soo?)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Success)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(It's completely off the beat.)
(Seriously...)
It's difficult to start right away.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Hacker Song has been struggling for 20 minutes.)
And then right away...
(I mean...)
I say, "St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry," when I pat my lap.
If I don't understand, please explain.
How many times do I have to explain?
(What?)
- You failed too. - Strawberry
It's "Strawberry, st-raw-berry."
(It's the sixth attempt already due to Ji Hyo's amazing play.)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - Strawberry, st-raw-berry. Okay.
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- Ready, start. - Let's slow down a bit.
- Ready, start. - Ready, start.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Strawberry
(Success)
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(She needs to say, "St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry".)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry
(Correct)
St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry, strawberry
(Haha even gets the fifth one right.)
St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry
(Kwang Soo, the ace player)
Strawberry, strawberry
Hey!
St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry, strawberry, strawberry
(You're the problem here!)
- St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry - St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry
(What was it?)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Say "st-raw-berry" three times. - She's right.
(It's a sad reality where Haha and Ji Hyo have to teach him.)
- St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry - St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry
(The three of them work it out together.)
No.
(What's wrong with me?)
Okay.
(You've been demoted.)
Kwang Soo, switch seats with me.
Kwang Soo will do the first one then.
(Ji Hyo goes back to the 3rd stool.)
We just have to repeat it over and over again.
(He suddenly gets timid.)
Ready, start.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
(Be honest.)
Don't you?
- Very much. - Should we go out and come back in?
- Let's pretend we just got here. - Should we...
(Can we pretend that it's our first time?)
pretend we just got here?
I'm so embarrassed.
We'll do it again.
Please edit out the first part.
We look so stupid.
(They censor themselves and decide it's unfit for broadcasting.)
- You can go out and come back in. - Okay.
What's wrong with us?
(The director is being considerate and agrees to film again.)
We were doing so well. Why is this so hard?
(1 minute after)
This is so embarrassing. We're so bad.
We got here first.
- Is no one else here? - Is no one else here?
(They hurry in.)
- We got here first. - I smell coffee.
It smells so nice.
- I'll sit here. - I'll sit here.
(They all sit down where they want.)
I don't know what game we'll be playing.
- Let's get started right away. - Okay.
(As soon as they sit down...)
We haven't even heard about the rules yet.
- Let's just go with our gut. - Let's go with our feelings.
(They'll go with their feelings as entertainers.)
- We're entertainers. - Okay.
We've been doing so well today.
- We have 10 years of experience. - Let's give it a try.
- I don't even know what game it is. - Do you know the intro?
- Pardon? - Do you know the intro?
Is it, "I like strawberries"?
- Not "st-raw-berries"? - I have a feeling.
(I have a feeling it's "I like strawberries".)
- Should we try it? - It has a nice ring to it.
- Okay. - It sounds so nice.
(The smart members guessed the introduction right.)
Let's try. 1, 2, start.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(How will the first attempt of the three geniuses turn out?)
- Strawberry - St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Ji Hyo misses the beat again.)
(Let's go out again.)
Let's pretend you arrive late. I'll stay here.
You arrive late.
(1 minute later)
- What's this place? - It looks cozy here.
(Pop-eyed)
Is no one else here?
It's nice and warm in here.
I see a xylophone.
(It feels good in here.)
- It must be something simple. - This mission is...
I like strawberries
(They waste no time.)
- Strawberry - St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry - St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(They even get the fourth one right.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(Following Haha, )
(Ji Hyo gets it right too.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, st-raw berry, strawberry
It's, "strawberry, st-raw-berry."
We were almost there.
(They fail at the seventh try.)
- What's this place? - Oh, my.
(They enter for the fourth time.)
- We're... - We're the first ones here.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(Let's slow down.)
Strawberry
You should have said "st-raw-berry" twice.
(She's timed out.)
- Was it my turn? - You're on my right.
(Was it my turn?)
Was it? I'm sorry.
How could she forget that?
(That's absurd.)
- It's scary. - I'm...
- It must be a simple game. - I think so.
(They enter for the fifth time.)
- Let's slow down a bit. - Let's slow down.
(It must be because of the speed.)
We're getting too carried away.
If we play it slowly,
can you speed it up afterward?
Ready, start.
(Let's play for real this time.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(Slow)
- Strawberry - St-raw-berry
(The beginning is no problem.)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry - St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, strawberry
(Once they slow down, they manage it pretty well.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(Ji Hyo gets the sixth one right.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, strawberry, st-raw-berry
(After Haha, )
(it's time for Kwang Soo to finish the game.)
(Will Kwang Soo manage to say "st-raw-berry" 4 times?)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- Yes! - We're done!
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(They finally succeed.)
(They manage to escape from the swamp of strawberries.)
This was our first try.
We succeeded at once.
(Acting until the end)
(It's still embarrassing even when they succeeded.)
We're on fire today.
- We're geniuses. - We didn't even know the rules,
- and we succeeded at once. - We're so smart.
- We only just got here. - Is this how you play it?
(We're on fire today.)
- Gosh, this is crazy. - I'm so thrilled.
(The three brains win the address and password.)
It's 3pm. The mansion is empty.
(It's 3pm, and the mansion is empty.)
Anyway, we have to get there first to steal expensive stuff.
(The three teams of thieves move to the empty mansion with the hints.)
- I know. - Hey.
(They have the address and password. Team Jong Kook has...)
Let's hurry up.
(the camera locations while Team Jae Suk has the patrol schedule.)
We have to get there first to steal good stuff.
(Which team will win by stealing the most valuable item?)
The team that steals good stuff first wins.
(It's past 3pm.)
(Who will enter the mansion first?)
(Team Jae Suk arrives first.)
All right. Let's go.
(There are more things to steal if they break into the mansion first.)
Thank you.
We need to get there first to get the good stuff.
(It seems like we've arrived first.)
Hey.
(They enter with the password they've obtained.)
- 252... - 252...
(The doors open.)
There you go.
(This is the secret mansion that will be broken into today.)
The mansion owner will go out from 3pm to 5pm.
(The thieves can steal things from the mansion...)
(between 3pm and 5pm.)
Steal valuables from the mansion until 5pm...
(They should steal valuables...)
and move them to your team's tent in the garden.
(and move them to their tents.)
The team with the highest total value of stolen things wins.
(The team with the highest total value wins.)
(Name: Tear of Yondu, Price: 30 million dollars)
Inside the mansion is...
a 30-million-dollar Tear of Yondu necklace...
and a one-time-use bulletproof vest to shield you from water guns.
(Bulletproof vest, One-time protection from water guns)
(There is only one bulletproof vest, and it's hidden.)
The one who finds the vest first gets to put it on.
If they get caught on surveillance cameras for more than 5 seconds,
(If they get caught on surveillance cameras for more than 5 seconds, )
the patrol guards will arrive.
(the patrol guards will arrive.)
Once you get caught by the patrol guards, you're out.
(Once they get caught by the patrol guards, they're out.)
Please fill your water gun with the water provided.
(Firearms experts can eliminate an opponent with their water guns, )
Your water gun can eliminate only one person.
(and they have only one opportunity.)
Each item has a tag on it,
(Appraisers can find out...)
(the prices of each item with their special tools.)
which will tell you its price.
Suk Jin, come here!
(They must stick to their parts to steal more than the other teams.)
- Okay. - We need an appraisal.
Guys, get out.
(The other teams also arrive in the meantime.)
Can we go in?
(The other two teams enter easily as Team Jae Suk opened the doors.)
Someone already broke in. Let's go in.
(Team Jong Kook has the hint of the surveillance camera locations.)
Shouldn't we do something about the surveillance cameras?
What's this?
(They easily found a camera thanks to the hint.)
I turned it off.
(A surveillance camera gets turned off.)
(They begin to turn off the surveillance cameras.)
(You are out if you are on the camera for over 5 seconds.)
(Thus, it's easier if you turn off the surveillance cameras.)
Okay. I turned it off.
Isn't this a surveillance camera?
- It is. - Look for them carefully.
(Team Jae Suk finds a surveillance camera by chance.)
- Turn it off. - Don't get caught on camera.
(More than 5 seconds)
Let's turn it off.
(He successfully turns it off before 5 seconds pass.)
What? You turned it on just now.
I turned it off. The light is at "Off."
(What? He turned it off.)
Isn't this how you turn it off?
(Taps)
(He turns on the surveillance camera.)
You turned it on.
(Goodness)
For goodness' sake.
Oh, it should be at "Off."
(You don't know anything about being a thief.)
- The light is at "Off." - You don't know the basics.
There are so many surveillance cameras.
(Everyone, be careful.)
- That's a surveillance camera. - That's right.
(Kwang Soo finds the camera that Jae Suk just turned off.)
(What?)
(He turns it back on.)
(He is proud because he thinks he turned it off.)
Why is the light at "On"?
(Startled)
- Did I turn it off? - The light should be at "Off."
(These thieves can't even distinguish on and off.)
I see.
I can't believe you.
(Embarrassed)
What is wrong with you?
(Meanwhile, Se Chan...)
How much is this? 3,000 dollars?
(He finds 3,000 dollar golf clubs.)
3,000 dollars.
(Let me steal it.)
(So Min was walking around aimlessly.)
This could be expensive.
It could be a good bicycle.
(She finds a pretty bicycle.)
All right.
(She rides the bicycle to the tent.)
Be careful.
(Team Jong Kook has stolen 5,000 dollars' worth of items.)
What is this?
(At that moment)
(A box with an R mark?)
(What's inside the box Kwang Soo stumbled upon?)
It's a bulletproof vest.
(A bulletproof vest?)
(This is incredible!)
This is incredible.
(Kwang Soo can nullify 1 water gun attack.)
Where is Haha?
Haha? Your teammate.
- He is downstairs. - Downstairs?
Why are you wearing a vest?
- Oh, it's a bulletproof vest. - That's right.
(Kwang Soo shows off his vest.)
Where did you get it?
What a coward! You were so scared of being eliminated...
that you put it on right away.
- Go and sit in prison. - Sure.
(Confident)
(Jae Suk finds something on the 2nd floor.)
What? Why is there a framed photo of me?
(A framed photo of Jae Suk is in the living room.)
It's a framed photo of you. I guess it has a price.
Let's check the price.
I don't have anything like this at my own house.
Let's see how much Yoo Jae Suk is.
(Jae Suk's photo is 10,000 dollars?)
It's 10,000 dollars.
(That's pretty expensive.)
That's incredible. I will move it to the tent.
(Here comes a 10,000-dollar item.)
I stole a 50,000-dollar item.
Let's check out the next room. Let's see what's inside.
(The two petty thieves are searching the room.)
- How expensive is that? - Why is there Yu San Seul's CD?
- How much is it? - 200 dollars.
(Yu San Seul's CD is 200 dollars.)
200 dollars. That's good.
Haha.
(And next to it...)
- That's my album! - Haha.
(Haha's legendary debut album no one has purchased, "The Gang")
That's my album.
- It's 15 dollars. - For goodness' sake.
- 15 dollars. - This album is really rare, okay?
(He is the only realistic appraiser in the mansion.)
This is...
(Where is Tear of Yondu?)
Tear of Yondu? Where is Tear of Yondu?
- What? - So Min.
This is the hacker's room.
- What's the hacker's room? - What?
(The hackers' true role is finally revealed.)
This is the hacker's room.
(If 2 or more people stay for over 5 minutes, )
(the alarm will go off and the patrol guards will show up.)
(There are 3 hacker's rooms in the mansion.)
(They might look like an ordinary study, )
(but they contain...)
(a hint on Tear of Yondu.)
If 2 or more people stay for over 5 minutes...
(If 2 or more people stay for over 5 minutes, )
- I found it. - So Min.
(the alarm will go off and the patrol will show up.)
(Ji Hyo and Haha enter the room, but cannot find the rules.)
- No way. - What is this room?
There are no surveillance cameras, right?
(Surprised)
- Haha, lock the door. - Let's lock the door.
I am a hacker.
(It's finally my turn.)
- This is a hacker's room. - I am a hacker.
- If two or more people... - What is this?
Se Chan, we need to do this.
We need to solve this
(There are a locked laptop...)
(and a piece of paper with a code.)
(Will the code lead them to Tear of Yondu?)
It's a passcode.
We will be fine if we leave within five minutes.
Let's set a timer.
Alarm watch. Stopwatch.
"Alarm watch"?
Stopwatch. Five minutes.
(The clock is reset if they leave the room.)
This is "I am."
(Serious)
(He uses his limited English skills.)
I, M. A, I, M.
(His knowledge runs out.)
I don't get it. What does "WXY" mean?
(Ji Hyo and Haha only repeat the code like parrots.)
A, B, C, D, E, F, G,
(So Min repeats it like a parrot too.)
H, I, J, K, L, M...
(She thinks for a while.)
(She begins to interrogate the cameraman.)
What? What did you say?
(You must know something, right?)
You saw something, right?
(She switches to investigating the witness instead.)
Please tell me what you saw.
(Se Chan joins her.)
Can I come in?
If you come in, the patrol will come after five minutes.
(It's okay for 5 minutes.)
- I am going in. - A, B, C, D...
I don't think you should fixate on the passcode.
(She doesn't expect much from Se Chan.)
Leave before five minutes are up. What time is it now? Come on.
Check the time.
Five minutes. I set the timer.
(At that moment)
What is going on?
- What did you do? - We didn't do it.
(A siren?)
We didn't set the alarm off, did we?
(Haha and Ji Hyo were together for more than 5 minutes.)
There are vowels and consonants. What is going on?
Two or more people have stayed in a hacker's room...
for over five minutes.
- What? - The patrol is on its way.
(The patrol guards are sent because of Ji Hyo and Haha.)
Do we need to hide?
(Are the patrol guards coming?)
(The patrol guards enter the mansion.)
I need to hide.
(The cowardly petty offenders scatter to different places.)
(The siren made them scatter.)
(The patrol guards make the rounds on the 1st floor.)
(They pass by the room in which Jae Suk is hiding.)
(Nervous)
(A few minutes pass.)
(The patrol guards leave without apprehending anyone.)
(I can go out now, right?)
Hey, So Min.
(They start to solve the hint again after the patrol guards left.)
Jong Kook, I can't solve it.
These books must be here for a reason.
Maybe the first letters of the books make out this code.
(The titles of the books are related to the alphabet hint?)
- A... - No.
(A deep sigh)
- That's right. - You know,
I shouldn't have become a hacker.
This is so hard.
The other team's hacker is Ji Hyo, so we can take our time.
(Ji Hyo has been studying the code outside for 10 minutes.)
I am not good at deciphering codes.
(Then she just repeats "I" and "M".)
I, M, A.
- You know, - What do you see?
(Meanwhile, Team Jae Suk...)
these alphabets are in order.
(He discovers that alphabets are written in order.)
U, V, W, X, Y.
- So... - Turn them into numbers.
(Abruptly)
A is one.
(Very loud)
(Shush!)
- For goodness' sake. - What?
(You need to be more careful.)
- It's right. - Do you want everyone to know?
- For goodness' sake. - But I figured it out.
(He is the type who likes to talk out loud what he learned.)
- What do you mean? - A is one.
(You both are very childish.)
- Listen to me. - What number is I?
(Talkative)
A, B, C, D, E, F, G,
- H, I. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9. - That's not how you solve it.
Here.
(Three letters would replace these question marks.)
Three letters...
would go into these question marks.
- That's right. - Now,
the ends are A and Y.
I wrote out the alphabet from A to Z.
(Exaggerated exclamation)
These letters are symmetrical.
That's what I am talking about!
- These letters are symmetrical. - Look.
(These alphabets are all symmetrical!)
W, X.
(If you divide all the letters in half...)
- All of them are symmetrical. - All of them are symmetrical.
All of them are symmetrical.
(There are only vertically symmetrical alphabets.)
We need to find three letters that are symmetrical.
(This is great!)
We did it.
What should I do with this?
(Burdensome)
Symmetrical letters.
- B. - B doesn't work.
(They count every vertically symmetrical alphabet.)
- C. - C doesn't work.
- H. - H.
- Look. - H.
- O. - O works.
- Keep your voice down. - T.
T works. T.
Hot. H, O, T.
(The answer is "Hot.")
- Hot. - Hot.
Let's go outside.
(While Team Jae Suk deciphered the code, )
Leave it behind.
Jong Kook, I think I figured it out.
(did So Min find out too?)
I need to find symmetrical letters.
- H. - H, O, T.
(She finds the symmetrical alphabets, HOT.)
- Three letters. - Hot.
- Hot. - Hot.
Let's try it.
H, O, T.
That's impossible.
(Now they just have to enter the password.)
(Was "HOT" not the password for the laptop?)
"H, O, T" doesn't work?
(How did this happen?)
But this is the hint.
Hey, Ha Na.
(If they figured out "HOT", but it's not the password...)
We got "H, O, T," but it isn't the password.
That means...
we need to find an object that says "HOT."
You know what I mean, right?
We need to find an object that says "HOT."
(There is an object with "HOT"...)
(in this hacker's room!)
You know what I mean, right?
This is an escape room.
(They start to search.)
Think of it as an escape room.
(Jae Suk finds something!)
"H, O, T".
(Amazing!)
"H, O, T."
(It is the water purifier...)
(that has "HOT" on it!)
(They find HOT!)
"H, O, T."
(He closely searches the water purifier.)
Should we take off the sticker?
(It looks like a sticker.)
I'll close the door.
(Another team could look.)
(He secures the room.)
(Once they take off the "Hot" sticker, )
(they find a writing.)
(Sand went into my ear, so I went to the hospital.)
(More people had mouth pain from eating meat.)
"Ear, sand, meat, and mouth." What do they mean?
(Sand went into my ear, so I went to the hospital.)
- They are in blue. - Let's see.
(More people had mouth pain from eating meat.)
- What could it be? - "Sand went into my ear,"
- Ear. - "so I went to the hospital."
(Why are four words written in blue?)
(At that time)
Haha's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
Police special forces have been dispatched.
Haha's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
Police special forces have been dispatched to arrest him.
(What's happening?)
- Haha? - Hurry and come out.
Running away won't be any use.
If his position is revealed,
doesn't it mean that he's caught on a surveillance camera?
Is that what it means?
(Haha was caught on a surveillance camera?)
Is it because he was caught on surveillance for a long time?
- Don't you think so? - With the water gun?
(How did Haha get eliminated?)
He got caught on the surveillance camera.
He's such a fool. Why did he get caught?
(Haha is arrested.)
(Haha is out.)
Shouldn't he leave the water gun with us?
(Haha has to hand the water gun to his team members.)
- He should hand it to us. - Right?
- That's true. - Kwang Soo.
Can you solve it? I have no idea.
I can't stay here longer than five minutes.
(Unlike Ji Hyo who didn't get "HOT", )
What's the hint?
"Sand went into my ear."
(Jae Suk and Ha Na are working on step 2.)
Ear, sand, meat, and mouth.
(At that time)
(They hear the sound of cuckoo.)
(They obtained a patrol schedule after clearing the mission.)
You will be given the patrol schedule...
if you complete the mission.
(Cuckoo sound indicates the start of patrol.)
(Patrol schedule)
(Patrol time and route at 3:30pm, on the 1st and 2nd floor)
(First patrol starts at 3:30pm.)
(Suk Jin runs away to a place where the guards don't patrol.)
Gosh, they're coming in.
(Without knowing, Jong Kook hides following other members' behaviors.)
(They must hide before the patrol guards find them.)
Where should I hide?
(They move in order.)
Hide here.
(Every member has finished hiding.)
(The patrol guards start to patrol assigned locations.)
(He gets nervous by the footstep sound.)
(They shouldn't patrol this room.)
(The patrol guards are searching assigned locations.)
(They move to the next room.)
(1st patrol at 3:30pm)
Se Chan.
(Suddenly)
Did you see the security during the patrol time?
(Of course not. I was also hiding.)
No.
(He sighs.)
Why?
Is someone on a mission...
(Is someone on a mission during the time of patrol?)
after making us hide?
Is someone on a mission after making us hide?
(Is someone doing something in secret?)
Really?
It might be true because I didn't see any security.
(Suk Jin's hunch)
Do you see any security guards?
(Se Chan checks if there are the patrol guards outside.)
You don't, do you?
(He can barely see.)
Someone is secretly on a mission right now.
(The room where Suk Jin and Se Chan are hiding)
(Surprised)
They're here.
- Security? - Policemen.
(He doesn't trust Se Chan.)
- Policemen? - Yes.
- You're lying. - They're here.
(My hunch is never wrong.)
Go outside and look.
(If you can't trust me, check for yourself.)
They're here indeed. They are policemen.
(He can't check in case he gets caught.)
I don't want to get eliminated.
(I'd rather not check.)
(1st patrol is over.)
Let's go.
(After checking that the patrol is over, )
(everyone goes back to their own hacker's room.)
When the security is on patrol,
(Jong Kook noticed something strange.)
all of us hide.
When we hide,
what if the spy does something?
Suk Jin said the same thing.
(He has the same suspicion as Suk Jin.)
If you think about it... Really?
It's strange that we hide.
(There must be someone who has a secret mission.)
Hiding is too easy.
Suk Jin, doesn't something feel strange?
- What? - Jong Kook said exactly...
(Something's strange.)
what you said before.
- Really? - Yes.
That's why I asked whether you saw the security.
(See? What did I tell you?)
I did.
- I saw them. - Isn't someone on the move?
When we hide, everyone hides, and no one does anything.
(Suspicious)
What if there's a spy who goes around...
with the security?
- All we have to do is hide. - Right.
(That could be it.)
Isn't it too easy?
I was hiding, and the security saw me...
(He adds on.)
All right, be quiet.
What?
- All right, be quiet. - What?
(No one asked for your story.)
(What is wrong with this guy?)
- Listen. - But this is...
- It's not that important. - If I don't talk about it...
(This is an important story.)
- Was it important? - It was very important.
It's very strange.
(It's very strange.)
We should figure it out to solve it.
(They must figure out the password first to find out something.)
- So Min, let's go in. - So Min.
We have to solve it.
(So Min is Team Jong Kook's hacker.)
- Don't go in. - What? You go in first.
Come in when I set the timer.
(She enters the hacker's room with confidence.)
I'm jealous of you.
Ji Hyo is the hacker on my team.
(He's jealous.)
- That's why I said that it's okay. - It started.
(He never thought he'd be jealous of having So Min as a hacker.)
We can take our time. It's Ji Hyo on that team.
(Relaxed)
She's writing ABCD on repeat. She's driving me crazy.
(She's writing the alphabets repeatedly.)
I thought that she was calling the spirits.
(I thought that she was calling some spirits.)
X, Y.
(Please let me know the password.)
Why doesn't it work?
(She can't figure it out.)
- Here's what I think. - There's something.
(Team Jong Kook thinks something feels leery.)
The owner of the mansion or someone is up to something.
(There must be the owner of this mansion or someone like that.)
Isn't it strange that there's a photo of Jae Suk?
(Why a photo of Jae Suk?)
It's strange that Jae Suk's photo is in this house.
(It's strange. Why is there a photo of Jae Suk?)
- Think about it. - Also, the price is...
(In fact, it's 10,000 dollars.)
- It's 10,000 dollars. - so expensive.
I wasn't going to say this,
(Kwang Soo shares something.)
but Haha's "The Gang" CD was 1.5 dollars, so I put it back down.
How can it only cost 1.5 dollars?
(It's not worth stealing.)
- I think it's Jae Suk's house. - It's strange.
(Is Jae Suk the owner?)
- Isn't it his house? - Isn't this Jae Suk's house?
- Yes. - This house?
He also interrupted you a moment ago.
(He also interrupted you a moment ago.)
Hey, I think it's right.
(It looks like Jae Suk owns the place.)
That's why his photo is pricey.
- That's what I'm saying. - Get out and go back inside.
(They suspect Jae Suk based on various evidence.)
- Right? It's strange. - Yes.
I think this is Jae Suk's house.
(Se Chan is looking for something to steal.)
What's this?
(He finds something.)
(He finds a safe by chance.)
(However...)
(Why is a siren ringing all of a sudden?)
What's going on?
Yang Se Chan has been caught on surveillance cameras.
Se Chan is out.
(This is where the surveillance camera is.)
This is where the surveillance camera was.
(Surveillance camera is on.)
Why is that on?
(Who turned it on?)
- Is it off? Like this? - You have to turn it off.
(Jae Suk definitely turned it off a while ago.)
(Someone turned the surveillance camera back on.)
Yang Se Chan has been caught on surveillance cameras.
Se Chan is out.
(Gosh, what a fool.)
That fool.
Why did he get caught? Where did it happen?
(Where did he get caught?)
Did he go to the restroom?
(Thieves are in chaos...)
(while figuring out the password and avoiding surveillance cameras.)
- Se Chan is out. - He got caught on camera.
I don't know. I don't think so.
(The more confusing it gets, )
(the more suspicious they become of each other.)
Who are you today?
- Me? - Yes.
- What about me? - What...
(However, there is no evidence.)
- You're very suspicious. - Why me?
(For now)
We have to be careful of the surveillance cameras.
(Jae Suk is concentrating on figuring out the password.)
(Ear, sand, meat, and mouth, how are they related?)
(Staring)
(What is that number lock?)
(Sand went in my ear, so I went to the hospital.)
(More people had mouth pain from eating meat.)
Ha Na.
(Come here, Ha Na.)
(Did Jae Suk notice something?)
Ear, meat, mouth.
- What's this? - Chinese characters.
(He finds numbers from Chinese characters.)
Chinese characters.
(Ear, sand, meat, and mouth)
(2, 4, 6, 9)
(Captain Jae Suk figures out the password.)
(Hacker Ha Na is off to try the password.)
- This is it. - I'll try.
Is it 2 and 4?
(She tries 2469.)
Four.
(She unlocks it.)
(Unbelievable)
- Is it number four? - Yes.
- You're a genius. - No.
(Exclaiming)
It's four.
(What is inside the cabinet that was locked?)
- What is it? - What?
They're balloons.
(Are there balloons on the plates?)
(There's one key next to a balloon.)
Do we have to inflate the balloons?
(He's curious.)
(They inflate the balloons first.)
Wait, ear is number two.
(At the same time, Jong Kook figured the password out.)
- Meat is six. - What about sand?
(The captains are working instead of the hackers.)
Sand is number four.
It's 2, 4, 6, 9.
Is it 2, 4, 6, 9?
What's this?
(There are only balloons in the cabinet.)
What is it?
(What on earth are they?)
What's the point of opening it?
There's a key. Goodness.
(Why am I going through this?)
(Where did Jong Kook go?)
I'm not smart.
(She introspects herself quickly.)
Class president in sixth grade.
(So Min's achievements)
I was the class president in the 7th grade...
and vice president in the 8th grade.
(She probably wasn't voted for being smart.)
I'm not smart.
What's this key for?
(What is the key for?)
I'll keep it for now.
(One man show)
Why?
(At that moment)
Ji Suk Jin's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
Police special forces have been dispatched to arrest him.
Someone else is out.
(Did Suk Jin get eliminated?)
(Jong Kook left So Min behind.)
(He found Suk Jin who is waiting for the patrol guards.)
I'm out.
- What? - I'm out.
(How did Suk Jin get eliminated?)
- Are you out? - Yes.
(He checks his name tag.)
Come this way.
- You got hit. - Is it the water gun?
(Goodness)
You got hit.
(Suk Jin's name tag got shot by a water gun.)
So Min, Suk Jin got eliminated.
(We're in trouble.)
He got hit by a water gun.
Suk Jin got eliminated.
(What? Water gun?)
He got hit by a water gun.
The water was pink.
(He notices something strange.)
- Each team will get a tool. - What's this?
(When they received a tool this morning)
(The paint was definitely blue.)
It leaks if you put water in before.
(Why is it pink?)
The water was pink.
- Was it pink? - Yes.
(Then Kwang Soo visits Jong Kook.)
- Whose is it? - Did you get it?
Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
(He checks if Kwang Soo has the water gun.)
Do you have a water gun?
Yes, I got a gun.
(I got it from Haha.)
- What? - I got it...
(Kwang Soo received the water gun from Haha.)
after Haha got eliminated.
Let me see your water gun. I have something to check.
(Checking)
- Shoot it. - You won't steal it?
(Just shoot it.)
No, just shoot it.
(The paint is blue.)
Suk Jin got eliminated.
(The paint of Kwang Soo's water gun isn't pink.)
He got hit by a water gun and the color was pink.
(They need to find the member with the pink paint.)
But the color was pink.
(Confused)
Ours shoot blue.
The announcements are different.
(The announcements are different.)
When Suk Jin got eliminated, the announcement was,
(When Suk Jin was eliminated)
"Ji Suk Jin's location is revealed."
("Suk Jin's location is revealed. Running away will be of no use".)
"Running away will be of no use."
When Se Chan got eliminated, the announcement was,
(When Se Chan was eliminated)
"Yang Se Chan is caught on surveillance cameras."
("Se Chan is caught on surveillance cameras. Se Chan is out.")
"Se Chan is out."
That means Haha got hit by a water gun.
(The announcement is telling the difference.)
Ji Suk Jin's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
(When Se Chan got eliminated)
Yang Se Chan is caught on surveillance cameras.
Se Chan is out.
Haha's location is revealed. Running away will be of no use.
(Haha got eliminated due to the pink paint!)
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk and Ha Na are still working on the balloons.)
Now...
(What do these balloons mean?)
(There are 3 balloons on each plate.)
(Only the last plate has 2 balloons and a key.)
I think...
(They rack their brains.)
it's about mixing the colors.
(Could that be it?)
It's about mixing the colors.
(Will mixing the colors help them solve the hint?)
- Right? - You are right.
If we mix the colors...
(Then the key has to do something with the color pink.)
Pink.
(Ha Na did an incredible job as a hacker.)
Ha Na, you are right.
Pink.
Look at the diary, it's pink.
(Done scanning)
(They find a pink diary!)
(The pink diary is locked.)
This is incredible.
(They open the lock with the key.)
(There's something inside.)
What is it?
"You are almost there. This is the last problem."
What is this?
("You are almost there. This is the last problem.")
"Cross you out from 'Partner' and reverse the rest."
("Cross the last syllable out from 'Partner' and reverse the rest.")
(Cross the last syllable out from 'Partner' and reverse the rest?)
Shall we retrace our steps?
What does this mean?
(Clueless)
(So Min is trying to figure out the use of the key.)
What is this?
This key is for a small diary.
(She had such diary when she was little.)
(From the key, she guesses that she needs a diary.)
(She finds the diary.)
(Jong Kook shows up at the perfect timing.)
Jong Kook,
- I found it. - Hey.
Come here.
- I got this. - What?
(Jong Kook with brain and So Min with petty tricks)
"You are almost there. This is the last problem."
- "Cross you out from 'Partner'..." - Jong Kook, I am exhausted.
(She racked her brain too much.)
Do you have an energy drink?
I'm exhausted. Do you have an energy drink?
(I want to solve the problem and relieve my exhaustion.)
I haven't studied this hard back in school.
(I haven't studied this hard back in school.)
I am serious.
(That's not something you should brag about, So Min.)
"Cross you out from 'Partner' and reverse the rest."
What are these?
What are these balloons?
(By the way)
The balloons are about mixing different colors.
(The crew member reveals the answer.)
You were supposed to find the pink diary that way.
But you found it without needing to.
(By the way, she skipped the balloons.)
I bypassed that step.
(She resorted to tricks.)
I am like a genius. I got the answer without thinking.
(Feeling proud)
(She suddenly opens the cabinet again.)
Jong Kook.
This is really fascinating.
Solving the patterns of the colors gives us pink.
(Showing balloons)
Really?
(Acting surprised)
Yes.
Mixing the colors...
(Laughing)
(Actress Jeon is embarrassed and bursts into laughter.)
Jong Kook.
Let me do it again. Give me another chance.
Let me do it again.
Oh, Jong Kook!
(Acting surprised)
(Yes?)
If we blow these balloons,
(If we blow these balloons, we get pink.)
we get pink.
Really?
- Really? - So...
(Let's blow the balloons.)
Then we get the pink diary!
(Then we get the pink diary! No way! It's unbelievable!)
No way!
That's it.
(The end of the secret of the pink diary)
- That's how we get the pink diary. - That's incredible.
I found it.
(Ji Hyo still goes over the letters like a ouija board.)
- Did you solve the passcode? - Kwang Soo.
(Let's give up.)
- I can't do this. - Jae Suk is suspicious.
(Kwang Soo suspects Jae Suk.)
Jae Suk is suspicious.
What do you mean?
(Suddenly?)
I think Jae Suk has another mission.
(She has no idea what's going on outside.)
(She has been inside the room for an hour.)
This is driving me crazy.
This sticks out from the other books on the shelf.
(This sticks out from other books on the shelf.)
Forget about "HOT."
What is this?
(She found the pink diary.)
There should be a key.
(They have to get the password to find the key.)
Why is that diary here?
(Kwang Soo is just as clueless.)
I can't open it.
(The two fools struggle.)
(Kwang Soo gives up.)
What?
(What?)
- What is it? - Where is that thing?
(Ji Hyo found something.)
- The pen? - Yes.
(She wants to use the appraiser's pen on the diary.)
That could be it.
(Eureka.)
(No.)
That could be it.
(Enthusiastic)
I will look for more items.
Did you find expensive items?
(She's not likely to find the password.)
Yes, I did. No one else but me is doing it.
This makes no sense.
(Jong Kook and So Min are trying to figure out the hint on the diary.)
- We don't have partners today. - I...
- Why does it say "Partner"? - I...
"You are almost there. This is the last problem."
(They read the hint again.)
"Cross you out from 'Partner' and reverse the rest."
What does "Partner" mean?
(Who on earth is the partner?)
- We don't have partners today. - Teammate.
"Cross you out..."
(Deducting)
Maybe it's about taking out.
(They're clueless.)
Take out what?
This makes no sense.
It's "Part." "You" is read as "Ner" in Korean.
(Cross "Ner" out from "Partner.")
(Part?)
(Partner)
It's "Part." "You" is read as "Ner" in Korean.
(Part)
- Part. - That's it.
(If they cross "Ner" out, )
If we cross "Ner" out, we are left with "Part."
(they're left with "Part.")
"Cross you out from 'Partner'..."
(They move on to the next line.)
Write "Part" in English.
"And reverse the rest."
("Reverse the rest.")
Reverse it.
(Reverse the rest?)
- Cross "Ner" out. - That's right.
Let's write "Part" in English. Give it to me.
(Jong Kook got an idea.)
Give me the spelling.
(Jong Kook starts writing "Part" in English.)
- It's T, R, A, P. - P.
It's T, R, A, P.
(They reverse the letters.)
Trap.
T, R, A, P. Trap.
(They reversed the letters and got "Trap".)
- We got "Trap." - T.
T, R, A, P. Trap.
(They quickly type in "Trap".)
It's trap.
(They are in!)
- We are in. - Trap.
(So Min and Jong Kook figured out all hints in the room...)
(and unlocked the laptop.)
Jong Kook, step outside for a second.
(Jong Kook goes outside to keep the patrol from coming.)
- I am anxious. - Okay.
- Close the door. - Trap. We got it.
(She just needs to check what's on the laptop.)
- The location of Tear of Yondu. - Hold on.
How is Ji Hyo supposed to solve this?
(Hold on.)
(They got the location of Tear of Yondo on the laptop.)
It's in the basement.
- I have been there. - I will take a photo of the plan.
- Do you know where this place is? - What?
(Sub-basement level 1)
I went to the basement earlier.
(Tear of Yondo is at the end of the center staircase.)
(The safe is located in the sub-basement level 1.)
- The password is "Trap." - It's "Trap."
(The password to the safe is also "Trap.")
Okay. I will go there.
(He moves to find the safe.)
(He is close to finding Tear of Yondu.)
(He goes down the staircase without hesitation.)
(He remembers to turn off the surveillance camera.)
(After turning off the surveillance camera, )
(he safely reaches the safe!)
(If he opens the safe and gets Tear of Yondu, )
(Team Jong Kook will win!)
(Once he enters the password, "Trap", )
(the safe opens!)
(He checks what's inside.)
(It's not Tear of Yondu, but a mysterious file.)
(He takes the file and moves hurriedly!)
Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
(At that moment)
Jong Kook!
Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
(He hears So Min's scream.)
- What is it? What's wrong? - Jong Kook!
Who is it? What's wrong?
(So Min got attacked by someone.)
Who was it?
- So Min's location is revealed. - Who is it? What's wrong?
Police special forces have been dispatched to arrest her.
Jong Kook.
(To make the matter worse, they hear the sound of cuckoo.)
(Jong Kook leaves hurriedly.)
I will go and hide.
My goodness.
(But Jong Kook doesn't know where the guards will patrol.)
All right. Come in quickly.
(He hides in a nearby room.)
(Team Jae Suk knows the patrol route...)
(and hides accordingly to avoid the patrol guards.)
(Ji Hyo doesn't know the patrol route, )
The patrol.
(so she hides as well as possible.)
(She hides every inch of her body in case the guards enter the room.)
I need to hide.
(The patrol guards enter the mansion.)
(Once he takes cover, )
(Jong Kook checks the file.)
(He finds something in the file.)
For goodness' sake.
This is yet another twist.
(What does the file reveal?)
There is a spy.
(A spy?)
(A mysterious report inside the file)
(Lure the 8 thieves to 1 police officer's mansion.)
There is a spy.
Today, we will play Empty House: Oh, My Thieves.
(A cafe in Gyeonggi Province before the shooting)
You are the police officer who is hiding among the thieves.
But the empty mansion the thieves will rob...
(The mansion the thieves are in...)
(belongs to you who are an undercover police officer.)
belongs to you, the police officer.
The police officer will carry out a sting operation...
(The police officer is on Tear of Yondu Project to arrest thieves.)
called Tear of Yondu Project to catch the thieves.
The object of the thieves' desire, Tear of Yondu,
(The undercover police officer has Tear of Yondu...)
will be in your possession, the police officer.
(thieves are looking for.)
You win by shooting the water gun on the thieves' name tags...
(If the police officer arrests all thieves with his water gun, )
(the police officer wins.)
and arresting all of them in the final race.
(If his or her identity is revealed, the police officer loses.)
You lose by getting eliminated by the thieves first.
The thief who eliminates you will take Tear of Yondu,
(If the police officer loses, )
(thieves that eliminated the police officer will get Tear of Yondu.)
and their team will win the race.
(There's a spy among us.)
(Knocking)
(Who is it?)
It's the police!
(Police?)
I didn't get hit by a water gun.
(I didn't even get shot.)
(The patrol guards come upon where Jong Kook's hiding.)
What? What is going on?
(Why couldn't Jong Kook avoid the police?)
Do I just get caught?
- Shall we go to the mansion? - Shall we do that?
(Team Jong Kook proceeded without knowing the patrol route.)
- Let's just go. - That's right.
- We can do that. - Let's go.
(So they didn't know the patrol route.)
(Patrol schedule)
(Patrol time and route at 4:30pm, on the 1st and 2nd floor)
(The room Jong Kook's hiding is part of the 2nd patrol route.)
(Jong Kook tries to hold out with his power.)
What happens now?
(But he's trapped.)
Do I just get caught?
(Jong Kook found out about the spy, but he couldn't avoid the patrol.)
- You are under arrest. - How can this be?
(The patrol guards found Jong Kook. He's out.)
Thief Kim Jong Kook was eliminated by the patrol.
(Team Jae Suk is moving to the safe after founding out its location.)
(They open the safe, )
- It opened. - It did.
(but the safe is empty.)
- Is there a hint? - No.
Aren't you looking for a hint?
(Frustrated)
I know, but we didn't find it.
We can't find it anywhere.
(They move to somewhere else without finding out anything.)
We need the hint to solve it.
(Ji Hyo is still inside the hacker's room.)
Ji Hyo.
The other team figured it out.
- Really? I found it. - What?
There's a piece of paper.
(Did Ji Hyo find something?)
I found it.
Look at it.
(She shares what she found with Kwang Soo.)
"Sand went into my ear, so I went to the hospital."
(Sand went into my ear, so I went to the hospital...)
(Everyone found it already.)
"More people had mouth pain from eating meat."
(What is wrong with her?)
What could this mean?
(Jae Suk is looking for hints.)
(In the room where Jong Kook was eliminated, )
(he finds a project folder.)
What's this?
(He checks the contents of the project.)
"Lure the eight thieves...
(Jae Suk discovers the existence of a police officer.)
to one police officer's house."
Ha Na.
(He tries to share the information with Ha Na.)
Thief Park Ha Na's location is revealed.
Police special forces will be dispatched to arrest her.
(How did I get caught?)
Where was the camera?
Thief Park Ha Na's location is revealed.
(The patrol guards find out Ha Na's location.)
What?
(Is Ha Na out?)
Police special forces will be dispatched to arrest her.
Why Ha Na?
(There's pink paint on her name tag.)
(Found by the police, Ha Na is out.)
Be careful, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo finally steps out of the hacker's room.)
- Why? - Not many people are left.
It looks like six members remain.
There are 2, 2, and 2.
(What? How many are left?)
To solve this...
- I had such... - What did you say?
(Surprised)
(What's wrong?)
- I had a hard time solving it. - Before that.
- How many people remain? - Six people, isn't it?
(What are you talking about?)
You were in there for too long. Follow me back in.
- Did something happen? - Stay inside.
(Ji Hyo has been disconnected from the outside world too long.)
- Why? - Everyone got eliminated.
That was such a long time ago.
(Frustrated)
Look, Suk Jin,
(They give an update to each other.)
Se Chan, and Haha are out.
- So Min and Jong Kook are out too. - What?
(Since when?)
- Really? - Yes.
(She finally hears the news.)
Only these remain?
I didn't know, Kwang Soo.
- I stayed here too long. - You stayed in this room too long.
You're like the one from "Old Boy."
- I know. - The world changed.
(As if she was trying to hide herself from a surprise attack, )
Let's see.
(Ji Hyo hid herself in a chest.)
(While she was hiding herself there, )
(many of her colleagues left.)
So Min's location is revealed.
Jong Kook was eliminated by security.
(Ji Hyo finally decided to step outside to the world.)
It's not six anymore.
My goodness.
(Jae Suk enters the room where Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are.)
Kwang Soo.
(Since the situation has changed, )
(Ji Hyo is suspicious of Jae Suk.)
Gosh, hey.
(Kwang Soo passes the water gun to Ji Hyo.)
(Calm down and listen to me.)
A police officer is inside.
(A police officer?)
- What? - Inside?
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo don't know about the police officer.)
- What do you mean? - It's a police officer's house.
- What do you mean? - It's a trap.
(He shares information about the police officer.)
Look at this.
(Now everyone knows about the police officer.)
Is this it?
There's no point in searching.
The police officer already has the necklace.
Do we have to eliminate the police officer?
(Surprised)
I think so.
(Only three people remain.)
(One of them is the police officer.)
It's 10 minutes before 5pm.
After 5pm, you will be locked inside this mansion.
(They must find the police officer...)
Let's go.
(to win before the mansion shuts down.)
Ji Hyo.
- It's Jae Suk. - How do you know?
He stayed with Ha Na all along.
(Kwang Soo suspects Jae Suk of being the police officer.)
Isn't it you?
No, how could I be?
- Isn't it you? - I'm not.
(Ji Hyo finds Kwang Soo suspicious.)
Why do you keep accusing Jae Suk?
(No one trusts each other.)
It's one of us three.
I know that it's not you.
And Ha Na got eliminated when she was with him.
(Is Jae Suk the police officer?)
We have 10 minutes left.
- Watch where Jae Suk is going. - Okay.
- I'm here. - What?
(Speak of the devil.)
Gosh, you startled me.
- You dirty... - I was telling her to be careful.
(Kwang Soo is rattled at Jae Suk's appearance.)
I was telling her to be careful since she's on my team.
(Ji Hyo can't get used to this world of mistrust.)
What happened while I was in the room?
In my opinion, it's not you, Ji Hyo.
(There are only 3 people left.)
(One of them is the police officer.)
It's not me.
I just came out after solving the passcode.
(Ji Hyo claims to be innocent.)
(Ji Hyo took a long time to figure out the hint.)
(What if she left the room during that time?)
(Kwang Soo is another candidate who could be the police officer.)
That's the surveillance camera.
(Thieves turned off the surveillance camera.)
(Kwang Soo turned it back on.)
(Did he do it to catch thieves?)
Why did you turn it on?
(The last candidate is Jae Suk.)
Why is my photo here?
(There was a big photo of Jae Suk from the start.)
It's strange that Jae Suk's photo is in this house.
(She's suspicious of Jae Suk.)
- And it's too expensive. - It's 10,000 dollars.
(Was there his photo...)
(because he's the owner of the mansion?)
(Everyone is suspecting each other.)
Is it you?
My goodness.
(Which one of them is the police officer?)
Ji Hyo, considering many things,
he's the police officer.
(Kwang Soo is always on the top of the list.)
Gosh.
Wait.
(If that's the case...)
- Your fate depends on me. - Explain your photo.
What?
If this isn't your house,
(There's a big photo of Jae Suk in the mansion...)
why is there a large photo of you?
(because he is the owner?)
What do you think?
(It's a trap set up by the undercover police officer...)
That was placed by the police officer who lured us here.
(to lure everyone to think that it's Jae Suk.)
As I said, this entire...
Why are you stammering?
(She's very suspicious of him.)
- This entire... - Why are you stammering?
Ji Hyo, you have to decide quickly.
(The identity of the police officer is becoming more mysterious.)
- We have no time. - Ji Hyo.
It's over once you're eliminated.
He's wearing a bulletproof jacket.
(He's the only one wearing a bulletproof vest.)
Do you understand what I mean?
He won't die.
(He can protect himself from elimination.)
The one who remains will be eliminated.
(If Kwang Soo is the police officer, )
- Okay? - I can't eliminate you.
(it's likely that he'll win thanks to the bulletproof vest.)
One of us has to take off his bulletproof jacket.
Conditions should be even.
- That's true. That's my decision. - Yes.
Let's make it fair.
(The thieves are at a disadvantage...)
Will you shoot me?
(if Kwang Soo is the police officer...)
- You have the bulletproof vest on. - We need to take it off first.
(because Kwang Soo is wearing a bulletproof vest.)
- Right. - Take off the bulletproof vest.
(Kwang Soo will always be suspected as long as he is wearing the vest.)
- Isn't that fair? - Let's start with that.
Okay.
(He takes off the bulletproof vest to clear suspicion.)
(Shooting)
Kwang Soo, take off the bulletproof vest.
Jae Suk's gun can't be used anymore.
(The bulletproof vest can't be used anymore.)
- Is that right? - Yes.
(Only Ji Hyo's water gun remains.)
Kwang Soo can't be...
(She observes Kwang Soo taking off his vest.)
It'll be difficult if he's not the police officer.
(Ji Hyo finds something.)
What is Kwang Soo doing? Wait.
(Inside the bag that Kwang Soo's cameraman is carrying around, )
Isn't it the same as mine?
(there's pink paint.)
Suk Jin got eliminated. He got hit by a water gun.
(Suk Jin was eliminated after getting shot by a water gun.)
The water was pink.
(It's the water gun that shot Suk Jin.)
It was pink though.
(If Kwang Soo has pink paint, )
What is Kwang Soo doing? Wait.
(Kwang Soo is the police officer.)
(There's no holding back.)
He has a water gun.
- Jae Suk, I'll shoot. - Go away.
(Officer Kwang Soo takes action.)
Today race is called Empty House: Oh, My Thieves.
(Before the shooting, a cafe in Gyeonggi Province)
You're the police officer hiding among the thieves.
I'll show you that justice prevails.
(Ambitious)
(Surveillance cameras that were turned off)
(Kwang Soo turned them back on.)
(Se Chan walked around without noticing the camera.)
Yang Se Chan is caught on surveillance cameras.
Se Chan is out.
(Caught on the surveillance camera, Se Chan is out.)
You're not the Kwang Soo I know.
(Kwang Soo can win only after eliminating all the thieves.)
(He eliminated Haha with his water gun.)
What?
(Suk Jin who had no idea was also eliminated.)
What are you?
Am I out?
Jong Kook, Jong Kook!
(So Min who was alone got eliminated.)
(Kwang Soo is the police officer.)
- How... - I'm sorry.
(He even eliminated Ha Na in secret.)
I'm sorry.
(In the name of justice, he eliminated many thieves.)
- Jae Suk, I'll shoot. - Go away.
(Kwang Soo's identity is revealed.)
- Go. - I'll shoot him.
(Kwang Soo shoots the water gun of justice.)
Please.
- Wait. - I'll do it.
(Whoever shoots the name tag with the water gun wins.)
Catch him.
Shoot Jae Suk!
- Why you... - You think I'd fall for that?
(Shooting)
(He is defending with his face.)
I'm the justice.
(He is fighting 2 thieves for justice.)
- Get lost, both of you! - That's nonsense.
(At that moment)
(Kwang Soo's water gun aims at Jae Suk's name tag.)
Go away.
(But Kwang Soo fails.)
(She counterattacks right away.)
- Shoot him. - I got it.
(The thief's water gun can eliminate only one person.)
I shot him.
(Did she attack him successfully?)
It's over.
(They check Kwang Soo's name tag.)
(There's a clear blue paint stain.)
- You got hit. - Did I get hit?
(Did I get hit?)
(He got hit.)
(We did it!)
- Ji Hyo. - He got hit.
Jae Suk.
- Did I get hit? - I'm sorry.
(Team Thieves win by eliminating the police officer!)
- I'm sorry for suspecting you. - It's okay.
- You did it, Ji Hyo. - Gosh.
(I can't believe I lost.)
How could he fool me completely?
(I had to win for justice.)
Goodness.
(The final race is over.)
- I'll announce the result. - Okay.
The final winner is Team Thieves.
(The winner...)
(is Team Thieves.)
Officer Kwang Soo lost.
(I could win.)
- Did you lose? - Did you?
- That's right. - He lost his initial intention.
(I knew that.)
Did Kwang Soo lose?
The final winner of today's race is...
(The final prize, Tear of Yondu, )
Ji Hyo who won Tear of Yondu.
(will be given to Ji Hyo who eliminated the police officer.)
Is it Ji Hyo?
- What's this? - What's this?
(It's Tear of Yondu.)
I came an hour early for this.
This is Tear of Yondu.
(Touched)
I should have worked harder.
(He's very disappointed.)
She was so funny.
When she came out after solving the passcode, everyone was dead.
When I came out, everyone was dead.
(Ji Hyo wins a nice present after stepping out of the room.)
Kwang Soo the police officer is the only one who lost.
(Police officer Kwang Soo is the only one who lost.)
(He'll be penalized with the water cannon.)
He'll be penalized with the water cannon.
- What? - It's the last thing that we hoped.
(We all wanted to avoid that penalty.)
How about this?
(Since he did such a hard work by yourself...)
Don't hit his entire body.
Just hit his head.
(He'll only get his head hit by the water cannon.)
- His head? - That's better.
- The head is the best. - Okay.
- I'll take that. - You can do that instead.
(That would be nice.)
Or get it in your face.
- Let's go out for the penalty. - Thank you.
(They go out for the penalty.)
Okay.
(He's standing alone.)
Kwang Soo will get his penalty.
It will only hit my head, right?
(It will only hit his head.)
- Only your head. - Thank you.
- Stay back and stick out your head. - Okay.
One,
two,
three.
Happy New Year!
(As soon as he says Happy New Year...)
Stand back.
(Splashing)
(We prepared a lot, thinking 8 thieves would get this.)
- Hey. - What was that?
Kwang Soo.
(You said it'd only splash my head!)
- There was so much water. - What was that?
What is this?
(He's completely soaked.)
- Okay. - Okay.
Good job.
(Thank you for joining the show today, Ha Na.)
- Good job. - Thank you.
- This is the first! - I couldn't get any sleep,
(There's a fancy party to celebrate an occasion?)
preparing for this.
(They reveal the presents they prepared with all their hearts.)
- It's empty. - Is that it? What is that?
(Their memories of 10 years are revealed with the presents too.)
Hey! That's our memory together!
If you're cute, scream!
(The party isn't over yet!)
(Even Jong Kook joins the parade of the cute acts.)
- Okay. - Kwang Soo.
That's so cute.
The rice with grilled squids in special soy sauce.
(A feast with rare dishes)
(Special effects you see only in blockbusters)
- This is no joke. - I totally got it wrong.
It's cold.
(The one who enjoys the party is the winner.)
What? He got a badge.
(And...)
- Where are you going? - Suk Jin.
(they introduce their friends who attended the party.)
Nothing good came from meeting you guys!
- Go! Leave! - Where's your pride?
(Sometimes, you can't see our behaviors coming.)
Get a grip! You know nothing about love!
(Sometimes, we express intense feelings.)
(What's the secret weapon that will move the friend's heart?)
- Congratulations. - Are you serious?
(A Special Party: Hungry Race)
Seriously?