- Hello.
- Hi.
We're going to get
our fortune read again.
We're getting our fortune read
for the new year.
- Has it been a year already?
- Hello.
All right. Well, this year...
- We should say hello first.
- Gosh, we're filming now.
(He was taking his time
to drink his coffee.)
(He quickly puts it away.)
- You didn't know we started?
- Wait.
- Don't act like you didn't know.
- I didn't know we started.
- He's like an American.
- Right.
- American style.
- Jong Kook...
- There's one thing he's scared of.
- What is it?
The viewers.
(It's the viewers.)
He's not scared of anyone else.
- I'm scared of them.
- Jong Kook is only scared...
- of the viewers.
- That's the only fear he has.
You didn't know?
He's also scared of me.
- He's scared of who?
- When I put on a straight face,
- he gets scared.
- You're a viewer too.
- Right.
- Is that so?
- You're also a viewer.
- That's true.
- That's right.
- I see.
Suk Jin is afraid of some people,
and one of them is Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is watching.)
First of all, we should deliver
our New Year's greetings.
The Year of the Metal Rat, 2020,
has dawned.
- The Year of the Metal Rat.
- Viewers, Happy...
- New Year.
- Happy New Year.
My goodness. Oh, my.
Gosh. Going down
and coming up is so difficult.
He struggles more and more
every year.
Whenever we deliver our
New Year's greeting every year,
there are only two people
who complain about bowing.
They are Park Myung Soo
and Suk Jin.
- Gosh.
- I'm serious.
- They never change.
- Gosh.
This morning, we overheard
Suk Jin's phone call.
Right. There's a story behind it.
Kwang Soo, Jong Kook,
- We were just talking.
- Se Chan and I were talking.
"Yes, Director. The foreigners
are making unusual moves."
(The foreigners are
making unusual moves?)
What on earth is going on
with you these days?
- What kind of moves did they make?
- No.
It's about the stock market.
- It was about stocks.
- Right.
Wait, that's...
I heard he was just a total filler.
- I'm not a total filler.
- He's...
I'm just a regular filler.
- He's a big filler.
- That's it.
Why did you put on a hat
that signifies a drop in stocks?
- It's blue.
- What do you mean?
Blue means that the price went down.
- You should wear red for the rise.
- Don't say that.
- Why did you wear blue?
- This has nothing to do with that.
It's blue.
It means the price went down.
This signifies the ocean.
On top of that,
it says "end" on his hat.
(On top of that,
it says "end" on his hat.)
- Is it over? The end of the rise.
- Oh, no!
- The end of the drop in the prices.
- The end of the foreigners' moves.
That's not what it means.
Haha is wearing the pants
for the rise.
- Right.
- That's it.
- His stocks will go up.
- This feels nice.
Colors are important
at the beginning of the year.
- Yes, it's important.
- It's important.
He's wearing a blue hat
at the start of the year.
- Suk Jin is in trouble.
- Right.
I'm sorry to bring this up.
- This is making me uneasy.
- Right.
(Haha checks his underwear.)
No.
He's wearing red underwear too.
- His underwear?
- His underwear is red too.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Haha.
(Kwang Soo is also
wearing red underwear.)
Nice. We're going up.
- My goodness.
- Let me see.
(Will he get lucky in the new year?)
Kwang Soo.
(Even Se Chan is wearing
red underwear.)
- What?
- My gosh.
- Yes.
- Hey.
Yes.
- Happy New Year.
- Hey.
What's happening?
Which red underwear is that?
- Hey.
- This is amazing.
- Me too! I'm wearing red too!
- Hey, you shouldn't show it to us.
(So Min wants to join the red wave.)
Hey.
- So Min.
- I'm wearing red too.
- Stop it.
- I want to be on the rise too.
Okay. Stop it.
- Don't do it.
- That's enough.
- What is she doing?
- Goodness. Hey.
What's wrong with her?
- I feel hot...
- Gosh.
- all of a sudden.
- I'm hot too.
- She just...
- Suk Jin.
You need to have red
in your underwear.
(Even Jae Suk is wearing
red underwear.)
(The energy of the rise
is spurting everywhere.)
- Hey.
- You shouldn't do that.
Stop it.
I want to join too.
- I want to join too.
- Stop it.
I don't believe in that stuff.
I don't.
- Gosh.
- Your underwear isn't red?
I swear. He's probably
wearing black underwear.
- Everything about him is black.
- It has to be black.
- You should make it bleed at least.
- Should I start bleeding?
(Somewhat jealous)
Since it's the new year, let's talk
about our goals in the new year.
Haha, what's your goal
for this year?
I want to learn.
What?
Right. I want to learn something.
- You want to learn something?
- Yes.
My oldest son crushed me
in everything.
Excuse my language. I should start
learning how to speak properly.
- Like your choice of words?
- I want to learn.
- He figured out you're not smart.
- He figured it out.
My son figured out I'm stupid.
(The depth of his knowledge
was exposed to his 8-year-old son.)
- Don't say that.
- It's heartbreaking.
He thought I was good at English
when he was five.
Since I went abroad often,
he thought I was good.
But when he turned six,
he figured out the truth.
Since we're talking about this,
let me share my story.
When my son was seven years old,
I read him storybooks in English
every night.
One day, my son said,
"Dad, don't read me storybooks."
(Dad, don't read me storybooks.)
(He was shocked
when his son said no to story time.)
- Because of your pronunciation?
- Because of my pronunciation.
- That must be the reason.
Gosh, that's scary.
He told me not to read him books
because of my pronunciation.
- Gosh, our dads of the show.
- Right.
So after he turned seven, I stopped
reading him English storybooks.
- Gosh, that's funny.
- That's true.
Great. So you want to learn more.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
She should quit smoking.
(Slandering her)
Please quit this year.
- Make 2020 the last year.
- Please.
- I hope she can quit this year.
- Right. It's about time.
- We should end the interview here.
- Quit smoking.
We hope that Ji Hyo
will stop smoking this year.
- I hope I can quit smoking.
- Great.
- She went along with it.
- She played along.
Do it for the sake of your health.
Great.
What about you, Suk Jin?
I definitely have a goal.
- Stocks going up?
- Nothing like that. It's not that.
- What is it?
I'll work on my lower body.
The robot...
I want to have
Jong Kook's lower body.
I'll show you a strong
and muscular lower body.
Just focus on getting strong first.
(His comment strikes home.)
Just do that first.
- Jong Kook.
- That was brutal.
- He's full of energy today.
- No.
- You know?
- Hey.
I've been getting
a lot of compliments lately.
- My goodness.
- Okay.
Your goal isn't what we expected
to hear in the opening segment.
- What? What do you want?
- It's too plain.
- He said it's too plain.
- Should I talk about stocks?
- That's all.
- What should we talk about?
Have a second child. Tell us
that you'll have another child.
My gosh, having another child?
- Why not?
- Another child?
- Yes. Work out for it.
- Develop your lower body.
- My gosh.
- Do you still have such desires?
- What?
- Do you?
(You're still going strong, right?)
(Let me say a few words of blessings
for the New Year.)
- Hey, that's crazy.
- If you still have...
"Crazy"? He said it's crazy.
That's funny.
It goes through the roof.
(He's still very healthy.)
I go by Fiery Suk Jin.
Fiery. He's fiery.
My goodness, Haha.
- What about you, Jong Kook?
- I want to stay healthy as always.
Shouldn't you say that your goal
is getting married in 2020?
Right. But getting married...
I'm sure you know this. At my age...
- You're careful about it.
- Right. I'm careful about it.
He cherishes himself too much.
He loves himself too much.
- He loves himself too much.
- Right.
(He's in love
with exercising and muscles.)
My gosh, my abs.
(He's in love
with exercising and muscles.)
My gosh, my triceps.
That's why he washes
his underwear on his abs.
- He uses soap too.
- Like this.
He can wash his underwear
on his abs.
What about you, So Min?
It's always been my goal.
I want to quit drinking.
That's one of my goals. Instead of
wishing to meet people organically,
I'm going to take more initiatives.
- Like BD? Blind dates?
- What?
I thought you said, "kiss."
- Well, I like that too.
- No, not that.
I like that too.
- I'll set you up if I know anyone.
- I want to be set up.
- I already introduce a lot of guys.
- Set me up with someone.
In fact, I already have faith
in Jae Suk.
- I'm eyeing someone right now.
- Right.
- Really?
- I just got to know him recently.
So if there's a chance, I'll set up
an occasion for them to meet.
I'm observing him right now.
- You'll set them up?
- Yes.
- What is it?
- So you could have fun?
(That's a reasonable doubt.)
Really?
Then, let me join you too.
Men can tell if a guy is
good or not. I'm serious.
This is for Jong Kook and So Min.
Set them up if you know anyone.
- I'll do that.
- They might end up dating.
(Will they end up dating
each other?)
- I'm serious.
- Yes, Jong Kook.
- I'll introduce a nice guy to you.
- Okay.
Do you know
the guy came to my mind first?
- Who is it?
- Se Chan.
(Don't look too far.)
So Min, date Se Chan if you can.
But he's such a nice guy.
You guys like each other.
- He's a great guy.
- You guys like each other.
The three of us should hang out.
- With Jong Kook? Sounds great.
- With Jong Kook.
That's great.
We prepared a race to celebrate
the Year of the Metal Rat, 2020.
Before we start the race,
we prepared a segment...
where you can get
your fortune for 2020 read.
Is it that time already?
(What kind of event...)
(will await the members
of Running Man this year?)
Let us introduce you
to Park Sung Jun,
the fortune-teller who will
read your fortune for the new year.
- Please come in.
- Yes!
I love this.
- Hello.
- We meet every year.
- We meet again.
- He brought a small briefcase.
- The briefcase.
- He has a briefcase today.
- Yes.
It feels like yesterday when
you tripped walking in last year.
- Yes. He tripped when he left too.
- Right.
It's the Year
of the Metal Rat, 2020.
I'll read your fortune
for the new year.
Jae Suk, you were born
in the Year of the Rat.
- I was.
- Right.
So centering around Jae Suk,
I'll see which members
are compatible with him.
- Our compatibility with him?
- Our compatibility?
I will start...
with Mr. Ji Suk Jin first.
- He's going first again this year.
- My gosh.
Can you also read his fortune
regarding this?
He said the foreigners are
making unusual moves today.
That's so funny.
- That's hilarious.
- Will it go up or down?
Tell him what will happen
with the foreigners.
- Hello.
Please read my fortune well.
Suk Jin, starting 2016,
I kept telling you...
- to do nothing.
- Right.
(2 years ago
during his fortune-reading session)
(For the past 2 years, you did well
holding yourself back.)
(Just hang in there 1 more year.)
- "Stay down. Do nothing."
- You told me to stay down.
"Don't do anything."
- Will it be different today?
- First of all,
you didn't do anything
for 3 years from 2016 to 2018.
- In the new year, finally...
- "Finally".
"Finally".
(He's been keeping quiet
for 3 years. What about this year?)
You will have good fortune
that can bring money and honor.
(You will have good fortune
that can bring money and honor.)
- I can't believe this.
- No way.
- It's here!
- He's on the rise!
- It's good news after three years.
- Congratulations.
- I'll treat you to a meal.
But even if he gets back
what he lost, it'll just be even.
Right. He's been losing
for three years.
He's been going down
- Things will work out for him now.
- Right.
So in 2020,
as long as your energy allows,
it's better to do everything
that comes your way.
- Really?
- He's working a lot lately.
- I've never heard such good news.
- Okay.
So in 2020, you'll go abroad more
as you'll have itchy feet.
You might perform
in other parts of Korea as well.
Right. Why don't you make your way
to Hollywood this year?
- Gosh, I'll go anywhere.
- You know?
So in 2020 and 2021,
you'll be lucky enough to move
around a lot and make a fortune.
If you miss this chance...
(If you miss this chance...)
(He'll be finally lucky. What will
happen he misses the window?)
You will have another chance
at the age of 64 and 65.
(That's about 10 years later.)
Ten years?
- Gosh, this is crazy.
- Oh, no.
Suk Jin, if you miss this chance,
you'll be in trouble.
Seriously. Suk Jin...
- never gets a good chance.
- That's too short.
I don't get this chance often.
- I should seize this opportunity.
- At the age of 64.
- The next one is 10 years later.
- 10 years later?
So you are very ambitious
when it comes to money.
You're somewhat ambitious
in holding a good title as well.
But as long as you don't embarrass
yourself, you'll have money.
That means he'll be a nouveau riche.
- He's spot on though.
- A nouveau riche.
Suk Jin just makes sure
he doesn't embarrass himself...
- or gets criticized.
- I can't say he's wrong.
So this year and next year,
don't get distracted.
- Just focus on your work.
- Okay.
- Yes, you should just work.
- Thank you.
- You should work.
- I can't believe this.
- Suk Jin.
I've never seen him smile
while getting his fortune read.
(Suk Jin's New-Year Fortune:
Money and honor.)
Thank you.
(But if he misses his chance,
he must wait until 64.)
Next,
- it's Haha.
- It's his turn at last.
- It's here.
- My gosh.
His days have been dark.
- His days have been dark.
- Right.
His fortune last year was the worst.
(Haha's fortune was
1 of the 2 worst ones.)
It's your turn. It's here!
You have a chance.
(Two years ago,
during his fortune-reading session)
(Your fortune this year isn't good.
It's the darkest fortune.)
(It's pitch-dark.)
Haha, so far,
- I never told you any good news.
- Right.
In 2018, you passed
the pitch-dark days.
- You passed them.
- It's over now.
- I can't wait.
- My business partner!
It's the end of the tunnel.
For 5 years starting 2020...
- For 5 years.
- For 5 years?
Hold on.
For 5 years starting 2020,
the world will be yours.
(For 5 years starting 2020,
the world will be yours.)
(His dark days are over.)
- Haha.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- Goodness.
- Are you crying?
- Hey, it'll last five years.
- My gosh.
Hey, that's a long time.
- I think I'll get only six months.
- That's amazing.
- Haha, it's here.
- Don't miss your chance.
- It's finally your time.
- My goodness.
Haha, you got it now.
(His dark days flash by
in his mind.)
- He's crying.
- He's really crying.
Haha.
(He's really crying?)
- Haha, we know how you feel.
- It's here.
- It's yours now.
You waited for a long time now.
Actually, my wife and I held hands
together and prayed last night.
(The master of waiting:
I know how you feel, Haha.)
You'll be on your way to reaching
the peak from 2020 to 2024.
- You'll be on the rise.
- My gosh, that's amazing.
- I'm really happy for him.
- At last.
Actually, Haha,
you need to support Jae Suk.
Of course. Yes.
- I've been distant from him lately.
- He has to support Jae Suk?
It's not about being close
or distant from him.
When you are with Jae Suk, it's
likely you steal energy from him.
- I do?
- Yes.
- I don't want to do that.
- I heard that before.
That's why I was really sorry.
So you need to help him out.
- Sure. I'll do anything.
- Okay.
Do I need to help him
financially or...
"Financially"?
- Should I give him 10 dollars?
- Hey.
- Give him some money every month.
- Okay.
- Gosh. Give him cash.
Send him some yogurt regularly.
What? He said Haha
should send me yogurt regularly.
Okay. I'll wrap it up well.
I'll visit you.
I was disappointed before.
Don't you like meat?
I'll bring you some.
Didn't you curse him two years ago?
Let's go!
- Hang in there!
- It's your era.
(Haha's New-Year Fortune:
5 years of good luck)
Next up is So Min.
- My gosh.
- It must be good then.
- At last.
- I'm curious about her fortune.
- Hello.
Sir, I heard I will have a bad
fortune for three consecutive years.
(She starts spilling intel
before sitting down.)
- Okay.
- Right? That's my fortune.
I heard that in January...
- She talks too much.
- Don't tell him that first.
- I mean...
- Wait. Just be quiet.
- In January...
- Be quiet.
I was told that I should be extra
careful in January and stay safe.
And I was informed that
it'd get better on February 4.
- When did she get hers read?
- Doesn't she go to church?
- Will I have a good year?
- Well, first, So Min,
you're a gem who was born in spring.
You have a strong energy of gold.
(She likes it.)
She's liking it.
You are sentimental
and get easily inspired,
but you fantasize too much.
(But you fantasize too much.)
(Showing off her fantasies)
- Fantasize?
- My gosh, that's spot on.
- He's precise.
- He's spot on.
How can he be so precise?
Whether it's people
or inanimate objects,
you easily obsess over them.
- That's true.
- She does obsess over them.
So in 2020,
the Year of the Metal Rat,
you will have a good fortune
for the spouse.
You may meet your other half.
- Gosh, So Min.
- In 2020?
- Your dream will come true.
- My gosh.
- Really?
- Yes.
So your lucky charm will help you.
That's your fortune.
- Someone will help her.
- A lucky charm will help her.
Sung Jun. My gosh, my bad.
- Don't be casual with anyone.
- Hey. What was that?
- Don't be rude to Mr. Park.
Gosh. I'm sorry.
- What's wrong with you?
- It slipped.
- Mr. Park.
- So Min.
That's one of the wishes she has.
She's so happy. She's just excited.
- She's happy.
- When? What month will I meet him?
First, after February 4,
your fortune will get better.
Can't I find out
which age group he's in?
First of all, let's look at
your fortune for your spouse.
You have no ties with younger guys
or guys around the same age.
You have ties with older men.
- He's disappointed.
- Se Chan.
He's the same age as me.
- She won't have ties with Se Chan.
- Does it mean it won't work out?
- He's liking it.
- Hey, you.
I know you're disappointed.
Don't pretend that you're okay.
Among the members of your show,
- you're compatible with one member.
- Who is it?
(Which member is compatible
with So Min as her spouse?)
It's...
(Who is it?)
It's Se Chan.
- Really?
- But they are the same age.
- They are the same age.
- We're the same age.
You are the same age. However,
the compatibility of you two...
is like a taffy stick.
- What?
- Taffy stick?
(Their compatibility
is like a taffy stick.)
- Wait. It sounds like a curse word.
- Wait.
Isn't that a bad thing?
When something is like taffy,
it has a negative connotation.
- It means they stick like taffy.
- Does it mean they are that close?
It means once we stick,
we can't be separated.
It means that we can't be
separated afterward. Right?
Yes, you will stick together
like a taffy stick.
Once you develop a relationship,
it will not break.
- If you get married,
- Why are you standing up?
you can't get divorced.
We can't get divorced?
Right. I won't let you divorce me.
(He's trapped in her love.)
On top of that, as for Se Chan,
since you're cute and adorable,
he'll do things for you.
He'll be a devoted husband.
(He'll be a devoted husband.)
(Devoted Husband Se Chan)
In fact, Se Chan is
such a warmhearted guy.
Of course.
He is a devoted husband,
but his class is low.
(He is a devoted husband,
but his class is low.)
(This devoted husband
is of low class.)
That hurts.
- That hit me hard.
- That's true.
- This is fun whenever we do it.
He tries to do things for you,
but he's lacking and incompetent
by nature.
- He can't fully satisfy you.
- Right.
- He can't reach your expectations.
- He's incompetent.
- We recently had a barbecue,
and he kept putting cooked meat
on my plate.
So that was touching.
I like grilling meat.
You're flirting with her.
You're giving her signals, punk.
- Thank you.
- So Min.
That's good news.
Congratulations, So Min.
(So Min's New-Year Fortune:
She'll meet the love of her life.)
(Her compatibility with Se Chan
is sticky like the taffy stick.)
Next,
- it's Kwang Soo.
- It's time.
Kwang Soo had the best fortune
up to last year.
He had the best fortune.
(Kwang Soo had the best fortune.)
(This year, 2018,
is the brightest year for you.)
(You'll be lighting
your last flame.)
(He said it'd be his brightest
and final year.)
(I'm still young.)
This is your fortune for this year.
You have stepped
on the tiger's tail,
but you'll survive by running away.
(He will survive by running away.)
You'll survive by running away.
What? What does he mean?
- Goodness.
- What is this?
Thankfully, you won't die.
You'll cause trouble,
but you won't die from it.
I stepped on the tiger's tail?
- What a relief.
- What?
In fortune-telling,
there's an energy called
the White Tiger.
While walking through the mountain,
you'll meet a tiger,
throw up blood, and die.
I'll throw up blood and die?
(This is the meaning
of the White Tiger.)
(It's frightening.)
- That's the White Tiger.
- Okay.
But since you have some luck
to begin with,
- you'll be able...
- I won't throw up blood and die?
to run away and survive.
So it's a relief.
- What a relief.
- Seriously.
You'll survive.
You'll be blessed
with love and money.
It's highly likely that you'll meet
a nice woman.
But you lack dating skills.
(He has a fatal weakness.)
- Dating skills?
- You see,
- Who taught him those skills?
- he does lack those skills.
Who taught him?
- Who taught him?
- He lacks those skills.
(Kwang Soo's New-Year Fortune:
Steps on the tiger's tail but lives)
(Possibility for a relationship,
but lacks dating skills)
Next is Jong Kook.
- Me?
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
For the past 2 to 3 years, you were
blessed with love and money.
But for this year,
- you'll be receiving less of them.
- Really?
It's best for you to be
more conservative and stable.
- Really?
- More conservative than now?
- More?
- Even more than right now?
If he becomes
even more conservative,
- He's already conservative enough.
- it'll be terrible.
Your best colors for this year...
are pink and red.
(How is pink his best color?)
Hey, that's your best color.
- It's pink.
- Apink!
(Jong Kook's New-Year Fortune:
He'll be blessed...)
(with less love and money.
His best color is pink.)
If you invest in someone
or something...
or lend money to someone,
you won't be able to get it back
9 times out of 10.
- Goodness.
- It's you.
- Hey.
- You're the chosen one.
Will I be blessed
with a marriage partner?
Of course, you do since I do.
For this year,
you'll be blessed with neither
money nor women.
(He'll have neither.)
He'll have nothing.
(Se Chan's New-Year Fortune:
He shouldn't invest.)
I'm doomed this year.
You'll be blessed with love.
- That's good news.
- You'll be able to find a man...
or gain honor.
As long as he doesn't have
too strong of an energy,
- you'll be fine.
- I see.
- That means it's not Jong Kook.
- He's disqualified.
- No.
- Jong Kook can be...
a devoted husband.
- Right.
- That's true.
- Suk Jin is a devoted husband too.
- Right.
So it Jae Suk.
Se Chan lacks in some ways,
but he's also devoted.
Sir.
- You need to be more precise.
- Sir.
- What you said was hurtful.
- Is it my brain or my face?
- Which one is it?
- Is it his face?
- This is driving me crazy.
- In various ways.
- In various ways?
He lacks all around.
(Ji Hyo's New-Year Fortune:
Blessed with love and honor)
(She should avoid
those with strong energies.)
You were born
in the Year of the Rat.
- You're right.
- You were.
You strongly prefer stability.
- I agree.
- He is like that.
- He never invests in anything.
- If you're unsure about something,
- you won't make a move.
- You're right.
- That's accurate.
You won't get along well with
Suk Jin who enjoys taking risks.
I offered him several suggestions,
but he never took any of them.
Ever since we got
to know each other,
he's been offering me
countless suggestions.
But I've never accepted any of them.
- That's why you're still friends.
- Precisely.
- That's why.
- Not even once.
If we work on something together,
we will fall apart.
I've never accepted
any of his offers.
This is your fortune for this year.
Last year, you've been quite busy,
so you need to take care
of your health.
You may have many expenses.
Have your eyes open.
You should work out with me.
(Jong Kook will help him
stay healthy.)
Since the southside is warmer,
it's better for you.
- The south?
- Yes.
Your best colors are red and pink.
- Red and pink?
- Yes.
You two are the same.
- We should wear matching clothes.
- You and Jong Kook are the same.
His best color is pink too.
I looked at your compatibility
with the other members.
My compatibility?
You have bad compatibility
with those born...
- in the Year of the Sheep.
- Who is it?
- It's me.
- Haha was born then.
Why?
Those born in the Year of the Sheep
and Rat have bad energy.
- I see.
- What?
There are various kinds of sheep.
- Hey, shut it.
- Come on.
(I'm a good sheep.)
- Okay.
- Give me one more chance.
- I understand.
- But there's more.
You and Haha aren't compatible
in every other way as well.
(Gasping)
(Is this an irony of fate?)
You should go on
your separate ways now.
That's funny.
- You are compatible with those...
- Do tell me.
born in the Year of the Cow.
- It's Kwang Soo.
- It's him.
Jae Suk.
- It's you.
- When you two meet,
you can bond with each other well.
(Of course)
- I give him dating advice.
- That's right.
- We bond so well.
- You become sentimental.
- That's right.
That's what happens.
I told you
I'm your best dating coach.
- He's been doing it for a decade.
- That's right.
But no matter how good
the advice is,
your innate lack of dating skills...
Okay.
- I got it.
- See?
Did you get that?
- He lacks dating skills.
- I only give you good advice.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
(Jae Suk's New-Year Fortune:
The south and pink are best.)
(Worst compatibility with Haha,
best compatibility with Kwang Soo)
Your new-year fortunes
have all been read.
We'll say goodbye to Sung Jun...
- and begin our race.
- Thank you.
I have something for Jae Suk.
- What is that?
- Let me give this to you.
What is that?
(His legs are asleep.)
- Sir.
- Are your legs okay?
- Are you okay?
- Hurry up.
(Actually, the same thing happened
last year as well.)
(Trembling)
(You should work out your legs
more often this year.)
- Sir.
- You should work out.
- Climb Mount Gwanak.
- I will.
- That's for you.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Goodness.
- Is that a mission card?
He seems to be in a lot of pain.
This must be the mission card.
Since you were born
in the Year of the Rat,
it must be related to you.
(They're curious.)
Hold on a minute.
(He walks away from the members.)
What?
(What could it be?)
- What is it?
- Let me see the briefcase.
- That didn't last long.
- I need the briefcase.
- Hold on.
- This is...
- Is he trying to run away?
- What is it?
- What did it say?
- Gosh.
He read it so quickly.
- Hold on.
- What was it about?
Let me see this as well.
The staff has his coat.
He must be running away.
Really? Let me see.
Seriously?
The staff has his coat.
He must be running away.
(He grabs onto the briefcase.)
(He runs away.)
- Shouldn't we catch him?
- Why do you want me to run?
Why?
(He runs away
and leaves the staff behind.)
Is this it?
Why are you suddenly telling me
to run away?
- Let him leave for now.
- What is going on?
- Why did he run away?
- He has good energy,
- so we should let him go.
- Is he leaving just like that?
Today's new-year race is called
The Rat with the Money.
Since Jae Suk was born
in the Year of the Rat,
he ran away with the briefcase
holding 1,000 dollars.
(The briefcase holds 1,000 dollars.)
(What was written on the scroll?)
(Run away with the briefcase
full of money right now.)
(Briefcase full of money)
The briefcase you have
has 1,000 dollars.
(There is 1,000 dollars
in the briefcase.)
You're the first owner
of the briefcase.
The briefcase's password has
6 digits with the last one being 0.
Through the missions, you'll be able
to obtain the numbers one by one.
Once one of you opens it
and obtains the money,
the race will end.
The other members can take
the briefcase...
from you by stealing it...
or by ripping your name tag off
while the briefcase is hidden.
However, if you rip the name tag
of a member who doesn't have it,
you'll get a five-minute time out.
A five-minute time out?
Among you, there are four snakes
who are eyeing the briefcase.
- 4 snakes?
(There are 4 snakes among them.)
(4 snakes versus
4 Running Man members)
- There are 4 among the 8 of you.
- 4?
If Jae Suk was here,
he would've done this.
He would've.
Nobody knows just yet.
We'll tell you later.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Jae Suk wasn't here,
- so I did it.
- They grabbed me by my collar.
The snakes won't know
who their fellow snakes are.
If one of the snakes ends up
opening the briefcase, they win.
If it's a Running Man member,
Running Man wins.
The one who opens it
can divide the money...
among their team members.
(The one who opens it
can choose how much to share.)
Now, you should go
to your designated places,
find out your identities,
and receive your mission maps.
- Okay.
- Got it.
Let's go catch the rat.
- We should catch that rat.
- Let's go.
Let's go and catch our Mickey Mouse.
- Let's catch the rat
We'll find out our identities here.
(They each get into their cars.)
- Here is your mission map.
- Okay.
You can pick wherever
you want to go.
- Wherever I want?
- Yes.
We need to pick the location?
I need to go to one of these places.
I need to pick one.
There is a total of six places.
Each mission has a limit
to how many can participate.
If you win, you'll be given
one number from the password.
Even if you succeed,
if the majority of the participants
are snakes,
the number won't be given.
What?
No way.
However,
even if you succeed in the mission,
if the majority of you are snakes,
you will not receive
a number in the passcode.
Instead, you will receive
a hint about the snakes.
About who they are?
So it's important to do the missions
without the snakes.
That's right, or don't let
be the majority.
- This is insane.
- You won't receive the number.
Let me tell you
which role you're playing.
Sure. That's most important.
You are...
(A snake or a Running Man?)
- You are a Running Man.
- All right!
(Se Chan is a Running Man.)
Snake or rat or whatever.
I'll rip them all apart
and teach them a lesson.
- Suk Jin, you are...
- Yes?
A snake.
A snake? What am I
supposed to do then?
I didn't fully listen earlier.
(What am I supposed to do then?)
(Him not knowing the rules
is worrisome.)
Jong Kook, you are a Running Man.
So I'm not a snake. Got it.
(Jong Kook receives a phone call.)
Hold on. It's Jae Suk.
(Hold on. It's Jae Suk.)
(Jae Suk's calling
when he's on the run?)
- Jae Suk?
- It's me, Jong Kook.
Yes, I'm here.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
We need to complete missions...
- in order to know the passcode.
- Exactly.
So...
come over here to me
without telling anyone.
Where?
The spot for mission number two.
(Completing the mission
will give them the first digit.)
The spot for mission number two?
- That's right.
- I see you believe in our fate.
- Of course.
- I know.
It's why I'm calling you
and Kwang Soo over.
Okay, I'll be there.
- See you soon.
- Sure.
(The call ends.)
Why did Jae Suk
call me over though?
What if I rip off his name tag?
I can't tell if Jae Suk is
a snake or not.
He currently has the money,
so I should head over there.
(Jong Kook heads to the spot
for mission number 2.)
Since we're doing this...
No one would admit to being a snake.
So Min is calling.
- My sweet taffy.
- My sticky partner.
My taffy, what's your role today?
A Running Man, of course.
(Se Chan asks about her identity.)
(So Min is a Running Man
just like I am?)
What do you say to you and me...
trying a mission for two?
(How about we
try a mission for two?)
Will you put your trust in me,
Ms. Running Man?
(Why don't we test
our sticky relationship?)
(Se Chan suddenly
sends her a proposal.)
Let's head
to mission number one then.
(Sure thing.)
Are you good with it?
Okay, I'll meet you there right now.
I'm heading to mission number one.
(If they succeed, they'll find out
where the case of money is.)
But I want to know
the passcode more.
Take me
to mission number five instead.
(She changes her mind.)
- Mission number 5.
- 5?
(Will the sticky partners
go their separate ways in 2020?)
I'll head right away
to mission number two.
- Sure, meet me here.
- Got it.
- Must we all gather first?
- Yes.
This is a mission for three,
so I called you and Jong Kook.
Gosh, this place
wasn't easy to locate.
- Jong Kook, hurry.
- Got it.
- We must succeed in this mission.
- Of course.
This mission will reveal
the first digit of the passcode.
The game is called
Catch with Your Forehead.
(Mission 2:
Catch with Your Forehead)
There are three different items
in these boxes.
You must stand before
an acrylic wall...
and catch the object
with your forehead.
At least two of you must succeed.
- At least two of us?
- Yes.
If you wish for another try,
you should eat a lemon slice first.
A lemon slice?
(To try the mission again
with the same members...)
(We had better get it done
in one try.)
Please choose your box.
I'll go first.
(Jae Suk chooses a box.)
- It's an easy one.
- It's a ddakji!
(It's a ddakji!)
- This is a done deal.
- We'll surely do this.
- Just two of us need to succeed.
- Got it.
(At least two of them
must catch it with their forehead.)
- Okay.
- Good.
Please kneel down first.
- Ready...
- Hold on.
(Once Jae Suk kneels down,)
(Kwang Soo gazes
at Jae Suk's name tag.)
(Glancing)
Just so you know,
when you knelt down,
Kwang Soo looked at your name tag.
- Seriously?
- It wasn't like that.
(A tattletale)
(So that you can
steal my case of money?)
I was only glancing.
What other reason do I have?
Ready, get set...
Jae Suk can do this.
(The ddakji drops.)
(Will he be able to...)
(catch the ddakji
with his forehead?)
(Did he catch it?)
(Groaning)
Go!
- Hold on.
- You failed.
What happened?
- Shall I go next?
- By the looks of it,
Jae Suk didn't want to succeed.
- I did.
- What's wrong with you?
- I didn't know how to do it.
- Ready...
(Jong Kook is next.)
(Will he be able to catch the ddakji
with the muscles in his forehead?)
- Gosh.
- What?
(He touched his forehead
for a split second.)
What was that?
Didn't my forehead touch the wall?
- It touched by then I lifted it.
- You did.
I lifted it off the wall. Why?
- Why did you do that?
- Because you're a snake.
I'm not!
(Because you're a snake.)
- You didn't want to get caught.
- That's not it. Let's try again.
- Again?
- We can do it.
(To try again,
they must eat a lemon slice.)
The one with the money
should eat it.
Darn it. Okay, I will.
Why did I lift my forehead?
(Glancing)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Jae Suk.
- Come on.
You have the money...
and this all began
because you ran off with it.
(A ripping sound)
I'll eat the lemon slice.
This all began
because you ran off with it.
(A ripping sound)
- We've only just begun, you know.
- Unbelievable.
- He's too exhausting.
- We've only just begun.
(He eats a lemon slice
worth 1,000 dollars.)
Good job, Jae Suk.
(A ripping sound)
(Jae Suk has
the case of money again.)
You did a great job.
That was good.
- I'll choose the same box.
- Sure.
It'll probably be the ddakji again.
What's this?
- A card?
- This will be too difficult.
Ready, get set...
(The card
is too difficult to catch.)
- I almost had it.
- You almost did.
I shouldn't look elsewhere.
No, looking at it makes it easier.
- I told you to look at it.
- I guess you're right.
- Darn.
- Choosing the right object is key.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo, eat the lemon.)
What?
Just eat the lemon, Kwang Soo.
You're the designated lemon-eater.
It should be the one with the money.
I'll eat it.
(That was unexpected.)
(Too sour!)
- It's really sour.
- It makes your teeth ache.
It's the sourest lemon I've had.
(After sucking in a mouthful)
Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk, just a little bit more.
- Are you all right?
- Darn.
- You're almost done.
Gosh, it's sour.
(After a struggling last bite...)
(A ripping sound)
(His name tag gets ripped off.)
(Kwang Soo gets his revenge.)
(Another ripping sound)
(Are you done with your lemon?)
(Are you done
ripping off his name tag?)
You guys are exhausting.
The case of money
belongs to Jong Kook now.
- Right.
- Darn it.
Kwang Soo, you choose this time.
We should've ended this
with the ddakji.
- It's quite heavy.
- Nice.
- It's a mini chocolate cake.
- That's good.
Nice one.
Let's do this.
- 2 out of 3 is all we need.
- Kwang Soo, you're up.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
Just get it over with.
Ready, get set...
We were too cautious before.
(The mini chocolate pie drops.)
(Will Kwang Soo be able
to catch it with his forehead?)
Okay!
(He caught it!)
Nice. You did it.
- That was great.
- My gosh.
- Okay!
- I'll go next.
Only one more of you
needs to catch it.
You've got this.
- Okay.
- You were a beast just now.
Ready, get set...
(Will Jae Suk be able to catch it?)
(He bangs his forehead
and then his nose.)
- Okay!
- Nice.
(He caught it with his forehead.)
- You did it.
- Are we good?
I did it.
Nice!
(If there aren't
more than two snakes,)
(they'll receive
the first digit of the passcode.)
You successfully
completed the mission.
If more than two of you are snakes,
you will not receive
the passcode digit.
- More than two of us?
- Right.
- This will tell us who we are.
- Exactly.
Among the three of you,
the number of snakes...
(Jong Kook is a Running Man.)
(If both of them are snakes,
no hints will be given.)
(How many of them are snakes?)
There are less than two.
(The number of snakes
is less than two.)
That's why you will receive
the passcode digit.
(Either they're both Running Men
or only one is a snake.)
One of you is a snake.
(Jong Kook's radar is at work.)
It really isn't me.
I'm not a snake.
See how close Kwang Soo is to me?
- What are you talking about?
- You see it too, right?
The first digit of the passcode...
- is eight.
- Eight?
- Eight? Let's write it down.
(The passcode
that has been revealed so far.)
I will give the case of money
to Jong Kook.
- But...
- To me?
That really hasn't
been my goal today.
It's probably safer
in your hands anyway.
- Right.
- Right?
- Who would steal it from you?
- Exactly.
- All right then.
- Let's head out.
- We'll go and do another mission.
- Sure thing.
Let's go.
(The three of them
head to another mission spot.)
(The location for mission number 1)
(Se Chan is there all alone.)
(He suggested to So Min
that they try the mission for 2.)
(Sure!)
(She changed her mind.)
(He waits for his sticky partner not
knowing that she has betrayed him.)
What if no one shows up?
(Can he see the future?)
(When will So Min be here?)
Wait. She's here.
Of course, she should be here.
She's here.
(Did So Min change her mind again?)
Hey, Cobra!
(Hey, Cobra!)
Unbelievable.
Did she just call me a cobra?
Where's Se Chan? Is he here?
- He looks...
- Yes, like a snake.
- A snake.
- That's what he looks like.
- Hold on.
- Look, it's Suk Jin.
- There they are. Hi!
- Suk Jin!
Greetings, partner.
- Hi, guys.
- Welcome, my new partner.
- You know...
- Are you a snake?
Neither Team Snake
nor Team Running Man...
is the villain today.
- Do we need 4 people?
- We need 4 people.
- Let's wait a bit.
- Let's wait.
- Let's have some bread too.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Let's wait inside.
- Let's go inside.
- Jae Suk is calling me.
- Tell him to come.
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is calling me.
- Tell him to come.
- Jae Suk, we need one more person.
- Where are you?
I'm at number five, the bakery.
Listen, come to the spot for mission
number four by yourself right now.
Mission four?
All right. Where is it?
(He tells So Min to come
to mission number 4 on speaker.)
(Everyone hears it.)
There are many snakes over there.
Come here by yourself.
We're three people here right now.
We need one more person
to carry out the mission.
They're one person short.
They're three people right now.
Then I'll go to mission number five.
You should hurry up.
- We need to get the passcode.
- Right.
I'll go find out the passcode.
Okay, I'll come
to mission number five.
- Okay.
- All right, see you.
- He's coming here.
- He seems to be with someone else.
He told someone
he'd find out the passcode.
It must be someone he can trust.
Ji Hyo, we need
to complete the mission...
- and get the case of money.
- Let's do that.
(To find out where the money is,
they have to complete the mission.)
What's this?
It looks pretty easy.
- Please have a seat.
- Okay.
This mission is for two people.
By completing this mission,
you can find out...
either who has the money
or where the money is.
It's called Extreme Times Tables.
"Extreme Times Tables"?
We'll ask you
multiplication questions,
and you'll take turns answering.
But you have to answer
the tens place correctly...
and the ones place incorrectly.
After both of you have answered,
you have to say the sum
of the two numbers...
within three seconds.
I'm sorry, but I think
I'll go to another place.
Me too.
This is too hard. We're supposed
to say the tens place correctly?
Yes, say only
the tens place correctly.
This is driving me crazy.
- We'll give it a try anyway.
- Let's give it a try.
All right.
- Memorize your times tables
What's 3 times 4?
It's 17.
(Success)
- Memorize your times tables
What's 5 times 3?
It's 21.
(Fail)
(5 times 3 equals 15.)
- You failed.
- What did you do?
I thought 5 times 3 equals 20.
- What's "5 times 3 equals 15"?
- 5 times 3 equals 15.
Right, 5 times 3 equals 15.
What was she even asking?
What a stupid question!
What's "5 times 3 equals 15"?
Yes, 5 times 3 equals 15.
The last round was a mistake.
- Give us another chance.
- What's "5 times 3 equals 15"?
If you're ready, let's start.
- Memorize your times tables
- What's 4 times 7?
- It's 35.
You failed.
- It's 38.
- You failed.
It's 63.
- It's 67.
- You failed.
- Memorize your times tables
What's 8 times 7?
It's 53.
- What's 7 times 9?
- It's 62.
(Success)
3, 2, 1.
(They need to say the sum, 115,
to complete the mission.)
- It's 118.
- It's 108.
- You failed.
- What's the correct answer?
- It's 115.
Gosh.
(They're disappointed
in their brains.)
(Here's your 5th lemon.)
Ji Hyo, I think...
either of us should leave.
- We need someone else.
- Right.
- Right?
- We need someone good at math.
This is...
Someone is calling me.
- Hi, Kwang Soo.
- Where are you?
I'm with Rattlesnake right now.
Let's meet up.
Let's meet up at a mission spot.
The others are together right now.
They're about to carry out
a four-person mission.
We'll go to the other four-person
mission spot. Where are you?
Where should we meet? Which number?
- Mission number 5?
- Let's go to mission number 5.
Okay.
Let's go.
- Let's go. We'll be four people.
- Unbelievable.
(They didn't complete their mission
and leave for a 4-person mission.)
(The members divide into 2 groups
and carry out 4-person missions.)
I'm hungry.
- Let's have some bread.
- I almost ate this.
- Do you have any money?
Red bean paste and butter buns
are tasty.
We have no money.
We can't eat anything.
The staff will pay for it.
- We have no money.
- They'll pay for it.
Are you stealing it?
- No. I have money.
- No.
Let's get this too.
- We should have this one.
- Let's get two of these.
- So Min, I'm on my way there.
- Are you on your way?
Please hurry up.
The snakes are eating bread.
- What?
- The snakes are eating bread.
What?
The snakes are eating bread?
All right.
(The hungry snakes
are gobbling up the bread.)
She said the snakes
are eating bread.
(The snakes must love food.)
Jae Suk is here.
I heard the snakes ate bread.
If you complete this mission,
you can find out the 4th digit...
and have lunch.
It's called Blind Michelin.
(Mission 5: Blind Michelin)
There are 13 ingredients
including bibimbap ingredients.
Without seeing the ingredients,
one member will decide...
how many teaspoons, spoons,
or ladles...
of each ingredient will be used.
You can pass up
to three ingredients.
If the four of you manage
to finish the dish, you succeed.
You'll get another chance
if you eat a lemon.
For example, you say, "5 teaspoons
of ingredient number 1"...
or "1 ladle of ingredient number 8."
- This is not good.
- We won't be able to enjoy it.
Please pick one person
to play the game.
I'll do it.
You can do this!
- Bring in the ingredients.
- Please.
(The ingredients are
shocking and horrifying.)
Gosh.
Are those bibimbap ingredients?
(There are both tasty
and scary ingredients.)
Gosh, that skate smells so strong.
There are ingredients
we absolutely don't want.
- Gosh.
- What is that?
You don't want
three ladles of anything.
Okay?
He probably can't hear me.
I can.
- You can?
- I just ignored you.
(What Suk Jin said was too obvious,
so Jae Suk ignored him.)
(How will their bibimbap turn out?)
Let's get started.
- This is bad.
- Let's go, Jae Suk!
- Ingredient number one.
- Ladles!
Ingredient number one.
(It's rice, one of the basic
bibimbap ingredients.)
- Ingredient number one.
- Ladles!
(We want a lot of it!)
- Ingredient number one.
- Ladles!
- Please.
- Two spoons.
(That's too little.)
This is driving me crazy.
(It's too little
compared to the size of the dish.)
(Calm)
- With some sauce...
- Ingredient number two.
- Pass.
- Pass!
For ingredient number two,
I'll use a teaspoon.
Good. Put just one teaspoon.
(Salt)
- Three teaspoons.
- Gosh.
(We're doomed.)
- It'll be too salty.
Two spoons of rice...
and three teaspoons of salt?
(A generous amount of sodium
is added.)
Ingredient number three.
- Ladles!
Put all of it.
One ladle.
All right, that's not too bad.
It'd balance out the saltiness.
That's good.
- One spoon.
- That's good.
That's good. We need it.
We need it.
- Two spoons.
- Perfect.
Two spoons of rice
and two spoons of gochujang?
- How will it taste?
- All right.
Ingredient number seven.
(Next up, ingredient number 7...)
(is wasabi.)
This is important.
Ingredient number seven.
Put a lot. Put ladles of it.
Wait, no.
- What's ingredient number seven?
- Is that what you want?
(So far, their bibimbap
is still edible...)
(as long as they avoid wasabi.)
(Will Jae Suk manage
to avoid wasabi?)
Two spoons.
(Generous)
- What?
Gosh, we're doomed.
We can't eat it.
- There's too little rice.
- It'll be too salty.
Ingredient number eight.
Fried eggs.
- Put a lot.
- Put ladles of it.
(Fried eggs might be able to
save their food.)
- Pass!
- Gosh!
(They explode their anger.)
Seriously.
Hey!
(Jae Suk hears their complaints
over the music.)
Seriously.
Hey!
That was the one thing
I'd been waiting for.
We can pass
up to three times, right?
Ingredient number nine.
- Choose between numbers 9 and 10.
- There are tasty ones, right?
(He has to choose
between skate soup...)
(and beef and radish soup.)
(What will Jae Suk choose?)
I choose ingredient number 10.
- Good.
- Okay.
(Beef and radish soup is
a safer choice than skate soup.)
(Beef and radish soup)
We still have some hope.
Choose between numbers 11 and 12.
(It's either stir-fried pork
or stir-fried grasshoppers.)
(What will Jae Suk choose?)
I choose ingredient number 11.
- Good!
It's not bad.
Ingredient number 11, okay.
Pass! You can pass up
some ingredients.
(What's the last ingredient?)
(Chocolate syrup?)
Pass ingredient number 13!
- Pass!
- Ingredient number 13.
(What will Jae Suk choose?)
- I'll use a spoon.
- Gosh.
(This is a disaster.)
Three spoons.
(As many as 3 spoons)
(They're about to eat
chocolate bibimbap.)
(You eat all of it.)
I'm out of here.
Is it over?
- We're in trouble.
- This is pretty bad.
We have only two spoons of rice.
- Only 2 spoons of rice.
- Only 2 spoons of rice...
and three spoons of wasabi.
There's salt too.
But it looks all right, at least.
- Let me see.
- It's assembled in a nice way.
We have stir-fried pork too.
- But...
- There's chocolate syrup too.
Should we add the stir-fried pork
to the bibimbap?
- Yes.
- Let's do that.
- Let's make it less salty.
- Just a little bit.
- Let's pour in some soup too.
- Just a tiny bit.
- It's very tasty.
- Put a lot of it.
Let's put some of this too.
Let's try it.
It looks pretty okay.
Doesn't it look all right?
It looks like Jeonju bibimbap.
- Is it okay?
- What do you think?
(So Min plucks up her courage
and tries it.)
- Is it okay?
- Is it salty?
The sesame oil balances it out.
(It's better than they thought.)
Does it taste good?
- The sesame oil saved it.
- It tastes good.
Gosh, it's too salty.
It's too salty. We can't finish it.
(The wasabi finally hits.)
(Intense)
(Their first try fails.)
We can never finish it.
Trust me this once.
- Okay.
- Try it.
We need to eat a lemon.
- I will add a bit at a time.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Scissors, paper, scissors, paper)
(Jae Suk and Haha lose.)
- For goodness' sake.
- Eat a lemon.
Rock-paper-scissors
- I can't believe it.
- Will you eat it?
What Sung Jun said was correct.
- Seriously.
- The two of you...
Jae Suk took my penalty.
What he said was correct.
I guess you like lemons.
What he said about that jerk
was correct.
(Getting angry
over the fortune told earlier)
Seriously.
Eat a lemon.
The 4-person mission
for the 3rd digit of the passcode...
is Add One More Syllable.
(The 5th mission:
Add 1 More Syllable)
Add One More Syllable.
Listen to a syllable
from the production crew...
and say a word that starts
with that syllable in succession.
The words must have
2, 3, 4, and 5 syllables in Korean.
For example, I could give you...
- "Ga".
Yes. Say the words
to the beat like this.
Purse, stingray,
steamed stingray, and so on.
You add a syllable each time.
- We say the words in order.
- That's right.
Five-syllable word?
Is there a five-syllable word?
- Yes.
- I am sure they found it.
That's right. Dasan Call Center.
- Like this.
- Yes, that's acceptable.
You are good.
If you aren't a snake,
give a five-syllable word.
We should switch positions.
- Why?
- Three-syllable words are easier.
Three-syllable words are easier.
I am not looking down on you.
- I just want us to succeed.
- I will give a three-syllable word.
- I will sit here.
- Two-syllable word.
- Give a two-syllable word.
- Okay.
- Let's begin.
- Let's go.
- Get ready, go.
- 1, 2, 3, 4
The first syllable is "Ga."
- Ghana.
- Ganada.
(Ganada?)
(They fail
at the three-syllable word.)
- Hold on.
- It's like the Korean alphabet.
Ga, na, da, ra, ma...
I thought they would accept it.
Ga, na, da, ra, ma, ba, sa?
"Stingray" was the example
they gave us earlier.
- I wanted to take it easy.
- Ji Hyo.
Would you switch seats with him?
Are you looking down on me or her?
- I am looking down on you.
- Me?
Say a two-syllable word.
I can say a three-syllable word.
I thought "Ganada" would work...
- if I insisted.
- Okay.
Let's try again.
Since you failed,
eat a slice of lemon.
Whoever messes up should eat it.
- It's the logical solution.
- He got it wrong.
(The member who said "Ganada"
eats a slice of lemon.)
(He will get
a year's worth of vitamin C today.)
I hate it.
Go.
- Ga, na, 3, 4
- 1, 2, 3, 4
The first syllable is "Mi."
Mi...
(Incorrect)
How can she fail to give
a two-syllable word? She is a snake.
- I couldn't think of one.
- Eat a slice of lemon.
Okay. I will do that.
It's obvious.
(Is she a snake?)
I couldn't think of one.
I think you are a Running Man.
Of course, I am.
I am a Running Man.
Se Chan is a Running Man.
You and Ji Hyo are snakes.
My goodness.
I am sorry. I wanted to remove
the booger in your eye.
Are you okay?
I forgot I had lemon juice
on my hand. I am sorry.
Okay. I found out
how you feel about me.
I forgot.
There was lemon juice on my hand.
(Ji Hyo finishes eating a lemon.)
- She is good at eating lemons.
- She is tough.
Which four-syllable word
would you have given?
I have one. Art academy.
- How about you?
- Seaweed soup with rice.
We could have ended the game.
We can add "with rice."
- That's right.
- We can add "with rice."
- Okay.
- Adding "Academy" works too.
I can give a four-character idiom.
- You don't know any of them.
- Just you watch.
- You make me laugh.
- You don't know any of them.
- Just you watch.
Okay. Let's go again.
- 1, 2, 3, 4
The first syllable is "Ah."
Dad.
Father.
Mister's place.
Arirang Pass.
- Mister's place.
- Arirang Pass.
- "Mister's place" is ridiculous.
- Seriously.
You little snake!
- "Mister's place" is ridiculous.
- I couldn't think...
of a four-syllable word.
There is a four-character idiom
that means "Pandemonium."
- There are so many words.
- Don't you know it?
- There are so many options.
- This is pandemonium.
Okay.
You know,
I made a mistake with "Mi."
- I am sorry.
- Give a two-syllable word.
(There is pandemonium in his mouth.)
My goodness.
Let's resume right away.
All right. Kwang Soo,
four-syllable words are easy.
- Seriously.
- That's right.
(Is he removing an eye booger?)
That's right.
Stop it!
Oh, the lemon! I am sorry!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
(Please don't try this at home.)
- Are you okay?
- You know,
- Everything is brighter.
- Right?
I am sorry.
- I didn't have an eye booger.
- No.
- Your eyes looked dull.
- Okay.
(I need to wake up now!)
- Let's go.
- Let's begin.
- 1, 2, 3, 4
The first syllable is "Na."
Country.
Butterfly hairpin.
Nai... Naijinman.
(Incorrect)
Jong Kook, I...
Please switch seats with me. Sorry.
How could you fail to give
a four-syllable word?
I am certain you are a snake.
- I can't think one.
- I will bet my fortune.
How many percent of it?
I will bet all of it.
You made it.
- You can stop working now.
- I, Lee Kwang Soo...
- I finally made it.
I finally made it.
(Kwang Soo becomes rich
thanks to a mission.)
Mom and Dad, I will be a filial son.
- Let's resume right away.
- Let's begin.
The first syllable is "Do."
(The first syllable is "Do.")
- City.
- "City".
(Ji Hyo misses "Do"
even though it is relatively easy.)
Hold on.
- "City".
- Let's go. They are snakes.
- Jong Kook.
- Let's go.
Even if we succeed,
we won't get the passcode.
- There is a hint.
- We won't get it.
I want to know for certain
if the two of them are snakes.
We know for certain.
It makes no sense to mess up
a two-syllable word.
(Are Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo snakes?)
Use all three chances
to pass up an ingredient.
- That's right.
- Yes.
That's the only way we can eat
tasty bibimbap.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Shall I choose
ingredient number one?
(Ingredient number 1 is
the fiery chicken sauce.)
(Please don't do that.)
(Pondering)
Pass!
(He passes up
the fiery chicken sauce.)
Ingredient number two. Hold on.
(There are bean sprouts
and shredded white radish.)
Ladles!
Ladles! Two ladles!
- Okay.
- Two ladles.
- Did I do it right?
- This is good.
- Ingredient number three.
(Fried eggs
add flavors to bibimbap.)
(Everyone stands up.)
- Five spoons!
- Okay!
That's good.
(Haha screams out his picks,
but something is suspicious.)
- All right.
- Stand up...
Stand up if it's good.
Remain seated if it's bad.
If something needs to be passed up,
run around.
(Jae Suk ran around
for the fiery chicken sauce.)
(He saw it
from the side of his eye.)
(Everyone stood up for fried eggs.)
(Brazen)
(He pretended to guess
with intuition.)
(It will be delicious.)
That's good.
Now, standing up is prohibited.
- What?
- My legs hurt.
- Okay, okay.
(He doesn't know
that they got caught.)
Now...
(It's time
for ingredient number 5, wasabi.)
- Now...
- Ingredient number five.
(He must pass it up.)
Now, standing up is prohibited.
(If they remain seated, Haha is
bound to have a few spoonfuls.)
(Wasabi)
(What do I do?)
(With her body,
she tells him to pass it up.)
My goodness.
(Do I pass it up?)
- Be careful.
- Why did you trip me?
Pass!
(She sacrificed her knees
and got a pass.)
My knees hurt.
- Be careful.
- My goodness.
She is in pain.
Be careful. Get up.
Be careful.
That hurt.
Ingredient number seven.
(It's time for chocolate syrup.)
(Everyone is remaining seated.)
(Chocolate syrup could be worse
than wasabi.)
(At that moment...)
- I need to go to the restroom!
- Pass!
(Is she going to the restroom
so suddenly?)
Good job.
So Min, are you going
to the restroom?
- She was in a hurry.
- My goodness.
Okay, okay. That was great.
All right.
(They manage to save bibimbap
from chocolate syrup.)
All right.
Choose between number 9
and number 10.
Number 10?
(Jae Suk throws a water bottle.)
Give him some water.
- I choose number nine.
- Okay.
Number 12?
- One teaspoon.
- Okay.
- That was incredible.
- We can eat this bibimbap.
(They finished making
the Jeonju bibimbap.)
- That was incredible.
- All right.
That was incredible.
- That was incredible.
- It looks delicious.
It's proper bibimbap.
Seriously.
It looks amazing.
(They enjoy the dish shamelessly.)
- Is it good?
- It is.
It's good.
(The easiest mission is
to finish one bowl.)
Gochujang.
Let's add this too.
This is actually good.
Mission accomplished.
As I have told you,
even if you accomplish a mission,
if a majority of you are snakes,
- you don't get the passcode.
- Correct.
Among you, there is...
(If Suk Jin is the only snake,
the passcode will be revealed.)
(If there are more snakes,
the passcode won't be revealed.)
a majority...
(If there are more snakes,
the passcode won't be revealed.)
of snakes,
so the passcode won't be provided.
- This is insane.
- There are two?
- You, you, and you.
- It's not me.
However,
I'll tell you
how many of you are snakes.
How many?
Among you, there are...
- I think it's 2.
- It must be 2 because it's not me.
- I swear it's not me.
- Among you,
- there are...
- I'm a Running Man.
Is it three by any chance?
- three snakes.
- See? It's everybody but me.
Is it three by any chance?
(All but one are snakes.)
- It's everybody but me.
- You're a snake.
- You tricked me.
Are you a snake?
He's a snake.
- You were a snake.
- You can't deny it.
Snake, snake, and snake.
I'm a Running Man.
I'm the only one
who knows the truth.
- I saw the mission.
- This is unbelievable.
I'm the only one who knows this.
They're all snakes.
I'm the only one who knows this
because I'm the real Running Man.
- I'm the only one who knows this.
- Everybody but me is a snake.
- I'm certain.
There are only filthy snakes here.
- What did you say?
- Filthy snakes?
(What did you say?)
Filthy snakes?
- You filthy thing.
- Hey!
I was being easy on you.
If you get angry, you're a snake.
- I'm not angry.
- If you get angry, you're a snake.
I'm not a snake.
(Haha lost his temper...)
(because he is a snake.)
(When he found out he's a snake,
he went for the 4-person mission.)
Snake So Min, Snake Jae Suk,
and Snake Haha.
- What?
- I'm certain.
I'm not sure about you,
so come with me.
- What? Me?
- Yes.
Regardless of who's a snake,
we need to find out the passcode.
There's no point of talking about
who could be a snake.
- Come with me, Mr. Snake.
- Okay, let's go.
- I think...
- You were a snake.
- Jae Suk...
- Everybody but me is a snake.
It's the briefcase!
- Don't get close.
- No, don't get me wrong.
Look. Listen to this.
Out of Haha, Suk Jin, Jae Suk,
and me, there are three snakes.
Three snakes, but I'm human.
- What?
- I'm human.
Hey, stay back.
- Are you a snake?
- Se Chan.
Three were snakes.
- 3 out of 4?
- I told you.
- That's what I was saying.
- There are no snakes among us.
There are no snakes.
- What happened to you guys?
- There was only one.
There was only one.
(From the four of them,)
(Jong Kook and Se Chan are
both a Running Man.)
(Either Ji Hyo or Kwang Soo is
a snake.)
- I'm human.
- It's either you or her.
- Is it you?
- I'm human.
I'm not.
I don't think it's you either.
(Jae Suk wants to know
what So Min's identity is.)
So I'm going to find out
what she is.
- I'm human.
- Come with us.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
I'll find out for sure.
(They go to a different mission.)
Give it to me.
- Oh, dear.
- I'll keep it for now.
(Jae Suk takes the briefcase
from Kwang Soo.)
It feels better
not to carry the suitcase.
Why?
Stand next to me.
(What? Why did she rip
his name tag?)
- There's no point in doing that.
- It was just for practice.
If you eliminate someone
without the briefcase,
you get a five-minute time out.
It's a rule.
- What?
- Come this way.
I explained the rules to you.
- Was I not supposed to do that?
- You're not, but I'll let it go.
- Why did you do that for?
- This is your fault.
- It's a rule.
You have to pause for five minutes.
- I didn't know.
- That was unnecessary.
I didn't know. I had no idea.
What was that for?
We're wasting time.
We're standing
in the middle of the road.
You should have avoided me.
What are we doing?
- We can't play without him.
- I mean...
(They unnecessarily stop
for 5 minutes.)
This is driving me nuts.
- We can't play without him.
- What am I doing all day?
(5 minutes pass.)
(She's sorry.)
Five minutes have passed.
You can start moving.
- From now on,
- Don't do that.
- stop doing weird things.
- I'm sorry.
- My gosh.
- You need to have...
a general understanding
of the rules.
It took us so long to get here.
- What's this?
- We're here.
What's this?
- What's this?
- Candies?
(Why are there candies?)
This 3-person mission for
the 2nd digit of the passcode is...
Candy in My Mouth.
- Candy in My Mouth?
- The person playing...
has to roll a candy on the table...
and get it in the mouth
of the person across from them.
If more than two of you succeed,
you win the mission.
- I'll start.
- Go over there.
You can't move your face
once you get in position.
- Open wide.
- You look like a snake.
(He scored in one shot.)
- This is how you do it.
- That's too bad.
(This is how you do it.
You must say "start.")
(You should have told us
in the first place.)
Starting.
(Jae Suk to Kwang Soo)
(Rolling)
Oh, gosh.
- I couldn't finish it.
- Should we?
Starting.
(He tries it for real.)
(It goes in.)
Okay!
We win if I succeed.
- This one is new.
- Go ahead.
(Kwang Soo to Jae Suk)
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk!)
Your teeth alignment is too...
- Why does that matter?
- You have to go lower.
Your front teeth are like a door
that's blocking your mouth.
Right? His teeth are blocking it.
You can't cross the line.
(He rolls the candy toward
Jae Suk's impregnable teeth.)
(Touch)
(It touches his hand and goes out.)
(He failed to cheat with his hand.)
- You try it.
- Me?
(If So Min succeeds,
they win the mission.)
Jae Suk's mouth is smaller
than you think.
- Roll it slowly.
- Starting.
Don't roll it too fast.
(She ignores...)
(Kwang Soo's advice.)
(It flies like a bullet,)
(goes in,)
(then bounces back.)
- It went in.
- It almost did.
- It went in, then came out.
- It went in.
- My tooth broke.
- Jae Suk.
I heard it.
That was three cushion.
(A masse shot is banned here.)
It bounced three times.
If I had dental implants,
I would have lost them.
Fail. If you want to go again,
eat a lemon.
Gosh, lemon.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's pick a person.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Me?
Hurry up.
Hurry.
It's vitamin C.
Eat.
Chew.
Let's go again.
I'll go first.
You first?
It's okay.
I can eat it, but you're not even
paying attention to me.
(He's fine with eating it.)
(They're unconcerned.)
- Starting.
- "Starting"?
(We'll see about this, So Min.)
How do I get it in there?
(Fail)
This is difficult.
His mouth is difficult.
Let's use your mouth.
Your teeth are closing the entrance.
(They switch to So Min's mouth.)
She has a big mouth.
Good.
- Okay.
- I'll do both.
Can I succeed twice?
- You can.
- Starting.
(He'll roll and get two candies in.)
Okay.
(It's like she sucked it in.)
(If he gets it in Kwang Soo's mouth,
they with the mission.)
Starting.
(Can Jae Suk give them the win?)
Okay.
(Goal)
(It attacked his molar.)
(This is a valuable win
that costed his molar.)
Okay! We did it.
(It's the three-cushion billiards
master's 2 shots, 2 kills.)
- The mission was a success.
- Okay.
This is the important part.
If you are less than
the majority of snakes,
I'll provide you with the passcode.
I'll give you the second digit.
Among you,
I care about what Kwang Soo is.
- there are...
- It's less.
(If Kwang Soo is a snake,
they don't get the password.)
- less than the majority of snakes,
- See?
- so you get the passcode.
- Are you human?
- I am.
- I told you I am.
(Snakes are less than the majority,)
(so Kwang Soo's identity is...)
(Running Man.)
(I would feel better
if I was a snake.)
(Nobody trusts him.)
(Then Ji Hyo's identity is...)
(a snake.)
(Did Jae Suk just meet
a fellow Running Man?)
Kwang Soo, I'm human. He's a snake.
We're human, human, and snake.
(So Min is saying
she's a Running Man.)
You know that I'm human, right?
- Yes, you're human.
- You are.
- I'm human too.
- I'm certain about you.
- I'm certain.
- Because earlier...
You're human.
I'm not sure yet.
- Kwang Soo, I'm human.
- Hey.
- Come this way.
- Passcode.
- The second digit is...
Second digit.
- 3.
- 3?
- Okay.
- Three.
What was it?
- The first one?
- We can't share.
- I'm not sure.
- I'm human.
(He goes to the back.)
I'm human.
What are you doing?
(He crawls low
and secures his target.)
Why did he steal it?
- He didn't rip my name tag.
- He can still steal it.
(He runs away.)
Jae Suk might be a snake.
If Jong Kook is human,
Jae Suk could be a snake.
(Who out of Jae Suk and So Min
is a snake?)
(So Min, who's likely a snake,
tries to call somebody.)
Bye, snake.
Snake.
(They keep insisting
the other person is a snake.)
- Yes.
- Kwang Soo, I'm human.
With Se Chan...
I'm human. I'm serious.
I didn't even stop you.
It's better to have a human take it.
You know, right?
Let's go for mission number six.
- How many people?
- Five.
- Because...
- Let's go there first.
Tell Se Chan to come too.
Let me call Suk Jin.
(He hides the briefcase
before he goes inside.)
(He enters the mission location.)
Where is the briefcase?
Don't tell people that I have it.
- Where is it?
- I hid it.
Where did you hide it?
If humans win,
do they share the money?
- That's right.
- Kwang Soo.
I will believe in you.
- You are human.
- The winner distributes money.
- I am human. If you are human...
- Promise you will share money.
- Of course.
- What will be the ratio?
- 5 to 5.
- Okay.
- 5 to 5?
- 5 to 5.
- I will hide it here.
- Where are you going?
(Glancing over)
(Kwang Soo brings the briefcase.)
(She takes off the name tag
from Kwang Soo's jacket.)
Is it mine now?
- Give it to me. Give it to me.
- What?
(Ta-da)
Give it to me.
- Give it to me.
- I will take this to the end.
I will put this on.
I shouldn't have come here.
(He regrets his decision.)
Give it to me. Stop it.
(Grabbing)
Stop it.
(How could you take off the name tag
from my jacket?)
(This is the end of a deal breaker.)
Stop it.
My briefcase! My briefcase!
My briefcase.
(She tries to protect the briefcase
and name tag.)
Stop it.
My goodness.
Hold on.
You know...
Know that I am human.
I am human.
- I am human.
- Firstly...
Give it to me.
Give it to me. Give up.
If you stop, I will share the money.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Put it back on.
- Let's stop.
Okay. I will put it back on.
(They negotiate a ceasefire.)
(I take it back.)
(They rip off each other's name tag
endlessly.)
(Putting on and taking off)
Give up already.
Give up.
(So Min gives up first.)
I am exhausted. I am exhausted.
(The briefcase goes to Kwang Soo.)
- I am exhausted.
- I shouldn't have entered this pit.
- I can't stand her.
- Don't go.
- You are like a zombie.
- Get lost.
(The end of the war)
Hey.
You need to trust me.
I am human.
- Suk Jin.
- What is it?
- So Min is insane.
- What?
(He runs into Suk Jin,
Jong Kook, and Se Chan.)
Here comes Jae Suk.
We need to do a five-person mission.
- Come in.
So Min, why did you do that?
- Hey.
- Jong Kook.
This proves that I am human.
In that case,
the five of you should do
the mission.
- That's right.
- I think...
If you are human, it's likely
that Jae Suk is a snake.
- You are right.
- I am a snake.
Everyone knows that I am a snake.
Let's complete this mission.
The 5-person mission
for the 5th digit of the passcode...
- is 5 in 10.
- 5 in 10?
Complete 5 individual missions
in 10 seconds.
If everyone succeeds,
the mission is a success.
I can do this.
(They try the missions many times.)
(They succeed
the 1st 4 individual missions.)
Good job.
I succeeded so many times.
(With the upright water bottle,
the mission ends successfully.)
We did it.
Before we hear the passcode,
- he should leave.
- What?
This is information for us.
I played the game with you.
Let's see if the snakes are
a majority.
Are the snakes a majority?
- No.
- The snakes aren't a majority,
- I knew it.
so I will give you the number.
We got it.
The 5th digit of the passcode is...
- 2.
- 2. Okay.
(The 5th digit
of the passcode is 2.)
(Only two digits remain!)
Where is the briefcase?
(Kwang Soo goes
to pick up the briefcase.)
(However)
(I put it right here.)
Did someone rip off your name tag?
- For goodness' sake.
- What?
Someone stole it.
- Who took the briefcase?
- This is intense.
No one leaves.
(Everyone, stop.)
(They get locked in.)
No one leaves.
- Where is the briefcase?
- Who is it?
Who touched my briefcase?
I was going to rip off
your name tag.
- I don't know.
- I don't care who took it...
as long as a Running Man wins.
Me too. I don't care
as long as a human took it.
But...
Jae Suk went outside
when we played a game.
(So Min suspects Jae Suk.)
I went outside
since there were five people.
I see. Jae Suk went outside.
Think about it. I went outside
since there were five people.
- The briefcase was hidden.
- Where was it hidden?
When Jong Kook and So Min were here,
I hid it.
- I had no idea.
- There is no way Jae Suk knew.
Only Jae Suk had time.
He didn't play the game.
I didn't know
where the briefcase was.
Let's say we suspect Jae Suk
and remove his name tag.
If he has it,
will he bring the briefcase to us?
Yes, he will.
If Jae Suk has it,
he will bring the briefcase.
I don't have it.
- Rip off his name tag.
If he doesn't have it,
you must pause for five minutes.
- Only the person who ripped it off.
- That's right.
You could drink coffee here
for five minutes.
- Was someone here?
- I guess someone was here.
I should call people
who aren't here.
Why are you trying to leave?
(Don't even try.)
(Jong Kook blocks the door.)
- Suk Jin is a snake.
- It must be him.
- Let me make some calls.
- It's obvious...
- that he is a snake.
- He hid it somewhere.
- Where is it?
- Where did you put it?
- Shall I remove his name tag?
Rip off my name tag.
I really didn't hide it.
I will rip off Jae Suk's name tag.
You... Fine. Rip it off.
- That will tell us.
- If that proves my innocence...
If you are wrong,
you will have to pause.
- I will do that.
- Go ahead.
Go ahead. I really don't have it.
(Ripping off)
- Bring it to us.
- Okay.
Since Se Chan took off
Jae Suk's name tag,
- he must pause for five minutes.
- I told you it isn't him.
(Jae Suk doesn't have
the briefcase.)
- It isn't me.
- Someone else took it.
- Shall we go out?
- Suk Jin took it...
or Kwang Soo told a lie.
He is leaving with a smile. Get him.
I can move, right?
Rip off his name tag.
Kwang Soo, pause for five minutes.
- What?
- See? It isn't me.
- What is going on?
- Where is my briefcase?
- Hurry up and put it back on.
- Where did it go?
- I didn't take it.
I...
Kwang Soo's name tag got ripped off.
So Min, pause for five minutes.
- It isn't me. Who took it?
- Who took it?
Who took it?
- It isn't me.
- It isn't you?
Suk Jin, pause for five minutes.
- What?
- Rip off everyone's name tag.
The one who took it isn't here.
Jae Suk, pause for five minutes.
- It isn't me.
- It isn't you.
Haha...
- and Ji Hyo didn't come here.
- When did they come?
- What?
- Did they sneak in?
- What? Haha!
- What?
Haha and Ji Hyo...
- didn't come here.
- When did they come?
- What?
Haha!
(They spot Haha as he passes by.)
(Speak of the devil.)
- What?
- It's Haha.
What?
(He tries to figure out
what's going on.)
What? What?
(Jong Kook gets Haha.)
He ripped off Haha's name tag.
- All right, Jong Kook.
- What?
We will bring you the briefcase.
- Okay!
- When did you take it?
(Haha was the culprit.)
Hey, why did you...
What is this?
You should have done better.
I was just passing by.
- Why did you pass by?
- How...
This could have remained a mystery.
- He isn't a snake, but a rat!
- Why did you pass by?
I was passing by in a hurry.
You...
- We did it.
- When did you take it?
- We will bring you the briefcase.
- Okay.
Jong Kook.
- All right.
- Jong Kook,
- open it if you can.
- I will give it a try.
I can't believe it.
(Life is all about
the right timing.)
What? Okay.
(The briefcase gets delivered
to him.)
(Two numbers are missing
from the passcode.)
(He goes from 00 to 99.)
This is...
- Thank goodness.
- Five minutes are up.
- Thank goodness Jong Kook took it.
- He is trying to open it.
(He is solving the passcode.)
You know the order, right?
- Jong Kook.
- You just need two more numbers.
- We need to stop the snakes.
- Are you trying the numbers?
- Did you open it?
- No.
Hold on.
Did you open it?
- Hey, you...
- It's not like that.
- Hold on.
- We just want to check.
- Hey, what is this?
- You need to trust me.
- I am human.
- We need to complete the passcode.
We need to get the orders right.
- For goodness' sake.
- Go to the tree.
Hey, hey.
Human.
(A tall zombie chases after him.)
(Snakes and Running Man
are meaningless before money.)
Hey. Hold on.
- Let's split the money.
- 5 to 5.
- That's my term.
If you betray me, I will chase you
to the ends of the earth.
- It will be troublesome for you.
- Okay.
It's 5 to 5. Okay.
Let's try the numbers.
There must be one, right?
There must be one.
(When will I try all the numbers?)
Let's go this way.
- What is that?
- He is coming! Hurry up!
(What is that?)
(Jae Suk shows up with a ride.)
- Hey.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
He is coming.
I am human.
(I'm a Running Man.)
- Hey.
- So Min is a snake.
We need to get him.
- Kwang Soo.
All of us are human.
You know that, right?
(Pondering)
Kwang Soo.
He isn't human.
(Inching closer)
This is endless, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo!
(Blinded by money,)
(Kwang Soo attacks Jong Kook.)
(Aren't Jong Kook and Kwang Soo
both a Running Man?)
Rip it off, Se Chan.
- The briefcase.
- The briefcase!
(Jae Suk steals the briefcase.)
- No, the briefcase!
(Take the money and run.)
I give up.
This is where I stop.
Jae Suk is a snake!
- Why is he so greedy?
- He can share the money.
I give up.
Jae Suk.
Open one side.
- Kwang Soo.
- Open one side.
Okay. Stay there.
I will keep my promise.
Let's share the money.
This is driving me crazy.
So Min isn't human.
So Min is a snake.
I am serious.
(Both of us are a Running Man,
so let's divide the money in half.)
(Confused)
(At that moment, Suk Jin appears.)
Did you open one side?
- You are a snake, right?
- What?
He is a snake, right?
(What is he talking about?)
- I think he is a snake.
- He is human.
I think he is a snake.
What is going on?
Take it. Take it and go.
- Run away!
- Hold him.
- I am holding him. Run away!
Hurry up and run away!
- Run away!
- Catch Suk Jin!
- We have to catch Suk Jin!
Go and open it.
He's a snake. He was a snake!
Be quiet.
(Jae Suk's identity is a snake.)
(While everybody was busy
checking each other's identities,)
(Jae Suk stole the briefcase.)
(They didn't notice it was gone,
and they kept on playing.)
(Jae Suk leisurely walked away.)
Haha.
Take this. You have to hide it.
- Okay.
- Do you understand?
I took it,
so they'll only question me.
Okay.
(This is what confused everybody.)
He's a snake.
- He's a snake.
- Be quiet.
- So Min is a Running Man!
Quiet.
(Snake Suk Jin earns a chance
to take it all thanks to Jae Suk.)
(He tries numbers from 00 to 99
for the remaining 2 digits.)
- Where did they go?
- Where are they?
- Maybe they didn't open it yet.
- 8, 3, 2...
What's the passcode by the way?
Where did he go?
Where is he?
I can figure this out. 2, 0, 8, 3...
And one.
Have you seen Suk Jin?
- He went that way.
- Thank you.
One... This is taking too long.
(Where is he hiding?)
(At that moment,)
(he finds Suk Jin.)
Hey! This is taking too long.
(He's shocked.)
Hey!
Goodness.
(Kwang Soo ripped Suk Jin's
name tag off and takes the case.)
Se Chan!
- Throw it.
- Jong Kook!
Throw it!
Here. Go.
Jong Kook! Come here. Jump.
- Hurry.
- Come.
- Sit. Put your back on the bench.
- Unlock it.
8, 3, 2...
(They guess random numbers.)
What?
Tell them.
- It's open.
- Not here.
- Oh, gosh.
What's going on?
- Hold on. Hurry up.
- Stop them.
(Stop the other team!)
Okay.
(They open the briefcase with
passcode 8, 3, 6, 1, 2, 0.)
- Okay.
- We opened it.
- We can do it.
- Calm down, Kwang Soo.
- Wait.
- Kwang Soo!
We're on the same team.
We're all a Running Man!
- We're all a Running Man.
- They're snakes.
- Get rid of these snakes.
- Move.
- Catch the snakes. Open it.
- Move them.
- Open it.
- I will.
Open it. Open it first. 1, 2...
(The briefcase finally opens up.)
Hold on.
(Kwang Soo screams
after squeezing his hand in.)
- Hold on.
- Hey.
- Let go.
- I will.
- I let go.
- Let it go.
(He tries to seize it again.)
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
- The snakes are coming!
- I let go.
- My hand is stuck.
- What's going on?
(Grabbing)
(Did Haha take the prize money?)
What?
- My hand is stuck.
- What's going on?
(He steals it from Kwang Soo
at the last minute.)
What?
(Race is over.
Haha took it, so the snakes win.)
What happened?
Kwang Soo.
- This is amazing.
- You really are a snake.
The victory goes to the snakes.
Yes, snakes.
(It's a sneaky win by the snakes.)
We should have divided it
among ourselves.
Why were you attached to
a small sum of money?
- Leave.
- What?
Humans, leave.
You're sneakier than snakes.
(It's an unfortunate ending
for the sneaky humans.)
Anyhow, Haha's the one
who took the money at the end.
- Haha was a snake. Snakes win.
- That was insane.
He was a snake.
- We almost had it.
- Luck just follows me.
- Kwang Soo.
- If you weren't greedy.
What's wrong with you?
I thought you were human.
You were a snake.
You're human,
but why do you live like a snake?
- Loach.
- I don't even know.
- You live like a snake.
- I don't know why.
- Haha won the money,
- How should I do this?
so please distribute it...
with the rest of your team
in any way you want.
It's the new year,
so you have to be nice.
I'm going to do well
for five years anyway.
- Yes.
- Right.
- Thank you!
- Here you go.
- Good work.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Let's try our best.
- I'll try my best!
- All right.
I wish you a long life.
You have a lot to achieve.
(He wishes Suk Jin a long life.)
- 250 dollars.
- Thank you!
I'll buy some tonic.
(I'll take care of my health!)
- What did he say?
- He's a disloyal subject.
- Tonic.
- Yes, you have to be healthy.
- Be happy!
- Thank you!
This side now.
- Take this.
- Oh, dear.
Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Us?
- Take it. I feel like it.
- Is this extra money?
- Producers.
- What's going on?
- Why are you being nice?
- Why are you doing this?
I'm going to do well for five years.
Writers,
you should go for a team dinner.
- What's this?
- We all have to give it up.
We all have to do it.
Put it together.
You should have a team dinner.
Team dinner!
My gosh.
Chan Hee, you should get some tonic.
(He reluctantly gives it up
to the only person who's older.)
(Thank you, Suk Jin.)
- This is great.
- This is funny.
- This is warm.
(This is a fake laugh.)
Chan Hee, eat some eels.
I'm happy
we are ending on a cheerful note.
- This is a heartwarming ending.
- It's warm.
We didn't intend it.
The Year of the Metal Rat has come.
- Viewers, happy new year!
- Happy new year!
(To all viewers who love
Running Man, happy new year.)
(The thieves are here!)
(Our target?)
(Tear of Yondu!)
(The legendary safecracker and
the cold-blooded hacker break in.)
(Rookie thief Park Ha Na
and a petty thief who dresses up)
(They only get 3 hours
in the ultra-luxury mansion.)
(There are 9 thieves,
but only one piece of jewelry.)
(There are traps lurking
inside the mansion to lure them.)
(However)
(Are there mysterious eyes
on the thieves?)
(They're being watched through
hidden lenses.)
(They hold their breaths.)
(They must hide from surveillance
and steal the Tear of Yondu.)
- It worked.
- Stop lying.
(The Thieves: Tear of Yondu)