Hello.
- Hello.
- What is this?
- Are we going on stage?
Today, we're having
the Devil's Whisper Race.
We will have four captains with
their distinctive styles of acting,
- and they are waiting backstage.
- Captains?
- Do we have captains?
There are four captains.
You will be sitting on your chairs
turning your backs on them.
Each captain will take turns
on stage to make their appeal.
If you're curious about the captain,
you can press the button...
to turn your chair
and greet the captain.
This is like "Voice of Korea."
Right. It's like "Voice of Korea."
You have only two chances
to turn your chair each.
- Two chances.
- Twice.
The captain who makes
most members turn around...
will get to pick two members first.
Please bring in the chairs.
Just so you know, the button
doesn't turn your chair around.
You should turn it yourself.
- We know that.
- So it's not automatic.
It's manual.
Please pretend it's automatic.
I'll make it look automatic.
- It doesn't require energy.
- This is nice.
I know. This is new.
It's very unique.
- Let's begin then.
- Okay.
Please bring in our first guest.
- Don't look.
- I won't look.
I'm not going to look.
Who could it be?
I'm really curious. I really am.
(Busan Stone)
- What? It's a guy.
- It's a man.
- Hi.
- What?
Hello.
I'm Pengsoo.
- That's not Pengsoo.
- This is Maenggoo.
He sounds more like Maenggoo.
- He's not Pengsoo.
- Isn't it Maenggoo?
He's Maenggoo, not Pengsoo.
Hello. I'm...
Busan Stone.
- Stone?
- Please pick me.
He's a terrible speaker.
He sounds old. A stone?
- He has a nice voice though.
- I guess...
he's a singer.
- A cheerleader?
- Music, please.
I guess he's singing.
- Is he singing?
- He's singing.
If he's a singer,
we will recognize him immediately.
(The intro begins.)
(He has a low and deep voice.)
- What?
- Seriously?
- Is he singing live?
- Who is he?
- Gosh, he's good.
- He sounds good.
- I'm pushing it. I want to turn.
- I'm really curious.
- I want to turn around.
(He picked "Stone Block"
from the drama, "Itaewon Class.")
I think he's a singer.
He has a great voice.
I didn't like his speech...
Gosh, So Min.
(So Min is the first one
to push the button.)
(Who is the first guest?)
(Busan Stone)
What was that, So Min?
(Excited)
Who is it?
(So Min greets him with applause.
Who on earth is he?)
I don't regret my choice.
Hang on. This is...
(Fatal charms, strong presence)
(He's Actor Ahn Bo Hyun
with his class.)
(He shows off his vocal skills
that's just as good as his acting.)
I don't regret my choice.
- He's good.
- I think I know this voice.
I know. He sings well.
(Please turn around.)
(Should they turn around or not?
That's the problem.)
Wait. This song is...
(Shocked)
(He steps back in shock.)
Why?
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- I'm so curious.
- Who is it?
- I'm curious.
- Kwang Soo.
- I want to push the button.
(He sings passionately
to make everyone turn around.)
It's not too late! Kwang Soo.
I want to push the button.
(Should I push it or not?)
I have to see him.
- "Itaewon Class".
- What? "Itaewon Class".
(Speechless)
I can't wait to see him.
(Hesitant)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(3 of them pushed the button,
and 5 of them didn't.)
(Saeroyi from Dongducheon is
excited to see the real class.)
(Making a bow)
- This is crazy.
- It really is.
I have a question.
I'd like to ask the man on stage.
On a scale of 1 to 10, how many
points would you give me?
- Why would he score you?
- What is he doing?
- Why would he give you marks?
- He's...
- What's that?
- Me.
He'd give zero points
because of your speech.
On a scale of 1 to 10,
what would it be?
I think highly of you,
so I'll give you seven points.
I was wondering...
Have you recently been in a drama?
Yes. I was in a drama
only a week ago.
- What?
- Only one week?
Hang on. Only one week?
I know what it is.
There's this drama.
It's "Itaewon Class."
- "Itaewon Class"?
- I guess that's him.
Is he Lee Seo Jun?
(Is he Lee Seo Jun
from "Itaewon Class"?)
(Suk Jin is really something
as he's heard.)
- He's Park Seo Jun.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- You're unbelievable.
- Who's Lee Seo Jun?
I'll give him zero points.
He got zero points.
(Right at the moment...)
(The countdown
to the closing starts.)
(They have only 2 chances
to turn around.)
Who is it? Is there someone else?
Time's up for the first guest.
- Really?
- I was going to turn around.
He sounds attractive.
I was about to pick him.
Now please bring in
our second guest.
I'll turn around this time.
I'll turn around
if it doesn't sound bad.
I'm really curious.
Hello.
It's a woman.
I'm Seocho-gu Golden Hand.
- Golden Hand?
- Yes.
(She's Ji Eui Soo who showed
her impressive acting...)
(as Jessica in the drama,
"When the Camellia Blooms.")
(She's a model and actress who will
bloom like a camellia.)
I'm Seocho-gu Golden Hand.
- Golden Hand?
- Yes.
- Does she live in Seocho-gu?
- Seocho-gu?
- She lives in Gangnam.
- Golden Hand?
Why is she Golden Hand?
I do need a golden hand.
(Silent)
- Aren't you going to sing?
- Aren't you doing anything?
- Are you performing?
- I'm doing it now.
We're getting ready
to show her talent.
They are bringing
some cooking utensils.
I guess she's preparing something.
That's why she's Golden Hand.
- Because she's a good cook.
- She cooks well.
Are you hungry?
- Yes.
I'll cook for you guys.
Are you going to cook?
I've never seen someone who cooks
to show their talents.
Is she Big Mama, Lee Hye Jung?
I've never seen
anything like this before.
- She's using a knife.
- I'm curious.
- I wonder who she is.
- While she cooks,
I will show your caricatures
she drew at home.
- What?
- Did she draw us?
She's prepared a lot.
I guess she's skillful
with her hands.
What?
- My gosh.
- It's me.
- She's really good.
- Can I keep this painting?
- Sure.
- This is amazing.
Did she draw it herself?
That's so nice.
She's really good.
It's me.
- She's amazing.
- She didn't draw the mustache.
How did she know
I didn't have the mustache?
It doesn't have a mustache.
Show us the drawing of Jae Suk.
It looks the same.
Isn't it Se Chan?
That's not me.
It would've looked like me
with glasses on.
It's not Se Chan. It's me.
- I'm sure she majored in art.
- She is...
- an expert.
- She's very talented.
Have you ever met anyone of us
in person before?
- On a TV show?
- Yes.
- Or on a private occasion.
- It doesn't matter.
No, I've never met anyone of you.
Which one of us did you want
to meet the most?
I...
wanted to meet Suk Jin.
(He presses the button...)
(and turns around immediately.)
(Laughing)
(Shouting)
Suk Jin doesn't know who she is.
Suk Jin has no idea who she is.
He doesn't know who she is.
(A total stranger)
(He just pretends to be excited.)
He didn't even call her name.
What kind of reaction was that?
Suk Jin, don't do that.
What are you doing now?
I'm making pasta.
Guys. She's making pasta.
- And she peeled the tomatoes.
- Pasta?
She cooks well.
(Jae Suk turns around
tempted by the pasta.)
(I see.)
Jae Suk turned around.
(He keeps silent so other members
won't recognize her.)
Guys.
- Eui Soo.
- It smells good.
I didn't understand
why you'd cook here.
Let us taste the dish
so we can make our choice.
Please let us try it.
Let me see. I want to try it.
- I'm turning around.
- I want it too.
(He turns around
driven by the pasta.)
Gosh.
Hang on. Wait.
We've met before.
- When?
(We have never met before.)
Kwang Soo has a good memory.
(They appeared in the same drama.)
(Kwang Soo's right to be forgotten)
This is amazing.
(Jae Suk enjoys the pasta
in Haha's ear.)
Let me see.
I want to see it.
(Glancing)
She's really good.
This is driving me crazy.
(If they turn around now,
they can taste her pasta.)
(Finally...)
(Haha turns around
at the last moment.)
I'm not kidding.
It tastes really good.
- She cooks well.
- This is great.
This is crazy.
- It's like a restaurant dish.
- I don't regret my choice.
I'm serious.
It's the best spaghetti
I've ever had.
- Seriously.
- Is it that good?
We have two guests left.
- Here's our third guest.
- I can't turn around anymore?
- No, you can't.
- I'm so curious though.
Did you turn around twice?
- Let's see.
- I just couldn't hold it back.
He will go crazy.
Typical mischievous boys...
- can't hold it back.
- They can't.
Let's see.
(The third guest,
Songpa-dong Thumper)
(And a drum?)
(Who on earth is he?)
Hello.
- What? Wait.
- I like his voice.
Hang on.
I'm from Songpa-dong.
He sounds like Lee Byung Hun.
I'm Songpa-dong Thumper.
- He sounds familiar.
- I've heard of the voice.
(He's Song Jin Woo...)
(who performs in various shows
with his characterful acting.)
I think I know this voice.
(Is he showing his bare feet?)
What is he doing?
What? I heard some noise.
Is he a taffy seller?
Clap your hands.
(He asks them to clap their hands
with explosive sounds.)
(They start to clap.)
I'm sure it's him.
Who is he?
Is he playing the drums?
(Energetic)
(The drum sound makes
their hearts resonate.)
(Suk Jin is excited
to hear the drums.)
(He pretends to hesitate
with exaggerated gestures.)
(Pushing)
What?
What was that? Hey!
- I didn't mean it.
- You were hesitating.
You hesitated.
Why did you pretend to hesitate
when you didn't?
Okay.
I knew it. It's you.
I don't want to turn around.
(The energetic drum
performance is over.)
I'm not curious.
By the way...
I have a question.
Yes?
Gosh, your voice...
Are you an actor?
Yes, I'm an actor.
(She doesn't want
to press the button.)
(What?)
(She didn't plan to turn around.)
No. Gosh.
- Hello.
- Hello. Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
- I pushed the button for her.
- So Min's response...
- I pushed it.
- She doesn't look too happy.
- Jae Suk pressed mine.
It was my last chance.
It's nice to meet you.
- Likewise. How have you been?
- Have you been well?
- Show us your talents.
- All right.
I'll lip sync.
- Lip sync?
- Yes.
- How will we be able...
- to watch him?
- We can't see that.
- If you're curious, turn around.
- I see.
If you're curious, turn around.
Right. Give me the music!
(They're curious
but won't turn around.)
(Jong Kook enjoys the view.)
Oh, my.
- He's good.
- It's as if he's singing.
- It looks so realistic.
I'm so curious.
I can't take it.
(Haha and Ji Hyo turn around.)
(She likes what she's seeing.)
He's good.
(It's a Spanish song.)
- You're good.
- You're really good.
You're good.
(My passion and joy
are all for you, senorita.)
I like it.
- It's so fun.
- He's good.
That's it.
- And...
- Lastly,
I have one last talent.
I can stand on my toe joints.
- What?
- On your toe joints?
Really?
(Everyone is surprised
by this unexpected talent.)
You're talking about what
ballerinas do.
(He stands on his toe joints.)
Can you do this?
This is worth watching.
- That's amazing.
- I can't believe this.
- How is that possible?
- My gosh.
(He really wants to see.)
(He can't take it anymore.)
(Shouting)
How is that possible?
(Kwang Soo shouts in shock.)
You can do that? What is that?
He can do it.
- You need to watch this.
- Okay!
- Is he a freak or what?
- How can he do that?
Can you do this?
- That's unbelievable.
- Can you?
- You're running out of time!
- He's amazing.
Time is ticking!
Sadly, your time's up.
- So many of us turned.
- Thank you.
- He's so talented.
- There's one last contestant.
Only Se Chan and Jong Kook
can turn around.
Really? Then are our teams fixed?
- That means...
- Let's do this first.
Please come on out.
(Hipster from Mt. Nam)
(Clickety-clack)
They're wearing heels, right?
(Hipster from Mt. Nam
looks interesting.)
(She's full of charisma.)
- Hello.
- Oh, my.
She has a great voice.
I won't talk much.
I'll just show you
how much swag I have.
- Swag?
Drop the beat!
(She's the last contestant
who has enchanted the members.)
I need to turn around!
(Lee Joo Young showed
her charismatic side...)
(on "Itaewon Class.")
(She's a rising star who has said
many famous lines.)
- Drop the beat.
- I need to turn around!
- What is going on?
- I want to turn around.
- Can I not?
(She grooves to the rhythm.)
This is just my style.
Put your hands up,
put your hands up
(This is "Caution" by Tashannie.)
This song?
I love this song.
- What?
- Turn around!
Turn around!
(Shouting)
(He gets excited whenever someone
from "Itaewon Class" comes out.)
I'm so curious!
(Dancing)
(He dances to the beat.)
(It's a soulful performance.)
She's good. She really is.
- Put your hands up!
- She's good.
Put your hands up!
She's really good.
(It's like a singing contest.)
I'm glad I still have a chance.
(These two middle-aged men
dance along.)
(She tore up the stage.)
I really want to turn around.
- I'm so curious!
- I really want to.
Her voice...
and her appearance
contrast each other.
She's really good.
Isn't she, Jong Kook?
- I became nostalgic.
- Who is she?
Can you sing another song
by Yoon Mi Rae?
(The countdown begins.)
- I'm so disappointed.
- 3, 2, 1.
- You've run out of chances.
- You're right. Who was she?
I'm at a disadvantage here.
- Hello.
- You were so good.
- You were.
- "Itaewon Class".
- Goodness.
- They're from the drama.
They are.
She's Lee Joo Young.
You see...
I wanted to turn every single time.
- Me too.
We all felt that way.
I wanted to turn around
for the last stage.
- I know.
- I really did.
Your performance was outstanding.
But I had run out of chances.
Let's start with Ahn Bo Hyun.
He's very famous these days.
Jang Geun Won.
(He calls his character's name.)
You were a boxer.
- Right.
- They're rivals.
- I love the drama.
- They are?
- What do you mean?
(Jong Kook just boxes for fun.
Ahn Bo Hyun is experienced.)
He used to be a professional boxer.
- I respect that.
- He was a professional boxer?
(Suk Jin suddenly approaches him.)
(He throws a jab.)
- Suk Jin, what was that?
- Did you look at his jab?
(Imitating)
It was a childish punch.
You'll fly away even before
getting punched, old man.
How dare you call me that?
- Old man.
- What did you say?
You'll fly away.
- Right.
- Watch out.
- All right.
- He has a huge fist.
You've once talked...
about Jong Kook's boxing posture
in another variety show.
- He criticized him?
- It was on "Radio Star."
- Yes.
- Really?
- So...
they asked him
about Jong Kook's posture.
He said it didn't look professional.
(He was being honest.)
He's forcing a smile.
He is.
You said that, right?
- He's forcing a smile.
- Well...
- You said that, right?
- Yes.
It was in 2018.
They edited it incorrectly.
That's what they did.
I respect him greatly.
- I admire him a lot.
- You said things before that,
- but they edit it like that.
- Yes, they did.
- Right.
- Next up is...
Seocho-gu Golden Hand,
Ji Eui Soo.
- Did you really draw those?
- Yes.
I bet it took you some time.
I spent three days on them.
She worked on them
for three days.
That's amazing.
You said you never met any of us,
- but we've worked together before.
- Really?
Yes.
- We both filmed "Dear My Friends."
- What?
- I can't believe she forgot me.
How could she not remember you
at all?
- I mean...
- Eui Soo.
She didn't think about you.
Was that intentional or what?
She shouldn't be embarrassed
about knowing me, right?
- I know her.
- Right.
So why?
Maybe her agency
made an announcement.
About what?
- "Ignore Lee Kwang Soo."
- What do you mean?
- Why didn't she recognize you?
- We should be more understanding.
It could happen.
It says that you can
kick toilet paper.
What is this?
- Kick toilet paper?
- Oh, this?
- You can do this?
- It's not easy.
- Messi did it as well.
- Can you do that?
- I'm not that good.
- Let's see.
- I guess she can still do it.
- It's not easy.
She's so talented.
(She chose this
UEFA Champions League song.)
- She must be good.
- I...
I asked them to play this.
I chose this song.
(This is her first time
showing off this talent.)
(How good is she?)
- Goodness.
- What was that?
(What?)
(Why is a roll of tissue here?)
- Goodness.
- What was that?
- What is this?
- Hey.
- Did we have...
- to catch it?
- Was that it?
It looked like
she was throwing a bouquet.
- What is this?
- I thought you could do it.
You couldn't?
I did practice.
- Try it again.
- Turn the music on again.
I'll do my best.
- You should kick it at least twice.
- Right.
Go on.
(Bo Hyun looks even more nervous.)
(Screaming)
(Surprisingly, she does worse
than before.)
- What was that?
- Hold on.
- You kicked it once.
- Why did she scream?
- She screamed.
She did that before as well.
But if she said
this was her talent...
She should've kicked
at least 2 to 3 times.
All right. Thank you.
(Ji Hyo reaches out her hand.)
- Do you want to do it?
- Me?
- No.
- Why did you reach out?
- Try it.
- Me?
- Just do it.
- Try it.
- Please play the music.
She'll do it.
- She volunteered?
- Yes.
You look shocked.
She reached out like this.
She did?
She changed a lot.
- Yes, she takes initiative.
- I was surprised.
- She wanted to try this.
- She wanted it.
- Give it to her.
- Hand it to her.
- Try it.
- Do it. Turn on the music.
- Turn on the music.
Go on.
She changed so much.
Just kick it twice, and you've won.
(How good is she?)
(She kicks it twice.)
Ji Hyo, I want to thank you.
- Right.
- Really.
- Ji Hyo.
- You volunteered.
- Pick it up.
- I hate Suk Jin.
- Why?
- "Pick it up."
I was just joking around.
- Goodness.
- I was just joking around.
Next up is Hipster from Mt. Nam,
Lee Joo Young.
Ma Hyun I.
I was amazed by your performance.
I'm so disappointed
that I couldn't get to watch it.
- Not many people can sing that.
- They can't sing that song.
- She was good.
- She rapped so well.
It's not easy to sing
like the original singers.
It's not an easy song.
I heard you debuted nine years ago.
Seriously?
- I'm a bit hesitant to say that.
- Why?
I've worked on independent films
since 2012.
- Still.
- They still count.
- That was your debut.
You're well known in that field.
- Please be quiet.
- What?
- Quiet.
- She shared something with us.
I was talking about her.
But...
- But...
- I love it when he does that.
- I was complimenting her.
- I love it when he cuts him off.
I was waiting.
That's Jae Suk's role.
- I wanted to let the viewers know.
- Don't.
- All right.
- Just stay quiet.
Be quiet.
Next is Song Jin Woo.
- I love him.
- Hello.
- Oh, come on.
He debuted through a musical called
"Oh, my Captain."
- That was 13 years ago.
- Really?
I could tell from his voice.
- His diction is great.
- He has a good voice.
They were in different majors,
but he and Kwang Soo...
went to the same university.
- We went to school together.
- Right.
- We both enrolled in 2004.
- You joined in the same year?
- Yes.
How was Kwang Soo as a student?
Well, this is just
how I thought of him.
- Sure, don't feel any pressure.
- It's just how I thought...
because I didn't
know him personally.
I thought he was a scumbag.
(A scumbag?)
- I...
- You're right.
- I saw him from afar and...
- A scumbag.
I thought he was...
a scumbag too.
- You too?
- In our class...
I'd see Kwang Soo approach...
and call him a scumbag.
Back then, he had a bob.
- Really?
- Yes, he looked like a sleazeball.
Really?
- Seriously?
- He had a bob.
Well, you shaved your eyebrows
into a thin line.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You know the Japanese style.
- Really? Like the Japanese style?
I spat on the floor
whenever I passed him.
And I also sprayed salt.
He was that ominous.
But then we'd meet and...
- Hello.
- Goodness, hi.
- How have you been?
- But from afar?
But from afar?
- That scumbag.
- What a sleaze.
Unbelievable.
That's why he's a scumbag.
But I was happy to see him do well.
They're so funny.
They're happy to see
each other do well.
Shouldn't you be annoyed
of each other's success?
- I was really happy for him.
- Seriously? You're happy for him?
- I was happy for him.
- There's also...
another talent Jin Woo showed us.
Remember how Lee Byung Hun danced...
- during his fan meet-and-greet?
- That dance?
- Right.
- I remember that.
- Haven't you seen it?
- I haven't.
Can you show us once more?
I call it the healthy teeth dance,
but they're just some simple moves.
It's the smile that matters.
His grin...
and his eyes that shoot lasers.
(His grin
and his eyes that shoot lasers)
(The healthy teeth dance)
(The elegant Lee Byung Hun)
(The cheap copy)
(What on earth is that?)
His face stays the same.
He looks just like Lee Byung Hun.
(It's a 99.9 percent match.)
- Look at his eyes.
- His expression stays the same.
If you look at Byung Hun's video,
- you'll see that it's the same.
- Really?
We should see
the original video too.
If you see the original video,
you'll see that it's the same.
- Exactly.
- They're the same.
I haven't seen it before,
but I can imagine it.
- I can almost see it.
- You'll see that...
he looks exactly like Lee Byung Hun.
- Right.
- How about "Despacito"?
- Sorry?
- "Despacito".
- But...
- What's he talking about?
- Well,
- I lip-sync to it.
- Can you show us?
Cue music.
(The music plays.)
This song isn't easy to lip-sync to.
Look at him splitting the beat.
(My gosh.)
(Amid his puffing...)
(seeps out a deep Latin scent.)
(He even lip-syncs
to the electronic sounds.)
(100 percent lip-sync)
This is smothering though.
- It's actually kind of scary.
- Right.
(Sancho Song is back.)
I can't look him in the eye.
Now bring back Lee Byung Hun.
(Latin meets Lee Byung Hun.)
(His unrivaled stage presence)
What's this?
(He starts pointing
his fingers at them.)
What on earth is this?
That was amazing.
(His performance
captivated everyone.)
- Unbelievable.
- Please give it up for Jin Woo.
(And now everyone's
been introduced.)
I'd just like to inform you
that So Min...
hasn't been feeling well
for a few days.
- She's been having dizzy spells.
- So she...
- went to see a doctor nearby.
- All right.
We all hope that...
she gets well soon...
as we begin today's race.
Let's do this!
- Yes!
- Nice!
- So Min, get well soon!
- Get well soon.
- Let's do this.
- See you soon!
Go, So Min!
Don't you worry about today's race.
Today's race is called
the Devil's Whisper Race.
There are eight players in total.
5 are angels while 3 are devils.
Only you know
which role you're playing.
Don't we have two devils now?
- One just left.
- Exactly.
So Min will be included
in the race today...
- even though she's not present.
- Really? Okay.
- We'll have to be wise.
- After each round,
the winning team will receive hints
about the teammates' identities...
as well as a chance
to swap out teammates.
After the race is over,
if your team
only consists of angels,
that team will win a chance
to choose a prize.
If the team has
an angel and a devil,
only the devil will get
to choose a prize.
If the team has
more than two devils,
everyone in that team
will receive a penalty.
You'll now form your teams.
In Voice of Running Man,
Jin Woo came in 1st place
with 6 votes.
Eui Soo is in 2nd place,
Bo Hyun is in 3rd place,
while Joo Young is in fourth place.
In that order, you will
each choose two teammates.
Jin Woo, go ahead
and choose two teammates.
It's important to choose
as many angels as possible.
- I see.
- Jin Woo?
It's as if you're forcing him.
Should you be this forceful?
Jin Woo.
- My first pick is Jong Kook.
- All right!
Of course.
(What?)
- She's trying to appeal to him.
- I love your enthusiasm.
- It's hilarious.
- All right.
Look at Ji Hyo taking initiative.
- Ji Hyo!
- Come on!
Yes, Ji Hyo.
Which family of Song are you from?
It's a stage name.
(Embarrassed)
That was hilarious. Jin Woo asked
which family of Song she was from,
and she told him it's a stage name.
Her actual surname is Cheon.
- I see.
- Her surname is Cheon.
- Her real name is Cheon Sung Im.
- A stage name?
There's a high chance
that he's a devil though.
(The teams)
All right then.
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's go.
You'll now play for a chance...
to receive a hint and
to swap teammates.
This is Battle Royal: Rip or Tear.
- Rip or Tear?
- Tear?
Rip or Tear?
One from each team
will compete in each round,
and you will play
a total of three rounds.
The members from each team
will try to outsmart...
the others for one minute,
and then try to rip name tags off
for 20 seconds.
So Min's not here,
so it's just the two of us.
So one of you
will have to play twice.
You're quite smart, right?
Yang Saeroyi can compete twice.
- Unbelievable.
- Yang Saeroyi?
If by any chance...
Don't be like that.
You will compete until
there is only one member left.
Points will be given to you
depending on how you did.
The team with the highest points...
will receive hints
about all the teammates...
and get a chance to swap teammates.
The team in second place...
will only get the chance
to swap teammates.
- Okay, good.
- Let us reveal...
the quizzes first.
5-second Compliment Game,
4-syllable Game,
and Sing 1 Line.
Only one from each team
will stay in the ring now.
All right. Good luck.
In the Five-second Compliment Game,
you will target your opponent.
The one that's been targeted
must say...
three compliments
about the one who targeted them.
- Three compliments?
- This isn't easy.
This isn't easy at all.
The game will continue for a minute,
and you'll be out of the game
if you get it wrong.
- We'll be out?
- The ones...
that survive this game
will begin Name Tag Elimination...
at the sound of the bell.
- Oh, no.
- I can't believe...
that Joo Young has to compete
with veterans.
- What?
- Unbelievable.
- She doesn't know how it's done.
- I'm sure she'll do well.
- Joo Young.
- The captains...
are relatively new to these games,
so they each get an extra life.
- Nice one!
- All right.
- Good.
The four of you will now sit.
Ji Hyo, stay positive.
I rarely compliment others though.
You're out if you get it wrong.
Ready, get set...
Haha!
Great tone of voice,
good acting, and pretty.
Suk Jin!
You're short but brave,
honest, and great.
- What?
- Honest?
Is that supposed
to be a compliment?
How is being short a compliment?
- It's debatable.
- It's a compliment.
It shouldn't be vague.
- He's short but...
- Go ahead.
Ji Hyo!
You're old but sexy
and you have a big nose.
(You're old but sexy
and you have a big nose.)
(It's the best compliment ever.)
- Hold on.
- How is being old a compliment?
- Hey.
- Is that a compliment?
Well, it means he's experienced.
- Well...
- It's a compliment!
- Right.
- Being old...
- isn't a compliment.
- You may be old...
- but you're still sexy.
- That's a good one.
- Ji Hyo, good one.
- Okay.
Joo Young.
The necklace is pretty,
so is your cap, and also your eyes.
Nice one.
She's good at this game.
- Suk Jin.
- Is it possible...
to be this pretty,
adorable, and lovely?
But...
- Hold on.
- Joo Young liked it.
- This shouldn't be allowed.
- This isn't right.
- That way of talking...
- Why not?
- This shouldn't be allowed.
- Rip their name tags off.
- Rip them off!
(The bell rings to signal
the Name Tag Elimination.)
- Rip them off!
- Go!
(They suddenly go after each other.)
Get them!
- Hold on.
- Get him.
You won't survive this.
(They go after Suk Jin
who's an easy target.)
- You won't survive this.
- No, don't attack me together.
Don't let him rip it off.
(Haha has Suk Jin's name tag
in his hand.)
(Will he be eliminated?)
Go after him.
(Joo Young suddenly appears.)
Go after him!
(Haha barely gets to safety.)
Joo Young, go ahead.
Go after his name tag.
- Go for it.
- Hold on.
- Go after him.
- Watch your back!
Watch out for Joo Young.
(At that moment!)
(Ripped off)
Nice one.
- Suk Jin...
- Good job!
- Nice one.
- What good does defense do?
The old but sexy Suk Jin is out.
The old but sexy Suk Jin is out!
The old but sexy Suk Jin.
- My gosh.
- I'm sorry, guys.
- It's all right.
- He just apologized.
(He held up his hand
for a high-five.)
(His hand has no place to go.)
Suk Jin held up his hand for
a high-five, but they ignored him.
Eui Soo just turned around.
- That's not it.
- Joo Young...
knows how to play this game
better than I do.
Ji Hyo ripped your name tag off...
so why are you taking it out
on Joo Young?
It was chaotic up there.
Suk Jin's mind is a mess right now.
- He's out of it.
- He's still sexy though.
- We'll begin with Joo Young.
- Sure.
Okay, let's go.
Ji Hyo!
You're talented, adorable,
and you have pretty dimples.
Okay, good.
Haha.
You're old, a great actress,
and you live in a cave.
Are those compliments?
Of course.
She never compromises.
Ji Hyo.
You give birth well
and your beard...
Am I the one who gave birth?
(Am I the one who gave birth?)
(Technically speaking,
he's not the one who gave birth.)
- Gosh.
- Hold on.
- Giving birth...
- Babies...
- You're out.
- That's not a compliment.
- There's no doubt about it.
- You're out.
- It doesn't make sense.
- That's not a compliment.
- It should at least make sense.
- Exactly.
- Let's do this then.
- Here we go.
You parted your hair well,
you have a small head,
and you have
such nice, straight eyebrows.
You're a fashionista,
you're wearing nice socks,
and your shoes match them so well.
She's good at this game.
You have no gray hair, your
shoulders are just broad enough,
and you have long legs.
- Rip off the name tag!
- Rip off the name tag, Joo Young!
- Don't be scared.
- I'll rip off your name tag.
Joo Young, go for it.
- Go for it.
- Good.
Gosh.
Haha is pretending to be strong.
(Haha pretends to be strong.)
Don't worry!
(Joo Young bounces off the ropes...)
(and tries a knee kick.)
- Joo Young, good job!
- Come on!
Why are you so strong?
Go, Ma Hyun I!
Joo Young tried a knee kick.
- Joo Young!
- Rip it off!
- It's been a while.
(Haha hooks Joo Young's leg.)
- Joo Young, no!
- Joo Young!
Get out!
(Haha goes for
Joo Young's name tag.)
Rip it off! The other side!
The other side! There you go.
- Joo Young is incredible.
- No!
Let go!
Hey!
(Joo Young counterattacks.)
- Yes!
- Oh, no!
(Joo Young's unexpected
counterattack creates tension.)
Yes!
Hey!
(Haha's name tag is ripped off!)
(No one saw this coming.)
She's so strong!
Gosh.
- Unbelievable.
- My goodness.
I didn't go easy on her.
Joo Young.
- What are you talking about?
- You definitely didn't.
- We can see that you didn't.
- Joo Young is so good.
- Joo Young is amazing.
- My gosh.
- Not everyone can pull that off.
- She's really strong.
She just grabbed his name tag...
and ripped it off right away.
She's incredible.
Joo Young even did a knee kick.
Next!
The 2nd round is
the 4-syllable Game.
Let's go!
The Four-syllable Game?
- Is it Joo Young again?
- Jin Woo, warm up! Good!
(He performs a takedown
against himself.)
- Jin Woo.
- Jin Woo, what did you do?
- What did you do?
- I thought it'd work.
- Let's go!
Yes!
Here comes the King of Ad-libs.
The King of Four-syllable Words.
- Give me your bag.
- The King of Ad-libs.
- Let me show you what I got.
- Jae Suk.
- You're not funny.
- I'll show you.
- The King of Ad-libs.
- Haha.
You can do this!
You get to pick a player
in this game too.
The attacker will pick one person...
and say the first 2 syllables
of a 4-syllable word.
- Hannam.
- Bridge.
- There you go.
You need to stay calm.
Relax.
- TV.
- XQ.
That's right.
- Cheongju.
- Bridge.
"Cheongju Bridge"?
- It exists.
- "Cheongju Bridge"?
- It doesn't exist?
- Search for it.
- It exists.
What's the correct answer?
There's no one correct answer.
It just has to make sense.
- That's not how it works.
- Isn't that right?
- It doesn't work that way.
- You need a correct answer.
- You need to follow the rules.
- This is not okay.
- You need a correct answer.
- You're out.
The Cheongju Bridge exists.
- It exists.
- The Cheongju Bridge exists.
You're safe now.
- That's what I had in mind.
- It exists.
That's what I had in mind.
That's why I threw salt at him
back in college.
(Kwang Soo is reminded.)
- He's so mean.
- I had to.
- Okay.
- Eui Soo.
- Jukma.
- Gou.
Hyeongseol.
Ji...
What is it?
- Hey.
- It's "hyeongseoljigong".
- It's too difficult.
- Did you know it?
- It's "hyeongseoljigong".
(It means
"the fruits of studying hard".)
- It describes this situation.
- Be honest.
With your hand on your heart,
did you know it?
It describes this situation.
I guess Jin Woo is not so smart.
He doesn't know "hyeongseoljigong".
- Jin Woo.
- You have another chance.
- Hold on.
- This is not good.
Did you say "hyeongseoljigong"
describes this situation?
- Kwang Soo.
- "Hyeongseoljigong".
What does "hyeongseoljigong" mean?
- This complicated...
- Space.
- space.
- We learned it.
Se Chan, can you tell us...
It describes this kind of behavior.
- That's what it means.
- Not my behavior.
- It suits Jin Woo's behavior.
- It describes your behavior.
This situation itself is
"hyeongseoljigong".
That's hilarious.
Our members are so funny.
- You're our captain.
- All right.
- They're all so smart.
- Let's go!
How about this one?
- "Who do you think you are?"
- No.
That doesn't count.
He's not even trying to be fair.
Start.
You need to know many words
to play this game.
- Infinite.
- Challenge.
Jajak.
Siin.
- That works.
- That's okay.
You were thinking of
the "birch tree", right?
(That's right.)
If I can find "jajaksiin"
in the dictionary, you're safe.
- Let's see.
- Is it in the dictionary?
- What's with you?
- Is that even a word?
You guys understood
what it means, didn't you?
I know "jajaksi" means a "poem,"
but "jajaksiin" doesn't make sense.
- "Jajaksiin"...
- He's being weird.
- I thought Jin Woo was smart.
- Exactly.
You guys understood.
Cameramen, you understood it, right?
Haha and I understood it.
- We understood it.
- You understood it too?
I looked it up at the National
Institute of Korean Language.
"Jajaksi" exists,
but "jajaksiin" doesn't.
Then what do you call
the person who writes a jajaksi?
- Hey, you're out.
- Come here.
- Throw some salt at him.
- I'll go back.
- See you.
See you guys.
- Eui Soo, you can start.
- She's good.
- Eui Soo will go first.
Arma.
Geddon.
- That was hard.
- I didn't know that one.
- For a second...
Yubi.
Mueon.
- She said, "mueon".
- She said, "muhwan".
- What?
- What's wrong with it?
- She said, "muhwan".
- Muhwan.
- Eui Soo...
She said, "muhwan".
- Eui Soo.
- Didn't you say, "mueon"?
- I said, "muhwan".
- It's "yubimuhwan".
My pronunciation is bad.
- She said, "mueon".
- No.
"Yubimuhwan".
I knew it when she juggled
with the toilet paper.
- She's a liar.
- It's "yubimuhwan".
- She clearly said, "yubimuhwan".
- Let's just move on.
Nerve.
Cells.
Alone.
- In Love.
- There you go.
- In the Mood.
- For Love.
(The name-tag ripping starts.)
Hey, attack Jae Suk first.
Team up with Eui Soo.
That's a good idea.
- Eui Soo.
- Attack the man.
- Forget about manners.
- Okay.
You have to win.
- Should I attack them?
- Go for it!
Get them! Go!
Attack!
He'll get tired soon.
He'll trip.
(Joo Young attacks from behind.)
(Joo Young grabs
Jae Suk's name tag.)
(Joo Young is so good.)
- She grabbed it!
- She grabbed it.
- What?
You ripped it off?
Why did you tease them?
Way to go!
Joo Young seems tired.
- It's going to be fun.
- Joo Young used a lot of energy.
Eui Soo, use your long arms!
Joo Young, try...
(Joo Young tries a low kick.)
She tried a low kick.
- She tried a low kick?
- Eui Soo...
Joo Young tried a low kick.
- Way to go!
- Oh, no!
(Fierce)
- No! Get back up, Eui Soo!
- Hey, it's almost...
- It's almost ripped off.
- Joo Young is so good.
- No!
- They're both good.
She's so good.
- It's right in front of you. Wait!
- Oh, no!
It's right in front of you. Wait!
- Wait!
(A backward roll)
Wait!
- She did a backward roll.
- Joo Young!
Do you really have to do this?
- Wait.
- Nice!
Incredible.
Time's up.
It was like the UFC.
But we...
She did a backward roll.
It was the best
Name Tag Elimination.
- They both did an amazing job.
- Good job, Joo Young.
- Bo Hyun, go!
- You can do this!
- Let's go!
- Bo Hyun, go!
- Gosh.
All the cheaters are here.
You two are
the "hyeongseoljigong" guys.
- Yes, that's right.
- "Hyeongseoljigong"?
"Hyeongseoljigong".
In the third round,
we'll play Sing One Line.
I'll say the name of a singer,
and you'll each sing one line
from that singer's songs.
Okay!
It's no problem!
(The singer feels confident.)
But if you fail to sing
within five seconds...
or sing a song that's already been
sung by someone else, you fail.
We have to sing a new song.
- Here's the first singer.
- Okay.
(The first singer)
Buzz.
- 5, 4, 3...
- 5...
Is Jong Kook already out?
(What?)
- 4, 3...
- He's out! Yes!
- Yes!
(Jong Kook is eliminated.)
(Let's celebrate!)
(Jong Kook is eliminated!)
Oh, "Coward".
- Jong Kook!
- Hey.
- What did you do?
- "Coward".
I'm a fool
That's a huge relief.
- Hey, what did you do?
- I'm a fool
(The huge mountain crumbles away.)
I don't know many Buzz songs.
- Far away
- "Don't Know Men".
(They tease Jong Kook.)
(Glaring)
(Se Chan comes to senses.)
Gosh.
- Hey, what's with you?
- Your love
I don't know many Buzz songs.
(5 seconds in,
Jong Kook is eliminated.)
- That's a huge relief.
- What is this?
You just sat there
for a few seconds.
Girls' Generation.
Tell me your wish
Trouble...
- That's the same song.
(Se Chan is eliminated.)
(Kwang Soo and Bo Hyun
move on to the finals.)
This is hard.
Cool.
- You know how much...
- Keep it short.
- For you, only for you
- Good job.
(The name tag ripping starts.)
- Oh, my.
- You're injured, right?
- I'm fine.
- You're okay?
Just a second. It hurts!
(Kwang Soo starts exaggerating.)
(I knew Kwang Soo would do that.)
(Bo Hyun hesitates
to attack Kwang Soo.)
- Just give up!
- Kwang Soo!
(Bo Hyun starts
feeling competitive.)
What's the point...
(Bo Hyun's name tag is ripped off.)
Okay!
- What's the point...
- Okay!
- Kwang Soo was faster.
- He was faster.
- What happened?
Is this...
Kwang Soo is back!
- Didn't you rip his first?
- Kwang Soo!
It takes skill to rip off name tags.
Turbo or Kim Jong Kook.
Can't you see me
hiding behind your back?
Every winter, the two of us
- That's the same song.
We win!
(Kwang Soo is eliminated,
and Bo Hyun's team wins 1 point.)
Some teams have the same score,
so let's play Five-second
Compliment Game one more time.
One player from each team will play.
- Bo Hyun.
- Jin Woo.
It's Five-second Compliment Game.
- I have many compliments to give.
- You can't repeat the same thing.
- Okay.
- You can do this!
You have one minute. Ready, start.
- Jin Woo.
- Yang Se Hyeong.
- Yang Se Hyeong?
- I mean, Yang Se Chan.
(Se Chan's pride is hurt
from the beginning.)
That's a weird way to attack.
- It's strange to attack this way.
- What?
- Jin Woo is out.
What?
I was going to ask
if Se Hyeong is doing well.
He was going to ask
I can't believe
you called me Se Hyeong.
- Jin Woo, come on out.
- It's just a game.
- Don't put your heart into it.
Jin Woo, how are you so bad
at games?
This time, Se Chan will go first.
(Se Chan, not Se Hyeong,
will begin the compliments.)
(The Name Tag Elimination starts.)
Gosh, this is what I want to do.
(Eui Soo lies down right away.)
Eui Soo, they won't attack you.
Eui Soo. Eui Soo,
they won't attack you first.
- Eui Soo, stand up.
- Roll over.
- Stand up.
No, Eui Soo. Roll over.
You guys are too much.
- Hold on.
- He grabbed it!
(Se Chan is out in an instant.)
(He used his long arms
as if he was playing with a nephew.)
- That was good.
- Jang Geun Won!
Okay, okay.
That was good.
(Bo Hyun is incredible.)
Now, compliment each other.
That was no joke.
- Shall I begin?
- Yes. Begin.
You have a small face
and great acting skills.
I enjoyed the drama.
Your skin is incredible.
You look great in black.
Your necklace is sexy.
You look great in red.
Those designer shoes suit you.
And the jeans look sexy on you.
- That sounds genuine.
- Seriously.
They might suddenly close
the distance.
Stop it!
- Stop it!
- He is ruining it again.
- I don't know what his problem is.
For goodness' sake.
You have sexy eyes. You are pretty.
Your nose is pretty.
(Haha, the President
of Furthering Love Stories Society)
You looked so pretty
when you made pasta.
Watching you made me want
to eat the pasta.
A woman who can cook
is my ideal type.
You have thick eyebrows.
Your hair color is very pretty.
Your nose is pretty too.
- What a sight.
- Why are you so happy?
Bo Hyun's ears turned red!
It's nothing to be happy about.
You need to win.
(Instead of attacking each other
with backhanded compliments,)
- Don't say what you mean.
- What is up with him?
(they act sweetly
as if they are on a blind date.)
You are very tall.
(At that moment,)
(the bell begins to ring.)
- Eui Soo, get up. Get up.
- I am sorry.
- Eui Soo, you need to get up.
Hold on. Hold on.
- Eui Soo, get up.
- Eui Soo...
He is ruthless.
- How could he do that?
- Eui Soo, grab him.
(Grabbing)
(Eui Soo's hand is
on Bo Hyun's name tag too.)
(Eui Soo's counterattack fails.)
- Eui Soo has skills.
- She is good.
- She has skills.
- It looks like jiu-jitsu.
- I can't see her.
There you go.
- Eui Soo!
- Come on!
- Eui Soo,
- She is good.
- not much time remains.
- He is the villain.
- Hang in there.
Okay.
(It ends in a tie.)
- Eui Soo.
- She survived.
You ruined your image
without ripping off the name tag.
Hey, hey.
Both birds ran away.
He didn't gain anything.
Eui Soo's head
was all over the place.
I think he fell in love.
- She did a good job.
- I couldn't rip it off.
- It was no joke.
- Seriously.
Team Ahn Bo Hyun placed 1st
and Team Ji Eui Soo placed 2nd.
The captain of the team
that placed first...
can check if a team has a devil...
and switch out
a member of your team.
I can do that after checking, right?
It can be any team
you are curious about.
It can be your own team.
When you ask,
we will say, "A devil exists"
or "A devil doesn't exist."
There is definitely one in our team.
- I can tell you that.
- Look at Jae Suk.
He is flustered.
- Don't ask about your team.
- Jae Suk, hurry up.
- I am not a devil.
- Don't ask about your team.
- Don't worry.
- Don't waste it.
- Don't do it.
- Ask about another team.
- It's better to do that...
- and swap teammates.
- Kwang Soo.
Which team will you ask about?
Ji Eui Soo's team.
- Will the answer be secret?
- He asked about our team.
- Our team?
- Yes.
In Ji Eui Soo's team, a devil...
- exists.
- I knew it.
- A devil exists.
In that case...
(At least one of them is a devil.)
What are you doing?
I can't believe him.
- Jae Suk.
- There he goes again.
What are you doing?
- Fight!
- Jae Suk is a devil.
- Bo Hyun.
- We don't know about Haha.
(They stick close to Bo Hyun.)
- Seriously.
- I am not a devil.
I say that because when we voted...
- Bo Hyun.
- You can't be sure about Haha.
- Both of them are dangerous.
- That's right.
You can't be sure about Haha.
Bo Hyun,
would you switch out a teammate?
- Yes, I'll switch someone.
- Okay.
- Bo Hyun.
- Switch him out for Se Chan.
(While Haha whispers,)
(Jae Suk sticks close to Bo Hyun.)
- He is a devil. He needs to go.
- Bo Hyun.
I get that you like Jae Suk,
but he needs to go.
Will you swap teammates?
Whom will you switch out?
I will switch out Jae Suk...
In the end, Jae Suk got kicked out.
- For whom?
- In the end...
- Bo Hyun, I can't believe you.
- It's the right choice.
- I can't believe you.
- Everyone knows he is a devil.
- You will regret this.
We knew this from the opening.
- Se Chan.
- That's right.
- Se Chan?
- Me?
- That's good.
- There you go.
- It's "Itaewon Class."
Seriously.
- Seriously.
Yang Saeroyi.
Joo Young, don't worry.
So Min is on the team too.
- That's right.
- Is So Min on the team?
Joo Young,
you should send So Min away.
- That team has two devils.
- What a twist.
- What did Jae Suk say?
- It's the devils' house.
So Min, I hope you recover quickly
and come back.
But So Min needs to go.
The captain of the team
that placed second...
can switch out one of the teammates.
But she won't receive a hint.
- No.
- You aren't a devil, are you?
But it would be dangerous
to keep him.
- I am not a devil.
- But he is too diligent.
- Shall we go as we are?
Should we?
It's not a bad idea. We will stay.
Okay. You will stay.
- "We will stay."
- They will stay as they are?
- Okay.
- She couldn't decide.
After the swapped teammates change,
we will move to the location
of the next mission.
(Se Chan and Jae Suk
have been switched.)
- Let's go.
Do you like your team?
- It's perfect. It's perfect.
- Of course.
- Right?
- It's perfect.
We have a talented captain.
There is no devil in our team.
- Earlier,
- Joo Young.
did you see Suk Jin?
What about him?
He couldn't remember
Joo Young's name.
"Hold on. Joo Young..."
(Earlier)
(Checking)
(He makes a meaningless comment.)
so strong.
She did her best.
I am sorry.
Joo Young was...
so strong.
We will play a game
while in transit.
It's the upgraded version
of the Frying Pan Game,
What's Your Name?
- What's Your Name?
Like the Frying Pan Game,
the attacker will say...
a member's name
and a number from 1 to 4.
The member who has been called
needs to say...
the attacker's name in that number.
- The attacker's name.
- Yes.
I played this game on "X-Man."
- I hosted the game.
- For example...
You win a point
if your attack has been successful.
- Let's go.
- We will play for 10 minutes.
The teams that place 1st and 2nd
will have benefits.
Let's do a good job.
- Let's go.
- Don't do badly on purpose.
(It's important to do well
in order to find the devils.)
- You can do well, right?
- Yes.
I can do well.
- Who wants to go first?
- It's obvious.
- He is the original player.
- I am the original player.
He is the original player of
all games but is terrible at them.
- Kwang Soo, leave him alone.
- He's...
Don't let him find out.
- This isn't hard.
- Eui Soo, you know the rules.
Let's go.
Ting, ting, ting, ting
Tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang
Frying Pan Game
Kwang Soo, four.
Jae Suk, Jae Suk,
Jae Suk, Jae Suk.
Joo Young, three.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo.
- There you go.
- Ji Hyo, one.
Joo Young, Joo Young,
Joo Young, Joo Young.
(Why did she say her name
four times?)
(Ji Hyo is daring
even if she doesn't know the rules.)
There is a big difference
between 1 and 4, don't you think?
She just kept going.
- She is back.
- I am sorry.
Team Lee Joo Young wins one point.
Don't apologize.
I didn't know Joo Young
was like that.
She looked at the camera
and did this.
(She showed her cute act.)
- Joo Young, good job.
- She did this.
- Do it like Joo Young.
- I didn't know she was like that.
(When the game began)
(Pretending to be cool)
(Kwang Soo spots her.)
Kwang Soo, three.
- I didn't know she was like that.
- Did she really do that?
- Yes. She did this.
- Let's do it together.
- Look for the camera.
(We should do this together.)
- Seriously.
- Look for the camera.
Let's begin.
Ting, ting, ting, ting
Tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang
Frying Pan Game
- Bo Hyun, two.
- Suk Jin, Suk Jin.
- Jae Suk, 3.
- Jae Suk, Jae Suk, 2, 3.
(He confidently says,
"Jae Suk, Jae Suk, 2, 3.")
I thought you were
the original player!
"Jae Suk, Jae Suk, 2, 3."
(The national MC
became nervous again.)
He is trembling. He is trembling.
He is trembling. Look at him.
- "Jae Suk, Jae Suk, 2, 3."
- Seriously.
Hey.
- Why did you say my name?
- I thought you knew this game.
- I thought you were good.
- Bo Hyun.
- What was "2, 3" for?
- What was that for?
- Don't worry, Joo Young.
- I'm not sure.
I think he's a devil.
- She's good.
- Let's get started.
Don't worry.
Ting, ting, ting, ting
Tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
Jae Suk, four.
Haha, Haha, Haha.
(He paused for a beat.)
Are you nervous?
You only said it three times.
- You said it three times.
- It's "Haha, Haha."
You were incorrect.
- Why is he so nervous?
- I didn't think it was me.
I didn't think
it was going to be me.
- I vouch for me.
- Don't worry.
- It's okay.
- People who are bad in this game...
are those who go home early
during our team dinners.
- You get it now, right?
- Okay.
- That's true.
- I got it.
- You don't stay long enough.
- Let's get started.
- Okay.
- Start.
Ting, ting, ting, ting
Tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang
Frying Pan Game
Eui Soo, four.
Jae Suk, Jae Suk,
Jae Suk, Jae Suk.
Suk Jin, two.
(Why is she attacking her own team?)
(Suk Jin, two?)
Eui Soo, Eui Soo, Jae Suk, two.
Suk Jin, Suk Jin.
- Jin Woo, four.
- Jae Suk, Jae Suk.
- What was that?
- Why did you go?
Why did you go?
What was that for?
- Are you playing by yourself?
- Mister.
What about her?
Why did you kill your own team?
Why did you kill your own team,
Eui Soo?
She attacked me.
I know.
He attacks and defends
at the same time.
I was startled at "Suk Jin, two."
I feel bad for you.
Let's play again.
We're starting with Suk Jin.
Ting, ting, ting, ting
Tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang
Frying Pan Game
- Joo Young, three.
- Suk Jin, Suk Jin, Suk Jin.
Jong Kook, three.
Joo Young, Joo Young, Joo Young
Suk Jin, three.
Seok Joong, Joo Young, two.
(Seok Joong, Joo Young, two!)
- Who's Seok Joong?
- Seok Joong!
Stop picking me.
- I see you.
- Don't do me.
I see you, so I can't help it.
- This is Ji Suk Jin's Game.
- Ji Suk Jin's Game.
Let Suk Jin take a breather.
Hey.
This is driving me insane.
- I know.
- You're the favorite.
Why did you kill your own team?
- Suk Jin.
- Stop thinking about it.
But still.
That was shocking for me.
- Pick Bo Hyun too.
- I didn't go once either.
- Why do you pick the same people?
- Call my name.
- He's behind, so we don't see him.
- Bo Hyun.
- Pick Jin Woo.
He was here the whole time.
When we play,
he stares at you with this look.
I'm going to pick Jin Woo.
- You have to look at them, Jin Woo.
- He's staring.
He wants to be picked.
Pick Jin Woo.
What's wrong with your hairstyle?
Do you have straight hair?
- Are you a sea urchin?
- That was so random.
- I wanted to mention it too.
That hairstyle was popular
when I was in middle school.
- Motorcycle hair.
- Exactly.
If I dye my hair yellow,
I'm Jang Hyuk from TJ.
That's true. It's Hyuk's hair.
That's true.
How does your hair do that?
- First place is...
- It's us.
Team Jin Woo.
- Really?
- It's us?
- Goodness.
- What was that?
- What happened?
- We didn't get picked a lot.
Team Joo Young is second.
- Are we second?
- Jae Suk.
(They obtain the hints
and move onto the next mission.)
(In the swaying flowers)
(They arrive at the next location
that feels like spring.)
Before proceeding with the final
race, we'll switch teams...
according to the results
of the second mission.
Team Jin Woo got first place,
so please come on up.
- Okay, let's go up first.
- Sure.
Which team's identity
would you like to check?
Our team.
That's a waste.
You threw away the chance.
- In your team...
- Oh, gosh.
(In your team...)
(Ji Hyo doesn't react the same.
Is there a devil in Team Jin Woo?)
- There's no devil.
- I told you.
What?
- Didn't you know?
- Pick a teammate to switch.
Look. Hold on.
(Team Jin Woo is going to stay.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Team Jin Woo...
is going to stay.
- Wait. Who did they pick?
- Who did they find out about?
- I can't tell you.
- He can't say.
- Both of you, come on up.
- Sure.
You can switch one person.
So Min or Jae Suk.
I want to win,
so I'll change up my team.
- I'll switch So Min with...
- Good call.
- She's not getting rid of Jae Suk?
- She's not?
- We'll take Se Chan.
- You'll lose for sure.
You're going to take me?
Look at Jae Suk.
It's confusing when it's your
first time on the show.
He made it complicated.
- You can't have two devils.
- You must get rid of So Min.
- Yes, I'll get rid of her.
- And...
take Se Chan.
- No, Joo Young. He's wrong.
- Joo Young.
(Who will be switched with So Min
and join Team Joo Young?)
(She has to bring an angel.)
I pick Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo!)
Kwang Soo?
Good one!
- Why?
- Good one.
- Good job.
- Why?
(Devil Jae Suk is also flustered.)
- Me? I mean...
- Good job.
- Good one.
- Great job.
- It worked out.
- Joo Young.
That team's done now.
(Why did she pick Kwang Soo?)
(During first mission,)
(Team Eui Soo stayed the same.)
(Does that team not have a devil?)
Kwang Soo, switch to white.
No, hey. This is insane.
This is better.
It's good to put them together.
This mission is called
You Can Tell From the Eyes.
Each team will take turns to play.
One person has to describe
the given phrase with their body.
Two people will try to guess.
You have three minutes.
The captain of the winning team...
will find out the identity of
a person of their choice.
- The identity?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- First of all,
Jin Woo is expressive.
(He's silly.)
(I can tell from the eyes)
(He's playful.)
- From the eyes
- Stop it. Just listen.
- Good job.
- This is fun.
- He doesn't miss a single chance.
- What's wrong with him?
He reacts to every word in the rule.
My gosh.
Are you in a bad mood
because you're on the same team?
I'm not in a bad mood.
Good job.
Many people don't know this song.
Kwang Soo, I understand
why you sprayed salt on him.
He drives me nuts.
Which team is going first?
- He's having fun.
- Let's play Game of Wits.
- Game of Wits.
Let's play Game of Wits.
Ready, start.
- 1.
- 2.
- Two.
- Good job.
Hey, I said good job!
- Why are you glaring at me?
- I didn't.
I'm just really into this game.
Three.
(Meanwhile, Eui Soo succeeds.)
Eui Soo is so...
- 4!
(They both said 4.)
- Why did you?
- You had to wait.
- This team is...
- Why did you go?
- Oh, dear.
- I'm going insane.
- Two of them.
- Okay.
- This is driving me nuts.
- What was that?
They'll show the phrase behind you.
We have to win first place.
You're pointing the water gun
at them only.
- Sure.
- Them only.
Ready...
(Mission starts.)
(Kwang Soo's phrase: A terrapin
waking up from a nightmare.)
- This is difficult.
- This is really difficult.
(This is going to be difficult.)
(What is it?)
- Sleeping.
- A sleeping giraffe.
A giraffe waking up.
Nightmare.
Having a nightmare...
(He just has to say,
"terrapin waking up.")
- Goldfish.
- A turtle having a nightmare?
Terrapin?
(You're right!)
Don't have a nightmare
and go to sleep.
(He goes the wrong way.)
A terrapin waking up from sleep.
(The terrapin is awoken
by the water gun.)
Please wrap up your final answer.
While sleeping...
(Terrapin waking up
from a nightmare.)
(He's frustrated.)
Surprised?
My goodness!
(Terrapin waking up
from a nightmare.)
(Why is the terrapin talking?)
Don't talk.
A terrapin waking up
from a nightmare.
- Okay!
- All right.
(She actually got this.)
Keep going.
(Let's keep this going.)
(A chipmunk that cracked its tooth
from eating an acorn.)
(He's trying to express a chipmunk.)
(Se Chan's chestnut hair)
Park Saeroyi.
Me? Wait.
Moron.
Wrong. It's not a moron.
Look at this! Look, Joo Young.
I can't look.
- Look. I can't describe this.
- I can't look.
(He explains the acorn first.)
How do I...
(What's that?)
(Right!)
Re, mi, fa, so, la, ti, do
- He used his voice.
- Re, mi, fa, so, la, ti
Acorn.
You peel the acorn.
Your tooth...
What's this? Why is this cracked?
- You lost a tooth.
- What was that?
You might as well say it.
You cracked a tooth
while peeling an acorn.
So?
(So?)
I'm not a rat.
What kind of game is this?
A bat.
- A bat.
- That's not it.
- He talks too much.
- He does.
- What's that?
- This is not easy.
- It's too bright.
- Sunglasses.
Sunglasses.
(A pleased panda with
brand new sunglasses)
Gosh, this is...
Expensive sunglasses?
- Gosh, this is...
- This is...
- Stop talking.
- I've never seen this before.
Stop talking!
New sunglasses.
I didn't see this last year.
It's new this year.
- Don't talk!
- Brand new sunglasses.
Brand new sunglasses.
- He talks too much.
- Wearing brand new sunglasses.
You almost had it.
That was so hard.
- That's impossible to guess.
- It's hard.
- Next team now.
- Next team?
You got a cramp, so you're upset.
- Ostrich that's upset with a cramp.
- Peacock.
- Jin Woo.
- You have a cramp.
- Show us the Lee Byung Hun dance.
- Show us.
(Did you call me?)
Seal.
- What's that?
- Hold on.
Is that Haha?
It's hard.
A crocodile that's in pain
from dislocating its jaw.
A hedgehog! A giraffe that's sad
with a long neck.
- We're first place.
- Okay.
- Good job.
- All right.
Let me announce the results.
Team Eui Soo is 1st place
with 3 points.
Yes. Be happy.
(Be happy.)
Captain Eui Soo, you can ask about
the identity of one person.
- We will disclose it to you.
- Can't she swap teammates?
No, she can't. It will be an option
for the next mission.
If there is someone you suspect...
- Let's ask about So Min.
- So Min?
- It's a good idea.
- Let's ask about So Min.
(They want to figure out
So Min's identity.)
- So Min.
- Right?
She is...
Is she a devil?
Is this her identity?
(So Min's identity is revealed
to Suk Jin and Eui Soo.)
- Is this her identity?
- Yes.
Really?
(What could be So Min's identity?)
This mission gives you
the last chance to swap teammates.
It's Only Shoot Ahead of You.
(Only Shoot Ahead of You)
- What is it?
- You will draw one ball...
that has a number from 1 to 11.
What you get will be your number.
Color the name tag of the member
whose number is right ahead...
with a water gun.
Then he or she will be eliminated.
Does the entire name tag need
to be colored?
About 90 percent of it
must be colored.
- Everyone has a target, right?
- That's right.
We will tell you whose number is
right ahead of yours.
We need to keep moving
and shoot the water gun.
The rankings depend on
when each team lost all the members.
- Let's pick the numbers first.
- Okay.
Come on out and pick a ball.
- Show it to the camera.
- Okay.
How cute!
All right.
(Jong Kook's number is 2.)
(Jin Woo is up next.)
(He makes
the Lee Byung Hun turn...)
(and picks a number!)
(That's hilarious.)
(Jin Woo's number is 11.)
(After the Lee Byung Hun lookalike,
you are up.)
- Next.
(Ji Hyo does
the Lee Byung Hun dance too.)
She has short arms.
(Ji Hyo's number is 9.)
(Other members pick a number too.)
(The order of the members
by their numbers)
- Please move to your location.
- Okay.
- We will reveal your target.
The member you need to eliminate...
is Jae Suk.
(Jin Woo's target is Jae Suk!)
Look forward to it.
The member you need to eliminate
is Jong Kook.
Are you serious?
You aren't lying, are you?
I have terrible luck.
(Who is aiming to eliminate
Bo Hyun?)
No way.
Bo Hyun.
He is on my team.
Since my team needs to win,
I will tell Bo Hyun.
Let's say someone
who seems to be targeting you...
chases after you.
We will give you a headband
you must wear during the race.
- Put it on.
- Then what?
If you hit the mark,
he or she must stop.
How would I hit this?
You can do it.
- The circle?
- Yes. It creates a 10-second pause.
If I am 3, I need to shoot
4's mark, right?
The race will begin.
(The countdown begins!)
(A chance to swap members
depends on this race.)
(Which team will win
the final race?)
(The race starts.)
- Bo Hyun.
- Yes?
- What's your number?
- Three.
I am four.
Am I the only one you can shoot?
You are the only one I can shoot,
but we need to survive until the end
if we want our team to win.
- My target is Jong Kook.
- Your target? Jong Kook?
You are done for.
- It won't be easy.
- Seriously.
It won't be easy
because he is uncontrollable.
Since I am your shooter,
put your mind at ease...
- and shoot Jong Kook's name tag.
- Okay.
Where could she be?
(The search for the target begins!)
Kwang Soo, what's your number?
(Kwang Soo's target is Jin Woo.)
(Walking closer)
Hold on. Am I...
You are walking towards me.
(He runs away to avoid
a possible shooter.)
(At that moment!)
(Someone shoots Se Chan!)
What is going on?
Am I Joo Young's target?
(Se Chan and Joo Young)
(While Se Chan is distracted,
she shoots at his name tag!)
(She runs away
after wetting his name tag a bit.)
- Joo Young.
- Joo Young!
Joo Young, is Se Chan your target?
Are you my shooter?
What's your number?
I don't know.
Watch your forehead.
(He tells her
to watch her forehead.)
What was that?
I will stop you right away.
Watch your forehead.
(Don't worry about my forehead.)
Haha, Joo Young shot me.
Joo Young shot me. She must be five.
My target is Jong Kook.
You should go and shoot Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is looking at them
alone.)
You can't do it now.
Shall we go together
so that he doesn't know who it is?
(Se Chan and Haha will be the baits
so that Bo Hyun can take him out.)
Shall we go together?
(Will Jong Kook fall
for the operation?)
1, 2, 3.
(1, 2, 3!)
(They all run to him!)
(Jong Kook blocks the path.)
(Se Chan and Haha work
as the baits.)
- Keep going.
- We want to look at the rooftop.
- Be careful.
- Don't jump down the stairs.
(When Jong Kook runs away,)
(Bo Hyun shoots the water gun.)
(But he misses.)
We are just going up.
One of you must be my shooter.
(He senses the danger
instinctively.)
- The three of us...
- One of you must be my shooter.
should pretend to shoot him
together.
(While Jong Kook runs away)
- What's your number?
- What?
- You aren't my target.
(You are my target!)
(Jong Kook attacks Kwang Soo
like a beast.)
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook)
(Team Bo Hyun uses this chance
to attack Jong Kook together.)
- Shoot! Shoot him right now!
- Hey.
- Shoot him right now!
- Jong Kook is annoyed.
(Bo Hyun shoots Jong Kook.)
(Bo Hyun is Jong Kook's shooter!)
Hang in there.
(Kwang Soo is
at the end of the cliff.)
(He counterattacks!)
You need to pause!
I hit your mark!
- Please pause for 10 seconds.
- You need to pause.
(Jong Kook needs to pause
for 10 seconds.)
Bo Hyun, he will pause
for 10 seconds.
(Bo Hyun uses this chance
to shoot Jong Kook.)
(He hits the name tag without fail!)
(He doesn't know
Bo Hyun shot him.)
Can he shoot me during the pause?
I got Jong Kook.
Jong Kook should be out soon.
(Although he hit the name tag
perfectly,)
(he couldn't wet all of it.)
He isn't out yet, right?
- We are almost there.
- Okay.
This plan is working.
(Bo Hyun versus Jong Kook)
(Jae Suk and Jin Woo)
I will take Jae Suk out.
(Jin Woo is looking for Jae Suk,
his target.)
(He suddenly pretends to be
a detective.)
(No one is looking,
but he becomes absorbed.)
(He is too serious about this.)
(What is he doing?)
He is pretending to be
in a detective drama.
(He rolls on the floor.)
(Ouch.)
(Excessive passion brought him
an unexpected backache.)
Gosh, the microphone.
That hurt a lot.
(Joo Young is still aiming
to get Se Chan.)
Where are Jae Suk and Kwang Soo?
(While Joo Young is
on a cute stakeout,)
He is coming.
(Jae Suk is looking for Ji Hyo.)
It's Ji Hyo.
(It's Ji Hyo!)
(Ji Hyo and Jae Suk)
No!
Stop it, Jae Suk!
- Stop!
- Ji Hyo!
(He holds her hands and attacks.)
Jae Suk!
(Kwang Soo joins in.)
(Kwang Soo holds her
while Jae Suk shoots.)
Ji Hyo.
- I shot her entire name tag.
- Jae Suk.
(Ji Hyo's name tag is soaking wet.)
- You are out.
- Ji Hyo, you are out.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
For goodness' sake.
I need to work fast.
(Jae Suk's next target is 8,
Suk Jin.)
I need to get Eui Soo.
Hee Soo, run away.
Get Suk Jin!
(Suk Jin protects the captain
whose name he doesn't remember.)
Hee Soo!
(At that moment,
Jae Suk attacks Suk Jin.)
Who is it?
Hey!
(Ripping)
(He shoots water gun
at the ripped name tag.)
- Suk Jin is out.
- Suk Jin, you are out.
What?
(Soaked)
You ripped it.
- Give me your water gun.
- Hey.
How could you rip my top?
It just ripped.
(I was too absorbed in the race.)
So you were my shooter.
(Meanwhile, Haha takes out Eui Soo.)
(I need to shoot Haha.)
There she is.
(Haha approaches Joo Young,
his target.)
(Joo Young doesn't know anything.)
- Am I your target?
- No.
(Joo Young and Haha)
(Haha attacks
when he gets a chance.)
(Shooting)
(She protects her back
and shoots at Haha.)
(Shooting his headband)
(Haha must pause for 10 seconds!)
For goodness' sake!
I knew he would do that.
I won't forget this.
- I am on pause.
- What?
Are you on pause? Come here.
Can you shoot
when I am on pause?
- Of course.
- Count 10 seconds!
I am on pause.
- I am on pause.
- It hasn't ended yet.
It ended a while ago!
- Haha is out.
- It ended a while ago.
- Show us your name tag.
- He is out.
Look.
(His name tag is blue all over
like a bruise.)
You are out.
Okay.
- Most of your name tag is colored.
- Really?
(He could be out
after a few more shots!)
- Hold on. Is it colored?
- Most of it is colored.
Bo Hyun, you almost got him.
You almost got him.
You can climb this big mountain.
(The new ace player, Bo Hyun...)
(versus The talented man, Jong Kook)
Pause already.
- Stop shooting.
- You need to pause.
(Kwang Soo is on pause.)
(That's good.)
My goodness.
(Jong Kook spots his chance
and runs towards Kwang Soo.)
(Life or death)
(Jong Kook is after Kwang Soo...)
(and Bo Hyun is after Jong Kook.)
(He's a sniper)
(He lands clean shots
on Jong Kook's open back!)
Jong Kook. You're out.
(He didn't know his name tag
was getting soaked.)
(Jong Kook is out.)
(Am I out?)
(This is Bo Hyun.)
I got him!
- Bo Hyun was behind me.
- You didn't know?
I was close. Thanks.
- Thanks, Bo Hyun!
- Thank you!
- You're after Kwang Soo, right?
- Yes.
(Don't thank me.
I'm going after you now.)
- I have to get Jin Woo.
- What?
I have to get Jin Woo.
- Do you have me?
- Sorry?
- Let's do this.
(3-way race between
Kwang Soo, Jin Woo, and Jae Suk)
(Bo Hyun is back!)
(He charges at his target,
Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo is in trouble.)
(He tries to escape.)
Catch him!
(Bo Hyun flew!)
(Flying shot)
Kwang Soo, you're out.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
(100 percent on target)
Kwang Soo, you're out.
(He has a high score and accuracy.)
We got this. We're good.
(He's dumbfounded.)
The next person you have
to eliminate is Number 11, Jin Woo.
- Really?
- For real?
Don't come. Don't come!
- Don't come!
- He's on his own.
I'm shooting a drama.
Detective Song, get it together!
Do you think
I won't be able to find you?
Don't move. I said don't move.
Detective Yu,
Detective Song is a traitor.
I already found him.
- 2 on 2.
- Who do you have?
- Hurry up.
(Jin Woo ambushes Jae Suk.)
(Bo Hyun charges at Jin Woo.)
I'll hold him.
Shoot. Bo Hyun. Shoot.
(While Bo Hyun tries to dodge
Jin Woo's water gun...)
- Jae Suk, you're out.
- Am I out?
- Let's take a step back.
- Jin Woo, you have to survive.
- Flip him around.
- Do it.
- Now.
- Jin Woo, you're out.
Jin Woo is out. I'll hold her.
Okay.
No!
I got her. Go now.
Go!
- No!
- Now!
Joo Young, you're out.
Joo Young is out.
(Is Se Chan aiming at Bo Hyun?)
It's game over.
- Is it over?
- Yes.
Is it over?
There's only one team left,
so you win.
Did we win?
I'm sorry. You must feel betrayed.
Can you edit this part out?
Please. I'm sorry.
- In the end...
- I'm sorry.
That was my last-ditch effort.
Everything was looking good too.
(Final race concludes
with an attempted betrayal.)
The final result of
Only Shoot Ahead of You.
Team Bo Hyun had 2 people left,
so they're 1st place.
Great strategy.
Team Joo Young is second place.
(Team Joo Young places second.)
Team Bo Hyun, please come on up.
(1st place gets a team member hint
and team member switch chance.)
Please tell me one team
you would like to find out about.
- One team?
- Yes.
I want to know...
(What team
does he want to know about?)
- about Jin Woo's team.
- Jong Kook.
Jin Woo's team.
- Us?
Not your own team?
On that team, there is...
(No devil)
(Everybody on Team Jin Woo
is an angel.)
(They're innocent and naive.)
Who would you like to switch?
We discussed this
at the end of the game.
We'll switch.
- Me?
- Yes.
Hey, you discussed without me?
- Because...
- Sure. I'll do it.
- Why? Are you upset?
- Listen to me.
No, I'm not upset.
This is just a bit absurd.
- How's this absurd?
- Come over here.
- Why?
- We discussed this.
- I tried so hard.
I know you did.
If you want to be safe,
just go as is.
If we're all angels,
we get the benefits anyhow.
- That's right.
- But if they're angels as well,
- it doesn't matter if we switch.
- Right.
- Good point.
- That's true.
It's the same. Can you go?
I'm hurt though.
- No, don't be hurt.
- I understand.
Who are you to say that?
- Haha.
- What did you say? Wait.
- You look more like a devil.
- What's going on?
- Think about it.
- Are you upset?
You're not a real devil.
This is just a game.
Please choose.
(What is Bo Hyun's final decision?)
- I will switch him with Jong Kook.
- Sure.
You shot me many times.
- That's true.
- Sure, thanks.
All right. Thanks.
Sure, we'll do this.
Hold on. I'm hurt.
- Why are you so happy?
- You look too happy.
It's the same.
- Aren't you hurt?
- I am.
It would have been nice
to end off on a happy note.
Joo Young from the team
that came in second.
Please tell me one person
you would like to switch.
Joo Young, I'll go there.
Why do you get to decide?
- Joo Young.
- Let him go.
That's not right.
- Joo Young.
- Look at this brat.
What's wrong?
- Captain Joo Young.
- Please choose.
(What is Joo Young's decision?)
(Will she switch her team
or stay the same?)
I would like to...
- switch Suk Jin and Jae Suk.
- Okay.
(Suk Jin and Jae Suk switch.)
- I'll switch.
- These two?
Then did the devils win already?
Please move over.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
We just have to switch our shirts.
- He's a devil.
- He's not.
(So Min went home already, but
she was suspicious the whole time.)
I knew it.
(So Min was an angel!)
(Jae Suk is the only devil
on Team Eui Soo!)
(Who's the devil on Team Joo Young?)
(Team Eui Soo has a devil.)
(The devil is either
Kwang Soo or Suk Jin.)
(Is there only one devil?
Or are they both devils?)
(What are their identities?)
The team switches have been done.
Please place your hand
on your marble.
It'll light up for the devils.
- Who are the devils?
- I have no idea.
If there are 2 devils in 1 team,
everyone on the team gets a penalty.
If there's only one devil,
only the devil wins a prize.
If there are only angels,
all three win a prize.
Correct.
- Joo Young must be really nervous.
- It's not me, Joo Young.
1, 2...
(Who's the devil on Team Joo Young?)
1, 2, 3.
It's not him.
(The devils are Jae Suk,
Kwang Soo, and Haha!)
- Haha!
- Devil!
(Suk Jin was not a devil.)
(There's a devil on each team
except for Team Bo Hyun.)
Success!
- We spread out.
- See?
I found out at the end.
- Did you notice?
- Yes.
(The devils all win a prize!)
(Devil Kwang Soo managed to
hide his identity...)
(until the end.)
(Devil Haha)
(You're a devil.)
When Jae Suk looked at me,
he looked like a devil.
Did you know?
We are devils on a variety show.
- You two were incredible.
- So Min was not a devil.
Everybody on Team Bo Hyun
and the three devils...
will pick a prize.
(They get to pick a prize!)
- This is my first time.
- I survived.
- Nobody gets the penalty.
That's true. There's no penalty.
Six of you will pick.
Your captain will arrange the cards.
Okay, I'm the leader of the devils,
so I'll arrange them.
- Why are you the leader?
- Why is it you?
- People found out about you early.
- Everyone knew.
Actually, he had
the majority of the votes.
Bo Hyun, you can arrange these
in any order.
- Arrange them and pick a number.
- Is there anything you need?
Weren't we 28 earlier?
- Right.
- I'll put one on there.
Massage chair.
You like 20s.
- I'm done.
- Pick a number each.
I've done this a lot recently.
I need a good one.
- You've done this a lot.
- I have.
You picked a lot, but the only thing
you took was my life-sized figure.
Pick a number each.
- Pick.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Is it on the bottom?
- Please look.
What number is it?
(Bo Hyun did well today.
What prize did he win?)
(He flexes his muscles.)
(He looked surprised.
What is his prize?)
What number is it?
(Lucky Prize Draw)
Tablet computer.
(Tablet Computer)
(This is Bo Hyun's class.)
- Really?
- Tablet computer.
(He got a tablet computer?)
Really?
- 23?
- 23.
- They're serious.
- You get it right away.
- You get it now.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I keep getting 40s.
A number of times.
The massage chair is 28.
Okay. Is it 28?
- What number is it?
- What's the first digit?
- I hope you get something.
- It's sharp.
Is that in the 40s then?
Seriously?
- Members' face candles.
- Did you get something good?
Number 41.
I got the Korean beef set!
See?
- Hey.
- What's going on?
- This is my first time.
- Hey.
- Protein.
- Number 47.
- Jong Kook.
(The miracle of number 47)
- Look.
- What's going on today?
- You got your favorite.
- Right.
I need to party.
- I'm not sure.
- It's okay.
There's a good vibe.
He has a good vibe.
Autographed name tags sound good.
- This is a variety show.
- I only get the 40s.
- What number is it?
- It's behind you.
- What number?
- It ends with zero.
- Go.
- It ends with zero?
(If it's 0...)
The Bluetooth speaker is number 30.
(Number 30 is a speaker,
and number 40 is Korean beef set.)
The Bluetooth speaker is number 30.
- Number 30!
- Really?
(Did he win a Bluetooth speaker?)
(There were good prizes
3 times in a row!)
(This is the butterfly effect
of lucky Bo Hyun.)
Let me see.
- Let's make SBS go broke!
- Hey.
(Unfortunately,
that became a reality.)
Wireless earbuds.
Okay!
- Kwang Soo.
- This is unbelievable.
- This is insane.
- That's awesome.
He said it's insane.
Number 22?
A laptop?
- Gosh, it's a laptop.
- A laptop.
(He's making up
for his all bad luck.)
SBS will go broke.
It's the leader's turn.
(It's the devil leader's turn.)
- What's your number?
- It's 47.
(Massage Chair)
(And Jae Suk's number is 47.)
(His goal is the massage chair.)
- It's 47.
- It's a dud.
Okay.
(He's the only one
who picked a dud.)
(Excited)
(Darn it.)
Okay.
Thank the Almighty of variety shows.
This is mine.
I guess I'm destined
to only host TV shows.
- You don't have any other talents.
- I can't do anything else.
- He has nothing.
- I don't have anything else.
He got caught as soon as we began,
so he's had a hard time all day.
(We'd like to thank Bo Hyun,
Eui Soo, Jin Woo, and Joo Young.)
(Team Comedian,
Team Actor, Team Singer)
(Cho Sae Ho, Rowoon, Lee Do Hyun)
(Noh Sa Yeon, Hong Jin Young)
(With the living legends,)
(all celebrities are
gathered together.)
(Next to a congenial team
of singers,)
(Team Comedian is arguing
about their ranks.)
(But...)
(the years of experience
can change?)
Okay. I got one.
(Their ranks changes in an instant.)
(In order to get
more years of experience,)
(they start the fiercest battle.)
(The years of experience are
forged by someone?)
(What if a red stamp is found?)
(They have to find out a hidden spy
to be ranked number 1.)
- Who is this?
- We might get caught.
(Running Man Class)