To the eighth floor? I see.
The eighth floor?
(Suk Jin shows up
in a neat outfit.)
It's the top floor.
(I look cool today.)
(He arrives at the opening venue
showing off.)
The captain...
- What am I?
- Suk Jin.
- Hang on.
What are you? Are you a spy?
No. The other guys already saw me.
Am I a pilot?
- A pilot?
- I look like a pilot.
He looks like a guy in a costume
who works at an amusement park.
(From the parade of Big Nose Land)
My gosh.
- Hello.
- What?
- What's that?
- I came with him.
- He's dressed the same.
- What's going on?
- What's with your pants?
I thought he was an elevator
attendant or something.
I was surprised.
Are we pilots or what?
- I guess so.
- And what are you?
What about me?
These are just my clothes.
You should get a hair cut.
He's right. You should look neat.
What's with your hair?
What's that? Is it
because of your new movie?
- Yes.
- Are you the only actor there?
(Are you the only actor there?)
Why are you showing it off?
- I'm not showing it off.
- You don't have to show it.
You seem so condescending.
It's not like that. My hair...
- It's not like he's the only actor.
- I know.
Why aren't the other members coming?
And why do you keep your hair long
every time you shoot a movie?
That's because
the director told me to.
Do you let your hair grow long
like that because of the director?
Why are you two
hitting it off today?
- This is crazy.
- That's not true.
I'm really stressed out today.
- Why?
- We just like each other.
Today, we are having
Trade King Race.
- Trade King?
It's called Trade King.
LA Lover Jong Kook will be
the captain of American traders.
And Asian Prince Kwang Soo will be
the captain of Asian traders.
- I see.
- He and I are captains?
Am I a captain?
And Jae Suk and Suk Jin will be...
customs agents and two MCs.
Customs agents?
What is a customs agent?
A person who takes
care of customs issues.
When I make a purchase abroad...
Stay quiet.
I'm trying to explain.
I should tell viewers
what a customs agent is.
Bo Pil is talking.
- I'm a fan of these clips.
- You only listen to...
movie directors.
- That's not true.
- Won't you listen to Bo Pil?
He's right. You should
listen to Bo Pil.
- Listen to Bo Pil.
- My gosh.
- I'm disappointed.
- What are you talking about?
- You disappointed him.
- Do you want me to disappoint you?
Jae Suk and Suk Jin will
handle the overall race...
and broker trade deals
to collect taxes.
(They will handle the race
and collect taxes from traders.)
You're good
at collecting money, right?
- I'm an expert in this.
- I'm not good at it though.
I'm good at collecting money.
- So Suk Jin is...
- It's Petty Gang again.
my subordinate, right?
- Your underling.
- No. You're my subordinate.
You're a member of Petty Gang.
You're my subordinate.
- You're obviously his subordinate.
- Right.
Now the members will
split up into two teams.
They will see the captains' names
on each door.
They will see the names
and pick a team.
But you two will be
in each other's room.
So those who pick Jong Kook...
will be joining Team Kwang Soo.
Okay, okay.
- It sounds fun.
- Okay.
So the members who get
into your room didn't pick you.
- Exactly.
I see.
I will be a little disappointed.
They will try hard
to hide their feelings.
They didn't pick you,
but they will be your team.
- Right.
- Okay.
If I get a lot of members,
I'll be disappointed.
If no one comes in,
Jong Kook will be disappointed.
I know.
Jong Kook will be upset
until tomorrow.
- This isn't a good time.
- Right.
We are having
another shoot tomorrow.
Haha should definitely come.
- Right.
- Haha has to be there.
Right. Haha must pick me.
The last episode was quite touching.
(Last week's episode)
(Which one comes first?
Jong Kook or his business?)
(He chose Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook was deeply moved
by Haha's choice.)
It was touching.
Today, I'll be able to see
if he was serious.
I know. Today...
If Haha comes in here...
It means he made fun of you.
We're in the pyebaek room.
Do you have some jujubes?
I'll throw them at him.
(Jong Kook is determined
to teach him a lesson.)
(Se Chan shows up humming
without knowing anything.)
(Jong Kook's favorite member no. 2)
Hello.
For today's race, it's important
to pick a good captain.
So we will let the members
pick their captain themselves.
If Se Chan comes in here...
Gosh, what should I do?
You know what I'm like
when I trust someone.
Right. He just gives his everything.
- I give my everything.
- Once he trusts someone.
Right. I'm not calculating at all.
Haha and Se Chan
might not come here.
(He's expecting to see them.)
Right.
(Humming)
Come on.
(Se Chan shows up.)
(It's been a long time.)
- I knew he'd come.
- My gosh.
(He feels betrayed.)
- I knew he'd come.
- Kwang Soo, wait.
- I'm sorry.
- Just keep singing.
Gosh, this is...
- Did you not even hesitate?
- No.
Listen to me.
The reason I came in here...
Did you not hesitate?
It's not that I didn't hesitate.
If I don't pick Jong Kook...
- The thing is...
- What?
(It's been a long time.)
I can't believe this.
I was going to slap you in the face.
I want to be in his favor.
So he's in the other room.
Right.
(It's So Min's turn.)
Let me choose a room.
(What's So Min's choice?)
Don't you think So Min will come?
- I'm sure So Min will come.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- I'm 100 percent sure too.
- Me too.
What if So Min picks the other team?
You'll be moved, right?
- Sure. I'll be moved.
- I know.
Actually, we had some talk
in the parking lot earlier.
Right. I saw you two having a talk.
It might affect her choice.
I know. She's... What?
See?
(So Min shows up,
letting Jong Kook down.)
(Flustered)
(See?)
This isn't the room.
What's going on?
(I know. What's going on, So Min?)
So Min.
- Yes?
- Come on in.
(Her eyes are wide open.)
- How could you...
- I told you so.
- This is just as expected.
- Come here!
You never go beyond my expectations.
I was 100 percent sure
that you'd pick this room.
- Just come here.
- Let me explain.
- Go ahead.
- Have a seat.
I was told we wouldn't be
using our physical strength today.
- So I picked the sly one.
- Just come and have a seat.
- You're not sly at all.
- Just sit.
This is just as we expected.
Do you think I like Kwang Soo?
I bad-mouth Kwang Soo a lot.
Why are you sitting on your knees?
(Her hands and knees have become
polite before she knew it.)
I don't know.
So Se Chan went to the other room.
- Gosh, Se Chan.
- Gosh.
I can't help but like him.
He got your back.
Se Chan has a face
that I can't hate.
- I know.
- His face is...
What are you doing?
I just can't hate his face.
- She's...
- Gosh.
You're such a troublemaker.
Just go sit there.
I'm in trouble. What do I do?
Our team is at a disadvantage.
(Next up is Ji Hyo.)
I already have my answer.
I'm sure about this.
Ji Hyo will go there,
and So Min will come here.
(I believe you, Ji Hyo.)
(Ji Hyo shows up.)
Ji Hyo is here.
Kwang Soo, what are you doing here?
Ji Hyo, why did you come?
I didn't know you would come.
I thought Ji Hyo would
pick the other team.
Isn't this Jong Kook's room?
Right. This is Jong Kook's room.
Then what is he doing here?
- They switched rooms.
- You can't say that to me.
You're supposed
to feel sorry for me.
I'm just flustered now.
- It's Haha.
- Honestly...
- If Haha...
- If Haha comes in here...
He is going to have a hard time.
Was Haha supposed to come in
after you?
If Haha comes in, I'll ask for
my money back right away.
My goodness.
(Haha comes in.)
Jong Kook. I knew it.
(Haha is about to return
the investment money.)
(I knew it.)
(Haha, how could you
do this to me?)
I knew it.
I really knew it. I swear.
- I came here because I knew it.
- Stop it.
Jong Kook, I really knew
you would be here.
- Stop lying.
- Listen. I really knew it.
- This is shocking.
- I knew it.
- I didn't think he'd come in.
- He acted like Jong Kook's brother.
- Hey.
- I really knew he'd be here.
- They were so close. My goodness.
- I knew it.
Jong Kook, see how relaxed I am.
Why are you sitting on your knees?
I don't know.
I'm comfortable in this pose.
Exactly. She's been sitting
like that.
(He threw his cap on the floor.)
(He's punishing himself
to reflect on himself.)
You lied to Jong Kook.
After all these years... Gosh.
- Come on. That's not why I'm here.
- How could you do this to me?
You see, I knew they switched
the rooms before I made my choice.
- I meant what I said.
- You're lying.
- Haha, I'm so disappointed...
- I'm in shock.
- You look pale.
- It itches. Darned mosquito.
(What? "Darned mosquito"?)
Gosh, I didn't refer to you.
I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- It wasn't like that.
- "Darned mosquito"?
- It was itchy. That's why.
- Come here.
- Are you making fun of him?
- No. I have a mosquito bite.
You know how much Jong Kook
hates that nickname.
You want a really big mosquito bite?
(Scared)
That was unbelievable.
Let's go for now. Let's get out.
Can we leave now?
Jong Kook.
- It has been a long time
- How could this happen?
Jong Kook.
(He's finally singing the song
to the one he wanted to sing to.)
Se Chan, you won
a lot of brownie points.
- It feels natural
- Just by the look on your face
- Ji Hyo.
- I can tell how you feel
- Like a close friend
- I knew Haha would betray him.
- Hello.
So, he smiles happily at me
only when I have a picture taken...
- at his restaurant.
- Exactly.
- He said he'll withdraw investment.
- He used me.
He meant it.
Only when we discuss
about his restaurant business.
I can't trust Haha.
Haha.
(He's going to lose an investor
because of his misjudgment.)
I'm not feeling well.
- Just as I told you earlier,
- Yes.
today's theme is Trade King Race.
- Jong Kook's team is Team America.
- Team America?
(Haha and So Min are cheering.)
(Jong Kook won't respond.)
I mean, this is...
- Jong Kook, come on.
- This is a variety show.
- Show some reaction.
- Stop being upset.
Are you on the robot mode?
He's just standing there.
I'll cheer up a little
when our guests arrive.
(It will be a long day.)
- Look at his face.
- The other team is Team Asia.
Team Asia!
Jae Suk and Suk Jin are
Team Customs...
- and today's MCs.
- Okay.
Team Customs will be given
100 dollars of fund.
Wait. Give it to me.
Why? Hey, why?
Suk Jin, I heard Jae Suk is
your superior.
- Of course, he is.
- And...
each of Team America and Team Asia
will be given...
- 200 dollars.
- We receive money too.
Is it for the captain?
- 200 dollars?
- It's for the team.
Also, as you might know
if you watched the show,
So Min and Haha made necklaces.
Yes, we did.
- Oh, right.
- I remember that.
I'll give it to Ji Hyo.
- I'll give it to Suk Jin.
- Okay.
Haha, you should make it pretty.
I'm making this for Suk Jin.
That's pointless.
All right. I'm done.
- That was quick. Haha...
- I'm off. Bye.
Haha.
- Oh, right.
- Yes, it was their penalty.
So Min and Haha, give them
what you made for them.
(Here you go, Jong Kook.)
For whom did they make those?
- We chose the same person.
- They already made their choices?
They already made their choices.
(She's giving it to Ji Hyo
as she planned.)
Oh, she picked Ji Hyo.
- I chose him...
- Your role model.
hoping he'll live young.
- Suk Jin.
- Me?
(He gave it to Suk Jin
hoping he'll feel younger.)
Thank you.
Since you received a gift,
it looks as if today is
your last day at work.
- We should give him some flowers.
- It's like his retirement ceremony.
- His retirement ceremony?
- Yes, his retirement ceremony.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
- Try it on.
- Now?
- You should...
- Try it on.
- try it on.
- You should try it on.
I can try it on later.
- I know you won't.
- I don't think I should...
He'll probably give it
to his stylist and say,
"Hey, you can have this."
- Pull it.
- Like this.
- It's pretty.
- It's nice.
- He looks great.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you for this.
- You did a great job.
- Indeed.
- You did...
- Thank you, Haha.
- It's nice.
He's lying.
He didn't mean that.
(He thanked Haha halfheartedly.)
He must be thinking,
"When can I take this off?"
- He thinks it's a hassle.
- He's waiting for the right moment.
Thank you, So Min.
This is so pretty.
- Today, we have guests.
- I see.
We'll meet them downstairs.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go, everybody.
- He's taking it off right away.
- He's taking it off.
- Suk Jin.
Put it on at least until you get
to the elevator.
- Haha looks so disappointed.
- You're the worst.
I'll cherish it.
"Let's go, everybody."
What was that?
Ha Na.
(They all moved to meet the guests
after Big Nose thanked Haha.)
For our today's theme,
Trade King Race,
two guests will join...
each of Team America and Team Asia.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Let's meet the guests who will join
Team America first.
Team America.
- Please come in.
- What's up?
(The 2 guests with American swag)
(Joon Park, Wassup Man, from god)
What's up, brother?
(Joon, what's up?)
Look. Ailee is here.
(Ailee, the Beyonce of Korea)
(It's nice to meet you.)
(They're greeting excitedly
as if they're in America.)
What's up?
- They really are Team America.
- No wonder.
- We got both coasts covered.
We got both
East Coast and West Coast covered.
- By the way, Joon.
- Yes?
Isn't it a little bit chilly
to wear a sleeveless shirt?
To be honest, if I had known
it would be this cold...
You know what I mean, right?
(This is Joon's signature phrase.)
- I haven't heard that in a while.
- "You know what I mean, right?"
- I'm freezing.
- Even I'm wearing long sleeves.
- Gosh. Look at you.
Now, let's meet the guests
who will join Team Asia.
I bet they're related to Asia.
(Screaming)
(Kangnam, the romanticist
who dotes on Lee Sang Hwa)
Oh, Kangnam is here.
- Welcome.
- Hey.
Yiren of EVERGLOW is here too.
- Hello.
- He's overacting.
He's forcing himself
to act more energetic.
- Come over here.
- He was too intense.
- He's overacting.
- Come over here.
- You don't have to do that.
- You're on this team.
- You're on that team.
- Oh, over there?
- Where should I stand?
- Your name tag is there.
- Kangnam...
When Kangnam just made his debut,
- he was so charismatic.
- My gosh.
- You gained some weight.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Why did you gain so much weight?
- Since I got married,
- Really?
- I've been eating a lot.
- You look great.
We have another guest.
A member of EVERGLOW,
- Yiren!
- She came on the show before.
- Yes, I did.
She came on the show before.
That's right. I appeared
for a short while.
Whenever she's on a TV show,
she draws attention.
- Really?
- Because she's pretty.
(Yiren's pretty face draws attention
whenever she's on a TV show.)
Ailee, did you release a new song?
- Yes, I released a new song.
- Really?
- What's the title of the song?
- Let's hear it.
It's "While We Were in Love".
- Let's hear her sing.
- Let's do that.
("While We Were in Love" by Ailee)
(Why didn't you tell me
while we were in love?)
(I can't imagine
how hard it must have been)
(Her beautiful heart-wrenching voice
makes everyone sentimental.)
(While we were in love)
(I did everything as I wanted)
(The sad melody reminds him
of his past love.)
She can sing like that
so early in the morning?
- That was awesome.
- It's so early in the morning.
But why does So Min look like
she's about to cry?
What's with your face? Gosh.
- What's wrong with you?
- That's enough.
- So Min.
- She ruined the mood.
- These days, So Min...
- Yes?
starts crying when she just
hears a love story.
- She's been single for two years.
- Thank you.
I think it's time for you
to publish another book.
"I Called Him Drunk".
("I Called Him Drunk",
Jeon So Min's 2nd book of essays)
I heard...
that EVERGLOW also
released a new song.
- Yes, that's right.
- Please show us a bit.
- Okay.
- The title track is "LA DI DA".
- I guess she'll dance.
("LA DI DA" by EVERGLOW)
(Awesome groove)
(Smiling excitedly)
(Her powerful dance moves
make her look charismatic.)
That was Yiren.
(Everyone is applauding
her beautiful dance.)
- She looked so different.
- That's a great song.
Indeed.
Today, we're having Trade King Race.
Three teams will compete,
and the last place team...
will receive a scary penalty.
Penalties these days
are not very intense,
- but they're annoying.
- It was...
- boring, and it took a long time.
- It's annoying, right?
- I know.
- Yes.
Each member of the winning team...
- will receive 20 dollars.
- 20 dollars?
After you complete a mission,
you will have time
to declare at customs.
You can gain additional mission fund
while doing that.
When we declare at customs?
Then we'll move to
another place to begin the mission.
- Okay.
(They're gathering at the place
where they'll complete the mission.)
(There are seats reserved
for the MCs.)
You two really are a duo?
Where should I sit?
- I'm looking forward to this.
- We're not a duo.
Please be gentle on us.
You know how powerful we are, right?
- Please be gentle on us.
- We make the decision.
Jae Suk, please be gentle on us.
Your smile looks so pretentious.
- Why don't you bring some snacks?
- I hope...
That's not how you ask a favor.
Do we have some chocolates?
So I can feed them.
(She gave up on competing fairly
a long time ago.)
I think I need to give the MCs
some food.
- First of all, we're going to...
- Yes?
Jong Kook, listen. There will be
punctuality score.
"Punctuality score"?
- Some of you are not here yet.
- Those punks are not here yet.
Only the guests are here
from this team.
- Exactly.
- It's a disaster.
Running Man
is a popular show though.
- What is taking them so long?
- Kwang Soo and I don't get along.
Hey!
- Don't...
- Come quickly.
Don't yell.
Let me yell at them
since I have power over them.
Listen. You must be punctual.
Jong Kook, one of your members
is missing.
Guys. About the punctuality score...
You were winning,
but they turned the tables.
- I know.
- They won.
But you yelled at us a lot.
- What?
- You yelled at us too much.
- Hey.
- Almost all of our members...
- are here.
- This is crazy.
Do you know what power I have?
- What is it?
- Do you have power?
Jae Suk and I get to decide.
We will decide the winner.
So you will have to
listen to Jae Suk.
- What?
- You can't decide it yourself.
Jae Suk and I have
our own opinions.
So can you make a decision
by yourself or not?
We will go 50-50.
So can you make a decision
by yourself or not?
This is a democratic society.
I can't decide anything alone.
We won't listen to you then.
What did you say?
We just need to get
on Jae Suk's side.
Jae Suk.
Se Chan just ignored me.
I'm the director here.
(He draws a line.)
If you're a director, what is he?
- What's his title?
- He's an intern.
- He's a section chief.
- A section chief?
Are you talking
about marinated crab?
Marinated crab?
That sounds about right.
- Chief Ji.
- It sounds good.
- I'm the director.
- Director?
Director Yoo and Chief Ji.
- Chief Ji.
- It sounds like a carrier.
Chief Ji.
By the way, Team Jong Kook
isn't still here.
Haha is getting makeup now.
- Why would he get makeup?
- Why?
- He even wears cologne.
- Everyone.
He started talking.
- It's started.
- We have 9 people out of 10.
- It's 90 percent attendance.
- Sure.
I agree.
He's very wise.
- You're so cool.
- Director Yu, you're very wise.
Hey, why are you
treating him differently?
- And...
- That's because...
- Chief Ji.
- you have no power.
You should be
respectful towards them.
- Right.
- I agree.
- The thing is...
- Now I have my power.
It's not like that.
This is a public office.
- A public office?
- We're here for the civil service.
- He's different.
- Sure.
- In the old days...
- You'll see.
I also have my vote.
You guys should remember that.
So your team has
a director and a parrot.
He's not a parrot.
He's a section chief.
- Chief Ji.
- Director Yoo and an old geezer.
Look at him.
- That punk.
- Look.
You can walk past.
Excuse me.
- We just...
- How did it go?
lost our points.
Let me tell you about today's race.
We are going to tell you
about three controversial stories...
being discussed online.
That's good. I like it.
We will hear your opinions
on the issues...
and decide if it's okay or not.
- We will make a decision.
- Let me see.
Excuse me, but...
(I want to see it.)
Will you stay still?
Just sit still.
I'm sorry, but you haven't been
an MC since "Six Heroines".
- Director Yu.
- I'm sorry,
but you haven't been
an MC since "Six Heroines".
- "Six Heroines"?
- Just stay quiet.
Keep your mouth shut.
You haven't done this
since "Six Heroines".
You need to watch your language
for the civil service.
I just want to see it.
So the captains will pick
one of these two.
Each team will pick
"Okay" and "Not Okay"...
and convince us accordingly.
- I see.
- I've done this before.
If we pick "Not Okay",
we should go against the idea.
It's not about our real opinion.
- Exactly.
- It's about what we pick.
I will tell you a story...
that's under great controversy...
on the Internet.
Who told you to drink water?
- I knew you'd get scolded.
- This is important.
- You're our captain.
- I'm telling you...
- about something important.
- You need to win his favor.
- How dare you...
- I'm sorry.
How dare you drink water?
I'm really sorry.
I just saw water here.
We have strong power here.
- I'm sorry, but...
- We have strong power.
Ailee was about to drink water.
- Go ahead and drink it, Ailee.
- Go ahead.
I will tell you a story...
Who told you to drink water?
(Startled)
I was thirsty. That was close.
(Ailee decided to suppress thirst
as the MCs yell.)
Ailee, you can drink.
What are you doing?
- Let her drink water.
- She was thirsty.
She's our guest.
- She says she was thirsty.
- It's okay. Go ahead and drink.
You are okay.
Ailee, I like your song, "I'll Go
to You Like the First Snow".
Stop it.
About the cue cards
Suk Jin is holding...
This one? It's fake.
This is real.
- It's real.
- It's nothing.
- This is real.
- No, it's fake.
I'll read a story.
This is like
"Men Who Top the Charts".
It has some words,
but it's different from mine.
It's just for a show.
It doesn't have the important part.
Suk Jin, switch seats with him.
- So there's fierce controversy...
- It's not fierce.
over these stories online.
Here's the first story.
- This is good.
- I'm excited.
We can make a coherent argument.
- We have So Min too.
- Sure.
- We're good at this.
- This...
has been under controversy...
for a long time
since we got cell phones.
- It applies to all of us?
- It's about...
(Sharing the phone password)
sharing the phone password.
Who do we share it with?
My girlfriend or parents?
- Your girlfriend.
- My girlfriend?
- Not my parents?
- No.
- Let me read...
- I'll...
read a story.
Stay quiet.
I've been waiting to read this.
(Chief Ji has been waiting
a long time for his part.)
Suk Jin. Just sit here.
- Stay quiet!
- Suk Jin, come have a seat.
I feel bad for Suk Jin.
My gosh.
Let me read a story for you.
- We will talk about this story.
- All right then.
- Chief Ji will read you a story.
- Right.
Please listen.
"We're a couple in our early 20s,
and we've been dating for 6 months."
- In their early 20s.
- Think carefully about it.
"We were watching a movie
together at home a few days ago."
"Then my girlfriend asked me
to unlock my phone."
All of a sudden?
"I thought she wanted to see
some photos, so I unlocked it."
"Then she asked me about
my messaging app password."
She asked about
his messaging app password.
She crossed the line.
"My girlfriend said..."
- Just stay still.
- Hurry.
This isn't important.
Just hurry and get it over with.
"My girlfriend said there should be
no secret between lovers."
(Yawning)
"She asked me to share
my phone password..."
"and messaging app password."
"I think even couples..."
Think carefully about this.
"She asked me to share
my phone password..."
"and messaging app password."
(He reads all the unnecessary
sentences of the story.)
(They all fall asleep together.)
- "We should have some secrets."
- Director Yu, please read it again.
Gosh, I'm startled.
- What happened?
- "After a long squabble..."
- Hey.
- Hello?
- Hi.
- Wake up.
(They can't continue.)
- How are you?
- Wake up, everyone.
Wake up.
(Chief Ji wakes everyone up
with the sign.)
- What?
- Why? What's wrong, Kwang Soo?
I just had a paralyzing nightmare.
(The story is like a nightmare.)
Everyone. This is
exciting, isn't it?
"We squabbled for a while, but
we failed to reach an agreement."
"So we decided to talk
about it again later."
"Is it okay to share
the passwords of phones..."
"and messaging apps
with my girlfriend?"
All right. Before we start
talking about it,
I wonder what you think.
I think we should never...
share passwords in any case.
- Why not?
- Why do you think so?
It's uncomfortable. I share
my passwords with my wife.
- I see.
- So whenever I get a message,
my heart beats fast.
- Why?
- I don't know.
- I didn't do anything wrong.
- Then why?
- Why?
- I don't know.
My wife might get the wrong idea.
- What?
- She might take it the wrong way.
Now I get it. One day, Suk Jin...
kept leaving the chat room
we were in together.
So I wondered
why he was being like that.
Why did you leave
the chat room with So Min?
The problem is,
you act cute with your messages.
When did I do that?
- That's not true.
- Suk Jin.
You send too many emojis.
- What's wrong about using emojis?
- That's not true.
Guys. I want you
to give your opinions now.
Is it okay to share your passwords
with your lover?
- Gosh, this is...
- Se Chan, go ahead.
I once broke up with my girlfriend
because of this issue.
- I knew it.
- We broke up.
So the thing is,
you can exchange some jokes...
with your friends on messaging apps.
Sometimes I send some jokes
to make my friends laugh.
I also send some pictures.
But my girlfriend
took it the wrong way.
- She thought I was being strange.
- I understand.
Are you talking
about the flight attendant?
- Hey!
- Okay. I get it.
- Why would you say that?
- Okay.
- He's mad for real.
- All right.
- I'm giving you a warning.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm really sorry.
- Can I talk about her as well?
- I apologize.
- I'll talk about her too.
Hey.
Don't mention flight attendants.
It also applies to Jae Suk.
Are you crazy?
- Don't say that.
- Keep quiet.
- His wife is watching.
- We all have a past.
- Really?
- Why would he talk about my past?
(What did you just say?)
Do you want me to talk about you?
- Do you want to start it?
- All right.
- Look at you.
- I get it.
- I have a lot to talk about.
- Okay, okay.
(The revelation of their past
happens one after another.)
What about you, Kangnam?
My wife and I share passwords.
We know each other's passwords,
but we don't check
each other's phone.
- You don't?
- No.
- But you know her passwords?
- I do, but I don't check her phone.
This is different.
Do you really think
your wife didn't check your phone?
- Yes.
- I'm sure she did.
Yes.
(He ends
the conversation right away.)
I think Kangnam doesn't
even want to talk to you.
He's the section chief.
- He's ignoring you.
- He still holds a high position.
- He is the section chief.
- He has his own title.
- I still have a 50-percent share.
- He has a vote.
You can't ignore him.
- Does he hold a high position?
- He has a vote.
We should respect
each other's opinion.
- You shouldn't ignore others.
- I agree.
And you can't make fun of others.
- Make sure not to do those things.
- Okay.
- I have my power.
- "Yes."
I think it's better
not to share passwords.
I've never shared
my password with my ex-boyfriend.
- But he figured it out himself.
- How?
- How did he figure it out?
- He looked over my shoulder.
That's dangerous.
Then he looked at my phone
and got me wrong.
"Why are you being
so kind to other guys?"
But her messages can be misleading.
- She's too kind.
- All right.
I'd like you to talk less.
What you said is like 80 percent!
You're the one who talked a lot.
Is he a bully or something?
- He sounds like a bully.
- He rarely talked.
- You did most of the talking.
- Talk less.
It feels like I'm listening
to a radio show.
If you don't want to get hit,
just stay quiet.
- All right. Continue.
- Let's say I told my boyfriend...
my password,
and he checked my phone once.
It should end there,
but he keeps thinking about it.
"Oh, right. I should check..."
"the friends she blocked
on the messaging app."
- He even checks those?
- He does.
- I didn't know that.
- And...
- That sounds scary.
- They even check things like that?
That's why I don't want to know
the password in the first place.
- I don't even start.
- It's better not to see it.
- It's distressing.
- Captain Jong Kook, you're up.
Here's what I think. It's...
Hang on. Don't get worked up
even before you start talking.
He's right.
Your shoulders are too broad.
The thing is...
If my girlfriend...
- She must have male friends, right?
- Of course.
I wouldn't want to see her texts
to them with my own eyes.
- You wouldn't?
- I would just trust my girlfriend.
- Exactly.
- Right.
It seems that most of you,
Suk Jin, and I...
- believe...
- Many are against it.
that it's right for a couple
to not share...
- each other's password.
- That's better.
- If you know the password...
- That's the prevailing opinion.
You'd want to look through the phone
if you know the password.
But 1 of the 2 teams here will
defend the opposite opinion.
- The captain of each team...
- I'm worried.
- will pick the side.
- You will pick the side.
- And according to the result,
- This is so important.
you may have to argue...
what is against your point of view
in front of us.
You have to convince us.
- Kwang Soo, pick the good one.
- You should pick the good one.
- I should pick Not Okay, right?
- Don't pick Okay.
(Not Okay seems easier
to convince the MCs.)
(Which one will
the unlucky Kwang Soo pick?)
- Right. Please pick Not Okay.
- You should pick Not Okay.
(Team Asia)
- It's Not Okay.
- Okay!
- Now...
(Team Asia picked Not Okay.)
- I made it.
- Good.
- We'll be okay.
- Let's win the first round.
- We'll be okay. It'll be easy.
- You never know.
- We can do this.
- You just have to...
- convince us.
- We can do this.
- Your team is Not Okay.
- Yes.
- This team is Okay.
You can just convince us.
Just as we said earlier,
if a couple shares the password,
it leads to a misunderstanding
and they end up breaking up.
- Don't cause a misunderstanding.
- You shouldn't do anything...
- that can cause a misunderstanding.
- What if you didn't?
Even if they did nothing suspicious,
it can lead to a fight,
- and they grow apart eventually.
- Even if nothing happened...
For example, I came back
from the restroom.
- Can you lower your voice, please?
- Exactly.
- I was...
- You're too loud.
I was the quietest among all of us.
You're too loud.
- I was the quietest.
- You're sitting close to me.
- You don't have to be that loud.
- Should I whisper to you?
- Calm down.
- Gosh, seriously.
- We're all wearing a microphone.
He's right. We need to stay calm.
Are we shooting an ASMR video?
- We need to stay cool.
- Speak quietly.
- What I'm saying is...
- In my opinion, in a case of...
- In my opinion...
(Turning their heads around)
- In a case of emergency...
- Poor Kwang Soo.
- Even Ailee cut him off too.
- She jumped in.
- She's really something.
- Let's hear her out.
- She's not an easy fight.
- I want to hear her out.
- In a case of emergency...
- I want to hear her out too.
Let's say I'm meeting my boyfriend,
and we got into an accident.
And my boyfriend is unconscious.
- I have to call his parents,
- Of course.
but I don't have their numbers.
I need to know the password
to unlock his phone...
- and call his parents.
- Exactly.
- That can't be an excuse.
- That's...
- an extreme case.
- Wouldn't you call his parents?
- You should call the rescue center.
- Exactly.
Listen to me.
People have their own ways...
of interpreting when they read
text messages.
- That's right.
- Therefore,
- even some meaningless texts...
- Exactly.
- can cause a misunderstanding.
- It can cause a misunderstanding.
- Such misunderstandings...
- You don't have to read them.
But what if you read some texts
unintentionally?
- Let's say your girlfriend...
- Yes?
or your boyfriend wants you two
to share each other's password.
- If my girlfriend wants that? No.
- Yes.
Then would you break up with her
even though you love her?
- He wouldn't break up with her.
- I would convince her...
and ask why she wants to
look through my phone.
Just tell me your password, Se Chan.
Once you unlock my phone,
we're over.
- All right. Just tell me.
- If you trust her...
If you look through my phone,
we're over.
Sure. I'll let you go.
Just tell me your password.
- You said you'll let me go.
- Yes.
I said I won't
look through your phone.
("We're over if you go through it"
versus "Just tell me your password")
(It's as if they are the only people
that exist in this place.)
(They won't stop arguing
as if they're a real couple.)
(Se Chan is
running out of patience.)
- Just tell me your password.
- Then why do you need it?
- You said you won't see it.
- Look at him. He's getting upset.
- He's getting upset.
(He's getting extremely upset.)
- I won't.
Se Chan. Gosh.
- Sit down.
- You said you won't see it.
- You just said you won't see it.
- Calm him down.
- I mean, you said you won't see it.
- Calm down.
(Se Chan took off his shoes
as he got angry.)
(I won't look through your phone,
but give me your password.)
- Calm down. Stop him.
- You said you won't see it.
- Then why do you need it?
- I mean...
- I know.
- He said he won't see it.
I just want to know
your password. That's all.
- Gosh. What else should I do?
- I just want to know the password.
- Sit down and drink some water.
- He won't look through your phone.
- He won't look through it.
- Gosh, I can't believe this.
I know. Just drink some water.
I won't, I promise. I want to set
my password the same as yours.
- In fact, this debate...
- Yes.
should be based on the premise...
that the couple will look through
each other's phone.
- It's only reasonable.
- No.
- There's no way you don't see it.
- That's not true.
- That's not possible.
- Why would you even ask for it?
I'm confident that I won't
look through the phone.
Based on the premise that they look
through each other's phone...
- I wouldn't look through the phone.
- That's not possible.
- How would that be possible?
- I wouldn't look through it.
You would become curious
if you know the password.
- That can start a fight.
- I can hold myself back.
(Arguing loudly)
- Listen to me.
- No way.
- Everyone, listen to me!
- You see...
(They stood up suddenly.)
- I mean...
- Calm down.
- See? Look at us.
- I wouldn't do that.
Talking about it alone
made us fight.
- Exactly.
- You should never share it.
There's nothing to fight over
if you don't know the password.
- If you share it...
- You can share the password...
without looking through the phone.
What we're saying is that it's okay
to share my password...
with the person I love...
- as a token of love.
- That's right.
It's okay.
- All right. Time is up.
- Oh, no.
The team that Chief Ji and I
have chosen as the winner...
of the first topic...
- You made the decision alone?
- about sharing passwords...
to a cell phone and
a messaging app...
They didn't even have a discussion.
- We should discuss first.
- Oh, right.
Didn't you two have a discussion?
I thought they agreed...
- Okay?
- Yes, I agree with you,
but this is very unpleasant.
I mean, I agree with you, but...
- That's all that matters.
- I agree, but...
- I knew that.
- I admit...
- I agree with him.
- We have the same opinion.
- They have a better chance to win.
- The first topic...
about sharing passwords.
1, 2, 3.
- Not Okay.
- Oh, yes.
(The MCs picked Not Okay.)
- Nice.
- Good job.
(Team Asia won the 1st round.)
- I admit they were right.
- Good job.
This is great.
- You see...
- It was a difficult topic.
- It was so difficult.
- That's true.
We won.
Kwang Soo's team won
the first round.
- I'm glad he picked Not Okay.
- This is fun.
- Next topic.
- This is also a sensitive issue.
- Good job.
- This is fun.
Actually,
when we first read this topic,
we thought the same thing again.
We're leaning toward one side.
"Giving your jacket
to your girlfriend's friend..."
- "on a cold day."
- Just get to the point.
That's difficult.
Okay or Not Okay?
Not Okay!
(Not Okay!)
- It's not okay.
- What was the topic?
- It can never be okay.
- "Not long ago, I was..."
"drinking beer with my girlfriend
and her friend in the terrace."
"It became quite chilly
in the evening,"
"and my girlfriend's friend said
she was cold."
"I was wearing a jacket,"
"and I wasn't cold,
so I gave my jacket to her."
- He made a mistake.
- "While taking my girlfriend home,"
"we started arguing."
"My girlfriend got mad at me
saying she didn't understand..."
"why I gave my jacket
to her friend."
"I did it only because her friend
was cold."
"Is it not okay to give my jacket
to my girlfriend's friend?"
- Do you think it's not okay?
- That's excessive kindness.
- He was being too kind.
- Many men don't know this.
- Let's hear So Min's story.
- So Min looks angry already.
- She's upset.
- She looks very angry.
First of all,
I have a similar experience.
If we just consider the situation
in this story,
it depends on what kind of girl
the girlfriend's friend is...
and her taste in men.
If her friend is popular among guys,
- she would be angry. However...
- I see.
- However...
- That makes sense.
- I see what she means.
- She has a point.
- You see...
- It's very important.
- Actually,
- That's a good point.
I have a pretty friend. One day,
the three of us went to a karaoke.
- I see what she means.
- But...
my boyfriend sang the songs
my friend wanted to hear.
- Of course, you'd get angry.
- He shouldn't have done that.
We had a big fight
while he was walking me home.
I see why you got angry.
But my friend is really pretty
and popular.
- That's what any men would do.
- She can attract a man...
just by talking to him.
It's so hard to figure out
what women want.
When you give a girl flowers,
sometimes she's happy,
but sometimes she gets mad at you.
- What must I do to make her happy?
- Exactly.
That's exactly my point.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Whatever I do, she gets mad.
I hope there will be a book
on this topic.
Since we're talking about it,
can anyone share a story...
about the worst person
you've ever dated?
- Yiren, what about you?
- No.
(She answered right away.)
- Hold on. He wasn't even finished.
- That was quick.
- She's an idol singer, you know.
- Yiren...
She seemed like she was
ready to say no.
- All idol singers react like that.
- Okay.
- I accept your answer.
Everyone, imagine a situation
where their roles are reversed.
Let's say your friend joins you
when you're with your girlfriend.
Your friend says he's cold.
And your girlfriend takes off
her jacket...
- The girl gives her jacket?
- and gives it to your friend.
- The girl gives her jacket to him?
- Yes.
- The girl...
- Imagine that situation.
- If you consider...
- If you imagine that situation...
Just as So Min explained,
I wouldn't mind if it's Kwang Soo,
but I'd be mad if it's Jong Kook.
(I wouldn't mind if it's Kwang Soo,
but I'd be mad if it's Jong Kook.)
- Gosh. Why?
- I was looking at you two.
- I thought I'd be okay with you,
- Exactly.
but if it's Jong Kook,
it would bother me.
That makes you upset.
- That thought crossed my mind.
- Exactly.
For example,
you let Se Chan or Suk Jin
tag along on a date.
And when he says he's cold, your
girlfriend gives him her jacket.
You would think,
"My girlfriend is so kind."
(My girlfriend is so kind.)
- Exactly. You'd feel that way too.
- I see.
- The same goes for you.
- Jae Suk.
- It's the same for him.
- Yes.
- That would make you...
love your girlfriend even more.
In a situation like that...
- If it's Suk Jin,
- "I'll be with her forever."
I wouldn't mind
even if she wipes his mouth.
That wouldn't bother me at all.
- Whatever she does,
- But...
I would only think she's kind.
- Honestly,
- I agree.
- I would love her even more.
- That makes sense.
But I think I'd react differently.
Let's say I'm with my girlfriend
and her friend.
If her friend says she's cold,
I would ask my girlfriend
if she's okay first.
- That's so sweet.
- You should start dating!
- I'm just saying...
- All he does is imagine...
- dating a girl.
- Wouldn't anyone do that?
- He knows everything about dating.
- Of course.
- He's like a dating expert.
- Yes.
You need to choose the side.
Ailee, pick one.
- I'm nervous.
- It doesn't matter.
- But the girl...
- Okay.
- She picked Okay.
- The other team is Not Okay.
- It's okay.
- We got Not Okay.
- It's not okay.
- It's okay.
I'm sure So Min will still
say it's not okay.
He can give his girlfriend
his phone password after that.
- That's right. It's okay.
- His phone password?
- It's okay.
- This is crazy.
(It's okay.)
(She went back on her conviction
to win.)
- It's okay.
- Why do you think so?
- Is it okay?
- It's okay.
- Please explain.
- I'll explain to you.
When a man acts like that,
he does it only to make
his girlfriend stand out.
- He's right.
- To make her look good.
- That's a good point.
- It shows that he has good manners.
However, some girls...
would think that he does it because
he likes her like So Min did.
But there are many women
who hate it.
- Yes, there are many.
- Kwang Soo.
- You're polite and considerate.
- Right.
- So that's what you do.
- It's an act of kindness.
- I bet people misunderstood you.
- Right.
- That's why you're against it.
- Of course.
- If that's the case...
- With Kwang Soo...
But this is what you do...
out of the kindness of your heart.
But this is her best friend.
If...
Darn. Truth be told,
I'm okay with it.
(Darn. Truth be told,
I'm okay with it.)
- What?
- It's okay.
You need to be more persuasive.
- I'm leaning toward them.
- You're not winning me over.
You're fine with it too, right?
Ji Hyo's okay with it too.
- Let us make a decision then.
- We'll make our decision.
Offering your jacket to
your girlfriend's best friend.
Is it okay or not?
- It's not.
- We've come to a verdict.
- It's okay.
You weren't able to persuade us.
You weren't convincing enough.
- Well...
- We couldn't understand it either.
- You're okay with it?
- You're only being polite.
The girlfriend should be proud.
(After the conclusion
of the following debate)
Of course, it is.
Team America who won
with a score of 2 to 1...
will receive 20 dollars.
(Team America wins!)
So that's how it goes.
Don't we get anything?
What about us?
You'll be rewarded too.
This is your first
customs declaration process.
Each team will take turns
entering that room.
While in there,
you will choose one box.
There are 10 boxes in total,
and 2 boxes each contain...
20, 40, 60, 80, 100 dollars
respectively.
Once you check the amount,
you'll bring it out...
and pay up half of that money...
- as tax.
- To us, right?
You are allowed to write down...
a smaller amount
than you should pay.
Let's say you chose a box
with 100 dollars.
You can lie...
and only hand over 10 or 20 dollars.
If you're caught in a lie,
the customs agents
will take everything.
- What if you're not caught?
- Then...
the agents will pay
your tax for you,
- and you'll take the full amount.
- If we don't catch them?
If they choose to check...
- even though I'm not lying...
- That's right.
- Right.
- The agents...
- will receive a penalty?
- They'll pay the tax instead.
Got it.
(The customs agents
must be cautious.)
The team that lost will go first.
These guys...
- This isn't easy, you know.
- They could...
try to trick us.
- Okay.
- They'll think that we'll lie.
- If we take the chance...
- It won't help us win.
- This is driving me crazy.
- But we need to take a chance.
What's best...
is for us to pick 100 dollars...
and pay up 10 dollars...
- without them suspecting us.
- Right.
Why won't they though?
They would.
Kangnam, pick one.
- Should I just choose?
- A smaller amount is better.
- Maybe 50 dollars.
- Just choose.
Anything? Then I'll...
- This one?
- Number four.
Four...
The choice is
20, 40, 60, 80, 100 dollars.
Please...
It's not too bad.
(How much money did they get?)
They'll doubt us for sure especially
since Kwang Soo's the captain.
(What will be Team Asia's strategy?)
It's all about how much money
was in the box they chose.
- Here they come.
- We're ready.
(Confident)
Ji Hyo, what's the amount?
- Well...
- Look at their expressions.
We picked our box.
- Hand it over.
- Pay your tax.
The box we chose had 40 dollars.
- 40 dollars?
- Yes.
- So you'll pay 20 dollars?
(So you'll pay 20 dollars?)
- There was a heated discussion.
- That's right.
- Hold on.
- He's not the kind of person...
to pay up 20 dollars
when all he has is 40 dollars.
What?
He'd only give up 20 dollars
if he had chosen 60.
That's right.
The rules say
he must cough up half.
- But he wouldn't.
- Right.
Yiren's too innocent...
to bluff in any way.
- How much was in the box?
- 30 dollars.
- 30 dollars?
- Yet you're paying 20 dollars?
- No, 40 dollars!
- Hold on.
(Flustered)
(Scoffing)
- We chose 40 dollars.
- Hold on.
- No, 40 dollars.
- Wait a second.
- 30 dollars?
- You chose 30 dollars,
but you're paying up 20 dollars?
I meant 40 dollars.
She got confused
because of the Chinese word.
He'd never pay up half.
- Right?
- Of course not.
Also, Kangnam's shaking.
Look at his fingers.
- Let me be honest with you.
- Sure.
You're absolutely right.
(Jae Suk, you're absolutely right.)
- 60 dollars was in our box.
- Right?
But?
We chose 60 dollars...
- But you're only paying 20?
- Yes.
- So you're lying to us.
(Did Kwang Soo confess
to tax evasion?)
- Hold on...
- Shouldn't you pay up half?
He's playing mind games.
He's trying to get us to confirm
what was in the box.
(If Kwang Soo is wrongfully
suspected, he won't have to pay.)
I think we should check.
Can you give me your hand?
This is Jong Kook's trick.
Your palm is wet.
(He can't hide
how sweaty his palm is.)
My gosh.
Don't do that.
Don't you do that.
(Jong Kook's lie detector test
is quite accurate.)
- Don't.
- His palm is sweaty.
It can't be wetter.
But his expression...
- Exactly.
- This is intriguing.
- Maybe we shouldn't check.
- It's getting interesting.
- We won't get much anyway.
- Exactly.
So we won't check.
(They've been cleared.)
- We won't get much anyway.
- That's the right choice.
There's not much to take anyway.
20 dollars is more than enough.
Okay, we won't check.
I have a feeling that
So Min will choose well.
- Really?
- Right, of course.
- She's not the luckiest type but...
- Really?
- Still. Just go ahead.
- Really? Let's get it.
- Not that one.
- This is the number I like.
- Really?
- I like this number.
- What?
- Go ahead.
It's all about
how much they pay up.
- We...
- Yes?
(We...)
We chose 80 dollars.
Let's get it!
(Jong Kook claims that
his team chose 80 dollars.)
So we'll cough up 40 dollars.
- That much...
- Hold on.
Why would we bother to check?
I mean...
If they're lying,
it means they chose 100 dollars.
The highest amount
they can get is 100 dollars.
Instead of 50, they paid up 40,
so that's a 10 dollar difference.
They're only pocketing
10 more dollars.
You'll go this far
for just 10 dollars?
- So 40 dollars.
- 40 dollars?
They must be telling the truth.
- Right.
- That's what I think.
We'll clear their team too.
- Then...
- Did they fool us?
Both captains will reveal
how much was in the box.
In our case...
(Team Asia already admitted
to tax evasion.)
(So how much was
actually in the box?)
Jae Suk was right on point.
- Right.
- He saw right through us.
(Jae Suk was right on point.)
(What?)
- How so?
- We chose 60 dollars,
and I insisted
that we only pay up...
20 dollars.
(Kwang Soo insisted
that they pay 20 dollars less.)
I knew it.
- Right off the bat...
- Right from the start...
- Jae Suk said...
- He said I was going to lie.
Still, I asked my team
to believe in me this once.
When Yiren said "30 dollars",
it was the amount
you originally had to pay up.
- That's right.
- I should've realized.
- Goodness.
- You're good at deducting though.
- I called it.
- What he said at first...
- I told you his palms were sweaty.
- My palms...
No one should be allowed
to check palms anymore!
- Anyway, good job.
- Nice.
- It went as planned.
- We won 20 dollars though.
How much did you choose?
Was it 100 dollars?
(Did Team America lie too?)
(We...)
- You told the truth, right?
- It was 80 dollars.
Of course.
(They made the right choice
not to check.)
That's right.
We played it safe.
- We had enough.
- Team Asia...
will receive four dollars...
which brings its total
to 240 dollars.
(After the first
customs declaration process)
Team Customs won 60 dollars
which brings its total...
- to 160 dollars.
- 160 dollars.
Team America has 260 dollars.
- Let's move on to the next mission.
- Sure!
It wasn't enough
for us to take a chance.
(They pay their taxes
and head to the second mission.)
Are we supposed to untie these?
(What are all these
tangled ropes for?)
- I'm intrigued.
- This is the second mission.
Why don't you explain the rules?
Sorry?
Chief Ji will take command
for once.
- But I'm clueless.
- Finally.
- Chief Ji?
Chief Ji doesn't know the rules.
- He doesn't know the rules.
- Let me see.
Two from each team will compete.
- Two?
- Yes.
After fastening your hands tight,
you'll be looking for
the rope with the R sticker.
The rope you choose...
That's the sound of him giving up.
No one told me the rules.
- Got it.
- This is new to him.
Can you explain the rules instead?
Do you see these?
You will put these on your wrists.
- On both wrists?
- Yes.
There will be a space between them.
You will then choose one rope...
and keep pulling
until you reach the end.
- Gosh.
- Because they're all tangled.
No way.
He sure is different, isn't he?
- It's easy to understand.
- It sure is.
That's because Suk Jin
is too much of an oldie.
Suk Jin's still in the process
of learning.
(His training never ends.)
Shouldn't it be over by now?
- It's taking too long.
- He's still an intern.
He dreams of being
a show host one day.
You can learn something
from this moment.
This is why you must always listen.
I wasn't able to
because of my trip to the restroom.
I see.
Will two from each team
please step forward?
Ailee, who do people say
you resemble?
- Actress Kim Min Sun.
- Right.
And Madam Hwang.
(While talking about
Ailee's lookalikes...)
Yes, I know who that is.
(Gently)
Thank you in advance.
(Secretly)
Was that a dollar?
Thank you in advance.
What...
(Money is given discreetly.)
Our team would appreciate the win.
- How much did she give you?
- A dollar.
(It's to get on your good side.)
(Of course.)
- Seriously.
- Got it.
- It's our money, right?
- Right.
(Mr. Ji makes sure
he's a part of the cut.)
The other team...
- We were given a dollar.
- They gave us a dollar.
I don't know. It just came our way.
- Kwang Soo...
- Kwang Soo,
is it okay with the other team
giving us some money?
What don't you come over here?
- What? Who gave you what?
- Come over here.
We're just telling you
what happened.
- A dollar...
- We were given a dollar.
- What...
- The other team gave them a dollar.
- What?
- It was to bribe them...
- Why bother though?
- The customs agents...
We'll reconsider
if you give us two dollars.
- If you think about it...
- The yellow one seems better.
- There's no use.
- Okay, let's play the game then.
Fine, go ahead.
(Embarrassed)
(Would the lobbying
have made a difference?)
The yellow one seems better
since it stands out.
- All right.
- The ladies will go first.
Good luck!
- Get ready.
- You've got this.
- You can do this!
- So Min took off her shoes.
But I'll still probably
be the worst.
- They could get stomped on.
- Ready, get set...
(Start.)
Good job.
- Ailee is fast.
- You have to go into the knot.
- You don't have to be in a rush.
- You can move slowly here.
You have to untangle it.
- Do it slowly.
- Go inside. Go in between it.
Go slowly.
- It's so tangled.
- So Min, that's not right.
- That's right.
- You have to go inside.
- Go in. That's right.
- Hey!
You have to go inside the knot.
- Go in. That's right.
- Hey!
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo
goes into the knot.)
This is so heavy.
Ji Hyo, show us your skills.
She's calm. Ji Hyo's calm.
- Look at Ailee.
- You have to push.
Ji Hyo isn't even making a sound.
Ailee, you need to go inside.
- You have to go inside.
- Look at So Min.
- Where is So Min going?
- Where are you going, So Min?
- Hey, So Min!
- I can't go in for mine.
- Look at So Min.
You have to go inside.
- Where are you going, So Min?
- Hey, So Min!
So Min.
Why are you putting her
on your shoulders?
I have to go in.
Move. I have to go in.
(I have to go in.)
Hey, So Min...
What is she doing?
What's wrong with her?
(They're shocked at the tiger moth
bulldozer who only moves forward.)
- What's wrong with her?
- Hey.
- So Min.
- I have to go in.
I have to go in this way.
We have to go in together.
Please!
Ailee is strong.
- Ailee...
- Look at Ailee.
- Ailee is strong.
- She's really strong.
Ji Hyo is also...
- Hold on!
- Ji Hyo is also...
(Pushing)
Good job, Ailee!
- Look at Ailee.
- You have to push.
You guys are so mean!
- Ailee is good.
- Keep going, Ailee!
- The blue one.
- Where?
(Ailee moves forward
with her Korean-American power.)
Ailee is done!
I'm okay.
I don't care. I just need to get in.
- What are you saying, So Min?
- Are you doing okay?
I thought she was done!
Why are you just going in?
- What is she doing?
- What are you doing?
- You can't go in like that.
- I have to go in.
- What is she doing?
Why do you keep locking
yourself in?
Ji Hyo, tie So Min up.
- I have to go in.
- What?
So Min acts like she's good,
but she's really bad at it.
She acts like she's good,
- but she's really bad.
- Hold on!
- Ailee is good.
- What's the point if she's good?
- So Min needs to come out to win.
- Ailee.
Ji Hyo, this is a game that
we can't lose.
She's pretty much
at the starting point still.
- Where...
- We can't lose even if we want to.
You can go slowly.
You just need to go in and come out.
Ailee is almost out.
(Keep going, Ailee!)
- She's finally out.
- Look at Ailee.
(Ailee squeezes out
the last of her energy.)
You need to move faster!
(Yiren is almost out too.)
- She's finally out.
- Look at Ailee.
You need to move faster!
(Rolling)
Ailee.
You have to keep going.
Look at Ailee.
Why did you roll all of a sudden?
Take your leg out.
(She rolled forward out of nowhere
while trying to avoid Ailee.)
Gosh, I'm so tired.
This is...
Just take it out like this.
Take this part out.
- Hold on.
- She's on your team, So Min.
Ailee is on your team.
Go in now.
- No!
- You're there!
- Yes!
- Ailee's out.
- She's done.
Ailee's done.
Ailee's in first place.
Ailee is amazing.
- You guys just need to come out.
- I'm so tired!
- This is incredible!
- She's out.
(Yiren from Team Asia arrives next.)
- Hey!
- Come on!
Even though Ailee got out,
we can't lose.
What's going on?
Yiren can't go in.
So Min, what are you doing?
Hey, So Min!
It's So Min versus Ji Hyo.
- What is she doing?
- So Min!
Don't let her go.
You got it. Just go forward.
- So Min. You got it.
- Stop!
You just need to go under the gray.
Then you're done.
You're done.
(She does her best to crawl out.)
Don't worry about her.
- Hey!
- Come on!
You're so cool!
(Ji Hyo has one last knot.)
(So Min arrives.)
This was exhausting.
You were almost to the end.
You are able to escape it.
You guys were great.
(The customs agents
are happy for them.)
Let's give them a round of applause.
What kind of game is this?
This is a great cardio exercise.
(In Round 2, Team Asia just enjoyed
the cardio and lost.)
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
(Team America takes the final win!)
Kwang Soo, that wasn't right.
It wasn't going to work.
It all tangled here.
(Covered in sweat)
We lost.
This was funny.
Team America has won this round too.
- Team America.
- We lost everything.
- Captain America.
- Team Asia keeps losing.
- I know.
- What's going on?
This fight was... Gosh.
(The 2nd customs declaration
process is coming.)
(Team Asia will start off...)
(the 2nd customs declaration process
because they lost.)
I think they're going to
check ours this time.
- I agree. They'll check ours.
- Right?
They will.
Did 60 and 80 dollars get
taken out? Or...
One of each was taken out,
- but there's one of each left.
- One of each is left?
Chief Ji,
we have to be organized.
We have to go with our gut,
not be organized.
- We have to be organized.
- It's not our first day on the job.
We have to go with how we feel,
our gut.
They're here.
(Will they be able to catch them?)
- How much did you make?
We picked 80 dollars.
- 80 dollars?
- Yes.
Then they're telling the truth.
- They must be telling the truth.
- They could be.
We really got 80 dollars.
We got 80,
so we need to give them 40.
- Right.
- It's better not to check..
- Yiren.
- Yes?
How much did you get?
80 dollars.
(Stiff)
- She practiced this time.
- Her smile...
Her smile is awkward.
- I always smile like this.
- Her smile was always awkward.
She can't smile widely.
Yiren got some training in there.
- That's right.
- Mental training.
Why are you all standing
with your hands together?
"Mental training".
Did you commit a crime?
- You're right.
- Hey.
Hold on. Let's calculate.
- You're calculating something?
- Hold on.
- You're calculating?
- What's going on?
Please take a step to the side.
We analyze charts here.
You haven't gotten
anything right until now.
He majored in Statistics.
- Look. We have to consider this.
- Okay.
That is...
- Explain it to me.
- They gave us 40 and 20 dollars.
I'm the director.
You should take your hand off me.
My gosh. Just do it, you punk.
You're a junior...
- from my neighborhood.
- This is a bit...
Before you became my director,
you were my junior.
You guys are at work.
You're working right now.
You can't do this at work.
I can rest my arm
if it feels heavy.
- Even still.
- Continue.
You shouldn't do this.
Take a look.
When it's 50-50,
they wouldn't give us 40 dollars...
if they got 40 or 20 dollars.
- Right.
- Do you understand?
We have to be realistic and think
that they got 80 or 100 dollars.
- Right.
(They paid 40 dollars in tax.)
- Isn't that obvious?
- That's obvious.
Why are you saying the obvious?
Why bother analyzing
the charts then?
- Why bother? That's obvious.
- My gosh.
- Those are the rules.
- That's... It could be 100.
I'm telling you the probability
because of this.
He's saying the same thing again.
- Why are you repeating yourself?
- Why are you doing that?
You said the same thing four times.
At least change your tone of voice.
Did you major in Statistics?
No.
If you didn't, why are you speaking?
- Did you major in Statistics?
- If not, why are you speaking?
He didn't either.
Okay.
Ji Hyo is smiling so comfortably.
I'll ask you once again.
How much did you bring?
- 80 dollars.
- Stop lying!
(Stop lying!)
- What are you doing?
- How dare you...
- How dare you lie to me?
- How can...
What's wrong with
this customs agent?
How dare you lie to me?
- Should we open it?
- Should we open it or not?
Should we open it? Are you smiling?
- Are you smiling?
- Do we look funny to you?
- Should we open it or not?
Don't be like this
and just ask Jong Kook.
Jong Kook will tell you what to do.
Come here.
- Let's just go with our gut.
- Okay.
(Let's go with our gut.)
- Let's do this.
- Even if they lied...
- Let's mark it,
- Right.
- If it falls.
- and if it falls this way...
- Let's do it.
- If it falls, you can pass.
If you were going to do this,
why did you talk about statistics?
We did this often back in the day.
- Back in the day.
- It was "Go clubbing or go home."
We did this to decide
whether or not to go clubbing.
This is it.
If this side comes up we'll check,
and if this side comes up,
they can pass.
Ready, start.
(The last method chosen by
the two customs agents)
Ready, start.
(Will they inspect Team Asia,
or will they let them go?)
- We have to let them pass.
- It's best 2 out of 3.
(It's best 2 out of 3.)
- In the end...
- What was the point of this then?
Just decide.
- We should do it again.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
- We did this back then too.
- They've already decided.
- One more time.
They're both curious.
I'm so curious.
(The results of the second time
is also pass.)
- One more time.
- You said 2 out of three.
- It's until it's what they want.
We did this when
we wanted to go clubbing.
Hold on.
- The same answer keeps coming out.
- This is weird.
Just open it then!
Open it!
If you're going to open it
anyway, why are you doing this?
- Okay.
- Did you...
see their faces?
You should've studied their faces.
When you said you would open it,
Ji Hyo smiled.
- Really?
- Yes, she did.
- Then let's not open it.
- Let's not open it.
- We're not opening it.
- I can't...
stand to see them smile.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo's smile, Team Asia
passes through Customs.)
- They're not opening it, right?
- They decided against it.
They decided not to open it,
and the other team can go now.
(Did Team Asia win with
a psychological strategy?)
- Goodness.
- There was a low probability.
- You're right.
- We have to consider probability.
- Right.
It wasn't likely.
What are they doing?
(We're so excited!)
Did you do all of that
to get 10 dollars?
(Is this a ceremony for
successfully evading taxes?)
Okay.
Did you do all of that
to get 10 dollars?
- We kept a good poker face.
- You're right.
They're coming out.
You have to check their faces.
(It's Team America's turn for
the customs declaration process.)
Their aura is...
Did you choose well?
We picked 80 dollars,
so we will give you 40.
(Did they pick 80 dollars too?)
This is the most confusing number.
The most confusing number...
is 40 dollars.
80 dollars and 40 dollars.
- This is...
- This declaration...
- Hold on.
- This is for real.
- 80 dollars is...
- No.
- No, it's...
- You each chose this?
Didn't you choose 80 dollars before
and give us 40?
- No.
- One of us is lying.
They chose the last remaining
80 dollars?
In the previous round.
- We're telling you the truth.
- We are.
Was there another 80 dollars left?
There were 2 boxes each
for 20, 40, 60, 80, 100 dollars.
- There are 2 of each.
- There were 10.
- If they're telling the truth,
that means we had 100 dollars.
- Or...
- What?
Or maybe they're trying to trick us
because they have...
- plenty of money.
- No.
He's so funny.
If they got a small amount of money,
would they...
Is there a problem
if we paid a lot...
- when we chose a small amount?
- Out of the 10...
- What if we win like that?
- What?
- What if we pay a lot of taxes...
- It's the same thing.
even though we chose
a small amount?
We only know about our duties
as customs agents.
Right. That's why I'm asking.
(We only know about our duties
as customs agents.)
- It's not that.
- Stay quiet.
- Don't say anything.
- What's wrong with that?
- What will happen?
- Would we pay 40...
- when we chose 40?
- What if we chose a small amount...
- I'm the one in charge, so...
- Okay.
You said we paid a lot
despite choosing a small amount.
Look. We chose 40 dollars,
but we paid 40 dollars.
How would that benefit us?
We have to catch someone.
We haven't caught anyone
in 30 years.
(We haven't caught anyone
in 30 years.)
They are too timid.
Let's go.
Let's decide by this method.
- Let's go.
- There they go again.
- What was the point of analysis?
- We will decide by this method.
- They are too unprofessional.
Bring it here.
I want to check the boxes.
- If we check...
- It's the result we wanted.
(The slip finally allows them
to check the boxes.)
- We will open the boxes.
- Okay.
Both captains will open the boxes.
- Kwang Soo, go first.
- Okay.
Say it out loud in a cool way.
We paid up 40 dollars.
The amount we had gotten was...
(The customs agents didn't check
their box.)
- 100 dollars.
- Come on!
(Team Asia got
a box containing 100 dollars.)
For goodness' sake.
I said we should check.
Let's spin.
(They won 10 dollars
by paying 40 dollars in tax!)
- Yes!
- Okay.
- We did it.
- There is one more box to check.
- Okay.
Jong Kook, open the box.
As for us,
- we got 80 dollars twice in a row.
- Really?
Stop it!
(Team America
gets their box checked.)
Did you really get 80 dollars?
- Stop it.
- We actually didn't get 80 dollars.
- What?
- Did they get 100 dollars?
(They finally succeed to catch
the tax evaders.)
- So what's the result?
- We are leading.
- Are we leading?
- We did it after 30 years.
- We finally caught them.
- We caught them.
- We did it to be funny.
- That's right.
- We knew this would happen.
- We did it to be funny.
We did it to be funny.
- We caught the tax evaders.
- They suddenly moved up.
Now, the teams are neck-and-neck.
They did a good job.
- Team Customs has 310 dollars.
- Really?
(Team Customs has 310 dollars.)
Kwang Soo's Team Asia has
300 dollars.
(Team Asia has 300 dollars.)
Team America has 270 dollars.
- My goodness.
- It's okay.
- We are at number one.
- It's not too bad.
- We are at number 1.
- It's a difference of 10 dollars.
We can do it.
Let's move for the final mission.
- Yes.
- Okay!
(What will be the result
of the final race?)
This place is incredible.
- Is it an amusement park?
- This is incredible.
When else
would we visit a place like this?
This is what Running Man is about.
What... What is that?
- What? What is that?
- What is that?
It's Kwang Soo.
(The strange-looking thing is
Kwang Soo.)
Hey.
I was so startled.
- There are so many strange things.
- Right?
- How fascinating!
- What is that?
Is that his back hair?
- Hold on.
- What is that?
- Is that his back hair?
Wasn't he wearing a wig?
- It's his real hair.
- Really?
- I don't know what to do with them.
- They are so annoying.
- There are so many strange things.
If we go on, he will hit us.
We need to stop.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
It's time for the final race.
The final race is called
the Fiery Trade War.
(The Fiery Trade War)
All three teams
including Team Customs...
will participate
in this Name Tag Elimination.
Each team will wait
at their respective headquarters.
Two people from each team
will enter the race...
and participate
in Name Tag Elimination.
Thus, it will be 2-on-2-on-2.
When one member gets eliminated,
another one will enter the race.
(The rankings will be determined
by the order of total elimination.)
Since Team Customs doesn't have
enough members,
Jae Suk and Suk Jin will have
two lives each.
(The members of Team Customs
can be resurrected once.)
Throughout the set,
you will find slips that are
the size of your palm.
They are the trade blockade cards.
You can cover one-fourth
of a certain member's name tag...
if you find one.
That's important.
That means up to three fourth
of the adhesive can be covered.
That would be helpful.
In accordance with the rankings,
the teams will get
50, 30, or 10 dollars respectively.
We will also give you 10 dollars
for every name tag you remove.
(10 dollars will be given
for every name tag removed.)
- The name tags you remove.
- So it's an individual game.
- No, no. It's a team game.
- I see.
Don't be like that.
He wants to betray us.
- Seriously.
- No, no. I am sorry.
- He wants to be on his own.
- No, no.
- I am sorry. It's not like that.
- He always has that wish.
Please move to your headquarters.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's discuss things
once we get there.
- We are at a disadvantage.
- Strangely, I think we will win.
We are at a disadvantage.
Life is all about overcoming
the disadvantages.
We can't win against five people.
Why can't we do that?
There will only be two people
from each team.
- That's right.
- But other members are in the race.
We are in the race too.
For goodness' sake.
Why would you be so timid
when we are in the race too?
I will rip off
the female members' name tags.
(He makes up his mind
to attack the younger women.)
Three teams are entering, right?
It would be best...
to keep the other teams wondering...
if they should form an alliance.
If I enter the race first,
the other two teams will team up.
- That's right.
- Let's not focus on...
- placing first.
- Okay.
- Let's just avoid placing last.
- That's good.
The penalty involves staying behind
for an additional shoot.
- It's the worst.
- Really?
"Let's place second."
- All right.
- Okay.
- Let's place 2nd.
Okay.
(The order of participation
for each team)
The race starts.
(Team Customs, Team Asia,
Team America)
(Team Customs begins to move.)
There must be a card here.
(They look
for the trade blockade cards.)
(They find a trade blockade card
on the wall.)
It's on the wall.
Suk Jin, go get it.
(Chief Ji
attempts to get the card.)
- How do I do this?
- Give it a try.
My goodness.
- My goodness.
- I can't believe him.
Hey.
- What is up with this?
- Are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
(Jumping)
Why... Why can't you do it?
- It's working.
- Give it a try.
Give it a try.
(He makes a fuss
as if someone is hindering him.)
(Chief Ji continues
to fight against himself.)
My goodness.
What was that?
Move. Hold tight. I will do it.
- Hey.
- Move out of the way.
(Chief Ji is panting
when he hasn't done anything.)
- Do you think you can do it?
- Of course.
- Hey.
- You shouldn't jump there!
Do you think you can do it?
(He disrupts the rhythm.)
- I jumped because you did.
- Wait over there.
Can you do it?
(After shooing away Suk Jin,
he resumes jumping.)
(He catches it.)
(They finally get
the first trade blockade card.)
Jong Kook. Kim Jong Kook.
(One-fourth of Jong Kook's name tag
gets covered.)
I wish someone would do that to me.
I wish someone would think
that I am formidable.
It's okay. I will make sure
people don't touch my name tag.
- It should be here somewhere.
- It must be on the wall.
Do you see it?
It's over there.
(They find
another trade blockade card.)
Go up there.
I will be on the lookout.
For goodness' sake.
Go up there.
The lookout duty is important.
It's quite hard
to go up the climbing wall.
I can't do it.
Ji Jin Hee is good at it.
Why are you talking about
Ji Jin Hee so suddenly?
Ji Jin Hee is an expert.
(Jae Suk begins to climb up.)
I will support you.
Let go.
(There are two team members,)
(but Jae Suk seems to be doing
all the hard work.)
You got it. You are good.
(Suk Jin cheers him on soullessly.)
- That's good.
- Okay.
All right. Let's use it
on Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
(They cover
a portion of Kwang Soo's name tag.)
Kwang Soo, someone used
a trade blockade card on you.
- Me?
- Okay, okay.
Why did they use it on me
instead of Jong Kook?
You should go in there
and rip off their name tags.
You should do it.
I have never gotten
my name tag ripped off.
I don't know the taste of it.
- The taste.
- I don't know it.
- Thus, you should do it.
- It's a bit sweet.
It's tasty.
Listen.
Kwang Soo.
Okay, okay.
Two more trade blockade cards
have been used on you.
- Two?
- It's over.
It's over.
You should go in there last.
(Three parts of his name tag
get covered.)
- It will come off so easily.
- This is just wrong.
Do you know what's fascinating?
For the first time,
I can see the name tag on my back.
(For the first time,
I can see the name tag on my back.)
I can see the name tag on my back.
It's the 1st time in 10 years.
- Hold on.
- Jae Suk.
- Who used another card on me?
- Again?
What is going on?
Three cards have been used
on Jae Suk.
Finish him off.
Eliminate Jae Suk first.
What should I do?
Why is everyone attacking me?
It will come off if I flick it.
Suk Jin, come here.
We should look for more cards.
This is bad.
(They hurriedly try to find
more trade blockade cards.)
- Where is Suk Jin?
- He is here.
Word on the street is that
your name tag is about to come off.
(Team America's target is Jae Suk
with the flimsy name tag.)
(Seizing each other up)
- Let's go.
- Go on your way.
- We will go on our way too.
- Go ahead.
(At that moment)
(I will rip off
the female members' name tags.)
(Chief Ji gets to work.)
I will rip off
the female members' name tags.
Hold on.
(Team Customs makes
a sudden attack.)
Hold on.
Go, go! That's right!
Haha! Haha got caught!
- Who caught them?
- Both of them got caught.
- Suk Jin and Jae Suk.
- He is out. Oh, he isn't out yet.
This is good.
Go downstairs.
Ji Hyo and Yiren, go downstairs.
(Ji Hyo and Yiren try
to attack them from behind.)
Suk Jin, Ji Hyo is coming!
Ji Hyo.
(It suddenly becomes a 3-way match.)
Hold on.
- Rip it off!
(At that moment,)
(Ji Hyo reaches
for Jae Suk's flimsy name tag.)
Be careful.
Be careful!
- Rip it off!
- No!
(At that moment,)
(Haha spots a chance.)
(Ji Hyo is out.)
(Haha ripped off her name tag
while she was attacking Jae Suk.)
Ji Hyo is out.
(My goodness.)
Let's go. Kangnam, get ready.
- Another member will enter.
- Kangnam, go.
- Kangnam, hang in there.
- Get Jae Suk.
Be careful
because Haha could backstab you.
Where is Yiren?
- That's good.
- Our team is doing well.
Haha got one.
Haha.
Hold on.
(Everyone is confused
by the change of members.)
(Suk Jin attacks Ailee
for the 2nd time.)
What? Jae Suk!
(It's time for Suk Jin
to do his job!)
- What?
- Jae Suk!
All right, all right. Stop.
(Is she grabbing him by his collar?)
- All right, all right. Stop.
- Haha.
(Ailee takes on Suk Jin
with one hand.)
- All right, all right. Stop.
- Haha.
(While Suk Jin is restricting
Ailee,)
(Team Customs takes on Haha.)
- Hold on.
- Rip off his name tag!
- Hey, hey.
- Get Jae Suk.
- Rip off his name tag.
- We got Haha.
(While they're holding
each other...)
- Get Jae Suk.
- We got Haha.
(Yiren attacks from behind.)
(Ripping)
(What? Did Yiren get Suk Jin?)
- What was that?
- Okay!
(Yiren's quick and well-aimed attack
was successful.)
(Yiren beat a member
with 10 years of experience.)
Yiren, rip it off! Nice!
- Rip it off!
- Good job, Yiren.
Good job, Yiren.
(Team Asia gets 10 dollars,
and Suk Jin loses 1 life.)
Yiren.
Suk Jin, you need to enter
the headquarters for a second.
I can't believe him.
I just...
Why did you do something so useless?
(He tried to take on Ailee
and failed.)
- Let's get Jae Suk.
- I am sorry.
Let's get Jae Suk. I am serious.
- Let's get Jae Suk.
- I promise.
- I am serious. I promise.
- Okay, okay.
I promise.
(However,)
(he pretended to shake her hand
and attacked her!)
Haha, you are a piece of trash!
Seriously.
That little...
I can't believe him!
(The bitter taste of betrayal)
Haha! I can't believe you!
- You bully!
- This is...
This is how it is.
This is just ridiculous.
He ripped off Yiren's name tag.
Yiren is out.
- All right.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Hold on.
What are they doing?
- They need to take out Kangnam.
- Right this instant,
- they need to take out Kangnam.
- That's right.
I am disappointed.
"I am disappointed."
They need to get him no matter what.
Let's go. Let's rip off
Kangnam's name tag.
- Kangnam. He is alone.
- Let's get him while he is alone.
I need to run away.
(He runs away.)
(They begin to chase after him.)
(Kangnam runs as far as he can.)
It's a dead-end.
Kangnam, don't overexert yourself.
(Kangnam is cornered.)
(What should I do now?)
- You can push me and run away.
- What?
- Gosh.
- I have a suggestion.
Let's rip off Jae Suk's name tag.
Let's team up...
- and rip off Jae Suk's name tag.
- Do you mean it?
- Yes.
- Copy. Okay.
- Do you mean it?
- It's done.
- He's over there.
- Do you promise?
- We put a stamp.
- It's real.
- So it's real.
What? What?
(Se Chan attempts
to make a surprise attack.)
Come here! We need to be together.
Rip off Ailee's name tag.
Come on up.
Come on up. Hurry.
Go, go, go. There you go. Haha!
(He is super excited.)
Hold on. I got her.
I got him!
(Ailee uses her super Saiyan mode.)
Ailee is too strong!
(Haha and Kangnam
has a 1-on-1 match.)
Haha!
(They grab each other's name tag
at the same time.)
(Who will rip off
the name tag first?)
(Haha ripped it off first!)
I ripped it off!
I ripped it off first!
(After Ji Hyo and Yiren,
Kangnam is out!)
Haha, my name tag is
about to come off!
(Ailee is subduing Se Chan.)
(I am sorry
that I couldn't save you.)
(Trapping)
(A seatbelt to elimination)
It's too dangerous.
It's too dangerous. Hold on.
(Let's just go. It will be hard
to place 2nd.)
His name tag is barely hanging on.
Leave, you punk.
(Se Chan is out.)
Good work.
(Haha and Ailee are invincible.)
Ailee is doing all the work today.
She is so strong.
(Kangnam and Se Chan are out.)
- Kwang Soo, I am sorry.
- Did he get eliminated?
(Oh, my goodness.)
- Did he get eliminated already?
- He did.
Kwang Soo,
you are the only one left.
- They should have waited.
- But...
(His name tag is about to come off.)
Am I the only one left?
(They walk proudly.)
Ailee, look at the camera.
(Full of confidence)
Haha took out Se Chan as well.
(Haha took out Se Chan as well.)
- What is up with Haha today?
- Today,
we might just win.
Ailee!
(The invincible duo's ceremony)
- Team America!
- Yes!
(Team America is leading
by a landslide.)
- Se Chan and Kangnam are out.
- Are both of them out?
- In this situation,
- What should we do?
we need to take out the weak team.
You know what I mean, right?
- That way, we will place second.
- That's right.
We have no choice.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yes.
We don't need to team up
with the weak team.
When I am with Ailee,
I have no fear.
She isn't the type to get scared.
Ailee is too scary.
(Kwang Soo heads over
to the teams.)
Where are they? Where are they?
- Hold on.
- How is it going to be?
Shall we get rid of him?
Firstly...
You will attack us, right?
- We will attack Kwang Soo.
- Me?
I want to have
another member enter the race.
- Kwang Soo.
- Hurry up.
- Let's hurry up and take him out.
- All right. Let's go.
Hey, hey!
(They attack Suk Jin instead.)
(The invincible duo
goes after Suk Jin.)
- Hey!
- Jae Suk!
(He quickly comes back.)
My goodness.
(If he gets eliminated again,
he will be out for good.)
My goodness.
(Ailee ripped off
Suk Jin's name tag.)
- For goodness' sake.
- Suk Jin is out.
Why did you run off like that?
(They have earned 50 dollars
so far.)
For goodness' sake.
He doesn't help me in any way.
- For goodness' sake.
- He doesn't help me in any way.
Didn't you know
that they would backstab us?
- Ailee is so funny.
- Why did you run off?
- You should have taken cover.
- I am exhausted.
I am exhausted.
This is not fun, you guys.
(The viewer at the VIP seat
becomes excited.)
- What is it?
- They got Suk Jin!
- What?
Our team is the best.
Haha is really good.
He is good at betraying.
(Haha is good at betraying.)
Kwang Soo, let's place second.
(Kwang Soo runs away diligently.)
I am exhausted. I am exhausted.
This is not fun, you guys.
(Careful)
(Kwang Soo aims to make
a surprise attack.)
(The members don't know
what's going on.)
(Will Kwang Soo's surprise attack
be successful??)
(Attacking)
(He tries to figure out
what's going on.)
For goodness' sake.
(It was the next door.)
(Reality hits him hard.)
I almost messed it up.
My heart is beating so fast.
(My goodness.)
I just lost my fighting spirit.
(He carefully opens the door
and goes outside.)
(They are gone already.)
How many name tags did we remove?
Ailee, take me out.
It will give us 10 dollars.
There are too many members
who haven't gone yet.
(Team America hasn't replaced
a single member.)
Take me out.
- Okay.
- 10 dollars.
Let's switch.
Take them on with Ailee.
(Joon goes in and Haha goes out.)
Is Haha out? Is Haha out?
I should have ripped off
someone's name tag earlier.
Joon is waiting. Joon.
(Haha goes back to the headquarters,
and Ailee is left alone.)
(Kwang Soo appears before Ailee.)
(Upon seeing that Ailee was alone,)
(he charged toward her.)
- Hey! Hey!
- You need to go now.
- Do I need to go now?
Where is the exit?
Which way do I go?
(Kwang Soo takes on Ailee.)
(Laughing)
(Kwang Soo attacks
with desperation,)
(but Ailee just laughs.)
(Struggling)
(I give up.)
(He runs away without looking back.)
- He is running away.
Ailee is laughing at him.
(I feel bad for Kwang Soo.)
(He realizes that he is no match
and runs away at full speed.)
Ailee is alone now.
Her arms didn't come off.
(How could she be so strong?)
(He renews his resolution
and tries for the 2nd time.)
Joon, you need to hurry up.
Kwang Soo is coming again.
(Joon just got into the elevator.)
(It's a golden opportunity
for Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo does his best
to remove the name tag.)
The elevator is too slow.
(Ailee is losing strength.)
(At that moment,)
(Jae Suk surprises him...)
(and rips off the name tag.)
(While he was focused
on Ailee's name tag,)
Kwang Soo's name tag came off!
(Jae Suk quickly removed
his name tag.)
(But the fight has just begun!)
Hey!
(Joon finally arrives and joins in.)
(Jae Suk lies on the ground
and holds them off.)
Joon. Pull him up.
- Is Kwang Soo's name tag removed?
- Yes, it is.
(It seems too hard to hold off
a 2-on-1 attack.)
Rip it off.
(Jae Suk rips off her name tag
when she lets her guard down.)
- Your name tag has been removed.
- Is Ailee out?
It's okay. It is.
Ailee is out.
(Ailee did a great job,
and she's finally out.)
(Until the next member comes out,
they can hold out 1-on-1.)
Okay.
(Jae Suk has 3 trade blockade cards
on his back.)
(He secured 2nd place,)
(but he must rip off the name tag
and get the money to win.)
They're coming!
I'm alone, so...
They're coming! Behind you!
(Team America's next player is...)
- It's Jong Kook!
- What?
Hey. Get him!
Why did you tell him?
Why did you...
(Jae Suk's name tag is hanging
by a thread as he waits his chance.)
Hold on. Okay.
I got him.
I got him. Joon.
(When Jong Kook has him and Joon
is about to rip his name tag off...)
- Let go.
- Rip it off.
(He avoided him.)
Rip it off.
You have to rip it off.
Grab it and rip it off.
(His name tag gets ripped off.)
- Grab it and rip it off.
- This is...
Look at this.
Who put it on like this?
This is...
One more.
Jae Suk has another name tag.
Okay.
(Jae Suk put on
his second name tag.)
(He holds onto a bit of hope as
he rubs his name tag on the wall.)
I need Suk Jin to be here.
He's over there.
Just come over here.
It's not going to be better
if you think about it.
Just come here.
(I have to die after I make
at least 10 dollars.)
- I'll tell you one thing.
- What is it?
Give up hope.
(Destruction of hope)
I'm sorry, but...
- Wanting a dramatic ending is fine.
- But...
Give up hope.
(Booing)
- Be careful.
- What do you mean?
My gosh. I got you.
I got you.
(They've played this game
hundreds of times before,)
(but he looks quite pathetic today.)
Just come towards the back.
(However)
(Jae Suk isn't the type
to end things easily.)
(The risk taker, Jae Suk,
grabs onto Joon's name tag.)
(Whose name tag
will be ripped off first?)
That's right. We got it.
- We got it.
- Just come towards the back.
(There wasn't an unexpected twist.)
Jae Suk, you're out.
I ripped it off first.
We won by a hair.
(Team America won the race.)
Jae Suk.
(You lost, but you fought well.)
He ripped off Joon's name tag too.
What is this? What about me?
What about me?
You're the princess.
What is this?
- Princess.
- I'm feeling good today too.
I would've been able to just
rip everyone's name tags.
That's too bad.
I was so determined
I even changed my pants.
First off, Yiren left first...
- for her comeback showcase.
- Right.
After we gave you 10 dollars
for every name tag you ripped off...
and 50, 30, and 10 dollars
for 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place,
Team Customs,
who was in 1st place earlier,
has a total of 360 dollars.
- You have 360 dollars.
- We have 360 dollars?
- Yes, you do.
- Okay.
And Team Asia, who was in 2nd place,
has a total of 320 dollars.
- So we...
- We still...
- It's a 40 dollar difference.
- Right, 40 dollars.
Right. And Team America,
who was in last place...
- We got this.
- We won.
They have a total of 400 dollars.
(Team America has a total of
400 dollars.)
(Team America wins.)
Nobody was eliminated.
That's too bad.
- So we...
- Two people will get the penalty.
The penalty is...
Do you see the rail above us?
- Yes.
- It's a zip coaster.
You have to hang there
and fly down.
(Today's punishment
is a zip coaster...)
(which runs at a high speed
at a scary height.)
- I can't. I'm afraid of heights.
- There's no bottom. You hang there.
- It has no bottom?
- It doesn't. You just hang there.
- I tried it, and it's scary.
- What about a rope?
We'll draw lots for this one.
Please choose one.
It's two of us.
Choose whichever one you want.
- I'm nervous.
- I...
Is this for real?
Please show us what you chose
at the same time.
- One.
- Do you want to trade?
Two.
Three.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
Good luck.
It's all the way there?
Kids these days are intense.
It's really high.
Go up.
(Se Chan gets the penalty first.)
What is this?
(Completely nervous)
It's so high up.
This isn't right.
If you fall while you go down,
won't you break your butt?
(We filmed with safety equipment and
the instruction of a safety guard.)
Just sit back.
(Taking a deep breath)
(It's at a height where people feel
the most fear.)
Hold on. When will you push me?
Hold on.
Departing in 3, 2, 1.
Hold on!
(He exposes his ugliness.)
(It's faster than he expected.)
(Shaking)
It's shaking so much!
(Kangnam proceeds with
the penalty.)
It's so fast!
(Kangnam who was laughing
has disappeared.)
This is so fast.
(Thank you Joon Park, Kangnam,
Ailee, and Yiren for joining us.)
(Suk Jin!)
(Everyone in the Yoo family
has gathered in one place.)
(The eldest, Jae Suk's family)
(Kwang Soo, youngest son,
Jae Suk, eldest uncle)
(Haha, eldest son)
(The youngest, Jong Kook's family)
(Ji Hyo, eldest daughter-in-law,
Suk Jin, eldest son)
(Jong Kook, youngest Uncle)
(The youngest, Jong Kook's family)
(So Min, youngest daughter-in-law,
Se Chan, youngest son)
(The Yoo family...)
(has gathered together
for the holidays.)
(At the shocking and
rebellious setting,)
(the family has fallen apart.)
(At that moment, they receive
a message from their late grandpa.)
(Protect my eggs, but steal
one another's to make jeon.)
(A war for the inheritance...)
(between the two families regarding
Grandpa's memorial meal will start.)
(The war of nerves between
the two families get fiercer.)
(Which family will complete the meal
and get Grandpa's inheritance?)
(Chuseok Family Race,
The Yoo Family's Inheritance War)