(In a remote building)
It's a prison.
What is this place?
Gosh, it's a prison.
"Wisdom comes with age."
I've been imprisoned so many times
after I became a celebrity.
I know. I wear
this prison uniform too often.
We just got here,
but we're told to get in.
Are we getting in there?
Get in there, inmates.
Well...
Suk Jin is relieving himself now.
(Suk Jin is relieving himself now.)
Is he trying to take out
the toilet and escape again?
- This is nice though.
- Gosh, I'm in prison again.
What is this?
I guess we have to crack the
lock combination to get out of here.
- It's an escape room.
- Someone must be coming.
- It's an escape game.
- This is an escape room.
Let me see.
- What is this?
- This is nice.
There are extra prison uniforms.
I bet there will be someone else.
There are more uniforms.
(Letting out a sigh)
(She gets ready to sleep
as if she's home.)
So Min is planning something
as soon as she gets here.
Isn't it that only the head
of the cell can sleep?
Is this what we're supposed to do?
Can we lie down like that?
(Is this your first time
in a prison cell?)
Will you hurry, you brats?
This looks fun.
I like stuff like this.
You're the underling here
because you came late, Suk Jin.
Look.
"Wisdom comes with age."
Suk Jin, time comes with age.
Isn't it that
"Disease comes with age"?
Farsighted eyes.
If you need wisdom,
you should come to me.
I guess we have
some petty criminals here.
I know.
I can see a few.
I'm pretty sure
you're a petty criminal.
I'm not a petty criminal. I'm...
Oh, I see. You're
an economic criminal.
Is he a white-collar criminal?
- That sounds perfect for him.
- There was a misunderstanding.
I had to come here...
- Are you an economic criminal?
- due to some misunderstanding.
It's very unfortunate.
You know he's a gambler, right?
- What?
- He's a gambler.
- Oh, that's right.
- A gambler.
- I'm okay with that.
He's a member of a gang.
And he's his underling.
- I'm his henchman.
- His minion.
- "Minion"?
- A gangster and his minion.
If you took good care of it,
I wouldn't have come here.
- I'm sorry. It's my fault.
- My gosh.
What about you? Why are you...
(It was a crime of passion.)
It was a crime of passion.
A crime of passion?
Are you the woman?
It was a marriage fraud.
- A marriage fraud?
She says it was a marriage fraud.
Did you get caught
making fake trades?
No. I was charged
with housebreaking.
Housebreaking?
Why did you do that?
- Why?
- Why did you break in?
Did you break in to sleep in there?
- Housebreaking?
- I did it to steal something.
I had no idea. She broke in.
Why did you break in?
I'm a real estate fraud.
I didn't ask.
- The thing is...
- What about you, 2365?
I'm afraid I can't talk to you guys.
- It's like...
- He's a petty offender.
It's about sensitive social...
and international issues.
That's ridiculous.
It has something to do with trade...
- and stuff like that.
- Trade?
I guess you did something good.
- Is that why you're here?
- The thing is...
It's about trade deals
between countries...
Do you know stuff like that?
So you're a pickpocket.
- A pickpocket?
- I'm not a pickpocket.
I'm sure that's what he is.
A guy like him usually gets
beaten up in a movie.
"Let's crush him!"
- Then he cries.
- Do you know anything about WTO?
Why are we locked up
in here, by the way?
(The inmates are locked up
in here without knowing the reason.)
What?
- Someone's coming.
- Who's that?
Stay quiet.
He's the prison officer.
(A prison officer shows up.)
A prison guard?
- He's the guard.
- He's the prison officer.
- What?
- He is...
- My gosh.
- He's the guard.
Jae Suk, he's my junior comedian.
- Stay quiet.
- What?
It's not like you're here for fun.
He's the one who said
Se Chan can't paint a big picture.
That's right.
Oh, right. It's him.
- Is that him?
- That's the guy.
- It's Gyu Jin.
- Stay quiet!
- Gyu Jin.
- Right.
(Se Chan and Gyu Jin perform
together in "Comedy Big League".)
(You can't paint a big picture.)
(He told Se Chan the bitter truth.)
(A weekend variety show is no joke.)
(You seem ashamed.)
Keep quiet.
Se Chan who can't paint a big
picture should be extra careful.
- Me?
- Be careful.
Okay. I will.
So you told Se Chan that he can't
paint a big picture the other day.
- Yes, I did.
- Right.
"Yes, I did." He sounds
polite to Jae Suk.
- Wasn't it from the script?
- He's doing an interview.
Are you feeling nervous
around Jae Suk?
Can I stop playing my role here?
No, you can't.
He needs an interview.
You should talk to him.
I'll keep playing my character.
How would you describe Se Chan?
He always asks if I had a meal
whenever we meet.
And he offers good ideas
when we plan our skit.
He's very nice.
What about as your senior?
I don't think there's anything
I can learn from him.
(There's nothing
I can learn from him.)
- Then...
- Hey... Excuse me, Officer!
Forget everything.
What do you think of him...
from the perspective
of a viewer of Running Man?
As a viewer of Running Man...
For the cast members of
"Comedy Big League", Se Chan is...
- almost like Jae Suk.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Don't say... I mean, Officer.
- Do you really act that way?
- No.
He has absolute power over us.
- Really?
- Yes.
As a matter of fact,
he has a lot of experience.
He's their senior by many years.
But seeing him on Running Man,
he's almost just like me.
He's almost just like me.
(Se Chan's junior comedian realized
he was a big fish in a small pond.)
Hey, did you plan all this or what?
That guard is trying to
trample on me.
I mean, just like me,
- Of course.
- I can see anxiety in his eyes.
(Gyu Jin stopped being nervous
thanks to Se Chan.)
- I'm worried.
- Anyway, Officer.
- Yes?
- Is there any tip...
on how we should behave here?
Of course, you should
get along well with each other.
- When the newbies arrive,
- Yes.
you should give them
the clothes in these baskets.
- We'll give the uniforms to them?
- No wonder we have a changing room.
- Give them the uniforms,
- Yes.
- and inform them, okay?
- Understood.
Newbies, come on in
if you're ready.
- Who could they be?
- Are they here?
- Who are they?
- Are they coming in right away?
- Oh, my.
- Who are they?
- They're coming... What?
- I heard that actors...
- Young Min is one of them.
- Who?
- And Ji Seung Hyun too.
- Oh, they're...
- I know them.
- Ji Seung Hyun.
- Hello.
- Oh, my.
- Yong Ji, hi.
- Hello.
- Oh, my. Hello.
- Hello, hello.
Why did a lawyer come here?
- Why would a lawyer end up here?
- Hello.
(Ha Do Kwon, Ji Seung Hyun,
Kim Yong Ji, Kim Young Min)
First, please introduce yourself.
You're still wearing this when
"Hot Stove League" ended long ago.
(He made a big impression playing
Kang Doo Ki on "Hot Stove League".)
(Ha Do Kwon,
the great supporting actor)
(I am here...)
(on Running Man!)
"Hot Stove League" ended long ago.
Why are you still wearing it?
- He must be into his character.
- Exactly.
I'm still practicing baseball hard.
- Are you still practicing?
- Yes, I am.
He has such a great voice.
He has a great voice.
Actually, I think he looks like
a prison inmate...
- more than anyone of us.
- Exactly.
Right? You see, he looks like...
an inmate who fights against
Jong Kook over power.
(Ha Do Kwon Clan
versus Kim Jong Kook Clan)
That sounds plausible.
- He looks upset.
- Indeed.
I'm going to get just one person.
- Oh, gosh. Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook.
(He declared war fearlessly.)
- It's been a while...
- That's good.
- since Park Sung Woong came here.
- I like this.
Anyway, do you guys know...
- what your crimes are?
- Yes.
Why are you here?
I'm imprisoned because I make
people around me...
feel unnecessarily nervous
with a menacing face.
But your face looks cute.
I don't understand.
He doesn't look menacing.
Look how he chuckles.
- You know,
- He looks just cute.
- they already created tension.
- He says you look cute.
He looks just cute. Why?
- This is real.
- Yes.
But he lives in Anyang,
and I used to live
in Indeokwon, Anyang.
- Really?
- They suddenly became friends.
- Are you younger than Jong Kook?
- How old are you?
You're older than me.
You were born in 1976, right?
- I was born in 1977.
- Really?
Which school did you go to?
I went to school in Gangnam.
Oh, in Gangnam?
- Then...
- Then he wouldn't like you so much.
- His voice is so charming.
- He values his school ties.
- Any school in Anyang.
- He's here to live.
- That's why he's here.
- Jong Kook really is a big fan...
- of regionalism and school ties.
- Exactly.
- I'm a big fan.
- He likes people from his hometown.
- That's right.
- Also, he...
- majored in vocal music at SNU.
- Really?
(Wow. Really?)
- At Seoul National University?
- Oh, Seoul National University.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
- You see,
- Yes.
the point
we should pay attention to is...
- that he majored in vocal music.
- Oh, I see.
- Not the university.
- It's a great university.
- He feels different from us.
- His image has changed.
He feels completely different now.
Do Kwon, could you...
sing a song for us?
The weather was nice
on my way here.
- It was sunny.
- A song to sing on a day like this.
- "O Sole Mio" would be great.
- "O Sole Mio"?
- "O Sole Mio".
- I'll sing the climax.
He has such a great voice.
I've never seen anyone
who graduated from SNU.
(Do Kwon's powerful voice
made their jaws drop.)
(His gentle voice is
resonating in the prison.)
He's amazing.
(His enchanting voice
wins hearts of women.)
(The song reached its climax!)
This is the important part.
(Breathing out heavily)
(He has goosebumps.)
(The dignifying, mesmerizing voice)
- That was amazing.
- And it's early morning.
- In this early morning.
- I practiced a little.
(Even a singer is impressed too.)
It's so early. I bet his voice
hadn't even been warmed up.
- He's incredible.
- My gosh. That was...
- That was absolutely beautiful.
- Next up is...
Ji Seung Hyun.
Hi. I'm Ji Seung Hyun.
(He starred in "The Gentlemen of
Wolgyesu Tailor Shop" and "Wish".)
(He's the actor who created
the legendary scene from "Wish".)
(He's good at emotional scenes
as well as action scenes!)
(He starred in various works.)
(Ji Seung Hyun,
the popular scene-stealer)
- When I was in Busan,
- Yes.
I was the leader of a gang group
called "Monster".
- He still has that vibe.
- That's exactly how he spoke.
- He spoke like that in the movie.
Awesome.
- That was the name, right?
- Yes.
- I'm getting nervous.
- That's right.
- Seung Hyun has met...
- Yes.
Ji Hyo before. Right, Seung Hyun?
We both starred
in "Lovely Horribly".
- "Lovely Horribly".
- So did I.
- I also worked with So Min.
- So Min too?
- She can't remember that.
- In the drama, "Maids".
(Laughing)
- She didn't know.
- "Maids".
She said she had never
met him before.
Apologize to him now.
- I'm sorry.
- So Min.
How did you not know
when you starred in the same drama?
She sees only what she wants to see.
- I remember that now.
- She forgot about him.
However...
Seung Hyun, is this your first time
on a variety show?
I appeared on a variety show
that you hosted.
- On another channel.
- You mean, "Happy Together"?
- Hold on. He didn't remember that.
- Did you just realize that?
(He got caught.
He failed to get away with it.)
- You didn't remember that, right?
- Jae Suk.
- I don't think he remembered.
- He usually remembers his guests.
I can't believe you.
I mean, he took a photo with him
like they were friends.
(One Day Friendship Photo)
- He changed his hairstyle.
- You shouldn't be like this.
- He does look different though.
- I was so surprised.
Next up is...
Kim Yong Ji.
(She starred in "The King: Eternal
Monarch" and "Mr. Sunshine".)
(She pulled off a double role
in "The King: Eternal Monarch".)
(Kim Yong Ji, the rising star)
(She stayed by Yoo Yeon Seok's side
quietly in "Mr. Sunshine".)
(Her crime is enchanting the viewers
with her irresistible charms.)
- She looked like Japanese.
- Indeed.
- I thought she was Japanese.
- Are you...
actually fluent in Japanese?
- I can't speak Japanese.
- Not at all?
- It was just her role.
- I see.
- Have you ever studied overseas?
- Yes, I have.
- Where?
- Oh, my.
In Canada.
- That suits her.
- Really?
- No wonder.
- In Canada?
I have a feeling that
she's good at speaking English.
- She looks like a foreigner.
- We were talking about Japan.
Why did you say "No wonder"?
Based on what...
- What made you think that way?
- Just...
- Don't say anything.
- She looks like Canadian.
- Why would you ask that?
- Just let me continue.
- I was starting to interview her.
- "No wonder."
- Don't say anything.
- She looks like...
- "No wonder."
- I knew it. No wonder.
You like maple syrup, right?
- Yes, very much so.
- "No wonder."
(The magical comment,
"No wonder.")
- It suits her.
- In Canada.
"No wonder."
(Somehow, it feels like
she'll do well on the show.)
All right. Following Yong Ji,
our next guest is Kim Young Min.
(He starred in
"A World of Married Couple"...)
(and "Crash Landing on You".)
(He played the worst husband
in "A World of Married Couple".)
(His crime is stealing women's
hearts with his fatal charms.)
He played a husband
who cheats on his wife many times...
- in "A World of Married Couple".
- I see.
But in real life, he got married
after dating for five years,
and he's been married for 13 years.
(He's been married for 13 years.)
What kind of husband are you
in real life?
I'm an obedient husband.
- Really? You are?
- Yes.
Are you more like your character
in the drama or the way you are now?
He wouldn't be like that character.
(He burst out laughing.)
- Wouldn't it be weird if he was?
- That's not what I meant.
- Listen to me.
- What kind of question was that?
- That was a bad question.
- You're the worst.
- You can't just pretend like that.
- I mean, what do you even mean?
Trust me. He must have
a little of that side in him.
- That's ridiculous.
- That can't be true.
- How else could he do it so well?
- Suk Jin.
- Gosh. That's ridiculous.
- Think of what he did in the drama.
That was just acting.
By the way, there's a song
called "There She Is".
- I'm so happy you're here
- I know that song.
- When we go to karaoke,
- Yes.
- this song is always the highlight.
- We sing at the climax.
I guess you sing the song often.
Is it your favorite song?
Yes, it's one of my favorite songs.
I see. "There She Is" is very...
One day
- She left me
(He suddenly started dancing.)
(No one expected him
to start dancing.)
He's so cute. He's so adorable!
I'm happy, I'm happy,
I'm happy you're here
(He's dancing
like he's being electrocuted.)
(I love funny dances
for variety shows.)
I'm happy you're here
She's back, she's back,
she came back to me
(It's hard to breathe.)
That's his true color.
(After letting out his excitement
to the end,)
(he's back as the shy Young Min.)
- That's his true color.
- Which is?
This is the real him.
- I'm so scared.
- This is the real him.
- I disagree.
- No. Listen.
- It's his character in the drama.
- No way.
- He's faking it right now.
- Jae Suk, this is the real him.
I'm happy, I'm happy
- He acted so playful suddenly.
- He reminds me of Im Chang Jung.
(Young Min revealed
an unexpected side of him.)
- "Dance with Wolf".
- That was unexpected.
Okay. All right.
- We will...
- You have to change your clothes.
You should get changed.
Newbies, please go
and change your clothes.
(While the newbies are gone
to change clothes...)
- Stop it.
- What?
- I'll be back shortly.
- Where are you going?
You shouldn't do that. Come back.
You should immerse yourself
in your character. Come on in.
What is this for?
- To hang clothes.
- Hang your bag here.
Hang it there.
- No, I won't.
- Why?
- No, someone...
- Trust me.
There must be a thief...
- among the inmates.
- They're here.
There's a woman too.
- They are the newbies.
- Okay.
(We are newbies.)
Shall we begin?
- All of a sudden?
- Good. This is nice.
Do you want hazing or something?
- They are good.
- I'm immersed in my role.
There you go.
It's stirring up dust!
Why are you doing it
when there are people around?
We will work hard.
- They are different.
- They're good.
They're different indeed.
It looks perfect for him.
I know.
It looks like he's done this before.
It doesn't seem like his first day.
Do Kwon? Okay.
- Good.
- Well done.
- What are you doing here?
- Come here.
What are you doing?
- Why are you acting like the head?
- He wants to be the head.
Don't pretend like
you're the head here.
I just thought they were
being quite obedient.
All right. Are you done
changing your clothes?
Yes.
- You're back, Officer.
- He's back.
You come here quite often.
- What do we do now?
- We get to see you a lot.
There will be more
than that. You'll see.
- He's good.
- You guys look good in the uniform.
- Okay.
- And you look beautiful.
(You guys look good in the uniform.
And you look beautiful.)
So you know we're having
the work program at 3 p.m.
(The work program is...)
(scheduled for 3 p.m.)
(Running Prison Schedule)
(Work Program)
- What's that?
- What's the program for?
Here's a brief description
of the program.
You will have a tough time
so you won't commit a crime again.
Make sure to brace yourselves.
There's a rumor that Se Chan's mouth
became like that after the last one.
- I bet he got hit.
- Did I get hit in the mouth?
- He got hit in the head.
- You're doing this well.
- It was pulled out.
- That's because you got hit.
That's why it's sticking out.
You're just like me.
- Did he get hit as well?
- Don't you make fun of me.
Is that why?
It grazed his mouth.
(As they all burst into laughter,)
(he feels at ease.)
I got hit,
and you were just grazed.
- Yours is sticking out a lot.
- You're right.
- Don't even try to escape.
- Okay.
And... Hang on.
(The novice officer
picks up something.)
- What's that?
- What?
- This is...
- Do we have rules here?
- We have rules.
- Gosh, we have partners.
- What?
- These are the rules.
(Rules of Running Prison)
- "Each inmate has a partner."
- We have partners?
I guess that's why
we have numbers on here.
"Once my partner is eliminated,
I get eliminated as well."
I think we're already paired up
with partners.
- What's going on?
- So who's my partner?
- Do we not know that?
- We don't.
- The right one?
- My number is 22.
- I think it's the left one.
- My number is 10.
We are partners.
- All right.
- Is this it?
- It's a secret.
- Is it 02 "diarrhea"?
- I bet there's a secret.
- Are we partners?
It says 02 "diarrhea".
- I think you're my partner.
- No.
It says farsighted eyes.
You can have a chat later.
Keep quiet.
As you guys know, you should...
- I think you're my partner.
- No.
- It says farsighted eyes.
- What's your number?
- Farsighted eyes.
- All right then.
Let me see.
I'm speaking.
The officer has something to say.
- I'm still talking.
- You're number 10.
I'm sorry.
Se Chan! I'm reading my line.
Why is he yelling at me only?
- He wants to rely on you.
- He's yelling only at me.
I'm trying to help you
paint a big picture.
- Are you trying to help me?
- Sure.
Why are your eyes so red?
- That's because he couldn't sleep.
- He couldn't sleep last night.
His eyes are red because
he lacks sleep and feels nervous.
- I know what it is.
- So it's not makeup.
No. Gyu Jin, please continue.
This is a letter, but it doesn't
say a sender or a recipient.
I don't know why we have it here.
- What's that?
- Let me see.
(A mysterious letter
has arrived at the prison.)
- Mr. Yang.
- Me?
He's helping you to paint
a big picture now.
- It's for a big picture.
- Are you serious?
- Follow me.
- Am I becoming a star?
- It's for your big picture.
- What's going on?
What is he doing?
I'll make you a star. Come here.
What?
- You'll make me a star?
- You'll be a star.
- What's going on?
- He's going to be a star.
Can I leave, Jae Suk?
- Go.
- He just left.
- What now?
- Stay right there.
- Don't turn around.
- Maybe he'll get a mission.
- Maybe he'll be a spy.
- You're not supposed to look.
- What?
- I can see you from there.
Why do I have to be here?
I can see him from there.
- There must be something.
- This isn't a big picture.
He's helping you
paint a big picture.
There must be something.
I think something's going on.
I think there's something important.
- It says 34.
- Can I take a look?
Don't turn around.
Ji Hyo and So Min, come back here.
- What's this supposed to be?
- Don't look at this.
(He feels flustered
as the inmates approach him.)
- "731".
- Gosh, no.
It's not fake.
It's really dangerous.
Bring it back.
- Take it from her.
- It's real.
- What's wrong with her?
- Don't act spontaneously.
- Gyu Jin is flustered.
- What is she doing?
- What's wrong with her?
So Min.
He's a rookie comedian.
- Give it back to me.
- Don't act spontaneously.
- Give me that.
- What's wrong with her?
- Why is she being like this?
- It's not an imitation.
- Give me.
- Give it back to him.
Don't be so spontaneous.
He's a rookie comedian.
He'd be flustered.
He has his own script.
Why are you being like this?
Don't do anything weird.
Can we just do anything
we want here?
You can do anything freely.
- Hang on.
- Can I get my own way?
As So Min messed with him,
Do Kwon asked,
"Can we just do anything
we want here?"
(So this is what we do.)
- You can have your own way.
- I can? I see.
- A weekend variety show is no joke.
- I know. It's not easy.
I'll tell you what to do. Come here.
What is Se Chan doing there?
- What is Se Chan doing there?
- He's getting special treatment.
He's talking to Se Chan.
(The officer tells
Se Chan something.)
Are they talking
about something important?
To me? Only me?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(What are these two
talking about now?)
Okay. Please make me a star.
(He comes back after hearing
something from the officer.)
- You can do this.
- Okay.
Tell us what he said.
- This isn't what usually happens.
- I know.
Why is he speaking
openly about something?
Gosh, this is a good one.
- What is it?
- I tried to read his lips.
- He said, "Only me?"
- What is it?
Did he tell you how to escape?
What was it about?
I can't tell you. I don't want
to share it with everyone.
Did he tell you about your partner?
No. It wasn't about partners.
It was about a benefit.
- A benefit?
- What was the letter for?
- I don't know about the letter.
- He didn't hear about it.
Look at Gyu Jin. He's talking
to the writer with a smile on.
I bet things went well.
Congratulations.
I'm really happy for you.
They seem happy.
As soon as he leaves...
- The writer seems satisfied.
- They even slapped high-fives.
They even slapped high-fives.
She thinks he did a good job.
- They look excited.
- Now he's smiling.
Gyu Jin's hands were
soaked in sweat.
You made a successful debut
in Running Man.
It was successful.
You guys are inmates
of Running Prison.
And you all are paired up
with your partners.
Who's my partner?
As the rules say,
your fates are entwined.
You will receive
what your partner earns,
and once your partner is eliminated,
you get eliminated as well.
Really?
So this is how you will
find out your partners.
You will team up randomly
and play games in each round.
And the winning teams will get
the commissary money of 10 dollars.
And your partners will get
the same amount of money as well.
(The winning team and their partners
will get the same commissary money.)
If you're on the same team
with your partner,
you get another 10 dollars.
(If they team up with their partner,
they get another 10 dollars.)
- Now I understand how it goes.
- So it's important...
to make a good guess
and team up with my partner.
With the prize money you earned,
you can use the commissary.
There's a commissary.
But if your partner spends money,
the same amount will be
deducted from yours.
- So we share our destiny.
- Saving money is no good.
- We should spend the money.
- We should.
The amount of money
you earn or spend...
is not open to others.
You can find out your partner
using the amount.
Before the work program,
find out your partner...
and escape from the prison
while the officer is away.
For the work program, you should
follow the officer's lead.
Okay.
Stand in two lines.
(Officer Shin Gyu Jin guides the
inmates with a comfortable voice.)
- What's all this?
- Follow me.
(Officer Shin Gyu Jin guides the
inmates with a comfortable voice.)
The gym looks nice.
(There's a gym
in front of their cell.)
- I agree.
- It's a rugby ball.
I guess it's a rugby ball.
- Come here.
- Is it rugby?
This is Jae Suk's favorite game.
- I love watching the NFL.
- He really does.
I don't know the rules though.
- I'm glad that you brought it up.
- All right.
But this is a special rugby game.
- A special rugby game?
- The rules are different.
The men will have
their hands and feet tied up.
You'll tie up our hands and feet?
With your hands and feet tied up.
And the women will have
their feet tied up...
- Only the feet?
- for this game.
The men are supposed
to throw the ball to score.
And the women can
only score a touchdown.
If the men score a goal,
they get three points.
If the women score a touchdown,
they get 10 points.
10 points?
It's a big difference.
You'll be playing for 10 minutes.
And the team with the highest
points wins the game.
All the members
of the winning team...
and their partners will
get the prize money of 10 dollars.
- So I...
- How do we team up?
I've already divided
you guys into teams.
- You did?
- You did it already?
Sure.
I split you guys into teams
to make Se Chan a star.
- Really?
- I planned the whole thing.
He's painting
a big picture for Se Chan.
- Here's the first team.
- Okay.
Song Ji Hyo, Ha Do Kwon,
Ji Suk Jin, and Yang Se Chan.
(Song Ji Hyo, Ha Do Kwon,
Ji Suk Jin, and Yang Se Chan?)
- This is a big picture.
- Hang on. Is this a big picture?
Wait. I can't be a star this way.
This is... It's just not right.
I think he called my name.
(They don't seem to be able
to paint even a small picture.)
This isn't a big picture.
- Are we a team?
- We're a team.
You can lead the team
to paint a big picture.
I watched all your episodes.
You always get eliminated
in the beginning.
- That was a long time ago.
- Are you sure?
- I want to win the prize money.
- With our hands and feet tied up?
(Team Green:
Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, Se Chan, Do Kwon)
(Team Yellow: Jae Suk,
Kwang Soo, So Min, Seung Hyun)
(Team Blue: Jong Kook, Haha,
Young Min, Yong Ji)
- Ji Hyo, you can score 10 points.
- You should score.
- We should pass the ball to her.
- That's what we need to do.
If things don't go well,
we will have to throw the ball.
All right. Let's begin
the first game.
We can't do this
even for five minutes.
(Team Yellow versus Team Green)
- Go.
- You're so good.
- Grab it.
Pass the ball.
Gosh, they're fast.
It's okay. Take your time.
Over here.
(Team Green passes the ball
to create space.)
- That's right, Ji Hyo. Go.
- Okay.
We're so good at this.
We have to block Ji Hyo.
Block her.
(They've got Ji Hyo covered.)
You have to go there. Suk Jin.
Slowly.
I'll block them.
Pass. Pass it to Do Kwon.
No. Why are you passing it to me?
- No.
- Give it to Do Kwon.
(It gets passed to Do Kwon.)
No.
(He spots Ji Hyo in the corner.)
Give it back to me.
- Touch the ground!
(He successfully passes to Ji Hyo.)
- Yes!
(They get a touchdown!)
(It's an unexpectedly amazing
scene created by the weakest team.)
Who was it? They are really good.
We're so good. This is crazy.
Gosh, that was incredible.
Hey.
We can do it like that too.
Let's start in the middle.
In the middle.
(But...)
(He speeds towards the goalpost.)
You said we were starting
in the middle.
(He plays the game like the infamous
petty criminal he is.)
(You said we were starting
in the middle.)
(Hitting)
(After a scuffle...)
- Wait. Hold on.
- Okay!
Are we allowed to hit people?
So Min, you need to come inside
no matter what.
Ji Hyo, we're allowed to hit people.
- That's three points.
- Ji Hyo.
- We're allowed to hit people?
- Careful!
There's someone behind you.
(After Kwang Soo's scuffle,)
(Tiger Moth So Min
starts getting physical.)
(At that moment,
Ji Hyo gets through an opening.)
- Ji Hyo!
- Touch the ground!
(He passes to Ji Hyo right away.)
(They get a touchdown.)
(She caught that?)
Hey. We're in trouble.
Touchdown!
- Amazing.
- Nice.
This is really like
American football.
- Really?
- Yes.
We have to focus. We do.
- We're on a roll right now!
- Let's go!
This is really like
American football.
- Defense.
- Running back, quarterback.
(He passes to So Min.)
- Touch the ground!
- Hurry up!
(What's this?)
- No!
- You're scaring me.
(She caught the ball, so why is she
rolling on the ground?)
What are you doing?
(Tiger Moth So Min is more concerned
about fighting than getting points.)
(Hitting)
(Tiger Moth So Min is more concerned
about fighting than getting points.)
No!
What are you doing?
(After a pointless scuffle,)
(she tries to get a touchdown.)
(If the ball crosses the line while
she holds it, it's a touchdown.)
(She let go of the ball.)
No, she didn't get a point.
(Unfortunately,
she failed to score.)
You should've run. That's too bad.
- So Min! Hey, So Min!
- Hey!
We were almost there.
(Team Green is
on the offense again.)
Ji Hyo. Block Ji Hyo.
(They invoke the ace alert.)
(Kwang Soo marks her.)
Hey. Hold on. Hey! Let go!
Gosh, you're crazy!
(He grabs her by the shirt
and carries her away.)
(Regardless of where the ball is,
his defense is grabbing her shirt.)
We got this. Seung Hyun, go up.
Do it! Pass it!
(They have 2 minutes left.)
(Se Chan interferes
right in front of him.)
(Hitting)
(It's a dignified play by someone
who loves American football.)
- Gosh.
- Hey. Seung Hyun!
Do Kwon! Pass it to Ji Hyo!
(He passes the package to Ji Hyo.)
Ji Hyo.
Touch the ground! Nice.
They're no match for us.
(The final score is 3 to 30.
Team Green wins.)
They're so good.
Pass it.
We need to practice.
- Are you practicing?
- We could've done better.
(They're warming up by passing
the ball.)
- She's good at catching.
- Gosh, she is.
- She's good.
- Okay.
I won't look at the ball
for this round.
I won't look at the ball,
and I'll focus on Jong Kook.
If you get the ball, run straight.
I'll grab onto Jong Kook.
- If I get the ball...
- This is Do Kwon's plan.
If I get the ball,
- I'll pass it, then grab Jong Kook.
- Okay.
Jong Kook, Do Kwon is determined
to get you this round.
- He just declared war on you.
- Are they finally facing off?
Right? Look at your arms.
- Why are you determined to get me?
- You will see...
- the ultimate scuffle.
- Do Kwon finally gets his chance.
Jong Kook, you have to be
on your toes this round.
Okay. Ready.
(Kim Jong Kook's Team Blue versus
Ha Do Kwon's Team Green)
(Ha Do Kwon said he's here
to get just one person.)
(And that chance has come.)
(What is the result of this match?)
You're fast!
(The second round starts.)
(Do Kwon runs ferociously
as soon as the game starts.)
(He misses on his 1st collision.)
Where should I pass to?
(They finally go up
against each other.)
(They begin tackling each other
without thinking about the ball.)
Where is it?
(Hitting)
(What?)
Do Kwon... Do Kwon...
Do Kwon. You took a fall.
He's scared.
Do Kwon, don't get scared.
Over there.
Do Kwon is so funny.
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not.
I think Do Kwon is sulking.
- Okay.
- Ready.
Do Kwon, get over here.
Start.
(We acknowledge his determination.
He's still covering Jong Kook.)
(He's not looking at the ball.
He's only looking at Jong Kook.)
Come in. Haha.
We have to do it fast.
(They're having a fierce battle
for the ball on Team Blue's side.)
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin!
(The weakest link, Suk Jin,
grabs the ball.)
Suk Jin.
- Take it.
- Let go!
Suk Jin.
Young Min is terrible at games.
(He's practically a paper doll.)
Why don't you have any strength?
(After the scuffle, Team Green
successfully steals the ball.)
Give it to Ji Hyo.
(He safely passes the ball
to Ha Do Kwon.)
- You.
- Ji Hyo, get in there.
(He can get a point if he can
get it in there,)
(but a 2nd collision occurs.)
(Flying)
(I feel bad for him.)
- It went in.
Ha Do Kwon.
(He exchanged his health
for the point.)
I feel like I've been in
a car accident.
(I feel like I've been in
a car accident.)
(The game starts again
with Team Blue on defense.)
Block him.
(He arrives in front of
the goal post in no time.)
- Block him. What are you doing?
- Block him.
- It's okay.
- What are you doing?
Okay. You have to get it in.
Come here.
(He's biding his time to pass to
Yong Ji to get 10 points.)
- Shoot.
- You have to get it in.
(He's still covering Jong Kook.)
- Good.
- Shoot.
(Because they have a tight defense,
it's hard to pass.)
His facial expression is so cheeky.
(He passes it to Haha.)
- Do Kwon, you have to get it in.
- I'm Do Kwon.
(Se Chan blocks it.)
- Hey.
- Do Kwon!
I'm Do Kwon.
(The ball rolls towards
Jong Kook and Do Kwon.)
(These two people go after the ball
at the same time.)
(After a complete loss,
a second match was created.)
(What are the results this time?)
(Jong Kook fell!)
Do Kwon.
Block Jong Kook. Do Kwon.
(He knocks over Jong Kook
and pushes the ball away.)
Pass it to Ji Hyo.
(He passes the ball to Ji Hyo.)
Nice.
Did she get it in?
(I finally did it!)
(I acknowledge his tenacity.)
He's so cool!
- Goodness.
- Did she get it in?
(Thanks to Do Kwon's pass,
Team Green gets 10 points.)
My goodness.
(They're out of energy.)
Do Kwon, don't get tired. Get up!
Cover Jong Kook some more!
- He's not a human being.
- Let's go!
He's not a human being.
- Do Kwon is amazing.
- Let's go.
I'm going to die here.
- That's right.
- Come in.
- Come here.
- Over here.
We're open here.
(Shouting)
(The tiger is out of control.)
Does this make sense?
- Does this make sense?
- Okay. We got it.
Can't we end this?
Let's end the game.
We still have that left.
With a score of 40 to 13,
Team Kim Yong Ji wins.
Okay.
That was good.
- You should've protected him.
- Hold on.
My mic fell out.
My mic keeps falling out.
Hold on. Jong Kook's mic.
(Fixing his mic)
Hold on. It fell into the crack.
Why did you send a woman?
(Why did you send a woman?)
It fell into the crack!
Send a guy.
(There was a reason why Jong Kook
was asking for a male staff member.)
It fell right into the crack!
- Just leave it!
- Did you put it in there?
I put it there,
and it went right in.
Can you put my mic back in?
(Jong Kook's mic fell out,
and he asked Kwang Soo for help.)
There's no one here.
(Putting it in)
Okay. We have to get it in.
(That is the secret behind
the crack.)
Why did you do that?
You're out of your mind.
Gosh, that was funny.
The team that came in 1st place...
and will receive 10 dollars each
in commissary money is...
Team Kim Yong Ji.
- We won?
- No way.
Each member of Team Kim Yong Ji
will receive 10 dollars.
Their partners will also receive
10 dollars.
The correctional officer will
show you the amount you have...
- in your commissary account.
- If your partner won?
Yes. You will get money too.
(You can guess your partner by
seeing how much money you have.)
Okay. Good job everyone.
I will give you your statement for
your commissary account.
Ji Suk Jin.
(They each receive a statement
for their commissary account.)
After you see how much money
you have,
- you have to return it to me. Yes.
- We do?
- Song Ji Hyo.
- I hope I have some money.
Yang Se Chan.
(He's checking his statement.)
I'm sure they have 10 dollars each.
- Right. We do.
- You do.
We have some money.
(The partners of these 4 members
have also received 10 dollars.)
(Yong Ji, who won,
is checking her statement.)
(Account statement, Kim Yong Ji,
Received reward, Total: 20 dollars)
(She got an additional 10 dollars?)
Please give it back to me
after you've checked it.
Here you go, sir.
Sure. Thank you.
(Her partner must be either
Jong Kook, Haha, or Young Min.)
Can one have 20 dollars?
If one of them is your partner?
Having 20 dollars
will sure be reassuring.
(That means...)
(Yong Ji and Jong Kook
are partners.)
(Seung Hyun and Jae Suk
received 10 dollars despite losing.)
(Haha and Young Min are paired
with either Seung Hyun or Jae Suk.)
There is a bit of time
until your next work program,
- so you'll get some free time.
- Free time?
With the money you earned,
you can buy anything...
- from the commissary.
- All right.
If you didn't earn any money,
- you can use the time to chat.
- All right.
- Enjoy your free time then.
- Sure.
Thank you!
Let's eat!
(They can buy the items
or put them on their tab.)
(However, what one partner spends,
the other partner will lose out on.)
Hello.
- Thank you.
- Gosh.
- What's the price range?
- I should eat something.
They're all a dollar.
- A dollar?
- A dollar.
This will be two dollars.
I'll take it from
your commissary money.
(Even in prison, you need to eat.)
Can you buy me one?
- Maybe a drink.
- I don't have any money.
- Put it on your tab.
- If I could, I would.
Put it on your tab.
Buy me one since we met
for the first time today.
- What?
- You're the older one here.
I don't have any money.
I'll return the favor
once I'm reborn as your junior.
Whoever earned money without winning
will have definitely spent it.
It's not just about
being physically strong.
- You need to be clever too.
- I don't know.
Is it important
to find your partner though?
- Of course.
- Why?
Because you'll be eliminated
if your partner is eliminated.
I feel bad for whomever
Suk Jin's partner is.
- He even told our guest...
- You're all clueless though.
- not to listen to the rules.
- Why not?
Because you'll get the hang of it
as the games go on.
Do Kwon responded by saying that's
why he always gets eliminated.
(Do Kwon proves that
he's a true fan of Running Man.)
I just hope that I'm not
partnered with Suk Jin.
(In a low voice)
(His inner voice came shooting out.)
(But just then...)
(Se Chan secretly
calls Kwang Soo over.)
Did you receive any money?
What? No.
Whose on your team?
(They exchange their opinions
in a low voice.)
Jae Suk and...
I mean, who do you think
you're partnered with?
Do you have no idea?
I didn't receive any money.
- Did you buy this though?
- Yes.
- I spent a dollar.
- What?
I spent a dollar.
Is that what you
called me over for?
Or was it just to steal
some of my chips?
(Se Chan was only after
Kwang Soo's chips.)
(He played me.)
What...
- Jae Suk...
- But I was just sitting there.
- Unbelievable.
- Jae Suk, hold on.
I was just sitting there when he...
(Kwang Soo tells on Se Chan.)
I thought he was going
to tell me a secret,
but it was to steal my chips.
That's what he called me over for.
You can't eat our snacks
without saying anything.
Yes, you at least ate half of mine.
Okay, I'll tell you.
- Can I enjoy this then?
- Sure, go ahead.
(Se Chan gobbles down the chips.)
So what was it?
(He tells Jae Suk
and Kwang Soo something.)
Se Chan!
Why are you ostracizing us
and only speaking to them?
- Let us know too.
- It's just Jae Suk.
What were you talking about?
(What did Se Chan say
to Jae Suk and Kwang Soo?)
Do Kwon hasn't said a word to you...
after colliding with you earlier.
Are you upset about something?
I didn't know
it would be this violent.
(He's upset.)
(The violent plays upset him.)
- Do Kwon...
- I mean...
You're pouting.
- Jong Kook's not a bad person.
- I said this at the beginning,
but there's something
cute about him.
He's quite adorable.
Didn't he enter saying,
"I'm going to get just one person"?
(Where did his confidence go?)
After one game,
I learned that I was wrong.
(And after the second game...)
All right,
so the second work program is over.
Suk Jin, Se Chan, Ji Hyo,
and Jong Kook earn 10 dollars each.
(Yong Ji also earns 10 dollars
thanks to her partner Jong Kook.)
(Do Kwon, So Min, and Kwang Soo
win money despite losing.)
(Their partners
are in the winning team.)
Officer!
(The inmates are one step closer
to guessing who their partners are.)
I'm sure you're all hungry.
- I'm starving.
- Of course.
- Gosh.
- It's already time for lunch.
A decent "lunsh"
has been prepared for you.
He said "lunsh" instead of lunch.
- Lunch time!
- Stack the food on your plate...
and sit at the table
after taking off your shoes.
- Thank you.
- Gyu Jin.
- Take off your shoes!
- You're doing...
a great job today.
Sorry?
(So Min hands the rookie officer
a sausage.)
Is it for me?
I hope we get along.
My gosh. Can you believe
this lunch we're having?
Everything looks delicious.
Thank you for the meal.
(Don't forget what I gave you.)
(Thanks, I'll enjoy it.)
(A dirty but warm deal was made.)
- Who were you gesturing to?
- No one.
Do Kwon,
why don't you sit with Jong Kook?
- Over here.
- Have a seat over here.
(It's obvious
who has seniority now.)
Have you suddenly lost weight?
You look gaunt for some reason.
You can't consider him
as a normal human being.
I think I've got the hang of it now.
He has the hang of it now.
He's clever too.
I had no idea he'd dodge
out of the way like that.
(The salad was dropped.)
(Variety show rookies
Young Min and Seung Hyun...)
(are the last to get their food.)
- It's not as far as you think.
- Exactly.
(A delicious lunch served
at Running Prison)
Does the food suit your palate?
Yes!
Since you followed my orders
so well earlier,
I'm going to...
give three of you...
a chance to win five dollars
for your commissary account.
(Tempting)
I can't give it away, so...
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- I'm trying to explain something.
- I needed more soup.
We're not here
to have a seminar, you know.
Does that mean
I can't have more soup?
Are you here on vacation?
- Please stay seated.
- Sure.
He seems like a true prison guard.
- Let me explain once again.
- He does.
I can't give it away for free.
(The game to acquire more money
in the commissary account)
I'll give it to whomever
says the answer that satisfies me.
So here we go.
Name a celebrity that I resemble.
(A celebrity
that Officer Shin resembles!)
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer!
Se Chan?
- Let me answer.
- Can I go ahead?
Just say the answer.
Park Seo Jun!
- Nicely done.
- Let me answer.
- Are you kidding me?
Jung Woo Sung!
- Nicely done.
- Let me answer.
V of BTS.
- That's a dangerous one.
- Shouldn't I have said that?
- His fans will be mad.
- You're out to get me, aren't you?
Let me answer.
- Yes, Jae Suk?
- Jung Chan Sung.
- Who?
- Jung Chan Sung, the Korean zombie.
(The resemblance is clear.)
Nicely done!
What a treat.
I thought that Jung Woo Sung
had walked in.
You look a lot like Jung Chan Sung.
Thank you for that.
The three of you...
won't receive the money right now.
It will be put into
your commissary account.
- Great. Thank you.
- All right.
- Please enjoy your meal.
- Hold on.
Will our partners
receive the money too?
- Yes.
- Our partners too?
Really?
- They'll also receive the money.
- Our partners too.
Just remember that my partner
will receive the money.
After you enjoy your lunch,
you will participate
in some more work programs.
Another officer
will be with you for those,
- so be nice to him too.
- Are you going somewhere?
Are you off to "Comedy Big League"?
- That's not it.
- There's a rehearsal.
I'll see you later.
(He suddenly bows.)
I'll show you how it's done there.
- What are you doing?
- Just let me be.
- Gyu Jin, take care.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Bye!
- You did well today!
- Bye.
- I hope you come by often.
(Enjoy the sausage.)
Everybody.
Here's your transaction history.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
(Their account balances
have been delivered.)
Haha.
(They're somewhat aware
of their partners now.)
This round made things clear.
Are you close to
guessing your partner?
Totally.
Really?
(Haha and Seung Hyun
make eye-contact.)
Are you close to
guessing your partner?
- Totally.
- Really?
Two dollars?
(Seung Hyun makes his way to Haha.)
Why didn't you come to me sooner?
(Why didn't you come to me sooner?)
(The two share the exact
same transaction report.)
(Haha and Seung Hyun are partners.)
(The partners are revealed
one by one.)
(The pairs)
- Okay!
- Thanks for the meal.
I'm still not sure,
but I've narrowed it down.
My partner will sure know
that we're partners.
You can go by the commissary
for one last time.
But we had a lot to eat.
(It's their last chance
to spend their money.)
We'll be notified
if the money is spent.
(Young Min heads inside first.)
I...
I am here to paint a big picture.
(He's here to paint a big picture?)
- That will be 10 dollars.
- I'll take it.
Did you buy the water?
Your name tag is different.
Really?
A different name tag?
- What?
- Why?
- Hold on.
- What?
- What is this?
- What is it?
- What's going on?
- Let me see.
- Why is his different?
What is this?
It's in gold letters.
(Young Min has a gold name tag?)
(Young Min came back
with a gold name tag.)
What is this though?
(A few hours ago)
- Se Chan?
- He must be helping you out.
(Officer Shin called Se Chan aside.)
If you go into the commissary...
and say "I am here to paint
a big picture" to the lady inside,
- she'll give you a Defense Right.
- To me?
If you say to the lady...
that you're here to paint
a big picture,
- she'll give you a Defense Right.
- What's that?
You'll have a chance
to save yourself from elimination.
You'll be given an advantage...
if you say you're here
to paint a big picture.
- Are you saying that...
- Really?
What is this?
(The gold name tag
is the Defense Right.)
Can it be bought?
Is he irrelevant in the game now?
How did he know that though?
- What is this?
- The Defense Right.
I'll buy one.
- What?
- What are you here to buy?
Me? I'm here for the shield.
That's not something we sell here.
Then is it Defense Right?
We don't sell that either.
Defense...
Next.
What? What was that?
What's on sale?
(Whispering)
Do I need to say something?
Go first.
- I don't have the money.
- Go first.
(She chants a spell she learned
from Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo fooled her.)
(She gave the chorus of a song
from the Goryeo Dynasty.)
- Is it wrong?
- Pretend you don't know anything.
It's wrong! It's wrong!
What is it?
- Did she say "Yalli yalli"?
- "Yalli yalli yallashong".
Yong Ji, what did you say?
(Listening attentively)
- That's not it.
- Tell me what it is.
(Another inmate asks
for information.)
Open, sesame.
I am serious. I am serious.
Why won't you believe me?
That's the code.
(Do Kwon was watching
without a word.)
(He gets up stealthily
and heads over to the commissary.)
Open, sesame. Open, sesame.
(Showing a cute dance)
(He completes the dance
as he has eavesdropped.)
- What would you like?
- What?
The name tag.
I heard that was the code.
(Bursting into laughter)
Open, sesame. Open, sesame.
(He tries the dance again.)
Is it wrong?
(My goodness.)
What was that?
You looked very cute.
Hurry up and tell me.
I am here to paint a big picture.
Oh, okay.
(Jong Kook learns the code
through Ji Hyo.)
I am here to paint a big picture.
- Would you buy it for 10 dollars?
- Yes.
What did you say?
(He shares the method
with his partner, Yong Ji.)
That was the code.
I am here to paint a big picture.
- Would you buy it for 10 dollars?
- Yes.
(After Jong Kook and Yong Ji)
I am here to paint a big picture.
My goodness. He bought it as well.
(Young Min, Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
and Yong Ji get the gold name tag.)
If there are no prison guards,
can't we escape?
(After Gyu Jin,
no prison guards are in sight.)
(Running Prison Schedule)
(Before the work program,)
(they must escape
with their partners.)
(They must take their chance
when the prison guards are gone.)
(A prison guard left
for the transfer of duties.)
Are there no prison guards now?
(This is the perfect opportunity!)
Let's go out and lock the door.
- Go out.
- Is there something in here?
What could this be?
(The mysterious letter in the drawer
must be something important.)
That safe must be important.
I saw a prison guard
put an envelope in it.
There must be a direction.
- Inside the drawer?
- Yes.
- This is... Hold on.
- How do you open it?
Does anyone know the combination?
Why would anyone tell you
so easily?
(No one knows
the combination of the lock.)
There must be a hint inside.
(Somewhere in the prison...)
(lies a clue.)
(Wisdom comes with age.)
(Running Prison Schedule)
There must be a direction.
- Inside the drawer?
- Yes.
(Jae Suk stares at the sign
on the wall.)
Maybe this means something.
"Wisdom comes with age."
(Wisdom comes with age.)
- It has to mean something.
- Right?
Wisdom. How old is wisdom?
- Jae Suk.
(Wisdom comes with age?)
- Right?
- Jae Suk. The order of age.
- That's right.
- Let's stand in that order.
- This is...
- The number.
Maybe something will happen
if we stand in the right order.
- Let's stand in that order.
- Shall I move?
This is...
Maybe something will happen
if we stand in the right order.
- Let's stand in the order of age.
- Let's try standing that way.
- Let's stand.
- Young Min is next.
- Okay.
- Who is next?
- Third.
- Am I next?
- Jong Kook comes next.
- Me.
- No, no.
- I'm next to Jae Suk.
Hurry up and come inside.
Let's line up in the order of age.
- Line up. We need to escape.
- Come here.
We are one today.
3, 4.
Blue...
(22BL 2366, 10UE 2371,
02DRA 2365, 34WER 2361)
- Blue.
- Blue drawer.
Blue drawer.
(22BL 2366, 10UE 2371,
02DRA 2365, 34WER 2361)
(Blue drawer)
- Blue drawer.
Line up.
"Com".
- "Combination".
Come here.
- Tell us from there.
- Come here.
- Cover your tag.
- This is the right way.
- That's right.
"Combination".
We have "combination".
- Eight.
- Hurry up and tell us!
I won't let you out
unless you tell us the combination.
We figured it out! Come over here.
- Put your hands down. Attention.
- Cover your tag.
- Do you want to rot in there?
(The four youngest members' numbers
make up the combination.)
- Cover your tag.
- Come on out.
- Combination.
- 8.
- Come on out.
These brats. Jong Kook, get them.
Come on out.
I didn't do anything.
You know I didn't do anything.
The youngest members.
- The four youngest members.
- Their numbers are the combination.
- 8412.
- 84...
- 84.
Let's read it together.
- Okay. Let's read it together.
- Okay.
All of us can survive
if we escape together.
- That's what I am saying.
- It will be war after we read this.
It's open.
(The blue drawer opens.)
- It's open.
- How did you figure this out?
- Let's read it together.
- Hold on.
- For goodness' sake.
- It's open.
- Come in.
- Calm down.
We can survive together.
- Let's escape together.
- We can survive together.
- Calm down.
- This is it.
(Will there be a method of escape
in the letter?)
We will learn how we can escape.
Read it out loud.
- Read it out loud.
- It's our last hope.
What? Boss!
There's a boss?
What does that mean?
"Boss, to help with your escape,"
"I sent a gang member to the prison.
Did the two of you meet?"
(The recipient of the letter is
the boss inside the prison.)
There is a gang member.
"For your escape, I prepared
a truck behind the gray wall."
"It will leave at 3 p.m. sharp."
"In case this letter gets found,"
"I hid the details
in the cell phone in the prison."
"Please find it
and check the text message."
- Inside the prison?
- Where is the cell phone hidden?
We need to check the text message.
(The boss and the gang member
aren't partners.)
Boss, if you and your partner get
on the truck, the gang will win.
If you get eliminated,
the gang member we sent
will become the next boss.
If that gang member
and his or her partner escape,
the gang will win.
If other inmates escape,
they will receive the prize...
and the gang will lose.
Please don't forget that.
(If regular inmates escape,
the gang will lose.)
"The work program that starts
at 3 p.m. is known to be brutal."
"So please escape safely
without getting eliminated."
Who is the boss?
It must be Young Min!
He was the first one to put on
the gold name tag. How did he know?
You're right. He had the information
all by himself.
There is no other way
Young Min found out about it.
Did you tell him?
I told Suk Jin,
but I didn't tell Young Min.
How did he know?
- His partner must have told him.
- That's right.
Come on out.
It's time for a cleanup.
(The cleanup begins.)
Okay.
I will clean up when I am asked.
Here.
I will take something that suits me.
(Among them are
a boss and a gang member.)
I think we are partners.
- We are...
- What?
Are we?
- I think so.
- We could be partners.
I think we are partners.
Why are Young Min and Jae Suk
so close?
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
They could be partners, right?
I am certain
Yong Ji and Jong Kook...
are partners.
I see my partner over there.
(Current Partners)
The weather is hot.
We need to clean up.
(Current Partners)
(The man everyone is suspicious of,
Young Min...)
(as well as Do Kwon,
pretend to clean up diligently.)
(But everyone is
thinking about escaping.)
My partner is Seung Hyun.
(Blowing)
My partner is Haha.
I don't know what to do next.
What's certain is
that Young Min is the boss.
I think the boss is...
one of the guests.
It's either Yong Ji...
(He suspects the guests.)
Young Min.
It's either Yong Ji or Young Min.
Young Min must be...
either the boss or gang member.
(Young Min is
under a lot of suspicions.)
(He suddenly utters a sound.)
(He shrugs.)
There must be people...
who realized that we are partners.
Without letting them know,
I will reveal my partner's name.
As for the identity of the boss,
I have an idea.
(Does Young Min know
who the boss is?)
With my partner,
I will find the cell phone...
and check the text message.
Then I will help...
the boss escape.
(Then I will help the boss escape.)
(That means...)
You are the gang member
who entered the prison...
to help the boss escape.
I see.
(The gang member, Kim Young Min)
Before 3 p.m.,
you must make the boss
and his or her partner escape...
in order to bring victory
to the gang.
You can find out who the boss is...
by the mark on the sole of the shoe.
- The boss?
- Yes.
(He must find the boss first!)
(During mealtime earlier)
(They took off their shoes
and had a meal.)
(Dropping)
(The gang member checked the shoes
by pretending to drop something.)
(While everyone was focused on
winning the commissary money)
(Dropping)
(He checked other shoes
by using the same method.)
(On someone's shoes,)
(Young Min spotted the mark.)
Boss gave me a sign a few times.
I hope my clumsy concept...
worked to my advantage.
(He suddenly changes.)
I will look for my partner first.
(He goes in search of Jae Suk.)
The boss is...
(The boss is...)
Really?
(Surprised)
- How do you know?
- I am the gang member.
You are the gang member?
(Since Jae Suk
is the gang member's partner,)
Really?
(he can escape the penalty
only if the gang wins.)
For goodness' sake.
Firstly...
(Jae Suk needs to work
for the victory of the gang.)
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin is looking
for his partner.)
I should hurry up and meet
Doo Kwan.
(Who is Doo Kwan?)
(He is Do Kwon, not Doo Kwan.)
Go to the side.
(He spots Doo Kwan,
also known as Do Kwon.)
- Do Kwon.
- Hello.
Suk Jin.
- You are my partner, right?
- Of course.
All right.
You used 3 dollars
and I used 2 dollars.
That's right.
At first, it was a dollar.
- That's right. A dollar.
- Yes.
- And at the end...
- Five dollars came in last.
Then it was 10 dollars.
Who do you think is the boss?
- The boss?
- Yes.
It's likely that Se Chan is
the boss.
- Right?
- He keeps messing up the games.
Wasn't he too forward
from the start?
- You are right.
- Right?
I think he definitely has a mission.
- Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
- Yes?
So Min, I have something to say.
The cell phone isn't the only thing
we need to find.
We need to find the fake wall.
What?
(There was important information
in the letter.)
(A truck for two
behind the fake wall)
We must get on the truck
behind the fake wall.
- That's right.
- Thus,
we need to find the fake wall
and stop anyone from getting on.
People will get on it
as soon as they find it.
How about the cell phone?
That's another thing that is hidden.
We need to find the cell phone...
as well as the fake wall.
There is the fake wall?
That's right.
Even in "Prison Break",
the character escapes
within the prison.
I think I can break most walls.
- That's not how it works.
- No?
- No.
- This could be a fake wall too.
- If I use my strength...
- How will we escape?
How will we escape?
- We need to think of a way.
- Yes.
All right.
(Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
are looking for a hint.)
It's cool in here.
Hold on. The air conditioner is on
in this room.
- What?
- Okay.
What is it?
(Jae Suk spots something.)
No one is here.
(They check and see
if they are alone.)
(What did Jae Suk find?)
I won't tell a soul. I mean it.
- Really?
- Yes.
I can't trust you.
I won't tell a soul for real.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Jae Suk takes a leap of faith...)
What is it?
(and shares information
with Kwang Soo.)
Here.
(Handing over)
Air conditioner...
It's an air conditioner user manual.
Why in the world did you hide
an air conditioner user manual?
You are the one who came.
I came because you seemed to be
hiding something.
- For goodness' sake.
(Jae Suk stars on Running Man
in order to make fun of Kwang Soo.)
I need to carry this around.
- Why did you pick something so big?
- I don't know.
There must be a use
for this cleaning tool.
- What?
- There must be a use.
There must be something here.
(What?
There must be something here.)
(When they come down the stairs,
a long hallway stretches on.)
What is this place?
It's just a cool hallway.
That door leads to the stairs.
- This door?
- Yes.
(Halting)
What? It's the fake wall!
(No way.)
It's the fake wall!
It's the fake wall. What is this?
(Behind the fake gray wall...)
(awaits the two-person truck.)
(It will leave at 3 p.m.)
(If they break the fake wall,
they can escape.)
(She begins to break the fake wall.)
Let's break it down.
(Kicking)
(It's harder than they expected!)
What is it?
It's the fake wall!
- What is it?
- The fake wall.
- What?
Really? Can we break it?
- I don't know. Try breaking it.
- Try breaking it.
We kicked it,
but we couldn't break it.
- It's too hard.
- Maybe this isn't it.
- Could it be a real wall?
- This is...
Would it be okay to kick it?
- Is it supposed to be this strong?
- Seriously.
- Hold on.
- We should call Jong Kook over.
Would it be okay
to work on different spots?
(They manually take off
the styrofoam.)
(Will they break it before 3 p.m?)
- What?
- Is it working?
Hold on. Let's do this instead.
Hold on.
I will stick it in.
- It's working.
- Okay. It's working.
Hold on. I will stick it in there.
- One...
- Ji Hyo, you are out.
(All of a sudden)
- One...
- Ji Hyo, you are out.
- For goodness' sake.
- Go, Ji Hyo.
Whose partner were you?
This is driving me crazy.
(Only Kwang Soo's bag
and name tag remain.)
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are out.
Why?
(When Kwang Soo got eliminated,
his partner got eliminated as well.)
Are Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo out?
- Really?
- Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are out.
- They are out.
- Really?
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo were partners.
Be quiet. Be quiet.
- Are you okay?
- Here.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo's elimination
makes them work faster.)
Move out of the way.
(The fake wall finally breaks!)
We got it.
(Once they get on the truck,
they will escape the prison.)
(They move past the fake wall.)
What?
There is a lock.
(The door is locked.)
What?
(The fake wall wasn't the end!)
Hang on. What is this?
What is this?
(Other inmates come running
upon hearing the noise.)
What's here?
- No, no.
- Let's see.
- What is up with them?
- One of you is the boss, right?
No.
- What is this?
- There is a truck.
There is a truck.
Beyond that door?
But we need a lock combination.
I know. There is a lock.
Can't we go outside?
No, we can't.
We need to open the lock.
- We need to open the lock.
- The two of you are a team.
- That's why you are together.
- So Min followed me.
The two of you are a team.
Why else would you be together?
Be careful, So Min!
(Seung Hyun suddenly attacks.)
(Se Chan runs over belatedly,)
(but So Min's name tag
got ripped off already.)
- What happens now?
- The two of you are a team, right?
The two of you are a team, right?
(If Se Chan was the boss,
Young Min will be the next boss.)
So Min.
(Was Se Chan the boss?)
So Min and Se Chan are out.
What?
(They simply got eliminated.)
(Se Chan wasn't the boss!)
- This is good news.
- So Min, I am sorry.
- My goodness.
- Seung Hyun.
- I am sorry.
- You didn't know.
No.
(Who is the boss
among the 8 remaining inmates?)
(The gang member, Jae Suk)
(Suk Jin, Do Kwon, Haha,
Seung Hyun, Jong Kook, and Yong Ji)
Let's get out of here.
We can't find a way.
What could be the combination?
We need to find the cell phone to
find out the combination. Let's go.
(The clue must be
in the cell phone.)
(At that moment,)
(Seung Hyun approaches the lock.)
Five digits.
(He checks
that the combination has 5 digits.)
The combination has five digits.
Where is Seung Hyun?
Why isn't he coming?
(Haha approaches the fake wall.)
Seung Hyun.
What is going on?
What's his role?
He must have a role.
Why else would he disappear?
- He disappeared so suddenly.
- He must have a role.
It's strange, right?
(Seung Hyun is looking
for something.)
(Why is he suddenly going around
on his own?)
Here comes Young Min.
We need to keep our distance.
He is the most suspicious.
- Be careful.
- Did you find a hint?
- No.
Don't come near. Keep your distance.
- Okay.
- Where have you been so busily?
I followed the others to there
and came back.
To there? Why did you follow them?
To find my partner.
Oh, your partner?
Haven't you found your partner yet?
Your partner or the boss?
(She gets to the point.)
- My partner.
- Something isn't right.
(Meanwhile, Haha)
Seung Hyun.
(He finally sees Seung Hyun again.)
I have been looking for it.
I finally found it.
Hey, I like you.
- I like you too.
- I am serious.
But you are the boss!
(But you are the boss!)
(What?)
(After Haha's comment,)
(his face became scary.)
(Is Ji Seung Hyun the boss
as Haha predicted?)
- Where have you been?
- Jae Suk.
- I've been looking for you.
He's slowly approaching you.
(Jae Suk already knows
that Young Min is a gang member.)
He's acting weird.
Are the two of you partners?
Hang on.
- They're partners.
- Are they?
- We're partners, but...
What? Wait.
- Wait. She's a fake.
- You two are partners?
That cleaner is a fake.
Hold on. That cleaner looks like...
We've seen her.
(She's the same person
they saw at the commissary.)
That cleaner is a fake.
(Jong Kook instinctively sensed
that the cleaner has something.)
Is there something in here?
Oh, yes. That's it.
(They found something!)
I was right.
- One name tag...
- "Name Tag..."
He and Jae Suk... What's going on?
(The other inmates are walking
towards the lobby.)
We can't let anyone else see this.
- What should we do?
- What is it?
- "A five-digit number..."
- Where should we find it?
(What secret could be written
in the document?)
(Name Tag Collection Log)
(A 5-digit number was given
in return for 5 name tags.)
(Could the 5-digit number
they traded 5 name tags for...)
(be the combination for the lock?)
"Name tags"?
Oh, I get it. So the name tags...
(They can't understand
as they haven't seen the lock yet.)
- Who has it then?
- It says...
Ma'am, this is a hint, right?
Excuse me. May I?
- No, you can't.
- I can check it, right?
- Can we all see it?
- Let me see it too.
No. You shouldn't have
let them see it.
Take a look.
(Only Haha who knows it's
a five-digit code understood.)
- Is this a hint?
- What does it mean?
There's someone who knows
the combination.
- For now...
- Excuse me.
- Did anyone find the cell phone?
- Come here.
- Haha.
- Yes?
I found the phone.
- What?
- I found it.
- Where?
- You shouldn't have said that.
- Sorry?
- Why did you say that here?
Just tell us. How did you find it?
- Gosh. I'm so stupid.
- How did he...
- Just tell us. How did you find it?
- Is that it?
Is that the phone?
Why did you show it to them? Why?
- What happens now?
- We can check it.
- Let's do that.
- I already did.
- Let's go in.
Close the door.
- Lock the door.
- Come on in.
- Show us.
- Why?
(What? Don't close the door!)
- What's going on?
- Why are you here?
(The cameraman who was filming
Do Kwon couldn't go in.)
- Why are we here?
- You should let the cameraman in.
(You should let the cameraman in.)
Hey!
How could you leave the cameraman
alone out here?
- 1 camera is enough for us.
- It's okay. We have 1 camera.
- In my opinion...
- You should let the cameraman in.
- This is...
- Just read it already.
I can't seem to
organize my thoughts.
(What hint could they find
on the phone?)
(Boss! Go through the gray wall,
and you'll find the final exit.)
(You need a five-digit code
to open it, which you can get...)
(by giving the cleaning lady
five name tags. I hope you succeed.)
We have to get them eliminated.
(They'll get the combination if they
give the cleaner five name tags.)
What are you doing?
- Why?
- I'll just let the cameraman in.
What about me?
(She's trying to go into the room.)
I was the one who opened it.
Let me know too.
- Yong Ji, I'm sorry.
- We can't.
- But I...
- I'm really sorry. Please leave.
I'm sorry. I think I can tell you
everything later.
That's weird.
(They stopped Yong Ji
and let only the cameramen in.)
(What?)
(Jae Suk successfully go in
like a loach.)
That's not fair.
They all went in.
Come on in.
You're the last one to come in.
Gosh, seriously.
What just happened? Why would he...
You're the last one to come in.
- Can't we share it with others?
- No, never.
- Let me see. Or tell me.
- Who are you to hold that?
My team found it.
- You should show us too.
- Okay. Just a second.
- Let us see it with you.
- You shouldn't do that.
- It says...
- Gosh. No.
(Screaming)
- No.
- What's going on?
- Go away.
- I'm almost done. Hang in there.
I said, no.
(30 minutes ago, he said he wanted
to do something before escaping.)
I want to beat Jong Kook.
Don't try that.
If you do, you won't be able to
escape today.
I really want to get back at him
while I'm in here.
(Do Kwon was adamant
although Suk Jin dissuaded him.)
Jong Kook will find his partner.
So I'm going to aim at his partner.
That's a good idea.
Stop it. I'm serious.
- Stop it.
- I'm almost done.
- Hang in there.
- I said, no.
(At that moment, he took off
her name tag.)
- Defense.
- He wants to...
- get Jong Kook.
- I have the Defense Right.
- You have the Defense Right?
- Yes.
Yes, she has the Defense Right.
I attacked her
just to get Jong Kook.
- But she has the Defense Right.
- Are you all right?
Excuse me. It's me, Young Min.
- We can never let him in.
- Of course.
He's the last one we want to let in.
Excuse me. It's me, Young Min.
(He's asking them
to let him in politely.)
- We can never let him in.
- Of course.
(But they won't let him in.)
What is he doing?
Jae Suk.
(The politest gang member
in the world)
Jae Suk.
That's not it. I should go.
(Yong Ji who used her Defense Right
left to put on a regular name tag.)
- Okay. That was crazy.
- Do Kwon is so energetic.
Do Kwon is...
(All he wants is
to defeat Jong Kook.)
He doesn't care about anything else.
- His son told him to beat him.
- I think so.
- 1, 2, 3, 4... We need name tags...
- Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook was trying to figure out
how to get the lock combination.)
Yes?
Oh, I get it.
I get it.
- I get it now.
- I got eliminated once.
Really? Who did that?
Was it Young Min?
- It was Do Kwon.
- Do Kwon?
- Do Kwon.
(I can't believe he did that
while I was gone.)
I think I know what it means.
Is it here?
So how many name tags do we need?
We need 5 name tags
for a 5-digit combination.
What do you think that means?
- We should take off name tags.
- Correct.
Let's go take off some name tags.
We need to submit five name tags...
to get the combination and get out.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk was
kicked out too.)
Who is it?
What is it?
I'm just wondering
what the text says.
Well...
I'm sorry,
but we can't tell you that.
Let's get out of this room for now.
- It turns out...
- You guys are mean.
- This is...
- Come on out for now.
- I think he has the Defense Right.
- Can you show me the phone?
(Share the information with me.)
- I'll give it back to you.
- Hurry.
(While following them,)
(Young Min came back.)
- What is it?
- Boss, you should escape.
(He suddenly changed
his attitude.)
(Did he just
called Suk Jin "Boss"?)
What are you talking about?
(What is going on?)
- You see...
- Is he the boss?
I heard you're the boss.
(I heard you're the boss.)
Yes. But don't tell anyone else.
Why did you say that here?
(Yes. But don't tell anyone else.
Why did you say that here?)
(Was Suk Jin the boss?)
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
- Seeing that I'm here alone,
- I guess I have a solo mission.
- Correct.
You're taking a risk.
- We mustered up the courage.
- I see.
- You are...
- Yes.
the boss of Petty Gang...
(Suk Jin is
the boss of Petty Gang.)
who is currently imprisoned.
I see.
Among the new inmates
whom you will meet tomorrow,
there will be a gang member
who will come to get you out.
And I don't know who that is?
- The identity of the gang member...
- Yes.
is closely related to the letters,
"Janbaripa", as in Petty Gang.
I advise you to take a careful look
around the commissary...
and the cafeteria
that will be open tomorrow.
(He can find out if he focuses on
"Janbaripa"?)
(Boss Big Nose searched items in
the commissary whenever he could.)
(He checked a drink
whose name has "jan" in it.)
(Number two was marked
with a circle.)
(Next, he found a snack
with "ba" in its name.)
(And he found number three.)
Can I eat the whole box or just one?
(He skillfully found "ri"
after that.)
(He found number 7.)
(Boss Big Nose suspected green onion
which is "pa" in Korean.)
(He rummaged through the green onion
for a while.)
(He found number 1.)
(So he found
the 4-digit number, 2371.)
(It matched the inmate number
of Young Min, the gang member.)
(Tapping)
(Boss!)
(With his outstanding observation
ability and concentration,)
(he won over Do Kwon
as well as the gang member.)
You and I are the stars
of this episode.
Why? This will be over
when we get out.
(However, Kwang Soo who was
with them was a problem.)
(He got eliminated only 10 minutes
after the race began.)
(Young Min was impressed
by the boss' drive.)
Kwang Soo.
You should paint a big picture.
(What is he talking about?)
That's not it.
- We're off.
- Take care of him, please.
Let's go. Let's go, Young Min.
(Now that we've taken care of him,
let's go, Boss.)
(Kwang Soo was taken aback
as he was eliminated too early.)
But...
- Are you three on the same team?
- No.
(Who are the three of you?)
What is this?
(Giggling)
You just have to
go to your cell quietly.
(Teasing)
(Spitting)
(Kwang Soo got angry
and tried to get back at them.)
(Darn it. I'm so angry.)
(Kwang Soo's attack
made them laugh.)
- This is the fun of doing this.
- Also...
- He's the gang member.
- You should know that.
(They strengthened their unity
while eliminating others.)
- The 4 of us are on the same side.
(Including Jae Suk,
we're a family.)
- Go and tell Jae Suk.
- Right. Tell him.
(Suk Jin, the boss of Petty Gang,
worked actively in secret.)
What's that?
I am the boss of Petty Gang.
(Rubbing)
(Warning: It can be erased easily.)
- Look here. It says I'm the boss.
- You really are...
- You are the boss of Petty Gang.
- And here.
- You really are in the Petty Gang.
- He's...
the gang member.
He's the gang member,
- and I'm the boss.
- It seems to suit him.
He looks petty, you know.
However, I'm worried
because I think...
- that Yong Ji brought Jong Kook.
- Exactly.
I think Jong Kook came with her.
What should we do?
Jong Kook must be...
- furious right now.
- Of course, he's furious.
Because Do Kwon eliminated
his partner.
I guess we receive something
if we submit name tags.
(Anyway, they need five name tags
to escape the prison.)
I have a lot.
He took off the name tag
of everyone he saw.
I lost the name tag I got,
so I went back to find it.
(Here's why Do Kwon was
collecting the name tags.)
I'll take this as a souvenir
because my son likes you.
(For his children,)
(he collected the name tags
one by one.)
I'll give these to my children.
I'll take this home too.
(So he collected four name tags.)
I'm glad I collected them.
He's so lucky.
He collected the name tags
for his daughter.
(His love for his children brought
him a great achievement.)
He wouldn't stop collecting
name tags.
I collected them only for my kids.
I had no idea.
- You're lying.
- It's true.
You're lucky.
Do Kwon is a unique case.
He's really unique.
I'm glad I collected them.
"You need 5 name tags
for a 5-digit combination.
We are one short.
If it's too hard to get one,
we can rip off one of our own
name tags and get it.
In the end?
Of course. We'll go together.
Gosh, this punk is really smart.
(He's too immersed in his role
as a gang boss.)
- Why did you call me a punk?
- I was in character.
Gang bosses usually say
things like that.
(Do you think
you're a real gang boss?)
Gang bosses usually say
things like that.
I thought I was in a movie
because they're here with us.
(Boss Big Nose is overly immersed as
he hasn't been a boss in a while.)
Here.
If you get eliminated,
I get eliminated too.
(It's time to go outside.)
If I get eliminated,
I'll leave it to you.
- Then...
- Please take care of it.
(At that moment...)
It's been a while since we did this.
We have to rip off
Do Kwon's name tag.
We have to rip off Do Kwon's
name tag...
and take all of his things.
(They're looking for the four people
who are hiding.)
They're not here.
They must've gone over there.
(At that moment...)
- They were in there!
- Who?
Jong Kook. You're angry, aren't you?
(They appear in complete fear
befitting of the Petty Gang.)
I'm quite angry.
How many of you are there?
Is it the three of you?
Do Kwon is hiding in here.
- Why is he hiding? Why?
- He said he's scared.
- He set up a barricade.
- Do Kwon...
said that he's afraid of you.
That's why.
Do Kwon, come out.
He said he's going to apologize.
Do Kwon, why did you do it?
I wanted the gold name tag.
That name tag.
Please forgive me. I was rash.
Do you only have
one name tag right now?
- I only have one.
- Really?
- I'm really sorry, but can we...
- In a circle.
- Can we talk in a wider space?
- Let's stand in a circle.
- Why?
- Pardon?
If we go to a wider space,
it would be easier to film.
- It would be easier to get beat.
- No.
Go first, and the four of us
will discuss it.
- Because...
- Honestly...
- If we don't have each other...
- Do Kwon has a ton of name tags.
- Give us a hint.
- He already has a lot.
- He has a bunch of name tags.
- We're going to talk.
Why did they band together?
We have to go and do it.
We must rip off our own name tags.
- Right.
- There's no need to face them.
- The way that I see it,
- Do we need to go that way?
we're going to have to face them.
Regardless, only one of the teams
can survive.
Right. Only one team will survive.
- There. Hurry.
- Where?
- The cleaning lady is there.
Hold on. Hold on a minute.
Hold on.
We have four right now.
- Let's rip off your name tag.
- Okay.
- Let's rip it off.
Here you go.
- This is five.
- This isn't enough.
- Why?
These two are...
- They're not exchangeable?
- Why did we rip it off?
What do you mean by
it's not exchangeable?
- You can't exchange Defense Rights.
Just rip mine off.
Oh, wait, Young Min dies then.
- First...
- I don't die.
Young Min and I must die here.
I think... No.
Then you need to die.
Right, I do.
Hurry.
- We have no choice.
I don't know if we'll be able
to escape.
- We have to get out.
- We have no choice.
We have no choice.
Here. There's five.
(They got five name tags.)
- Jae Suk and Young Min are out.
- What?
I told you.
Do you think they're trying to
go down with the combination?
Should we go to where
the combination is?
Do you think
they're trying to go down?
We have to catch them and
rip off their name tags then.
(In the meanwhile, Petty Gang is...)
You know what I'm saying, right?
- Your name tag...
- 42...
- needs to be ripped off to win.
- 42098.
- Okay?
- Can we go down now?
Let's go up.
- We'll go out and distract them.
- Okay. Distract them.
- Then go down this way.
- No.
(They come together to risk
their luck when...)
They're here.
(The boss has been seen.)
- Hey.
- Run!
Go that way!
Hold on. That way.
- Go back. Downstairs.
- Downstairs.
- Move.
- Where are you going?
Hurry up.
Open the door.
Go.
They're over here!
- What should we do?
- They're over here!
- Haha.
- Come here!
(Jong Kook got him.)
I ripped it off. He's out.
He still has a chance.
(He survived because it was
a Defense Right.)
(Meanwhile, Do Kwon,
a man who's like fire, is...)
Try opening that door.
Suk Jin's name tag.
(While Do Kwon distracts everyone,
the boss disappears.)
(Escaping at full speed)
Suk Jin had two name tags.
10 minutes until the truck leaves.
(They have 10 minutes left
before the escape truck leaves.)
- He opened the door. We got him.
- Open it!
Hold on! Jong Kook.
- You said you'd forgive me.
- We got him.
Okay.
Fine, I'll be heroic
and go against Jong Kook.
Hurry.
Get in here.
- Get in here.
- What is this?
Okay.
- Get in here.
- What is this?
Okay.
(Haha is out.)
(Jong Kook eliminates Haha
and Seung Hyun first.)
- Okay.
- Haha and Seung Hyun are out.
Why?
Give me a second.
(In the world of inmates, there are
no eternal allies or enemies.)
There aren't any cameras in here.
Let's take this outside.
Let's do it right outside.
- Yong Ji, come in here.
- Jong Kook.
Let's go someplace nice.
This isn't a nice place.
- Let's go someplace nice, please.
- Hold on.
42098. Do Kwon needs to get here.
- Let's look cool.
- Hold on.
Yong Ji, follow me.
You can't go with him!
- You can't go with him!
- Hurry up and follow me.
(Jong Kook and Yong Ji leave
to go after the boss.)
Do Kwon needs to get here.
(Do Kwon leaves the room
to protect the boss.)
(But...)
Hold on.
(This was all a set up
orchestrated by Jong Kook.)
I'm standing backward
on the stairs.
(He successfully lured Do Kwon out.)
(Ha Do Kwon versus Kim Jong Kook)
Yong Ji, come here.
(Ripping)
Hold on.
(This is a match where their prides
are on the line.)
Hold on.
(Do Kwon isn't losing to Jong Kook.)
(At that moment,
Yong Ji goes behind him...)
(and successfully rips off
his name tag.)
- Ha Do Kwon is out.
- We did it.
- Ji Suk Jin out.
- What?
- Why?
- Your partner got eliminated.
(Boss Big Nose got eliminated
when he was so close to victory.)
This is driving me crazy.
(That was really close.)
Is it over?
- Good job.
I wanted to face you 1 on 1.
You have less than two minutes
to escape.
(This is the memo with
the combination he hid earlier.)
(Jong Kook and Yong Ji
need this number.)
- No.
- Hey!
(He's chewing up the only
record of the combination.)
You shouldn't eat that!
You shouldn't do that.
It's delicious.
- Give it to us.
- Hurry.
- Hurry up and give it to us.
- We should go.
- Share the prize.
Okay. I'll give it to you.
You can give it to your daughter.
(Spitting)
- Don't do this. This is gross.
- Let's go.
(It is 2:59 p.m.)
This is so gross.
(They have to get on the truck
prepared for the boss to win.)
What is the number?
This is the number.
What is it?
(Do Kwon's last fight
took up a lot of time.)
This is so gross.
- 2?
- 42098.
- 4, 2, 0, 9, 9, 8. Yes.
- 0, 9, 8.
(They unlocked the lock.)
- We got it.
- Gosh.
- Let's get on.
(They finally found Petty Gang's
escape truck.)
Gosh. In the back.
(After many twists and turns,
they are about to escape.)
Gosh.
My goodness.
You've successfully escaped!
(Regular inmates, Jong Kook
and Yong Ji, successfully escape.)
We did it. Okay.
(The race is over.)
The final result of the race.
Kim Jong Kook and Kim Yong Ji
have successfully escaped.
(Kim Jong Kook and Kim Yong Ji
have successfully escaped.)
I was almost there.
I'll show you the prize set.
(It's a complete set of tofu
to celebrate their escape.)
It's tofu.
It's really tofu.
There's even a gift card.
- Congratulations.
- There's a 100-dollar gift card.
- Really?
- Amazing.
- We'll send you the mobile coupon.
- Okay.
This supermarket is known
to have a large variety.
- Right.
- Is this a product placement ad?
I agreed to give my prize...
to Do Kwon.
- He doesn't like it.
- So he can give it to his daughter.
This is for Do Kwon.
(This is a gift for Do Kwon,
who put on a great fight.)
He put the combination in his mouth
and refused to give it up.
He tried to chew it up and eat it
at the end.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Son, this is how hard I worked.)
- He's so nice.
- Well done, everyone.
- Thank you.
(We'd like to thank Ji Seung Hyun,
Kim Young Min, Kim Yong Ji,)
(and Ha Do Kwon for running
with us on this hot day.)
(August 3, 2020 at 3 p.m.,
Inside the Interrogation Room)
(One suspect is shedding tears.)
(And two men are watching him.)
What is all of this?
(4 hours before the incident)
(International departure)
(Running Morning Soccer Club
Pre-season training)
(Kwak Do Won, Kim Sang Ho,
Kim Dae Myung)
(However,)
(they are banned from travel as they
are suspected to be salt smugglers.)
(Through domestic investigation,)
(they must clear out the criminals
hiding amongst them.)
(Criminals and police officers are
hidden amongst innocent citizens.)
(A silent pursuit for them
is starting.)
(Everyone is surprised at what
happens in the investigation room.)
One of us could be the criminal.
(How will the case of
the terrible salt smugglers end?)
I'm a police officer.
My gosh, stop being a fool.
(Operation: Clear Out the Criminals,
Domestic Investigation)