- Hello.
Hello.
- Hey.
- You're here.
- Kwang Soo.
- Hello, Jong Kook.
Look at him. Gosh.
Aren't these pants for Heungbu?
- What?
- This is what Heungbu would wear.
- They are stylish.
- They are a little...
You said that when I wore them.
It's different from what you wore.
Yours had patches.
- Suk Jin.
- These have patches too.
- They are different.
- You just don't look good in them.
How dare you say that, you fool?
Go ahead and hit me. Just do it.
He would never hit you.
He pretended to hit you,
but he actually made a heart shape.
(I will punish you with a heart.)
I always wait for him
to punch me, but he never does.
You know what?
So Min's doctor...
advised her to be
hospitalized for a while.
Dear viewers,
please don't worry about her.
She's a cheerful girl.
She'll be back soon.
- I know.
- I hope so.
Today, we prepared a race where
you give your juniors warm touches.
Warm touches for our juniors?
It's called Running Man Class Race.
- What?
- Touches for juniors?
- Then...
- It says Team Comedian,
- Team Actor, and Team Singer.
- Is that what we're doing today?
Are there going to be
junior comedians?
We've divided you into three teams
according to your job.
Team Comedian has Jae Suk,
Suk Jin, and Se Chan.
- I see.
- Right. We are comedians.
Team Singer has Jong Kook and Haha.
And Team Actor has
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo.
It's a little ambiguous
for Kwang Soo though.
(It's a little ambiguous
for Kwang Soo though.)
He's also a comedian.
What are you talking about?
- He's a comedian slash actor.
- What's ambiguous?
- Isn't he a comedian slash actor?
- He's not just an actor.
- It is ambiguous.
- Right.
- But I'm actually an actor.
Aren't you a comedian slash actor?
- He's Jack Black of Korea.
- Right.
Jack Black?
- I'm flattered.
- Jim Carrey of Korea.
I'm very flattered.
- You're amazing.
- I'm grateful you say that.
- You're great.
- I'm very honored.
- You're just like Jim Carrey.
- Right. He's like Chow Sing Chi.
- There are many actors like that.
- I'm flattered.
You will wear a badge that shows
your years of experience today.
- My gosh.
- A badge?
Hang on. How long have I been
in this industry?
Suk Jin, do you have
28 years of experience?
Gosh, it's been 30 years
since my debut.
Jae Suk is the senior here.
I have the longest career.
You've been in this field
for 16 years?
Yes. It's been 16 years.
- I made my debut in 2005.
- It's been a long time.
It's a long time.
She has 20 years of experience.
She's a senior.
Gosh, it's been 20 years already.
- Ji Hyo is a senior in her field.
- That's true.
Not yet, Jae Suk.
- Yes, you are.
- No.
- That's not true.
- We have about 150 years...
of experience put together.
This is a little
embarrassing though.
- We're like turtles.
- Why is it embarrassing?
- Kwang Soo has 13 years.
- That's right.
Does it include your model career?
I made my debut
in a TV commercial.
(Kwang Soo made his debut
in a TV commercial in 2008.)
That's when you debuted.
- Is that it?
- Yes.
You've been a comedian since then.
He has the hairstyle
of a would-be comedian.
Look at his face. It's obviously
a picture of a comedian.
He lifted the left corner of his
lips. That's what comedians do.
I tried to look cool
when I took this picture,
but I was harshly criticized.
"That's not you."
"Pull yourself together."
What's with you these days?
- Why do you try to look cool?
- Today,
entertainers who debuted either
before or after you are here.
I want to team up with someone
who debuted after me.
Guests, please come out!
Will the comedians try to be funny,
falling on purpose or something?
- It's Cho Sae Ho.
- He debuted 20 years ago?
- Rowoon!
- It's been a while.
Oh, my.
Do Hyun!
- Oh, my.
- Hey!
You're both so good-looking.
- Hi, Sa Yeon.
- I missed you.
- She's our mom.
- Beautiful Deer.
What's incredible is...
that Sa Yeon has been
in the show business...
for 43 years now, surviving
all the ups and downs.
(She's been in show business
for half a century now.)
- Right?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
- This is why you adore me.
- You're the best.
Can you...
All right.
(Jae Suk pats Suk Jin
on the head.)
- Jae Suk debuted first.
- Right.
- I can see you debuted first.
You definitely debuted first.
- Should I put up with this?
- You should.
- All right.
- You should just laugh it off.
- Next up is...
Hong Jin Young.
- Hello.
- Jin Young.
Our little sister, Jin Young.
- How are you doing these days?
- I happen to...
have released a new song recently.
- I released a new song.
- You released a new song?
All right, let's hear it.
(Jin Young performs her new song
right away.)
- That was fast.
- I can't wait.
I'm sure she's hiding something.
(She starts performing
without even introducing her song.)
Is it tango?
("Love Is Like a Petal"
by Hong Jin Young)
- It's tango.
- You dance?
(The intro has
a catchy tango melody.)
She dances a lot in this song.
(This time, we even get to see
her dance moves.)
(Don't leave me)
(Stay close to me)
(Just one more day)
(She sings so passionately
as if this is her concert.)
(The song is upbeat yet emotional,
which is Jin Young's trademark.)
(She finishes the song perfectly.)
That was amazing.
You're a singing machine.
Thank you.
Next up is...
- Cho Sae Ho.
- Is it me?
Sae Ho won the KBS
Music and Talk Award last year.
It was from MBC.
- It was from MBC.
- The MBC Music and Talk Award.
I still don't understand.
- Why did you win that award?
- What is that award anyway?
I've shown outstanding musicality...
- and been active...
- The Music and Talk Award.
- on talk shows.
- All right.
One of us won the Popularity Award.
We should respect
the Music and Talk Award.
I won the Social Media
Popularity Award too.
I respect that.
Thank you.
Every award Sae Ho wins
seems to disappear the next year.
It's given out only that year.
Also...
Sae Ho...
Suk Jin, looking at you
from the side,
your complexion is pale.
(Your complexion is pale.)
(Sa Yeon's diagnosis
catches Suk Jin off guard.)
- All of a sudden?
(Everyone else finds it hilarious.)
She was staring at him
the whole time.
His complexion is pale?
- His complexion is pale?
- Are you sick?
Gosh, I'm healthy.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
His complexion is pale?
- What do you mean?
- What does she even mean?
He looks so pale.
- It's just my makeup.
- It's his makeup.
It's just that his makeup is
too bright.
That's the funniest thing
I've heard this year.
Next up is the rising star,
Rowoon!
- He's really good-looking.
- He's so handsome.
He's a great singer too.
- He's been on this show before.
- Right.
Are you the one who wore my jacket?
- That's right.
(Rowoon briefly appeared
in the Unboxing Race.)
(Rowoon is wearing
Suk Jin's jacket.)
(The same jacket
looks completely different.)
- Can you try Suk Jin's jacket on?
- Come on.
Just try it on.
Look at Rowoon.
He looks amazing
even in a white T-shirt and jeans.
- This is the best outfit for him.
- You look better now.
Let me see.
Gosh, Rowoon.
So that's how this jacket
should look.
- That jacket looks great.
- Thank you.
It's the Grim Reaper!
(The Fashion Grim Reaper is here.)
Who are you?
(Seeing Suk Jin in broad daylight
makes you back away.)
That's hilarious.
After his appearance on this show,
he became the most searched person.
Lee Do Hyun!
(This actor with 4 years of
experience has unexpected charms.)
- The clubber!
- More than anything,
Running Man made him
known to a lot of people recently.
Did your family watch the show?
Yes, my mother asked me
why I danced like that.
(Do Hyung's club dance...)
(made his mother worried.)
(Her worry is understandable.)
- Give Do Hyun a big hand!
- Thank you.
(All the guests
have been introduced.)
Today's race is called
"Running Man Class Race,"
and you'll compete for prize sticks.
The prizes look amazing.
Each of you will start
with two sticks.
After each mission,
more sticks will be handed out...
The team with the most sticks wins.
The winning team can draw as many
prizes as the sticks they have.
You'll win a massage chair today.
To move up the hierarchy,
you can buy years.
One stick is worth five years.
That's a big jump.
That will give you an edge
in the next mission.
- The more years, the better?
- I guess I'm at an advantage.
That's right.
At any time during the race,
you may ring the Senior's Bell...
and give those below you
advice and encouragement.
It means nagging.
Please change
and go to the first mission spot.
(Let's start the mission!)
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Can I get some water?
- Pardon?
- Can I sit here?
Sit here.
- Do you have any water?
- Have some of Jae Suk's.
- I don't want someone else's.
- I'll get you some.
You don't have to do that, Rowoon.
I didn't ask you to do that.
Suk Jin, get your water yourself.
(Rowoon ends up
getting water for Suk Jin.)
I didn't mean it.
I want to drink some water too.
Everyone, the first mission
where you can win prize sticks is...
- Songs from the Old Days.
Guess the top three songs
of each year...
according to
the largest streaming sites.
(Guess the top 3 songs
of each year.)
Each team will take turns
selecting a year.
The team that gets the song title
and singer right wins a point.
You can also get
an additional point...
if you get a score higher than 90.
After five rounds,
prize sticks will be handed out
according to the teams' scores.
- That sounds fun.
- We can cover many periods.
- Okay.
- Team Comedian has an advantage.
- We're the most likely to win.
- You're right.
I've been the King of Kings
on "Challenge 1000 Songs"...
- many times.
- Really?
Yes. I've been the King of Kings
2 or 3 times.
"Challenge 1000 Songs"?
- You must have won a lot of gold.
- I was on the panel...
- with Chang Hee.
- Really?
Gosh, what was that?
(Pinching)
- What was that?
- Sae Ho,
he wants you to be quiet.
- He's way above you.
- Okay.
Are you allowed to punish
those below you today?
- It didn't hurt my feelings.
- Of course not.
- I just felt a little prick.
- Just a little prick.
Which team should go first?
- Should Team Actor go first?
- All right.
- We have some young members.
- They know many recent songs.
- We choose 2010.
- 2010?
You're to guess the number 1 song
of 2010.
- The number 1 song?
- Of 2010?
- It's 10 years ago.
It's 2010.
The number 2 song is
"Nagging" by IU and Seul Ong.
- "Nagging".
- Every single thing I say
- Is for you
- Ji Hyo.
- Hey! Stop pretending you know it.
- Even if you don't like it
I have to say it
She got the lyrics completely wrong.
- Let's stop
- It's a recent song for you, right?
It's a recent song for her.
- It's a recent song for her.
- Good job, Ji Hyo.
- Say, "Let me answer."
- Okay.
- Should we try it?
- I think it might be right.
- Let me answer.
- Rowoon.
"Heartbeat" by 2PM.
- That's wrong.
- "Heartbeat".
No matter how hard I try
- Let me answer.
"Bo Peep Bo Peep" by T-ara.
I think it's right.
(Wrong)
Let me answer.
"Tell Me" by Wonder Girls.
That's wrong.
That's from 2008.
- It is?
- Yes.
- Let me answer.
- "Abracadabra"...
by Brown Eyed Girls.
(Wrong)
I'll give you a hint.
It's a four-member girl group.
- Let me answer!
- "4Minute" by 4Minute.
- That's right.
- No?
- 4Minute!
"Hot Issue" by 4Minute.
- I don't think it's 4Minute.
- I think it's right.
It's not 4Minute.
- Here's another hint.
- Okay.
You haven't even mentioned
this girl group yet.
(It's a 4-member girl group
that hasn't been mentioned.)
- No?
- Really? A four-member girl group?
The number one song is by
a girl group we haven't mentioned?
Who else was popular?
And it's the number one song?
Jewelry... Let me answer!
"I Really Like You" by Jewelry.
(That's from 2003.)
That's from way back.
- Gosh, don't do anything.
- Come on!
I really like you
It's not that song?
- Why not?
- Please don't mention Bunny Girls.
- How can we not remember it?
- But you'll recognize the song.
I'm sure they came
on Running Man too.
- Right.
- Of course.
- If they did...
- I know!
- What is it?
- Miss A.
It's that song.
- Miss A!
(The hyenas smell something.)
(Rowoon starts dancing.)
- 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- "Good Girl, Bad Girl".
- Let me answer!
It's a Miss A song.
- "Bad Girl, Good Girl."
(Correct)
Isn't that what we said?
- I even danced.
- We got it backward?
- We said, "Good Girl, Bad Girl."
- I even danced.
We said, "Good Girl, Bad Girl."
I just want to sing.
- A good girl on the outside
- A bad girl on the inside
- Can we dance?
- No, we can't.
("Bad Girl, Good Girl",
The number 1 song of 2010)
JYP.
(They get an additional point
if they get more than 90 points.)
(They do the dance moves too.)
- So shut up, boy
(Jin Young shows off
her singing skills.)
Yes!
Nice!
(Yes!)
(She doesn't know
the melody or the beat.)
She doesn't know that song.
She's clueless.
- Why aren't you singing the song?
- She's the Suzy in our group.
- I don't know it.
I don't know the song.
(Thanks to Jin Young,
they successfully sing the song.)
- Well?
- What's the score?
- You sang out your heart.
(90 points or over
will give them an extra point.)
(What's Jin Young's score?)
You did great.
What a relief. It's not over 90.
Hey, it's you on the screen.
- It's not over 90.
- It's you, Jin Young.
No way. Did you see that?
I can't believe
she only scored 89 points.
Jin Young, that was amazing though.
Good job, Jin Young.
Let's go next.
That was so close.
We guessed the artist correctly.
The song was a huge hit.
I was serving in the military
at the time,
so all the soldiers
sang along to this song.
"Bad girl! Good girl!"
We all went crazy.
- You're wearing the military color.
- You're right.
- We all are.
- Sae Ho, what were you up to?
I was doing well, I guess.
(Sae Ho ends the conversation.)
(What...)
What kind of an answer
did you want from me?
- I can't make it up?
- You're asking him that?
- Just look at his expression.
- What were you up to back then?
Guys, gather around.
(Team Comedian gather.)
Did you have to open your big mouth?
- I only answered a question.
- Sae Ho, you were wrong.
- What...
- Just keep your mouth shut.
Always answer questions
to the best of your ability.
- It's all I ask.
- Hands behind you.
- There's no need for that.
- Is that so?
Jae Suk doesn't like that,
you know.
- What...
- We can stand freely.
- Suk Jin.
- What? What should I do?
- Our junior comedians are watching,
- I see.
so I'd appreciate
courtesy and respect.
Let's do a good job, okay?
- Think before you talk.
- We've got this.
- Sure.
- Got it.
- So we can ask...
- Let's brings it in.
- On 3. 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
- Let's go!
- That was quite nice to see.
- That was nice of you, Jae Suk.
It's all about seniors and juniors
coming together today.
- Please choose a year.
- We're up.
- How about 1985?
- What?
- 1985.
- But I was born in 1986.
1985...
Can you be more considerate?
I was born in 1986.
Let's try 1985.
- Can you guess it right?
- I know I can.
- But there's also Sa Yeon.
- Sa Yeon will know it too.
We'll go with the year 2000.
- Who are you to decide that?
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- 1985...
Suk Jin, watch what you're saying!
- Gather around.
- Aren't you ringing it too often?
- Is this a dictatorship?
- Hold on a second.
- A dictator?
- I wanted the year 1985.
- But this...
- I mentioned the year 1985.
But this...
We should go with a year
that is comfortable for everyone.
Then you should've
discussed it with us...
instead of just announcing it.
- Isn't the year 2000 the best?
- It's perfect.
(An unconditional reflex)
I prefer the year 2000 too.
- You rats.
- What?
- All right then.
- I can't believe you two.
- On 3. 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
- 1, 2, 3, let's go.
The year 2000.
- The year 2000.
- That was nice teamwork.
- The year 2000!
You must guess the song
that came in third place.
- 3rd place?
- The song in 3rd place?
Can you at least tell us the genre?
- It's an upbeat dance number.
- A dance number?
Let me answer!
"Festival" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
- I think that's right.
- Let me answer.
"The Way This Guy Lives"
by SECHSKIES.
Let me answer.
"Don't Know" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
"In the Bus" by ZaZa.
Seriously?
- Why? He said it's upbeat.
- I like that song too but...
- That was released in the 90s.
- He said it was upbeat.
"Achilantis" by BoA.
- What was that?
- What did he say?
Unbelievable.
Are you kidding me?
- Just keep your mouth shut.
- Sae Ho!
Guys, please think about
what you're saying before saying it.
All right? Now, bring it in.
- 1, 2, 3, let's go.
- Let's go.
- But...
- You two.
Don't bother
addressing them yourself.
- I have seniority here.
- You two,
- don't make me stand up again.
- That's enough.
(Upsetting)
Here's a hint for you.
(Could this be it?)
- Let me answer!
- Go for it.
Let me answer.
"Dances with DOC" by DJ DOC.
("Dances with DOC" by DJ DOC)
Let me answer.
"Run to You" by DJ DOC.
("Run to You" by DJ DOC is correct.)
(What a bummer.)
It was "Run to You."
- No way.
- Come on!
Go for it.
Jump, jump!
I'll show you how it's sung.
Bounce with me, bounce with me
Bounce with me, bounce
(Kwang Soo's bouncing
close to the floor.)
What on earth are you doing?
I can't dance properly yet.
He's really good
(He's really good.)
He's a singer, after all.
So this was the song.
(Jong Kook's singing
hits our eardrums.)
(Se Chan's lip-syncing
attacks our eyes.)
(He expresses his comedic side
by lip-syncing.)
Go, Jong Kook!
(What score
did singer Jong Kook get?)
What did he get?
(It's 91,
so they get 2 extra points.)
Nice one!
- All right.
- Nice!
(Only Team Singer has three points.)
(Team Singer is able
to take a strong lead.)
- Team Singer is at an advantage.
- Right.
- We keep getting the titles wrong.
- That's two in a row.
We want to sing too, you know.
We want to show you
how well comedians can party.
- Unbelievable.
- We don't get chances like this.
- We'll hold on to the mikes.
- Right.
- It'll be ours anyway.
- Let's try to sing a song too.
- Team Actor, choose a year.
- We'll go with 2008.
You must guess the song
in first place.
Why don't each team
come up with one answer each?
That's a good idea.
I love the way you run your show.
- Why are you kissing up to him?
- It's because I know him.
Hold on a second. We're sorry.
- But...
- Jae Suk, tell him.
I won't say who it is,
but one of you...
has been evaluating
the performance of others.
- That's not nice at all.
- I thought it was a nice idea.
And Suk Jin,
don't tell others that
their guesses are absurd.
- But...
- I'd like him to dance too...
when we're dancing together.
- Also...
- But...
- You're not setting an example.
- Hold on.
(Second-in-command Suk Jin
gathers the other two.)
Jae Suk can say that, but not you.
- Guys, sit down.
- Sure.
I'm sorry about that.
- I was going to answer but...
- That's enough.
There's no need.
I need to quickly buy
some extra years.
- You can buy some right now.
- I can't say anything.
You can buy some.
Can I? But I'll wait for now.
Here's a hint for you.
It's a girl group.
A girl group?
"So Hot" by Wonder Girls?
Good one!
Let me answer.
"So Hot" by Wonder Girls.
(That is correct!)
(Finally, we got it right!)
How on earth did you know?
- Nice.
- Good job, Do Hyun.
(He couldn't be more touched.)
It was "So Hot."
"So Hot".
Ji Hyo had an advantage
since 2008 is recent for her.
Don't be absurd.
- This is a song I really like.
- JYP.
Ji Hyo's a fan of Wonder Girls.
- Ji Hyo knows this song.
- Isn't this it?
JYP.
You know it too.
(They're already feeling the heat.)
- Wonder Girls.
- We're back!
(After limply swaying his body)
Who on earth
sings like that in Wonder Girls?
(Kwang Soo sounds like a mosquito.)
(Their version of "So Hot"
seems slightly off though.)
(Is this right?)
(What score did Ji Hyo
get for her team?)
- What's her score?
- Probably 35.
I bet she scored below 50.
- Look.
- Seriously?
(She received a higher score
than predicted.)
- Look.
- Seriously?
- We get two extra points.
- It's all about being loud.
- You need to sing loudly.
- This is absurd.
Are you kidding me?
When they were singing just now,
Jin Young couldn't take her eyes
off Rowoon.
Don't tell people that!
- Why not?
- When did I look at him?
- She kept on staring at him.
- I didn't.
- It was too obvious.
- I didn't look at him.
Rewind and check.
Jin Young was like this.
(Rewind and check.
Jin Young was like this.)
(While Team Actor was singing)
- Unbelievable.
- She didn't even hide it.
- I didn't look at him.
- Even I saw it.
- But I didn't.
- Is he like Won Bin to you?
- Still...
- Shut it!
The moment she got caught,
she put her arm around Jong Kook.
- I saw it.
- No way.
It's fine though. I understand.
I'm sorry, but aren't comedians
usually loud and active?
- We've been doing poorly.
- Our guesses have been way off.
How is it that you don't know
any of the songs?
I think I know why.
We never really think about
the songs when listening to them.
- We're busy dancing.
- You're right.
Like this.
(Dancing)
Why do you all dance the same moves?
- We...
- Your dance was identical.
- It's our basic move.
- We...
- We don't memorize titles.
- No, we don't.
- We just party.
- Yes, exactly.
All we care about is standing out.
- Then...
- Is it our turn now?
Let's go with the year 1985
since Suk Jin's confident.
I doubt Jong Kook knows...
- songs from back then.
- It's a tough one.
Sa Yeon's my only competition.
- But...
- We choose the year 1985.
You will guess the song...
- in third place.
- It won't be easy then.
- The year 1985...
- In 1985,
the song in first place was...
- "I Can Love Again" by Sunflower.
- Who?
I don't quite remember that song.
In second place was "Yesterday
Today and" by Cho Yong Pil.
(It's a song I know!)
(The older guys all chime in.)
- Let me answer.
- Sure.
- "Spark" by Cheon Young Rok.
- "Paper Crane".
- "Spark".
("Spark" is incorrect.)
- Let me answer.
- "Teahouse of the Winter"...
- By Cheon Young Rok.
("Teahouse of the Winter"
is incorrect.)
- Park Nam Jung...
- Lee Yong?
- No.
- "Last Night in October".
Lee Yong was popular
in the early 80s.
- You're wrong.
- It was in the 80s.
- Let me answer. Can I try?
- I know I'm right.
- No. It's not Lee Yong.
- It is.
"Last Night in October" by Lee Yong.
Suk Jin's driving me crazy.
- Lee Yong's...
- This is 100 percent wrong.
"Seoul, Seoul, Seoul".
- That's not even his song.
- Is that Lee Yong's song?
I don't think I can be
on the same team as him.
- Why?
- Come on.
Goodness.
He makes us assemble too many times.
- Come on.
- Stop doing it.
- Junior.
- What?
I already told you.
Lee Yong was from 1980 to 1981.
- I'll buy it now.
- No wonder he gets scolded.
How many years can he buy?
- 5 years.
- He can buy 5 years?
I'll buy. He's making me mad.
- Okay.
- Oh, gosh.
I want to do whatever I want.
- How many years do I have?
- 33 years.
- It was 1982.
- He didn't sing that year.
- Na Hoon A?
- Right.
- All right.
- Let me answer. Koo Chang...
Mo's...
There's that song by Koo Chang Mo.
That song...
- That's not it.
- Please give her a second.
- I have no clue.
- Let me answer.
- "Heenari"...
- "Heenari".
by Koo Chang Mo.
("Heenari" by Koo Chang Mo
is correct.)
See?
We almost had it.
(We almost had it.)
Right, it's "Heenari."
"Heenari," right.
- That was so close.
- "Heenari".
"Heenari".
"Heenari". I couldn't remember.
Bring me the mic.
- What is it?
- Check, check.
"Heenari" is playing.
- "Heenari".
- This is "Heenari".
- What is this song?
- Let's go for it.
Hello, viewers.
Team Comedian is finally here.
- Please give a round of applause.
- Nice to meet you.
- "Heenari".
- You waited for a long time.
- Written by me.
- Written by Choo Sae Ho.
- Choo Sae Ho.
- Please play the music.
Like Cho Sae Ho.
- What is this song?
- I really like this song.
- "Heenari".
(He's enthusiastic.)
I'll buy some years.
(Abruptly)
- He's buying some years.
- I'll buy.
- Why? Why are you buying?
- I'm more senior than you.
- Hey, be quiet. Wait.
Put your mic down.
- What?
- Hey.
Hold on.
Give me your mic.
I'm more senior than you.
- I'm your senior.
- I am!
- I bought more years.
- Hey!
You're watching a scene
where comedians are fighting.
Did you buy more?
(They try to sing
while the seniors fight.)
What are you doing?
(They get their microphones
confiscated.)
(You have to give me the mic
so that I can sing.)
Dance in the background.
(3 microphones in 1 hand)
- Like I have
- I'll buy.
(I'll buy!)
(Suk Jin reclaims number 1.)
- I'll buy again.
- Junior.
- What's going on?
- Stop it.
(They're agitated by
the panic buying of years.)
- Why did you
- Grab him.
(They listen to Jae Suk
and collect his mic.)
I bought more!
(They used up
all their sticks for one song.)
(I finally get to sing a line.)
Bring it.
(He collects all the microphones.)
I bought more.
- Again?
- I did.
How many did you buy?
(This is hilarious.)
(He tries to sing,)
(but Suk Jin steals the chorus.)
- It's not your turn.
- The youngest can't do anything!
Thank you.
(The juniors finally take the mic.)
(Last syllable)
It's done.
(Their job was to
clean up the song.)
- What was this?
- Did they get over 90 percent?
You did well.
- They got 98 percent.
- 98 percent.
That makes no sense.
I used up all the sticks,
and nothing changed.
Jae Suk, you have 40 years.
- 40 years, okay.
- Suk Jin has 38 years.
That was a mess. What is this?
- I have no power.
- And...
- Hold on.
- Seniors.
You can't steal my mic
while I'm singing.
- I know.
- The senior is...
supposed to go first.
I was going to pass it on to you.
- Why would you go first?
- Let's bring our hands together.
I'll do it anyway.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
- 1, 2, 3.
We got 98 percent.
Each stick is worth five years.
- I can't do anything.
- Like I have a disease of the mind
(Sae Ho is still hyper.)
(Is it the bell again?
Who is it now?)
- Se Chan rang the bell.
- Yes, I rang it.
- Go ahead.
- Hold on, Sae Ho.
- What? Did he buy?
- He did.
- Hold on.
- He bought some years.
When did you buy?
(A moment ago)
(I'll buy 5 years.)
- Did you buy?
- Yes.
(Sae Ho was getting on my nerves.)
Don't comedians have
a strict hierarchy?
Why are you trying to stand out?
- I am not.
- I can see it.
- Why are you trying to stand out?
- He's trying to stand out.
- I don't like your attitude.
- Actually,
- Se Chan is making a good point.
- Why would you do that?
Don't act that way.
I'll pull your ears.
- Okay.
- Understood?
I've never seen somebody
get their ears yanked.
Can you do better?
Can you do better or not?
- I can.
- Say, "I can do it" three times.
I can do it. I can do it.
I can do it.
Okay, go back to your seat.
I gave a lesson to the junior.
- Good job.
- Have a seat.
- Sit.
- This is necessary.
- Right.
- I'll take this role.
- Good.
- Somebody came...
- Stop it.
- You're an important intermediary.
- I'll try my best.
There's one question left.
We pick 2015.
- 2015.
- That's not too long ago.
- Let's go.
- Guess the number one song.
- Number one.
- "Loser" by BigBang was sixth.
- Loser, loner
This was a mega-hit song.
Let's get this right.
This was earlier. Let me answer.
"Growl" by EXO.
- Let me answer!
- "Gangnam Style" by PSY.
- "Gangnam Style".
Hey, don't get too excited.
Goodness.
Let me answer.
- We didn't say anything.
- It's fine.
- Try it.
- He's more senior.
- Go.
- "Bang Bang Bang" by BigBang.
("Bang Bang Bang" by BigBang
is correct.)
(Team Comedian earns 1 point.)
How did you know?
You punk.
Let's get ready to shoot.
Okay. Bring it.
Here.
- Jump.
- Mic.
(He pretends like
he knows how to have fun.)
(Warming up)
(Cue the music!)
(Creaking)
(This semi-comedian wants to join.)
(They all do their own thing.)
(This is a mess.)
(Let's have some fun.)
- Jae Suk.
(The cool part is for Jae Suk
with the highest seniority.)
(He chimes in.)
(What is Suk Jin doing?)
(This is how comedians have fun
in karaoke.)
Here it is.
(Their excitement is
about to explode!)
Line up!
(Get ready to fire.)
- Bang, bang, bang
(Is he twirling a folk arts hat?)
(Shoot, shoot, shoot)
- Bang, bang, bang
Shoot, shoot
(Their energy reaches the climax.)
(They try so hard to stand out.)
(Shoot, shoot, shoot)
That was good.
- We burned it up.
- Great job.
We burned it up.
Let's get 100 percent.
(This is their version in 2020.
What is their score?)
(92 percent!)
- Okay.
That was great.
I feel much better now.
- Excellent.
- I feel liberated.
Me too.
This feels like we're at
a karaoke bar. It's fun.
"Cheer Up" by TWICE.
"Wrongful Encounter" by Kim Gun Mo.
(Team Actor earns 2 points,
and Team Singer earns 1.)
You're all tied,
so we'll do one final round.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Sure.
- Please guess 1st place for 1998.
Second place was
"Breakup with Her" by Kim Hyun Jung.
Third place was "Sorrow" by COOL.
Let me answer.
"We Are the Future"...
Good one.
by H.O.T.
It's that period of time.
That's right.
H.O.T and SECHSKIES.
Let me answer.
- "Ppuyo Ppuyo" by UP.
- What are you talking about?
Let me answer.
- Wait.
- What are you talking about?
- Can't I give my opinion?
- Wait.
- Hold on.
- Should I be criticized?
- Cut it out.
- I could be wrong!
- I'm not playing.
You were supposed to
discuss it with us.
"Ppuyo Ppuyo" is
number one in my heart.
Hey, you.
- Kwang Soo can't do that.
- No...
No...
- I can have an opinion.
- Hey.
You have to discuss it with us.
- I had an opinion.
- We lost our chance.
- I thought of it.
- Sit down. Be quiet.
Don't talk. Sit.
- Be quiet.
- Wait, you...
Be quiet. Sit.
- Be quiet.
- They're laughing and watching me.
We lost our chance because of you.
(They lost discipline
because of Kwang Soo.)
She almost slapped him.
(Ringing)
- It was Suk Jin.
- Stand up.
- Why?
Why do you care
if she pinches his cheek?
- Well, I...
- Why do you care about their team?
I thought it would be fun.
All right.
- Act appropriately.
- Okay.
- Sure.
- Act appropriately.
- Okay.
Look away when he's scolding me.
- Let me answer.
Is this it? "Thorn Tree"...
by Jo Sung Mo.
("Thorn Tree" by Jo Sung Mo
is incorrect.)
Oh, gosh.
- Why?
- Sa Yeon.
That was a genuine reaction.
I heard a pelican.
Oh, gosh.
A pelican.
Let me answer.
Uhm Jung Hwa's...
"Poison".
"Poison" by Uhm Jung Hwa?
("Poison" by Uhm Jung Hwa
is correct.)
See?
(Team Actor gets the last question
correct and wins!)
(This is the class of the senior.)
Did they come from behind?
- They did.
- That's true.
First place is Team Actor,
2nd is Team Comedian,
and 3rd is Team Singer.
- That's preposterous.
Following the ranks for Team Actor,
Ji Hyo will get 8 sticks,
Kwang Soo will get 7,
Rowoon will get 6,
and Do Hyun will get 5.
(They get sticks according to
their seniority levels.)
After Round One, here's the tally.
(Current Number of Sticks
after Round 1)
(Team Actor, Team Comedian,
Team Singer)
(The first mission is over.)
I don't remember any songs.
I know.
I'm not here to work.
I laughed so hard.
- I had a lot of fun.
- Because of him.
- Because of Jae Suk.
- All right.
This mission is called
Running Man Has Red Buttock.
What's that?
2 people from each team will play
for a total of 3 rounds.
Monkeys have red buttocks
That's the tune. You have to make
a sentence with the given keyword.
The next person has to take the word
the previous person ended with...
and create a new sentence.
You have to be witty.
Right.
But if the production crew thinks...
- the sentence doesn't make sense...
- Then it counts as a failure.
- Okay. We can do this.
- I'm good at this.
We're like experts.
Now we can have a real talk.
We are specialists in this.
- He's good at music and talk.
- He's an expert at it.
He's good at games
about music and talk.
- Sure. It's about music and talk.
- Music and talk.
Now we need 6 people,
2 from each team.
(2 people from each team go first.)
- You should go first.
- Do you want to try?
- Can we do that?
- Sure.
- You and I.
- You two should go first.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Sa Yeon, why don't you go first?
- Go ahead.
- I'll do it with her.
- All right.
- Okay.
- You two are a team.
We have to win this game.
Good luck.
Let's win.
Yang Saeroyi and Cho Saeroyi.
Let's do this.
(I'll show you what I got.)
Ready.
(What's the first word?)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
- It's easy.
- Hurry.
Start.
Lee Kwang Soo's face is long
What's long is a nose
- What?
- What was that?
What are you talking about?
(She sounds like she's singing
a Korean traditional song.)
What was that?
If you don't know
what to do, just say so.
- This is unbelievable.
- What was that?
- What are you doing?
- You should sing in tune.
She doesn't even know the rules.
- Was I singing off-tune?
- Monkeys have red buttocks
What's red is an apple,
an apple is delicious
- I see. Okay.
- What's long is gimbap
- I see.
- Gimbap is black
Now Sa Yeon goes first.
- All right.
- Okay.
Start.
Sa Yeon is pretty
Who's pretty is Ji Hyo
Ji Hyo is beautiful
Who's beautiful is Sa Yeon
Sa Yeon is a singer
A singer is good
What's good is love
Love is my girlfriend
- What?
- What did he say?
Love is my girlfriend
- What?
- What did he say?
- What? What did you say?
- Are you seeing someone?
(What did I just say?)
- What?
- Who is it?
- What was that?
- Hang on.
- Hey.
- It still makes sense.
It makes sense.
- It's just about love.
- Hey.
We will talk about it later.
Love is my girlfriend.
Why is he sending a video message
all of a sudden?
- Se Chan is seeing someone.
- You should tell us about her.
The word is girlfriend.
- Okay. Start.
- Start.
My girlfriend is
Se Chan's girlfriend
- What are you talking about?
- Hang on.
My girlfriend is
Se Chan's girlfriend
(It's like a crazy soap opera.)
This is strange. What was that?
- I'm sorry.
- Why did you say that?
That's not right.
Hey, what are you up to?
- Are you seeing my girlfriend?
- I'm really sorry.
How could you do that to Se Chan?
(She covers her mouth in shock.)
- What was that?
- How could you say that?
This is just...
He meant a female friend.
I'm friends
with Se Chan's girlfriend.
Do Hyun's friend is your girlfriend.
- She's his female friend.
- I see.
- My female friend.
- He meant a friend who's a girl.
- A friend who's a girl.
- Exactly.
- Okay.
- You should say a female friend.
It can be misleading.
(This drama is so fun.)
- Do Hyun just got minus one point.
- Okay.
- Do Hyun goes first?
- From Do Hyun.
The word is Cho Sae Ho. Start.
Cho Sae Ho is a rock
What?
- Hang on. I'm a rock?
- A rock?
Wait. This isn't right.
I meant his body.
That's what I mean.
He has a firm body.
- His body.
- No.
- Your body.
- I see. You mean my body.
- It's firm.
- Do you mean his head?
- Are you sure you meant his body?
- Seriously, that's what I meant.
- Are you sure?
- I meant his body.
- Sae Ho, he meant your body.
- I see.
Okay.
You should've said
Cho Sae Ho's arms are like a rock.
- I'm serious.
- His body is like a rock.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- It's so funny.
- You can't repeat the same thing.
- Start.
Ji Suk Jin has a big nose
Who has a big nose is Lee Kwang Soo
Lee Kwang Soo is sick
Who's sick is Jeon So Min
Jeon So Min is Se Chan's girlfriend
No, you should continue.
- Continue.
- That's true.
- Go ahead.
- It's true.
- Right.
That's not true.
Let's just continue.
Se Chan's girlfriend is Jeon So Min
Where is Jeon So Min?
- He asked a question.
- That doesn't count.
- Gosh, why are you so bad at this?
- That's not it.
It's music and talk.
What's wrong with you?
- You're not good at this.
- Hang on.
What they said before me...
- Round One is over.
- Okay.
Why do comedians have no wit?
Sae Ho, you're really bad.
You're terrible.
- Why is it so hard?
- I didn't do anything wrong.
Let me show you something.
Show them your wit.
Watch and learn.
Okay.
- Let's do this.
- All right.
Look what I do.
- Let's start.
- Watch.
- Start.
- This is easy.
Cho Sae Ho is not funny
Who's not funny is Lee Kwang Soo
Lee Kwang Soo is cool
Who's cool is Rowoon
Rowoon is tall
Who's tall is Lee Kwang Soo
Lee Kwang Soo is ugly
Who's ugly is Yang Se Chan
Yang Se Chan is hideous
Who's hideous is Yang Se Chan
Yang Se Chan is...
No, this isn't right.
She said the same thing.
I'm standing right here.
I'm very offended.
I'm standing right behind you.
It's like Sae Ho and I are
getting beaten out.
- Can you say good things about us?
- Am I hideous?
- All right.
- Good things.
- Let's be positive.
- Jin Young goes first.
- Ready.
- Let's do this.
Start.
Haha is funny
Who's funny is Cho Sae Ho
Cho Sae Ho is fat
Who's fat is Kim Joon Hyun
Where is Kim Joon Hyun?
- Okay.
- What?
(Where is Kim Joon Hyun?)
(He looks for a person
while playing a game.)
No. That doesn't count.
(Impressed by his wit)
Jae Suk, are you nervous?
Do you feel nervous
when you play this game?
- Are you nervous?
- Kim Joon Hyun eats a lot.
Why is he so bad at games?
- Are you feeling nervous?
- Is that what we do?
- Are you nervous? I'm asking you.
- No.
Look. I'm not nervous at all.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
Yang Se Chan has curly hair
Who has curly hair is Ji Suk Jin
Ji Suk Jin is weak
Who's weak is Yang Se Chan
Yang Se Chan has...
protruding teeth
(Sudden oral acceleration)
- No. This doesn't count.
- He does have protruding teeth.
It was too late.
It's true that
he has protruding teeth.
His mouth is protruding.
That's true. I do
have protruding teeth.
I didn't make that up.
- He has protruding teeth.
- That's true.
If you have protruding teeth,
you need dentures
You go to the dentist for dentures
You go to the dentist
for a dental implant
Who needs a dental implant
is Yoo Jae Suk
Yoo Jae Suk is...
Where is he?
Are you nervous?
Are you feeling nervous?
Is this driving you crazy?
Where's your wit?
(The nation's beloved MC feels
nervous when he plays games.)
- You're the worst.
- You can say Jae Suk is handsome.
- My gosh. He's the worst.
- Jae Suk.
- What's so hard about it?
- Jae Suk has ugly teeth.
- You should say that.
- Stay still.
- Jae Suk has ugly teeth.
- My goodness.
- What do you want me to watch?
- Don't say anything.
He just said he'd show me something.
- Just stay still.
- What do you want me to see?
He sounded so nervous
when he said his answer.
"Where is he?"
Just relax. Take a deep breath.
- I'm sorry. I apologize.
- Where is his wit?
- Okay.
- You should've said,
"Yoo Jae Suk is a grasshopper."
Rowoon goes first.
(Lee Do Hyun)
Lee Do Hyun is an actor
Ji Hyo is also an actress
Ji Hyo is 40
Who's 40 is...
I was 40 years old 10 years ago
(He sings a trot song he made up.)
(They all burst into laughter.)
(Even the trot goddess has
never heard this song before.)
What's your problem?
What's wrong with you?
Why did you become so unwitty?
- What's gotten into you?
- What's wrong with you?
Why are you being like this?
- Stop it.
- Go home!
- Hey.
- He's...
- He's still nervous.
- Was it 10 years ago?
10 years ago
He always criticized Suk Jin.
Are you doing this on purpose?
- Are you doing it on purpose?
- Why would you say that?
You have no sense of wit.
- Is it a musical or what?
- We can make a song with it.
- Was it 10 years ago?
- It was 10 years ago
(The melody is quite catchy.)
- Let's begin again.
- All right.
Good luck.
(Suk Jin goes first)
Start.
Rowoon is a model
Who's a model is Yoo Jae Suk
Yoo Jae Suk is tall
Who's tall is Han Ki Bum
Han Ki Bum is taller
What's taller is Mount Baekdu
Mount Baekdu...
The air is nice there.
(He sounds like the honorary
ambassador of Mount Baekdu.)
What was that?
What are you talking about?
- What was that?
- You are disappointing.
- What's wrong with you two?
- Why can't you play games?
- What was that?
- Guys.
We need to gather them together.
- What's wrong with you?
- Hang on.
Come here.
- That's the best you can do?
- What was that?
Hey, you...
What did you say about Mount Baekdu?
That was very disappointing.
Shut it. Stay quiet.
- We better do well.
- Comedians are the worst.
Comedians are the worst here.
The second mission is over.
We tallied the points.
The winners are...
Team Singer.
I knew it. We did better
than we thought.
The second place is...
- It's us.
- Team Actor.
(2nd place, Team Actor)
Well done.
You gave more wrong answers
than the other teams put together.
Really?
We will reflect on ourselves.
(The second mission is over.)
- Do you want me to move over?
- I'll sit there.
(Where should I sit?)
- Sit over there.
- Where?
- Sit there.
- Here?
- Do you want me to sit here?
- Then I'll go there.
Okay. Let's do that.
(Obedient)
(While they sit together...)
We will move for about 10 minutes.
- This is the last race.
- Okay.
Jae Suk. Did anyone of you...
- get a mission or something today?
- No. Why?
I took a look at the sticks earlier.
- It said something.
- It had something on it.
I didn't know that
until Se Chan told me.
(The break after the second mission)
Gosh, there are a lot of sticks.
(He takes a look at the sticks
unintentionally.)
(What is this?)
Do we have other missions
or something today?
I don't know.
It says something on the sticks.
- What?
- What is that?
It says something here.
(It says something on the sticks.)
What is this?
It says spy.
I guess someone stamped it.
- Someone stamped it on my stick.
- Someone stamped it.
Something's going on.
Yes. The sticks had something red
stamped on them.
I couldn't really make out
what it said.
I think it read "spy."
(Is there a spy among them?)
Sae Ho looks a bit flustered.
- I think it read "spy."
- I'm not.
- There were three syllables.
- I have no idea about this.
I think it read "spy" in red.
Sae Ho, your lips are trembling.
I don't know anything about this.
Did you meet
the producer beforehand?
- Be honest.
- I met the writer in the morning.
She just told me
to make today's episode fun.
- Did she say anything else?
- Then why aren't you doing that?
(Jae Suk criticizes
his performance.)
- Come on, Sae Ho.
- I... Wait.
Why aren't you making this fun?
It feels weird for me to say this,
- but wasn't I funny enough?
- No.
It wasn't enough. We want more.
I think I did enough.
Not all the names
had "spy" written on them.
Only a few had it.
- What does the color red mean?
- I have nothing to do with this.
- Everyone.
- I didn't see any sticks.
To tell you the truth,
- there are spies, indeed.
- Are you serious?
(There are spies.)
(A big twist)
Every team has a spy.
There are more than three teams.
Including Team Spy,
there are four teams.
Really?
- So you're saying...
- So there are three spies in total.
- there are both team...
- Right.
and spy matches?
Right, there were a total
of four teams.
Throughout the missions
you've carried out so far,
the spies have stamped...
the sticks.
My gosh.
- Seriously?
- When did you see those sticks?
When did you see them?
- Hold on.
- When did you see them?
Some names aren't stamped.
Mine was red.
I didn't see any.
I didn't see anyone touching them.
The stamped sticks...
belong to the spies.
Your stamped sticks
will be taken away from you.
- Darn it. Who are the spies?
- We need to be careful.
- But...
- I just saw them.
If the spies have the most sticks
at the end of the race,
Team Spy wins.
If your team has more sticks
than them,
you win.
- We need to look out for them now.
- Our team is in the lead.
So that's why they didn't let us
touch the sticks.
Rowoon, why are you smiling?
- I smile all the time.
- But the spies are...
- You're suspicious.
- It's not me.
- Do the spies recognize each other?
- That means...
Se Chan isn't a spy.
- Because...
- Why not?
- He's the one who brought this up.
- If I'm a spy, then why would I?
- It could be intentional.
- No.
Gosh, he said I did it on purpose.
- I think it's Sae Ho.
- Me too.
- It's him.
- It's not me.
- But...
- I'm not special enough...
to be a spy.
- That's true.
- Right?
I'm not the star of today's episode.
- So it's not you.
- I...
It's not me.
- That's sad.
- I'm not special enough.
I think it's Do Hyun.
- I think it's you.
- It's not me.
- Really?
- I fulfilled my task...
during the opening scene.
Do you want me to take a guess?
- Sure.
- In Team Actor, it's Do Hyun.
All right. Next?
In Team Singer, it's Haha.
- What?
- And in our team, it's Jae Suk.
Suspect everyone
except for those three.
- You look nervous.
- It's Rowoon.
- It's really not me.
- It's definitely you.
When I said Do Hyun's name,
Rowoon nodded...
- as if I was right.
- No.
- And...
- All I did was agree with you.
When we suspected him,
- he smiled.
- Really?
- I'm always smiling.
- He smiled like this.
I thought you were looking back,
but you were watching him.
- I wanted to say that earlier.
- No.
- Her body was twisted like this.
- You were looking at Rowoon.
- No, that's not true.
- She knows everything about him.
She was watching him...
the entire time.
- That's not true! Be quiet!
- Jin Young is...
- It's right.
- Rowoon's spy.
- She's been watching him only.
- That's not true.
- No.
- Is Rowoon the spy?
He is.
- Really?
- I'm too stupid...
to deceive others.
- Really.
- Wait a minute.
I think Sa Yeon doesn't like me.
Why not?
She suspected me of stamping them
with my crutches.
- Are you sure...
- That's different.
you didn't stamp them
with your crutches?
I didn't. I was holding
onto my crutches.
How is that possible?
How could I have stamped it
with my crutches?
- It just doesn't make any sense.
- Let me check your crutches later.
Be my guest.
It's really not me.
- You can do that.
- Let me see your hands.
Let me see if any of you
have ink on your hands.
- You're right.
- The ink.
- Let's see.
- They could have ink on them.
Sa Yeon, why are your fingers red?
- What?
- Are they?
- Sa Yeon.
- It's not me.
I think she has
good blood circulation.
Is it because you're healthy?
Let me see.
- He's clean.
- Check Sae Ho.
He should've checked my bag
or something, not inside my ear.
- Why would he look in there?
- For hygienic purposes.
Is that so?
(They fail to find any ink.)
- When did they do it?
- Could it be a spy...
from another team?
- Do Hyun.
- Right.
- You had trouble focusing today.
- A spy from another team...
- could stamp instead?
- I did my best today.
- Really?
- He wasn't that talkative today.
I did my best...
- because I didn't win last time.
- No.
The spies don't want their team
to win.
You know how your eyes widen
when you lie?
The spies recognize each other.
Why can't I stop suspecting him?
Kwang Soo.
This is what I think.
Do Hyun is the spy of Team Actor.
- Why?
- He's acting. No, I'm sure.
- He's been acting all along.
You were only fixated on Rowoon,
so how would you know that?
Why would you say it like that?
Why would you say that?
You've been staring at Rowoon.
- It's seriously not me.
- Why would you say that?
This is the first time I've seen you
ever since the opening scene.
- Why would you say that?
- You're right.
- I didn't see you for some time.
You're the key suspect here.
Are you caught?
I think it's Haha.
It's probably Se Chan.
- I want to do that as well.
- Don't you think so?
- Or is it you?
- No, it's really not me.
- Are you sure? You promise?
- Of course.
- Do you promise?
- I do.
It's either Jong Kook or Haha.
I think it's Haha.
When we were singing "Poison,"
- you and I were dancing, right?
- Yes.
- I looked back.
- This is driving me crazy.
Jong Kook was behind the sticks.
He was smiling and dancing.
- Exactly. How would I have...
- That's when I thought...
- stamped them while dancing?
- He was looking for a chance.
I had wondered
why he was still back there.
You're driving me crazy.
(This was during the first mission.)
(Jong Kook was dancing alone
in the back.)
(Did he stamp them
during this moment?)
- I was going to say this when...
- Hey.
Was I just standing there?
- No, you were dancing.
- I was dancing.
- You were looking for a chance.
- Was I back there for long?
- I don't know about that.
- It was only for a brief moment,
- But I saw you back there.
- so how would I have done it?
- I know you could've done it.
- This is unbelievable.
When we were doing
our second mission...
- Jae Suk, Jae Suk.
- Right.
There were many people in the back.
Those who were too focused
on the game...
probably couldn't see
what they were doing in the back.
- You're right.
- You disappeared several times.
- Hold on. Jae Suk said...
- Right?
that Rowoon was tall enough...
- to watch from the back.
- Right.
- It's not me.
- Because he's tall.
(This was
during the second mission.)
(Rowoon, who was tall,
watched from the back.)
(Did he stamp them?)
- It's not me.
- Because he's tall.
It's really not me.
- That's when you stamped them.
- It wasn't me.
- I'm serious.
- But...
- didn't we...
- Was it you?
It's really not me.
I'm terrible at lying.
- They were together.
- I'm really bad at it.
- Who are the spies?
- This show feels much harder...
now that there are spies.
After hearing about the spies,
I keep suspecting my teammates.
The final game is called...
Offense or Defense Hide-And-Seek,
Photos Can Kill.
What is this?
Each team will take
both offense and defense positions.
Every round will be 10 minutes long.
There will be 3 rounds in total.
This sounds difficult.
- I bet it is.
- The 1st 2 defense teams...
will have three minutes to hide
in the annex.
The offense team will have
bells tied to them...
and will have 10 minutes
to find them.
- It's hide-and-seek.
- Correct.
However, this isn't
Name Tag Elimination.
You must take a photo
of their name tag or face.
For their face, the eyes, nose,
and mouth need to be visible.
For the name tag, two syllables
need to be visible.
- Can we cover our faces?
- Can we?
Then you should aim
for their name tag.
What if they lie down
and cover their face?
You'll have to lift them up.
You'll have to step on them
until they put down their hands.
You can just lift them.
Are you guys thugs?
You have the same face and gaze.
This is just how
we're inclined to be.
- Really? Okay.
- Yes.
If the defense teams...
find the hidden cone hats
and wear them,
they'll acquire one year's worth
of experience per hat.
How many hats are there?
- Come on, now.
- Be quiet.
- Just be quiet.
- Let the seniors take over.
What will you do?
We'll explain it to you
once he's done talking.
Just pretend to be a doll
while you're here.
What does he mean?
Just act like a doll
while you're here.
- Just stay still.
- Gosh, he's so noisy.
- He's too ugly to be a doll.
- That's right.
He needs to regain his weight.
You don't have the face of a doll.
- He's so ugly.
- What's wrong with him?
The more cone hats you wear,
the more years you receive.
But you could get caught easily.
- The cone hat gets taller.
- It adds to your height.
You should make the decision.
After Round Three,
the team that eliminated more people
will receive more sticks.
I see.
What could be the spies' objective?
The small tables you saw earlier...
are hidden
throughout the building.
If the spies find them first,
they could put a stamp
on more sticks secretly.
- We could catch them in the act.
- You are right.
Lastly, a member
of the offensive team...
must stay behind
and do a separate mission.
- What?
- What separate mission?
The result will decide
if the defensive teams wear bells.
I will explain later.
Once we take a photo,
do we send it to someone?
- Be quiet!
- For goodness' sake!
You can ask the cameraman
after you take a photo.
You can ask the cameraman.
- Keep quiet.
- You should go behind the cameras.
Sit like a doll and go home.
Do you want to go
behind the cameras?
- Is that it?
- You won't take a single photo.
- Do you want me to get angry?
- Seriously.
Senior Yang, calm down.
Okay. I will calm down.
I don't want to suffer after today.
We just need to take photos.
That's right.
We don't need to remove name tags.
Why do you keep talking?
I am not an ambitious character.
- That's right. You aren't.
- I am not ambitious.
So you aren't impatient.
Of course not.
(Impatient)
Don't look at the cameras.
- Listen.
- I am not impatient.
Seriously.
Jong Kook.
Ask, "Where is Jin Young?"
Where is Jin Young?
Here!
(Cute)
I am sorry,
but stop acting like you are
on "We Got Married."
- When did I do that?
- That show got canceled.
Ask again.
Where is Jin Young?
Here!
(She keeps saying, "Here.")
It's really cute.
Where is Jong Kook?
- Let's go.
- Come on and say it.
- It's really cute.
- Stop it already.
Say, "Here." Where is Jong Kook?
Here.
(Here.)
(She is a Kim Jong Kook tamer.)
- It's really cute.
- For goodness' sake.
- It's really cute when men do it.
- Hey.
Where should we hide?
Let's go to the first floor
and hide.
For goodness' sake.
(While the Here Couple looks
for a place to hide)
I will find the cone hats first.
Cone hats. Cone hats.
Okay. I found one.
Where are the cone hats?
Sae Ho.
- Did you find anything?
- No, I didn't.
- Cone hats.
- I am looking for cone hats.
(Everyone focuses on
finding cone hats.)
- One minute remains.
- Isn't this it?
- Okay.
Isn't this it?
(It's a traffic cone,
not a cone hat.)
Isn't it a cone hat?
That isn't it.
For goodness' sake.
A cone hat.
I will go and hide now.
I need to hide.
You can't stay here. Go.
(Everyone starts to hide
when the hiding time nearly ends.)
(Peek-a-boo)
(The defensive teams finish hiding.)
(Jae Suk walks around
without hiding.)
I need to put a stamp on them.
(If he needs to put a stamp
on the sticks...)
Today,
we will have a race that concludes
the episodes with the prize draw.
Put a spy's stamp on your sticks
and the members' sticks secretly.
If the spies collect
the most number of sticks,
Team Spy will win.
Gosh, it will be hard.
(Jae Suk had to secretly put
a spy's stamp on the sticks.)
(When everyone left after lunch,)
(he approached a stick table.)
(He quickly put a stamp
on a few sticks...)
(and exited as if nothing happened.)
(While everyone was hiding,)
(he put a stamp on so many sticks.)
I should be careful
not to get ink on my hands.
(Who are the spies
in Team Actor and Team Singer?)
Now, put a bell on yourself.
(They put a bell on themselves.)
Now, you will go and find them.
You have 10 seconds.
- Good luck.
- Do well.
- Okay.
Five minutes came to an end.
Find the defensive teams.
(Where are they hiding?)
I can't see anything.
(Ringing)
I think someone is there.
(Se Chan is hiding
behind the curtain.)
(The sound of bells startle him.)
Someone... Someone is here.
Someone is here.
(He holds his breath.)
- Is someone here?
- Yes.
(To the left of the place
Ji Hyo and Do Hyun are searching,)
(Se Chan is hiding merely 5m away.)
Maybe in here.
(Maybe someone is in here.)
It's locked.
Is no one here?
(They don't look
behind the curtains.)
Where is Rowoon?
(Ji Hyo and Do Hyun
leave the studio.)
(He lets out a sigh of relief.)
What is this?
This is...
(My goodness.)
Hey.
So many sticks have a stamp.
This is insane.
How did this happen?
(Rowoon approaches the stick table.)
A spy must have stamped them.
(Halting)
This is no joke.
What?
(They don't notice Rowoon at first.)
(Finally, they spot him.)
(Suspicious)
- Is it you?
I thought one of you could be a spy.
(Rowoon runs away hurriedly
when they begin to suspect him.)
You...
Hey.
(Why is he running away?)
(Is Rowoon the spy in Team Actor?)
(Peeking)
- What are you doing?
- You startled me.
- Where did you find this?
(He gets scared easily.)
- What are you doing?
- Where did you find this?
- It was easy to find.
- Really?
- Hey.
- I am nervous.
(Ringing)
(They escape to the elevator.)
(Do Hyun follows the voices.)
(He suddenly turns
toward the elevator.)
(The door isn't closed yet.)
(It slowly begins to close,)
(but Do Hyun is
just around the corner.)
(Please close faster.)
(The doors are finally closed!)
(Do Hyun misses them in a pinch.)
(I definitely heard voices.)
(They breathe again.)
(They almost got caught.)
Where did you find it?
- It was easy to find.
- Let me try it on once.
My hair got matted.
What are you talking about?
How did you win an award
in the music and talk show division?
Let's get off.
Come on.
- I will go this way.
- Okay.
(They part ways again.)
(He finds a cone hat
right in front of him.)
Sae Ho, it's here. You are a fool.
What? How did you find that?
Where was it?
Se Chan.
Sae Ho, I found a cone over here.
Give me one. Is there one?
(Se Chan is nice.)
Hurry up.
You...
(Sae Ho, here is
a cone-shaped snack.)
- A cone-shaped snack.
- Forget it.
Are you talking about ice cream?
Here is a cone-shaped snack.
Hurry up and put it on.
(Put them on your fingers.)
He made fun of me.
(I have no time.)
(Meanwhile,
Jae Suk the spy is hiding.)
(He meets Haha,
the cone hat collector.)
Why do you have so many cone hats?
Are you making a tower?
It's like Dabo Pagoda.
Why aren't you doing anything?
What? What do you mean?
(He got caught.)
I am hiding.
Why aren't you doing anything else?
- What else should I do?
- Look for the cone hats.
I have seniority.
Why should I find the cone hats
when I have seniority?
(Something seems off
about Jae Suk.)
You are acting strange.
A mission for the representative
of the offensive team starts now.
Stick in 10 swords
into the barrel with 16 slots.
If the pirate pops up,
you must give one of your sticks...
to a member of a defensive team.
If the pirate doesn't pop up,
you can put a bell
on a member of a defensive team.
Let's start right away.
(Popping up)
(For goodness' sake.)
To which member
will you give a stick?
I will give a stick
to Haha of Team Singer.
It will go to Haha.
You heard the bells earlier, right?
You can't see me, right?
All right.
(Someone approaches
Team Actor's stick table.)
(This person begins to stamp
the spy's stamp.)
(Then the spy quickly leaves.)
No one is in the restroom, right?
- Gosh, you startled me.
- Ji Hyo.
- You startled me.
- You can't find anyone, right?
I can't find anyone.
This place is too big.
There must be someone in here.
(Rowoon heads somewhere
after a short conversation.)
- Rowoon. Rowoon. Rowoon.
- Yes?
Let's look once more.
I think someone is hiding in here.
Someone must be hiding in here.
It's the perfect place.
(She gets a hunch.)
(Jong Kook and Jin Young
are hiding nearby.)
- Seriously.
- Quiet.
Our bells are so loud.
(The sound of the bells approaches.)
(What?)
- Someone is there.
- Who is it?
(Who is it?)
(They shield
their eyes, nose, and mouth.)
(Unfortunately, the member
they found is Jong Kook.)
Who is it?
Cover your nose and mouth.
- I am sorry.
- Don't worry.
- I can't help it.
- It's okay.
(Ji Hyo moves in with a camera.)
(Jong Kook fights Ji Hyo off
with his nose and mouth covered.)
This is driving me crazy.
- Come on. Hold on.
- Where should I go?
- Keep covered.
- For goodness' sake.
(Rowoon attempts to get a photo.)
(Those who want a photo
versus Those who don't want a photo)
Come on.
- Who are they?
- Stop it.
Come on.
Look here.
- Look here.
- My face.
I will take a photo.
Hurry up and take a photo.
- Hurry up and take a photo.
- Hold on.
Hide.
I can't do it.
- Come on.
- We picked tough opponents.
- Take the picture.
- I got a photo of Jin Young.
- No.
- Did you get it?
- I got it.
- You should have stayed hidden.
(He got a photo that shows
her eyes, nose, and mouth.)
Jin Young is out.
- Who?
- Jin Young is out.
- Did he get a photo of her face?
- Yes, he did.
- Really?
- Yes. Who took it?
Look behind you!
(At that moment,)
(Do Hyun tries to get a photo
from outside the window.)
The window is reflective.
(Jong Kook stands his ground,)
(but Ji Hyo is tough.)
Come on.
(While Rowoon aims for his face,)
(Ji Hyo aims for his name tag.)
Come on!
We did it.
I got a photo of it! Kim Jong Kook!
(She succeeded to get
two characters in the photo.)
Rowoon, we caught the big fish.
We caught the big fish.
(Jong Kook is out.)
I had no clue
they were hiding over there.
The first race is over.
Five members of Team Comedian...
and two members of Team Actor
got eliminated.
Now, Team Singer will be
the offensive team.
They are dead.
- The other two teams will hide.
- Let's hide.
- Kwang Soo, we will be back.
- We will be back.
- We will get going.
- Sae Ho, you are in Team Comedian.
Why is a junior taking so long?
Senior Yang.
- Senior Yang.
- Do you want a beating?
(You punk.)
Don't raise your fist.
Sae Ho, we need to talk.
- Senior Yang.
- Listen.
- When the seniors leave...
- Are you a nagger?
I am not a nagger.
Why did you move so slowly?
I have a kind heart.
If you take advantage of that,
I will become a gangster.
- Why would you do that?
- You are such a nagger.
- I am the real nagger.
- I know that.
I know that.
- You are the worst nagger.
- I don't want to lose that title.
Here comes
the absolute worst nagger.
Who is talking so loudly
on the street?
I am sorry.
- It was you.
- It was me.
All right.
I will start from the bottom.
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, would you stay
with Jae Suk?
- Why?
- He is suspicious.
- He is acting strangely, right?
- Yes.
- I am suspicious of Jae Suk too.
- From now on...
- Stay with Jae Suk.
- Stay with him.
- I will trail him.
- Okay.
- Shall we work together?
- Yes.
Sae Ho.
- Where did you hide earlier?
- Over there.
There is a good spot.
Do you want to see it?
- On the first floor?
- Yes.
- The place with the black cloth.
- You're not a spy, are you?
I am not a spy.
- We think Rowoon is the spy.
- Really?
- We are suspicious of Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk?
- Yes.
- Seriously.
Rowoon and Jae Suk are
in the same agency too.
(What?)
- Really?
- They are in the same agency.
That has nothing to do
with the race.
Running Man wouldn't do that.
I know that,
but they are in the same agency.
- You and I are in the same agency.
- You are right.
- We are in the same agency.
- I also think...
Rowoon is suspicious.
He said,
"I think I know who the spy is."
Seriously.
- Let's hurry up and hide.
- Okay.
- See you later.
All right.
(Se Chan halts on his way to hide.)
This time,
can I hide here and see
if anyone does something?
I will hide here.
Should the cameras stay here?
That's right. Stay away.
I will be over here.
(Will Detective Yang's effort
pay off?)
You will go and find them
after two minutes.
Jong Kook can do something cute.
Do you want to see it?
Stop it.
- Where is Jong Kook?
- We got it on the camera.
Hurry up.
We got it on the camera.
They don't need to see it.
- Show them. It's cute.
- No, no.
- Hurry up and do it.
- For goodness' sake.
Why won't you do it now?
Please tell me in advance
if she is visiting the show.
I'm going to say it.
Where is Jong Kook?
Here.
(Here.)
What was that?
(They can't believe
what they heard.)
- What was that?
- Seriously.
- What was that, Jong Kook?
- What did you do just now?
- I don't even know.
She roped me into this.
- Where is Jong Kook?
- Here.
(They give an encore performance.)
(I don't want to hear it.)
Jong Kook.
I am cringing.
That was ridiculous. My goodness.
(Be quiet!)
"Here"? You make me laugh!
What's wrong with him?
(What's wrong with him?)
It's something Jin Young does.
You will leave in 10 seconds.
Don't edit this out.
Okay? Make sure you air this.
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
- Don't edit this out.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Don't make them edit it out.
- Let's go.
- We will be back.
- Bye.
- Do a good job.
- You have an important role.
(How many members
will Team Singer eliminate?)
- There is a spy in here.
- Where?
- Here.
- Among the three of us?
(Haha is acting strangely.)
Why are you laughing?
For goodness' sake.
Haha, you keep going around
on your own.
Jin Young,
get a hold of yourself.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Let's get them.
Where are they hiding?
It would be the best
to stay in here.
(Ringing)
(Startled)
(I hear a noise over there.)
(He enters a room.)
(Shouting)
(Excuse me.)
I am not here.
Please stand over there.
(While Suk Jin was looking
for a place to hide,)
(Jong Kook heard a shout.)
Hello.
(He follows the shout to the door.)
Didn't you hear something?
(Scary knocking)
Do you want to build a snowman?
Jin Young, we don't have time.
(Jin Young and Jong Kook
have manners.)
Hurry up and find him.
Oh, there he is.
(Did he spot Suk Jin?)
(A photo with eyes, nose, and mouth
or two characters of the name tag)
Jin Young, move.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay. Get ready.
(Will they be able to eliminate
Suk Jin?)
Pull him up.
All right.
Three.
(He pulls Suk Jin up easily.)
(All three characters of his name
are visible.)
All done.
How did you see me? Was I visible?
You were visible.
(Suk Jin gets eliminated
right away!)
I need to find a cone hat
(At that moment,)
(he spots the offensive team!)
(He runs away right away.)
(Haha runs after him!)
(My legs, save me.)
(Relaxed)
Just get a photo taken.
- Turn around.
- No.
- Hurry up and turn around.
Let me go this once.
- I will give you a prize!
- Okay, okay.
I will give you a prize.
I am serious.
I will give it to you
instead of my mom.
I am serious. Haha.
- I will give it to your mom.
- No, no.
But... Really?
- I will give it to your mom.
- No, no.
- But... Really?
- Yes. I will give it to your mom.
Let me get a photo.
- Really?
- It's okay.
Let's get a pretty photo.
One... If I get a prize,
I will give it to your mom.
- Look pretty. 1, 2, 3.
- Really?
(He gives a big smile.)
(Please give me the prize.)
- Really?
- Ma'am.
Ma'am, I will give you the prize...
- Mom, Haha made a promise.
- if I get it.
Ma'am, I love you. Stay healthy.
- I love you, Mom.
- Okay.
- Haha.
- Don't worry.
If I get the prize...
(Meanwhile, Sae Ho)
(He is doing something
with a yellow sign.)
(You can't see me, right?)
(His hiding place
grabs attention from afar.)
(The sound of bells approaches.)
(Sae Ho is here.)
(I got caught.)
(He got caught.)
- Jin Young, get ready.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook and Jin Young
get ready to work.)
1, 2, 3.
(A piece of cake)
(Humiliated)
(Sae Ho's hide-and-seek ends
in a humiliating fashion.)
He is so cute.
(I didn't expect this.)
I couldn't even find a cone hat.
(Sae Ho heads to the jail.)
I go down this way.
(He stumbles upon a stick table.)
(How many sticks
does everyone have?)
- What are you doing?
- Gosh, you startled me.
(Detective Yang attacks.)
I got you.
You tried to stamp them, right?
- What are you talking about?
- No.
- I saw it.
- For goodness' sake.
You tried to stamp them, right?
- What are you talking about?
- I saw it.
- For goodness' sake.
- Hold on.
Gosh, there is a lot.
So you were the spy.
You are a fool. You are a fool.
I waited all this time
to catch someone in the act.
You sneaked up.
- You tried to stamp the sticks.
- I will tell the truth.
- Sae Ho.
- I got eliminated already.
I get that, but why did you...
No. Since I got eliminated,
I can't do anything.
- I was just passing by.
- I know what I saw.
I am serious when I say this.
I am not a spy.
I am serious. I am not a spy.
I am sorry. I will get going now.
For goodness' sake.
Is he stupid or what?
My hunch was right.
My 23 years of experience paid off.
I knew he would come.
He actually came.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk,
the real spy...)
I will stamp all of them.
(He is running a factory.)
(Thus, Round 3 ends.)
(Team Singer eliminates 3 people.)
I will give you sticks
per the result of Round Three.
Do we get nine?
Haha and Sa Yeon, I caught a spy.
Are you certain?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Sae Ho is a spy.
- Sae Ho?
- My goodness.
One of them must be the spy.
What happened?
Gather around. I caught a spy.
For goodness' sake.
You are an utter fool.
It's no wonder he looked worried.
- Hey.
- You need to trust me.
You are a spy.
I got you. You are a spy.
- It's him! It's him!
- For goodness' sake.
- You kept acting suspiciously.
- The final results are out.
- Okay.
Like I told you before,
all the sticks with a spy's stamp
belong to Team Spy.
The sticks without a spy's stamp
belong to the respective team.
I checked earlier.
I'd rather be a spy.
They were all stamped.
This was Running Man Class Race
with seniors and juniors.
The team with the most number
of prize sticks is...
(This was a competition among
the three teams and Team Spy.)
(Out of the four teams,
which team has the most sticks?)
Team Spy with 88 sticks.
(Team Spy wins with 88 sticks.)
They stamped everything.
Yes, everything was stamped.
- We only have to find two.
- We can catch them.
We'll catch them.
Please write down...
three names of people
who you think are spies.
We'll count them and the three most
voted will stand on the platform.
We have to vote.
Let's recommend suspicious people
from each team.
- Okay.
- We have to write three names.
We know our own teams the best.
Sure. We'll deduce first.
I think it's Sae Ho.
I watched quietly for five minutes
without looking for the cone hat.
I watched to see
if anybody was stamping,
and he came along casually.
He approached the table
like the culprit...
and looked at Sa Yeon's sticks.
He reached for his back pocket.
I made a sound, and he got startled.
We got it.
- What was I supposed to say?
- Why did you do that?
- Old chap.
- Hey, old chap.
Why did you reach for
your back pocket?
- Old chap.
- Let's listen to him.
- Listen to Sae Ho.
- I'm telling the truth.
- My gosh.
- Sae Ho.
Do this motion. Show us.
- Let's see.
- I did this.
That was it.
- Let's see.
- I did this.
(That's obviously
the gesture of the culprit.)
- That's what...
- That looked so natural.
I caught him.
I rest my case.
It might be true.
- At that moment...
- You're bad.
Suk Jin.
(Screaming)
It's not me!
- Come on.
- Suk Jin.
- It's not me.
- Congratulations, Sae Ho.
- You had a huge role today.
- That's it.
We're finished.
- We're done.
- That's it.
- That's all for us.
- Thank you.
Team Singer is next.
We think...
it's either Haha
or if there's a huge twist,
- it could be Sa Yeon.
- It's not Sa Yeon.
Okay.
Let me say this.
These two went around together,
so they have an alibi.
- Right.
- But it's not me.
If Sa Yeon denies that it's her...
Is Haha usually that calm?
If he's a spy, he should be
screaming like him.
- It's not me.
- He should be screaming like him.
- I'm not a spy.
- Old chap, stop it.
Who's the spy? Say it.
Who's the spy on their team?
- Jae Suk.
- Hold on.
We'll ask him who it is.
- Say it.
- Who is it?
Who is the spy on this team?
I'm not a spy, so I don't know!
- Who is it?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Fine.
- The person in charge...
Fine. Stop it.
Go on the platform, and we'll know.
If you consider
one tangible evidence,
Jong Kook danced in the back.
- I recommend him because...
- Over that?
- Because...
- She asked me.
Don't do anything.
- You're doing that again.
- Don't do anything.
Stop it!
He's the spy!
- I'm telling you!
- I'm going to splash water on you.
I'll splash this on you
so that you come to your senses.
(Goodness!)
I'll write your name
so that you get more attention.
That's enough.
- Why would you write my name?
- Stop it.
(Jae Suk can't hide his smile.)
It might be Jae Suk.
It might be him.
Sae Ho is too enraged,
so I don't think it's him.
Sae Ho is too frustrated.
It's not me.
Let's listen to Team Actor.
We think it's Rowoon.
- You two talked.
- We picked him out...
- What's the reason?
- from the beginning.
Because of what happened
when we were the offensive team,
we were suspicious of him.
That's what I said.
I said it was Rowoon
from the beginning.
It's because you only look at him.
- No, Ji Hyo. That's not true.
- It is.
- It's so true.
- Let's vote now.
- No, but...
- I wasn't even funny.
- No.
- We thought it was him too.
I don't think it's Rowoon.
Each person will write down
three names.
- 3 names?
- 1 per team. Yes.
Let's go with our gut feeling.
Our gut feeling.
(If they don't catch 2 of 3 spies,
the spies win.)
I'm done.
I'm not sure.
(Which 3 will get the most votes
and stand on the platform?)
- I don't know.
- Me neither. This is a headache.
It's not easy to guess all three.
This is not easy.
- Everybody.
- Yes.
- We have the final result.
- Okay.
The first person with
the most number of votes was...
(Most voted on Team Actor)
Rowoon. Please come on up.
Rowoon.
We had no choice.
- We know this is unfair.
- Exactly.
On Team Singer, it was Haha.
Me?
(Most voted on Team Singer was
Haha with 7 votes.)
I can't do anything
because of Jin Young.
(Jong Kook and Jin Young were
together the whole time.)
That's true.
It's Dong Hoon then.
(Haha went around by himself.
Is he the spy on Team Singer?)
(Haha had 7 votes,
and Jong Kook had 5.)
On Team Comedian,
it was Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk?
- This is insane.
Why didn't you pick Sae Ho?
- You're right.
- It's Sae Ho.
You people!
Why didn't you pick Sae Ho?
- Didn't you write Sae Ho's name?
- Why didn't you pick him?
- You didn't pick Sae Ho?
- Didn't you write Sae Ho's name?
I saw with my own eyes.
- Why didn't you write his name?
- Why didn't you pick him?
- I wrote him down.
- It's not me, Se Chan.
Why didn't you write his name down?
Sae Ho, did you write
your own name or not?
Why would I write my own name?
It's not me.
That's true. My bad.
Why is it me all of a sudden?
- Hey.
- My gosh.
If there are 2 or more spies
from these 3,
Team Spy loses, and the next team
with most sticks wins.
I thought Jae Suk didn't do
anything today.
I did nothing.
First, Suk Jin,
please remove Rowoon's name tag.
- Okay. Is it on the name tag?
- Yes.
- 1.
- All right. 1, 2, 3.
(Rowoon was not a spy.)
- He's not?
- Oh, dear.
I can't do it. I can't lie.
- Wait.
- I'm really bad at lying.
- It's Kwang Soo then.
- It's not me.
- I swear it's not me.
- It's not Rowoon?
I swear it's not me.
Let's go with Haha next.
- Let's reveal both together.
- It's Ji Hyo.
- Together.
- 1, 2, 3.
(Jae Suk's already resigned himself
but Haha will decide the winner.)
(If Haha is not a spy,
Jae Suk's Team Spy wins.)
- 2, 3.
(Haha was not a spy.)
- He's a spy.
- Hey!
See? It's not me.
(Team Spy wins.)
- What's this?
- He's a spy.
(I told you it wasn't me!)
You...
- Come here! I told you it's not me!
- Hold on. Sae Ho.
- I told you!
- Sae Ho.
It's Jong Kook!
I said it was Jong Kook.
It's not him.
(Sae Ho finally proves
his innocence.)
You failed to catch the spies,
so Team Spy wins.
All right!
I'll reveal the identities
of the other two winners.
- Who are they?
- Okay.
- Today's spies were...
- It's Jong Kook.
Jae Suk,
Jong Kook, and Do Hyun.
(Do Hyun and Jong Kook
were spies as well.)
(This is where Jong Kook was
most suspected.)
(He danced with elaborate steps...)
(and sealed the spy's stamp.)
(When he was talking to Jin Young,)
(he stamped without her knowing.)
(Do Hyun framed Rowoon as the spy.)
(He followed Rowoon around
and was bold about stamping.)
Spy.
(I was the spy.)
Jong Kook and Do Hyun.
(Team Spy wins.)
- Me? Was it me?
- Come here.
I said it was Do Hyun.
- You should have argued.
- I told you.
- Why didn't you argue?
- I did.
I told you
he was dancing in the back!
- You did.
- Okay.
I was dancing and stamping.
Okay.
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and Do Hyun
get to pick the prizes.)
Team Spy obtained 88 sticks,
so each person can pick 3
to a total of 9.
Today's my last chance,
so I have to win something.
- The Almighty gave you nothing.
- They gave me nothing.
They didn't give you this.
Do Hyun, arrange the cards.
(Do Hyun will move the cards.)
I usually get the 40s.
- In the 40s?
- Yes.
I'll move the tablet computer
to the 40s.
- Number seven.
- I'll go with this.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this!
Starting with Do Hyun, pick three.
- Go in order.
- This is the last time.
Everything's up for grabs.
- Is this the last time?
- Yes.
Please take the massage chair.
(He picked 3.)
I'll give you a good one.
What is it?
Wait.
- What is it?
- You have to show us.
(What did he get?)
What are you doing by yourself?
- Why, Do Hyun?
- Number 11.
What is it?
- Premium wet wipes.
It has premium on it.
- Okay. And then?
- And then?
Number 21.
- Dud.
- Dud. And then?
- Is it number 1?
- Number 48.
A bar of gold.
(Number 48 is a bar of gold!)
You took a really good one.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
Take it.
I'll go next.
- Thank you.
- I'm rooting for you.
It's a dud.
Is it a dud?
- What is it?
- What number is it?
- A gift card.
(Jong Kook's number 33 is
a 10-dollar gift card!)
Gift card.
- That's amazing.
- Is it 10 dollars?
- That's better than nothing.
- It's better than nothing.
I have a good feeling.
- I'm going to do really well.
- It's going to be big, right?
It's going to be big today.
- This is your last chance.
- Right.
I'll go right away.
- What is it?
- Number 24.
(Jae Suk's 1st number is 24!)
Massage from Jong Kook.
(Massage from Jong Kook!)
Yes.
You're incredible.
- How incredible. I'm sick of this.
- You're truly incredible.
- This is something big.
- This is so strange.
- I have two left.
- My gosh.
- Number 3 or 30.
- I have 2 left.
I have number eight.
- Number eight?
- Oh, dear.
I'm speechless.
This is a big deal.
Give me some energy!
- Jae Suk! Jae Suk!
Last one.
I think this is good.
- This one.
- It's good. It's two digits.
Number 42.
(Can he avoid his unlucky fate?)
(Suk Jin's face cushion!)
There you go!
(This is the class
of the unlucky one.)
Use this as a pillow.
- It's a pillow.
- You can get the massage now.
Lie down. Put this under your head.
Put it under your head.
- Put it under your head.
- You actually picked it.
- Here.
- This is the worst outcome.
- Lie down. Here.
- My gosh.
- Massage.
- This is absolutely the worst.
- Nothing can be worse than this.
- I know.
- Let's just get it over with.
- Okay.
(It's the perfect scene
for the grand finale.)
Darn it.
A little more.
Go ahead and hug the cushion.
That's enough.
Okay.
You got the life-sized Lee Kwang Soo
figure and Ji Suk Jin cushion.
You guys never leave me alone.
(The members are at a campground
to celebrate the 500th episode.)
(Celebrating the 500th episode
of Running Man)
(They have 5 guests
to celebrate the 500th episode.)
(Bo Mi and Cho Rong of Apink)
(Yoo Jung of Weki Meki,
Chungha, Mi Joo of Lovelyz)
(Seasonal food to celebrate spring)
(However...)
(They create shocking scenes
with paint all over their body.)
(Even Harlequin is here.)
(However...)
(While their eyes are covered,)
(they are dragged away somewhere.)
(There's the protagonist
of the camping...)
(who tries to eliminate everyone.)
(Who's the greedy one
who terrorized the campground?)
(500th episode, Greedy Camp Race,
Did you eat before running around?)