(A day in March that feels
like spring is around the corner)
- What's all this?
- My gosh.
- What is all this?
- Gosh, that's going on?
This is so nice.
Wait. What's with the violin?
- What is this?
- There's a red carpet.
- Hello.
(The microphone wearing ceremony
for excellent members?)
- Hello.
The microphone wearing ceremony
for excellent members?
Does that mean
I'm not an excellent member?
Suk Jin, you can stand on
the straw mat.
You should be here, Suk Jin.
I can't believe this.
- Why on a straw mat...
- Go to the straw mat.
(The reason Suk Jin gets
pushed to the straw mat is...)
(He took last place last week,
so he was decided to get a penalty.)
(He's supposed to shoot
the intro without a microphone.)
Should I be here?
Gosh, this is so...
What is going on? This is like...
(Just sit on the ground.)
It's just about a microphone.
Why do I not get a chair?
I'm supposed to do this
only without a microphone.
- This is so nice.
- Why would you do that?
Gosh, they're bringing something in.
Suk Jin should dress up
like a criminal then.
(Something is being served
on a silver platter.)
- This isn't funny.
- Thank you.
(The thing
on the silver platter is...)
Now we should talk.
We can talk now.
We will put them on you
if you stay seated.
- Will you put this on me?
- Yes.
I haven't been
treated like this before.
It feels so awkward. I just
got on my knees before I knew it.
Thank you.
- What's going on?
- The audio director usually says,
"Please put on the microphone."
She usually sounds very chic,
but she got on one knee today.
I like the system here.
What should I do?
Can you even hear me?
You can't?
Do you hear me or not?
- Why?
- They can't hear you, Suk Jin.
They can't hear my voice.
They don't even look at Suk Jin.
I shouldn't look at him.
(Haha looks around
right at the moment.)
(He drops something.)
(A macaroon)
(Humiliated)
He'll ask for more.
You can't do that already.
He's eating it already.
(After hesitating a while,)
(he puts it in his mouth secretly.)
My gosh.
(He tries to keep his last pride.)
Look at Suk Jin.
He picked it up and ate it.
- You can't do that.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
Who told you to share
your food with Suk Jin?
Don't give it to him.
- Haha did it.
- You shouldn't do that.
Look at him.
- He's eating it.
- Look at him.
All right. We have
pleasant guests for today.
I will bring them in.
Who are they?
(The black toes
look somewhat familiar.)
- This music is...
- It's "I've missed you, my friend."
My gosh.
(Is he the guy we know?)
(He's here.)
- Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo!
(They all stand up to greet him.)
(Emotional)
Kwang Soo.
(Glad)
- Gosh, he's here.
- Hello.
- You're back.
- Hi.
- He's here.
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo. You should wear socks.
I can't wear socks.
Your foot must be cold.
Kwang Soo, I've really missed you.
I know. I've missed you too.
(He's back with a bright smile.)
- I'm glad he can walk on crutches.
- I know.
(He's excited to see Kwang Soo too.)
Why are you sitting on the ground?
(What is he doing there?)
He took last place yesterday.
This is a penalty.
- It's a penalty.
- He doesn't have a microphone.
I don't need to talk to him then.
That's right. You don't.
Suk Jin called me a lot
when I was in the hospital.
Really?
He called me
right after I got surgery.
He said he even went hiking
in a wheelchair when he was injured.
Did he go hiking in a wheelchair?
My mom heard it...
and said,
"Suk Jin is such an old fossil."
He kept saying that.
"When I was your age..."
"I went hiking in a wheelchair
after my surgery."
He's so awful.
(He's making an excuse.)
He still sounds like that.
And we have real guests
for today's Running Man.
Really?
Is there someone else?
(Who is the guest
for today's Running Man?)
- It's Daniel.
- Hello.
Hello.
(Kang Daniel has topped the idol
charts for 103 weeks.)
(Kang Daniel is ranked 1st
before his comeback.)
(He shows his sexy charm on stage.)
(And he shows his cute
and naive charm on Running Man.)
He's getting more handsome.
You've become a lot cooler.
- Come here.
- Daniel!
- Welcome.
- Wow.
(They react in totally
different ways to him.)
Daniel, please tell us
how you've been doing.
I've been getting ready
to make my comeback.
- I see.
- Thank you...
for having me here again
after a long time.
We and a lot of fans
have waited for your comeback.
Welcome, Daniel.
Thank you.
(I'm here too.)
- Daniel, can you sing our new song?
- Sure.
- Please give him a big hand.
- I'll show you a little.
I'm excited.
(Kang Daniel's comeback is
revealed in Running Man.)
(His new song, "2U" will be
released on March 24.)
His steps are so light.
(The groovy beats and dance
are perfect for warm spring.)
He's so good.
This is Kang Daniel's dance.
(It's something they can
rarely see in Running Man.)
- His steps are so light.
- It's so light.
He's so nimble.
- My gosh.
- I'm so jealous.
(The ending makes
people's hearts flutter.)
This is it.
(The ending makes
people's hearts flutter.)
Tell me
(Hello?)
(They are just acting up.)
What was that, Suk Jin?
(Would you like some makgeolli?)
(Today's race begins in earnest.)
Today,
we will have a family race
where three moms will be captains.
- Are there moms?
- Moms?
We will have three guests
who have shown...
impressive acting as a mom.
And they are waiting
in each room of the building.
Really?
- Moms.
- Really?
The door of each room says
what kind of child they want.
If you think it applies to you,
you can enter and complete a family.
If there are too many children
in a room,
or you don't like the mom you chose,
- When I don't like my mom?
- you can move to another room.
We can move to another room.
Jae Suk, Haha, and Kwang Soo.
- Go to your moms first.
- Okay.
- Can we go now?
- Yes. This way, please.
Wait.
(Jae Suk, Haha, and Kwang Soo are
here to see their moms.)
- Gosh, this is...
- Hang on.
(The moms wrote
about the children they want.)
"A good-looking child"?
"A child with a good appetite"?
I do have a good appetite.
Good-looking?
My looks...
To be honest,
I'm not so good-looking.
But I'm not that bad.
- I don't even want to answer that.
- Since when?
I know that
I don't have great looks.
- But...
- I don't know what to say.
Why does he seem so confident?
You don't belong to any room.
You're just like Se Chan.
You're Se Chan's level.
I can say you are smart.
- Me?
- You are smart.
Let's say you're smart,
and you have a good appetite.
Kwang Soo, which room
are you going to?
I'm going to Room 101.
What's Room 101?
It's good looks.
- He's trying to be funny.
- Haha.
- He should be funny.
- What are you talking about?
I will let you
choose first, Kwang Soo.
You can be funny all you want.
- Okay.
- If I have to choose one thing...
Okay. Just go.
(Who are the moms
in the three different rooms?)
(A good-looking child)
I want Jae Suk to be here.
What if I burst into laughter?
(Where should I go?)
- Where should I go?
- Then...
should I go to the room
as a child with a good appetite?
(Kwang Soo goes to Room 101 where
the mom wants a good-looking child.)
(Cautious)
- Gosh, hello.
- Welcome.
(Whose voice is this?)
- Pardon?
- Come on in.
Are you alone?
(She has a charismatic voice.)
(Mom Hwang Young Hee)
What about Dong Sik?
(She can show
incredible maternal love...)
(and also pull off a strong mother.)
- Come on in.
- Okay. I'm on my way.
(She sounds charismatic
scolding him.)
(This mom is too scary.
I should go to another room.)
I'm sorry, but can you help me?
You're injured for real.
My gosh.
When did you get hurt?
You sound like a real mom.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Jae Suk. You're the smart one.
You should go to
the Intelligent Room.
I'm afraid to go there.
Which one of us is smarter here?
You even know a lot of idioms.
Knowing idioms doesn't mean smart.
You're the smart one here.
- Get off me.
- I should go to this room.
I'm the only one
who can be here.
(She's waiting for children
with a good appetite.)
(Mom Lee Il Hwa)
- Jae Suk. Come on in.
- It's Il Hwa.
(She's a mom with an open hand.)
(She's also generous
when it comes to acting.)
Come on in.
- Il Hwa.
- Yes.
- What are you doing?
- Are you hungry?
Yes. What are you doing here?
Have a seat.
Gosh, why are you making gimbap?
You know what?
I don't know what
other moms are like,
but my mom is the prettiest one.
I think my mom is the best.
(Mom Il Hwa is like a shy girl.)
I should go to the Intelligent Room.
Actually, I'm quite intelligent.
(Who's the mom
waiting for a smart child?)
Mi Sun. Gosh.
I mean, Mom.
Where are other guys?
Why are you alone?
(Mom Park Mi Sun
looks like a mom in reality.)
(She was Mi Dal's mom
in "Soonpoong Clinic.")
(And she's a famous comedian,
Park Mi Sun.)
Have a seat.
Gosh, this is
like "Soonpoong Clinic."
- Come in and have a seat.
- Okay.
- Why are you alone.
- One went to the Good-looking Room.
- Have you been doing well?
- This is no laughing matter.
My gosh. You seem so serious.
Do you think
this report card is a joke?
(What is she talking about
a report card all of a sudden?)
- Hello.
- Are you shooting us now?
- Yes.
Are we shooting something?
The camera is on.
This is a family race where
three moms are the captains.
You are the moms
and the captains of each team.
Children will go into
the rooms they want...
and join your skit.
Only the children who complete your
secret mission can be your team.
Young Hee's mission is
I take after Mom,
I'm sick and tired of how I look,
and I do the splits over 2m.
And Mi Sun's mission is
I take after Lee Bong Won,
How can love change?,
and doing mental calculations.
Il Hwa's mission is
this is how it should taste,
doing a double thumbs up,
and having ice cream
covered in sesame oil.
As soon as you complete
a family of four, you get a benefit.
So you should lead your children
to say or do your missions.
Can we name the children we want
all at the same time?
- Haha.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
I want Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin?
- Is he older than me?
How old is he?
He's one year older than me.
I don't want him.
(She doesn't want a son
who's older than her.)
(The moms start their skits
to get their children.)
You know what?
If you studied
according to my plans,
your grades would've been good
enough for the Ivy League.
How is this possible?
You placed at the top of your class
during the midterm.
But you took 200th place
in the finals.
Can you believe this?
- My life...
- Are you still...
seeing that wench?
I told you not to date her.
I said you can date good girls
once you go to college.
Enough of college talk.
That's enough. Stop it.
What's your problem?
We've already talked about this.
You should break up with her.
(You should break up with her.)
Mom, I have three children.
You have three children already?
(Speechless)
My gosh. I can't believe this.
What should I do with him?
You should focus on your studies.
Everything has its time.
What's your problem?
Where did you get that from?
Who do you take after?
Lee Bong Won. It's Lee Bong Won!
(Lee Bong Won!)
(It's done.)
Haha. You succeeded.
- Did I succeed?
- Yes.
(What is going on?)
Am I intelligent?
- Did I make it?
- Obviously, you're my son.
You are my child.
Now you can complete...
- your family with your mom.
- Okay.
Bring the other kids.
Bring smart ones.
Who do you want?
What about Ji Suk Jin?
Well...
Bring him if he has nowhere to go.
- I bet he has nowhere to go.
- Okay.
He's a pathetic guy.
I will give you an acting lesson.
You should be a celebrity.
- Me?
- Sure.
You are so talented.
You're very tall.
- I'm...
- Because you take after your dad.
And who did you...
get your face from?
(Who did you get your face from?)
I take after you, my mom.
That's right.
(I take after Mom.)
Mom. So she's my mom...
(Young Hee's first son
is Kwang Soo.)
- Hello, Young Hee.
- Gosh, So Min.
- Hello.
- Come in.
Just come on in.
This is the Good-looking Room.
That's why I'm here.
We have a lot of good-looking
members here, but why...
I think you picked the wrong room.
- Have a seat.
- You came to the wrong room.
Hello, Young Hee.
Hello.
Why are you making gimbap?
You wanted to eat gimbap.
You told me
you wanted to eat my gimbap.
Did I?
(Jae Suk can't help
but feel confused.)
So I made a lot of gimbap for you.
(She's a loving mom
with giving hands.)
- You wanted to eat gimbap.
- It has chili peppers in it.
I know. It's very spicy.
- I see.
- Do you like spicy food?
You should taste it...
- and see if it's your mom's gimbap.
- Okay.
- Try this and tell me.
(Open your mouth.)
(Taking a big bite)
Do you like it? Is it spicy?
Is it what you used to eat?
Yes, it is.
- What?
- I must say...
(This is how it should taste.)
this is what I used to eat.
(She fails her mission.)
I stopped eating gimbap since then.
- Who is it?
- What?
- Il Hwa.
- Hello.
Come on in, sweetheart.
(Come on in and have some gimbap.)
Mom.
Mom, what is this?
Is it spicy gimbap?
You know what?
- Mom's gimbap...
- Tell me if this tastes right.
is really spicy.
(It exceeds the limit of spiciness.)
- Gosh, the aftertaste is so...
- Is this...
Mom, your second son is here.
This is your second son.
- Mom.
- Look who's here.
This isn't a joke.
Come on in.
- Gosh, this is so...
- Come have a seat.
- I feel so comfortable around Mom.
- Me too.
My mom is about my age.
My mom was in "Soonpoong Clinic."
I'm in trouble.
- Is she your age?
- My gosh.
- What should I do?
- Mom.
- Should I call you Mom or Mi Sun?
- She's your mom!
- You.
- I'm sorry.
- Yes?
Are you sure these are your grades?
- How did we do?
- What's wrong?
You used to be at the top
of the class.
What's going on?
- 200th place?
- Is this possible?
- I used to be in 1st place.
- Our grades plummeted.
- What happened?
Why are our grades fluctuating?
You guys are strangers to us.
Our family never had kids like you.
- Who are you?
- I'm...
- Why are you...
- the firstborn?
- He's your eldest brother.
- He is?
- Haha.
- Where are your manners?
Go get the stick.
- Yes, Mom.
- What is this?
I'll bring one.
(He's making the situation worse.)
(He tells her to reproach them.)
Especially this punk right here!
(You need to chew him out
the most!)
- Break his legs!
- There's the stick.
- Got it.
- Give that to me.
There is one.
I have somewhere to be.
- Goodness.
- Don't let them off easy.
Sit down. Where do you think
you're going?
- Well...
- Gosh.
Why does the youngest
look like that?
Am I the youngest?
Don't you remember what I told you?
You age if you meet too many girls.
I've also wanted...
to fall in love.
Your dad once told me that
he'd never make me suffer.
But look at me now.
I'm suffering so much.
Do you think love lasts forever?
That's not true.
Love doesn't last a long time.
You think your love
may last forever,
but that's not true.
Bong Won looked lonely too.
I met him at a sauna recently,
and he was eating alone.
How dare you call your dad
by his first name?
- Where are your manners?
- How could you call him that?
He was eating all alone.
Listen to me.
Love doesn't last forever.
I'm begging you.
Say something.
- Mom.
- Hold on. It seems like...
- All right.
- we need to say something.
- It does.
- Right?
- Do you think love lasts forever?
That's not true.
Love doesn't last forever.
Love is...
Love changes after three years!
- Love changes!
- Love can always change!
- And...
- I keep telling you...
that love changes after three years!
- That's spicy.
- Yes, a bit.
Mom likes to make spicy dishes.
- Isn't it tasty?
- Yes.
What do you do to show
that it's good?
- What?
- What do you do?
(He looks gloomy.)
What do you do to show
that it's good?
Why is this so spicy?
It's Portuguese.
- Portuguese?
- They do it in Brazil.
What do you do to show
that it's good?
(What do Brazilians say
if something's tasty?)
- Thumbs up.
- Okay!
(Il Hwa's Secret Mission:
Double thumbs up)
But...
you do it with two hands.
(How do you do it with both hands?)
- Thumbs up?
- Yes.
Double thumbs up!
(He gives two thumbs up.)
(You're the best.)
- Jae Suk, you've succeeded.
- What now?
- You and Il Hwa are a family.
- Yes!
- Who is it?
- Thumbs up.
- Daniel!
- Hello.
- Hey.
- He's our youngest.
- Come on in. Welcome.
- Hello.
Who went to Room 101
in your stead?
- Se Chan.
- No way.
(Se Chan went
to the Good-looking Room?)
- Not you?
- No, Se Chan went there.
- No way. You didn't go there?
- No, Se Chan did.
He's handsome.
- Where's Room 101?
- You guys...
Where is it? Is it here?
I'm representing Dongducheon.
- Se Chan the Handsome is here.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Leave. Don't be ridiculous.
- Hey!
- Get out.
- Mom.
- Hello, Mom.
- Get out.
- Why?
- This makes no sense.
- Mom.
- Mom. Hi.
- You and Jae Suk are...
- He's fine.
- Mom.
- I'm Se Chan the Handsome.
He's not your son. Look at his face.
Hello, Mom.
I'm good-looking.
I'd like to see how flexible
you guys are.
So Min, can you show me...
a leg split?
Are you flexible?
No.
- Split our legs?
- But I'll do anything...
to become your son.
I can rip my mouth as well.
- How should I do it?
- I should measure it.
Like this?
- You're very flexible.
- Gosh.
(Stretching)
She might touch the ground.
200cm.
I want to have a good-looking mom.
I need to be in this family as well.
You don't belong here.
You're not her son.
(She wants to destroy
the family tree.)
You're not her son.
- Se Chan.
- Just...
If you can't split that well,
it means you're rejecting me.
Not at all. Mom, I can do this.
(Mom, I can do this.)
Hey.
(He fails.)
- All right. Measure it.
- You're...
blatantly rejecting me.
- How much is it?
- 180cm.
(He fails.)
I'm not even 180cm tall.
You were never...
Get lost.
What did you say?
(She rejects him.)
Fine, then!
Get lost if you don't want
to get hit.
I'm going to find a new mom.
- Okay, just watch me.
- Watch what?
My goodness.
- What?
- Welcome.
Goodness. Wait.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
They're strict about looks.
So get lost.
- I've already found a family.
- You should leave.
- Really?
- Daniel, come in.
- Come in.
- He's the best-looking one.
She told me to get lost.
- She said that to me.
- Did you say that?
- Hey.
- He failed, right?
- Well...
- She told me to get lost.
I told him to get lost for now.
She told me to get lost.
(The terrible son leaves.)
- Fine.
- Come here.
- Goodness.
- Where were you?
You came well. You are good-looking.
- You failed.
You're my younger brother.
You belong here.
Thank you.
Sit down.
(Her voice becomes softer.)
I do recognize your face.
- You're a famous idol.
- He's Daniel.
- His name is Kang Daniel.
- I'm Kang Daniel.
- You're Kan Daniel?
- Yes.
- It's Kang, not Kan.
- You're him?
- Yes.
I'm sorry. I do know you.
But I didn't think
it'd really be you.
- You thought he was a lookalike?
- Yes.
(She's happy to have found
a proper heir to the family line.)
I didn't know it was really you.
It's me, Mom.
Daniel. All right.
- Uncle.
- Who is it?
- Father.
(They address him differently.)
- Goodness.
- What is this?
- Are you busy?
- Hello.
Hello.
(She looks reluctant to see him.)
- You were here?
- Have you found a family?
I was...
- You don't have the looks.
- somewhere else.
I didn't like the other mom.
(She's disappointed that
he hasn't found a family.)
I went to the Intelligent Room.
I had to keep solving problems.
(Unaware of how she feels,
he keeps complaining.)
- Sit down.
- Okay.
Mom has a plan.
Aren't we around the same age?
Come on.
- Get into character.
- Yes, Mom.
Look into the mirror
and tell me how you look.
Try role-playing by yourself.
Role-playing?
She didn't make us do that.
Suk Jin, you've been blessed
with charms since you were born.
You're way too humble.
Why are you so timid
when you're this good-looking?
Have confidence.
I think it's best that you leave.
(She agrees silently.)
Ever since the beginning,
she wasn't happy with me.
- That's not true.
- No, I think you weren't.
- You see...
- Is this family set?
- No.
- Just say that it is,
and I'll leave.
- Should I?
- Yes.
(He tries to save face.)
- Should I?
- Yes.
(That would be great.)
Goodness!
None of us had to role-play.
I shouldn't have come.
I should've known better.
Suk Jin.
If you're feeling too lonely,
you can come back.
- Okay, Mom.
- I will...
- always be waiting.
- Mom!
- I'll see you later.
- But first,
- So you're all set.
- you should be independent.
That's not the way out.
That's the bathroom.
What?
- Where do I go?
- Over there.
- Mom, bye.
- Suk Jin.
- He's definitely not one of us.
- I just want you...
- to become independent.
- Bye, Mom!
You can come back
if you're struggling or lonely.
Okay!
This isn't good.
I'm running out of places to go.
I am.
- Mom
- Se Chan!
Dad
We have finally met
Goodness.
We've finally met.
- Se Chan.
- Hello.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
- Aren't you hungry?
- I'm famished.
- Have some.
- Okay.
Open wide.
How does it taste?
Does it taste like the one
from before?
(The spiciness spreads
throughout his body.)
(The taste brings tears
to his eyes.)
This brings tears to my eyes.
It's really good.
Really?
How does it taste?
What?
- It's full of love.
- You were here.
She's my mom.
- Right?
- It's really spicy.
- Her cooking skills have changed.
- I was dying too.
- Since it's spicy...
- It is.
This is honey.
- It's ice cream with honey.
- Have some.
(It's a mixture of sweet ice cream
and nutty sesame oil.)
This is honey.
It's full of honey. I made it.
(It's very greasy.)
(What is this unfamiliar taste?)
He knows how to react well.
He's fit for this family.
(He reacts as best as he can.)
Look at him.
He's good.
Goodness, Mom!
- This is...
- The greasiness is killing me!
- Gosh!
- Try it.
I'm thinking about opening...
- an ice cream shop.
- Right.
- Try it.
- Gosh.
I really thought it was honey.
Gosh, the inside of my mouth
is glistening.
(His mouth is full of greasiness.)
- How much does he need to eat?
- Six spoonfuls.
Go on.
(He finds a pile of gimbap
underneath the cloth.)
Do I need to finish all this?
No.
(Startled)
- I'm out!
- No!
- I'm going! I can't eat all that!
- I might die!
- No!
- I'm on an empty stomach!
Eat it.
Eat up.
(Thanks to her motherly love,
she feeds him more.)
It's not easy to become a family.
Eat up.
- You little punk.
- This is your last.
(Good boy. Eat up.)
- Done.
- Hold on. Where's the water?
- You're done.
- Have some water.
- Here.
- You're done.
- Drink up.
- Good.
- Good job.
Good job. Here.
Give me a minute.
- Goodness. Have some more.
- I won't be a part of this family.
- Have one more.
- Just this much.
- Wait.
You only need to have
three spoonfuls.
- Hurry up.
- Eat some.
- What is that?
- I'm begging you.
- Look at her.
- Mom.
- Hold on.
- You disrespectful son!
How dare you make your mother kneel.
Everything in here
is good for your immune system.
All I want is for you to be healthy.
You want me as your son?
- Of course, I do.
- Of course.
That's why I got down on my knees.
- Hold on.
- We all...
- have protruding teeth.
- Oh, dear.
There's no doubt
that you're my brother.
We don't take after our mom.
We look like our dad,
hence the protruding teeth.
- Right.
- Now eat.
- There.
- Good boy.
So...
My gosh!
- He cleared the bowl.
- Since you cleared the bowl,
you are now part of Il Hwa's family.
I finally met my family!
Jong Kook, welcome to the family.
What a relief.
How can love change?
My youngest daughter,
- I will give you a pop quiz.
- Sure.
You must calculate
the numbers in your head.
Sure.
What is 13 multiplied by 4 plus 8?
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo's brain
is fully activated.)
If it's too hard for you,
just run out of here.
I'll search for my next mother.
Ji Hyo, is it too difficult?
Should I ask you another one?
What is 24 multiplied by 2...
plus 30?
- 23?
- 24 multiplied by...
- 2...
- 24 multiplied by 2.
Plus 30.
(Mi Sun is unfazed
by Ji Hyo's ridiculous response.)
What is 24 multiplied by 2 plus 30?
- It's difficult.
- Right?
It's 78.
- That's correct.
- Is it?
My gosh. No way!
- I did it.
- Unbelievable.
Can you believe it?
- Nice.
- How did you do it?
- No way.
- Awesome.
All right then.
- So Daniel...
- Yes?
- Look in the mirror.
- And?
And talk to yourself.
Think of this as an acting class.
What is it like to look
in the mirror every day?
Compared to Suk Jin,
you're giving him a lot of chances.
I'm a human being after all.
Yes, of course.
- Go ahead.
- What's with your hair?
The color's off and
the eyebrows are weird.
When did you dye your hair?
- Two days ago.
- I see...
you don't like keeping it one color.
- Right.
- If that's the case,
how do you feel about it?
I mean...
You're being direct.
Must you be this direct?
- Se Chan and Suk Jin...
- I'm just saying what I want to.
- My hair...
- I understand, but...
- Still...
- I'm fed up with it.
- What?
And so...
put that in four syllables.
Are you kidding me?
- She's feeding him the answer.
- In four syllables.
- It has turned into a quiz show.
- My face...
- Your hair...
- I'm fed up with it.
My gosh.
(Young Hee is desperate,
but Daniel is clueless.)
S and K...
Are you kidding me?
(Even moms are allowed to be fans.)
Is this allowed?
Gosh, how sickening.
- What?
- Oh, no.
- That's so close!
- Is that not it?
- Unbelievable.
- I'll give you one last chance.
- Sure.
- It's not some foreign flavor.
Right. This is how it should taste.
- Correct!
- This is how it should taste.
(Il Hwa is the second mom
to complete her family.)
We did it.
- Did I get it right?
- Suk Jin succeeded.
Then...
Be harsher with your words.
It should be harsher, right?
I'm sick and tired of it.
(Young Hee's hidden mission)
(That's it!)
Gosh, that wasn't easy.
- It wasn't easy to guess.
- I know.
It wasn't easy.
(The teams)
Please welcome your moms
who are also your team leaders.
Park Mi Sun, Lee Il Hwa,
and Hwang Young Hee.
(Let's have a good time, Moms.)
I know we're just
playing a game here, but...
how can Suk Jin...
call Il Hwa as his mom?
I'm having
a hard time accepting this.
It's making me angry.
You see it in real life though.
There are sons who look
older than their moms.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- Mom.
- It's making me angry.
Also, he's her youngest son.
- That's just how it is.
- He's younger than I am.
That's ridiculous.
He's first, I'm second,
and you're the youngest.
Why? You're the youngest son.
How is it that all three boys...
only take after their father?
(They look nothing
like their mother.)
It happened that way.
It's the same with you all.
We should've taken after our mother.
Anyway, let's have Il Hwa
say hello first.
- Hello.
- Please say hello.
Hello, everyone. I'm Lee Il Hwa.
- You know...
- I'm...
- a mother of three.
- Goodness.
I hear that you've been wanting
to come out on our show.
Well, I'm good at
physical activities.
- Really?
- Yes.
Haven't you practiced yoga
for a long time?
- Right, she has.
- Actually, I haven't.
- Just sit, Kwang Soo.
- I'm fine!
(Kwang Soo's eager since
he's back from a break.)
Just sit.
I want to chime in!
- Just sit.
- But...
- Sit down.
- We were in the same show,
so we're close.
- All right, fine.
- We get it, all right?
- Be more attentive to your own mom.
- Just sit.
- Mom...
- Should I disown you?
- Gosh, of course not!
Did you hear that?
"Should I disown you?"
I'm sorry.
Next up is Hwang Young Hee.
(Young Hee will say hello next.)
This is my first time meeting you,
you know.
Is there something about you
that strangers don't know about?
- Those who I haven't met before?
- Yes.
They say I'm pretty.
- That's right.
- Exactly!
Those who meet her
for the first time say that?
- Of course.
- That's right.
- Of course, she's pretty.
- Right.
I was surprised by her beauty too.
I get what you're saying though.
- In TV series...
- That's right.
The characters I play
have really curly hair and such.
I guess I look quite different
compared to that.
- I look prettier than I do on TV.
- In person though,
- you seem highly sophisticated.
- That's right.
- Look at what she's wearing.
- Exactly.
Even the way she talks.
Is that so? Well, I agree.
She's even using the terms
youngsters use.
Did you hear it?
- It's how youngsters talk.
- How sophisticated.
So that was Young Hee, everyone.
Lastly, let's welcome...
the grand comedienne
who's also...
a steady rock for all comedians.
Please welcome Park Mi Sun.
Mother!
There's something we should
congratulate her on.
- What is it?
- She has an online channel...
and the number of subscribers...
- has been growing.
- I saw you going to restaurants.
- I saw that.
- Me too.
- If that's the case,
come over here
if you want to know more.
- Anyway, I've been doing my best.
- Right.
- So that was Park Mi Sun!
- It's not easy though.
All right!
Welcome, Mi Sun.
Today's race is called...
Another Rice Cake to the Ugly Child.
The number of rice cakes
given to you will differ...
depending on how you do each round.
After each round, the moms...
will hand out the rick cakes to
the children who disappointed her.
The child with the most
amount of rice cakes...
will receive the penalty...
while the mom with
the lowest amount of rice cakes...
will be rewarded as
Mother of the Year.
We give out decent prizes, you know.
You can hand out
all the rice cakes to one child...
but also keep some...
if none of the children
disappointed you.
- The mom can keep some?
- Yes.
You can reduce
the amount you have...
by eating the rice cakes too.
- Really?
- We can eat them?
I love rice cakes!
Then, a different amount
of rice cakes...
will be given to you...
according to the order
in which you formed your teams.
Team Mi Sun that was formed first
gets one rice cake.
- Nice.
- We were formed our team first.
Look at that.
This is nice.
It looks delicious.
We could easily eat that.
Next, Team Il Hwa gets two.
- Nice.
- What a relief.
I'm glad we're not given three.
Team Young Hee will receive three.
Her mission was the hardest.
The mothers will now
hand out the rice cakes...
to her children
who disappointed you.
- I see.
- All right.
Right now?
All three of them
are the apple of my eye.
So maybe the one
I can rely on the most...
(The most reliable
out of the three?)
should be given the rice cake.
The child I trust the most is Haha.
(Haha!)
(What a twist.)
It wasn't me? Why?
I thought it'd be me
since I'm on "My Little Old Boy."
I'm afraid...
Go, Haha!
- Go, Haha!
- Nice one.
How cool.
- That was cool?
- Next up is Il Hwa.
Mom, go ahead.
(Without a word,
she slides one over to him.)
She didn't even say anything.
She gave it to us
without even explaining why.
- Mother!
- He's my eldest son, you see.
So he gets a free pass?
- Eldest sons are important.
- He's my eldest.
I can feel it, you know.
I can tell that
she adores me the most.
- You can feel it?
- I bet it's why...
you wanted us on your team.
Even we can see that.
- We can tell too.
- Il Hwa...
adores me the most.
You'll change your mind
at the end of the day.
- All right.
- I'll be nice to you.
- I'll be nice to you too.
- Next up is Young Hee.
- There are a lot.
- Back in the day,
mothers would sacrifice themselves.
Just so that you don't argue,
- I'll give you one each.
- Shouldn't you...
consider who took the most time?
- Shut it!
- Shouldn't you consider...
(Shut it!)
(Mom?)
You're the best!
- Young Hee...
- She's the best.
- She was going to hit me.
- Kwang Soo needs her.
- I love it.
Mom!
Mom.
(Your daughter is here!)
My daughter is born
to be a celebrity.
Right?
(So Min shows off her talents.)
Mom.
(Bouncing)
Mom!
Both my daughter and my son...
are talented and sociable.
You have a bright future
ahead of you.
Why would you put that in there?
It's a trend.
The shooting has begun,
so stop fidgeting around.
We have our mothers here today!
- I'll put it aside.
- No, let me help.
I'll do it for you.
- Just sit there.
- They'll criticize me.
It's fine.
Wait, who's criticizing Haha?
The one with the protruding teeth.
The one with the protruding teeth?
I thought he was talking about me.
Wasn't it me?
Our mom has two sons
with protruding teeth...
and one son
who looks older than her.
(Se Chan, Jae Suk, Suk Jin)
The son who looks older than her?
- Did you take after her then?
- Yes.
I take after our mom.
Wait, there's honey.
It'll at least be tasty.
You can eat the rice cake
with what we have prepared.
It'll be delicious.
Can we have it with honey?
Thank you.
(Daniel gets honey.)
(The rice cake tastes
even better with honey.)
(Daniel wants to eat up
all his rice cakes.)
Wait.
You in the middle,
are you a family member too?
Me? Yes, I am a family member.
- I don't think so.
- I am.
I take after Mom the most.
I gave all the good features
to one child.
I love the words she uses.
She has such a good sense of humor.
Daniel has his mom's eyes.
I had plastic surgery.
(I had plastic surgery.)
(She didn't have to confess
to having plastic surgery.)
You didn't have to say that.
She's so straightforward.
- It's Cheongdam-dong style.
- Gosh.
She's so straightforward.
(Mom is not afraid
to tell the truth.)
By the way,
is that your real name?
Lee Il Hwa.
That's such a sophisticated name.
- Does that mean...
- Il Hwa.
"one flower"?
I use the character for "one"
that banks use.
Mi Sun,
- what does "Mi" mean?
- Does it mean "beautiful"?
"Crazy"?
(What is that?)
(Suk Jin tries to remember all
the Chinese characters he knows.)
My name means
"beautiful and kind."
- Does your name mean "crazy water"?
- No, it doesn't.
- That's not what it means.
- You're crazy about water?
No, I'm not crazy about water.
Dogs are crazy about water.
- Dogs are like that.
- Hey!
- You're a dog.
- My mom named me!
Dogs are crazy about water and snow.
We're just curious.
No, it doesn't mean "crazy water."
Daniel is going crazy.
He was a dog.
"Kwang" means "light,"
and "Soo" means the "waterside".
- "Crazy water".
- "The light by the waterside..."
Suk Jin's name means
a "real stone."
- No, it doesn't.
- A "real stone"?
It means a "real stone."
- It means "tin" and "stars."
- It means a "big stone."
- His name means a "big stone."
- A "big stone"?
A "big stone".
- What about your name?
- It means the "world" and "shiny."
- "Make the world shine."
- I thought it meant "side dishes."
"Side dishes"?
What kind of side dishes?
- The "world" and...
- Seasoned cucumbers?
- Cucumbers?
"The world's side dishes."
- "The world's side dishes."
- The "world" and...
Dried squid.
Dried squid?
- Se Chan must be annoyed.
- They're so annoying.
So Min, what about your name?
"So" means "bright,"
and "Min" means the "sky."
Her name suits her.
- "Min" means the "sky"?
- Yes.
- The "bright sky"?
- "Bright as the sky."
(Daniel suddenly giggles.)
- She is bright.
- She is.
I still keep thinking
about "side dishes."
- We talked about that a while ago.
- Are you still thinking about it?
- The "world" and...
- Which side dishes do you like?
It was a while ago
that we talked about side dishes.
Daniel must secretly
look down on you and me.
- No, I don't.
- I'm serious.
I've been feeling it the whole time.
- It's hilarious.
- You find side dishes so funny.
It's here.
- Oh, my.
(Their lunch arrives.)
Our lunch is here. But I'm full.
I haven't had Chinese food
for a while.
- These days...
- I ordered...
braised seafood and vegetables.
She ordered
We ordered tangsuyuk.
I ordered braised seafood
and vegetables with rice.
She ordered braised seafood
My mom is pickier than I thought.
(I want braised seafood
and vegetables.)
Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
- The fried rice tastes good.
- It tastes good, right?
It tastes really good.
It tastes amazing. I love it.
That jjajangmyeon looks amazing.
What did you say?
(She speaks softly.)
Hey.
When Il Hwa sees jjajangmyeon,
she says,
"That jjajangmyeon looks amazing."
- Then you have to open it?
- I have to do everything for her.
You're her son.
- You're her real son.
- I'm her real son.
She doesn't tell you to open it.
- Thank you for lunch.
- Right.
Because they want to make us full
so that we can't eat rice cakes.
(It's to prevent them from reducing
the amount of their rice cakes.)
Is that why they're feeding us?
- That's right.
- That makes sense.
Daniel is smarter
than the rest of us.
None of us realized that.
We were just happy to eat.
So Min said it,
but Suk Jin compliments Daniel.
- So Min said it?
- Yes.
- Let's pretend Daniel said it.
- It was a woman's voice.
It was a woman's voice.
(Why is he laughing?)
- What?
- Did you just see that?
Suk Jin wanted Se Chan
to give him some tangsuyuk.
He gave Se Chan this plate
without saying anything,
and Se Chan just put it down
on the table.
(Se Chan just put it down
on the table.)
(A moment ago)
(Give me some tangsuyuk.)
(Se Chan puts the plate down.)
Can you...
Can you give me some tangsuyuk?
Hey.
- We're brothers.
- You're the youngest one.
- Still, give me some tangsuyuk.
- The youngest one can have some.
Mom didn't raise us like this.
(He gets just one piece.)
- I'll give you more.
- Okay.
Mi Sun is nicer to me.
Mom, be nice to your son!
Mi Sun is nicer to me than you are.
- What could it be?
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- Did you enjoy your lunch?
- Yes!
- It was delicious.
- I'm full!
We can't eat any rice cakes anymore.
- We can't.
- We're going to perform a mission.
The first mission is...
Yang Se Chan Game.
- I know what it is.
- Is there such a game?
It's the game where you have a name
on your cap and sound stupid.
(This is how
Yang Se Chan Game works.)
(You're to guess
the name on your cap.)
(You can ask
the other player questions.)
(It's important to ask
the right questions.)
(Se Chan gave
many hilarious wrong answers.)
It's called Yang Se Chan Game?
According to the order in which
you provide correct answers,
the team that answers first
gets one rice cake,
the team in second place gets two,
and the team at the bottom
gets four.
- Four?
(The team at the bottom
gets 4 rice cakes.)
The rice cakes will be
handed out after each round.
We definitely don't want to
end up at the bottom.
By the way,
Young Hee,
do you understand the rules?
Not completely.
I asked Il Hwa, and she said,
"I don't, but I'll do my best."
(She still sounds elegant.)
She's honest.
(Who will play first?)
Who should go first?
- Should the stupid ones go first?
- All right.
- The impact...
- It's too strong.
Ji Hyo was just so cute.
When he said,
"Should the stupid ones go first?"
she said, "Should I go first?"
(Ji Hyo said, "Should I go first?")
That was cute.
Should the stupid ones go first?
Should I go first?
(Should I go first?)
- Do you admit it?
- That was cute.
Ji Hyo...
- Ji Hyo is a candidate.
Se Chan will represent us.
(Se Chan represents Team Il Hwa.)
- Here comes Ji Hyo!
- Our Ji Hyo!
- Shouldn't Kwang Soo play?
- Do you want to play?
They're the stupidest ones among us.
I watch the news these days.
I'll show you
the flames of questions.
The "flames of questions"?
Shouldn't you say
"proper questions"?
I'll show you "proper questions."
The "flames of questions"?
Close your eyes.
(The names are revealed.)
All right.
(English actor Charlie Chaplin)
- That's hard.
- That's what he got.
- Oh, my.
(Hong Gil Dong)
- Gosh.
- It's not bad.
- Are you done?
- Oh, my.
(Bong Joon Ho, the genius filmmaker
who won 4 Academy Awards)
Hold on.
(They see each other's names.)
Those are the names you have?
- They're all pretty easy.
- They're easy.
Is it a man or a woman?
(Is it a man or a woman?)
(Well...)
- You can tell her that much.
- Hey.
- Why are you hesitating?
- I mean...
(He doesn't want
to give her a hint.)
Why are you hesitating?
- Why are you hesitating?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. It's been so long.
- I can't believe you.
I'm sorry.
Once you're in the game,
you can't help it.
- It's a man.
- It's a man?
(Charlie Chaplin)
Have you seen this person
in real life?
- In real life...
- If they've met the person?
- Have you met this person?
- In real life?
- If I've met him?
- Yes, in real life.
Not just in books or on TV,
but in real life.
(Laughing)
He's pretending to be sharp.
Did you see his face?
Have you ever seen this person
in real life?
(He crosses his legs.)
- He looks so confident.
- Answer my question clearly.
Don't think you can avoid it.
No, I haven't yet.
- You haven't?
- No.
That sounds like
you're not going to meet him ever.
- Okay, Ji Hyo.
- Gosh.
That was sharp.
- He sounds like a detective.
- The stupid ones are debating.
My goodness.
Have you seen this person
in real life?
I have.
- In real life?
- Yes.
- I have.
- It's possible.
- In real life?
- I have.
I really have.
Seriously?
Even the cameramen look puzzled.
- Are you sure you have?
- Yes.
Okay.
What is this person's occupation?
(What is this person's occupation?)
(He looks Kwang Soo
straight in the eye.)
Good job.
Am I better at this now?
What do you think? Am I better?
What is this person's occupation?
(I can't believe Se Chan
asked that sharp question.)
First, Ji Hyo, answer me.
(Sharp)
This person makes things.
- What?
- This person makes things.
This person makes things?
Like food?
This person makes food? Okay.
- For now,
- He's so sharp.
Baek Jong Won is on my radar.
(Baek Jong Won is on my radar.)
Let's move on.
(This is why this game is called
Yang Se Chan Game.)
That's a good guess.
Next.
What is this person's nationality?
(What is this person's nationality?)
(Kwang Soo asks a sharp question.)
Don't just say
this person is a foreigner.
Give me this person's
specific nationality.
- You don't know it, do you?
- I don't.
(Confident)
She doesn't know it,
but she looks so cool.
- I really don't.
- What's this person's nationality?
- This person...
- I'm sure Se Chan doesn't know.
I know it exactly.
- What is it?
(Charlie Chaplin is
an English actor.)
He's either from East Germany
or West Germany.
(He's either from East Germany
or West Germany.)
He's from around there.
- You're right. I get it now.
- Right?
It makes sense.
I know what you mean.
- I know what he means.
- I get it.
- That's all I can say.
Is he from the Soviet Union period?
- Within my knowledge,
- You're incredible.
this is all I can tell you.
He's either from East Germany
or West Germany?
My goodness.
Let's go.
(What should I ask them?)
His occupation.
- Gosh.
- Come on.
They have their own questions
they want to ask.
You should cover your mouth
when you cough.
(She defends her son.)
- What do I do for a living?
- Good question.
She changed the wording
to save her pride.
(Laughing)
She is proud. She is proud.
She changed the wording
to save her pride.
I did it to make it seem like
I didn't hear you.
- "What do I do for a living?"
- What do I do for a living?
They need to answer that.
Give me the occupation.
In some people's opinions,
you do the bad deeds.
- But they are ultimately good.
- He knows well.
What do I usually wear?
(What do I usually wear?)
Kwang Soo made a lot of effort.
- You said East and West Germany.
- The answer is easy.
- Seriously.
- You mostly wear...
baggy pants.
(Baggy pants?)
- Baggy pants.
- It's true though.
- It's a big hint.
- Baggy pants.
- Seriously.
Do you know what baggy pants are?
- Baggy pants?
- Do you know what they are?
- He gave a big hint.
- Seriously.
- It's a crucial hint.
- I know.
- I am...
- He gave a big hint.
I am an honest person.
- Ji Hyo, it's your turn to answer.
- What was this called?
- A bow tie?
- Yes.
(Kwang Soo, it's a crucial hint!)
A bow tie.
(If I combine East Germany,
West Germany, and bow tie...)
- Pringles?
(Pringles)
You need to say, "Let me answer."
- Pringles!
- Really?
The snack you can't stop eating
once it's open?
once it's open.
Maybe it was made in the time
of East Germany and West Germany.
- Pringles.
- Seriously.
Daniel burst out laughing.
- Daniel.
- My goodness.
Pringles has a face.
- The logo.
- It resembles your character.
- The style.
Ji Hyo.
What do I usually wear?
That's good, my daughter.
He has a costume.
His costumes and clothes...
- Costumes and clothes?
- You mean "features and clothes."
- I understood.
- You understood, right?
- You only got one word wrong.
- Costumes and clothes!
- Don't look down on Se Chan.
(Jae Suk figured it out.)
You like to wear arm warmers.
- That's right.
- Really?
- You are right.
- You wear arm warmers often.
You like to wear arm warmers.
I don't think I have seen you
without arm warmers.
I think I know who I am. Hold on.
(Did she figure it out?)
(Someone who does bad deeds
but is ultimately good.)
(Someone who wears arm warmers)
Let me answer.
Hong Gil Dong.
(Hong Gil Dong)
It's correct, right?
- How did you know?
- It's correct, right?
Arm warmers gave me a hint.
Why did you tell her that?
I thought you would say KCM
because of the arm warmers.
Don't be ridiculous.
Hong Gil Dong.
Gosh, Ji Hyo.
How did she figure it out?
I didn't think she would succeed.
The rediscovery of Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
She is above us.
- We need fewer rice cakes.
- Seriously.
Kwang means "Crazy"
and Soo means "Water."
Se means "World"
and Chan means "Side dishes."
- So they are crazy side dishes.
- Crazy side dishes.
Se Chan, go. Ask him a question.
What did I appear in recently?
- That's good.
- What did I appear in recently?
I saw you on SBS.
(You saw me on SBS?)
- It makes sense.
- That's right.
The most personal is
the most creative.
- I saw you on SBS recently.
- It makes sense.
(The answer is
the most personal and creative.)
I saw him on YTN.
I saw him on every channel.
That means I am a popular celebrity.
A popular celebrity?
- I saw him on Channel A.
- For goodness' sake.
Do you know your nationality?
Since I was on SBS,
I must be Korean.
He became annoyed.
Suk Jin picked the worst timing.
(Since I was on SBS,
I must be Korean.)
- Think about it.
- A Korean man.
- Hold on.
- He got an idea.
- YTN?
- Yes.
- YTN, Yonhap News...
- Say your answer.
- YTN?
- He got an idea.
- Every news channel.
- He was on every news channel.
- That's right.
- He got an idea.
- I know who I am.
- Say your answer.
(Someone who was
on every channel recently)
Yang Joon Il.
What are we going to do?
- For goodness' sake.
- This is driving me crazy.
Am I wrong?
- Am I wrong?
- I can't believe it.
- Recently...
(Sighing)
- Yang Joon Il?
- He was on every channel!
- Yang Se Chan Game!
(This is why it's
Yang Se Chan Game.)
- Isn't Yang Joon Il the answer?
- For goodness' sake.
I am so annoyed.
- He is unbelievable.
- This is driving me crazy.
Ask him for the exact occupation.
- The occupation.
- That's a good idea.
The winner will get the occupation
that comes up on a search engine.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins!)
Who am I? I was on every channel.
I was on Yonhap News, YTN,
and other news channels!
Tell me. Who am I?
What's my occupation?
Tell him.
He makes movies and dramas.
- Movies and dramas.
- Tell him!
(Kwang Soo plays dirty.)
What?
Stop acting like
you don't know who he is.
- Tell me.
- He mostly makes movies.
He mostly makes movies?
I took too much of a detour.
- You twisted it too much.
- I know the answer.
Let me answer.
(Will he succeed this time?)
- Bong Joon Ho.
- That's right.
(Bong Joon Ho is correct.)
- That took you long.
- I took too much of a detour.
Seriously.
- Who am I?
- You were close.
- I was close.
- Pringles suited the description.
You are right.
(Team Young Hee comes in last!)
- Now...
- Let's distribute the rice cakes.
- Rice cakes.
- Moms will bring them.
- We get one.
- I should get ready to take one.
Young Hee will distribute
the rice cakes first.
I am at fault...
for raising my children wrong.
But I will raise them strong.
- All of them?
- Me?
(Kwang Soo gets all the rice cakes.)
- All of them?
- Me?
(She knows what to do.)
All four of them?
- This is so sudden.
- She is cool.
- Seriously.
- Young Hee is cool.
- She did the right thing.
- I agree.
- It's my fault.
- It was your round.
If it's your fault, why did I get...
- I will raise my children strong.
- This is too much.
Mi Sun is next.
My daughter should be cherished.
I will keep this.
- I will keep this.
- What a loving family!
Kwang Soo, you can do well.
I envy Ji Hyo.
- How heartwarming!
- My daughter did a great job.
My mom is the best.
I wish my mom would do the same.
- Now,
- I wish my mom would do the same.
Il Hwa.
(Glancing over)
What?
(What?)
That came out of nowhere.
She suddenly gave the rice cakes
to Suk Jin.
- I didn't expect this.
- That came out of nowhere.
- Suk Jin suddenly got them.
- I thought they were for me.
- Why did you give them to me?
- Thank you, Mom.
He didn't even play the game.
Il Hwa!
Don't be rude!
Don't yell at your mom!
- Don't call your mom by her name.
- What a bad son!
- Stay in character.
- I am sorry.
- Thank goodness.
- It's okay.
(The rice cakes are distributed
after Round 2.)
That was hilarious.
Those who haven't gone will play
in the last round.
- Okay. Me, Jong Kook, and Daniel.
- Daniel.
Jae Suk knows
which questions to ask.
- I will show you how it's done.
- Okay.
Give us the ad-libs.
I will give you the ad-libs.
All of us are people, right?
People.
I see.
Okay.
(Jong Kook is Xuanzang,
a monk who travels with Sun Wukong.)
All of us are people.
- All of us are people.
- Okay.
- I get the idea.
- This is hard.
(The worst villain in the galaxy
who wreaked havoc with a snap.)
("Thanos" will be difficult.
Will he be able to get it right?)
Foul play will immediately earn you
a rice cake...
- since this is the last round.
- Okay.
Daniel.
What's my nationality?
He is...
It's hard to talk about
his nationality.
- Give him an approximate.
- He must live in a country.
An approximate? There is
no such thing in nationality, okay?
- Why are you angry?
- Don't be ridiculous.
Don't get angry at Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo becomes upset.)
You can't talk about
someone's nationality that way.
- He is...
- You know,
he has many nationalities.
Let me tell you this. I can't lie.
We don't know about his nationality.
- You don't know about it.
- That's right.
- It's true.
- From which time period am I?
- Time period.
- It's a good question.
- It's really good.
It's difficult to say
what era this is.
- I agree.
- It's difficult.
- It's difficult?
- It's hard to say what it is.
Just tell me roughly.
- It's not like that.
- I don't need a specific year.
- That's not what I'm asking.
- Can he do this?
- He can.
- The era.
I don't really know this person.
Even if you don't know them,
you know the setting.
- What's in the background?
- People are all the same, idiot.
- That's not true.
- We're all the same.
- There must be a setting.
- There are water, air,
mountains, and the sky.
- Goodness.
- Tell him, Daniel.
- Let's see what you say.
- Daniel.
The person is from a long time ago.
- A long time ago?
- Sure.
That's true.
I'll ask about my occupation.
- What do I do?
- Your occupation?
This person...
They're great.
protected somebody for a long time.
(Lee Bong Won's guardian)
- Daniel.
- Yes.
We need something strong.
You don't have an idea yet.
What's my occupation?
- That's difficult.
- Occupation?
This one's hard to answer.
I personally think this person is...
- a gangster.
- What?
(This person is a gangster
who destroys people with a finger.)
- What did you say?
- A gangster.
- Isn't it true?
- A gangster?
- He's a gangster.
- I agree.
I think so.
- You're right.
- He's a bad boy.
This person is worse
than a gangster.
- Very bad.
- Okay.
- I can't deny that.
- It's true.
I can't deny that.
I see.
Is this person alive?
(She's right behind them.)
- This person?
- Yes.
- Watch what you say.
- Hold on.
- Why?
- Because...
- Why are you hesitating?
- You're going to get a warning.
- This is too...
- Why are you hesitating?
- You have to give me an answer.
- Is this person alive right now?
- Yes.
You are hesitating?
- Yes, I would say so.
- You would say so?
- I would.
- So they're alive?
- Sure.
Daniel.
What kind of outfit
do they usually wear?
This person?
What I saw mostly was...
- a sleeveless shirt.
- True.
It was a sleeveless shirt.
I guess it's a sleeveless shirt.
It's a sleeveless shirt?
- It is.
- It's true.
- He's not wrong.
- Isn't it a sleeveless shirt?
- It is.
- I was right.
They like tight-fitting clothes.
- They like it tight-fitted.
- True.
I agree. It's not loose.
Is this person not from Earth?
They like tight-fitting clothes.
- Is this person not from Earth?
- He's narrowing it down.
Well...
This person is...
What are...
this person's features?
Their overall features.
That's a good question.
This person likes
loose-fitting clothes.
I think they're kind of hip.
- They're hip?
- Right.
- I agree.
- They're hip.
I think they wear a hanbok.
Daniel.
Is this person an alien?
An alien? Hold on.
Wait. Hold on.
- This is...
- No, no.
- When...
- I'm not sure.
there is a good question,
we're like...
(They inhale, look away,
and flinch.)
What are you looking at?
- An alien?
- No, they're not an alien.
What are you looking at?
Good question.
Are they an alien? Wait.
Some people might mistake them
for an alien.
- I agree.
- You could be mistaken.
- It's possible.
It is. They go back and forth.
It's not for certain.
That was sharp.
Let me answer.
(Let me answer!)
(Unknown nationality, gangster,
sleeveless shirt, and an alien)
(Can he guess Thanos
with just 4 pieces of information?)
Thanos?
(Thanos?)
(Correct)
How did you know?
- How did you know?
- How did he know?
Sleeveless shirt.
- That was amazing.
He goes back and forth.
He had great questions.
- I thought Thanos was a dinosaur.
- Do you like superheroes?
Me too.
- That was amazing.
- I didn't think he would be right.
Good job.
I thought ours was
the most difficult.
- Hold on.
- This person wears a hanbok.
Does this person have
a special hairstyle?
Good question.
(Chuckling)
- Why?
- What are you looking at?
- Jae Suk.
- There is one.
- You have to tell him.
- Answer.
Bring your voices down. Have a seat.
- He'll answer.
- Sit down.
- Fine.
- Tell me in two minutes.
You can't say it otherwise.
The hairstyle.
- You have to say it.
- They have something on their head.
- What?
- There's something on their head.
- True.
- They wear something on their head.
- They do?
- Yes.
Let me answer.
(It's an old person with loose-fit
clothes and something on the head.)
Sun Wukong?
(Incorrect)
(Goodness)
(Sighing)
What was that?
(He couldn't hide it.)
Daniel.
- Sit straight.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong, Jae Suk?
- Why are you here?
- Have some water.
- What's wrong?
It's not over yet.
(He drinks some water
and calms down.)
(It's Jae Suk's turn to
ask a question.)
- Well.
- Okay.
How many characters are
in my name?
- Sorry?
- How long is the name?
Yes, how many characters are there?
- 2 characters?
- 2?
- Yes.
- What?
- That's just the first name.
- Right.
Hey.
- Why?
- What's wrong?
That was my strategy.
You can't say that.
Because...
These people.
He deserves a rice cake.
He only asked for the name,
so that's what I told him.
Hey!
Look at that.
- Goodness.
- I got this for telling you.
He got a rice cake.
- I still told you.
- Jae Suk,
you have to get this right.
Let me ask a question.
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is confident.
Jae Suk is down.)
Go ahead.
- Is he best friends...
- Go on.
with Sun Wukong?
(Teasing)
(They go to the temple together.)
(Jong Kook's decisive question)
(He cools himself down with water.)
They're not.
- They are not?
- No?
- I thought they were best friends.
- They are not.
- Be honest.
- They're not best friends.
You shouldn't do anything wrong
to this guy.
They're not best friends.
You never know
what they're thinking.
- Don't do anything wrong.
- You never know.
- You don't know what people think.
- Is that right?
- You never know.
- Are they not close?
Jong Kook's harassing him.
Just throw the white towel.
Keep going. One more time.
- I can't keep watching.
- I'll get it right.
- Keep going.
- Are you sure?
Let me answer.
Xuanzang.
(Correct)
(Team Mi Sun is 2nd place
and gets 2 rice cakes.)
- How did you know?
- How?
Yours was hard.
It was hard.
Let's distribute the rice cakes.
I got one during this game.
That was his fault.
One each.
(Handing over)
(Se Chan gets all 4.)
Mother, all four for me?
What for?
What's wrong with our mom?
- Why? Out of nowhere.
- Our mom.
She just gave me four.
(The other teams distributed
the rice cakes as well.)
(Current Number of Rice Cakes)
(Team Young Hee,
Team Mi Sun, Team Il Hwa)
This is the final mission where
moms and kids must work together.
It's called Mom's Back Slap.
We hid two name tags
for each member.
You must find somebody else's
name tag, stick it on your back,
and get slapped in the back
by your mom...
in order to give rice cakes to
the person on the name tag.
(Find somebody else's name tag
and get slapped in the back.)
We have to find
other people's name tags.
For the moms, they can only
rip off name tags of other moms.
If a mom gets
their name tag ripped off,
we'll add two more name tags
for their children.
We have to protect our mom.
Meanwhile, Kwang Soo will...
be cutting rice cakes
at a designated spot.
I have to cut rice cakes?
Yes, once somebody gets
slapped in the back by their mom,
they will get as much rice cake
Kwang Soo has cut by that time.
- Oh, dear.
- Is it by weight?
- I can get the rice cakes too.
- Of course.
- You can get some too.
- I won't know who it's for.
You have to be smart about it.
- Exactly.
- I can't just keep cutting.
You can give the rice cakes
to your own team too.
Right.
- Let's get started.
- Yes, buddy.
(Which team will smile at the end?)
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook will do
everything, mom.
- I know. I'm going to stay still.
- Just stay still.
You can win without a drop of sweat.
- Really?
- Yes, for sure.
I feel reassured.
They're specialized
for situations like these.
I see.
Our team is at a disadvantage
because of me.
- Let's try to use this.
- Right.
- It could be an advantage.
- Yes.
If you find a name tag,
and she can slap your back...
I'll run here and tell you.
If you're in trouble, yell.
(Like this?)
Do you have a strategy?
(Team Il Hwa is quiet.)
We're not like that.
Nothing works the way we plan.
We're awkward.
Look at our team. We're awkward.
Look at us.
We forget our strategy
after a few seconds.
- Really?
- We are just...
- We know.
- I really like our team.
You have to face life head on.
- We just have to move fast.
- Head on.
I really like our mom.
She's very kind.
She's really nice to me.
- She loves her first child.
- She does.
We had so much fun.
Let's start the race. Five...
(They have to find the name tags
and get slapped in the back.)
(The moms have to rip other mom's
name tags for an added benefit.)
Start.
(Race starts.)
- We have to find the name tags.
- Let's hurry.
Haha, look for them.
There must be one in the playground.
(Haha looks for name tags.)
Okay.
(Jong Kook protects
his mom closely.)
Over there.
Jong Kook is protecting her.
- Gosh.
- My gosh.
- It's okay. We're good here.
- We're okay.
The children are okay.
Moms have to be careful.
- Should we go for it?
- Really?
No, I'm okay.
Do you want to?
(Team Il Hwa approaches them.)
(Goodness)
Never mind.
(The handshake wakes him up.)
I was mistaken. Please keep going.
Please go ahead.
There's no reason to fight.
Let's...
- go this way.
- Let's keep going. We just started.
Is there a plastic bag?
(The other members are searching
for name tags.)
Would it be in a box?
Where is it?
(He finds Jong Kook's name tag.)
- No way. No way.
- Did you find a name tag?
- Did you find it?
- Jong Kook. Jong Kook's name tag.
Hold on!
(It's an opportunity
to give rice cakes to Jong Kook!)
- Jong Kook's name tag.
- Hold on!
There are no footsteps.
There is dust everywhere.
Mom!
Kwang Soo's mom!
Here! I am on my way.
Mom, hold on! Mom!
Hold on.
Let me cut another one.
Calm down!
- Hold on!
- Wait a second.
Let me cut another one.
Let me cut two rice cakes.
Go up there.
What is going on? Did you yell?
- We found a name tag!
- Where is it?
- We found Jong Kook's name tag.
What is it?
It's Suk Jin.
(Slapping)
- One more.
- Whose name tag is it? Mine?
- No, no.
- Thank goodness.
(Thanks to Daniel,
Jong Kook got more rice cakes.)
Two and a half.
I cut up a lot.
(All of these are for Jong Kook.)
- You got more rice cakes.
- Me?
Did someone find
my name tag already?
(Did someone find
my name tag already?)
- Daniel, you found it. Good job.
- Yes.
Please find Kwang Soo's.
- We need to find name tags.
- Yes.
Se Chan.
Let's remove...
Young Hee's name tag.
She is all alone.
(Team Il Hwa spots Young Hee.)
(Only moms can remove
each other's name tag.)
- Remove her name tag.
- You should do it.
- Only you can do it.
- I said...
we shouldn't remove
each other's name tag.
You need to remove it.
That's how we win.
She is alone.
- There she is.
- You are right.
- It's hard to find the name tags.
- Let's pretend to look for them.
- You didn't find any, did you?
Did you find any name tags?
Why are you alone?
Seriously.
- Young Hee.
- Hold on.
(The two weak sons attack her.)
- Young Hee.
- Rip off her name tag.
Rip off her name tag. Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
- Kwang Soo!
- Don't slice the rice cakes!
- Hurry up.
- Kwang Soo!
- What?
Okay! Hold on!
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
- Hurry up.
- Don't slice the rice cakes!
(Young Hee's name tag
gets ripped off.)
- Don't slice the rice cakes!
- Hurry up.
(Despite screaming,
her name tag gets ripped off.)
Kwang Soo, stop!
Why would you walk around alone?
(Daniel heard his mom's cry.)
Kwang Soo, stop!
(Mom.)
Two name tags of each
of her family members will be added.
Two of each member.
- What should we do now?
- Okay.
I see that I shouldn't walk around
alone. I am sorry.
(Young Hee's children are
at a disadvantage.)
- Kwang Soo, stop!
- What? Stop?
- Stop, stop.
- What?
You should have said that first.
- I mean...
- You should have said that first.
- Whose name tag got ripped off?
- Our mom.
Our mom.
Our mom?
- Our mom?
- Yes.
It can't be helped.
This won't do.
I won't walk around alone.
I have a question. Sir.
I have a question.
Sir, is this a team competition?
Well, to moms,
the teams are important.
But you can play individually
if you want to avoid the penalty.
- Does that mean moms' rice cakes...
- Really?
- won't affect the children?
- I mean...
(So Min takes out...)
Hey! What are doing?
(Kwang Soo's name tag.)
- Really?
- Hey!
- What are doing?
- Really?
- Don't be like that.
- No, no.
- Let me think about this.
- Hey.
So Min, it has been a while.
- This is your true color.
- It's not like that.
Mom, look at her!
You need to put it
on your back first.
- Really?
- Yes.
Let me think about this.
Let me think about
when to put it on my back.
If she does that,
I will get back at her.
- Haha.
- What?
- I found one over there.
- Where?
- Whose is it?
- Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin is on Se Chan's team.)
So?
What are you...
Are you going to play individually?
That's what I always do.
- I can't rip off your name tag.
- What?
I know.
(Haha finds Suk Jin's name tag.)
Mom!
(At that moment)
Mom, hurry up!
- Mom, hurry up!
- What is it?
Hurry up!
Jong Kook, please stop Suk Jin.
(At Haha's request)
- Did you put it on yourself?
- Yes.
Jong Kook, please stop Suk Jin.
(She slaps Suk Jin's name tag
right in front of him.)
- I gave you a back slap.
- All right.
I got Suk Jin.
What you sliced so far
will go to Suk Jin.
Suk Jin?
I see that it's best to slice
as much as I can.
(Suk Jin gets more rice cakes.)
Hey. Shall we...
Se Chan, shall we remove
her name tag again?
- Young Hee?
- Yes. Let's rip off her name tag.
Se Chan, let's do it one more time.
She went this way.
I need to find a name tag.
(Oh, my goodness.)
(They can catch Young Hee
whenever they want.)
Hang in there.
Go away! Go away!
Rip off her name tag.
- No! Mom!
- Come on.
- Mom!
- Okay.
- I am sorry.
- Young Hee, stop wandering alone.
- Protect Mom!
Where are Daniel and So Min?
(The two children wander
without knowing what happened.)
Look at that. Even close friends...
- turn on each other to win.
- Seriously.
You shouldn't walk around alone.
I will end you.
(2 name tags per member
of Team Young Hee get added.)
What should I do?
- There is no other way.
- You must find the name tags.
I must find the name tags.
But I am afraid they will rip off
my name tag again.
Shall we rip off Mi Sun's name tag?
- Will we be able to do that?
- Mi Sun...
Gosh, here they come.
They look strong.
- I'm actually sloppy.
- No, you aren't.
- Don't show it.
- Okay.
Don't show it.
Glare in a scary way.
It's okay. Make yourself look scary.
Let's go. Let's go.
We won't be able to do it
because of Jong Kook.
- We need to find the name tags.
- Hey, there is Young Hee.
- There is Young Hee.
What? My mom?
We can beat So Min, right?
- Let's make a move.
- Ji Hyo.
- Mom wants to make a move.
Mom, run away!
So Min, I...
- Mom!
- They are coming again.
- It's okay.
- Get her.
- Daniel isn't here.
- Hold on.
Protect her.
Help Mom rip off Mi Sun's name tag.
Oh, no!
Mom! Mom!
(Young Hee grabs
Mi Sun's name tag too.)
(It's Young Hee's chance
to retaliate!)
(The weakest mom
versus The sloppy mom)
(What will be the result?)
(Ripping)
(Young Hee gets her name tag
ripped off again.)
I feel bad for my mom.
- Our mom is the best.
- I feel bad for my mom.
Our mom is the best.
Did you see the way our mom
grabbed her by the collar?
I will find the name tags!
(Mom, I will find the name tags!)
Everyone is ripping off
her name tag.
Mom, I think
we can stop ripping off name tags.
- Let's stop.
- We got it on the camera.
- Are you okay?
- I am at the edge of the cliff.
I will end you all.
This is yours.
- We need to do it.
- Daniel.
(Daniel has been running
for a while.)
Mom!
(He has Haha's name tag
on his back.)
He found someone's name tag!
Kwang Soo!
Where is Mom?
Daniel, wait.
Give me some time!
- Mom!
- Daniel.
Let's wait.
(It's time for payback.)
(Mom, I did well, right?)
- Kwang Soo, slice many rice cakes.
- Hold on.
Mom, let me slice two more.
- 2?
- He will slice 2 more.
- Slice two at a time.
- Okay.
- Let me slice two more.
- Hold on.
Those will go to Daniel.
What?
No way.
Daniel is out.
- Those will go to Daniel.
- What?
Daniel, I am sorry.
(I am out?)
Why is there so much in my tray?
We can add more rice cakes
to Haha's tray.
- Why is there so much in my tray?
- That's right.
That's right. Keep slicing.
- I will slice four rice cakes.
- Okay, okay.
It's the most I have sliced at once.
Watch your fingers.
(She worries like a mom.)
How is it going?
I sliced four rice cakes.
It's the most I have sliced at once.
- Kwang Soo, how is it going?
- Hold on.
I can't find any name tags.
- So Min is out.
- What? Me?
Why am I out?
- What?
- So Min, I am sorry.
- What are you doing?
- You got four rice cakes.
- Why?
- Daniel found Haha's name tag.
- Why...
- Slice more rice cakes.
Then you should have given them
to Haha, not me.
I wanted to do that
after slicing four rice cakes.
I can't find any name tags.
So Min has the most.
She came out on top.
Stop it.
- Stop slicing rice cakes!
- It's not like that.
Daniel found Haha's name tag.
I will slice three rice cakes
this time.
(He can't stop slicing rice cakes.)
(Jae Suk is looking for name tags.)
(What? He finds
Kwang Soo's name tag.)
I will see
how things are going first.
(With the name tag on his back,
he approaches Kwang Soo.)
- Did you slice a lot?
- Yes.
- How many did you slice?
- I sliced two so far.
I can slice five rice cakes.
Since there isn't much time left,
- slice as many as you can.
- Seriously.
I don't know who will get them,
- but you should slice a lot.
- These rice cakes are soft.
You are slicing 3 at a time.
You should slice 4 at a time.
- There are...
- Come on.
too many name tags of ours.
- You worry me.
- Did they get you again?
Yes, it happened 2 times.
I can't even win against 1 person.
- So I don't know what to do.
- You know,
all the moms are looking for you.
I am like an impala.
- Young Hee, how are you...
- A herbivore.
Kwang Soo, you shouldn't slice
so many rice cakes.
- The unfortunate one will get them.
I sliced five rice cakes so far.
Whoever gets them will be over.
It's bound to happen.
- Whoever gets them will be over.
Kwang Soo, there are
many of our name tags.
Anyway,
- keep slicing.
- In that case...
- We play individually anyway.
- You are right.
Hold on. He has
Kwang Soo's name tag on his back.
Let's go.
(Why is my son's name tag
on his back?)
(He gets a back slap
right after the discovery.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Oh, it's Kwang Soo?
- Hold on.
- Someone got all these rice cakes.
- Seriously. This is insane.
Put them in Kwang Soo's tray.
No way!
Why did you slice
so many rice cakes?
You told me to do that!
- I didn't know it was you.
- Kwang Soo,
he has your name tag on his back.
That's why he told you to cut more.
These evil people.
I'm so mad.
This is too big.
This shouldn't count.
(He looks satisfied.)
- People are evil here.
- I think this is too much.
I didn't know.
If I knew,
I wouldn't have been so good.
Isn't it fun though?
I don't know why, but this is fun.
(She's simple.)
What did you say before?
Yours and mine are similar.
I should stop cutting.
(While Team Young Hee is
falling apart)
- Did you find more?
- No.
- You didn't, right?
- Daniel, did you find one?
- No, I didn't.
(He was stalling.)
(He finds a name tag on the wall.)
(Yes)
(It's Jae Suk's name tag.)
(They're startled.)
It's Jae Suk's.
(They're on the same team,
but it's not his.)
Cut, Kwang Soo!
- Do I cut?
- Keep cutting.
- Do I cut? Take your time.
- Cut some more.
- This too.
- Cut a lot.
Mom, this too.
- Cut some more.
- Who is it?
- Jae Suk.
- Wait.
- Earlier.
(I don't know anymore.)
(Jae Suk made him mad.)
- Are you sure it's him?
- Yes.
But they can't find ours.
Use a knife.
(His insanity explodes.)
Goodness. Use a knife.
This too. I have five lines.
- That's not the problem.
- Six lines with this.
(He cut for revenge.)
Wait.
Now!
(He signals.)
- There you go.
- Now!
- We got it.
- I ripped it.
It's Jae Suk.
I'm sorry
for being an incompetent mom.
No, don't say that. Please.
Where's my stamp?
(He finally took revenge
for his mom.)
Should I cut or not?
- Keep cutting.
- Do I stop?
Why do I have so many?
It was Daniel.
You'll get the penalty soon.
- Why do I have so many?
- All right.
Why do I have so many?
What's all this?
What's wrong with mine?
Kwang Soo, you don't want to be
in last place, right?
Look at my back.
(So Min's name tag?)
- You have to cut a lot.
- No, don't.
- It's So Min's.
- Mom.
(I'm sorry, Mom.)
(To be honest,)
(people found all my name tags,)
(so I'll probably get last place.)
You're playing by yourself, right?
- Mom.
- What's going on?
Hit her name tag.
Kwang Soo,
- we have the most.
- You're in last place.
I don't want you to get last place.
Keep cutting.
- Aren't you going to cut more?
- There's so much.
- Stop cutting.
- No, Kwang Soo.
- Keep cutting.
- Don't.
- I don't think that's right.
- That's for So Min.
- Stop cutting.
- Look.
I don't care about So Min.
(He made up his mind.)
I have so much.
- Cut a lot.
- The last place gets the penalty.
- Only the last place does.
- Is that what I taught you?
I can't find more.
(She doesn't have a clue.)
- Suk Jin! That's So Min's team.
- Come this way.
Fine, I'm coming.
- My mom can hit you.
- While I walk over there...
Hold on, Suk Jin!
- Hurry up.
- Up to this.
Up to this.
- How long?
- I'm almost there!
- He wants you to wait.
- Two more.
Two more.
- What's going on?
- Two more!
- Who is it?
- So Min, it's yours.
- So Min!
- No!
- Whose name is it?
- So Min, it's yours.
(No!)
Stop him.
Run away!
(He's about to be slapped.)
- Stop him.
- Run away!
(Please don't slap my name tag.)
- Hurry up.
Run away!
- What?
- Run away!
- What's going on?
- Hurry up.
- What are you doing?
- Hurry.
- No.
Now!
- Now!
- Slap him.
- Slap him!
- This is ridiculous.
- She slapped him.
(She slapped his back.)
(Jeon So Min)
What? This is so unfair.
- So Min.
- What was that for?
- This is not how you play!
- So Min.
- Hey! You!
- She got six more.
So Min.
This is not how you play.
You evil person.
(Kwang Soo kills his team,
and the race is over.)
Hey.
- I was happy you had so much fun.
- Kwang Soo.
You should write in your diary.
(It's been 3 weeks,
so they're more generous.)
It's nice for him to come outside
after a long time.
I was just cutting rice cakes,
and I had so much fun.
It feels like
we volunteered for him.
- I had so much fun today.
- Exactly.
Another Rice Cake to
the Ugly Child race.
The winning team is...
(Today's winning team is...)
Team Mi Sun with 4.967kg.
(1st place is Team Mi Sun.)
(Honey, I'm bringing a prize home.)
- Our mom worked so hard.
- My mom is the best.
- She worked so hard.
- She's the best.
So Min has so many.
We all have less than her.
Kwang Soo thought
this was one-on-one.
Daniel.
(The person with the heaviest bag
gets the penalty.)
He has a lot too.
I kept on waiting.
2.680.
0.386.
0.398kg.
1.508.
Take some rice cakes home.
- It's between So Min and Kwang Soo.
- They're the last two.
It's wide. Look.
You can't tell.
So Min's is taller.
This is going to be a tight race.
- Kwang Soo has more on the bottom.
- Kwang Soo.
- They weren't cut.
- Long ones.
Kwang Soo.
What?
- What is it?
- 4.856.
- 856.
4.856.
- 4.856.
- So Min.
So Min.
(How heavy is her bag?)
- It's over 4kg.
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- You have to be careful.
- Wait!
- Wait.
- The tie too.
- It was So Min at the end.
- Weigh the tie too.
- Weigh that too.
- Be accurate.
Put it in the middle. Good.
Again.
Please weigh it again.
Fine.
There you go.
- 4.908.
- Again.
- Weigh Kwang Soo's.
- We'll try one last time.
It's 52g difference right now.
- 4.908.
- Again.
She's getting the penalty.
(The difference is really small,
so they weigh Kwang Soo's again.)
I should have cut two more!
You just got back,
and you might get a penalty.
- That's incredible.
- No.
- We don't know yet.
- Are there more rice cakes?
Are there any on the ground?
I'll place it on the scale.
(Will Kwang Soo receive a penalty
on his first day back?)
The tie too.
(Or will it be So Min?)
(On the second time,
his bag weighs...)
- 4.854.
- 854.
Okay!
(His bag is 4.854kg.)
(He's still 54g less than So Min.)
What's the difference?
With a 54g difference,
So Min comes in last place today.
No way.
(The last moment
changed everything.)
Did you have fun, Kwang Soo?
This must be paradise.
This is what I live for.
He's happy.
Please bring the prizes.
(It's time to pick the prizes.)
This is so good.
The prizes are really good.
- There are many good ones.
- There's a good variety.
- Korean pork.
- Korean beef set.
- I want this.
- There's Korean pork.
You might get something
like this too.
- Face cushion.
- Who is that?
You can do this
if you don't want to see the face.
(Suk Jin's face cushion.
You can hide his face.)
This one's useless.
How are you supposed to
get rid of it?
That's the worst.
- It's nice to have one.
- It's the worst.
It doesn't even fit in trash bags.
Mi Sun, you're the captain and mom
of the winning team.
Let's do the lucky prize draw.
I want to try this.
Place your favorite items on
your favorite numbers.
I'm doing it randomly.
- This is fun.
- Right?
- It makes you nervous.
- That's what makes it fun.
Please pick a number.
All right.
Let's see.
Let's go for the massage chair.
Pick number 28!
Number 28.
(She picked one!)
- 1, 2, 3.
- Look at it.
(She throws it.)
Why did you throw it?
- 30...
- 33.
(She picked number 33.)
(What's on 33?)
Oh, dear. This is 33.
It's a dud. Oh, dear.
(She's sad.)
She dropped it.
That was a dud!
- It's okay.
- He's cold-hearted.
He is.
Lastly, So Min.
You have to receive the penalty.
It's a simple penalty.
The other two moms will
spray water on her...
so that
she can pull herself together.
That's great.
That's nothing.
- What?
- Should we do that?
That's nothing.
It's okay. I got a prize last week.
- This is not a bad penalty.
- It's not.
They are the moms.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Should I pour some more?
(Kwang Soo,
should I pour some more?)
What do you think?
- You need to pour some more.
- This is nothing.
Kwang Soo is asking him
to pour some more.
"Se Chan, pour some more."
This family is a mess.
I know.
(Take this!)
(Kwang Soo is finally back.)
I thought
we would let it go for once.
Do you feel better now?
So Min.
This finally feels like Running Man.
- You feel better.
- I do.
I feel really bad.
I haven't done this before.
Please do it.
- She's going to run at her.
- This is nothing.
Pull yourself together
and listen to your parents.
You're too far away.
(Splashing)
(She misses on purpose.)
(She aimed for his face.)
- That was a mistake.
- I'm sorry.
- That was a mistake. Sorry!
- That was a mistake.
- Well...
- Oh, dear.
- So Min...
- She can't aim.
So Min got...
- 5 something.
- That was bad.
I meant to do this, but did that.
- It was a mistake.
- It truly was.
That's understandable.
(It feels like Kwang Soo got
last place for some reason.)
(Kwang Soo's Idols are
getting ready to debut.)
(However,)
(is Running Man watching them?)
(Is there a traitor?)
(The idols fall into trouble
right before their debut.)
(Their greed to
obtain the name tags)
(The teamwork starts to
fall apart...)
(in the hidden secret room.)
(The only weapon to destroy
the weak idol team)
(The deal with evil for name tags)
(They should never let their
guards down even when lying down.)
(Which team will keep their name
tags and have the last laugh?)
(Idol versus Running Man,
Center's Dignity)