(It was filmed before the practice of social distancing step 2.)
Hello, hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Everyone's temperature was checked and the area was disinfected.)
- Our spots are marked. - Hello.
Ji Hyo sent me black raspberries.
Did you send them to everyone?
- Yes. - You think I sent them selectively?
- You didn't send any last time. - To whom?
- To me. - What do you mean?
Remember gwamegi?
(A few years ago)
- Suk Jin. - I sent it to you.
- You sent him black raspberries? - Why?
They won't be any use to him.
Goodness.
(He found his target.)
What is he saying?
Jong Kook, you were waiting for the right moment to say it.
Suk Jin can use them to make kimchi.
- To make kimchi? - Yes.
He can enjoy them because they're sweet.
They're sweet.
(It's for kimchi or for his sugar level.)
What do you know?
- Why are you blushing? - I am not.
You lose if you blush.
- He lost. - I'm not blushing.
It's because it's hilarious.
I expected it, but why is it so funny?
(It's the effect of bokbunja.)
I heard that Ji Hyo has been generous these days.
(There are many nice stories about Ji Hyo.)
- Why? - About what?
She sent coffee to everyone.
She sent it to Solar.
- That's right. - Yes.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
Are you out of your mind?
- "Out of your mind"? - I wanted to be generous.
She makes an effort to maintain her relationships.
(Ji Hyo has changed.)
- Now... - She got rid of her walls.
- Ji Hyo broke down her walls. - Now?
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo breaks down her walls and opens up to the world.)
She's opening up to the world.
- At the age of 40? - She was in a cave before.
She's 40, and now she's opening up.
(She starts a new life outside of her wall.)
- That's impressive. - That's great.
Ji Hyo, what happened to you?
(Why did she suddenly change?)
It's nothing.
Will you be making a sudden,
- important announcement? - No.
(Is she getting...)
- Are you getting... - Is it all for your wedding?
(Is that why she's giving out presents?)
- Are you getting... - Is that why?
There's a rumor about So Min's relationship.
- What's going on with you? - What's with you?
("Rumors about Oh Dong Min and Jeon So Min's Relationship")
("They Deny Their Relationship", "They're Just Close Friends")
I have many male friends.
(Sad)
Now they're blocking my way.
Why would you go to an escape room?
(Why would you go to an escape room?)
Isn't that where you go with your boyfriend?
- Did you go camping with him? - By the way...
(Did you go camping with him?)
- Camping? - No.
We didn't go camping, but these days...
(We're just friends.)
- That's impressive. - No.
- Did you even go camping with him? - That's not true.
Now that I think about it, she was friendlier than usual...
(Is that why in the green room...)
to Se Chan in the waiting room today.
Exactly. Suddenly, she told me to come...
(That's how she uses Se Chan for her scandal.)
- and offered me a seat. - She told him to come next to her.
They talked while sitting on a sofa.
You're the only one for me.
She's setting up a shield.
My goodness.
(Shield Se Chan blocks scandals.)
I'm an easy target as her shield.
- You know... - Se Chan must be confused.
She's pretending to be close to everyone including Oh Dong Min.
(Se Chan is useful in many ways.)
Se Chan is acting as her smoke bomb.
Since two days ago, Se Chan didn't respond to my messages.
- After the news about Dong Min... - Are you upset?
- That's right. - Just pay attention to him.
No, he's just a friend.
His name is Oh Dong Min. You mispronounced his name.
It's Oh Dong Min.
(He should know the name right before making fun of her.)
What you said is a song by Choi Heon.
- You understood what I mean. - Right.
(Introducing today's race with hot news)
Today, you're students at Brahms Music School.
(Students of Brahms Music School)
- A music school? - You'll be showing off...
your music skills.
What's Brahms?
- It's an instrument. - An instrument?
It's one of the instruments in an orchestra.
An instrument?
(Johannes Brahms is not a musical instrument.)
Four students at the same school are waiting for you.
(Johannes Brahms, a composer known for "The Hungarian Dances")
(Who are the 4 students that enroll at Brahms Music School?)
- Really? - Please come out.
Please come out.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
- Hello. - What's going on?
- My goodness. - Ji Hyun
(Kim Sung Cheol, Park Ji Hyun, Kim Min Jae, Park Eun Bin)
- Gosh. - Eun Bin.
- Hello. - It's good to see you.
(Nice to meet you.)
(Park Eun Bin, a popular actress appearing on "Hot Stove League",)
("Hur Jun, The Original Story", and "Hello, My Twenties!")
It's Ji Hyun. Wow.
(Park Ji Hyun in "Gonjiam: Haunted Asylum", and "Rookie Historian...")
("Goo Hae Ryung" and Running Man Episode 475)
It's Min Jae.
(Kim Min Jae appeared in "Dr. Romantic", "Goblin",)
("Flower Crew: Joseon Marriage Agency" and "Love, Sling".)
All right.
(Kim Sung Cheol appeared in "Prison Playbook",)
("Kim Ji Young, Born in 1982", and "That Winter, the Wind Blows".)
Do you like Brahms? Why did I ask him that?
(The four actors are the cast in "Do you like Brahms?")
(The drama tells a story of dreams and love.)
All right.
What do you think when you look at the four of them?
(If 4 casts are here...)
- They're in a new drama. - Are they promoting it?
(They're here to promote the drama.)
- Promoting? - It must be an SBS drama.
Look, Eun Bin seems embarrassed.
- Don't be embarrassed. - Okay.
Promoting isn't bad.
(Shy)
- In that case... - What kind of drama is it?
(Tell us about the drama.)
Is it about youth?
That's right. We're here to promote it anyway.
- Please do. - Okay.
It's a Mon-Tues SBS drama called "Do You Like Brahms?"
(New SBS Mon-Tues series, "Do You Like Brahms?")
"Do You Like Brahms?"
(All new premier on August 31)
- It's at a music school. - That's why today's theme...
- is a music school. - Yes.
- It takes place at a music school. - It's a youthful...
(It's a youthful melodrama that's based on classical music.)
melodrama that's full of emotions based on classical music.
- Is that so? - The roles that we play...
(So Min's already into it.)
are 29 years old.
(Promoting)
- What? - It's about questioning...
(It's about questioning dreams and love at the end of their 20's.)
dreams and love at the end of their 20's.
- Love? - That's what...
- it's about. - Are you guys couples then?
(The couples)
Is it a love triangle?
(Watch the drama for all the details.)
Isn't that right?
Should it be a secret for now?
- Of course. - I see.
I bet there's a couple and one of them interferes.
(He doesn't know better.)
You're the one interfering. My goodness.
(He interrupts without knowing better.)
- That's what makes it fun. - Let them promote.
Normally, the way Eun Bin promotes is...
that she hopes that people enjoy the drama.
(Nowadays, people promote their films and dramas naturally.)
She's discreet about it.
Now, she said the entire synopsis.
(She promotes the drama thoroughly.)
I think she memorized it.
- The first episode is on August 31. - Like a machine.
(Firm)
- It's tomorrow. - Tomorrow?
(Please be sure to watch it.)
That's right.
Please be sure to watch it.
We have these four guests today. What's the theme today?
(What kind of race will they have with these four?)
All 12 of you are students at a music school.
You'll take a simple music test...
(They'll be assigned to a grade from 1 to 4...)
and be assigned to your grade from 1 to 4.
(based on a simple music test.)
- I hope I'm in a higher grade. - Are questions related to music?
- Yes, they are. - That's a relief.
It's a total of 10 questions.
The top three enter fourth grade.
(3 people will be placed each from the 4th grade to the 1st grade...)
The next top three enter third grade,
second, and first in order.
(in the order of their test scores.)
It's better...
to lie about your score and grade.
(It's better to hide their scores and grades.)
- I'll tell you why later. - Is that so?
- I'm good at that. - The higher your grade, the better.
(What kind of music test is it?)
I wonder what the questions are.
- We'll bring in desks and chairs. - Okay.
Please open the test.
(They open the test paper.)
(They nervously read the test.)
Okay, do we start?
- Gosh, isn't it that one? - I can do it.
My goodness. Why are we taking a test?
(He hates all kinds of tests.)
- Do we start? - Now?
- "Listen to the classical piece." - Do we write it down?
(Running Man Music Exam)
It's a listening question.
Do I write down the answers with the pen?
Open up the PDF file.
(They submit their answers using the given phones.)
- Take out your pen. - With the pen?
Write down the answers and send them.
Do we start?
(Listen to the piece and write down the title.)
Here's number one.
- What's this piece? - I definitely know it.
What's this piece?
- It played at Western restaurants. - Right.
- When you order a course meal. - Yes.
(They used to listen to this while cutting pork cutlets.)
Either pork cutlet or hamburg steak.
I definitely know it.
- What is it? - Brahms?
- What? - Isn't it by Brahms?
It's by Brahms?
Isn't it by Brahms?
- This? - What?
It's 3 syllables plus 2 syllables.
(Hint: 3 syllables plus 2 syllables)
I thought it was something else.
Isn't it what I think it is?
(On the tip of her tongue)
I can't remember the last word.
Here's the second question.
(Next are the titles of songs by Jang Beom June.)
Play music for the second question.
Number one.
(Listen to the four songs and list the titles in order.)
(Each is worth 2.5 points.)
(Glancing)
Number two.
(He spots her trying to cheat.)
These are Beom June's songs that I'm not familiar with.
(These are hit songs that everyone knows.)
Number three.
I have no idea.
(They sound all the same.)
(They all sound familiar.)
I have no idea either.
Number four.
(4 similar yet different songs by Jang Beom June)
What was it?
I don't recognize this one.
(The listening test ends.)
Next is a short answer question.
(They can submit the answers to the remaining problems.)
You get an advantage if you submit first.
(Write the names to these people in the right order.)
Option number three...
and four. Aren't they the same person with different wigs?
They're definitely different.
I'm just writing down names that I know.
(Recalling all the foreigners' names they know)
Did you write "Sam Hammington"?
No way.
These two are confusing.
- Aren't they the father and mother? - Right.
- What is this? - Father and mother?
Which one is the father?
But they're both men.
Why are they father and mother?
(We're talking about the father and mother of music.)
Father of music and mother of music.
- Is it Vincent van Gogh? - My goodness.
- Gogh was a painter. - He was a painter.
Was he?
"Amor Fati"?
(The answer is "love of one's fate".)
I knew it before.
Amor party
(She tries to cheat again.)
Come on.
(Looking around)
(She cheats with a calm attitude.)
Eun Bin, you can't cheat.
- She's cheating a lot. - No.
(No one knew she plays dirty.)
I didn't know she was like this.
(Read the lyrics below and write the title and the singer of the song.)
"Just imagining it feels like my heart is about to burst".
"Just imagining it feels like my heart is about to burst"?
Based on "I might cry", it's a recent song.
I might cry
(Nasal voice)
- Cry, cry - What?
- Amor fati - Amor fati
(They sing along in the middle of the test.)
That's right.
(Choose the number of total members of the groups listed.)
Is SEVENTEEN a group of 13?
Were there six in god?
How many were in H.O.T?
There were 23.
(It's a very wrong answer.)
If you can get two right, you'll get the top score.
(They write down their answers.)
I'm finished.
Please send it.
- Is it better to send it quickly? - I'm done...
(It's advantageous if you submit it earlier when the scores are tied.)
If your scores tie, the person who sent earlier wins.
(It's time to submit the answers.)
"Message", "Search PDF".
Five.
- I sent it. - I should just write what I know.
(The bad students always submit their test last.)
(The test is over.)
While we check your answers, we'll give you the answers.
(Revealing the answers)
Number one is "Love's Greeting" by Edward Elgar.
(Number 1. "Love's Greeting" by Edward Elgar)
I wrote "Love's Conversation".
(A series of wrong answers that are just extraordinary)
Isn't it called "Our Love"?
Min Jae and Haha wrote "Our Love".
- "Our Love". - "Our Love".
(They're happy to hear it.)
Question number two.
(The Jang Beom June problem that confused everyone)
Number one.
("It's Hard to Face You")
"It's Hard to Face You".
Number two.
("Yeosu Night Sea")
"Yeosu Night Sea".
- Number three. - "Love, At First".
("Love, At First")
- Number four. - "If You Really Love Me".
("If You Really Love Me")
(Write the names to these people in the right order.)
Question number three. The first is Beethoven.
That's obvious.
The second is Mozart.
- I got it wrong. - I should've written it.
- The third is Handel. - Okay.
The fourth is Bach.
That's right. It wasn't van Gogh.
(He acts like it was close, but he only got Beethoven right.)
If you wrote Bach, can you get three points?
(Speaking like the top student of the school)
- That's amazing. - I remember them.
(Speaking like the second-best student of the school)
- You do? - I learned it when I was young.
(Types that become talkative when grading)
I remember it clearly.
In general,
students with bad grades are the loudest.
(They're just all talk.)
I'm getting so many correct.
Ji Hyo will definitely be in first grade.
Instead of listening, she's watching a video.
(She's not even interested in grading.)
She's not curious about the answers.
It's because I did well on the test.
(It's obvious she's all talk.)
I don't need to check my answers.
Here's question number five.
You'll recognize when you hear it.
Number five?
(Read the lyrics below and write the title and the singer of the song.)
It was right.
("What is Love" by TWICE)
It's "What is Love?" by TWICE.
(The three who cheated got the same wrong answer.)
It was TWICE as I said.
(Feeling awkward after sharing the answer)
The lyrics seemed like TWICE's songs.
Please remember...
that it's not helpful to say what you got wrong.
- Right. - It's better to act.
I got everything right.
The questions were so easy.
- I've been lucky thus far. - These are so easy.
(There are always students who listen well to stuff like this.)
Eun Bin, did you do a terrible job?
I did very well.
- Really? - Yes.
I was the first to submit the answers.
(Proud of submitting her answers early)
- Really? - Yes.
Question number 10.
The answer is number three.
(Grading the test ends with the 10th problem.)
That's right!
If you don't know, it's always number three. Awesome.
(A lot of bad students pretend to have taken the test well.)
I should be one of the top students.
Gosh, I got one wrong. I'm doomed.
(They sound like they're at the top of the country.)
You got one wrong?
You mean you got one right.
- You mean you got one right. - How can I...
(Lowering his head)
- Kwang Soo. - get one wrong?
What's wrong, Kwang Soo?
I got one wrong by mistake.
It might as well as be zero points.
(They're doing everything that they couldn't in school.)
Here are the results.
(Revealing the test results and the grades)
Check your own score.
I'll scold you if you're in a lower grade than me.
- I... - We graded you fairly.
(They half expectantly and half worriedly check their grades.)
We won't receive any inquiries about the test result.
(The scores make them speechless.)
- Goodness. - Gosh.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
Everyone.
No way.
Goodness.
(They're assigned to a grade based on their score.)
Was I this smart?
We have to decide on the team for the first mission.
(Time to decide the team for the 1st mission)
- We have four guests. - Yes.
Three of you will pick your members...
(Ji Hyun, Min Jae, and Eun Bin will form their teams.)
by playing rock-paper-scissors.
(Results for Team Ji Hyun, Team Min Jae, and Team Eun Bin)
- Everyone? - Yes.
(The first mission after deciding the teams)
This is the first period at your musical school.
During this period, you can improve your music skills.
(Dreaming of Being Gifted in Music)
It's called Dreaming of Being Gifted in Music.
We're dreaming of being gifted.
Each team will pick a penalty sign...
(1 member of a team will choose...)
and sit next to it.
(between a finger flick or a toy hammer.)
You'll hear four remixed songs of different periods.
(They'll listen to 4 songs combined into one.)
Answer as soon as you recognize it.
(They get 1 point every time they get the right answer.)
When you answer correctly, you win one point.
Okay.
If you get a finger flick from Se Chan or Jong Kook,
(The two best finger flickers)
you'll die.
Is the weapon for hitting or getting hit?
(Toy hammer)
I'll explain.
At this time...
(Will you?)
(Producer...)
You embarrassed him.
(That was mean.)
- You're so cold to an aged man. - Come on.
We have guests too.
Why did you scold him?
(Our Suk Jin)
It's all right.
Suk Jin is close to being 60.
(Treat him well.)
It's all right.
(A robot who says, "It's all right")
I was the one who interrupted when you were talking.
- Right. - It's okay.
- Don't think like that. - It's okay.
(Is he comforting Suk Jin?)
- It's all right. - Come on.
I stopped Bo Pil from talking.
It's okay, Bo Pil.
(The eldest member lets it slide.)
That's how he acts when he's furious.
Every time you answer correctly, you get a point.
(Explaining the penalty rules that Suk Jin was curious about)
Each team has three members.
(1 person from 3 teams)
A member from three teams will take a seat.
The one who answers correctly...
performs the penalty on 1 of the 2...
(The one who answers correctly performs the penalty...)
from the other team.
(on 1 of the 2 from the other team.)
- After answering? - You do it?
These six are sitting in the finger flick zone.
(The people sitting in the finger flick zone get finger flicks.)
These six are in the toy hammer zone.
(The people sitting in the toy hammer zone get toy hammers.)
You should sit in the finger flick zone.
- Can we choose? - Yes.
(Their seats decide who will be in charge of the penalty.)
In terms of pain, who's on your team is important.
If Jong Kook and I are on the same team,
(It'll be a match with their lives on the line.)
everyone will be doomed.
- You can use different flicks. - Is this possible?
It's your choice.
(Various types of finger flicks are allowed.)
This can't be possible.
(Getting warmed up)
Please stand up.
Starting with those in blue vest, pick your seat.
(Time to choose their seats before the game)
- Okay. - Each person?
(They're more cautious than ever during this meeting.)
The one who can answer...
Since there are four songs, I can do it.
Where should I go?
Jong Kook should go to the finger flick zone.
(No matter what...)
- I'll sit here. - Okay.
(He reserves a seat in the finger flick zone.)
Only one person from each team can sit in the zone.
(Where should I sit?)
(He sits next to So Min.)
Go away, Jae Suk.
Don't come here.
Come here, Ji Hyo.
(This zone only has the weaker members.)
Go.
- Is the team with Ji Hyo full? - Yes.
- We can be at ease. - Right.
(Another pure area without Jong Kook or Se Chan)
Be at ease.
- Who's sitting here? - This is...
(Where will Jong Kook sit when everyone avoids him?)
Sit here.
- You should sit here. - No.
No, no.
- I don't hit everyone so hard. - Okay.
(Getting frightened as she sees the professional finger flicker)
Really?
(There's only one seat where you can avoid Jong Kook.)
Where will you sit, Min Jae?
(Approaching at the same time)
(Urgent)
Where will you sit, Min Jae?
Hold on.
(They get into a fight.)
(A low kick without hesitation)
Se Chan.
(They struggle to avoid Jong Kook.)
- I can't sit there. - Why would you sit there?
- You sit there. - Where are you going to sit?
- Send Kwang Soo here. - No, no.
(Kwang Soo gets his spot stolen.)
- Okay. - No. Where will you sit? Wait.
(Kwang Soo is taken aback.)
No. Where will you sit?
- Nice. - Where will you sit?
- It's perfect. - Please sit there.
(This is your seat.)
- Is he really going to sit there? - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(He can't let go so easily.)
- Why should we? - Come over here already.
Come here, you punk.
Darn it.
I've been sitting next to him for 10 years in a row.
I sit next to him whenever the penalty is finger flick.
(Kwang Soo has been Jong Kook's finger flick slave for 10 years.)
- I could've been in trouble. - When it comes to finger flick...
(Left: finger flick, Right: toy hammer)
(They all found their seats.)
We'll play 4 songs at the same time. You can just get 1 song right.
(All 4 songs will be played at once, and they must guess 1 song each.)
- Just the song title, right? - Four songs at the same time?
You have to tell us both the singer and the song title.
(They must name both the singer and the title.)
Okay. Let's go.
(The first song will be played.)
Here's the first question.
(Try to guess what songs they are.)
(Four different songs are being played at the same time.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(Sung Cheol was faster.)
Sung Cheol, go ahead.
Hwasa's...
- What was it? "Maria". - Oh, you just...
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(Incorrect.)
- Hwasa's "Twit". - Correct.
("Twit" by Hwasa)
(Correct.)
- Okay. - Oh, right. "Twit".
(Oh, I'm such a twit.)
Oh, right. "Twit".
You may hit one of them.
Se Chan, come on.
(They forgot the power the winner has for a moment.)
You got the right answer because of me.
- What? - You knew it because of me.
Right. My team member practically gave you a hint.
(Haha tries to protect his own team member.)
(He's acting cute.)
I gave you a hint.
- I choose Min Jae. - Gosh.
(Min Jae will be hit.)
I'll hit Min Jae.
(Shivering in fear)
Oh, gosh. I...
(Everyone knows about the finger flicker's power.)
- He's really good at it. - It stings.
You'll be surprised when you wash your face tomorrow morning.
(It's a testimony of a person who actually experienced it.)
- Okay. Get ready. - Oh, gosh.
(The reason why Kwang Soo was surprised while washing his face...)
(Hitting)
(The painful finger flick made him miss her mother.)
- It really hurts. - At least, he has a fringe.
(He's finger flick will make anyone a very good child.)
With the fringe down?
(He spoke casually to him because he's scared.)
Part his fringe.
- Part his fringe. - I'll do that.
(Coaching)
- That would be better. Good. - Like this.
(His delicate hands remove the curtain protection.)
- Yes, that's good. - He'll be surprised.
(Tearing up)
Oh, my gosh.
Don't worry. It will be over quickly.
- Hey, Min Jae. - It will be over quickly.
(He is about to cry.)
- You can get a chance to hit him. - It'll be over quickly.
(It's an advice from someone who already went through with it.)
It'll sting a little. Think of it as getting a shot.
- You can get a chance to hit him. - Stay still. Here we go.
- I can't watch that. - Me neither.
(I can't look.)
(A shot of finger flick was fired.)
My goodness.
(It hurts more than he thought it would.)
All right. Let's continue.
Min Jae, don't forget this.
- Look at him. He's angry. - Okay.
(He is now fully charged with revenge.)
Let's get fired up.
(The mood is heightened.)
- Let's continue. - He's so cute.
(Three songs are left now.)
(Everyone becomes more focused after Min Jae got the penalty.)
All I can hear is "Twit".
Let me answer. "Sorry, Sorry" by Super Junior.
("Sorry Sorry" by Super Junior)
- Wrong. - Was "Sorry, Sorry" played too?
(Correct.)
(The time for finger flick came again sooner than expected.)
He's so good at this game.
(Impressed)
(Who shall I pick this time?)
- How did he know that? - Should I go with the same person?
You should give Sung Cheol a chance as well.
Give it a try. It's worth it.
(I highly recommend it.)
You shouldn't make too many enemies.
(He tries to protect Sung Cheol.)
Should I go with the same person?
- Of course. - Yes, you should do that.
(He feels uneasy as he becomes another target.)
- Why would you make more enemies? - Hold on a second.
- Hang on. - Exactly.
(Wait a minute.)
Don't give Min Jae a hard time.
(The two brothers come out to save Min Jae.)
Why are you meddling in this? Let him choose.
- They're on the same team. - Let them both try it.
- Exactly. - Let him get a taste of it.
(Sung Cheol, it's always painful to be youth.)
Let him get a taste of it.
- He should get a taste of it. - Of course.
You know what it feels like only when you try it.
It's worth the pain.
(It might be too spicy.)
Right. He must be so curious.
(He's about to have a taste.)
- Here we go. - It will sting.
(He got a taste of it.)
- Exactly. - Gosh.
(Shocked)
(It looks so painful that everyone is surprised again.)
(Well...)
(Clenching his teeth)
- That won't be good enough. - Don't get me wrong.
(Sung Cheol)
(Oh, is it not good enough?)
- That won't be good enough. - Don't get me wrong.
Don't be mad. It's just a game.
(Don't frown.)
- Okay. - Get the right answer to hit him.
(These two are really eager to revenge after the flicking.)
- Let's go! - I want to get the right answer.
They can endure it because they're actors.
(Only two songs left.)
Now, we'll continue playing the music.
(He looks bloodthirsty.)
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
Is it "I Really Like You" by Lee Ji Hye?
- Lee Ji Hye? - Lee Ji Hye's "I Really Like You"?
(Incorrect)
I'm sorry.
(They're listening to the songs again.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Jewelry's "I Really Like You".
("I Really Like You" by Jewelry)
(Correct)
Eun Bin almost got the right answer.
She almost got the right answer.
(Eun Bin nearly had the answer.)
I heard Ji Hye's version of the song.
I'm sorry.
(Sit down, Jae Suk.)
- Jae Suk, cover your mouth. - Okay.
- Go ahead. - To prevent it from popping out.
(Beware of the protruding mouth)
- If you're going to hit him hard... - Hit me.
- Shouldn't he take off his glasses? - Hit me.
Go ahead and hit me.
Just wait and see what I'll do next.
(He acts strong.)
(Just watch Jae Suk.)
- His front teeth will be revealed. - Go ahead.
- Hit me. - His front teeth will be revealed.
Hit me.
(His mouth sticks out even further.)
(The hit on the back of his head caused it to stick out more.)
- That wasn't weak at all. - Exactly.
- That wasn't weak at all. - Fine. All right.
(Extremely eager)
- This is war. - That was good.
- Good job. - Wait until I get the right answer.
(Only one song left.)
- That felt so good. - Get the right answer.
Only one song is left.
- Darn. I can't hear any songs. - Right? Isn't it frustrating?
(Frustrated)
- Isn't it frustrating? - Play the music.
(The music is played again.)
(This is very frustrating.)
I can only hear the songs that we already got right.
(He's on his knees with determination.)
What was it?
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
"First Love" by Clon.
("First Love" by Clon)
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
("Holding onto the End of the Night" by Solid)
"Holding onto the End of the Night"...
- by Solid. - I think it's Clon's song.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
(The last song is not easy.)
"My Only Friend" by Solid.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Clon's "Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah".
("Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah" by Clon)
(Correct)
Okay.
(Their faces turn pale.)
Oh, it was "Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah".
(That was close.)
(It's time to check the answer.)
(Se Chan is dancing to the song to celebrate.)
(But the 2 of them can't smile as 1 of them will get hit.)
Min Jae, come on.
(Min Jae is feeling blue and frustrated.)
(Looking)
- Which one... - He should choose one of them.
They're looking at me with a pitiful look.
Don't worry.
(The thought of the finger flick makes them tear up.)
- Let them play rock-paper-scissors. - That's a good idea.
(This time...)
(They'll decide the victim with rock-paper-scissors.)
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - I'll get hit.
- That'll be better. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- You see... - Oh, yes.
(Min Jae wins.)
- Oh, yes. - I said I'd get hit.
(Exhilarated)
(After the desperate struggle,)
(Sung Cheol's forehead shows up again.)
His finger flick is blunt.
I'm going to get hit later anyway.
(Hitting hard)
He hit him really hard.
(Exclaiming)
(That was really a strong blow.)
- He hit him even harder. - He hit him so hard.
That was amazing.
(He goes through an out-of-body experience.)
- Sung Cheol. - That was amazing.
Sung Cheol, you're having a nosebleed.
(Really?)
Sung Cheol.
(He feels sorry.)
- He endured it well. - Right?
(We shall revenge.)
We'll move on to the next question.
(So Min and Haha switched their seats.)
- The beginning part is important. - Okay.
(It's important to catch a song that they know first.)
- So Min, let's do well this time. - Play the music.
(Try to guess what songs they are.)
(Everyone is listening closely.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
("December" by Turbo)
"December" by Turbo.
- Okay. Nice. - Good job.
(Correct)
"December" by Turbo.
(As soon as Jong Kook gets the right answer,)
- Okay. Nice. - Good job.
(Kwang Soo's face turns pale as if his stomach got upset.)
Good job.
(Whose forehead will Jong Kook flick?)
Good job, Jong Kook.
(Yes, you.)
- But Eun Bin... - Is it Turbo's song?
- But Eun Bin... - Stay still.
- might want to experience it. - Why would she?
(He tries to make Eun Bin the victim.)
- Stay still. - That's scary.
- Just let me hit you. - Eun Bin...
It'll be over quickly. You saw them earlier.
(It'll just sting a little.)
(The most powerful finger flick)
(She even closes her eyes.)
(He's having dry heaves.)
Good job.
(Didn't something just come out of my mouth?)
I think he got a dent on his forehead.
(It hurts, right?)
Play the music.
(Only 3 songs are left.)
- Let me answer. - But it hasn't...
"10 Minutes" by Lee Hyo Lee.
("10 Minutes" by Lee Hyo Lee)
No, that's not one of them.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Yes.
"I'm Your Girl" by S.E.S.
Let me answer. "More and More" by TWICE.
("More and More" by TWICE)
(Correct)
(Nice!)
(How did you guess it right?)
- Eun Bin, how did you know? - I heard the song many times.
Which one will you hit?
(Whose forehead will Eun Bin flick?)
I am going to hit Kwang Soo.
Me? I just got hit.
(About to cry)
I just got hit. Why me?
It's better to hit the one who just got hit.
(It's a good choice.)
- He's dazed right now anyway. - Well, I don't mind...
- I can't hit hard. - It would be better.
(Kwang Soo will get flicked for the second time in a row.)
Here we go.
(Hitting lightly)
That was cute. That was really cute.
(It was really light.)
He seems happy. Kwang Soo liked it.
That's not the reason. I'm sure none of you knows,
but she hit my nose with the palm instead of flicking her finger.
(She pretended she would flick her finger,)
She hit my nose with the palm...
instead of flicking her finger.
(but she hit his nose.)
- With the bone here on the palm. - I know.
- It's hard. - You always do that to me.
How hard did she want to hit me?
Eun Bin seems to like cheating.
(Eun Bin has the potential to be another tiger moth.)
Two songs are left.
Play the music.
(Only 2 songs are left.)
Let me answer. "Eternal Love" by Fin.K.L.
("Eternal Love" by Fin.K.L)
(Correct)
(Good job.)
(He finally gets a chance to hit somebody else.)
Which one is it?
(Whose forehead will he hit?)
(He doesn't hesitate to choose Eun Bin.)
Did you choose her?
(It's not me?)
- You'll hit her? - How could he choose her?
(You're horrible.)
Let me explain.
Rather than fighting against Jong Kook...
Good. Change your direction.
(That's a good idea.)
- He has a point. - I thought I should...
(It was the most rational choice for Kwang Soo.)
- make a wise decision. - You're right.
But Kwang Soo, you know that Jong Kook will attack you...
if he gets a chance, right?
I can't believe him. Suk Jin, check the color of your vest.
(What's wrong with you?)
Check the color of your vest.
- Check the color. - Oh, I'm on your team.
(He realizes it a little late.)
- Check the color. - I'm on your team.
(We were on the same team.)
(Suk Jin accidentally attacked his own team member.)
- I forgot that. - You see,
- we always join the team... - Exactly.
that's the rival of Jong Kook's team.
(It's very possible.)
- Check the color of your vest. - We're on the same team.
(It's very awkward to be on the same team.)
- I should check it often. - Yes.
Can I hit my team member when I get the right answer?
(No way.)
Can we volunteer to get hit instead of her?
- Yes, you can. - Sung Cheol.
(Me?)
- Me? - He's good at reacting.
(It was really good.)
Continue the momentum. You were hit already.
(The screen is not on pause.)
You can do it.
- You should do it for her. - You're a man.
(After looking at Sung Cheol's desperate look...)
Sung Cheol is contemplating.
- I'll get hit. - Okay.
I didn't hit you hard earlier, right?
By the way, Eun Bin, do you have a shoot tomorrow?
- Yes, I do. - Eun Bin, do you have a shoot?
I have a shoot tomorrow.
I'll hit her on the head, not the forehead.
- On the head? - It won't be visible.
(He'll flick the side of her head as an alternative.)
- That's a good idea. - Here.
- I'll hit on the side of the head. - On the side?
- I can't hit hard either. - Right?
- Kwang Soo can't hit hard. - It's just a game.
(I'm sorry.)
Hey, how could you...
(He hit the side of her head.)
(Oh, boy.)
(They laugh at Eun Bin's reaction.)
- Goodness. - Eun Bin.
- Hey. - Are you a human?
(I didn't put any strength in the flick.)
- How could you do that? - Are you insane?
- No... - You call yourself a human?
I didn't know how to do it.
Eun Bin. I'm sorry.
(Feeling guilty)
- I'm sorry. Are you okay? - Eun Bin. Are you okay?
(Even she thinks it was funny.)
- You should check. - Eun Bin. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Hey.
(Kwang Soo doesn't discriminate anyone when flicking.)
How do you call yourself a human?
Can I go home?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
(He really means it.)
- It's okay. - She must be startled.
She has a good reaction.
(That was good.)
I think I can answer the questions better now.
(Enthusiastic)
Right. You can do it.
- Let's go. - Are you okay? You can do it.
(Current points)
Okay.
- Go, Team Green. - Play the music.
(There's only one song left.)
(I'll get it right this time.)
Let me answer.
"Love and Remember" by god.
("Love and Remember" by god)
(Correct)
Really?
(Team Orange is only 2 points away.)
- We need to improve. - How did you know?
We better improve.
I really can't hear anything.
Who?
(Jae Suk gets to hit with a toy hammer.)
Wait. Who should I pick?
Make them play rock-paper-scissors.
Right. Play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Honestly, I want to hit So Min. - She won.
(Ji Hyo wins.)
Ji Hyo. Did you win?
- Yes, I won. - Okay.
- But I won. - You won.
I won.
(What a twist.)
Jae Suk wanted to hit Ji Hyo from the beginning.
Maybe he was thinking he will hit the winner in his head.
Right. I wished you'd lose. I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
(It's sad.)
(Rock-paper-scissors is only for show.)
I'd already made up my mind.
- Okay. - Okay, Ji Hyo.
Then now...
(Clean shot)
Okay.
- That sounded refreshing. - Right.
(Current points)
This is the third question. Play the music.
Let me answer.
- Min Jae. - Let me answer.
(As Min Jae shouts,)
(Se Chan looks nervous.)
- Min Jae. You should answer it. - Five,
(It reminds him of their ill-fated relationship.)
4, 3...
(His forehead still hurts from the flick.)
(He finally got a chance for revenge.)
- Min Jae. You should answer it. - 5, 4...
- Don't be nervous. Answer it. - Okay. It's Haha's...
"Nino Maximus Keyser Soze".
It's...
(Sneering)
- Let me answer. - Oh, please.
Oh, please.
"Story of a Little Kid" by Haha.
("Story of a Little Kid" by Haha)
(Correct)
- Hey. - Oh, please.
(He blew up his chance for revenge.)
- I forgot. - You didn't know the title.
- Gosh. - Oh, thank you.
- That was... - You didn't know the title.
(I'm safe.)
You didn't know the title.
(Thanks to Min Jae, Haha got it for free.)
Why do you keep giving it away?
- I know. Why? - I...
I forgot the title.
(Very sad)
Who are you going to hit?
Why aren't you taking it off? Take it off.
(The cap)
(He'd already decided the target in his mind.)
Here?
Okay. Just hit anywhere. Hurry up!
(Pretending to be strong)
Hit me already. I need to answer questions. Hurry up.
(Delayed spike)
Gosh.
Hit me already. I need to answer questions.
(He got a strong one for acting tough.)
Good shot.
(Angry)
- I'm so angry. - You have three songs left.
Play the music.
(They have 3 songs left.)
(Wait. This song is...)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
"Aing" by Orange Caramel.
("Aing" by Orange Caramel)
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Yes.
- Two... - It's ZE:A's
(Jong Kook gets a chance.)
- "After Effect". - "After Effect".
("After Effect" by ZE:A)
(Correct)
Okay.
- Pardon? - Why do you look sad?
(You didn't know.)
Why do you look sad?
How about hitting the back of Kwang Soo's head instead?
(Nosy)
- Why... - Hit Kwang Soo?
(Me again?)
Sure. I won't hit his forehead. The back of your head doesn't hurt.
Me? The back of my head doesn't hurt?
- It doesn't hurt. - You want me to hit you with this?
(Angry)
No.
Hey. The top of the head doesn't hurt.
(He decides to hit in the crown instead of the back of the head.)
- Wait. - It doesn't hurt at all.
I...
(Cracking)
(His head is split in half.)
(Swearing)
(Shocked)
(Screaming)
That was really loud.
(It feels good to hit the top of the head.)
That was loud.
Hey. The top of the head doesn't hurt.
Everything looks green.
Don't lie.
- I'm serious. Everything is green. - I said stop lying.
(Do you have a problem with your vision?)
(The top of the head can feel pain. It's been checked.)
That was amazing.
I think that was the loudest.
(The flick literally rings a bell in Kwang Soo's head.)
That sounded like a watermelon though.
That was strong.
(The king of flick approves.)
You have two songs left. You can't get up and discuss.
(They have 2 songs left.)
- Let's do this! - Play the music.
(Music plays again to find the 2 hidden songs.)
Let me answer.
It's Park Hyo Shin's...
(Sung Cheol got flicked twice.)
(He finally got a chance to revenge.)
- That was too much. - That was...
Let me answer.
It's Park Hyo Shin's...
(Will he be able to take his revenge on Se Chan?)
5, 4...
Four...
("Memories Resemble Love" by Park Hyo Shin)
- "Memories Resemble Love". - Let me answer.
(Incorrect)
(He loses his one and only chance.)
"Snow Flower" by Park Hyo Shin.
("Snow Flower" by Park Hyo Shin)
Yes!
(Correct)
"Snow Flower" by Park Hyo Shin. Yes!
(Oh, right. "Snow Flower".)
Come on.
(Someone's as angry as Sung Cheol.)
You're out of control.
(My Jong Kook)
(Happy ceremony)
Calm down.
(Jong Kook's excited.)
That's scary.
(If he answers the question again, people will be injured.)
- Hey. - That was scary.
(Staggering)
- Yes! - Anyway, I'm happy.
- I'm happy. - That was good.
(Meanwhile, someone waits for it in the corner.)
- Good. - That was close.
- Was it correct? - Good.
Was it correct?
Good.
(His legs feel weak. He staggers.)
That was insane, Jong Kook.
Look at Kwang Soo. He doesn't want to get hit.
He's sitting politely to avoid the hit.
(Polite)
The back of the head wouldn't hurt.
(Don't worry.)
I already hit the forehead and the top of the head.
(Jong Kook looks for a new area.)
Hit me in the back.
(He decides to hit the back of the head.)
- Here? - That's...
- How about here? - Honestly,
I can't hear well since the last hit. I can't answer the questions.
Then you tell me.
- In the back. - I'll stroke. You tell me.
I'll stroke. Tell me to stop.
- Stop. - Here?
Okay. Is this okay?
(Customized service)
(He chooses the lower area that is most insensitive.)
We'll get to see Kwang Soo bowing.
- Thank you. - Wait.
(I'll bear it.)
Kwang Soo. It's all right. This doesn't hurt at all.
Did you hit in the back of the head?
Happy New Year.
Give them a bow.
(She bows too as she feels sorry.)
Good.
It's okay, isn't it? It doesn't hurt in the back.
(It's already been 8 months, but still, happy new year.)
- Good job. - It doesn't hurt, does it?
(It's a lie that the back of the head doesn't feel pain.)
Okay. Okay.
It's the last question. Play the music.
(They have only one song left.)
(They can only hear the songs they answered already.)
Let me answer.
- All I can think of is her - No.
(Covering his mouth)
Let me answer.
(Jong Kook couldn't answer.)
(Jae Suk from Jong Kook's team gives it a try.)
It's Hong Kyung Min's...
- 5, 4... - It's...
(If he answers it, his team will be in the lead.)
"Broken Love".
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
(Incorrect)
Let me answer.
(Sung Cheol who was a little faster gets the chance.)
- It was Sung Cheol. - Let me answer.
Sung Cheol was fast.
"Broken Friendship" by Hong Kyung Min.
("Broken Friendship" by Hong Kyung Min)
Okay. Let's do this.
(Correct)
- Let's do this. - Why couldn't I remember it?
(He finally gets a chance.)
- Why didn't you remember? - My flicks aren't strong.
I feel sorry for Kyung Min.
(They're buddies.)
Sung Cheol. Make it good.
I can't do it.
(Kim Sung Cheol, the variety show novice)
- You have to do it. - Hit this for practice.
(They test his strength before the flick.)
Practice on this.
(It's pretty strong.)
- That was pretty strong. - Right. That's what you do.
That's what you should do.
(It's pretty strong for someone with no experience.)
He's strong.
I've never done it before.
(Se Chan opens his forehead, which Sung Cheol wanted desperately.)
Right here...
You should practice on this.
(Famous Jong Kook is deployed.)
That's right. That was good. You got it.
(He can't help smiling at the thought of flicking Se Chan.)
Okay. Remember this.
- If you... - No. I don't know anything.
(Cutting off)
- I'm going to be a gangster now. - Okay. Sure.
(He pretends to be strong to hide his anxiety.)
- He's going to be a gangster. - I sure will.
- I need a support. - Put your hand. That's right.
Put your hand on the protruding...
(Hitting)
(Eyes opening wide)
You did it.
(Unimaginable power)
He has the talent.
- You have the talent. - Good job.
(He found an unexpected talent.)
You have the talent.
(That's how it feels.)
Good job.
You have the talent for it.
(Vicarious satisfaction)
- Good job. - Well done.
- Was that good? - Yes.
- That was really strong. - Okay.
No. Now I have a reason to become a gangster.
Good. Okay. Let's do this.
(As Se Chan becomes a gang, it's a tie.)
All gangsters have a reason. They didn't just become a gangster.
That hurts.
(Team Green answered "SOLO" and "Because You're My Woman".)
It's the last question. Play...
the music.
(They look for the third song.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Gosh.
"Bingo" by Turtles.
(Incorrect)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(All three teams try to answer it.)
- No. - Let me answer.
You should play rock-paper-scissors.
(Since it's a crucial moment, they'll play rock-paper-scissors.)
Let's do it. Let's go. Rock-paper-scissors.
(The current score is 6 to 4 to 4.)
(If Team Green answers this question, they win.)
Now, now. Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
(Jong Kook of Team Orange is out.)
- Nice job, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
So Min.
(They know the answer.)
(The rock-paper-scissors will determine the result.)
Kwang Soo. We need to take revenge.
This is the last one. If we win, it's over.
(Two proud geniuses)
(The result of the first game depends on the rock-paper-scissors.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors. Okay!
(Kwang Soo of Team Green wins.)
"Airplane" by Turtles.
("Airplane" by Turtles)
Okay!
(Correct)
(That was close.)
That was good.
(Team Green wins.)
That was close.
Now, Team Green won.
Why... I don't get to hit someone?
Go ahead.
(Hitting means more to Kwang Soo than his team winning.)
(What?)
- Wait. - He didn't hit me right.
(He ruined it from straining too much.)
- It's over. - No.
(Kwang Soo blew up the chance that he worked hard to earn.)
- You hit me. It's over. - It doesn't count.
- It doesn't count. - It's over.
(Let me try again.)
- No. - You flicked already. It's over.
- No, it doesn't count. - It's over.
(He finally hits Jong Kook right.)
I'm sorry.
(He came back to his senses.)
(He's acting cute with all his body.)
He just hit me.
I'm sorry.
(I'll let it go since I hit him three times.)
Okay, okay.
He's generous.
(The first mission ends with Jong Kook's tolerance.)
I'll announce the result of the first mission.
- Ji Hyun's Team Green placed first. - That was close.
(Team Green won the first mission.)
(They'll get to enjoy the benefit.)
- I'll tell you the benefit. - You tried hard.
It's the first Promotion Time where you can guess...
(They can guess each other's grade...)
(and earn the Promotion Badge in Promotion Time.)
each other's grade and earn the Promotion Badge.
You can ask one person from each team their grade...
(They can reveal the grade of 1 person they want...)
(from Team Blue and Team Orange.)
in front of everyone.
After guessing the grade,
(They'll have a discussion based on the revealed grade.)
we'll pick 1 person randomly among you 4.
(1 person from Team Green selected randomly by staff...)
(will enter the Promotion Booth.)
That person will place three people in each group.
(That person will place 3 people in each box,)
(1 person from each team.)
Then the person with the highest grade...
will receive the Promotion Badge.
(The person with the highest grade...)
So, if Sung Cheol's the highest, he receives one badge.
(in each box wins the Promotion Badge.)
They'll be able to place them.
(They can guess each other's grades using the result.)
So based on the results, we have to guess one another's grades.
But what's important here is...
(If 2 people are in the highest grade together,)
If there are two people who are in the same grade,
they will be eliminated, and the next highest grade will get it.
Really?
(they will be excluded, and the next highest grade will get it.)
- Either you win or get eliminated. - Overlapping is the worst.
- Really? - First,
Team Green must decide which person they want to ask...
(They must decide which team's grade...)
from each team.
(between Team Blue and Team Orange to ask.)
- Should we gather up in our teams? - Yes.
(The 2 people whose grades are revealed will be at a disadvantage.)
We can ask two people.
Yes, we can ask two people.
Should we ask who's in the lowest grade...
- or who's in the highest grade? - The lowest grade.
- The lowest? - That way,
(Ji Hyun claims it'll be easier to get the Promotion Badge...)
when we place each person,
(if they find out who's in a lower grade.)
we can write them down.
We have to ask about Jong Kook or Jae Suk...
(Kwang Soo claims that the final race will be easier...)
because at the end during the race...
- we can calculate our moves. - It will help us.
(if they know which grades Jong Kook and Jae Suk are in.)
Should we ask about Jong Kook first?
(After the discussion)
We've decided. We want to know about Haha from Team Blue...
(Haha)
and...
- Jong Kook from Team Orange. - Jong Kook from Team Orange.
(and Jong Kook's grades will be revealed.)
Haha...
- is in second grade. - Goodness.
How did I get one wrong?
(This child who cried out when he got one wrong...)
(barely got 25 points and was placed in 2nd grade.)
This is the same as getting it all wrong.
Haha...
(It's followed by Jong Kook's grade.)
- is in second grade. - Goodness.
Kim Jong Kook is also in second grade.
- Goodness. - Now,
(Jong Kook's grade is unexpectedly low with 27.5 points.)
the four of you must come to a consensus,
and the person that is chosen will go inside the booth.
(Team Green will get 3 minutes for a meeting.)
We don't know who will go inside the booth, right?
(They will randomly choose who will go into the booth.)
Right. We'll choose that person in three minutes
Then what grade are you in?
Are we not allowed to tell?
(We can help each other only if we know that.)
We need to know that...
- We need to know. Let's reveal it. - to place them together.
I'm in fourth grade.
(I shouldn't have asked.)
- It's true. - I'm sorry, but...
If you're in fourth grade, it's over because I...
I'll be honest, I'm in third grade.
- I'm in third grade. - I will...
bet everything I have on the fact that you're in first grade.
(Se Chan is...)
No. That's not true.
- He's a kid. - I...
(I assure you.)
I'll choose the person now.
(They will start the random draw to choose the representative.)
The person who will place everyone...
- is Song Ji Hyo. - Oh, my gosh.
(Ji Hyo is picked.)
- Did you understand the rules? - Song Ji Hyo will...
- Ji Hyo... - To be exact,
do you know what she said earlier?
(Don't even mention it.)
I told her we needed to place them,
and she asked me what a badge was.
It's "place", not "badge".
You should go.
(Too big a responsibility compared to her degree of understanding)
You can go in now.
You can't explain it to her.
- She needs to go right in. - I have high hopes.
- Yes, me too. - Ji Hyo...
(The other teams have hope as Ji Hyo is picked.)
I have high expectations.
I hope Ji Hyo makes a complete mess of things.
(She enters the booth with worries and hopes.)
- I am expectant. - You know what we mean, right?
- I understand. - We'll show you the placement,
(1 member of each team will be placed in each box.)
and then we will announce who won.
You can make your guesses with that.
(The member in the highest grade for each box will get a badge.)
So you have to go in there no matter what.
(You have to be the representative.)
You can betray your team from in there.
Ji Hyo will place them so that she benefits from it.
(At least...)
(Ji Hyo contemplates for a long time with a vacant look on her face.)
(She places herself in Box 4.)
(She places Haha and Jong Jook who overlap in 2nd grade with her.)
(Surprisingly, she understands the rules well.)
(If she's not in 2nd grade, she gets the badge.)
You know what you're doing, right?
(Ji Hyo understands the rules very well today.)
I expect something nice, Ji Hyo.
- I'll show you the placement. - Okay.
(Revealing the result of Ji Hyo's placement)
This is how Ji Hyo placed everyone.
Okay.
- Ji Hyo... - Okay.
- In the first room... - understood the rules.
- The person to get the badge... - This is hard.
in the first room is...
Park Ji Hyun.
(Promotion)
Ji Hyun is in a higher grade.
In the second room, it's Kim Sung Cheol.
(Promotion)
In the third room, it's Jeon So Min.
In the fourth room, it's Song Ji Hyo.
(Promotion)
- Hold on. - We were fooled.
(Ji Hyun, Sung Cheol, So Min, and Ji Hyo get promoted.)
- They are in a higher grade? - Hold on.
(Getting the badge doesn't always mean you're in the highest grade.)
We don't know if they're in a higher grade.
There could've been eliminations because they overlapped.
(The one in a lower grade might have gotten it...)
That's possible too.
(because there were 2 members in the highest grade.)
- Hold on. Wait a minute. - Ji Hyun is in a high grade.
(The badges they were given will be applied before the final race.)
You will use the badges during the race.
It doesn't change your grade right now.
Please put it on.
I guess So Min got a lot right.
(Envying)
I can't believe this happened.
I got bad grades when I was a student.
(Too much information)
- We'll move on to the next mission. - Okay.
(They move on to the second mission after the first promotion.)
I think our guests definitely got better scores than us.
(2nd period of the music school before lunchtime)
Did you guys cook here?
(A sumptuous feast)
They must've cooked.
- What is this? - Soy sauce marinated crabs.
(Plump soy sauce marinated crab...)
- It looks delicious. - Soy sauce marinated crabs.
(and savory acorn jelly)
- This looks amazing. - It's acorn jelly.
- I love acorn jelly. - Are you letting us just eat it?
(Their eyes open wide before the meal with 8 side dishes.)
- This looks delicious. - Can we just eat it?
Why? What did we do to deserve it? Do you just like us?
(Jumping the gun)
Are you just giving it to us?
(It's yet a pie in the sky.)
- They must be taking dishes away. - Before the final race,
this is the final mission. We're in second period.
(2nd period before the final race)
We're going to test your sense of beat and rhythm for a chance to eat.
(Testing their sense of beat and rhythm for a chance to eat)
We're going to play Break Up Strawberries.
(Break Up Strawberries)
- Break Up Strawberries? - Break Up Strawberries?
What are we breaking up this time?
(We're breaking up strawberries?)
Using the word "Strawberry",
you're going to break it up according to the beat.
(They'll break up the word "strawberry" according to the beat.)
- St-raw-ber-ry. - For one, it's...
- St-raw-ber-ry. - St-raw-ber-ry.
- For two, it's... - Straw-berry-straw-berry.
- For three, it's... - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry.
For four,
it's "Strawberry-strawberry strawberry-strawberry".
- St-raw-ber-ry - St-raw-ber-ry
- Strawberry-strawberry - Strawberry-strawberry
(Song Ji Hyo, a student at the music school, lacks a sense of rhythm)
- Strawberry-strawberry - Gosh.
St-raw-ber-ry
- St-raw-ber-ry - St-raw-ber-ry
(Guys...)
Show me.
(Ji Hyo's hopeless.)
Don't laugh.
- St-raw... Strawberry. - Someone who's good should show us.
(Team Green's cause of worry, Ji Hyo)
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry - Everyone.
(On the other hand, Eun Bin understands the rules right away.)
Every time you get one wrong,
you must give up one dish.
(They give up one 1 dish every time they get one wrong.)
- What? - You must return it when you lose.
Gosh, Jae Suk is bad at this.
(They get 1 point if their attack works.)
(Nervous)
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- We'll start with Suk Jin. - I'll start.
(Suk Jin will go first.)
- Let's go! Let's do this! - We'll start with Suk Jin.
(Whispering)
- Let's cheer before we start. - Do three no matter what.
Let's cheer before we start. One...
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
(Team Orange plans to go for 3 beats, which is difficult.)
Let's go!
We should go after Ji Hyo.
Okay. I understand.
(Team Blue's target is Ji Hyo.)
Right? That member is bad, right?
- Suk Jin too. - Get ready.
(And...)
- Suk Jin. - We're starting.
- Jae Suk. - Let's go!
(Full of targets)
- Ready, set, go. - Let's cheer before we start.
Let's cheer before we start.
(Team Green is giving Ji Hyo a last-minute lesson.)
- Let's go! - Strawberry
- Straw-berry-straw-berry - Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry - Strawberry-strawberry, It's three.
- Get ready. - We're starting.
(Round 1 begins with Suk Jin's attack.)
- Ready, - Attack.
set, go.
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
Sung Cheol, three.
(Happy)
(Sung Cheol fell victim to Team Orange's plan.)
- Sung Cheol. - This is really hard.
(Team Orange easily earns 1 point.)
Please return one of your side dishes.
- The soy sauce. - The soy sauce.
(They give up the soy sauce.)
The soy sauce.
- Where should I put it? - I'll do it.
Let's go!
(Kwang Soo ran over to help them return the side dish.)
Where should I put it?
I'll do it.
Let's go!
(He got up,)
Our referees will collect it.
(but the referee came, so he wasn't helpful.)
You should eat the meat.
Kwang Soo, you shouldn't wander around during a shoot.
(You punk.)
Do I start now?
(At a loss for words)
(He is always waiting for a chance to attack Kwang Soo.)
- Good luck! - Okay.
- Team Blue will start. - Okay.
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
(Eun Bin of Team Blue resumes the game.)
- Kwang Soo, four. - Strawberry-strawberry-...
(4 beats)
strawberry-strawberry
Jae Suk, three.
Strawberry-strawberry- strawberry-strawberry
(His fist lost track of the rhythm already.)
Jae Suk, three.
Break up strawberries
(Flustered)
Jae Suk, three.
Break up strawberries
(He was flustered and suddenly sang about strawberries.)
Hey!
(His game fright recurs.)
Focus.
If it's Kwang Soo's turn, he's bound to go after you.
(Can you please focus?)
It's either you or me.
(Feeling refreshed)
- Try not to go after Jae Suk. - My gosh.
(He's not good.)
- Jae Suk is... - Gosh, I feel refreshed.
(His face gets red as he's taken aback.)
I feel refreshed!
(Kwang Soo, who was always being teased, gets 1 point.)
Well done. Nice shot!
Let's take out the soy sauce.
- Take out the soy sauce. - Take out the soy sauce.
(Team Orange gives up the soy sauce.)
Take it.
We're going to go after Jae Suk, so take out the acorn jelly too.
Look.
(Checking his beat again to prevent themselves from giving up more)
- St-raw-ber-ry - St-raw-ber-ry
- I got it. - What comes after?
Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry- strawberry. This is four.
(Listen.)
Strawberry-strawberry- strawberry-strawberry
- Strawberry-strawberry - Is Suk Jin teaching him?
- Straw-berry-straw-berry - Try three.
(An unusual scene)
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(3 beats)
- That's right. He's good now. - I got it now.
(He passes the inspection.)
Set, go.
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
(Team Orange: 1, Team Blue: 0, and Team Green: 1)
- Kwang Soo, three. - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(3 beats)
- So Min, four. - Strawberry-strawberry-...
strawberry-strawberry
- Ji Hyo, one. - St-raw-ber-ry
(Ji Hyo's part goes by smoothly.)
- So Min, two. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-straw-berry
- What was that? - She did a good job.
(Offbeat strawberries)
- What was that? - Straw-berry-straw-berry
- I did it right. - No, you didn't!
- What was that? - It was right.
No.
(Isn't this it?)
That sounded more like three.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry - Straw-berry-straw-berry
(This is the correct answer.)
- Hold on. - I'm happy because this happened...
(Pleased)
- after she acted like she was good. - You made a fool of yourself!
(Pleased to see another one with no sense of rhythm)
How much more exact did I have to be?
Straw-berry-straw-berry
- See? It's right. - What kind of game are you playing?
- You made a fool of yourself. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
(Staring)
- Take one out. What will it be? - Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-straw-berry
I'm so sorry.
(Right.)
Don't you feel sorry to us?
(We're giving up another dish.)
Take one out. What will it be?
We'll take out the ssamjang.
You can't remove just that one.
(This whole thing is a set.)
We'll take out the ssamjang.
(She tries to give up ssamjang only.)
- You can't remove just that one. - It's a set.
- Eun Bin plays dirty too. - Eun Bin...
(What was that?)
She's also a bit...
- She doesn't play nicely. - She doesn't.
(Eun Bin is another expert on playing dirty.)
- Let's take this one out. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
(They give up dried laver and kimchi.)
So Min, be strategical.
Okay.
(Strategically?)
- Hey. - I'm going to get it this time.
(So Min decides to play strategically.)
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
Jae Suk, three.
(She calls on Jae Suk strategically.)
- I'm going to get it this time. - Break up strawberries
(Nervous)
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
Jae Suk, three.
Strawberry-strawberry- strawberry-strawberry
(It's 3, but he did 4.)
Strawberry, strawberry, strawberry, strawberry
(A good harvest for strawberries)
(Yoo Jae Suk, Bad at strawberry games, Gets it wrong every time)
Strawberry
Why is he so bad at games involving strawberries?
(Amazed)
- He's bad at strawberry games. - Don't be so nervous.
(Please...)
- Don't be so nervous. - This is driving me crazy.
(He practiced so hard, but he's of no use during the actual game.)
He's nervous.
If I get it wrong again, just beat me up.
Take out the acorn jelly.
- Take it out. We won't eat it. - How many times is this?
(They give up acorn jelly pretending to be okay.)
- Hold on. - We won't have the acorn jelly.
- Try three again. - You should've given the lettuce.
(Practicing again)
(3 beats)
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry - Good.
That's right. I'm good at practices.
- You'd be good if you were calm. - He's too nervous.
(His sense of rhythm goes back to square one when the game begins.)
Are you afraid of strawberries?
- This is how I was as a rookie. - Prepare yourself at every round.
- You will be chosen every round. - Okay.
(The strawberry game brings back his rookie side.)
I'll go. Ready, start.
(They resume while staying nervous.)
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
(Team Orange: 1, Team Blue: 1, and Team Green: 2)
- Ji Hyun, two. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
(2 beats)
Strawberry, four.
- What was that? - What was that?
Straw-berry-straw-berry Strawberry, four.
(She defends it well...)
(but fails in attacking.)
- What was that? - She did such a good job too.
- You need to attack. - She did such a good job too.
Ji Hyun, who's Strawberry Four?
- What did she say? - She couldn't attack.
What did she say?
She just said Strawberry, four.
(I don't know.)
Who is that?
(Is there someone named Strawberry here?)
- What's she saying? - Is someone named Strawberry?
- Who's Strawberry? - Is someone named Strawberry?
Does anyone have the nickname Strawberry?
(We're looking for Strawberry.)
- Strawberry, four. - Strawberry.
Do we have a spy today?
I kept thinking about saying strawberry.
(She's only thinking of strawberries.)
She kept thinking about strawberry.
- Just think about Jae Suk, two. - Okay.
(A winning plan)
- If you do that, it's over. - Isn't this wrong?
- They have to take something out. - They do.
(Team Green gives up acorn jelly.)
- Let's take out the acorn jelly. - Let's do that.
Since we took out the soy sauce, we'll take out the acorn jelly.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry - We have the main dishes.
- What is it? Strawberry-strawberry - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- St-raw-ber-ry - Strawberry. For 2 and 3,
(Nervous)
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(Don't get it wrong.)
I got it down perfectly this time.
- I will do it perfectly this time. - Ready, go!
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
(Team Orange: 2, Team Blue: 1, and Team Green: 2)
Eun Bin, three.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(3 beats)
- Jae Suk, two. - Strawberry-strawberry
(He was resting his hands after his turn.)
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry Jae Suk, two.
Strawberry-strawberry
(He fails right away.)
(Get over here.)
It was like he was attacked.
- Hear me out. - Grab him.
Get him.
(The beat destroyer is under arrest.)
Kick him.
- I mean... - Just watch.
(Urgently)
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry Isn't this right?
Why can't you do that during the game then?
(What's the point of getting it right this time?)
Here. Take one of his legs.
(They grab both of his legs.)
- Actually, lay him on the floor. - Hey.
(They force Jae Suk to lie down.)
- You need to be taught a lesson. - Hold on.
(It has been a while. It'll help you come to your senses.)
(Trembling)
Let go of him. Get a grip on yourself!
(The split wakes him up good.)
Get a grip on yourself!
Get a grip on yourself.
- Why... - He must've dreaded his turn.
- Unbelievable. - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- I got it now. - Exactly.
- Don't tense up. - I won't.
(Sighing)
Always think that it's your turn.
(He is as nervous as when he was just a newbie.)
I was like this in my rookie days.
- You know what I mean, right? - Let's practice.
Jae Suk, three.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(His gesture is wrong too.)
- Jae Suk, three. - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(He failed to tap his thighs.)
- Right? - Tap your thighs first.
- Tap here. - Hold on.
Tap... Hold on.
Tap here.
(His thighs get smashed.)
Tap your thighs first.
(The terrorizing Jong Kook gives a lesson he'll never forget.)
Got it?
- Tap your thighs first. - Got it.
(Education)
- I will. - Tap your thighs first.
(Complete)
- I got it. - Unbelievable.
(The spartan beat lesson ensures you to remember.)
Okay, I won't forget that.
That'll help you stay within the beat.
Let's practice once more.
(Practice)
- Jae Suk, four. - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(3-beat)
Strawberry-strawberry
(He chanted the 3-beat instead of the 4-beat.)
You need to say "strawberry" four times.
- Okay, got it. - What's with your fingers though?
(What's wrong with him?)
- What's this? - Don't you dare chime in.
(He even adds new gestures.)
- What are you trying to say? - Don't you dare speak.
(What is it?)
Is it a white flag or a blue flag?
- Like and dislike. - What?
Like and dislike.
Unbelievable.
(Team Orange's table is clearing out fast.)
- Let's give up the lettuce. - Sure thing. It's useless.
What about the dried laver? Okay, that could go next.
(He gives up the lettuce.)
The doenjang stew is cold now, so...
- I'm sorry, but... - Sounds good.
Did you taste the food?
- Who ate the food? - What on earth?
(Did you eat already?)
- What... - You actually ate it?
(They're chewing something.)
- Eun Bin, really? - What do you think you're doing?
(While Team Orange is preoccupied in getting the beat down...)
Here.
(She takes a bite.)
Is it good?
(She takes a bite too.)
I don't get it though because no one knows that we ate it.
(She shares how she cheats as if it's a clever skill.)
I'm sorry, but did you taste the food?
(But they're immediately caught.)
- Who ate the food? - What on earth?
(The two sly sisters didn't even swallow the food.)
- What... - You actually ate it?
- Eun Bin, really? - What do you think you're doing?
You should give one up.
I get why So Min did it, but I didn't expect this from Eun Bin.
- What? - You corrupted her.
I'm regretting liking you in "Hot Stove League".
(Eun Bin is learning cheating skills next to So Min.)
Let's go again.
- All right. - Let's do this.
(Team Orange: 2, Team Blue: 2, Team Green: 2)
Ready, set, go.
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
Strawberry-strawberry- strawberry-strawberry
- Jae Suk, two. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Se Chan, three. - Strawberry-strawberry... Gosh.
Nice!
Strawberry-strawberry... Gosh.
(Jae Suk manages to score for the first time.)
Nice!
All right!
- See? - Nicely done.
- You can do it, you know. - What did I tell you?
(Jong Kook's splitting leg lesson achieved a miracle.)
He's actually gotten better.
- I had no idea he'd manage this. - He's actually gotten better.
(I can't believe Jae Suk actually made it.)
- Sometimes, a beating is required. - That was nice.
(Satisfied)
I have a feeling that Jae Suk will be able...
to return my attack.
- You... - You can be sharper.
Think more about how you'll manage his attack.
I can't believe it's Ji Hyo saying this.
(Surprised)
She's not bad at this, that's why.
Se Chan can take it once, but not twice.
(Teasing)
- Not twice. - Yes, I can see that.
(Jae Suk teases only after getting one win.)
Please give up a dish.
- Let's give this up. - Jae Suk's back in the game.
(Team Green gives up kimchi and laver.)
I know.
- I can do this game perfectly now. - As irony would have it...
The chemistry...
(Se Chan's on the offensive next.)
- Attack Jae Suk again. - St-raw-ber-ry
- Is it my turn? - Yes.
(Se Chan begins the next round with Jae Suk as the target.)
- Let's go again. - Strawberry...
- I'll go with Jae Suk first. - Strawberry...
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
- Jae Suk, three. - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Se Chan, four. - Strawberry-strawberry-...
strawberry-strawberry
(They now exchange well.)
Jae Suk, two.
Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Se Chan, four. - Strawberry-strawberry-...
strawberry-strawberry
Haha, two.
(Blitz)
Strawberry-strawberry
(The blitz makes him say it clearly but off the beat.)
(That was good.)
Jae Suk, that was a long battle.
- What a long battle. - Nice!
(Haha failed to respond at Se Chan's blitz.)
- We did it. - What a long battle.
Nice!
- That was awesome. - Jae Suk,
that was a long battle.
(Thanks to Haha's cute two strawberries,)
- Strawberry-strawberry - It went back and forth.
(the long exchange finally comes to an end.)
- Okay. - Why make it sound so cute though?
- Please hand in a dish. - Okay, got it.
(Team Blue returns the lettuce.)
- Okay. - Good.
- Go, go. - A beating from Jong Kook...
- It wakes you up, doesn't it? - Jae Suk.
- It woke you up. - You're way better now.
(Jae Suk improved rapidly after Jong Kook's lesson.)
I'm someone who needs a beating.
- You're perfect at this now. - I know.
Beatings work for those old.
(The final round's offense...)
Is it my turn then?
(will be done by Ji Hyo.)
- Ji Hyo will go first. - Right.
- Break up strawberries - Break up strawberries
- Jae Suk, two. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
(It's a 2-beat.)
- Ji Hyun, three. - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(Skillful)
- Min Jae, one. - St-raw-ber-ry
(It's a 1- beat.)
- He's so good at that. - Ji Hyun, one.
St-raw-ber-ry
- Suk Jin, two. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-straw-berry
(His hands weren't on point.)
(He creates a new beat by being off-beat.)
Did you see that?
- What was that? - I mean...
Didn't it remind you of this catchphrase?
(I saw that somewhere.)
- This. - Hold on.
You were off to a good start.
(Now that Jae Suk is good, Suk Jin makes a mistake.)
- The beat was just wrong. - What on earth was that?
- Straw-berry... - Straw-berry-straw-berry
(Goodness)
- What on earth was that? - What's with the tongue?
What was the reason for that?
(Thanks to Suk Jin Team Green earns another point.)
That's too bad. I know I could've won this round.
Once again, Team Green is the winner.
(Team Orange: 3, Team Blue: 2, Team Green: 4)
They keep winning.
We'll warm up the food for you.
(Team Green wins the 1st place for the 2nd period too.)
That's too bad.
(That was close.)
It really was a close game.
(They feel sad even after losing so many times.)
- We could've won. - I know.
- Two? - Yes.
You can ask one from each team.
(Team Green can check 1 person's grades to be revealed...)
(from Team Blue and Team Orange.)
Why don't we ask this person?
Eun Bin and Jae Suk.
(They decide to ask about Eun Bin and Jae Suk.)
Right, Jae Suk.
We'll ask Eun Bin from Team Blue...
and Jae Suk from Team Orange.
(They'll check the grades...)
(of Jae Suk and Eun Bin.)
This will probably reveal the answer. Let's write it down.
(What are their grades?)
Eun Bin is...
- in fourth grade. - Okay.
- Okay. - Really?
(Eun Bin guessed many questions correctly.)
...in fourth grade.
(Eun Bin's in 4th grade?)
- Okay. - Really?
(Ji Hyun was promoted because Suk Jin is also in 4th grade.)
- Then Suk Jin is in fourth grade. - Right.
...in fourth grade.
(Suk Jin's in 4th grade with 37.5 points.)
- Okay. - Really?
And Jae Suk...
- He's in first grade. - What?
- That kid! - Hold on.
(Shocked)
- Really? - Are you kidding me?
You're in first grade?
I'll probably be top of the class.
(Jae Suk bragged about getting a high score.)
(But in reality, he only scored 15.)
- Seriously? - You were bluffing!
(His bluffing comes to light.)
You got most of the questions wrong.
You told me that you had a high score.
First grade?
(Embarrassed)
- You said you scored higher. - Oh, dear.
First grade?
- He... - Consider yourself dead.
Our grades have mostly been revealed.
(1st grade, 4th grade, 2nd grade)
- And Eun Bin's in 4th grade. - Mine's been revealed too.
(4th grade Eun Bin is in 1st place with 57.5 points.)
Gosh, that's awesome.
This time, Kwang Soo will decide the groups.
(The lottery picked...)
- Okay! - Kwang Soo...
(Kwang Soo to be in charge of forming promotion groups.)
He only thinks of himself, you know.
(It's the last opportunity for a promotion.)
(How will Kwang Soo sort out the groups?)
What matters the most is my promotion.
How the others do is none of my business.
In order to figure out their grades though...
(He places himself...)
(with 1st grade Jae Suk and 2nd grade Haha.)
- Kwang Soo? - Yes, I'm done.
(Kwang Soo's placement result)
Just like last time, the ones at the top...
(Kwang Soo, Ji Hyun, Sung Cheol, and Eun Bin get promoted.)
will receive the Promotion Badge.
(Ji Hyun, 3rd grade, Suk Jin and Eun Bin, 4th grade)
- Hold on. - What happened?
(Kwang Soo, Jae Suk, and Haha)
No way.
Kwang Soo got promoted?
(Kwang Soo gets promoted?)
- Out of those three... - Kwang Soo?
He's in third grade then.
(Kwang Soo must be in 3rd grade.)
- He's in 3rd grade then. - Yes, 3rd grade.
- Kwang Soo's in third grade then. - You're right.
(He gets caught.)
- He's in third grade then. - We figured it out.
(Who else other than Kwang Soo got a promotion?)
We figured out his grade.
Kwang Soo's in third grade.
(1st grade, 2nd grade, 3rd grade)
(Promoted)
(4th grade, 4th grade, 3rd grade)
Then So Min's in 4th grade.
(Promoted)
- I'm sure of it. - Kwang Soo's in third grade.
(2nd grade, Unknown, Unknown)
Kwang Soo's in third grade.
(Promoted)
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyun, Eun Bin, Sung Cheol,
(Unknown, 4th grade, Unknown)
(Promoted)
- you all get a badge. - Got it.
Can we eat now?
(Everyone's grade is slowly being revealed.)
We'll get together after we eat.
(Who will be the winner of this final race?)
Thank you for the meal.
I can't believe my grade was revealed.
- It's now time for the final race. - Right.
(The final race)
This is The Sole Winner,
(Brahms Music School, The final race)
the chance to be the sole winner at Brahms Music School.
(The Sole Winner)
What?
The Name Tag Elimination will take place for 30 minutes.
(After a 30-minute name tag elimination race,)
Out of those who survive,
(the person with the highest grade will win.)
the one with the highest grade will win.
Out of those who survive,
(The person with the highest grade will win.)
the one with the highest grade will win.
You're eliminated for good...
when your name tag gets ripped off as a first grader.
- If I lose it as a 3rd grader... - You'll become a 2nd grader.
(They move down if their name tags get ripped off...)
- That means Jae Suk... - Then we have an extra life.
(when they're in 2nd grade or higher.)
- I mean... - Then if Jae Suk...
- loses his name tag... - How can first graders survive?
Jae Suk is mine.
You can only take off the name tag of a person...
(You can only take off the name tag of a person...)
in the same grade as you or in a lower grade.
(in the same grade as you or in a lower grade.)
The person who took off a name tag gets to be promoted,
(The person who takes off a name tag gets promoted one grade,)
and the person who lost a name tag gets demoted to a lower grade.
(and the person who loses a name tag gets demoted one grade.)
But if you remove the name tag of someone in a higher grade than you,
(If you remove the name tag of someone in a higher grade than you,)
you get demoted to a lower grade.
(you get demoted to a lower grade.)
Oh, we get demoted?
However, you can form an alliance with others.
(They can form an alliance.)
If you hold hands together, your grades will be tallied.
(If you hold hands together, your grades will be tallied.)
You can eliminate others in the same or lower grades.
(You can eliminate others in the same or lower grades.)
What's important is that only the person who removed a name tag...
can move up to a higher grade.
(If you remove someone's name tag with your ally,)
Likewise, if you ally with someone else and remove the name tag...
(only you will move up or down.)
of a person in a higher grade, only you will be demoted.
Even if you formed an alliance.
Then some of us will probably attack others as a group,
(Betrayal is expected.)
and then attack their allies too.
- That's possible. - Can I...
drag my partner around?
Can I drag him around in a lying position?
Yes, you can.
(Scared)
- There won't be a problem, right? - If I drag him around...
What does the Promotion Badge do?
You will move up to higher grade according to the number...
(They'll move up a grade according to the number of badges they have.)
of the badges you have before we begin the race.
- I see. - Ji Hyun has two.
(Ji Hyun moves up from 3rd to 5th grade as she has 2 badges.)
Also, there are Up and Down Rooms here and there, which open randomly.
(Also, there are Up and Down Rooms which open randomly.)
Only the first one to find it can use it.
(Only the first person can use it.)
- Oh, I see. - They will open randomly.
Right. Those are our last hope.
Do you think we can enter any of the Up and Down Rooms?
- You think we have enough time? - I know.
(Blocking false hope in advance)
- No one will pair up with Jae Suk. - This is frustrating.
- He must be lonely. - You'll be alone.
(It will be a tough race for the 1st grader Jae Suk.)
- It'll be a lonely fight. - This is driving me insane.
Please move to your starting place.
(They'll move to their places for the race.)
Jae Suk is mine, everyone.
(The result of the music test...)
(they took this morning will be revealed.)
The result came out. We'll reveal the result to you.
Don't share it with others.
(Suk Jin in 4th grade, Eun Bin in 5th grade, So Min in 5th grade)
(Kwang Soo in 4th grade, Ji Hyun in 5th grade, Sung Cheol in 5th grade)
We graded you fairly.
We won't receive any inquiries about the test result.
(2nd grade)
That's great.
(Jae Suk in 1st grade, Min Jae in 1st grade, Ji Hyo in 2nd grade)
- My gosh. Today is my lucky day. - Oh, gosh.
- I can't believe this. - Nice.
(1st: Jae Suk, Min Jae, 2nd: Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Haha, Se Chan)
(4th: Kwang Soo, Suk Jin, 5th: Ji Hyun, Sung Cheol, Eun Bin, So Min)
You're in second grade now, right?
I'm in third grade, you brat.
(Angry)
- You moved up? - Of course.
(They're lying to each other from the beginning.)
(Kwang Soo in 4th grade, Ji Hyo in 2nd grade)
Did you say you're in 4th grade? You're in 3rd grade now.
(Clapping)
- I'm in 5th grade. - Oh, I see.
(Flustered)
- I'm not asking for a high-five. - You're in 3rd grade now.
- I'm in 5th grade. - Oh, I see.
(She gave him a high five as he revealed his grade.)
I'm not asking for a high-five.
What can we do when we can't even communicate with each other?
(Frustrated)
Why did you hit my hand?
Hey, then were you a fourth grader?
(Embarrassed)
Yes, I was. How many times should I tell you?
(Brazen)
That can't be right as far as I know.
(She high-fived for no reason.)
You'll see.
(Park Eun Bin, 5th grade)
I wrote down what I found out.
(Meanwhile, Eun Bin figured out everyone's grade.)
I'm in 5th grade. So Min is in 5th grade.
I can stay in the race until I lose my name tag five times.
(Securing airtime)
(Jeon So Min, 5th grade)
Sung Cheol is in 5th grade. Ji Hyun is in 5th grade.
I'm going to attack...
(Kim Sung Cheol, 5th grade)
whomever I run into.
(Park Ji Hyun, 5th grade)
I'm a fifth grader.
(She looks relaxed.)
Suk Jin is in fourth grade.
Kwang Soo is in fourth grade.
(Ji Suk Jin, 4th grade)
I'm planning to let Jae Suk tag along with me as my assistant.
Petty Gang is back. He'll be my right-hand man.
- You'll ally with him? - Yes, I'll ally with him.
(Lee Kwang Soo, 4th grade)
From the moment she gave me a high-five,
I only thought of sending her to jail so she can rest.
You're unusually confident today.
It's because...
As I told you earlier, I studied music as a little boy.
I learned to play the piano and other types of...
musical instrument including the violin.
Jong Kook is in second grade.
(Kim Jong Kook, 2nd grade)
Rather than forming an alliance,
I should eliminate them...
and use their power to...
Se Chan is in second grade.
(Yang Se Chan, 2nd grade)
And don't ally with So Min.
- She'll definitely betray you. - I understand.
So Min and Kwang Soo are dangerous.
(People to watch for)
Ji Hyo is in second grade.
(Song Ji Hyo, 2nd grade)
You know that the Up and Down Rooms will open later, right?
I know the rules. Up and Down Rooms?
I missed that part.
You can worry about it when you enter it.
(Spacing out)
Haha is in second grade.
It will be pointless to ally with lower graders.
(Confessing)
That's what only Petty Gang would do.
The only way I can survive is...
(Yoo Jae Suk, 1st grade)
to ally with a person in a higher grade.
(Kim Min Jae, 1st grade)
Because I'm in first grade, I have no confidence.
But I will show you how I go up from the last to the first place.
(They get ready for the race with a motive.)
Now, the race will begin.
I really hope I can make that happen.
"The race starts."
The race starts.
Oh, gosh.
(Jae Suk started looking for someone to ally with.)
(He found Eun Bin in 5th grade.)
- Eun Bin. - Shall I come to you?
- Eun Bin. - You're in first grade, right?
(He approaches Eun Bin for an alliance.)
- Eun Bin, I think... - Oh, no.
(At that moment, Kwang Soo shows up!)
If those small fish join forces, things will get complicated.
Before they form an alliance...
(Kwang Soo said he would hunt for small fish.)
Eun Bin, I...
(He started running when he saw Jae Suk.)
(The small fish hunting has begun!)
(Jae Suk will be out if he loses his name tag.)
Hey. Wait.
(Then)
Wait. Hold on.
- Follow me. - Hey. Wait.
(Jae Suk allies with Se Chan and So Min.)
- Hey. - What's going on?
(The table is turned.)
Se Chan.
- Kwang Soo, take off his name tag. - Kwang Soo, hold him.
(Kwang Soo makes a strategic retreat.)
So Min, let's go and help Jae Suk.
Hurry up.
(They start chasing Kwang Soo right away.)
Go back. Too many are coming down here.
(What?)
- Too many are coming down. - Let's go.
(Urgent)
- Come join us. - Let's form an alliance.
(3 high graders formed an alliance.)
- The three of us? - We'll be invincible.
- Really? - We'll be...
- in 15th grade. - Now, we're in 15th grade.
- Let's say it. We're in 15th grade. - We're in 15th grade.
- Okay. - Let's go downstairs.
(The 15th graders got into action right away!)
Let's get them all.
Go back.
Take off his name tag. Come on.
(Flashpoint)
- I'm holding your hand. - Take that off.
(Calculating each other's fighting strength.)
- Wait. Let me think. - Take it off.
They're in 4th, 5th, 1st, and 2nd grade. Take it off.
Someone is coming.
(Haha heard the commotion and came.)
- He's in first grade. Take it off. - Let's join forces.
(Trying to form an ally)
- Eun Bin, hold my hand. - Hurry up.
- Hold my hand. - Hurry up.
- We're in a higher grade. - Hold my hand.
(We shouldn't ally with them.)
- Take off his name tag. - Haha.
(Grabbing)
- What are you doing? - What?
(The unexpected peace treaty)
- Why did you hold Kwang Soo's hand? - I'm stuck.
(Flustered)
I didn't mean to...
I'm stuck here.
(Haha got stuck.)
- But... - Eun Bin... Wait. No, wait.
(They suddenly change the target.)
- Why are you... - Jae Suk.
(He tries to escape,)
No, don't let go.
- Jae Suk. - Let go.
(but Kwang Soo catches him.)
- Hold on. - Jae Suk.
Hey, Jae Suk is...
(Taking off the name tag)
Gosh.
(His name tag is removed!)
- Gosh. - I removed his name tag.
(He ends up giving away his name tag.)
- I removed 1 of his name tags. - Kwang Soo took 1.
(As the 4th grader Kwang Soo eliminated the 2nd grader Haha,)
Kwang Soo gets promoted, and Haha gets demoted.
(Kwang Soo moves up. Haha moves down.)
- Wait. - Can we remove their name tags now?
(Then)
- Yes, you can. - Stop. Don't do that.
(Meanwhile, Min Jae hides himself during a commotion.)
- Don't take it off. - I should avoid them.
I need to find the Up and Down Rooms first.
(The Up and Down Room is 1st grader's only hope.)
But there are too many people up there.
Seriously...
The Up and Down Rooms are open now.
(The Up and Down Rooms where they can get promoted are open now.)
There are Up and Down Rooms where you can get promoted.
Where are the Up and Down Rooms?
(It opens randomly, and only the first person to enter can use it.)
We have to find the Up and Down Rooms.
(Low graders look for the Up and Down Rooms.)
Is there an Up and Down Room there?
This is crazy. I really need to find an Up and Down Room.
(He must find it before the others do.)
Oh, gosh. What is it?
I found an Up and Down Room.
(He finds an Up and Down Room!)
(The 1st grader Kim Min Jae enters the booth.)
Where is it? Okay.
(He's checking the mission that he has to complete in the booth.)
Next. There.
(Staff put the mission on the phone.)
First, choose one person you want to promote or demote.
Next, write down your name and someone else's on three balls,
(Write down your name and someone else's on three balls.)
and put the balls in the Up Box or the Down Box.
(Put the balls in the Up or Down Box.)
You will pick one ball by yourself,
(The person picked will be promoted or demoted.)
which will decide the person to be promoted or demoted.
For example, if you want to get promoted,
(If you want to be promoted,)
(write your name and someone's name and put the balls in the Up Box.)
Write down someone else's name on 1 of the 3 balls,
(If you pick your name, you'll be promoted.)
and write down your name on the rest 2 balls.
Next, put the balls in the Up Box.
If you pick a ball with your name on it, you'll get promoted.
(Promoted to 2nd grade)
I can write down my name on two balls, right?
(You can't write your name in all three balls.)
I'll write down Eun Bin's name on one ball.
I'll write my name on another ball.
(He'll write his name in 2 balls and put them in the Up Box...)
So there's a better chance that I'll pick my name.
(to be promoted.)
Now, I'm putting the balls in the Up Box.
(He puts the balls in the Up Box.)
(Min Jae is mixing the balls unlike the cast of Running Man.)
Please let me get promoted.
Okay.
(2 balls with his name on them and 1 with Eun Bin's name on it)
Please let me get promoted. Please let me pick the right ball.
(Which one of them will be promoted?)
Okay.
(He picked 1 ball.)
How could I pick this one?
How could this happen?
(Eun Bin?)
(I'm ruined.)
Does that mean this person will be promoted?
Gosh, seriously.
(Eun Bin is promoted thanks to him.)
Let's go together. We're invincible.
(The four are forming an alliance.)
Let's go inside.
(They carefully move inside.)
Okay. Let's go.
This is crazy.
How dare you?
- This is crazy. - How dare you?
(Glancing)
Why? I wasn't doing anything.
(There's a sign of betrayal.)
- I won't take off your name tag. - She's holding...
- I won't take it off. - Hey.
(1st grader Haha is sensitive.)
- I'm just checking. - Let go of my hand.
- Haha. - We're holding hands together.
(They keep watching each other.)
Haha, let go of my hand just for a moment. I'm hot.
- It's too hot. That's all. - Let's abandon him.
(Abandon him.)
(Se Chan gets caught.)
So Min, you're a fifth grader now, right?
10th grade... And you're in 1st grade, right?
(They exchange another look.)
(He understands the message.)
- No. - What do you mean?
- No. Don't betray me. - Haha.
- No. - Why?
(There's no forever enemy or forever ally.)
- Don't do that. - What? I wasn't doing anything.
- Don't let go of my hand. - Haha, let go.
- Let go of Eun Bin. - No!
(Immature members aim the youngest member.)
- So Min. - You're so mean.
I came on a variety show after a long time.
(Appealing to emotions)
- I know. - You'll be on another show.
One show wouldn't be a problem.
(It doesn't affect him at all.)
- No. - One show wouldn't be a problem.
Hold on. I...
(It's almost wrapping up.)
- Let me catch my breath. - Okay.
- Before I stand up... - Wait. How could you...
(Pulling)
(They change the target!)
Eun Bin, get up.
- Come on. Get up. - I... I got him.
Hey, don't...
(Ripping off)
(He lost his name tag in a blink.)
- Eun Bin, get up. - Hey!
(Wasn't Haha a 1st grader?)
Can I just get up?
- I am out. - Let's summarize.
- I am out. - Don't lie.
- I was a first grader. - Don't lie.
I was a first grader.
(It's too early.)
Haha is out.
- My goodness. - Haha is out.
(Is he really out?)
(Haha's name tag got removed in 1st grade, so he is out.)
- My goodness. - Haha is out.
- Se Chan, - Did I move up a grade?
(Se Chan is promoted to 3rd grade for ripping off Haha's name tag.)
you moved up a grade.
- Let's go, Eun Bin. - What?
(He's finished here.)
That little...
(Haha was discarded in cold blood.)
Gosh, I am so annoyed.
(He lingers around.)
How did this happen?
Give me that.
(Even an eliminated student gets a mission.)
It's an important mission.
(An important mission?)
Let's go.
(The members are busy playing the race.)
Hold on!
- Who is that? - Who is that?
(Haha reappears with an important mission!)
- Hold on. - What's going on?
(He got eliminated earlier.)
Haha.
- Were you given a role? - Was it the Up and Down Room?
(What's going on?)
- Was it the Up and Down Room? - You are very curious, right?
(Haha revived after getting eliminated.)
- Yes. - What's your role?
- Take a look at this. - What is it?
(Which important mission did he take on?)
(The status board of the current members?)
"The number of members per grade"?
(He revived as a human bulletin board.)
I see.
- The sixth grade. - You managed to survive.
(He's carrying out his mission.)
Who are the first graders?
One of them must be Jae Suk.
(Everyone guesses each other's grade.)
Who is the other one?
- Min Jae. Where is Min Jae? - Min Jae.
(The other 1st grader)
You are right. Where is Min Jae?
- I haven't seen him around. - He must be hiding.
(Min Jae's whereabouts is unknown.)
- What is he doing? - Shall we go and take him out?
(They decide to look for Min Jae.)
Shall we go and find Min Jae?
- Let's go and find Min Jae. - Okay.
Someone's name tag got ripped off.
(He is having a lonely fight.)
Is Haha out?
- Are you a fourth grader? - Yes.
(On the other hand, the three formed an alliance.)
Then our combined grade is 10.
- 10. - I am in the middle.
If one of you...
You know the Electricity Game, right?
- If one of you... - I will stand in the middle...
- so that it doesn't happen. - Hold on.
(Electricity Game?)
If one of you squeezes my hand to send me a sign,
(It's a sign of betrayal.)
I can attack right away.
There is no reason for us to turn against each other.
(No sincerity)
Let's not do that.
(So Min feels the squeeze as soon as they finish talking.)
(She'll get an electric shock.)
Kwang Soo.
Give me your hand.
(A storm is coming.)
- Come on. Don't be like that. - So Min.
(It's torturous.)
What's the use of ripping each other's name tag?
(He doesn't mean it.)
What's the use of moving up a grade?
Hold on.
(They talk of trusting each other but uncomfortable silence ensues.)
This is driving me crazy.
Come here.
Let's go someplace quiet.
(They move to someplace quiet to take someone out.)
(Sighing)
This is like...
the Mafia Game.
(They barely hold on to their rationality.)
- We are close... - I am feeling the squeeze.
- to having a ruckus break out. - Seriously.
In order to survive,
- you can either stay still... - Yes.
(Thinking about a way to survive)
or rip off someone's name tag.
All right.
(They play the Electricity Game again.)
Did everyone send a signal?
This is my signal.
All right.
(Squeezing)
By the way,
both of you are giving me a squeeze.
Hey.
Both of you are giving me a squeeze.
(The signals of betrayal are all over the place.)
Hey. I thought you gave me a signal.
Stop sending him a signal.
All right.
(They try the Electricity Game again.)
1, 2,
three. Let go.
(They twist Se Chan's arms so that he wouldn't run away.)
(At that moment)
- No. - They are coming!
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyun, and Min Jae appear!)
Hold on. Hold on.
(8th grade versus 10th grade)
We can't win against them.
- Hold on. - We can't win against them.
(Kwang Soo's alliance is stronger, but they don't realize that.)
I got him.
Kwang Soo, cut ties with them.
Cut ties with them.
- Do it. - No, no.
- No. - Cut ties with them.
(Kwang Soo's swayed by the sweet temptation.)
We won't survive without you.
(Should I cut ties or not?)
You were struggling before.
Hold on. Why are you doing this to me?
(Jong Kook goes after Se Chan.)
Rip off Se Chan's name tag.
(Ripping off)
Okay.
(He removed Se Chan's name tag!)
Rip off Se Chan's name tag.
(The moment his name tag got ripped off,)
(Kwang Soo let go of Se Chan's hand!)
Okay!
- Let's summarize. - Let's summarize.
(Because Kwang Soo let go of his hand, Se Chan's degraded.)
- Their grades are too high. - My grade isn't that high.
(They're both in 3rd grade.)
Jong Kook's grade is too high.
(Jong Kook in 4th grade, Se Chan in 2nd grade)
- Their grades are too high. - No, my grade isn't that high.
Please put this back on.
(This is ridiculous.)
Why do you guys betray each other?
(Pitiful)
- Don't hang out with Kwang Soo. - No, no.
- I didn't start this. - Se Chan, don't...
(Sad)
- Really? - They are just like me.
(They're the same.)
- The three of you should scatter. - Let's scatter.
We are in a pretty good place.
(Feeling confident)
Our combined grade is 10.
That this rate, Jong Kook will win again.
- We shouldn't fight. - Let's not do that.
(She's repeating what she said before.)
- Let's not do that. - We lost because we fought.
I won't do it. Let's not betray each other.
(They promise not to betray.)
Okay. Keep your promise.
- Okay. - 20 minutes remain.
There is a time limit too.
(Se Chan sends So Min a signal.)
I didn't do anything!
(Do you have a problem?)
You little...
(A civil war breaks out.)
Stop it.
So Min. So Min.
I am sorry.
(A betray after a betrayal)
- So Min. - I am holding his hand.
- I am holding his hand. - You two, make up.
(The trio can't trust each other.)
Let's hold hands again.
My arms are about to fall off!
Let's just...
I am sorry, but please get us a small room.
We will put an end to this.
It won't end.
(Sick and tired)
All right. We're done.
I need to survive no matter what.
(Jae Suk in 1st grade looks for a chance in concealment.)
I will show you.
If I enter the Up and Down Room and become a second grader,
(He plans to move up to 2nd grade through Up and Down Room.)
anything could happen.
(I will move up a grade no matter what!)
- All right. - You know,
(Meanwhile, the 4 are forming an alliance.)
a 6th grader doesn't need to stay a 6th grader.
We could rip off a sixth grader's name tag.
(If many people are in highest grade,)
- That's right. - We could do that.
(the next grade with one person wins.)
(It might be more beneficial...)
Do you want to see the status board?
(to become the only person in the grade.)
- Yes! - Yes, we do.
- Do you want to see it? - Yes!
(Haha appears with the status board.)
Let's see it.
(The current grade)
The fifth grade is...
The fifth grader will win at this rate.
(Only 1 person is in 5th grade.)
Hold on. Hold on.
(If the race ends now, the 5th grader wins.)
To be honest... Hold on. Please listen to me.
(The 6 people appear from the other side.)
Shall we take them on?
(Provoking)
- Let's do that. - Right now?
(6 is superior in number. Is the total sum of grade high as well?)
- Hold on. - So Min.
- It's not a good idea. - So Min.
- Is our combined grade higher? - Yes, it is.
Then Kwang Soo should attack.
(The sum of 6 people is 19.)
- Okay. Let's do it. - Kwang Soo.
(Whereas the sum of 4 people is 17.)
Hold on. Stay still.
(Even if 6 people's name tags get ripped off, it doesn't affect them.)
It's okay even if your name tag gets ripped off.
- Our combined grade is higher. - It's okay even if it happens.
(Certain)
- You are right. - It's okay even if it happens.
It's okay even if your name tag gets ripped off.
(Certain that their combined grade is higher, the 6 members attack.)
Let's go.
So Min, why did you hold her hand?
(At that moment,)
- What? - What?
(So Min suddenly betrays her group.)
- We can still win. - No, no.
- Can we attack? - We aren't sure.
(16th graders versus 20th graders)
- Hold on. - Should we go ahead and attack?
(Sung Cheol goes ahead and attacks.)
- No, no. - Should we go ahead and attack?
(The table turns as So Min betrays.)
- Should we try it? - Hold hands.
- Should we try it? - No, no.
(He can't finish the attack because he is unsure.)
- Sung Cheol, please. - Go.
- Should we try it? - Their combined grade is lower.
- I think we can win. - No, no.
- We need to attack now. - Really?
(The cause of this situation)
- You... - Okay.
- Hold on. - Okay.
(Suk Jin changes his spot to block So Min from betraying.)
- Where are you going? - I am staying here.
Let go of my hand, you fool.
(His voice shakes terribly.)
- What is up with you? - Why are you so excited?
Suk Jin must be in first grade.
- Me? Think that I am in 1st grade. - He isn't in 1st grade.
(Suk Jin's in 1st grade.)
Should I rip off Suk Jin's name tag?
(The confrontation continues.)
Sung Cheol and Eun Bin's grade is too high.
(They know Sung Cheol and Eun Bin are in 6th grade.)
Their combined grade alone is 12.
- Is it 12? - Hold on.
- Shall we scatter? - Shall we do that?
(Suggesting a breakup)
- Let's do the calculations first. - Let's scatter.
(They decide to scatter for now.)
- There are too many people. - Go.
- Go. - Isn't our combined grade higher?
(After seeing them leave,)
- I don't think so. - No.
Sung Cheol and Eun Bin's grade is too high.
(they guess the grade.)
- I am sorry. - They are coming!
(At that moment)
They are coming!
(Sung Cheol makes sneak attacks.)
Hold on.
It's okay.
(While everyone pays attention to Kwang Soo,)
They held hands. They held hands again.
This won't do.
(Suk Jin attacks Se Chan.)
- Okay. - He did it.
I did it.
(He succeeded to rip off the name tag.)
- I did it. - Wait.
(Our grade is probably higher.)
- The result... - My name tag got ripped off.
Kwang Soo didn't let go.
(Kwang Soo didn't let go of the hand.)
He didn't let go.
Suk Jin, you moved up a grade.
(Suk Jin becomes a 4th grader.)
Really?
- Suk Jin, you moved up a grade. - Really?
(Se Chan becomes a 1st grader.)
- Is his grade higher? - Okay. I will put it back on.
We can attack them as a group again, right?
- In that case... - I am going to leave.
(Kwang Soo's alliance realizes that their grade is lower.)
Can we rip their name tag off?
- Here... - Let's resume right away.
(1st grader Se Chan runs away before getting his name tag ripped again.)
Se Chan left. Se Chan left.
- Se Chan left. Se Chan left. - Let's rip off Min Jae's name tag.
(This is bad.)
Let's rip off Min Jae's name tag.
(Sung Cheol attacks Min Jae.)
- Hold on! - Let's rip off Min Jae's name tag.
- I don't want to get eliminated. - Don't do it.
(Ji Hyun tries to help him,)
Hold on. Hold on. Let's talk.
(but Suk Jin blocks her.)
- Hold on. - Hold on. Hold on. Let's talk.
(They try to negotiate through words.)
Listen to what I have to say.
- I... - What is it?
(They've let go of hands already.)
What is it?
(His name tag gets ripped off!)
Okay, okay.
(HIs name tag got ripped off before Kwang Soo held his hand.)
- That's good. - His name tag got ripped off.
- Is he out? - Sung Cheol ripped it, right?
(Min Jae)
- I was a 1st grader. - Were you a 1st grader?
(Whining)
- Really? - Does that mean you are out?
- I was a first grader. - I told you not to do it.
(Min Jae is out.)
- I told you to listen to me. - I didn't know.
Why did you have to rip off my name tag?
(He becomes the status board carrier.)
For goodness' sake.
Now...
(Currently, the 5th grader is winning.)
- We will leave. - Go ahead.
- What's your grade? - 5... 4th grade.
(Ji Hyun)
- Are you in fourth grade? - Yes.
- You are in third grade, right? - Yes, I am.
If I rip off your name tag,
I will be a fifth grader.
(Kwang Soo attacks her.)
You can't rip off my name tag.
(If Ji Hyun is in 4th grade and Kwang Soo is in 3rd grade,)
(Kwang Soo will move down a grade upon ripping off her name tag.)
Is it okay for you to do that?
(Kwang Soo ripped off her name tag in the end.)
Aren't you in third grade?
(Why did he rip off her name tag if he is in 3rd grade?)
I guess he isn't in third grade.
Kwang Soo.
(Isn't Kwang Soo in 3rd grade?)
You moved up a grade.
(Kwang Soo who lied moves up a grade.)
I am sorry, Ji Hyun.
Let's go.
(Ji Hyun moves down a grade.)
I am sorry, Ji Hyun.
(He means it.)
Where is the Up and Down Room?
(So Min became a 2nd grader by Suk Jin.)
I don't think this will end anytime soon.
(So Min spots Haha with the status board.)
It will take some time.
(She uses her cell phone to zoom in on the status board.)
It's Haha.
It will take some time.
Two sixth graders, two fourth graders,
(She can see it.)
and two first graders.
(Upon checking the status board,)
- It's So Min. - Jong Kook.
(So Min approaches Jong Kook to team up with him.)
Jong Kook.
(Please team up with me.)
Hey, forget it.
You are a betrayer. Come here.
(Refusing)
Hold on!
- Hold on. - Done.
(He removed her name tag without hesitation.)
(Jong Kook becomes a 6th grader and So Min becomes a 1st grader.)
You are so mean.
(She traded her grade for the bitter taste of betrayal.)
- Okay, okay. - You are so mean.
So Min, come here.
(He is an expert in teaching people a lesson.)
What am I going to do?
(So Min became a 1st grader.)
I need to run away.
This became a game of wits.
(Unless Jong Kook's the only 6th grader, he can't win.)
What's your grade? I will give you a consultation.
(Volunteers to be the counselor)
- You are in 5th grade, right? - 6th grade.
- 6th grade? - Yes.
(Haha becomes a counselor from a status carrier.)
You moved up too much.
Right? Right?
(Serious)
In order to make you win...
- Third graders have no chance. - No? Why not?
(Counselor Double Ha's lecture on how to win)
(Listening)
It's most likely that a fourth grader will win.
You should rip off these two members' name tag.
(It's an on-point lesson.)
It's crystal clear.
(The customer's satisfied.)
The status changed. Let's think of a way.
(Kwang Soo got his name tag ripped off and became a 4th grader.)
Sixth grade?
- That changed fast. - No one is in fifth grade.
(Then)
This is it. This is the way.
(Become a 5th grader.)
You should get betrayed.
So I should get my name tag ripped off.
(He tells Jong Kook to become a 5th grader.)
Get your name tag ripped off and hide.
That's right!
(This customer is touched.)
- Good luck. - Okay.
(Counselor Double Ha)
Why are you alone?
(Sung Cheol and Ji Hyun show up.)
What's your grade?
(Get your name tag ripped, sir.)
Are you in sixth grade?
(Pretending to be on alert)
- Which grade are you in? - Second grade.
- Take him out. - It doesn't seem that way.
(Decoy)
You can't avoid it. Fight him!
(Jong Kook will move to 5th grade if his tag is removed.)
Fight him! Get a good shot!
(Let's make him a 5th grader!)
Get a good shot!
(Jong Kook is planning to be the final winner.)
Fight him! Fight him!
(He acts as if he's using strength.)
Ji Hyun, watch your hair.
(Jong Kook let Ji Hyun rip off his name tag.)
Jong Kook, you moved down a grade.
(He moves down to the 5th grade as he has planned.)
- This is driving me crazy. - Ji Hyun, you moved up a grade.
(The counselor is extremely satisfied.)
Let's scatter.
(The timid 1st grader, Jae Suk is hiding.)
(He runs away upon hearing someone's footsteps.)
Jae Suk!
(Kwang Soo rushes to Jae Suk after finding him.)
I won't rip off your name tag. I don't need to do that.
- Really? - Yes.
(Jae Suk allies with Kwang Soo.)
I don't need to do that.
There is only one fifth grader, and it's Jong Kook.
(Kwang Soo updates him on the current status.)
- Which grade are you in? - 4th grade. No, 3rd grade.
(Are you really in 3rd grade?)
There are so many fourth graders.
I saw you walk around while holding someone's hand.
I had teamed up with Ji Hyun. I ripped off her name tag once.
You shouldn't do that when you have a girlfriend.
What are you saying?
My girlfriend has nothing to do with this.
(Flustered)
I don't understand what you are saying.
(He can't speak properly as he got too flustered.)
Hold on.
You shouldn't do that.
(Am I wrong?)
What are you saying?
- You were alone with Ji Hyun. - Someone is coming.
(He has a clear line between professional and private life.)
Hey.
(They move downstairs upon hearing someone approach.)
Kwang Soo.
The situation keeps changing.
- It's Se Chan. - Jae Suk.
- Which grade are you in? - First grade.
(He investigates Se Chan's grade.)
How about you?
I am in third grade.
Things became complicated. It's a ruckus upstairs.
(I'm also in 1st grade.)
Se Chan, you moved up a grade due to the Up and Down Room.
(Se Chan gets promoted to 2nd grade.)
Me?
- You are in second grade. - Hold on.
(It's amazing!)
- Hold on. - Then Jae Suk is the only one.
(So Min picked Se Chan's ball from Up and Down Room,)
(which helped Se Chan to move up a grade.)
The status board is here.
(Perfect timing)
- Min Jae. - Min Jae, come here.
(Min Jae appears with a status board on his back.)
Min Jae, come here.
So many things changed.
(What's the current status?)
There are two people in every grade.
This is giving me a headache.
(The number of members in each grade)
(6th grade: 3, 5th grade: 1, 4th grade: 2, 3rd grade 0,)
(2nd grade: 2, 1st grade: 2)
This is giving me a headache.
You said you are in third grade, but you aren't.
Why is no one in third grade?
(He gets caught lying.)
- What happened? - What is the meaning of this?
- Are you a ghost? - What are you?
(Is Kwang Soo...)
- What are you? - What are you?
- Let's hold hands and talk. - What are you?
(Abruptly acting timid)
- What are you? - Are you a ghost?
(Thinking)
No one is in third grade.
What happened?
(Be honest.)
I don't know.
(He lost his mind.)
(He can't think of any excuses.)
- I mean... - I forgot about my grade.
- Which grade are you in? - My name tag got ripped off a lot.
(Kwang Soo's lie made everything more complicated.)
This is...
I am in second grade.
(I'm not in 3rd grade.)
- You are in second grade? - Yes.
Hold on. Hold my hand. Listen.
(If Kwang Soo in 2nd grade...)
(allies with Se Chan, who's also in 2nd grade...)
Things will be interesting if we team up.
(Together, we'll be in 4th grade.)
If we rip off Jae Suk's name tag...
- What are you saying? - I mean...
(A very sensitive 1st grader)
- It was just a discussion. - Don't be like that.
(It's so fun to tease.)
There is no reason for the three of us to argue.
- Let's move. - I will keep updating the board.
Hold on. It looks like...
(He suddenly stops as he tried to walk away.)
I am in the highest grade. Let go.
- What? - Let go.
Are you in the highest grade?
Which grade are you in?
- He is in 2nd grade. - I am in 2nd grade.
- He is in second grade too. - If we team up,
(Se Chan and Jae Suk)
our combined grade is higher.
I was joking around.
(Calm down.)
Don't joke around like that.
- Let's hold hands for a while. - Seriously.
Okay.
This is driving me crazy.
(They move with their hands held tight.)
I can't act rashly.
(Glancing over)
Hey.
(Jae Suk tries to attack.)
(Annoyed by the betrayal, Kwang Soo strikes back.)
Hold on. Hold on.
(They grab each other's name tag at the same time.)
(Se Chan is holding Jae Suk's hand.)
Hold on.
(Jae Suk rips off Kwang Soo's name tag first!)
(Kwang Soo said he is in 2nd grade.)
All right.
(Then Jae Suk and Se Chan's combined grade is higher.)
- Which grade are you in? - First grade.
I am in second grade.
- Jae Suk, you are out. - Why?
(Is Jae Suk out?)
- Jae Suk, you are out. - We were holding hands.
(If Jae Suk is eliminated even when holding hands with Se Chan...)
- That's right. - So?
Which grade are you in?
(That means Kwang Soo wasn't in 2nd grade.)
I didn't lie.
Kwang Soo, which grade are you in?
Don't ask, you punk.
He must be in sixth grade.
Are you in fifth grade?
(We were fooled again.)
I can't believe him.
(What grade is Kwang Soo in?)
Okay. Let's stay together for now.
(It's nearly the end of the race.)
I really am in fifth grade!
Come on.
Three...
What?
(The fierce battle to be the sole winner erupts everywhere.)
- We are doing you a favor. - Why?
- We are doing you a favor. - What?
(There's no point being in a higher grade.)
Either a 4th grader or a 5th grader will win.
(Some waits quietly for the chance after being the sole grader.)
- Promise to share the prize. - Okay.
(Some sacrifice to let another to be the sole grader.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Make sure you win. - Let me change the status.
- Come on. - You are so mean.
(A fierce battle over promotion and demotion.)
Sung Cheol, you are so mean.
(Will you rip someone? Or get ripped?)
- No! Don't do it! - Come on.
- No! - Hold her hand.
(The status changes rapidly towards the end of the race.)
All right.
The race ends.
(Who will be the last one standing?)
Please gather around.
As I explained earlier,
the only member of the highest grade will win.
(If there are many multiple top graders,)
(the next grade with one person will be the winner.)
Sung Cheol is in sixth grade.
(He will win if there are no other 6th graders.)
Eun Bin is in sixth grade.
My goodness.
(If there's only 1 5th grader, the 5th grader will win.)
Suk Jin is...
- in fifth grade. - Okay.
- Why did you become a fifth grader? - Seriously.
(He gives up.)
Jong Kook is in fifth grade.
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is...
- in fourth grade. - I knew it.
- Yes! - Kwang Soo will win.
Ji Hyo and Ji Hyun are in third grade.
- Kwang Soo is the winner. - Yes!
I can't believe it.
(Kwang Soo's strategy for victory)
(He realizes there is no other 4th grader.)
I should get my name tag ripped off.
That's right. I should get my name tag ripped off.
(On purpose)
Who will do it?
Who are they?
(He finds a group of people who formed an alliance.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Hold on. He wants to get his name tag ripped off.
(He is begging them to remove his name tag.)
- Let go. - Let go for a second.
(They sense that he is acting suspicious,)
Let go for a second.
(but Suk Jin removes Kwang Soo's name tag.)
What? What is up with him?
Let's go.
(Kwang Soo successfully moves down to 4th grade.)
- Which grade are you in? - I am in second grade.
(Kwang Soo lied that he's in 2nd grade.)
- Are you in second grade? - Yes.
(If he rips other's name tag, he'll move up to the 5th grade.)
Hey. Hold on.
(So he made Jae Suk rip off his name tag!)
Jae Suk, you are out.
- Jae Suk, you are out. - Why?
(It was Kwang Soo's strategy to become the sole 4th grader.)
- Thank you, Suk Jin and Jae Suk. - How did he keep it that way?
(Thank you for ripping my name tag off.)
- How strange! - Like I always say,
it's a good idea to take him out in the beginning of the race.
- We shouldn't leave him behind. - We shouldn't leave him behind.
(He's been tricked for 10 years.)
Please bring in the prize for the best student...
(The prize for the best student of Brahms Music School)
- from the music school. - What is it?
Please let it be a xylophone.
A triangle.
- Please let it be a xylophone. - I haven't won a prize in a while.
(What will be today's prize?)
Please let it be a xylophone or a recorder.
A pipe.
That's incredible.
Really?
(Turntable)
- He will receive a turntable. - It's nice.
- It's a good prize. It's pretty. - It's really nice.
(It's the best gift for a music school.)
It's pretty.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's an antique.
(He loves it.)
The four members who were eliminated will get a penalty.
(The 4 eliminated people must receive penalties.)
- Bring in the penalty. - I forgot about the penalty.
(Today's penalty)
- There is a penalty. - There is a penalty.
Out of 4 sponges, 2 contain ink...
(Out of 4 sponges, 2 contains ink, while 2 contains water.)
- and two contain water. - Oh, no.
- Please. - Please.
(I really hope to pick water.)
- It's pretty visible. - You can't change your choice.
(So Min doesn't hesitate to choose the 2nd one.)
- I choose this one. - Number four.
(Haha picks the 4th one.)
So Min picked number two.
Min Jae.
(Min Jae, after pondering, picks the 1st one.)
- I pick number four. - I can't tell.
(Jae Suk automatically gets the 3rd one.)
You can't tell by looking.
2 sponges have water and 2 sponges have...
- One, - That's right. Hold it up.
(It's a 50 percent chance.)
two,
(Which two chose the ink sponges?)
- three. - Stamp your face.
Rub your face. Get your face in there.
Keep going. There you go.
(Haha gets a sponge with water.)
(Min Jae gets a sponge with water too.)
Rub your face.
Rub your face. Get your face in there.
(In that case)
Keep going. There you go.
(So Min and Jae Suk get ink on their faces.)
(How did the two of them get those sponges?)
(It's a shocking look.)
My goodness.
(They are very unlucky.)
- I can't believe it. - This is the best.
The drama will start airing tomorrow.
(Thanks to Eun Bin, Min Jae,)
Please watch "Do You Like Brahms?".
(Sung Cheol, and Ji Hyun for joining us today.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Please Watch "Do You Like Brahms?")
We did it!
(Running Man Thief Race ended with the thieves' victory.)
Jae Suk, Haha, and Ji Hyo's joint birthday party.
(Jae Suk, Haha, and Ji Hyo's joint birthday party)
- Someone is playing a role. - There is a thief, right?
(Is there a copycat criminal?)
It's a new job. I will be a hacker.
(They set out to catch a thief who is aiming to steal a jewel.)
- Judge. - I will be a head-hunter.
A detective and a profiler?
(Profiler, detective)
They are for the guests.
(And those who are watching them?)
What?
- The real ones are here. - The real detective and profiler.
(The real ones are here.)
I heard about the crime.
- He is the first profiler. - It feels so real.
(The 1st-generation profiler in Korea, Pyo Chang Won)
I have experiences.
Ma Dong Seok's character was modeled after him.
(The model of "The Outlaws", Detective Yoon Seok Ho)
If Room A is real...
(The experts will catch the 2 thieves!)
At what time did you arrive?
I have been watching,
(They will analyze and dig deep for the interrogation!)
and there is something I don't understand.
- It's so scary! - So here they are.
There are so many.
(The moment you let your guard down, the photos will capture everything.)
I help up the bag. It was the same.
This was open, and...
(A match of deductions will keep you on your toes!)
Kwang Soo's behaviors were strange.
- We need to catch the thieves. - That's bound to happen today.
(What will become of the thieves who are aiming for the jewel?)
We got them.
(Running Man Thief Race 2, The Copycat Criminals)