(It's drizzling.)
(It's a training institute
in Gyeonggi Province.)
(And there's a departure
lounge in the building.)
Hello.
(She shows up slithering her way
through the production crew.)
- Hello.
- What is So Min doing there alone?
- Hi.
- Hello.
Did you gain some weight?
- Oh, you lost weight.
- No, we never talk about that.
- Gosh, seriously. Hey.
- It's true.
- I haven't done it in a while.
- Hello, Haha.
- That's too much.
- Haha, why are you wearing pajamas?
- He must be...
- My gosh.
My wife has similar pants like them.
- He's wearing pajamas and slippers.
- They're called "fridge pants".
- I can't believe you, Haha.
- Look at this.
(Contempt)
- What's with your face?
- What do you mean?
Don't say weird things like that.
- He's trying to change the subject.
- Don't do that.
(Haha is making fun of his face
to change the subject.)
(He found something
and burst out laughing.)
- Oh, my.
- Hey, Haha.
- Did you carry our mission bag?
- Yes, I did.
I carry it on another show as well.
- Rumor has it that you stole it.
- That's not true.
- Why did you take that bag?
- In that bag,
there were only two caramels.
- Caramels?
- Why would he take that bag?
- It's for Running Man...
- Haha, that's why our staff...
call you a caramel thief.
I heard them talking in whispers
earlier.
Haven't you heard
that stealing props brings...
- three generations bad luck?
- Exactly.
People actually say that.
- It brings bad luck for 3 years.
- Oh, right. For 3 years.
- It brings 3 generations bad luck?
- For 3 years.
- You mean, Dream, his children,
- I heard that too.
- and me?
- 3 years, not 3 generations.
- You didn't make that up though.
- I see.
- They say...
- 3 generations?
- it brings bad luck for 3 years.
- I said three generations instead.
- That's too harsh.
That shows how dedicated I am
to Running Man.
- What is that?
- We see his photo every week.
- Must we talk about it?
- Let's not do this.
- Suk Jin is...
- Let's just skip it and move on.
- He uploads too many photos.
- He's practically...
- I bet he does that intentionally.
- addicted to social media.
- We saw so many photos of him.
We also tried it with
the other cast members' photos.
- Really?
- You did?
- Is that me?
- Is she Jae Suk's mother?
- I look pretty.
- Let me have a look.
- Is this me?
- You look...
- better than I thought you would.
- Right?
I look like this lawyer...
- called Choi Yoon Ah.
- Exactly.
I met her on a TV show.
You're right.
Jong Kook looks like Pak Se Ri
with makeup.
(He looks like the rich girl
who's good at golf.)
I think I look pretty.
My face looks quite sharp.
- Who's next?
- Oh, man. Kwang Soo looks...
What? Hang on.
- He looks like...
- What? Hang on.
I look okay.
(He just looks like
he's wearing a wig.)
He looks like
a retired volleyball player.
- He looks like Kim Yeon Koung.
- Right?
- Is that So Min?
- Hey, but...
your face looks so long.
To be honest,
I realized I shouldn't make fun of
any of you...
because I thought it was my mother.
- I won't say anything about you.
- Okay.
- Please don't make fun of it.
- All right.
- And Ji Hyo looks like...
- She looks like Sung Hoon.
- She doesn't look different.
- I think...
- she looks like Sehun of EXO.
- Indeed. She does look like Sehun.
Right? She looks like him.
- She's very handsome.
- She would be if she were a man.
- Next up is Se Chan.
- Look at him.
- The application failed.
- My goodness.
He beat another application.
The application failed to
change his face.
One of our writers looks like this.
I don't remember her name,
but he looks a lot like her.
- His photo is so shocking.
- Nothing can change his face.
Se Chan has his own
unchangeable image.
Actually, Se Chan needs to...
- get a test done today.
- Yes.
- He's not feeling well.
- It's nothing serious though.
- It's nothing serious.
- It's a minor illness.
He just needs to get a test done.
- We'll continue the shoot tomorrow.
- Yes.
- He'll come tomorrow.
- He'll join us tomorrow.
- That's a relief.
- We'll be starting the race soon.
You'll leave Korea shortly,
so please check the bags behind you.
- I see.
- Is this important?
- We'll leave Korea?
- Where?
- It must be this week's theme.
- It's a theme.
- What is it?
- It says, "Running..."
- It says, "Pre-season Training".
- Soccer?
- "Morning Soccer Club..."
- "Pre-season Training"?
- They don't do pre-season training.
- I like the idea.
- A morning soccer club?
- Are we going to play soccer?
You are members of
Running Morning Soccer Club.
- You'll leave for the training.
- Is that so?
We invited three outside players
to join you for the training.
- Really? We have more players?
- Outside players?
I... I'm just worried
I might be a nuisance.
(After receiving soccer balls
from the staff,)
(three mysterious players
entered with the soccer balls.)
(Surprised)
Oh, my.
- You should've told us...
- Dae Myeung is here.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
I was so surprised.
(Kwak Do Won, Kim Sang Ho,
Kim Dae Myeung)
(The three great actors gathered
for the movie "The Golden Holiday".)
(They will show off their perfect
chemistry in the movie.)
(Today, they will maximize
their chemistry on Running Man.)
- They rarely go on a variety show.
- Exactly.
Before we begin...
The three of them starred in
the movie "The Golden Holiday".
Kwak Do Won, Kim Sang Ho,
and Kim Dae Myeung are here.
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
(Welcome.)
Do Won, could you...
You brought soccer balls.
I don't know. They told us to.
(He speaks in a friendly way.)
- You see...
- He looks so natural.
There's always someone like him
in every morning soccer club.
- Holding a bottle of makgeolli.
- There's always someone like him.
- He'd play only for five minutes.
- He looks so natural.
- Sitting in a shade.
- Please say hello to the viewers.
Hello. I starred in the movie
"The Golden Holiday"...
Basically, I'm here
to promote the movie.
- I'm not good at this.
- He's honest.
- We all know that now.
- We all know that.
- Of course, we know.
- Following "Steel Rain 2: Summit",
you starred in "The Golden Holiday".
I'd like to tell you something
before we begin.
- I had a shoot all night.
- Oh, I see.
So my voice is hoarse now.
- So I...
- What did you shoot?
The movie title is "Firefighters".
- "Firefighters"?
- You're shooting another film?
- Anyway...
- We heard four movie titles...
- in only 20 seconds...
- All right. Be quiet.
Why would you...
- In only 20 seconds...
- All right. Be quiet.
(Angry)
- But we just heard...
- Be quiet.
- Do Won is talking.
- four movies...
- Stop it.
- He's right. That's enough.
- Do Won, please continue.
- Yes?
- Let him finish.
- Go ahead. What is it?
Even Do Won also pretended
he didn't hear me.
(Ignoring Kwang Soo is popular
among actors as well.)
That would be great to use
to make a video clip, right?
That was good, right?
Gosh, seriously.
- That's also my job.
- I see.
- People love to watch it.
- You work so hard.
- Of course, I work hard.
- Some people like it.
Dae Myeung, please say hello
to the viewers.
- Hello.
- He's a great actor.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Kim Dae Myeung.
He's the best.
You starred with Kwang Soo
in "The Sound of Your Heart".
That's right.
- He played Kwang Soo's brother.
- Yes.
How was Kwang Soo back then?
Wasn't he arrogant?
No, he was very polite...
and nice to other people
as far as I remember.
But he looked completely different
on Running Man.
He's not in his right mind here.
(He has a different persona
on Running Man.)
He's crazy.
Jong Kook thinks everyone is crazy
except for himself.
- He's the only normal person.
- In the whole world.
Sang Ho, please say hello
to the viewers.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Kim Sang Ho.
(Kim Sang Ho, the acting artisan
who can pull off any character)
- He was on "Village Survival".
- Yes, we worked together.
We starred in
"City Hunter" together.
- That's right. We worked together.
- Yes.
- We went to the Philippines,
and he was like a Korean Wave star.
So many fans would
follow him around.
- Because of the drama?
- Everyone recognized him.
They all just asked me...
where Lee Min Ho was.
(The fans asked me
where Lee Min Ho was.)
I said, "I don't know."
Everyone recognized him.
(Sang Ho is treated as a top star
like Lee Min Ho.)
- You're internationally popular.
- He must be.
Kwang Soo is the one
who's internationally popular.
(Bowing)
Next up is Dae Myeung.
(As he complimented Kwang Soo
unexpectedly,)
(Jae Suk glanced at Kwang Soo,)
(and changed the subject.)
There's nothing wrong
with talking about me.
- It was good enough.
- Calm down.
- It was interesting. Don't worry.
- It was good.
We need to hear as many stories as
we can while interviewing them.
- Don't try to get more air time.
- Exactly.
Now, we're going to leave
for the soccer training.
- You'll go through security.
- What do you mean?
Please go through security.
(The state
of the art equipment appeared.)
Only the ones with bags should
go through it.
Only the ones with bags.
- I'm nervous.
- Go ahead.
(Do Won is going through it
with the soccer balls.)
- But...
- Go ahead.
(Beeping)
(The alarm went off.)
- But...
- What?
- He has something.
- He got caught.
What's going on?
- Kwak Do Won.
He got caught.
A suspicious object
has been detected.
I will search your belongings.
(A suspicious object?)
- I will search your belongings.
- What's going on?
Is there something inside the balls?
I think there's something
inside the balls.
(Looking at the agent)
What could it be?
(He's watching the process
with his hands behind the back.)
If you look at Do Won's pose,
he looks like he's thinking,
"What on earth is going on?"
As if he's thinking, "Hurry up."
- There must be something in there.
- What is it?
(He's cutting open the ball
with shaking hands.)
He's cutting it. I guess there's
something in the ball.
Something inside the ball
was detected.
(The assistant director is
moving his hands nervously.)
He looks serious.
- Seriously.
- If it requires acting skills...
Don't be nervous.
(His dry lips are trembling.)
Why is he shaking?
Hyeong Gu, why are you shaking?
It's because he has no acting
experience. He's our staff.
You should register in
an acting class.
(Being the assistant director of
Running Man requires acting skills.)
(Their criticisms made him
even more nervous.)
Oh, there's... I think there's
something in it.
(His lack of dexterity
frustrates everyone.)
Gosh. I'll do it.
Move.
(He ended up losing his patience.)
- Do Won, please calm down.
- Gosh.
- He's doing it by himself.
- No, please.
- Move.
- Please calm down.
- Gosh, seriously.
- He's doing it by himself.
He's doing it by himself.
(Startled)
(He lacks acting skills
and gets scared easily.)
You can do it from above like this.
Look at Do Won. My goodness.
What is he doing?
- Why is it taking you so long?
- He can't do it.
Will a pigeon come out of it
or something?
(By the time everyone is
getting tired...)
It's just a ball.
(He found mysterious white powder!)
(Something was found in the ball.)
Is that drug?
(What is that?)
In the ball,
seasoned salt was found,
which is a hazardous item.
(Is seasoned salt a hazardous item?)
- I'm sorry, but...
- Seasoned salt?
Hold on. I'm sorry, but can that
be detected by a metal detector?
Why is seasoned salt
a hazardous item?
(The assistant director left
after leaving the seasoned salt.)
And why is the studio...
Seasoned salt was found...
in Do Won's soccer ball.
Then you should arrest him.
Therefore, Do Won is arrested in
the act of smuggling seasoned salt,
- and on the suspect list.
- Okay.
Do Won, please put on
the suspect uniform now.
He's a suspect. He became
a suspect from the beginning.
(He became a suspect in an instant.)
Everyone, today's mission is
to find out the criminals...
who are in the morning soccer club.
It's the anti-criminal operation,
Domestic Investigation Race.
Among the 10 members
of the morning soccer club,
there are two criminals who tried
to smuggle seasoned salt out...
and two police officers
who infiltrated into...
the group to catch the criminals.
(There are 2 police officers who are
here to catch the criminals.)
There are police officers as well?
If the officers fail to arrest the
two criminals or get eliminated...
during the race, the criminals win.
If they arrest the two criminals,
the officers and citizens win.
The winners will get a prize,
and the losers will get a penalty.
And Do Won is a suspect here,
so if his team loses,
two people including himself
will get a penalty.
So you'd better try your best
to make your team win.
So it's about reasoning again.
(Sang Ho wasn't so good
at reasoning in "Village Survival".)
Gosh, I'm not good at it.
This is crazy.
- I'm here to have fun.
- Sang Ho hates reasoning.
- You should just run.
- He really hates it.
He seems to hate it.
Let's move on to the next place
to start the race then.
- Okay.
Good.
- Let's have a seat.
- Okay.
(Groaning)
(He keeps groaning which doesn't
happen a lot on variety shows.)
(He sounds so friendly.)
Please give me a bottle of water.
Just throw it.
(Kwang Soo starts moving right away
as soon as he hears it.)
- Look at Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo is nice.
I guess this is how
he's become Asian Prince.
- Kwang Soo, I want one too.
- Okay.
(He's an official errand boy.)
Kwang Soo, why are you going around
during the shoot?
- It's not like that.
- Why are you wandering around?
The director is waiting for you.
Behave yourself.
We can't start because of Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo,
we can't start the shoot...
- because of you.
- Sit down.
We should work.
My goodness.
Can't you walk around the streets
in Southeast Asian countries?
That's not true.
Can't he walk around the streets
in Southeast Asia?
- Kwang Soo?
- It's not like that.
- He can walk around.
- He can?
(He's popular, but he has
no problem getting around.)
All right. Here's the first mission.
Those who win this mission
will get the first hint.
It's the nationwide survey,
Anxious Seat Lineup.
Okay.
We conducted a survey of
people of all ages beforehand.
We will give you a keyword
of a survey in each round.
With the keyword,
you will split into two teams.
Once the teams are decided,
we will reveal the survey.
Then each team will select...
two members who are likely
to be ranked highest.
The four members will sit
on the conveyor.
The team with lower ranks
will be sent into the penalty room.
- There's a penalty room?
- My gosh.
(The team with lower ranks
will be sent into the penalty room.)
- Gosh, it's confusing.
- I know.
I understand the part
where we split into teams.
What are you writing down?
Why are you putting it down?
I just don't understand it.
I watched this show a lot,
but I still don't
understand the rules.
They will explain the rules again.
I get the part where we are
divided into teams.
Once you're split into two teams...
(The director is explaining
the rules again.)
You will pick two people who are
likely to be ranked highest.
- For example, the strongest...
- Okay.
I understand it perfectly.
(Okay. I understand it perfectly.)
(The actors keep
cutting Kwang Soo off.)
- Gosh, why did you do that?
- Nice.
I just tried to make things clear.
Nicely done, Sang Ho.
(It's always fun
to cut Kwang Soo off.)
It's fun, isn't it?
- This is fun.
- I know. It's really fun.
It's Jae Suk's fault!
(It's Jae Suk's fault!)
Let me give you
the first keyword then.
The first keyword is office workers.
(Keyword: Office workers)
The keyword is office workers.
- Office workers?
- Yes.
Someone who'd make
a good office worker?
The person who'd be good
at working at a company.
Since Do Won is the suspect,
he gets to pick...
five members who are likely
to be ranked high.
The question can be the person
who'd make a good office worker...
- or a bad one.
- Exactly.
We don't know it yet.
So Do Won needs to think carefully.
It's about office workers.
Do Won should pick well.
1, 2, 3, 4, and 5.
1, 2, 3...
Let's split here.
- Just like that?
- He sounds so insincere.
Let's split here.
- Just like that?
- He sounds so insincere.
- That's nice.
- He just cut us in half.
- That's neat.
- He's bold.
- He just doesn't want to move,
- What was that?
so he cut us in half.
How could he do that?
I like Mr. Kwak.
He seems broad-minded.
- Mr. Kwak.
- You know "The Man Standing Next".
(Kwak Do Won, Manager,
He plays his cards right.)
- It's simple and neat this way.
- I agree.
So you are now Team Blue
and Team Red.
- Okay.
- I'll tell you about the survey.
We asked this question
to office workers.
(Office workers)
"The person whom
you don't want as your boss."
- What?
- The person you don't want.
(The person whom office workers
don't want as their boss)
The question is "The person whom
you don't want as your boss".
- It must be Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook.
I'm sure it's Jong Kook...
- or Kwak Do Won.
- I think it's Kwak Do Won.
It must be one of these two.
Let's imagine
that Kwang Soo is our boss.
- The company would go under.
- It will go under. I agree.
- Why would you say that?
- It's a bogus company.
It will soon go under.
We just need to pick
a boss we don't want.
Why would you talk
about a company going under?
I think Jae Suk will say
good things all day,
so he won't make a good boss.
- You said nice things first...
- He nags a lot.
The beginning and end of your speech
are totally different.
It'd be nice to hear good things
for the first one minute.
- You think?
- But it would last for hours.
He wouldn't stop talking.
Each team should pick two members.
It should be me and Do Won.
- Okay.
- This is about images.
- You should definitely go up there.
- It should be you and me.
I think people wouldn't want me.
It should be you and me.
Do Won and I will go up.
- I have no idea.
- I'm sure Jae Suk is ranked high.
I'm not sure who will win.
I'm so curious.
- So the thing is...
- This is...
the team who's ranked higher wins.
- Exactly.
- If we don't win, we get a penalty.
I see.
It moves
either to the left or right.
We will put together your rankings,
and the team with
the smaller number will win.
And the conveyor will move
towards the losing team.
- Good.
- Let's do this!
I'm sure they're ranked 1st and 2nd.
He just doesn't know about himself.
All right. One.
(Which team will get a penalty?)
- Two.
- He will say good things all day.
- He wouldn't make a good boss.
- Three.
If the conveyor moves this way,
does that mean we win?
- See? I knew it.
- Did we lose?
- Right.
- Three.
(Jae Suk and Do Won win.)
(Jae Suk and Do Won are
not desirable bosses.)
- You win.
- We win?
- It's moving this way.
- We win.
(They don't get a penalty,
but they're not pleased.)
Well done.
I knew it.
- That's high.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook and Suk Jin are
in the penalty room.)
- We're doomed.
- Okay.
This is disappointing.
- Gosh, hang on.
- What's wrong?
- Hey!
- That's enough.
That's just too much.
(What's happening
in the penalty room?)
Why? What's going on?
I can hear a spray.
(Jong Koo and Suk Jin
are coming out.)
- They're here.
- Okay.
- They're coming out.
- Come on.
- My goodness.
- Gosh, this is a little...
You look younger.
This is...
(Giggling)
You've become younger.
- Let's go down.
- What's that?
It's not a penalty.
Jong Kook, your hair looks
like the Korean flag.
- I know.
- It's the World Cup all over again.
As I saw Suk Jin, I thought...
he seemed somewhat familiar.
In "What on Earth", there was...
a middle-aged man
who tries to look young.
(There's a middle-aged man
who lives a young life.)
- Exactly.
- He's just like the man.
"I walk around the traditional
market with dyed hair."
- He tries to look young.
- With a funny T-shirt.
He lives a young life.
My gosh, it's so funny.
Let me tell you the survey result.
We surveyed office workers
in their 30s and 40s.
Jae Suk is in first place.
Gosh, Jae Suk is number one.
- Look at that.
- Jong Kook is in second place.
It's so close.
I knew it. There's my name.
- So we won.
- No, it's a tie.
But the team
who's ranked higher wins.
- That's right.
- Really?
People say Jae Suk
and Jong Kook would nag a lot.
- They think we'd nag a lot.
- I know.
- And Kwang Soo is number three.
- Why is that?
- What about Kwang Soo?
- They say he'd be too mischievous.
I look mischievous.
What about Suk Jin?
Suk Jin looks condescending.
(They picked Suk Jin
because he seems condescending.)
(He tries to look nice
with partly dyed hair.)
Let's move on
to the second question.
Nice. All right. We won anyway.
Here's the second question.
- We surveyed housewives.
- Okay.
- The person...
- Who'd help around the house.
who'd be messiest.
(Who do housewives think
would be the messiest person?)
My gosh.
(They all stare at one person
at the same time.)
He's too strong a candidate.
- He's hard to beat.
- In our team...
Our team...
I just want him
to go up there himself.
I want him to
go up there spontaneously.
- We have one strong candidate.
- We have one person in mind.
- I don't want to point him out.
- We have a winner.
He's just too strong.
I think all the five members
of this team put together...
can't beat him.
- Ji Hyo and Sang Ho are going up.
- Okay.
Our team is really...
- Ji Hyo?
- We have Ji Hyo and Sang Ho.
That's because...
Ji Hyo spends
most of her time in bed.
Who should go up from our team?
I think I'm going up again.
(So Min's eyes stop at someone.)
- Well...
- And Do Won.
- Do Won and I should go up there.
- You should go up.
Do you mind going up?
- No.
- Let's do that.
Actually...
Suk Jin, why do you feel
uncomfortable around Do Won?
I'm not uncomfortable.
- It's so obvious.
- That's not true.
- You sound polite.
- He's a lot younger than you.
- He is younger than me.
- He's way younger.
I'm a big fan.
I'm being respectful as a fan.
Do Won, get up.
Stand up.
(He works up the nerve
and calls Do Won's name.)
What if we win again?
I'm sure we will win this time.
I'm nervous
because people in there sound busy.
- They're busy doing something.
- They're in a rush.
- They're clattering.
- They're busy.
Please show us the result.
I didn't see this coming.
Move the conveyor. One.
- I'm not nervous at all.
- Two.
(Sang Ho and Ji Hyo are sure
they will win.)
(Who are the winners?)
Three.
Okay!
(Surprisingly,
Suk Jin and Do Won win.)
- We won.
- Hey, we won.
Really?
- What's going on?
- We won.
- Seriously?
- Who would beat Sang Ho?
- My gosh.
- That doesn't make sense.
We have Sang Ho here.
(Ji Hyo and Sang Ho come out
after getting the penalty.)
Come over here.
(Behind the cute idiot is...)
- What a surprise! That's right.
- Goodness.
- Gosh, Sang Ho.
- You surprised me.
(He looks good in this makeup.)
(What a surprise!)
- It looks good on him.
- That really surprised me.
- Oh, my.
- You're so cute.
- It looks so good on him.
- He's so cute.
That really surprised me.
- It suits him.
- Sang Ho is so funny.
- He's so cute.
- He's so funny.
(Sang Ho looks good in everything
for no reason.)
He looks like he could have
a younger sister like her.
- Oh, my.
- I saw someone like that.
Jae Suk!
He looks like the character from
"Dr. Slump".
- He looks like her 50 years later.
- Arale.
- 50 years later.
- But...
These two were ranked higher.
That's incredible.
- Who is it?
- I'm so curious.
- I really am.
- I'll reveal it now.
Who's in first place?
- Kwak Do Won?
- Really?
Kwak Do Won is in first place?
I'm in second place?
(Haha can't accept that he's in
2nd place either.)
There were various reasons as to why
Do Won came in first place,
but one of them was because he looks
like he might have athlete's foot.
(He looks like he might have
athlete's foot.)
- I have it.
- Why would they say that?
What do you mean? I have it.
- He admitted his athlete's foot.
- This is surprising.
This is the fourth question.
(Revealing the second question with
the keyword "foreigner")
The actor who's likely to succeed
if they went to Hollywood.
- I knew it.
See? I told you.
We're in trouble.
We showed foreigners your photos
from photoshoots and commercials.
We showed them these photographs.
Let's see.
- Who are these people?
- Hold on.
Sang Ho. Sang Ho could go.
- Look at Do Won.
- I...
Who is that? Hold on. Who is that?
- Ji Hyo looks great too.
- She's a strong contender.
Ji Hyo's photograph is great.
I looked at Ji Hyo's photograph and
then at her, and it surprised me.
I was really surprised.
- Why?
- I think... Hold on.
Who is that girl?
- Is that So Min?
- Is it?
I look like that with makeup on.
Why did you use a photo application
instead of doing a photoshoot?
I didn't.
I look like that with makeup on.
They photoshopped her chin.
Do you think they might've
chosen me?
- I don't think so.
- I doubt it.
Do you think they might've
chosen me?
(Everyone is in unison when they say
it's not him.)
You're not on the list.
- You...
- Why not?
- Hey.
- There's no way.
- That picture...
- Why can't it be me?
That picture isn't good.
That picture makes you look like
an insurance broker.
- An insurance broker?
- You do.
- The employee of the year.
If I'm being honest.
Or a candidate in a local election.
- Who will be chosen in our team?
- Suk Jin...
I think it could be Dae Myeung.
- Or Kwang Soo?
- I think...
it's Kwang Soo and Sang Ho.
- Kwang Soo?
- He's a good choice.
- Kwang Soo...
- Because...
he looks like an actor.
- Okay. Kwang Soo.
- Let's go with Kwang Soo.
- Should I go up?
- Yes, you should.
We'll go with Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
- I feel like I'm going to my spot.
- Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo is quite popular
among foreigners.
Okay. Let's see the results.
They lost. They're busy over there.
- They're busy over there.
- It's really busy back there.
- I hear something.
- What is it?
One.
(This question is a matter of pride
for celebrities.)
Two.
(Kwang Soo and Sang Ho
have a strong presence.)
Three.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook
have an overwhelming visual.)
- Okay.
- We lost.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo win!)
- Ji Hyo was too strong.
- I knew we'd win.
- Thank goodness.
- It was Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
Isn't this Sang Ho's special?
I know, he got so many penalties.
I know. This is Kim Sang Ho's game.
Please come out.
Oh, my. What is this?
They got it done.
Is that it?
That's the penalty.
- How cute.
- Sang Ho is so cute.
- I was wondering what it was.
- Sang Ho.
- How cute.
Kwang Soo, you don't look
as funny today.
- Kwang Soo.
- You always looked the funniest.
- You don't stand out today.
- You don't.
You don't catch our eyes.
- Do I look that funny?
- Yes, you do.
You look so cute.
Come down.
I'll reveal the results.
It's very interesting.
- Okay.
- Is it?
What is this?
- So Min's in first place?
- In second is Kim Jong Kook.
- It was me?
- See? I told you.
- I'm in fourth place?
With Ji Hyo there too. I was right.
- So Min would succeed too.
- I'm in last place?
I should go.
I'm in last place?
(I'm in last place?)
Kwang Soo was in last place.
They must've chosen without
considering popularity.
What are you doing now?
Yang Se Chan...
- beat me.
- Se Chan is in sixth place.
What happened?
I'm okay with coming in last place,
but I'm so mad
that Jae Suk beat me.
- My gosh, Kwang Soo...
- Seriously.
I guess Kwang Soo's picture
didn't have any appeal.
I guess he's in last place. He must
not be appealing to foreigners.
So the result is out.
- I wonder how it came out?
- This is what's important.
The person who won the most is...
Kwak Do Won, who won all five times.
(Kwak Do Won won all 5 times.)
- Really?
- You won every time?
He won five times?
I'll tell you what kind of hints
Do Won can get.
Out of the 10 of you,
2 of you are police officers,
and 2 of you are criminals.
We can choose two people who aren't
police officers at random...
- and tell you who they are.
- Really?
In other words, they are
either a citizen or a criminal.
Or we can tell you two people
who aren't criminals.
Then those two will be either
a police officer or a citizen.
You can come up and whisper
which one you want to know.
If you ask me up here,
I'll tell you.
What is he saying?
I don't understand.
- He sounds like a police officer.
- I don't understand.
- He sounds like a real cop.
- It's hard, right?
Yes, I don't understand.
- Even if...
- He seems like a police officer.
- Even if I study, I don't get it.
(His question will differ depending
on his identity.)
(What is the question that
Do Won asked?)
Tell me the two
that aren't criminals.
(Tell me the two
that aren't criminals.)
- That was too loud.
- You're supposed to whisper.
- We can hear it all.
(He asked a question that
only a citizen would want to know.)
(Then he asked another question
that is inaudible.)
This is the answer to your question.
(If it was the same as
his initial question,)
You have to make sure no one sees
your notebook.
(then Do Won is either
a citizen or a police officer.)
If that was a fake,
then I acknowledge him.
- We're friends.
- I know you are.
(What question did Do Won
ask the production crew?)
Why don't we have more chairs?
What is this?
What is "Running Cinema"?
The second mission is...
a game where you must all
work together.
It's Speak With Your Actions:
Cinema Nightmare.
I like things like this.
- The 10 of you are in 1 team.
- What's this?
If you answer more than
3 of the 5 questions,
we will give you two hints
that will help the citizens.
If you answer two questions right,
the citizens and the criminals
will get one hint each.
If you only get 1 question right,
the criminals will get 2 hints.
I think Sang Ho might curse
while playing this game.
No, I won't.
It means the criminals will try...
to prevent us from getting...
- the right answers.
- That's right.
I understood it. See? I get it.
You understood it too quickly.
That's suspicious.
It's suspicious that
you understood it already.
As if he already knew the rules.
As if one of our writers
told you the rules in advance.
This is how the game will proceed.
Five representatives will step up
for each round,
and there is a 100-second
time limit.
We're going to show the first person
a summary of a movie.
They must explain it with
their bodies and pass it along.
This is really hard.
This is hard.
If the last person gets the title
of the movie right, you get a point.
- How are we supposed to do this?
- This is too hard.
- This is hard.
The actors must get it right.
- That's right.
- I'm sure it'll be famous lines.
It's not a famous line.
It's a summary of the movie.
It's a summary?
When did he mention that
it was a famous line?
He didn't say anything about
a famous line.
Are you hearing things now?
- He's trying his best.
- He is.
He's just trying to do his job.
Let's choose someone
who's good at it.
Let's have the actors go.
We can make a team that's filled
with good players.
- Let's do that.
- Then we can see who gets it wrong.
- That's right.
- Also...
- I want Do Won to go.
- So Min?
- Do Won.
- I want to see him.
We need to include our members.
We need to include someone
who's good.
Someone who's good. Who's good?
- Should I go in?
- Jae Suk.
- You should stay out of it.
- You need to stay out of it.
- You can try later.
(The person who's afraid of games
can go later.)
All of our aces are up.
Ready, set,
(What's the first movie the ace team
will do?)
go.
(They must undergo 7 trials
in the underworld to be reborn.)
Is this the movie?
This is hard.
How would you explain it?
- Does it start once I turn around?
- Yes.
- The clock started.
- Did it?
This is hard to explain.
- It's hard.
- It's really hard.
Okay.
(They must undergo 7 trials in the
underworld to be reborn.)
This is good.
(You die and go to the underworld.)
I'm sure he can figure it out.
(It's a good start.)
- This is Grim Reaper.
- I think he'll get it.
You only have 100 seconds.
That's not a lot.
That's it. You can go now.
(They only have 100 seconds.
He quickly explains it to Sang Ho.)
(You die.)
This is good.
(You go to the skies.)
(Sang Ho explains it
just as Jong Kook did.)
Sang Ho knows the answer.
He knows. He's doing good.
(You get judged.)
- They're doing good.
- This is good.
- He got it.
- He explained it well.
He got it.
Good.
Okay.
Go. You only have 100 seconds.
- He has to know this.
- Come on.
I think they'll get it.
But sometimes you forget the title.
(He explains it with the same
movements to Do Won.)
Oh, my.
- I don't think he knows.
- This is weird.
He has to explain dying more.
(It's the same explanation,
but he doesn't seem to know.)
My gosh. This is driving me crazy.
- How much time is left?
- We don't have time.
- He doesn't know?
- This is...
You should do a better job.
Doesn't Do Won know?
It was exactly the same.
- How can he not know?
- He just needs to copy it.
(Will Do Won explain it correctly
to So Min?)
- Go ahead.
- The sky?
(He's pointing at the sky?)
- He's acting weird.
- We need to be quiet.
(The movements were, "After you die,
you go to the underworld".)
- Go ahead.
- The sky?
- He's acting weird.
- That comes later.
That's right.
(He's acting a bit weird.)
- He's acting weird.
- We need to be quiet.
They died. They died in the sky.
The order is off.
(It's time to portray the judgment.)
"You punks!"
("You punks!")
"What are you doing, you punks?"
(She's immersed.)
What's wrong with So Min?
They died in the sky.
They hold on to this and go...
(She turns on her own dubbing.)
- "You punks."
- What's she doing?
(He's judging them over here.)
(She's shooting them over here.)
Oh, my.
Gosh. They're acting weird.
- Jeon So Min.
- "You punks!"
- "You punks."
- Jeon So Min.
- So Min.
- This is how So Min is.
What is this?
- In the sky.
- You have 10 seconds left.
Kill.
(Oh, "Along with the Gods".)
Oh, "Along with the Gods".
("Along with the Gods" is correct.)
- You did great, Jong Kook.
- You surprised me.
Good one.
- I honestly had no idea.
- How did you know?
What was it though?
- "Along with the Gods".
- Really?
- No way.
- Amazing.
I didn't know what it was either.
- Really?
- I just did what you did.
I thought you understood!
- You did it so well though.
- Unbelievable.
- We thought you knew.
- It seemed that way.
- Really?
- It's crucial to have a good start.
Jong Kook did a good job
explaining it.
(A nice start and a perfect ending)
I think Suk Jin should participate.
- Suk Jin?
- Yes, I agree.
- We need to filter people out.
- We know now.
- We have a basic idea.
- Dae Myeung, you can answer.
- I don't know if I can do this.
- You know a lot of movies.
You aren't allowed
to make any noises from now on.
- Sure.
- Got it.
It's over for me
if I don't do a good job.
- Exactly.
- So do your best.
- I'm watching you.
- Okay. You can count on me.
Ready, set, go.
(The story of an expert face reader
who tries to prevent a revolt)
That's a difficult one.
This is a hard one.
It's too difficult.
("The Face Reader")
Think wisely, Kwang Soo.
This may be your last chance.
How can one explain this?
You can do it.
(He starts off by making
a big fuss about it.)
(The story of an expert face reader
who tries to prevent a revolt)
- This is really difficult.
- What's he up to?
Is that the best he can do?
(He makes puzzling gestures
near his face.)
- Wait, hold on.
- What?
- What is that?
- Hold on a second.
- What on earth is that?
What is that?
(This and that)
Hold on a second.
Kwang Soo's done for.
(I'm the King!)
He's done for.
- What is this?
- What are you doing?
- Hey!
- Seriously?
(He gives up explaining
what the movie is about.)
- Kwang Soo!
- Let's move on.
- What on earth are you doing?
- Hey.
- What is this?
- What are you doing?
(No one can understand
what he's doing.)
(He confuses Sang Ho
with his slow-walking.)
Why would you do that?
- That...
- Hey!
I don't know what that is
even though I'm aware of the answer.
- He messed it all up.
- He's one of the criminals.
- What on earth is that?
- You never know though.
He messed it all up.
(Just forget it.)
- You!
- Sang Ho might've understood it.
- You never know.
- He's a criminal.
I'm clueless even though
I know the answer.
(Sang Ho does
exactly what Kwang Soo did.)
- How can one guess anything?
- What is that?
- This isn't nearly enough.
- I know.
- What on earth is that?
- Unbelievable.
(The reason it's crucial to
have a good start)
I think Sang Ho...
- Do Won's next.
- I'm sure of it.
Sang Ho doesn't know what it is.
He only copied what he saw.
Someone might catch on though...
if they pinpoint what's crucial.
(Someone might catch on
if they pinpoint what's crucial.)
It's even weirder now.
I know what the answer will be.
I think I know too.
(Face-palming and slow-walking)
- I think I know what it is.
- What?
(Suk Jin thinks he knows.)
- It's gotten weirder.
- He doesn't know.
He's clueless.
This is weird.
What on earth is this?
- Time over.
- Is it...
- What?
- That old movie.
- What's the answer?
- It's enough to make a guess.
- I think I know what it is.
- It's enough to guess the movie.
(All they have to go on is
the face and slow-walking.)
- I think I know what it is.
- It's enough to guess the movie.
- "Face Off".
- That's what I thought too.
- Right?
- "The Mask".
- That's what you said too.
- Here's the answer.
- What's the answer?
- "The Face Reader".
How does that explain
"The Face Reader"?
Remember the scene
with Lee Jung Jae?
- Yes, of course.
- He's walking up the stairs.
We only know what that scene is
because we're aware of the answer.
(He did a poor job
reenacting the scene.)
Forget it and just sit back down.
- Kwang Soo sure seems suspicious.
- I agree.
- He made it impossible to guess.
- It was too difficult.
Shouldn't we score a point
in this next round?
Yes, we should.
- So Min or Jong Kook then.
- Yes, So Min.
- Yes, us.
- I'm not a criminal.
- I'm not one either, actually.
- "Actually"?
Why would you add "actually"
at the end?
- Hold on. Isn't that weird?
- It really isn't me.
- Actually?
- I get it though.
- You need to explain.
- No, wait.
- It just popped out.
- You're playing.
- Actually?
- It isn't me.
Am I suddenly being suspected?
He always makes it worse
for himself by talking too much.
- Actually?
- Whenever he plays a devious role,
he actively accuses other people.
- Right?
- That's so true.
Okay, let's do this.
- It's not me.
- So how will it be?
Dae Myeung, you should play too.
(Do Won asks his manager
for something.)
- Get ready.
- Just one.
Did he bring it?
- Let me pass it along.
- What is it?
Do Won has a sore throat.
- Candy for his throat?
- Thank you.
- Can I get one too?
- No.
(He demands one as well.)
Why?
- This is his medicine, you know.
- I know.
Why would you take his medicine?
I don't mind.
- Why take his medicine?
- I hated his tone.
- He needs it for his throat.
- Do Won...
has a sore throat.
- Are you kidding me?
- His manager passed it along.
- But...
- You don't even talk that much.
- Don't take it!
- It won't hurt though, right?
Just don't.
(He isn't that comfortable
around Do Won but...)
He never passes up on a chance
to eat things.
I'll explain what I read, okay?
- The five of us will compete.
- Yes, let's.
Go!
(Which sentence will Do Won
have to explain?)
It's not easy.
See? This isn't easy at all.
Hold on. I don't think
I know that movie.
Which movie is that?
Please begin. The clock is ticking.
Do it!
- He's doing great.
- Who is that?
- Is that Sang Ho?
- And Do Won.
(He describes a high school girl.)
- Sang Ho's watching.
- He might swear soon.
It might throw Sang Ho off though.
My gosh.
(He shows off his cute side.)
What is it?
(Lovely Do Won)
- Nice.
- You look so sweet.
(He shows off his sweet side
with gentle steps.)
- Is it Sang Ho now?
- No.
- Do Won's being cute.
- Really?
The way he's describing it...
- Is he doing a good job?
- Yes, he's being sweet.
Doesn't he look like Winnie the Pooh
in the orange shirt?
He does.
He looks like a teddy bear.
(Teddy Bear Do Won needs
to go back 25 years.)
25 years!
(The pent-up frustration
makes him roar like a bear.)
- What?
- What is it?
- What was it?
- What's going on?
- What?
- Seriously?
Do it again, will you?
- What was that?
- Show us!
- What did he do?
- He was amazing.
He talked during the game though.
The movie was "Sunny".
(They fail Round 3 because
Do Won gave a verbal hint.)
- It was weird though.
- It's too difficult to explain.
- We're going super easy on you.
- This...
It's too hard to explain
just that one sentence.
You're all doing a good job though.
- What do you mean?
- Seriously?
You're all doing a good job though.
Then we would've gotten
more than one right.
- What do you mean we're doing well?
- Are you kidding me?
What exactly are we doing well?
What's with that arrogant tone?
How are we doing a good job?
- We're getting all of them wrong.
- How are we doing a good job?
We're doing good
only from your standpoint...
because we're getting them wrong.
Get ready...
(After they calm down,
Round 4 begins.)
Ready, set, go.
(They guessed 1 correct,
and now they have 2 chances left.)
(The story of a father who lived
through Korea's history since 1950)
- My gosh.
- This won't be easy.
- That makes me even more nervous.
- Goodness.
This is how you describe that movie?
Goodness.
It can be described
in a much simpler way,
but that's what you chose to write?
(It's summarized
in a difficult way.)
It can be described though.
The movie is famous enough.
(The story of a father who lived
through Korea's history since 1950)
(Shoot! Throw!)
- What?
- He's making noises.
He shouldn't make noises.
Shouldn't he keep quiet?
Sound effects are fine.
Please refrain
from sound effects too.
(No sound effects)
- It must be a war zone.
- A battlefield.
(He describes the same scene,
but while muted this time.)
What's taking him so long?
He must be the criminal.
The time already...
Already?
- He's the criminal for sure.
- Shouldn't I be explaining by now?
This is hilarious!
- Gosh, this is hilarious.
- What on earth is it?
I should be explaining this by now.
- Is it still not you?
- No.
(Finally, it's Sang Ho's turn.)
(Kwak Do Won, Suspect,
Used up all of the time)
Guys, we have caught
one of the criminals.
- He's the criminal.
- It'll be an easy win for us.
He's not just the suspect.
He's actually the criminal.
(He used up half of the time.)
(Just like Do Won did,
Sang Ho describes a battlefield.)
(Then he describes
finding and hugging his family.)
- No way.
- We're done for.
There's a chance
that he'll get it right.
Maybe.
That looks odd though.
Wait, that wasn't it at all.
(Jae Suk left out the first part.)
He's not doing it right.
(He then moves on
to the shooting gesture.)
He described that scene afterwards.
- You're right.
- It's like he's describing love.
- This is weird.
- You're making me anxious.
- Don't fall for it.
- Please move on.
- Jae Suk changed it up.
- It was super weird.
I can't help but be suspicious.
(They all start to doubt Jae Suk.)
- A bomb?
- Please move on.
What on earth is this?
(Only the gathering part
was focused on.)
What on earth is this?
- What...
- I have no idea.
(It went from finding his family
to carrying something.)
- Is this a mine or a tank?
- This is... What?
I don't know
which is why I kept asking him.
It's nearly impossible
to describe this.
- What is this? Hold on.
- Your time is up.
- I have no idea.
- Hold on.
- Let me think it through just once.
- Go ahead.
Over there!
(So Min's Dubbing)
"You guys, carry these."
(She then carries a package.)
(Finding family, Carrying a package)
- Is that how he did it?
- It's what Suk Jin did.
The only movie that comes to mind
is "The Front Line".
- What was it?
- It was hard to describe.
Jae Suk changed it up.
- It was weird.
- It made me suspect him.
Do Won, why don't you
show it to them?
- Do Won, go ahead.
- I...
I'm only allowed to describe
what is written, right?
It's impossible though.
Look, mister... I mean, Director.
You give it a try. It's impossible!
- Show us though.
- Okay, I will.
My gosh.
Is he doing it?
(The story of a father who lived
through Korea's history since 1950)
(A long time ago)
He is shooting.
- A grenade.
- A bomb.
(Up to here, the movements were
easy to understand.)
Death.
- But you...
- You...
- Your younger sibling.
- Yes.
- Your younger sibling...
- You have a younger sibling.
- Everyone died.
- Everyone got separated.
(Flapping)
(I get it.)
That must be it.
Everyone got separated.
The family members got separated.
- "Ode to My Father".
- The family members got separated.
"Ode to My Father".
- "Ode to My Father".
- It was "Ode to My Father".
- It's so hard.
The description is so hard.
It's so hard.
How are we supposed to guess?
It makes no sense.
(It's time for the last question.)
Be careful.
Don't give us an overly hard one.
- Let's succeed.
- It's too hard.
Get ready.
Set, go.
(What will be the result
of the last question?)
- Describe exactly what you see.
- The title...
It's too hard.
It's impossible to describe it.
(Yawning)
- Sang Ho!
- Yes?
Did you yawn just now?
Are you bored?
No, no. I am sorry.
Shall we begin?
I need to activate my brain.
Please be clear
when you deliver the information.
(Guess the answer.)
- Do it exactly like him.
- Just copy what you see.
Please see if Haha messes it up
on purpose.
Jong Kook is doing a good job.
Jong Kook isn't a criminal.
- No, he isn't.
- He is doing a good job.
The fact he is describing it
like that...
He isn't a criminal.
- But you never know.
- It's time to move on.
(It's Sang Ho's turn.)
There wasn't anything else
I could do.
(Lively movements...)
(and realistic facial expressions)
We need to be quiet.
(Absorbed)
An actor is surely different.
- Please move on.
- He is good.
- His facial expressions...
- There isn't a sound.
(It's Dae Myeung's turn.)
There isn't a sound...
even when he jumps.
Actors are good
at using their facial expressions.
It's becoming more detailed.
(They keep adding more details.)
It really is becoming more detailed.
Actors sure are different.
(Okay!)
We need to get this one right.
- What? What's going on?
- He is...
He is a bit strange, right?
We need to get this one right.
What?
(Exaggerated movements...)
(and strange facial expressions)
You make me laugh.
- He is definitely strange, right?
- I mean...
- You make me laugh.
- He is definitely strange, right?
I mean...
It was going well at first.
(My goodness!)
(The actors have given
an exceptional performance.)
It's him. It's him.
- What is that?
- It's him.
- Is he channeling Gollum or what?
- That's Gollum.
- It's him.
- I mean...
The quality fell drastically.
Is he channeling Gollum or what?
Gollum of "The Lord of the Rings".
Okay, I got it.
(Is it "Mission: Impossible"?)
- Is it right?
- You can't ask for a hint.
(If So Min gets it right,)
(they can narrow down
the criminal candidates.)
Gollum? "The Lord of the Rings"?
Gollum?
(Will So Min get the answer right
despite Haha's terrible acting?)
Gollum of "The Lord of the Rings".
You can't ask for a hint.
"The Thieves".
("The Thieves")
(Correct)
(She got the answer right
in a surprising turn of events.)
- How did she get it right?
- See?
- I am not a criminal.
- You were Gollum.
(Korean and Chinese thieves join
to steal a diamond in Macau.)
(Sang Ho and Dae Myeung
created this miracle.)
That was incredible.
I knew it was "The Thieves".
Right?
- I knew it.
- You were Gollum.
No, I wasn't.
She is a genius.
How did she know?
(Haha's chaotic performance
couldn't deter her.)
Sang Ho and Dae Myeung
did an amazing job.
Their performances had
so much depth.
We saw Haha's acting skills
from "Holy Daddy".
- Right?
- We enjoyed your performance.
- "Holy Daddy".
Haha's acting skills
from "Holy Daddy".
I will reveal the identity
of one person...
who isn't a criminal.
That person would be
a civilian or a police officer.
Okay.
To the two criminals,
we will reveal...
the identity of one person
who isn't a police officer.
The criminals will know,
"That person is a civilian,"
"not a police officer."
One person who definitely isn't
a criminal is...
(He picks one at random.)
(Song Ji Hyo)
Song Ji Hyo.
I knew that.
I'm just a citizen.
As for the criminals,
we will pick one at random...
and relay the information
via a text.
- A text?
- To the criminals?
Why don't you tell the criminals
to come forward?
(Whose identity
did the criminals get?)
- We will keep our eyes closed.
- That's right.
It's time for the final race.
It's your last chance to arrest
the two criminals...
who are hiding among
innocent civilians.
Through the 2 interrogations
that open every 30 minutes,
you can arrest the criminals.
If you arrest both criminals,
the police officers
and civilians win.
If you fail to arrest
the criminals...
or all the police officers
get eliminated first,
the criminals win.
Every 30 minutes, we will gather
in the interrogation room.
You can vote
for a criminal candidate...
and check the identity of the person
who gets the most number of votes.
Inside the building,
10 members' name tags are hidden.
If you turn in four name tags
at the detective agency,
you will see
if there are more police officers,
more criminals,
or the same number of both.
- We will see that.
- You will see that.
If all four people are civilians,
you will get,
"There are neither criminals
nor police officers."
(There are neither criminals
nor police officers.)
If we add Ji Hyo's name tag,
the result will be more helpful.
(The combination of name tags
is very important.)
We will announce the result
to everyone...
without revealing
the four name tags.
Then we will be able to lie
about the four names.
(The criminal will be able to lie
about the 4 names.)
Now, please move to your spot.
Let's go!
The last game made me certain...
that something's up
with Kwang Soo and Haha.
That's what I think.
(Ji Hyo is suspicious
of Kwang Soo and Haha.)
(She is a civilian!)
It definitely seemed like...
Do Won guessed the answer wrong
on purpose.
Jae Suk and Haha.
(Do Won thinks the criminals are
Jae Suk and Haha.)
When Jae Suk describing the movie,
he was too clumsy.
I think either Haha or Kwang Soo is
a criminal.
(What could be
the identity of these 4 people?)
I will stick the name tag
before the race begins.
Okay.
(The person
with the police officer name tag,)
(Kim Dae Myeung)
Today, you will have
the Domestic Investigation Race.
You are a senior police officer
and a newbie police officer...
who infiltrated
a morning soccer club...
after receiving a tip-off...
that some criminals are smugging out
seasoned salt.
So 2 police officers need to catch
2 criminals.
We need to catch two criminals
among civilians.
Song Ji Hyo.
(Even after the second mission,)
(Dae Myeung stayed alert
since he is a police officer.)
I will do my best.
(Will Dae Myeung be able
to arrest the 2 criminals?)
The race will begin.
Five,
4, 3...
2, 1.
The race starts.
Finding the name tags is a priority,
right?
(They diligently search
for the name tags.)
Does everyone search this way?
(The name tags
are hidden very carefully.)
What?
(Looking around)
A really nice camera
is following you around...
right now.
- Right?
- Yes.
Why is it following you around?
I guess I will do something.
I don't know what,
but I guess I will do something.
You are suspicious.
You are too suspicious.
- Where are you going?
- I am going to find the name tags.
Should I stay here?
- No, no. Let's meet later.
- Should I...
- Later? Can I move?
- See you later.
Of course. You should move.
(Sang Ho made a suspicious comment.
What could be his identity?)
Jae Suk. Earlier, Do Won...
- I hear Kwang Soo's voice.
- He made sure...
(He puts on a kind smile.)
What's your role for today?
I am nothing.
I think he is playing a role today.
Me?
That's right. How did you know?
(He holds his hands together.)
(He moves his hands awkwardly.)
- Wasn't it really awkward?
- Jae Suk.
It was the worst performance
I have seen in my life.
- "How did you know?"
- Who rubs hands together like that?
It's not like that.
You should find the name tags...
and stop being suspicious of me.
Suk Jin,
just get your name tag ripped off
and go to the jail.
If we stay too far from Jong Kook,
- he will become suspicious.
- You are right.
- Why are you...
- We were on his way to find him.
There is nothing.
(Meanwhile,
Dae Myeung the police officer...)
(is searching diligently.)
- Welcome.
- Gosh, that startled me.
Insert your card...
- Welcome.
- Gosh, that startled me.
(Gosh, that startled me.)
(The newbie police officer
gets startled about everything.)
(Peeking)
Dae Myeung.
(Flinching)
What are you doing? What's there?
- Dae Myeung.
- Yes?
You are a civilian, right?
- Me?
- Yes.
(Thinking)
What's good about it?
Just tell me what your identity is.
- Are you a civilian?
- You seem like a civilian.
I am a civilian.
(Meanwhile,
Haha is looking for a name tag.)
(He finally finds a name tag.)
(The name tag he found belongs...)
(to himself.)
It's mine.
(He acquired his own name tag.)
It'd be easier to figure out.
(If he acquires 3 more name tags,
he can go to the Detective Agency.)
(Sang Ho finds something too.)
I found one.
(He acquires a criminal candidate,
Do Won's name tag.)
I need to find them fast.
(He takes off his shoes
and searches diligently.)
Do Won.
Did you find something?
No.
Am I really supposed to search
every room?
You know two people
who aren't criminals, right?
Two people who aren't criminals.
- You got the names as a hint.
- That's right.
(Do Won claimed that he asked
for 2 people who aren't criminals.)
Who were they?
Well,
I don't know if I should tell you.
- You shouldn't, Do Won.
- I shouldn't, right?
- You shouldn't.
- But you can tell...
those two people.
You can tell those two people
since they aren't criminals.
- Right?
- You can tell Ji Hyo.
(Torn)
Ji Hyo and her.
- Was So Min one of them?
- Yes.
(Ji Hyo and her.)
(Do Won claims
that So Min is a civilian.)
- Was she 1 of them?
- I was?
Yes. She is a civilian.
- I am a civilian.
- Was it a good idea to tell you?
Was it? It wasn't, right?
- To be honest...
- You could be a criminal.
I could be a criminal,
so you shouldn't share information
unless you are certain.
Seriously.
- You shouldn't do that.
- No.
- You are right.
To be honest,
I am suspicious of Jae Suk.
Me? Why?
Did you receive a hint?
No, I didn't. It's just a hunch.
- For goodness' sake.
- A hint...
(Do Won stares intently.)
Now...
(He averts his eyes.)
- Jae Suk.
- What?
What?
(He suddenly changed the subject.)
Come on.
I am not a criminal.
(Stern)
Are you just a fool?
- What are you saying?
- Are you just a fool?
(Do Won does some fact-checking
without a warning.)
What are you saying?
I am a civilian.
You are suspicious too.
He is just a fool.
But...
I think...
(Her name tag almost got ripped off
due to the frame.)
Someone who does that
is a bigger fool, don't you think?
She almost got eliminated
because her name tag got caught.
Had it come off,
you would have gotten eliminated.
Really? Really?
The name tags wouldn't be here,
right?
Let's search a bit more.
- Would they be someplace visible?
- We should go upstairs.
I don't think we should stay here.
- Ji Hyo, did you find something?
- It looks like you did.
I didn't find anything.
The layout of this building
is difficult today.
- Seriously.
- What?
I heard you go, "What?"
- What is this?
- What?
(What is this doing here?)
- I know what it is.
- Seasoned salt.
(Do Won passed security
with soccer balls.)
(Seasoned salt came out
of the soccer ball.)
- What is it doing here?
- Keep it.
Do the criminals need to find this?
I bet the criminals
need to find this.
(Do the criminals need
the seasoned salt?)
(Dae Myeung is absorbed
in looking for the name tags.)
(He spots something!)
(Dae Myeung finds
the seasoned salt as well.)
(However,)
(he glances around...)
(and bags the seasoned salt.)
(Why is a police officer bagging
the seasoned salt?)
(The police officers' hidden rule)
(1 pack of seasoned salt...)
(equals 1 blank name tag.)
(Police officers can use it
as a name tag of their choice.)
I don't have much time.
- Suk Jin.
- You don't seem like a criminal.
- You are working very hard today.
After we collect four name tags,
let's call Ji Hyo over.
Let's make her go in.
- My goodness.
- It's a good idea.
- Did you find anything?
- Listen.
- Name tag.
- Does anyone have a name tag?
- I have one.
- Really?
- I have 1.
- Then we have 4.
- We have four.
- What?
- We can't trust anyone right now.
- That's right.
Let's give the name tags to Ji Hyo
so that we can go in...
- and check.
- That works.
Ji Hyo is a civilian anyway.
(The Detective Agency exists
at every building.)
(If you take 4 name tags,
you can see...)
(the ratio of the police officers
and criminals.)
- Haha.
- All right.
- Kwang Soo.
- Suk Jin. Who is the last one?
- Do Won.
- I think...
- We have four name tags.
- Let's take these...
- to Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
Let's find Ji Hyo.
We have
Haha and Kwang Soo's name tags.
- I know.
- This is insane.
- This is unbelievable.
- Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo, come here.
Yes?
- Come here.
- Hurry up.
- You are safe.
- We have a mission for you.
- Ji Hyo, go ahead.
- Okay.
- All right.
(She has 4 name tags in her hand.)
I took on a big mission.
Suk Jin, Do Won, Kwang Soo,
and Haha.
(She submits the four name tags.)
Ji Hyo has no reason to lie.
She has no reason to lie.
We are 50 percent there.
That's right. We are nearly there.
Whose name tags did she take?
Haha, me...
- Do Won and me.
- Kwang Soo, calm down.
I am just happy that I will be able
to focus on the race now.
Calm down.
Do Won and Suk Jin. Okay.
(The result finally comes out.)
It's out.
(What the ratio of the criminals
and police officers?)
(No way!)
- She's here!.
- The Detective Agency...
- Don't say anything yet.
- Everyone, be quiet.
According to the result...
(More police officers or criminals,
the same number of both, or neither)
(What's the ratio
among these 4 members?)
The number is equivalent.
- What?
(The same number
of police officers and criminals?)
The ratio?
- Really?
- Then...
There could be one of each...
- or two of each.
- Yes, one of each.
- Police officers and criminals...
- The same number.
They are in the same number.
There is either 1 of each
or 2 of each.
- In that case...
- Two of each is unlikely.
- It's unlikely.
There must be one of each.
(Everyone is busy deducting.)
(Dae Myeung shows
a meaningful smile.)
The first race is over.
Come to the Interrogation Room.
You acted so strange at times.
I don't have a clue today.
There wasn't Jae Suk's name tag.
I am not a criminal.
He could be the second criminal.
I think my initial guess was
completely off.
It's time
for the first interrogation.
Currently, there are
a total of 10 people remaining...
which includes 2 criminals
and 2 police officers.
Please discuss freely...
and arrest a criminal later on
with a vote.
All right.
(Who will be picked as a criminal
after the first interrogation?)
Let's make our guesses
based on the result we got...
- from the Detective Agency.
- Let's do that.
- Leave this to us.
- Okay.
- We shouldn't start...
- anywhere else.
- At first,
I received two hints.
(I received two hints.)
(Do Won received a hint
after the first mission.)
- That's right.
- There we go.
You should tell us what you know.
- Hold on.
- Why didn't you tell us sooner?
- I will tell you now.
- But we don't know...
if he will speak truthfully.
- Since I wasn't sure.
- This is important.
You know, Do Won looks...
a bit like a retired detective.
(He looks
a bit like a retired detective.)
(He is 100 percent in sync
with the position.)
- Right?
- That's right.
Do Won looks
a bit like a retired detective.
- A private investigator.
- He works as one now.
He quit and began to work
as a private investigator.
I will share what I know
to prevent civilian casualties.
- You should do that.
- You should.
That's right. You should tell us.
I ask that you trust me to be...
- a civilian.
- Okay.
Two people who aren't criminals.
The man with a kind face, Sang Ho.
Where is he?
- Sang Ho.
- He has a kind face.
- He isn't a criminal.
- He isn't?
- In the beginning...
I don't think
Sang Ho is a criminal either.
- Go on.
- And the other one is...
the woman who got the answers right
like a genius in the mission,
- So Min. She isn't a criminal.
- So Min.
- I told you that I am not.
- Did you get her name?
- The staff randomly picked,
- and they got Sang Ho and So Min?
- and there was So Min's name.
- So Min isn't a criminal.
- Really?
- I knew it.
- Why wouldn't you believe him?
- I knew you weren't a criminal.
- I knew it.
- So Min isn't a criminal.
- It's that jerk.
(Suddenly)
(Incredulous)
What are you saying?
(Is Do Won's claim true?)
Kwang Soo, do something
about your hands.
- Seriously.
- Can't you relax your hands?
He is definitely a criminal.
(He makes hearts.)
I am not a criminal.
If Do Won is a criminal...
- There could be a police officer.
- Right.
It's ironic...
- because the ones that came up...
- "Ironic"?
Why did you suddenly use
the word, "Ironic"?
Doesn't it suit the situation?
Go ahead and tell me!
No, no.
Doesn't it suit the situation?
- I doubt you know what it means.
- "Ironic".
Isn't this an ironic situation?
Can you spell it?
- "Ironic".
- Hold on.
Is it an English word?
He asks if it's an English word.
- Didn't you know?
- He asks if it's an English word.
My goodness.
When you say it's ironic...
- Do you know what's strange?
- Do Won...
I don't know who the criminals are.
I have a hunch.
Dae Myeung is strange.
Is Dae Myeung strange?
- He is strange.
- Dae Myeung is strange.
I think he has a different agenda.
- Yes. He is a bit different.
- I am a civilian,
but he seems to be looking
for something different.
He could be something else.
For example, if he's a civilian...
just like me,
he would feel lonely,
so he would talk to the others.
But he seemed to try to
stay away from others.
- He must have his own mission.
- Exactly.
He and I were alone together
in this building.
- He had to find something.
- Exactly.
- He's suspicious.
- Somehow, he seems...
- Kwang Soo.
- Why are you acting weird?
Kwang Soo, make up your mind
whether to swallow saliva or...
- I can tell it's in his mouth.
- My gosh.
(Kwang Soo can't seem to swallow
saliva maybe because he's nervous.)
- I can tell...
- But...
Can't I do whatever I want
with my saliva?
What's with you?
I wanted to...
I wanted to play with it
in my mouth.
Why would he...
- I wanted to play with it.
- But why...
(Laughing loudly)
(Laughing hard)
(He's laughing so hard
that he can't breathe.)
My, this is hilarious.
My stomach hurts. Oh, my stomach.
(Laughing)
Hey, Do Won.
What's so funny?
- What's with him?
- Hang on a second.
- Are you done?
- Is laughing like that weirder?
- Or not swallowing saliva weirder?
- What...
- What is wrong with him?
- Who are you to tell me what to do?
- It's my saliva.
- What's wrong with Do Won?
- Swallow it or spit it out,
- It's hilarious.
- it's my decision to make.
- They're so funny.
- Do Won, are you...
- Because you were looking at me...
(Laughing quietly)
(While Do Won is laughing so hard
that he cries...)
- How did you...
- I wanted to play with my saliva.
- Hey, you. Dae Myeung.
- You don't have to explain it.
- Why aren't you laughing?
- What?
(He got caught.)
- He rarely laughs.
- Why aren't you laughing?
(The man who can't laugh next to
the man who can't stop laughing)
Why won't he laugh?
I just... It's not like that.
- He can't laugh.
- Why won't he laugh?
Seriously, why won't he laugh?
It's not that I couldn't swallow it.
I didn't swallow it.
(The man who keeps laughing,
the man who can't swallow saliva,)
(the man who can't laugh)
Does saliva matter now?
- It has nothing to do with this.
- Is that so?
- My goodness.
- It's weird whether you laugh hard,
- or not laugh at all.
- Exactly.
- Everyone is weird all of a sudden.
Here's a thought.
It's just my opinion.
(Kwang Soo suggests his opinion
to find the criminal.)
Do Won said the names of those
who are not the criminal...
- loudly enough for us all to hear.
- Yes, he did.
- You all heard him, right?
- Yes.
That means...
he's either a police officer
or a civilian.
Because he said it loudly.
However, that might've been
his intention.
- What did you say?
- What was that?
(He pronounced a word strangely.)
- What does that mean?
- What's with your pronunciation?
- Why did you say it like that?
- What did you say?
- He did it on purpose...
- What did you say again?
I think...
- Your lips...
- Your mouth is dry.
stuck to the teeth
because your mouth was dry.
If you'd had enough saliva,
you would've pronounced it properly.
- Repeat after me.
- We found the criminal too soon.
This is crazy.
Has everyone picked me?
- No, it's not like that.
- We were just discussing.
- We should put it to a vote.
- Then...
- I'll show you something...
- That's true, but...
- Those two are not the criminal.
- Kwang Soo will show us something.
I won't show it to all of you.
- Really?
- What is it?
- I think he has a big hint.
- A big hint?
Wait.
Then Ji Hyo and...
(What will Kwang Soo show everyone
when they're suspecting him?)
- What? He has a lot.
- How did he find so many?
(He has so many name tags.)
He has a lot.
My gosh.
- How?
- Why do you have so many of them?
- I bet those are blank.
- I...
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- I know...
- You know what?
- This is the one I gave you.
- But I couldn't find any.
- "Kwak Do Won". What's this?
- And who else?
- I already visited there.
- What?
- Really?
- You visited the Detective Agency?
- Yes, I did.
(He already the Detective Agency?)
- That doesn't make sense.
- How did he get so many...
- He found so many of them alone.
- I visited there.
- It's Dae Myeung's.
- Whose are they?
(He got everyone's attention.)
Wait. It's Dae Myeung's.
You found all of these?
- Did you use them?
- That's Suk Jin's.
- I visited there.
- Is it true?
- Yes.
- Which Detective Agency...
- Then why wasn't it announced?
- That's a good point.
That's a good point. That's odd.
- You brat.
- He's lying.
(The result would've been announced
if he had been there.)
Gosh. He lied again.
- You brat.
- He's lying.
(Ji Hyo pointed out
an important fact.)
Gosh. He lied again.
He must have brought...
the used ones.
- I wish we'd heard him out.
- This is unbelievable.
- He stole them from the staff.
- You should give him...
- We should've heard him out.
- It wasn't announced.
- All right. Okay.
- How could he...
- He lied.
- Okay. I admit it.
- I admit it.
- That was close.
Hear me out.
- These...
- One.
- You're right.
- Two.
- I stole these at the office.
- Three.
- Right? I was right about that.
- Yes.
- I found them in a big bag.
- Hey.
(Earlier on, Kwang Soo was
looking for a hint.)
(Rummaging)
(He found the name tags
in the staff's bag.)
(His criminal instinct kicked in.)
(He made fake hints
in a dishonest way.)
(Kwang Soo, the petty offender,
left after making fake hints.)
I cut them
and put them in the envelopes.
- These are fake.
- Did you know this?
- This is...
- They're fake.
- Why did you do that?
- Exactly. Why did you do that?
It looked like you were going to
narrow it down to me.
I did it to prove that I'm not.
He pronounced the word strangely
because he was nervous.
(Was it because he was nervous?)
- "I was cornered..."
- It doesn't mean...
that I'm the criminal.
That's enough!
(He even used violence in the end.)
It's not because I'm the criminal!
He's the criminal.
He just proved it.
My goodness.
- Listen.
- It's over.
- But...
- Hey.
We must eliminate him even if
he's a civilian. Do you know why?
- He confuses us.
- Absolutely. He's weird.
- Wait.
- We must eliminate him.
Let's start the voting.
The person who gets the most votes
will be revealed and out right away.
- Goodbye, Kwang Soo.
- Why would he show us that?
We have no choice.
But Kwang Soo...
Whenever we do things like this...
- But you know...
- Wait.
Let me say something
for the last time.
But we all voted already.
Why were you so impatient?
Why didn't you hear me out?
- Tell us why you're not.
- I'll tell you.
Tell us something that's true.
I am...
(He barely got the chance
to defend himself.)
(Will he say something
that can convince them this time?)
the police officer.
(I am the police officer.)
(Kwang Soo is...)
(the police officer?)
Gosh, that's ridiculous.
(Gosh, that's ridiculous.)
Well, I'm going to...
I'll go out to find the next one.
(Ridiculous?)
(It's not worth hearing.)
I'll just... I'll go out...
- Wait.
- I'll go out to find the next one.
Is he really the police officer?
- I am the police officer.
- Is he?
I'm the police officer.
If I get eliminated,
- and if I'm the police officer...
- Yes. Who?
(While claiming that he's
the police officer to the end,)
You think it's Haha?
(he picked
the most suspicious person.)
(He picked Haha.)
It's your last word.
- Okay. I get it.
- If I'm the police officer...
I have 2 name tags. If anyone also
has 2, let's submit them together.
Let's go straight to
the Detective Agency.
- I have one too.
- Let's go together.
I'm so curious if that's true.
- If it's true, I'd be shocked.
- Right?
- The result came out.
- Okay.
I'll announce the result of
the first interrogation.
- Kwang Soo got the most votes.
- I knew it.
- Kwang Soo...
- Did everyone vote for me?
- Tell us his identity.
- I can't tell you that.
Can someone take off...
- His name tag?
- his name tag? Please stand here.
I'll be shocked
if he's the police officer.
What happens
if he's the police officer?
We'll have to start over again.
- He's definitely the criminal.
- Just remember this.
- Those who suspected me...
- Never.
One.
(Kwang Soo claimed
he's the police officer at the end.)
Two.
(What could be his real identity?)
(Police Officer)
(He's the police officer.)
(Unbelievable!)
(The newcomer Dae Myeung's
senior police officer was...)
(Kwang Soo.)
(Kicking)
(He really is a police officer.)
You should have told us sooner.
(I told you
I was the police officer!)
- You should've told us sooner.
- Jae Suk is suspicious too.
- Why didn't you tell us?
- Why didn't you, you fool?
The criminal...
- Did you ask why didn't I tell you?
- I mean, if you were...
- I told you that and showed you...
- This is shocking.
You two are junior and senior
police officers.
(He worked undercover
with Dae Myeung.)
Did you find any?
- Did you find any?
- No.
I found one, but my name was on it.
- Really?
- Yes.
If you find mine, tell everyone.
- I won't tell anyone...
- You should tell everyone.
(Unlike how he led the team,)
(he was picked as the criminal.)
(Dae Myeung looked away from him.)
(Dae Myeung,
why aren't you laughing?)
(Awkward)
(Dae Myeung lacked experience
as a newcomer police officer.)
(He turned a blind eye to him
to avoid being suspected.)
- You should've told us that.
- You should've told us sooner.
But I don't know
who the criminals are.
- You should've told us sooner.
- There would've been someone...
- who tried to save you.
- Exactly.
- You should've told us that first.
- But I don't know who they are.
- We would've...
- You should have worked...
- with Ji Hyo who is a civilian.
- You should've told us.
But she wouldn't believe me.
- Exactly. You should've told us.
- Instead, you lied to us.
- Why did you show us the name tags?
- Exactly.
- That was totally pointless.
- Indeed.
You were all suspecting me
from the start.
- We're in trouble.
- Gosh, seriously.
Haha does seem anxious right now.
No. I... I'm confident.
(Who could be the two criminals?)
We should find them quickly.
We're in trouble.
(The police officer is out.)
(1 of the 3 of them is
1 of the criminals.)
The first interrogation session
is over.
Now, we'll begin the 2nd session
in 30 minutes.
- Dae Myeung is suspicious.
- Yes?
(They are trying to find out
who the criminals are.)
His behaviors were suspicious.
As if he was afraid
we might found out about him...
I know he had his own strategy,
- but it was too obvious.
- A criminal or police officer.
- He's either one of them.
- He must be a criminal.
- A criminal?
- Yes, he's a criminal.
Do Won is suspicious too.
He does laugh loudly like he did.
- I know.
- But his reactions are too loud.
We already know
one of the police officers,
so there's a higher chance
of him being a criminal.
That's what I'm saying.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is moving
to the jail.)
I had no choice.
I'm okay with everything else,
but I was most hurt...
when you ignored me
when I looked at you.
I thought that if I sympathized
with you at that moment,
- we would both die.
- I understand.
But I kept looking at you.
I will succeed no matter what.
I kept looking at you,
but you turned away.
(He cut ties with him
when they locked eyes.)
That's what you did.
(They got further away
from each other.)
But if you win,
- we both win.
- Okay.
Catch them no matter what.
(Dae Myeung must find
the 2 criminals...)
(for the citizens
and police officers to win.)
Is it still like that?
(The police officer, Dae Myeung,
looks for someone.)
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- All of a sudden...
(He has a rendezvous with
Ji Hyo, who's definitely a citizen.)
- I have this.
- Right.
I'm actually a police officer.
Please help me.
Really?
(The lone rookie officer begins
to win over the citizens.)
(He plans to find the criminals
by working with the citizens.)
Okay.
(The prime suspect, Do Won,
appears at that moment.)
- Did you find anything?
- No. I didn't.
You're a criminal, right?
You punk.
No, I'm not.
You're the criminal, right?
Are you a police officer then?
I'm a citizen.
He's a citizen.
- Did you find anything?
- I didn't find a single thing.
I need to find something.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo,
the conversation ends naturally.)
(Sighing)
It's not him.
(It's not him.)
I should find them quickly.
- What?
- What? Did you find something?
You surprised me.
- Do Won.
- I heard someone laugh.
I don't know if we're looking
for the same thing, Do Won.
(Full of suspicion)
So Min! The look in your eyes
has changed.
(Do Won became the prime suspect
after the first interrogation.)
If that's the case,
why would I give you the hint?
None of you knew it.
Why would I tell you
who the two citizens were?
- Why did you?
It's because you're the criminal,
you punk.
Do Won.
- You're good at cornering people.
- No, I'm not.
(The two prime suspects, Haha
and Do Won, have a battle of wits.)
You're incredible.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk is...)
Why do I find you to be
so suspicious?
Come on, Sang Ho.
- There's nothing to suspect.
- Sang Ho.
Come over here.
- I'm sorry.
- You're hurting my feelings.
Jae Suk.
- How could you do that...
- I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
- My gosh.
(Ji Hyo left Jae Suk out
and brought Sang Ho with her.)
- Dae Myeung is...
- Yes?
a police officer.
He's a police officer?
That's why
he didn't say anything earlier.
That's why he didn't say anything
since before.
(The rookie police officer is busy
looking for name tags.)
(He finds a name tag.)
(He got Ji Hyo's name tag.)
(He even found Jae Suk's name tag.)
(Yoo Jae Suk)
(Including Haha's name tag,
he has 3 name tags.)
(He looks around...)
(and enters the Detective Agency.)
(At that moment!)
(Do Won spots Dae Myeung going in.)
(Dae Myeung doesn't know
Do Won saw him and enters.)
Let me check.
(He needs 4 name tags to check.)
(He submits the name tag
and the seasoned salt.)
The name of the salt is...
Kim Dae Myeung.
(He exchanges it with
his own name tag.)
(He submits the name tags of
a police officer and a citizen...)
(as well as the name tags of
2 prime suspects.)
(1. If there are more criminals,
Haha and Jae Seo are criminals.)
(2. If there are
more police officers,)
(Haha and Jae Suk are citizens.)
(If there are equivalent, either
Haha or Jae Suk is a criminal.)
(What are the results
from the Detective Agency?)
(The number of criminals
and police officers is the same?)
(As a result,)
(1 of these 2 is a criminal.)
(Dae Myeung found out
from the Detective Agency that...)
(either Haha or Jae Suk
is a criminal.)
According to the Detective Agency,
the number of criminals and
police officers is the same.
I wonder whose name tags
they submitted.
It's equivalent?
You submitted it just now, right?
- They submitted it?
- They did.
But there was the same number.
We don't know who was submitted.
Is that so?
We need to find out though.
(They all move to find Dae Myeung.)
- Dae Myeung. Who did you submit?
- Dae Myeung.
Who did you submit?
- I didn't find any.
- We heard you submitted it.
- What do you mean?
- Everyone knows.
- There was an announcement.
Me? I didn't submit anything.
(He plays innocent.)
- Oh, my.
- Look at him.
(Dae Myeung lies out of haste
without figuring out the situation.)
There was an announcement.
If it was you
and the results came out,
- tell us who the citizens are.
- Share with us.
Tell someone who has been confirmed
as a citizen.
Tell someone like Ji Hyo or So Min.
I heard you submitted it.
How did you do it?
- Everyone knows.
- Dae Myeung is...
- I really didn't submit them.
- Dae Myeung was...
a bit scared,
- so I think he lied on a whim.
- He lied.
There was an announcement
that the number is equal.
Don't reveal everything, but just...
(One slip of the tongue
leads to Dae Myeung's crisis.)
- Tell a citizen. Tell Ji Hyo.
- Wait.
- Tell Ji Hyo.
Tell Ji Hyo. Hurry.
Hurry up and go.
(Ripping)
(What? He ripped off the name tag?)
What was that?
- What?
- What was that?
Hurry up and do it.
(Dae Myeung's attack happened
in a blink of an eye.)
(About 20 minutes ago,
during the first interrogation)
(Kwang Soo told Dae Myeung
that Haha was the criminal.)
(The Detective Agency results said
1 of these 3 was the criminal.)
(Kwang Soo said it was Haha.)
(If you see Haha,
rip off his name tag.)
(He decided to attack as a part of
his contingency plan.)
(He attacked the prime suspect,
Haha, in the time of crisis.)
(What is Haha's identity?)
What was that?
(Haha is a citizen.)
(What?)
(Why is he a citizen?)
What did you do?
- Why did he do that just now?
- He thought you were a criminal.
- He's a citizen.
- Why did you rip his name tag off?
- Why did he do that just now?
- He thought you were a criminal.
(Dae Myeung the police officer's
attack ended in failure.)
I told you.
You fool.
He was a citizen. Oh, no.
You should've discussed it first.
- Let's protect him.
- We had no idea.
- Then...
- Let's protect him.
We're in trouble because
he ripped off his name tag.
(According to the first results,
the remaining suspect is...)
Oh, my.
- Is it Suk Jin then?
- Okay.
(Suk Jin
eliminated Kim Dae Myeung.)
Is it Suk Jin then?
(Before Do Won could finish,
Suk Jin attacked Dae Myeung.)
Okay. Yes!
(Then...)
(Does that mean...)
- He doesn't know anything.
- You're a police officer.
Hold on.
- What is this?
- What is going on?
(The last police officer,
Kim Dae Myeung, is out.)
- What is this?
- What is going on?
(Nobody suspected him.)
- What?
- You are the criminal?
Are you the criminal?
Yes, I am.
(Ji Suk Jin, the criminal)
Last week, you had a big role...
- as the boss of Petty Gang,
- Right.
but you couldn't escape
and lost the race.
We'll give you a chance
to make up for it today.
(A chance for revenge came
after a week)
We thought it might be hard
for you to do it alone,
so we brought you
a right-hand man.
(Because it's a hard task
to do alone,)
(the right-hand man of
Petty Gang joins.)
(The right-hand man of Petty Gang,
Yoo Jae Suk)
- Hello.
- Come here.
- My right-hand man.
- He's a weakling.
- This...
We're in trouble this week too.
The two of us can't do anything.
My right-hand man.
I'm not the type to be able
to work for someone.
I'm the boss of Petty Gang.
- Again?
- You're my right-hand man.
I made the Petty Gang,
but why is he the boss?
Today's results will determine...
whether or not we'll keep this...
- Petty Gang universe.
- Why would we keep it?
We should. Petty Gang is nice.
And it's nice for you
to be a right-hand man.
What's so nice about it?
I can't work for someone.
Don't think of it as working for me.
You're the next in line.
(The two criminals put the fate of
Petty Gang on the line.)
You can smuggle
in the seasoned salt by changing...
a real soccer ball with a ball
filled with seasoned salt.
- Then...
- Is it obvious which one it is?
Let's see.
We hope you are successful.
Okay. Don't worry.
(He complained, but he worked hard
as the right-hand man.)
(Jae Suk played a role in failing
at the group mission,)
(and prevented them
from getting hints.)
(Jae Suk, everyone is saying
that you're acting weird.)
(He escaped to a remote area
after his boss' warning.)
Even if I get eliminated,
it's okay because Suk Jin
has infiltrated them.
(You're not the criminal, right?)
(Sly)
(Boss Big Nose appeals...)
(to Do Won's kindness by saying
he had a role last week.)
(He gained everyone's trust and
survived by acting as a citizen.)
(Nobody suspected him, and they
involved him in their deductions.)
They're telling me everything.
There's something thrilling
about this.
(There's something thrilling
about this.)
He just said my name.
- Is this for real?
- What were you going to say?
No way.
What happened just now was...
I said, "Is it Suk Jin then?"
(The timing was amazing.)
That's why I ripped off
his name tag.
- This was so much fun.
- Why did you rip off Haha's?
- It was fun.
Ji Suk Jin ripped off
Kim Dae Myeung's name tag,
so the criminals won.
(Amazing)
(Smiling from ear to ear)
(Suk Jin did it?)
I can't believe this happened.
(Not even the right-hand man
expected this from the boss.)
Suk Jin ripped off
Dae Myeung's name tag?
(The final mission is over.)
My gosh.
This is really fun.
We should've shared the information.
We should've shared it.
I didn't trust anyone.
- I can't believe this.
- Gosh.
- Yes!
- I should've helped him.
You know what?
I belong to Petty Gang.
I can't believe this.
- I belong to Petty Gang too.
- Petty Gang.
Why would you have the tattoo?
- It's Petty Gang.
- Okay. Petty Gang.
Are we going to
keep using that gang?
We are petty gangsters
of Petty Gang.
Why did I trust Suk Jin?
Do Won was a citizen
who was caught up...
in the set-up crime.
Do Won was a citizen.
I thought he might be innocent,
but I couldn't trust him...
- because of his shirt.
- It's because of the shirt.
This is the story of our new movie.
I see.
The suspect, Do Won's team lost,
so Do Won and another person
will get a penalty.
Do Won, please pick a person
whom you want to get a penalty with.
Okay.
(Who'd be Do Won's penalty partner?)
- Dae Myeung.
- Yes?
(Dae Myeung...)
(He has a guilty look.)
Dae Myeung deserves it.
- He deserves it.
- I think...
- Dae Myeung should get a penalty.
- I'll gladly get a penalty.
The penalty is brushing your teeth
with bay salt...
which is known to be
good for your teeth.
- The penalty isn't that bad.
- It's nice.
This is a good thing.
Brush your teeth for 30 seconds.
Make sure to show that it's salty.
(Make sure to show that it's salty.)
My goodness.
(Why would he force them
to do things like that?)
(It is salty though.)
(Suk Jin forces the guests
to show some reactions.)
You're the worst.
He did a good job today,
so he's being condescending.
Do Won, are you all right?
- Gosh.
- Dae Myeung, are you okay?
It's all my fault.
And the winner, Petty Gang,
will get a prize.
What's the prize for Petty Gang?
You will get 10 movie tickets each.
- Really?
- That sounds great.
- Wow.
- It's a great gift.
It's really nice.
I hope you will enjoy good movies.
Please remember that
our movie will be a lot more fun.
Please watch it.
(It's an objective review
by the leading actor.)
- "The Golden Holiday" is fun.
- It's "The Golden Holiday".
Please enjoy the movie. Thank you.
- Thank you.
(We'd like to thank Do Won, Sang Ho,
and Dae Myeung for joining us.)
(Once you shoot the gun,
it will be pandemonium.)
(We're not going to die like this.)
(It's time! Shoot it.)
I'm a legendary sniper.
(With balloons on their backs,)
(the legendary snipers
have a gunfight.)
(But...)
(they are connected
to each other with some rope.)
(Those who are connected...)
(are one team.)
(United they stand,
and divided they fall.)
(If they want to sever the link,)
(they have to raise
the average standard.)
(They have some activities that are
as thrilling as the Nevis Swing.)
(With this link,)
(who will be
the last one to survive?)
(The link average race,
Cut Off to Survive)