The leaves are turning red.
(It's fall, the season of
fall men and women.)
You look like
you can never be a thief.
It was my day off.
It's not easy to work
with stupid guys.
I'm his right-hand man?
How do you think we'll do today?
We all look great.
He's a human weapon.
I'm a thief.
Why am I the right-hand man
of Petty Gang?
Of course,
you're the right-hand man.
- Am I wrong?
- I'm a petty thief.
Hello.
- Hello.
- What are you doing?
- Who are you greeting?
- Pardon?
Are you saying hi to the air?
- Gosh, seriously.
- I think...
- he's immersed in his character.
- I think so too.
- There's no one here.
- What is he talking about?
This is role play
where there's no one else here.
What do you mean by that?
Even thieves must be polite.
- Hello, Chan Hee.
- Hello.
What are you doing?
Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- What's with his outfit?
I got confused about today's theme.
- You look great in this suit.
- And I dressed too casually.
I had to change my clothes
before the shoot.
He's wearing his stylist's jacket.
You look like one of those
hipsters at Hongdae.
- You think you're one of them?
- I dressed like a thief.
Suk Jin, are you going to
attend a funeral?
Hey.
- You look like...
- Suk Jin.
Can you give them
my condolence money for me?
- Are you going to attend a funeral?
- I'm...
- I'm a hero in black.
- What?
- Are you dressed as Tae Jin Ah?
- No, I'm a magician.
He pulled a dove out of his hat.
(Kwang Soo is his assistant.)
- Look.
- He can pull out a rabbit.
- What was that?
- You saw that, right?
I thought you were dressed
as Tae Jin Ah.
- The boss and the right-hand man?
- By the way...
Why am I the right-hand man
of Petty Gang?
- Are you the left-hand man?
- I mean, I'm powerful enough...
- to merge his gang into mine.
- That's ridiculous.
There are a lot of people
in my gang.
- Jae Suk is his senior comedian.
- Exactly.
Okay. Let's say...
that I'm the real power
of Petty Gang,
- and he's the boss with no power.
- No.
The person who looks best...
Jong Kook, are you
going somewhere...
to punish someone?
He looks so scary when he's just
wearing a black shirt.
- Are you going to beat someone up?
- Today...
I have some work to do.
- He looks so scary.
- Indeed.
- He looks really scary.
- He does look like a human weapon.
I have some work to do later.
- "Invader"? You dressed boring.
- He looks scary.
(Suk Jin is nitpicking
at everyone.)
- She doesn't look boring. You do.
- I don't look boring.
- You look most boring among us.
- She looks boring.
- She looks flashy.
- You're in no position to say that.
She doesn't look charismatic at all.
If you see the back, it's like
killing 2 birds with 1 stone.
- She's like a chameleon.
- Is this real leather?
2 birds with 1 stone?
(2 birds with 1 stone?)
She used a four-character idiom.
- Ji Hyo, have you been studying?
- No.
- Then how do you know that idiom?
- Of course, I know that.
I think she learned the idiom
while playing cards.
That's possible.
You mean, the online card game?
- So Min.
- Yes?
Isn't she too dressed up?
Your outfit is gorgeous,
but isn't it too much?
I stole this necklace.
- Really?
- You stole it?
It's stuck on my neck
because I'm a human magnet.
- It's a metal necklace.
- She actually stole it.
(He's trying to set her up.)
Today, you are...
criminals who committed crimes
in different areas of the country.
- I see.
- That's cool.
You were invited by the chairperson
of the Tomb Robbery Association.
- Because we're good at what we do.
- Exactly.
- The chairperson invited us?
- We have great abilities.
I rarely accept an invitation
like this.
To be exact, I'm amazing,
and Suk Jin is just okay.
No, it's the opposite.
- I'm much better than him.
- Mr. Amazing and Mr. Okay.
- Ji-kay and Yu-mazing.
- "Ji-kay"?
- I like that. Ji-kay sounds cool.
- Ji-kay.
- Ji-kay's so cool.
- "Ji-kay's so cool."
- Cool.
- I like that.
- That suits him.
That's so cool.
- He likes it.
- He looks happy.
- Suk Jin likes it.
- He's happy with it.
- "Ji-kay's cool."
- He's even blushing.
- He'll mention it on his broadcast.
- "Ji-kay's cool."
The major crime that the chairperson
planned for today is...
- robbing a tomb.
- A tomb robbery?
- We have two guests to join you.
- Oh, we have guests.
- We have guests today.
- Let's meet our guests.
- Please come out.
- Who could they be?
I think they're over there.
- They're coming to rob a tomb.
- Who are they?
It's a motorcycle.
- They're on a motorcycle.
- Where?
No, it's an ATV.
- What's going on?
- Who is he?
- Oh, my.
- It's an ATV.
(This man is riding across the lawn
showing off his masculinity.)
- Who is he?
- What's going on?
- That's Lee Je Hoon.
- Oh, my.
- Hey, Je Hoon!
- Je Hoon.
- Wait. Oh, he's Je Hoon?
That's Lee Je Hoon.
Hey, Je Hoon.
- That ATV...
- Did he steal that ATV as well?
(Who is he?)
Lee Je Hoon.
(Surprised)
She looks excited.
- You didn't know?
- Hi, Won Hee.
Didn't you know, So Min?
- So Min is surprised.
- Why?
So Min is so excited
that Je Hoon is here.
- Hello.
- It's been a long time.
(She gives a thumbs up only when
her favorite celebrity comes.)
So Min, look at him.
- He's glowing.
- Hi.
My, he's handsome.
(The next guest is showing up
amid raised expectations.)
That's Im Won Hee.
- Won Hee.
- Oh, my. Won Hee.
- Hi, Won Hee.
- It's been a while.
(Im Won Hee
with great screen presence)
We didn't order delivery food.
(We didn't order delivery food.)
His ATV looks...
- His ATV...
- Did he steal that ATV?
It's a type that you see
at tourist attractions.
He's acting so cool on it.
(Taken aback)
- Oh, no.
- I should've gone that way.
(He went the wrong way.)
Turn around.
(Won Hee turned his head
instead of the handle.)
(I'm going the wrong way.)
(He barely made his entrance
showing off his pitiful presence.)
- Won Hee.
Welcome, my dear Won Hee!
He's acquainted with Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook will help him
adapt to Running Man.)
- You're here, Won Hee.
- Hello.
Won Hee is here.
Hello.
- The star from "Dachimawa Lee".
- Won Hee.
- "You punks."
- You know...
I believe he doesn't need
any introduction.
I believe so too.
Gosh. These petty thieves
smelled the money.
- He has the vibe.
- Indeed.
- He's so handsome.
- He's glowing.
- As if he has a lamp inside of him.
- He's glowing. What did you say?
It's as if he has a lamp
inside his body.
So Min once said...
that Je Hoon who has plump lips...
- is her ideal type.
- Really?
- You...
- Who? Je Hoon?
(Her legs are wobbly.)
- You...
- Who? Je Hoon?
Why are your legs wobbly?
- I bet the information leaked.
- So Min said that.
I see why she...
That's not true.
- No wonder why she dressed up.
- I didn't realize...
- You knew he would be here, right?
- I bet she knew.
I really didn't know. I swear.
- I was really surprised.
- She's lying.
I always wanted to come back
on the show at least once...
- to redeem myself.
- You lost last time you were here.
- You must've been disappointed.
- Last time I was here,
I was covered in mud.
(Surprisingly, this is Je Hoon.)
Being covered in mud,
I felt so humiliated.
- I see.
- So...
- Right. I remember that.
- When he came on the show,
he gave me bad advice on stock
investment while hiding with me.
- Really?
- The stock price plunged.
- That's right.
- Really?
- I lost 30 percent.
- That's right. I heard that.
By the way, Won Hee,
how did the blind date go?
Oh, right. He went on a blind date.
- She seemed so cool.
- Do you keep in touch with her?
- They looked great together.
- I went on a blind date.
I'm not sure.
I haven't met her again since then.
- But maybe...
- So you two are staying in touch.
We'll see how things turn out.
I see. That's great.
- It's still going on.
Great. It's still going on.
- I don't know how it'll turn out.
- It's still going on.
He's still keeping in touch
with her.
Well, I haven't talked to her...
It'll work out somehow.
If he's not staying in touch
with her, it's not going on.
(Suk Jin has a point.)
- I mean, if he hasn't...
- Don't be like that, Suk Jin.
- You know I'm right.
- Still, he can have hope.
- Suk Jin, come on.
- You never know...
- what could happen between them.
- He should keep in touch with her.
- Suk Jin, don't say that.
- Exactly.
Won Hee thought he had a chance.
Won Hee, I'm sorry.
But you should call her...
If you think about it
from a common-sense perspective...
- Won Hee, it's still going on.
- Won Hee...
Won Hee is covered
with gold accessories.
- I'm showing off my accessories.
- He's wearing so many rings.
- Look at his watches.
- Gold.
That's amazing.
Won Hee,
you might get metal poisoning.
Be careful not to get
metal poisoning.
By the way, Won Hee,
do you appear only
on SBS' variety shows?
I've been appearing
only on "My Little Old Boy".
Would you refuse any offers
from other networks?
- Yes, for now.
- Why?
I have to act in dramas and movies.
- He's just like Kwang Soo.
- I'm only on "My Little Old Boy".
- Only on "My Little Old Boy"?
- Yes.
- Kwang Soo appears only here.
- Exactly.
- I heard that.
- He didn't get any other offers.
- We're actors...
- Come on.
Why would you say such a thing?
(That's why we can see him
only on Running Man.)
Anyway, Won Hee and Je Hoon
are here.
Je Hoon came back on the show
after four years.
Let me ask about your roles
in your new movie.
Je Hoon, could you please
tell us about your role?
The role I played
in the movie "Collectors" is...
a genius tomb robber.
- You played a tomb robber.
- A genius robber.
My character is
the master of digging.
He's good at shoveling
and operating an excavator.
- He's also...
- Like Drill Man?
Today, it's...
Robber versus Robber:
Faceless King of Tomb Robbery.
You are criminals from different
areas in the country,
and you've been invited by
the chairperson...
of Tomb Robbery Association
who's planning to rob a tomb.
One of you is the chairperson
of the Tomb Robbery Association,
and there are two undercover
police officers among you.
- Police officers?
- Yes.
- Oh, wow.
- It'll be difficult.
There are 1 chairperson
and 2 police officers.
Kwang Soo is suspicious.
(Is it me again?)
Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo won't show any reaction.
Kwang Soo, did you take up
one of the positions?
(Shuddering)
Is it you?
You must be a police officer.
Or the chairperson?
If Jong Kook suspects him now,
it's over.
- He's shaking.
- He won't be able to do anything.
(He'll be suspected
until the shoot ends.)
- It'll be stressful.
- If Jong Kook keeps an eye on him,
- he'll struggle to the last minute.
- Until the shoot ends.
The look on his face...
The 10 of you gathered
as the chairperson invited you,
but two of you don't
share the same goal.
You will be divided into two teams
to carry out the missions.
Also, you will rob a tomb
by yourselves.
You will receive different benefits
depending on the result of the game.
- What's "tomb"?
- I don't know either.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Kwang Soo just asked me
what "tomb" is.
And he said, "I don't know either."
Do you mean we should be obedient?
What do you mean by that?
It means an old grave.
Oh, an old grave?
A grave?
So it means an old grave. I see.
(So it means an old grave. I see.)
(He didn't say anything
although he didn't know either.)
Don't say anything. That's better.
- It's best not to say anything.
- Absolutely.
- Don't say anything like he does.
- Just don't say anything.
No wonder why Se Chan
didn't show any reactions.
Each item you may find
in the tomb has its own price.
The price will be revealed
only to the individual.
(Only the total amount
will be revealed.)
The chairperson
and the police officers...
already know the prices
of the items.
- His pronunciation isn't so good.
- When you go in there,
- they will probably choose...
- Oh, my.
Bo Pil, do you know
what Won Hee just said?
He said,
"His pronunciation isn't so good."
(He tells him about his comment
right away!)
- I'm sorry.
- Don't talk like that about the PD.
"His pronunciation isn't so good."
How can you laugh
at his pronunciation?
His face turned red.
He practiced hard to say that.
I'm really sorry.
I guess it's because
you're wearing a mask.
Mask? It's because
he's wearing a mask?
- I'm sorry.
- You just say what you want.
He says anything he wants to.
Your face turned all red.
So the chairperson and the police...
- He's nervous.
- know the information.
So you should take a good look
at what everyone's bringing.
- What they're bringing?
- Yes.
- So...
- He's pretending he's listening.
He's already hurt by your comment.
- You shouldn't pretend.
You're pretending.
- I am listening.
- My goodness.
(Really listening)
Now we need to see how well
you can rob a tomb.
So we're going to test you
to see how good you are.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
Please show it to them.
So they're testing us?
I'm sure I can do this
just by looking at it.
- You're right.
- A real robber...
- It's a piece of cake.
- just know what to steal.
Yes, it only takes a look.
- What is it?
- Oh, it's sand.
Okay!
This is an excavation site
of a historical site.
Among 15 potteries
buried under the sand,
there are 5 genuine ones
and 10 imitations.
Members who find the genuine ones...
will be given 1,000 dollars
for their mission.
- 1,000 dollars?
- Yes, 1,000 dollars.
- If we find genuine potteries?
- Yes.
After we decide
who goes in what order,
two members will do it at once.
- Each will get a brush.
- All right.
You have one minute to
find the potteries.
And if you find genuine potteries,
you'll get the money.
All right, I understand.
I can tell which ones are genuine.
Of course.
Robbers just know when they see it.
- They can tell.
- Sure.
You'll know if you just tap on it.
One more hint. The genuine potteries
don't have any patterns on them.
And the imitation ones
have Kwang Soo's face on them.
- Kwang Soo's face?
- My face?
Well, it's worth nothing.
- Why me?
- I should take it off.
On the imitation ones?
So they're imitations
of Lee Kwang Soo.
Maybe he has a role.
- Why else would his face be on it?
- Right. Lee Kwang Soo.
Now let's divide into groups of two.
I'll go with the thug.
- Okay.
- I'm going with the thug.
All right.
Then Je Hoon and Suk Jin
should team up.
- All right.
- You two are so different though.
(They're so different
but they will team up.)
He will make Je Hoon look good.
- I'm the only idiot.
- All right.
(I'm the only idiot?)
- What is he saying?
- Idiot? Who?
"I'm the only idiot"?
He wanted to say "Follow me".
But said it wrong.
- "I'm the only idiot".
- Really?
"I'm the only idiot"!
I wasn't sure
what he was talking about.
Well, I don't want to.
I guess he just said
what he was thinking.
He thought, "I'm the only idiot".
- He should've said, "Follow me."
- Yes.
"I'm the only idiot".
- So I'm teaming up with Won Hee.
- All right.
- And I'm with the petty thief.
- I'm going with Won Hee.
As a very smart robber, I think...
- Right.
- we should taste the sand.
- Yes.
- Taste the sand?
You really have to do that?
(Is he really
going to taste the sand?)
- Seriously?
- He's tasting it?
He's really going to play
the role like that?
My goodness.
There's a similar scene
in the movie.
Oh, there's a scene like that?
- Yes.
- Does he really taste it?
Yes, that way you know it.
This isn't it.
- He's really tasting it?
- That's so old school.
(Now let's take a closer look.)
(He used one finger to touch it.)
(Then he used
another finger to taste it.)
My goodness.
(Shamelessly using
an old-fashioned comedy.)
- Shameless.
- Gosh.
- Now taste it.
- You're shameless.
- Everyone, try tasting it.
- Je Hoon, try this one too.
Okay. Let me see.
(Doing the shameless comedy again.)
He doesn't know when to stop.
- This isn't it.
- He keeps doing it.
Well, he kind of looks cool.
- He's imitating him.
- Lee Je Hoon, you look good.
He's like a detective
in the old days.
Okay, everyone, try tasting it.
(The right hand doesn't know
what the left arm is tasting.)
This is endless.
Gosh, the hands are connected
to each other.
(Tasting the sand
with Bluetooth hands?)
(Good at old-fashioned comedy
since he was originally a comedian)
Why is the camera here?
Yes, he's smart.
- That one looks promising.
- No, no. That's mine.
I called shotgun on it.
(They found a camera
next to the pottery)
No, no. That's mine.
I called shotgun on it.
Isn't he the one
you called shotgun on?
(Is Je Hoon the one
she called shotgun on?)
(Love Frog wants to call shotgun
on Je Hoon and the pottery.)
Gosh, you're amazing.
- You called shotgun on him.
- No, I mean the pottery.
This is why she's Love Frog.
Love Frog?
(Love Frogs mainly inhabit
near Love.)
(So embarrassing)
Can't you let me have it?
No way. That's mine.
All right. You can have it.
(No way. That's mine.
You can have it.)
- Hey, what was that?
- Hey!
I can't believe it.
- Then I will dig this one out.
- Suk Jin is alone there.
(Suk Jin's alone.)
Me too.
(Everyone was having
a great time with Je Hoon.)
(Suk Jin couldn't fit in.)
(He just played his role
alone as a robber.)
- No one cares about him.
- It's okay.
- He just wandered around.
- I'm fine.
Je Hoon was
filming a movie over here.
- Did you choose one?
- Yes.
- This is the one.
- Get ready.
(Test robbery starts!)
The spout of the pottery
seems genuine.
- The spout?
- Yes, it's genuine.
- You have to dig it out quickly.
- I'm sure of it.
You have to hurry.
(The genuine ones are patternless.
Imitations have Kwang Soo's face)
It's patternless.
(Suk Jin took out his pottery.)
(Peekaboo)
It's a fake!
Kwang Soo's face is on it.
(Suk Jin picked the fake one!)
(Je Hoon is digging up
the one So Min wanted.)
(Will this smart robber
find genuine pottery?)
It's up to you two.
It's patternless.
(Peekaboo again!)
- Gosh.
- It's on it too?
It's a fake again!
Kwang Soo!
That's nice.
- Okay.
- Okay, okay.
I knew I should have
tasted the sand.
My goodness.
It's like he's filming a commercial.
It's our turn.
Our turn?
It might be in the center.
- The real one will be there.
- What is wrong with your shoulders?
- The center.
- What's wrong with his shoulders?
- You're right.
- He looks bigger today.
Jong Kook is like...
an owner of a fitness center
who doesn't go out much.
Yes, he's been out in a long time
so he wore something nice today.
He's an owner of a fitness center.
- So he only has gym clothes.
- Right.
But he needs something to wear
to people's weddings.
- That sounds like me.
- Right.
Fitness center owners
dress up like you.
- Get ready.
- Okay.
(Second test robbery starts!)
- Se Chan's is a fake.
- Okay!
(Se Chan picked an imitation!)
(But the fitness center owner
picked a genuine one!)
He found one. Amazing.
(The rest of the members
went through the test.)
(Haha, Jae Suk, Won Hee, and
So Min found genuine potteries.)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo
found imitation potteries.)
So the first test mission is over.
- Now here is the prize money.
- Okay.
- It's not real money?
- Se Chan, I'm so sorry.
- It's all right.
I'm so sorry.
(Going somewhere?)
It's okay. We don't need it anyway.
It's a great start.
Where's my money?
Did you find a genuine one?
You didn't.
Right.
- I didn't find one.
- What's wrong with Je Hoon.
What's wrong, Je Hoon?
He claims he found a genuine one
so he wants the money.
(Did he think it'll work?)
He's really weird.
What happened
for the last four years?
What's gotten into him?
- Now we'll move on...
- We should've won that.
to the main mission.
(Jae Suk, Won Hee, Jong Kook, Haha,
So Min have 1,000 dollars each.)
(Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, Je Hoon,
Kwang Soo, Se Chan have nothing.)
- This place is nice.
- Yes.
They built a place like this?
This is a hideout for
the Tomb Robbery Association.
- I see.
- This is a hideout?
It sure looks like it.
It's the first mission which you can
get benefits for your robbery.
Okay.
You have to rob other members'
romantic feelings.
It's called,
Love Signal, Heartthrob Quiz.
(Rob their romantic feelings!
Love Signal, Heartthrob Quiz)
- So Min loves it.
- She's excited.
(Her heart is pounding
to hear the word "love".)
- So Min loves it.
- She's excited.
So Min is so excited.
- Don't do this kind of mission.
- She looks pleased.
Can't you stop
giving us such missions?
I have nothing to offer.
We conducted a survey
on love affairs.
We surveyed 102 unmarried men
in their 20s and 30s.
- Only men?
- Yes.
We will give you four answers
with each question given.
And you just have to guess
the top answer.
(Choose the answer
people answered the most)
- All right.
- It's easy.
Discuss it with your team members
and choose two representatives...
so they can pick two seats
to sit in them for a minute.
You have to choose the right
answer after the minute is over.
The one who sits on the right answer
will get points.
Okay.
- What?
- What does he mean?
There are four answers.
If you think number one
is the right answer,
- You just sit there.
- Yes.
I got it.
- On a washbowl.
- I didn't understand it.
Gosh, this is so hard.
- I should keep up my spirit.
- Now we'll divide you in two teams.
Lee Jae Hoon and Im Won Hee
are team leaders.
- All right.
- We are?
Members' names are written
on the sticks.
- I see.
- Yes.
You can pick one by one.
But So Min and Ji Hyo's sticks are
with colors.
So each can pick only one.
- So...
- Shall I?
Is there any member
you want as your team member?
The one I want?
Are the names written on them?
You have to pick.
It will be written inside of it.
- You will know who it is.
- Wait a minute.
Say which member you want.
You said the producer
has bad pronunciation.
- I'm sorry.
- But you don't understand so well.
- Well, I...
- He keeps talking to himself.
- My goodness.
- I'm sorry.
It happens when I'm acting too.
If the director says something,
someone else
explains it to me again.
- I see.
- I'm sorry.
So say the member I want
then I should pick, right?
- Yes.
- Just pick one.
- It was an interview.
So is there a member you want?
Among us?
Well, I don't know.
Who do you want to be teamed with?
Who do you want?
- Yoo Jae Suk?
- All right.
(Yoo Jae Suk)
Why are you looking there
when you're talking about me?
I thought he was going to pick me.
Yes, he was looking there
and picked him.
- I thought you were picking me.
- Just let him be.
And he looked at me too.
I think he's just shy.
Now I'm good. I'm good.
So what should I do now?
- He's good now.
- What's next?
His face turned red.
- His face turned really red.
- We should listen to Je Hoon too.
The one I want
as my team member is...
Jong Kook.
(Je Hoon picked Jong Kook.)
I'm sitting right here
and you picked him?
Did you have to
pick someone far away?
But why did he have to
look at me when he said it?
Okay, then which do you want,
So Min or Ji Hyo?
(If he has to pick one, who will he
pick? So Min or Ji Hyo?)
Well, I...
- I'm really good at this.
- Really?
- What?
- Quiet down.
Don't say anything.
- Come on.
- So Min, don't say anything.
You can't do that.
- I want him to pick me.
- What are you doing?
You're confusing him.
I was just anxious. That's all.
(She tried to make him pick her.)
- Then I'll make a choice now.
- Okay.
(Then I'll make a choice now.)
(Je Hoon is looking at So Min.)
- He made up his mind.
- So Min.
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
(He refused to recruit So Min.)
So Min has been rejected.
You see...
Actually, I prefer Tak Jae Hoon.
(She rejected him
to get back at him.)
I prefer Tak Jae Hoon to him.
- So Min is the worst.
- I thought Tak Jae Hoon would come.
- She's getting upset.
- I didn't it was Lee Je Hoon.
You can start choosing
your team members.
(Starting with Won Hee,
they'll pick spoons in turns.)
- Won Hee, go to the center...
- Who is it?
(Team Won Hee's first member
is So Min.)
(She's not happy about it.)
Who is it?
- It's So Min.
- Is it So Min?
- She's not happy about it.
- Why did you sigh like that?
- That hurts my feelings.
- Why did you do that?
- Won Hee reacted too late.
- You could've faked it.
- She sighed so loudly. My gosh.
- So Min seemed disappointed.
- Ji Hyo.
- All right.
- He picked Suk Jin.
- I'm the only idiot.
Everyone on my team except for me
knows nothing about dating.
- Kwang Soo can sit here.
- Please sit with your team.
- Can you move to the side?
- No.
- Sit next to him.
- Come on.
- No. You sit there.
- Hey, come on.
- Come on. Just sit there.
- Why are you doing this?
- Sit there while you have a chance.
Just sit down.
- Come on. Sit here.
- No. I said, no.
- I'm giving you a chance.
- No.
Stay there.
Se Chan, don't do that.
I know you don't want it.
That's not true.
- It's like a sad movie, right?
- I almost cried.
Se Chan had a tear
while telling her to move.
He was crying from only one eye
while smiling to hide his tears.
(I won't let her see me crying.)
- All the dating experts gathered.
- Absolutely.
- Exactly.
- That's interesting.
Won Hee is an expert on dating.
I went on a blind date not long ago.
That's great.
But it didn't go well.
- You don't know that.
- It's still going on.
- It's not over. You never know.
- "It's not over."
Now, I'm going to tell you
the first question.
What is the best method of
winning arguments with a girlfriend?
- Oh, that...
- Well...
If you try to win her to the end,
your relationship will be over.
- Tears of a man.
- You see...
- Right. Crying.
- Wouldn't that mean you lost?
- Crying must be the answer.
- There's a really simple method.
You can just apologize first.
- Then she'd ask, "What for?"
- Exactly.
- Right?
- Yes.
- "What are you apologizing for?"
- It feels like I'm on a quiz show.
- You don't even know.
- It's never what I think it is.
- "I'm sorry for everything."
- Right?
This is not a good method.
But many men use this method.
They ghost their girlfriends.
- That's the worst.
- Oh, gosh.
- Completely.
- That's so pathetic.
- I didn't know he was this petty.
- Completely.
- That's the worst thing to do.
- I know. It's the worst.
- I always lost in an argument...
- Saying, "I love you"?
when my boyfriend seemed pitiful.
- Of course.
- When he tried to appeal to pity.
If he's sick and seems to have
gotten thinner,
it makes me think
that he can't live without me.
- I saw it with my own eyes.
- Fainting 3m away from her...
while she's looking at you.
It's an effective way.
It's more effective when she's
looking at you from behind.
You're so petty. Every method
you suggested is so pathetic.
They're cowardly and petty.
It's more effective if you faint
when she's watching you from behind.
While she's watching you
from behind.
Now, I'm going to reveal
the four answer choices.
(The answer choices are revealed.)
- See? Saying sorry is an option.
- You were right.
One of them is listening to her
without saying anything.
That's upsetting. Number two is
definitely not the answer.
- That would anger her even more.
- It's definitely not the answer.
- It makes a woman angry.
- Right.
- Could number three be the answer?
- It's my style.
Number four is my style.
- That's the worst method.
- It's my style.
Number three?
- I like number 3.
- I'd choose number 3.
- I'd choose number three too.
- Won Hee...
Won Hee picked it
based on what he hopes for.
(Being romantic is the best.
Kiss her so she stops speaking.)
- Won Hee...
- With his lips...
That's what I hope for.
Based on what he hopes for,
- he picked number 3.
- I'd choose number 3.
You shouldn't do that right away.
- It could backfire.
- Then what should be done first?
Do number 1 before doing number 3.
- Or number 2 before number 3.
- I'm sure it's number 3.
Je Hoon, what would you do?
If I argue with my girlfriend,
I would...
do number 2, number 1,
and then number 3.
- 2, 1, 3.
- 2, 1, 3?
- Oh, 2, 1, 3?
- Number 2?
That would be a perfect way.
You listen to what she has to say,
apologize to her, and kiss her.
- Would you not do number 4?
- Number 3 must be the answer.
If you argue back, she might think
you don't care if you break up.
Men rarely go with number four.
The worst option is
number 4, 3, and then 1.
- That's the worst.
- Jae Suk, that's me.
That's how I usually act.
I argue back before apologizing
and then get slapped in the face.
- 4, 3, 1 is the worst combination.
- 4, 3, 1...
"Hey! You're in no position
to say that to me."
- You know so much about dating.
- Of course, I do.
He knows so much.
I specialize in things like this.
He doesn't have much experience
but knows so much about dating.
- I specialize in petty things.
- Exactly.
- I know...
- He hasn't dated many girls.
- True.
- He wasn't popular with girls.
- Why would you say that?
- Gosh.
If you repeat number three,
it would be even worse.
(Being romantic is the best.
Kiss her so she stops speaking.)
You would get slapped in the face.
(Too much romance)
That's so funny.
Okay. Please bring us the tubs.
- I think it's number three.
- This time...
- Which of us should go?
- I think it's the answer.
- Kwang Soo and I will go.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo, I'll secure number 2.
- I'll secure number 1.
- Number 1 and 2.
- But...
Jae Suk, we'll secure
numbers 1 and 2.
- Okay.
- But I think it's number three.
I don't think number two is
the answer. You'd get yelled at.
You're right.
I'll go with number three.
(Fortunately, they picked
another option.)
I want to sit in the first one.
- Okay. I'll make sure of it.
- Okay.
- Someone hit me in the back.
- You can go with number three.
- I'll go with number 1.
- 1 of them hit me.
- You said you'd go with number 2.
- He wants number 1.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome. Come here.
- Sit here.
- What are you doing? Kwang Soo.
- Go ahead and try.
- Ready...
(Whoever claims the tub
after a minute wins the right.)
(The countdown starts now.)
(He fell on the floor
in an instant.)
- Sit down.
- Thank you.
Okay. Good.
Jong Kook, he's hitting me.
Jong Kook.
(The sly brothers are
attacking him together.)
Number four might be
the correct answer.
- Number four.
- Kwang Soo, lift him up. Come on.
- He's lifting Haha up.
- That's good.
- Go on. Go.
- He picked Haha up.
- Good.
- Sit down.
30 seconds remaining.
Kwang Soo, let's stay closer.
- That's a good idea.
- He's sitting in number three.
- 2.
- Number 4 can't be the answer.
- What if it's number 4?
- Let's see.
- Hold on. It hurts.
(Which of the four
chose the correct answer?)
- I hope it's number one.
- The correct answer is...
- Number 3.
- 32 percent chose this option.
That's so high.
The correct answer is...
(Is it number 3 or 4? Or is it
number 2 that Se Chan fought for?)
"An eye for an eye.
Argue back logically..."
"so she has nothing to say."
(The correct answer is number four.)
(Neither number 2 nor number 1
was the correct answer.)
- I thought it wasn't the answer.
- Me too.
To be honest, I thought
it could be the answer.
- It's hard to believe.
- I was wrong.
- I'm shocked. Times have changed.
- I have goosebumps.
Saying sorry is ranked second.
Number 2 is ranked 4th,
and number 3 is ranked 3rd.
- I see.
- Number four isn't a good solution.
- I didn't expect this.
It's hard for us to guess
what men in their 20s and 30s...
- would think about such matters.
- We're like old fossils.
What were we talking about?
We thought about the old-fashioned
way of dating.
- I became an old fossil.
- Exactly.
- It's an old-fashioned way.
- It's shocking.
Here's the second question.
"What's the most cowardly thing
you've done to your girlfriend?"
- The most cowardly thing?
- Yes.
- The most cowardly thing.
- Okay.
- Usually...
Men usually do such things
when they get dumped.
They would bad-mouth their
ex-girlfriends.
- That's petty too.
- A cowardly thing?
- It's cowardly.
- It happens.
- You've done that before, right?
- That's petty.
- He's so petty.
- I guess he has.
- Jae Suk, that's you.
- That's petty.
- That's him.
- You're cowardly and petty.
I understand because you were young.
- It's cowardly. What about you?
- Exactly.
- Anything cowardly?
- Cowardly things.
I haven't... What did I do?
I haven't done any cowardly...
I didn't ask about
the things you have done.
Oh, right. Things that others
would do.
If you still don't understand
the rules...
We're not sharing
our personal experiences.
Well...
Bad-mouthing the ex-girlfriend
after the breakup.
I just said the same thing.
- Won Hee, come on.
- What is he doing right now?
- Write a script for him.
- He said the same thing.
- I'm sorry.
- I can't believe this.
- Won Hee.
- I just said the same thing.
Maybe I was talking
about a different situation.
- As if no one had said that.
- My goodness.
- Unbelievable.
- He said it 30 seconds before that.
- What is wrong with him?
- I'm sorry.
Je Hoon, do you have any ideas?
In my case,
I really liked this girl,
but I told her I hated her.
- I see.
- That's cowardly but cool.
To play hard to get?
Yes. Well, I liked her so much,
but she wouldn't tell me
how she felt about me.
- Because of your pride?
- It hurt my pride.
- So I said I hated her.
- Kwang Soo, tell them.
- You know...
- Tell them what you did before.
- When a couple breaks up,
- Yes, tell that story.
- the man asks for his gifts back.
- Exactly.
- Did you do that?
- Gosh.
Of course.
That's not right. Don't you think?
You're still paying for the gifts
you bought for her every month.
Exactly.
Why would anyone ask
for their gifts back?
Or you know it's not right,
but you need money urgently,
so you take money
out of your girlfriend's wallet.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- No way.
That is so pathetic.
Everything you said is so pathetic.
They're all so cowardly
and pathetic.
That's hilarious.
(After hearing a lot of
pathetic stories...)
- "I thought of ending things too."
- That's similar to Je Hoon's story.
"Saying I thought of ending things
too as she broke up with me."
"Okay. I thought of
ending things too."
- "I'm glad you said that."
- "I'm glad to hear that."
I've done number two before.
Number two.
"Leaving where we were when she was
looking at an expensive item..."
- "saying it didn't look nice".
- You see...
- That sounds very real.
- That sounds real.
I can assure you that you'll do that
a dozen times in marriage too.
- I...
- Not just while dating someone.
- I can relate to that too.
- Really?
Yes, it happens.
- I'm sure men do that a lot.
- I've done this a lot before.
- That's unexpected.
- "Saying I loved her..."
Number three is so funny. My gosh.
Read number three.
"Saying I loved her..."
- "just to get to second base".
- Right.
That's...
"I love you. You trust me, right?"
- "I love you. You're the only one."
- "I love you."
- "You trust me, don't you?"
- "I love you so much."
That's impressive.
"Lying that something urgent
happened to rest at home..."
"on the day of your date."
This happens too.
- In a long-term relationship...
- That sounds real.
Men in a long-term relationship
usually make such excuses.
This is from men
in their 20s and 30s.
- Right.
- They don't have a lot of money.
So I think most of them
picked number two.
- That's most likely.
- Number two.
As a guy though,
number three
seems the most cowardly.
But for those in their 20s...
- Number 2.
- Number 2 could be right.
Please choose two from each team.
- From each team?
- Won Hee, go ahead.
- Won Hee, you're up.
- And So Min.
- My answer would be number 4.
- Number 1 isn't so bad.
It'll be Ji Hyo and Je Hoon for us.
- Number one...
- Start.
- How about 1 and 2?
- 1 and 2?
- Number 2.
- Go for number 2 immediately.
Won Hee, go for number two.
That'll be our safe bet.
Get ready...
(1 minute begins! Start!)
Won Hee, be careful.
- What?
- I knew it.
Won Hee, be careful.
(I knew it.)
There's an insect in here.
- Won Hee, hold your ground.
- Won Hee!
Hold your ground.
Wait, my arms hurt.
- Get inside.
- Won Hee!
- Hold your ground.
- Is this how it'll be?
- Please get up.
- This is how it'll be?
(He learns about the Running Man way
while on the floor.)
- I give up.
- Je Hoon gave up.
- Head back inside.
- But I am inside.
- I'm in the tub.
- Look at Won Hee.
- But I'm already in it.
- Get back in there.
How?
- Hold on.
- You secured your tub.
Just stand up and walk back in.
(He takes Haha's advice
and leaves the tub.)
Won Hee!
(The number 2 tub gets stolen.)
- This isn't right.
- You can't leave it completely.
This is wrong.
- What...
- Are you kidding me?
- This isn't right.
- You can't leave it completely.
- This is wrong though.
- Nicely done!
- Won Hee, seriously?
- That was mean of him.
- Is this how it'll be?
- Unbelievable.
- Oh, dear.
- Who told me to get up?
I can't believe Won Hee.
You all selected your tubs.
- Let me reveal the ranking then.
- Sure.
In first place is...
(The answer to the second survey)
Saying "I love you"
just to get more physical.
(The answer was number 3
which Won Hee chose!)
See?
See? What did I tell you?
- See?
- No way!
- Unbelievable.
- Can you believe it?
It's number 3, not 2?
- It was number three.
- No way.
Number 3 had 38 percent
while number 2 had 21 percent.
- Not number one then.
- No way.
Number 1 was in 3rd place
while number 4 was in 4th place.
I'm suddenly reminded
of all the times someone...
- confessed their love to me.
- Hey.
The winner of this game
is Team Je Hoon.
(Team Je Hoon wins the entire game.)
You'll now head out
to the first site.
- Sure.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
- All right.
Over here, guys!
(The robbers head out
deep into the woods.)
- Open the door.
- What is it?
- What is this place?
(A tomb that was hidden)
- What...
- We must be role-playing.
- It's cool though.
- Here we go.
We're here to rob the tomb.
(The reason why the chairperson
gathered the robbers)
- It's pretty though.
- What is this place?
A land of mystery.
- Hold on.
- What is this place?
I see several rooms.
(The undercover officers will begin
their investigation here.)
Look at the cool flames.
- What is this?
- What?
- What is this place?
- It's for us to rob.
- The category list.
- What?
China, furniture, statues,
- paintings...
- What now?
(The category of items
they can steal.)
- We're here to rob the place.
- The setting's so cool.
Consider me intrigued.
(Welcome to the tomb you'll rob.)
It's giving me
an "Indiana Jones" vibe.
- Gems.
- This is great.
(The well-designed set
gets them into character.)
There are lanterns too.
- This is a working lantern.
- Hey, you're right.
- It's an actual lantern.
- Exactly.
- Robbers.
- Yes.
This is the real reason...
why the chairperson
gathered you here.
We have the chairperson
and police officers among us.
Right, the chairperson is among us.
There are two
police officers, right?
- Yes.
- Who invited us here?
(Who invited us here?)
That awkward tone.
"Who invited us here?"
Don't do that on purpose
just to seem suspicious.
Suk Jin's not playing
any major role today.
(Jae Suk doesn't
suspect him at all.)
Could the police officer be dirty?
It's time for the first robbery.
In the amount of time you have,
you'll take whatever treasure
you like from the tomb...
and bring it back out here.
Each team will get
a chance to enter.
The winner of the previous game
will get a minute...
while the losing team
will only get 30 seconds.
In the two rooms you'll enter
lie all sorts of treasure.
There are seven
categories in total,
and items from the same category
have the same price.
- Some are worth zero dollars.
- Zero?
Others are 1,000, 2,000,
and 3,000 dollars respectively.
One category has items
worth 10,000 dollars.
10,000 dollars?
- Then that's all you really need.
- Yes, exactly.
- Got it.
- Just know...
that the chairperson
and police officers...
know which items are the priciest.
(The chairperson and police officers
know what's worth 10,000 dollars.)
Then we'll be able
to suspect who it is.
Anyone who steals
the priciest item...
(What they steal
will serve as evidence.)
(Glaring)
(Me? It's not me.)
Hold on a second.
Wait, have you already
begun your investigation?
- Who...
- Of course.
- Who are you looking at?
- I just...
My eyes met Jong Kook's
about three times just now.
You can take as many as you want.
Just bring them to your station
in the amount of time you have.
Any broken items...
or those you didn't have time
to place won't count.
Once the teams are done,
I'll privately let you know
the price of your items.
- Privately?
- Yes.
The winning team will head out
with those lanterns.
Good luck.
- The lanterns are so pretty.
- It must be dark inside.
Get robbing.
Let's go.
Come on!
(Dark and dim)
Right here.
- Everything's set.
- My guess is that...
the bigger and harder
to move the item might...
Let's go.
(They take a look around
before robbing the room.)
How do we...
I see coins here.
This is what I'm taking.
Books.
Can one even take this?
- How can you carry that?
- Can one carry this?
(The statue is too big
for anyone to carry.)
The china seems pricey.
(Old pieces of china
definitely seem pricey.)
This chair too.
(Je Hoon checks if one can
carry the large cupboard.)
The time... How long do we have?
- A minute.
- I see.
- Get ready...
- The heavier items.
(The robbing begins.)
Hold on a second.
Why are you all heading over there?
(Je Hoon places the china
on top of the cupboard.)
Not these.
Not these small ones.
- Hold on.
- Be careful.
- Those books.
- They're too heavy.
It's too heavy.
It's just too heavy.
(Ji Hyo only takes
what she can carry.)
(Meanwhile, Je Hoon
takes a lot of the china.)
(Jong Kook utilizes
the muscle he has.)
We can at least bring two.
(He steals the statue
that's taller than him.)
- What's that?
- It's a statue.
Is it that heavy?
That doesn't look...
too expensive to me.
They're being
petty thieves that they are.
Yes, like petty thieves.
Suk Jin stole what fits him.
He brought the books
he would've read.
- Old books.
- They're his, right?
(Old books that are reminiscent
of Suk Jin's school years)
- The books he probably read.
- She stole china.
You brought a lot.
- They don't look expensive.
- I agree.
Jong Kook...
- What is that?
- Bigger items...
aren't necessarily pricier.
Bigger doesn't mean pricier.
Gosh, it's heavy.
It doesn't seem
that expensive to me.
- He's faking it.
- It's so heavy.
Je Hoon, be careful.
- What...
- Look at what he brought!
- Time's up.
- Is it over?
- It's over.
(Je Hoon stole a cupboard
and six china pieces.)
What you're carrying now
don't count.
Time's up.
- Okay.
- These don't count?
Haha, what were you thinking?
It's harder than expected.
Suk Jin brought items
from a variety of categories.
Yes, exactly.
From four.
A painting, china pieces,
books, and a statue.
I stole some gems...
and R coins which are valuable
in the Running Man world.
Coins.
- These are probably the priciest.
- You don't need anything else.
All I need are the R coins.
All right.
The second team is up next.
- Guys, let's go.
- Let's go.
- R coins are the most valuable.
- Okay.
I don't need a lantern.
(Determined)
This won't be easy.
The flames are fake.
(Team Won Hee gets 30 seconds
to search the tomb.)
(Won Hee chooses
the light paintings.)
(So Min fills her bag
with treasures...)
(and then goes for the statue
that's bigger than her.)
My arms hurt.
Why is this so heavy?
You won't believe how heavy this is.
(Kwang Soo loads the items
on the cupboard like Je Hoon.)
(Wobbly)
I dropped the books!
- Time's up.
- I'm done.
Already?
What on earth.
- My hands hurt.
- Those aren't allowed.
- No?
- My hands hurt.
- They're so heavy.
- Tell me about it.
- I thought this looked cool.
- Me too.
But it broke.
You broke it?
- Someone broke it.
- Wait...
- It's broken.
- No, it's almost broken.
- Hold on.
- Look at the crack.
What's broken isn't allowed.
See?
I specifically said so
at the beginning,
- so that doesn't count.
- He's right.
- No way.
- Guys,
out of the 10 of you,
the one with the lowest amount...
- Zero dollars?
- The lowest amount is...
(The one with the lowest amount
out of the 10)
It's 1,000 dollars.
- What?
- Did he or she only steal one item?
- The one with the highest amount.
- The highest amount.
- How much is it?
- The highest amount...
- is 20,000 dollars.
- What?
(The one with the highest amount
has 20,000 dollars.)
- He or she must've known.
- Hold on.
Maybe it's someone
who stole two of the same kind?
You have a point.
- It smells like prior knowledge.
- Exactly.
Look over there.
There are two paintings.
20,000 dollars?
But he also has some china pieces.
That could be worth nothing.
- You're right.
- This person knew.
- I have two of the same kind.
- 20,000 dollars?
I stole two of the same kind.
- The statute.
- That he did.
- I don't think it's me though.
- He stole two statues.
You'll each be told
the amount you stole.
- Make sure no one else sees it.
- Got it.
- Sure.
- I doubt anyone will.
- Ji Hyo.
- Sure.
- I think I know who it is.
- Thanks.
This must be kept a secret.
(They can make assumptions
depending on their amount.)
- So...
- Darn it.
(Haha was confident that
the gems and R coins were valuable.)
(Haha has the least amount
at 1,000 dollars.)
This narrows it down.
- I think I know who it is.
- You can tell...
- once you calculate your amount.
- Right.
You can tell who has two
of the priciest items.
(Statue: 10,000 dollars)
(Jong Kook has the highest amount
with 20,000 dollars.)
But that person
might've stolen the items...
- without knowing their value.
- Exactly.
(Other members stole statues too.)
(Suk Jin,)
(Se Chan,)
It's bigger than you.
(Suk Jin, Se Chan, and So Min)
(Could the chairperson
or the police officers...)
(who know the prices be among them?)
Does it mean we're going to start
playing mind games now?
That's it, right?
- It started way before.
- Play what?
It already started?
- Please Won Hee. Pay attention.
- What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
- What's wrong with him?
- I'm sorry.
- I'll join now.
- It started with the show.
- Really?
- Why would we begin now?
I thought
we were just starting that.
I'm sorry.
- All right. We will...
- We started already.
- move on to our second mission.
- Okay.
(They move on to the second mission
after 1st round of tomb robbery.)
Nicely done.
- Mine!
- Gosh, that was pretty tough.
Mine. It's mine.
(But why are the members
playing foot volleyball?)
Mine!
- So Min, take your time.
- Kick it high.
Kick it high.
(What? What was that just now?)
(The ball goes back to Won Hee.)
(Gosh.)
(Suddenly dancing the mask dance
from Bongsan)
- He's awful at this sport.
- Come on, Won Hee.
- Won Hee.
- He can't kick.
I missed it just once.
- Won Hee is an entertainer too.
- Gosh.
So I can't kick
because I messed up once?
All right. Gather around.
- We have to gather around.
- Where?
It was fun.
As you warmed up
by playing foot volleyball,
- you sized each other up, right?
- Yes.
Won Hee can't kick.
- Won Hee...
- We found out.
- You can't kick at all.
- I was so shocked.
- We did it on "My Little Old Boy".
- He's an entertainer.
I wasn't that bad.
- I'm unexpectedly good.
- Won Hee.
All right. Teamwork is
important for the second mission.
It's called Spare Nothing
for Foot Volleyball.
Spare Nothing?
Four members from both teams will
play a match of foot volleyball.
- 4 members.
However, in order to get the ball
over the net to the opposing team,
all of the members in your team
must touch the ball at least once...
and pass it over the net.
(Everyone in the team must touch
the ball before passing it over.)
- What?
- To get the ball over...
(That won't be easy.)
If you fail to get the ball over
after everyone has touched it once,
everyone must touch the once again.
Wait. We...
You will divide into your teams
just like before.
So we're going
to have different teams now?
But...
What's the prize of winning
this foot volleyball match?
It's just like before.
Won Hee, why do you think
we're playing games?
(Chuckling)
- Won Hee.
- I wanted to know in detail.
- I'm sorry.
- Let me tell you this in advance.
Let's pull out a spoon.
- Okay.
- You'll go first?
- Should I go first?
- Do you want to go first?
You can choose one color.
- Green or yellow?
- Who's thinking about me?
He's looking at you now, So Min.
- Who?
- Je Hoon.
Je Hoon, I'm good at this.
I can do well. I'll do my best.
- I'll try to choose So Min.
- Pick me this once.
Will her wish come true?
(Will So Min's wish come true?)
- How did he pick her?
- Really?
(He picks So Min.)
- How? How did you know it was her?
- Good for you, So Min!
- She's happy.
- No, she might be bad at it.
- How did he do that?
- All right.
- Let me get Jong Kook.
- Gosh, Won Hee.
(Please let it be Jong Kook.)
- Did you pick me?
- Yes, I got him.
- You got him?
- Yes!
We have this in the bag.
- We got this in the bag.
- Gosh.
- How did you pick me?
- We got this in the bag.
Jae Suk is the best of
the remaining members. Seriously.
Let it be Jae Suk.
- Gosh, it's Suk Jin. Good.
- Gosh. Okay.
- "Gosh, it's Suk Jin."
- It's all right.
Well done.
- We're totally ruined.
- Guys.
- Gosh, this is...
- It's...
- What a team.
- I should try my best.
All right. You can warm up now.
- Let's warm up.
- We won this!
- 1, 2, 3, 4. And over the net.
- Okay.
- Okay. 1, 2, 3, 4?
- So Min, good luck!
One,
- two.
- That's right.
- Won Hee.
- It's Won Hee's turn.
Do a header.
- Won Hee.
- It's Won Hee's turn.
(Kicking in the air)
(Captain Im shows potentials
to be the weakling of the team.)
Nice. He can't kick!
- I'm messing it up on purpose.
- When that happens,
- put your head on the ball.
- Okay. I got it now.
- He's going to be trouble.
- I'm messing it up on purpose.
- We didn't start yet.
- We'll zero in on Won Hee.
Let's go after Won Hee.
We'll start now.
- Let's go. Okay. Go.
- Get it. You got it, right?
Nice serve.
- Stay close.
- One.
- Two.
- Great.
- Pass it to Ji Hyo.
- Do a header. Pass it to her head.
- Two.
- Great.
- Pass it to Ji Hyo.
- Do a header. Pass it to her head.
- Over the net.
- Nice!
Save it!
(Save it!)
Look. Won Hee, listen.
When the ball is high,
just do a header.
- Bump it with your head.
- Should I put my head on it? Okay.
- Won Hee was scolded, right?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- He raised his voice.
- You got scolded, right?
- Do you agree?
- Don't focus on only kicking.
- Won Hee.
Are you under a lot of pressure?
Should I take over?
(Team Je Hoon continues
to play offense.)
Move. Out of my way! Won Hee. Gosh.
(He suddenly bumps it with his belly
as Jong Kook screams.)
(What was that?)
Move. Out of my way! Won Hee. Gosh.
- Gosh.
- One.
- Two.
- Gosh.
It's out. I'm sorry.
No, it's okay. Next time, just move.
Won Hee. Won Hee,
he scared you just now, right?
- "Move!"
- He got scared.
Don't try to receive the serve
wherever it goes.
- I won't do it.
- Okay.
It's too much.
- So Min, cover that part.
- We can do it.
- He's causing so much trouble.
We can do it.
- Nice. Use your body. Shoulders.
- One.
Yes. We got it.
- Won Hee!
- Okay.
- Won Hee.
It's here.
(Will he be able to redeem himself?)
- Do a header.
- Okay.
- Okay. It's here.
- Do a header.
(He manages to get it over the net.)
(Suddenly flustered)
- Great.
- The ball is still alive.
- Okay.
- Je Hoon.
- Yes. Je Hoon, take your time.
- Go.
- Nice.
- Great.
- Jong Kook.
- Mine.
Won Hee.
(Sprawling)
(He leaves his team
utterly vulnerable once again.)
(His anger level is going up.)
Why did you come to me?
Why did you move?
- You should have stayed there.
- He's crying.
He's the worst.
(He's provoking Won Hee
by tapping on his bottom.)
- It's all right.
- Okay.
(Coach Jong Kook is
trying hard not to lose it.)
Good luck.
So Min, I'm right behind you.
Don't you worry. Mine!
One.
- Two.
- So Min.
- Come here, So Min.
- I should kick it too.
Great. Do a header.
- That's it!
I got it.
- Okay. Get it.
- This is it.
Won Hee, kick it high.
Won Hee got the ball.
- Won Hee, kick it high.
- Won Hee got the ball.
Won Hee.
- Run.
- Just kick it gently.
- One more time!
- Kick it again!
- Just kick it gently.
- One more time.
- One more time, Won Hee.
- Do it again!
(Do it again!)
You could have kicked it again!
(Coach Jong Kook lost it
in the end.)
- You could have...
- We could have gone one more round.
I think you gave up too early.
- I forgot.
- You didn't know the rule, right?
I forgot.
You got scolded, right?
- He did.
- Yes.
Won Hee, the Black Sheep.
Nice.
Let's catch up.
Okay. Wait.
- One.
- So Min, wait.
- Two.
- So Min.
- Three.
- Jae Suk.
- Four.
- That's it.
- 1.
- 1. All right.
Touch the ball. No.
- Bump the ball.
- Three.
- Won Hee!
(It's the weakling,
Won Hee's turn again.)
(He had to be trained
by the scary coach.)
(He must get the ball over the net
this time no matter what.)
- Bump the ball.
- Won Hee!
(Kicking with vigor)
- Great.
- Won Hee!
(A fiery shoot with determination)
(He finally did it!)
- Yes.
- Yes!
Well done.
- Good job.
- I knew it.
It's all right.
Okay.
(Team Won Hee is feeling confident
after their first score.)
Any part of your body
has to hit the ball.
(They will continue their offense
with Jong Kook's serve.)
- Jae Suk.
- All right.
Wait. So Min, this is yours.
- So Min.
- You can get it over the net.
- That's it.
- Good luck!
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo.
(Flailing)
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo.
(Suk Jin juggles the ball.)
(Sighing)
Nice!
Nice try.
- Great.
- Gosh.
- So Min, that was perfect. Good.
- Well done.
(They resume the match
after calming down.)
- Mine!
- It's hard.
Wait.
So Min, bump it gently.
- Bump it gently.
- Okay.
- Three.
- That's it.
- Haha, get it.
- This is dangerous.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
- Okay. It's mine.
- Suk Jin.
Do a header.
See? That was long.
- Gosh. Save it.
- It's back again.
(Boiling with anger)
- Do a header.
- Like this.
- When you kick, the pass is long.
- Okay.
- Just put your head on the ball.
- Everyone is getting scolded.
Suk Jin and Won Hee are
getting scolded so much.
No. Not yet. Don't give up yet.
We can do it.
- Yes, we can do it.
- We can do it.
- Let's go.
- We're doing well now.
We're doing well.
- You got it, right?
- Of course.
- One. You get it.
- Suk Jin.
- Gently.
- Won Hee, you get it.
Use your head! Won Hee.
- Gently.
- Won Hee, you get it.
(Kneeing the ball)
- Gently.
- Won Hee, you get it.
(The weakling is back.)
Your head! Use your head!
You have a head. Use your head!
- Why would you kick it?
- Where did you hit the ball with?
(He's getting scolded for using
his foot during foot volleyball.)
I'm sorry. Sorry.
No more mistakes from now on.
He's driving me crazy.
This is crazy.
I should start doing headers.
- Okay. It's over.
- It's all thanks to Won Hee.
- It's over.
- You can play this time.
- It's all thanks to him.
- Let's do this!
- Okay.
We can do it!
Let's go.
- Great.
- Move.
- Out.
- No, it's in.
- Great.
- Out.
(Move!)
(Jong Kook does a Sargent jump.)
(He miscalculates
the point of contact.)
(Gosh. Darn it.)
(Covering his mouth)
What's wrong with you?
(He was bragging so much earlier.)
- You said you got it.
- You should have moved.
You said you got it.
- We got two.
- Listen.
You said you got it.
I told you to move.
Why didn't you move?
That's hilarious. It's hilarious.
- It's hilarious.
- Keep going.
It's so funny.
- Hold on.
- Let's play now.
Hey, whose team are you on?
(Suddenly coming to his senses)
Whose team are you on?
- What are you doing there?
- You can't laugh at him.
- Right. I get why he's laughing.
- I can understand him laughing.
- But you...
- You can't laugh at them.
You're on our team.
How can you laugh at us?
- I'm sorry.
- All of us are working hard.
- What are you doing?
- You can't do that.
- Should you be laughing now?
You can do it!
- Gosh.
- Don't give up yet.
It was hilarious.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
(They resume playing
after suppressing their anger.)
Good.
- Mine.
- Great.
- Okay. Great.
- One.
Nice.
- I'll kick it high.
- Okay.
So Min, it's your turn.
- Great.
- Gently kick it over.
- That's it. You got it.
- Nice.
Gosh.
You got it.
(It's an embarrassing moment
for him.)
(The audience is satisfied
with his slapstick comedy.)
- Are you okay?
- My gosh, look.
- He tripped.
- I'm okay.
- Are you okay?
- It was so sudden.
- Are you okay, Jong Kook?
- Sorry.
- That was funny.
- You're okay? Are you pretending...
- to be okay because you're ashamed?
- I'm okay.
- You're okay, right?
- I'm fine.
It's so funny seeing Jong Kook
so flustered like that.
Hey, Jong Kook.
This is the set point.
- Okay.
- It's the match point.
It's the set point.
So Min, that was perfect.
That's it.
Kick it when it comes down.
(Determined)
(Will the game come to an end now?)
- Nice serve.
- Mine.
- Great.
- Okay.
- One.
- Go.
(The ball goes sideways.)
(At that moment, Won Hee runs over!)
(Will he redeem himself
and save the team?)
Won Hee, are you okay?
(He suddenly slides.)
(Laughing)
Are you okay?
(Won Hee saved everyone
from boredom.)
(His body couldn't handle
the pressure.)
Won Hee, are you okay?
(Sighing)
Is something the matter?
What is up with you today?
Are you okay?
Is something the matter?
- Are you okay?
- Nice try.
The game is over.
The game is over! The game is over!
- Good job.
- The head. The head.
The difference between Je Hoon
and Won Hee divided the results.
- I know. Je Hoon did really well.
- That's what I think.
- Je Hoon did really well.
- Seriously.
(Glancing over)
(He puts his arm
around Won Hee's shoulder.)
- Won Hee.
- Won Hee, are you crying?
No, no. No, no.
- Won Hee, it's okay.
- Jong Kook didn't hit you, did he?
- No, no.
- Why is your face so red?
People who just turned on the TV
might take it the wrong way.
- I am okay.
- Smile, Won Hee.
Smile.
We will now go to the last tomb.
- Okay.
It's the last tomb.
Hey, I know what to do now.
I know what to do in order to help.
- You have one minute.
- Okay.
Get ready. Set, go.
(Team Je Hoon starts robbing
for 1 minute.)
(Looking around)
You should have told us!
- They said we start right away.
- Still...
(Haha picks up a painting.)
(Se Chan and So Min enter
another room.)
Where are the gems?
I can't take it outside.
Come on.
(Je Hoon keeps looking
for something.)
(He picks up a statue.)
(Did he pick it...)
My goodness.
(because it's
the most expensive item?)
A minute.
I should bring a big one.
It has nothing to do with size.
All statues are the same.
- Really?
- Yes.
Is the price the same as before?
(Je Hoon brought an item
that is worth 10,000 dollars.)
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
I dropped it.
(Where is he headed?)
(Another statue?)
(Time's up.)
We will appraise the items
you brought.
(Jae Suk, Haha, Ji Hyo,
Je Hoon, and So Min)
We only made one trip.
The second team will go now.
- Okay.
- I have three items.
- Let's go.
- We have 30 seconds, right?
- 3 paintings.
- 30 seconds.
Jae Suk's painting is damaged.
- It's damaged.
- The painting is fine.
- No, it's damaged.
- The painting is what matters.
His face is crumpled.
- The painting.
- His face is crumpled.
- No, no.
- The frame could be expensive.
- The painting is fine.
- I can't accept an item like this.
This item is damaged.
Okay! Nice shot!
Let's see the ones behind it.
I will get back at you.
You can move that one.
Shall I move it?
- Okay. Let's go.
- Get ready. Set, go.
(Team Won Hee's robbery starts!)
All right.
(Did Jong Kook decide to get
the furniture?)
There is nothing.
We can only make one trip.
- Suk Jin.
- We can only make one trip.
- Put it down.
- You can put it there.
- Come on.
- 2, 1.
They didn't get here on time.
You guys are out.
(Won Hee and Kwang Soo, Suk Jin,)
(Ji Hyo, and Jong Kook)
Here are the results
of the second robbery.
The lowest price is zero dollars.
The highest price is...
(The highest price)
- 10,000 dollars.
- Who is it?
(Je Hoon is the one
behind the item!)
Did anyone bring one item?
- It can't be someone with one item.
- Hold on.
- Je Hoon.
- Me?
I just brought one item.
- Did you bring 1 item?
- He brought 1 item.
(Did Je Hoon pick a statue
by chance?)
(Je Hoon looked for a statue
as soon as the robbery began.)
(Could Je Hoon be the chairperson
or a police officer?)
- Did you bring 1 item?
- 1 item.
Things are becoming clear.
The ones who didn't bring any items
can't be the chairperson.
They didn't do their best.
Perhaps they did it on purpose
in order to avoid suspicion.
- Really?
- I don't know if they are...
the chairperson or a police officer,
but I have my eyes on a few people.
- It's obvious.
- Is Jong Kook going at it again?
I am not it, right?
- Kwang Soo isn't it.
- Okay!
Kwang Soo isn't it.
I didn't try my best
during the foot volleyball match.
- What?
- Never mind.
- I was just saying.
- Why are you mumbling?
- Seriously.
- Why are you so unsure?
There is no way Won Hee is it.
- Won Hee isn't it.
- For goodness' sake.
I am giving you a hint.
Let's move on.
I will now give you
the rules of the final race.
It's Tomb Robbers versus Betrayers.
- Betrayers.
- Tomb Robbers versus Betrayers.
If the chairperson
or the two police officers are out,
the race ends right away.
When everyone is dispersed
before the race...
(When everyone is dispersed
before the race...)
Is that really necessary?
Before the race...
(Listening)
- What are you doing?
- I am listening carefully.
We look like robbers, right?
- Suk Jin is covering his ears.
- Seriously.
The sound resonates this way.
Before the race begins,
(The robbers don't want to miss
a word from the producer.)
- every criminal will get...
- Every criminal.
- one chance of betrayal.
- Betrayal.
(Every criminal will get
one chance of betrayal.)
One chance?
- What is that?
- Do we only get one chance?
If you betray the chairperson
and side with the police officers,
the odds of the penalty change.
(The odds of the penalty change.)
The number of members doesn't matter
with Team Police.
If Team Police loses,
one member will get the penalty.
(If Team Police loses,
1 member will get the penalty.)
But if Team Chairperson loses,
everyone except for one member
will get the penalty.
(Everyone except for 1 member
will get the penalty.)
(A betrayal brings down the odds
of getting a penalty.)
Then...
- I should betray.
- You can join Team Police...
- to avoid the penalty.
- The chairperson...
and the robbers are
on the same team, right?
- That's the case now.
- If you betray...
You can betray.
If you think about the odds...
Everyone will betray
the chairperson.
However, not everyone can betray.
Are there limits?
Members who want to betray
and join Team Police...
- must pay the price.
- We need money.
The price will be revealed
when you go to your spot.
- We need money.
- I bet it's expensive.
- You can't betray if you are poor.
- There is a price.
Once you decide to betray or not,
you can use your mission money...
to buy a hint on the police officers
or the chairperson.
(Buy a hint on the police officers
or the chairperson.)
If you make wrong deductions...
and rip off
a fellow team member's name tag,
you will be out right away.
(You are out if you rip off
a fellow team member's name tag.)
Please go to your spot...
to decide on the betrayal
and purchase a hint.
- Okay.
(What will become
of the Tomb Robbery Association?)
(Current amount of money: Jong Kook,
Je Hoon, Suk Jin, Se Chan, So Min,)
(Jae Suk, Haha, Won Hee, Ji Hyo,
and Kwang Soo)
When will you tell me
how much I need to betray?
Hurry up and tell me.
I have a lot of money.
I have 12,000 dollars.
The current amount of money
you have is 23,000 dollars.
The price of the betrayal.
(The price of the betrayal is...)
The price of the betrayal is
7,000 dollars.
(7,000 dollars.)
- And...
- It's quite expensive.
- 7,000 dollars.
- What?
7,000 dollars.
(Since Jae Suk has 9,000 dollars,
the betrayal will take everything.)
(Will he betray the team
or stay loyal?)
This is driving me crazy.
The price of the betrayal is
7,000 dollars.
It isn't that expensive, but...
7,000... 7,000 dollars?
Then I have just the amount.
There must be members
who can't afford to betray.
That's right.
They might not have enough money.
- Am I in the last place?
- You are in the last place.
Among all the members?
(He is in the last place
among 10 members.)
7,000 dollars?
(Se Chan has 18,000 dollars.)
I will betray!
(I will betray!)
It's in my nature.
I need to avoid the penalty.
Since there are two police officers,
they are more likely to win.
Okay. I will buy it.
I have to buy it.
Since I have enough money,
betrayal seems like a good choice.
- I will betray.
- Okay.
Kwang Soo and a few others...
- will betray.
- A lot of people will betray.
(Some of them could be police offers
who are acting.)
Betrayal?
(This man is torn.)
I don't know. Should I betray?
People shouldn't betray.
(People shouldn't betray.)
(How will it be?)
How will it be?
There is no reason for me...
(There is no reason for me...)
to betray.
(Je Hoon announces that there is
no reason for him to betray.)
(1 hour before the shoot
at E Cafe in Yangpyeong)
You two are undercover officers
who received tip-offs...
and infiltrated
Tomb Robbery Association.
You win if you find and eliminate
the chairperson.
I will give you
the price of the items.
(They memorized
the price of the items in advance.)
(He got relatively cheap items
during the 1st robbery...)
(in order to avoid suspicion.)
(Then he succeeded to get
a statue...)
(during the 2nd robbery.)
(He acquired 10,000 dollars.)
(Je Hoon, a police officer,
blended in with the robbers.)
I will find the robbers who betrayed
the association...
and ask them...
to identify the chairperson.
(Among
the four new police officers...)
(is a police officer
who didn't need to betray.)
(Meanwhile, other members)
I won't betray.
- I won't betray.
I will stay on this team.
I will say that I used my money.
"I used 7,000 dollars..."
"and became a police officer."
I will say that.
That's the loyalty
of the tomb robber family.
(The chairperson is hiding
among them.)
- You could purchase a hint.
- Okay.
It's 10,000 dollars per hint.
What are you playing at?
Unfortunately...
How could a hint be
more expensive...
than the betrayal?
Is a hint more expensive?
(He only has 3,000 dollars.)
- There are two types of hints.
- Okay.
One type lets you inquire about
a specific member's affiliation.
(- What's A's affiliation?
- A is a member of Team Police.)
The other type
lets you inquire about...
the chairperson
or a police officer's identity.
(- The chairperson!
- The chairperson is a comedian.)
I brought two statues earlier.
They cost 10,000 dollars each.
There were other people
who brought them.
I will inquire about Je Hoon.
He is too suspicious.
(Jong Kook receives a password.)
(He needs to find and open
the hint box to receive the hint!)
Then I will buy two hints
on the police officers.
Since there are people
I am suspicious about,
the hints will make me certain.
The hints will narrow them down.
Firstly, Jong Kook...
made a lot of money...
during the robberies.
I think...
there is a chance...
he knew the price of each item
because is the chairperson.
I will buy a hint
on Jong Kook's affiliation.
Then I will use 10,000 dollars...
to buy a hint on the chairperson.
(5 robbers versus 5 police officers)
Actually,
if I were a police officer,
I would stick
with the other police officer.
(Serious)
(Cawing)
The crows are laughing at you.
They didn't laugh. They cried.
They cried.
Crows cry, not laugh.
(Even crows would laugh...)
You drive me crazy.
(at his simple-minded deduction.)
Where could the lock be?
(What?)
Je Hoon, where are you going?
(He finds Jae Suk,
a robber who hasn't betrayed.)
Mr. Chairperson.
- Mr. Chairperson?
- Yes.
Why are you calling me that?
Mr. Chairperson.
- Hey.
- I will be loyal to you.
- Did I become the chairperson?
- Yes.
- Je Hoon, I am not the chairperson.
- Really?
Yes.
(The rookie police officer's tactic
isn't very effective.)
(Isn't he the police officer?)
- Ms. Chairwoman.
- Hello.
(His next target is Ji Hyo,
a robber.)
You must be exhausted.
Gosh, I am exhausted.
(He doesn't gain
any helpful information.)
Mr. Chairperson.
You are here.
You aren't it.
(He figured out
that Haha is an underling.)
- You aren't it.
- I was happy for a second.
Jae Suk, how much money
did you have?
- Me?
- You had some money, right?
- I didn't have a lot.
- Really?
According to Suk Jin,
- the statues cost 10,000 dollars.
- Really?
That's what Suk Jin said.
He stole a statue...
- and got 10,000 dollars.
- I got it too.
- You and So Min stole one each.
- Me too.
- Did you steal one?
- I stole one.
Jong Kook stole 2
during the 1st robbery.
He got 20,000 dollars.
What are you doing
during an important conversation?
What are you doing?
- Did you just pick your nose?
- Why did you pick your nose?
Can't I pick my nose?
We were having
an important conversation.
This much finger went inside.
Did you see that?
What?
He picked his nose.
- What about it?
- I mean,
you didn't scratch your nose.
You picked your nose for real.
For goodness' sake.
Why wouldn't I do that?
Ji Hyo, did you have a lot of money?
In any case,
we should gather information.
Let's find the hints.
- I mean, treasures.
- During the second robbery,
I didn't make any money.
- Se Chan.
- Yes, Jong Kook?
- You punk.
- Jong Kook.
Did you betray?
- I can't tell you about that.
- You are right.
Right now...
Hold on. You have a lot of money.
Hold on. What makes you think
that I have a lot of money?
- Hold on.
- I know you do.
It's strange that you know
how much money...
- I have.
- Hold on.
- You are like a judge.
- Listen.
I will be honest with you.
I received a lot of money...
for the items I brought back.
Then I did some calculations...
and figured out
that you made a lot of money.
Jong Kook, be careful.
It's not like that. The way...
- he talks...
- Are you on his side now?
Now that Jong Kook
isn't suspicious of you,
you seem confident.
- This is insane.
- Did you get a hint already?
- Not yet.
- Right? Of course, you didn't.
But hints are meaningless,
Kwang Soo.
I already have candidates
on my radar.
(The 2 of them are
on Jong Kook's radar.)
I just need to go and check.
Won Hee isn't a police officer.
- He is just...
- No, he isn't.
- He is just here as a guest.
- Jong Kook.
He just came here to play
a game of foot volleyball.
That's why he came today.
(Walking around)
- Won Hee!
- Yes?
What are you looking for?
Money.
(What does he mean?)
I am looking for money.
(Won Hee still doesn't understand
the rules.)
It's hard to get a hint.
I am looking for money.
It's hard indeed.
It would be so easy to take off
the name tag.
It's not the time yet.
- I got you already.
- You startled me.
- Really?
You got me already.
(Laughing)
(Won Hee avoids
everyone's suspicion.)
(Meanwhile, Je Hoon,
a rookie police officer,)
(was looking for a hint box.)
(He finally finds one.)
There is a lock.
(It's the number 2 hint box
he was looking for.)
There we go.
(A box containing a hint
on the chairperson)
"The chairperson was born
after the month of May."
(The chairperson was born
after the month of May.)
(What?)
Jong Kook was born on April 25.
Then he isn't the chairperson.
Oh, my goodness.
(The strongest candidate,
Jong Kook, doesn't have a role.)
Then Jong Kook doesn't have a role.
(Jong Kook gets taken out.)
Haha, Jae Suk...
(The real chairperson is
among them.)
Ji Hyo can't be it.
No way.
Hold on. There is a room.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook)
What's the number? 20!
It's the box I was looking for.
I didn't know...
there was a place like this.
2457.
(A hint on the 2 police officers
is inside.)
2457.
(He carefully punches in
the numbers.)
Let's see it.
("They debuted
after Kim Jong Kook did.")
"They debuted
after Kim Jong Kook did."
People who debuted after I did...
That's too broad.
"They debuted
after Kim Jong Kook did."
- Jae Suk, I found another hint.
- What is it?
The police officers debuted
after I did.
Too many people fit
that description.
Either Se Chan or So Min
could be a police officer.
- It's entirely possible.
- Right?
But I think So Min is...
a former robber
who switched teams with money.
- She would have done that.
- That's right.
Then there are three.
There are three police officers.
Jae Suk.
I need 2,000 dollars.
Hurry up and give them to me.
- Jae Suk.
- She is energetic.
There is something about her.
Don't be like that.
- Hey.
- Give me 2,000 dollars.
You are older than me.
It's only 2,000 dollars...
for me.
Oh, those words make him weak.
And I will give you...
- 1,000 more dollars.
- Why?
Why?
- Are you giving her more money?
Go and use it.
- There you go.
- Why?
(Ripping)
(He removes So Min's name tag!)
Go and use it.
Let's see it. Let's see the result.
- You betrayed the association.
- I bet she did.
- It's obvious.
- You can't say anything.
(What was So Min's identity?)
A robber-turned-police officer,
So Min is out.
(A robber-turned-police officer,
So Min is out.)
- It's you, isn't it?
- You betrayed us.
- Right.
I was sure of it.
We were talking about you,
and you suddenly appeared.
So this is expenses for a journey.
Yes, money for the journey
to the afterlife.
Farewell, friend.
- All right.
- I shouldn't have come here.
I shouldn't have...
(Taking the money back)
A robber-turned-police officer,
So Min is out.
(Team Police member,
So Min is out!)
(Original police Je Hoon)
(I should've protected her.)
Whatever.
(Moments after!)
(Ripping!)
What did you just do?
A robber-turned-police officer,
Suk Jin is out.
Who are you?
(Team Police loses two members.)
(So Min and Suk Jin are out
and Je Hoon is alive.)
(So one of them
is the last of the original police.)
(Jae Suk is looking
for a hint box.)
(He finds a hint box.)
(What kind of hint did he buy?)
Tell me about Se Chan's identity.
Yes.
2, 4, 2, 7.
(Opening the hint box)
I knew it.
(So what's Se Chan's identity?)
(He's a police officer!)
It was here, number 2.
Je Hoon.
Je Hoon, what was the number?
(What was the original
police officer's number?)
You two are undercover officers.
You will pretend to be criminals.
So we're police officers?
I'm glad. Normally, I get to be
robbers or bad guys.
But I get to be an officer
because I'm with you.
I'm an officer. Good.
(They went undercover
to find the chairperson.)
We can get a hint
with 2,000 dollars.
- 2,000 dollars.
- Okay.
(Handing 2,000 dollars)
We want a hint on the chairperson.
They suspect
that I'm a police officer.
So you should make them think
you're the chairperson.
- Then, use me as bait.
- Are you sure?
Tell them you think
I'm the police officer.
(I'm the chairperson.)
- I am the chairperson.
- No, you're not.
(And Yang Se Chan is
a police officer.)
(He is the chairperson.)
(There weren't many hints
in the beginning.)
(So Je Hoon could avoid suspicion.)
(Succeeded)
This is a problem. We're in trouble.
- We should rip off their name tags.
- But the good thing is...
- Jong Kook isn't the chairperson.
- No.
If we rip everyone else's name
tag off, we will win.
(It may work if it isn't
Jong Kook's name tag.)
Who eliminated So Min?
Jae Suk did.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
Did you know Se Chan
is the prime suspect?
- I didn't know that.
- It's odd that you don't know that.
How can you not know that?
I didn't get any hints.
It's not about the hint.
I guess you betrayed us then.
- No.
- He has the character to betray us.
I didn't have any money.
So Min said the same thing.
"Jong Kook,
I didn't have any money."
But I know Ji Hyo is a robber.
Yes, I am.
Because I got the hint.
I'm a robber.
You got the hint
that says she's a robber?
- Well, I...
- Where did you get it?
You can't carry the hint around.
- No, you can't.
- This one's different.
What do you mean? Let me see it.
- Maybe he found it.
- He's lying. Look at him.
- Show us.
- Let me see it.
- That's the one they gave us.
- Yes.
I have one too.
(Kwang Soo shows them
a piece of paper and it says...)
(Song Ji Hyo)
You wrote it down.
You found it up there, didn't you?
I saw it lying around.
They won't give us a hint
like that, you fool.
(The one lying around
like Ji Hyo said)
(Kwang Soo fabricated
the hint himself.)
(He used his fake hint...)
(to prove he's a member of
Tomb Robbery Association.)
(So he used it again
to avoid suspicion.)
Ji Hyo, I think he's trying
to avoid something.
(His action caused more suspicion.)
This is crazy.
I'm not the one.
Where are you going?
(Testing)
You're a robber.
Why would I eliminate you?
Just rip it off.
You want to, don't you?
- You're dying to take her name tag.
- Don't make that face.
Everyone suspected that it was me.
- If I were...
- Why are you framing Ji Hyo?
I'm not.
(Trying to get out of it)
I want us to be on the same team.
(Something isn't right.)
Even if I were a police officer...
(Grabbing)
What are you doing?
Kwang Soo, let's stop this.
- Kwang Soo, sorry.
- Don't do this.
- But...
- You've been weird.
- Yes.
- What?
- You've been acting weird.
- We have to do this.
- Don't.
Don't do this.
(Right then)
(The only way to survive
is to run away!)
(They take action since they've
been fooled by him for 10 years.)
(Finally, they rip off
Kwang Soo's name tag.)
(I told you not to rip off
my name tag.)
(They just eliminated
their own team member.)
Jong Kook is out.
(Robber Jong Kook is out.)
(So Kwang Soo was a robber too.)
- Seriously?
- I told you.
(I told you we're on the same team.)
Why were you acting so strangely?
I wasn't acting strangely.
I was just trying...
find the hint and money.
You should've told us.
I told you from this morning.
- I said it from the beginning.
- Then why would you lie?
Why would you lie about things?
I have a sickness.
What? A sickness?
People suspect you because you lie.
Why would you lie?
It's just a sickness
I've had for a long time.
If you know it's a sickness,
you should get treated.
Kim Jong Kook, why are you out?
- What?
- I eliminated Kwang Soo.
Why would you rip
Kwang Soo's name tag off?
He lied about something.
He acts strangely all the time.
Try to understand me.
Come on. I thought he betrayed us.
(They found out Kwang Soo's identity
by sacrificing Jong Kook.)
- You should work harder for me.
- Just go.
What is it?
(He finds a hint box.)
The chairperson made a debut
after 2000?
(Debuted after 2000?)
(So the chairperson
is either Kwang Soo or Ji Hyo.)
The chairperson made a debut
after 2000.
After 2000?
It's either Ji Hyo or Kwang Soo.
- Did you betray them?
- Yes.
Good.
They must be looking for you.
Hey, Yang Se Chan
is a police officer.
- And Je Hoon?
- He's an officer too.
Who's the chairperson then?
Are you the chairperson?
- No.
- You couldn't do it?
- Didn't you have money?
- I only had 3,000 dollars.
- He didn't have any money.
- Me neither.
Is it Won Hee then?
(Is Won Hee the chairperson?)
- Won Hee is...
- Is everyone here a robber?
- Won Hee is the chairperson?
- I'm a robber.
I'm really a robber.
I am too.
If Won Hee is the chairperson
he's in big trouble.
But...
Se Chan and Jae Hoon
went up there.
- Then we should...
- Wait.
get Yang Se Chan right now.
Or the chairperson...
Won Hee can't run around like this.
They both went up.
He couldn't trust us so he went up.
What's wrong with him?
I think they believe that you are...
Well, they're going to attack me.
But they won't attack you.
So you should attack them.
It's either Ji Hyo...
- or Kwang Soo.
- Yes, those two.
So you should take the lead
and attack them.
- Get Ji Hyo.
- Yes, either one of them.
I don't think you can win Kwang Soo.
But I don't think
you can win Ji Hyo either.
Do you think you're strong enough?
It's not like I can rip it off
after asking her.
You should rip it off
when her guard is down.
How can do that?
- They're professionals.
- I can't do it though.
You should go down.
They're not suspecting you.
Everyone thinks you're a ghost.
So just wander around.
They don't even imagine...
that you will
rip their name tags off.
So let's call this "Ghost Mission".
- So just rip it?
- Yes. "Ghost Mission."
Okay. I'll do that.
I should've just fought.
- It's Won Hee.
- Where?
- Won Hee!
- Where is he?
Won Hee!
Won Hee, come here!
- Why?
- What?
You're the chairperson, aren't you?
Am I the chairperson?
What are you talking about?
You should tell us now.
- Tell you what?
- You have to be the chairperson.
What?
What are you talking about?
Won Hee needs to pull through.
My gosh.
- There they are.
- Won Hee.
They're sticking to each other now.
Yes, they are.
Won Hee, what happened?
I found out. It's not me. It's him.
Won Hee is the one.
- He's the one.
- How can you prove it?
What? I have the hint.
- Show us.
- What?
Prove it.
I have a hint too.
(Team Police can't attack
because they're outnumbered.)
Wait a minute.
I didn't do anything.
(He suddenly touched
Jae Suk's name tag.)
I'm not sure of anything.
Just calm down.
You can trust me.
- Aren't you a police officer?
- No!
It's Won Hee. Just trust me.
It's not me.
- It's really not me. Please.
- Are you sure?
What are you doing behind her?
(Kwang Soo caught him.)
What were you doing?
He was looking at their name tags.
- Why did you do that?
- Why did you?
My goodness.
Kwang Soo isn't for sure.
Who eliminated Jong Kook?
We can't tell you that.
(Won Hee slowly approaches someone.)
(Staring)
(It's not a good time
to attack right now.)
(Very worried)
(Everyone's here.)
(And he's getting closer
to Ji Hyo from behind.)
- Wait. What?
- What is he doing?
(Everyone can't believe it but
he ripped off Ji Hyo's name tag.)
He's a police officer.
You did it when everyone's around?
- What was that?
- I can't believe it.
Song Ji Hyo is out.
(A robber, Song Ji Hyo is out!)
Are you a police officer?
(That means the chairperson
is Kwang Soo!)
(So they found out
who the chairperson is.)
- Are you a robber?
- What? I can't trust anyone.
- Then we should get him too.
- What's going on?
(Ripping off his name tag
mercilessly)
(But right then!)
(While everyone
is watching Won Hee,)
(Se Chan attacks Kwang Soo!)
- What?
- Here we go.
(The moment they figured out
everyone's identity...)
Hey, Je Hoon!
- Je Hoon!
- Get Kwang Soo!
- Hey, get him!
- Kwang Soo!
No, you can't do this!
- It's Kwang Soo.
- No, wait!
Je Hoon, it's Kwang Soo.
Come on.
Take Se Chan's name tag off!
(Je Hoon's attacking Kwang Soo
the chairperson!)
Why would you take it off
when everyone's around?
- I wasn't supposed to do that?
- No.
(Tomb Robbery Association will lose
if they get Kwang Soo!)
Je Hoon!
(He got Je Hoon's name tag!)
- No!
- Je Hoon!
(Original police, Lee Je Hoon
is out!)
- Gosh, he took mine.
- Come here!
- Eliminate Se Chan!
- No.
(If they get Se Chan,
Team Robbers will win.)
- Eliminate Se Chan!
- No.
(The situation has changed.)
Rip it off.
(The original officer Yang Se Chan
is out.)
Both officers have been eliminated.
(Team Robber wins.)
(Touched)
It was intense until the end.
I almost got my name tag
ripped off.
Won Hee. Won Hee!
What did I tell you?
I told you to rip Ji Hyo's name tag
off when there was no one around.
There are so many people.
You think they're ghosts or what?
- In front of nobody?
- What was that?
I'm supposed to rip it off
in front of nobody?
- Why did you do that?
- If I have to rip it off...
How can I rip it off
in front of nobody?
You did the opposite.
- What's wrong with him?
- Did I ruin it?
I was surprised.
Did I do it wrong? What's going on?
I'm sorry.
I don't know how the rule works.
Our last hint was after 2000,
- so there were only two.
- Right.
- So...
- Are you the chairperson?
- Yes.
- I knew it.
You are...
(Lee Kwang Soo, chairperson
of Tomb Robbery Association)
(Chairperson Kwang Soo
knew the price.)
(He robbed only cheap items
to avoid suspicion.)
(As a result, he escaped
from Jong Kook's radar.)
(He used money as an excused
and acted like a robber.)
(Kwang Soo found out
that Suk Jin was a police officer.)
(Ripping off)
(It was Kwang Soo who eliminated
Suk Jin.)
(The chairperson hid
his identity...)
(and worked secretly.)
- Gosh.
- I knew it.
- That was close.
- You tried so hard too.
- It was you.
- You should've told me.
We won thanks to Won Hee.
I couldn't believe Won Hee.
The winner of Robber versus Robber:
Faceless King of Tomb Robbery is...
Team Chairperson.
That's us.
There was a reason Kwang Soo...
- didn't betray us.
- He had an unavoidable reason.
He couldn't because
he's the chairperson.
The chairperson should pick
one person to receive the prize.
- That's...
- Really?
- Yes.
- That's nice.
The prize is a luxury teacup.
Pick one person.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Sure.
- She matches the teacup.
- Yes.
- It's pretty. It's expensive.
- This is nice.
- Ji Hyo. It's perfect for soju.
- Right.
- It's just one sip.
- That's awesome.
One person from Team Police...
- will receive a penalty.
- That's what's important.
- This is why I had to betray.
- I wish it's Suk Jin.
- Today's penalty is...
- What is it?
- the water basin bomb.
- What? Water basin?
It's going to be cold.
- That's perfect.
- It's going to be cold.
I wish the person who betrayed
should be it.
- That's better.
- From there,
- pick one, Won Hee.
- Here.
- I'm safe.
- You passed.
I'll go next.
(2nd betrayer Suk Jin)
(It's him.)
(Betrayer Suk Jin will
receive the penalty.)
What happened? How did it go?
It's a party.
- How did it go?
- It's a party. This is nice.
- The betrayer gets the water basin.
- To the betrayer.
My goodness.
- I just had to pick that one.
- It's heavy.
- It just had to be that one.
How do you want it?
- 1, 2, 3.
- Sprinkle at once.
Slowly. Yes. That's it.
(A cool water bomb to a betrayer)
(It's too cold to speak.)
That's awesome.
(Wet)
- It's a water cannon.
- That was a good one.
He's completely wet.
- You totally got me.
Good job. Suk Jin is good.
- It was good.
- Good work.
(Finally)
(It's the Jeju Island Special.)
(They haven't been to the sea
for a long time.)
(They all feel great
by the sea breeze.)
(The island with wind,
rocks, and women)
(Han Ji Eun, So E Hyun)
(Choi Yeo Jin, Lee Ju Bin)
(Jeju Restaurant Tour...)
(is what they wished.)
(Just because they came
all the way to Jeju Island,)
(it doesn't mean
they all can have fun.)
- Meow.
- Come on.
(Extraordinary strong girls'...)
(ruthless match)
(Dirty fight in Jeju Island)
(She went to school with So Min.)
(There is an awkward reunion
with a schoolmate.)
Hey.
(There's tension between the two.)
(Extraordinary relationship)
(What will happen to them?)
(The Jeju Island Special:
Wind, Women, Rocks, and Bombs)