- Hello. - Hello.
(It's already the last episode in 2020.)
Hello.
What? Why are you wearing denim jackets?
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan are wearing matching.)
I don't know. I just put it on and realized Kwang Soo's wearing it too.
Are you two running a shopping mall together?
Gosh, no.
- Suk Jin. - Yes?
Why do you look so mischievous today?
What did you say?
(Glad)
Hello, Suk Jin.
You guys go ahead and talk.
I'm putting on the microphone now.
Why are you yelling at us?
- Why are you so upset? - What's so upsetting?
- We were complimenting your outfit. - What made you upset?
He wouldn't even say hello to us without a microphone.
(Disappointed)
He's really ridiculous.
(His work hour begins with the microphone.)
Once I put on the microphone, my work begins.
Suk Jin wants to join us,
so he keeps leaning forward. He can't wait to talk.
(Hesitating)
(He's eager to talk.)
It's not done, but he wants to talk already.
(He's a pro who wouldn't move without a mic.)
- I know. - He can't wait to come here.
Dogs find it hard to wait.
Jong Kook, isn't that what you wore last week?
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook appears.)
These are my own clothes.
It's cold outside.
(He always wears something perfect for a workout.)
Why are you wearing your own clothes?
Why do you have your stylist then?
(The stylist)
Why is she coming with you?
Just to show off.
I see.
That's 1 of the 5 world's greatest mysteries.
(What does a stylist mean to Jong Kook?)
You got your hair done.
- Why did you not change? - Why is Ji Seon here as a stylist?
(He creates a job to show off.)
Just to show off.
Suk Jin, you are wearing Cheon Young Rock's glasses.
- It's from the 1980s. - He looks young, right?
(Suk Jin's been wearing glasses for fashion.)
- The glasses... - He looks younger.
I wore them the other day, and people liked them.
- You look a lot younger. - I see.
- You look younger. - That's not why I'm wearing them.
There is a limit to how much younger he can get.
What limit?
(1 less)
You look like 54.
There is a limit to how much younger he can get.
(1 or 2 years are his limit.)
It's just a couple of years at most.
I'm healthier than you, though.
It's not like he looks younger. He looks less old.
(Brutal fact)
- Exactly. - Hey.
- He can't look young. - That's...
(Suk Jin's about to get knocked out.)
the best we can do.
Hey.
My friends my age are going to kill you.
- Who's going to kill us? - My friends my age.
Do you think my friends will let it happen?
Do you want to fight?
- You're no match for them. - My friends born in 1972...
(A man born in 1966 versus a man born in 1972)
My friends won't let this slide.
I will bring my friends together.
Seriously...
It will be hard for Suk Jin to bring his friends together.
- It's hard. - They rarely get together.
(He starts to find group meetings too tiring.)
For Suk Jin,
I think four would grab him by the collar, to begin with.
Why would they grab me by the collar?
(Ji-rasoni carries the team by himself since morning.)
- They will. - No, no. Why?
Why would they? We're having a conversation.
He's not a good fighter.
But he's wiry.
- And he's resilient. - Right.
(Laughing)
Do you want to know how he fights?
He just lets his opponent hit one side of his face.
He just offers them to hit his cheek.
(He turns the other cheek for two more punches.)
- His cheek. - I say, "Just hit me."
But I never pass out.
He says he never passes out.
(The oldest member's struggle leaves them sighing.)
I never pass out.
- I feel bad for him. - You know what?
It's like we're on "Lee Suk Jin Show".
What? Why would you say that?
Can we just hit you and wrap this up?
- No way. - Come on. Just one punch.
(He suffers helplessly from the other members.)
- Why would you hit me? - By the way...
- I should hit you and wrap this up. - Stop it already.
Your face turned red.
It's because it's hot in here.
(He talks back every time.)
Now Suk Jin's all warmed up.
We can finally begin now.
(Shall we start the show now?)
- Let's do this. - Yes, let's do this.
- This feels good. - Hello, everyone.
(They warm up their mouths and get ready for the opening.)
Hello!
Hello, everyone.
Let's do this.
This is our last episode this year.
- Is that so? - Really?
Really?
I just hope this year ends soon.
Yes, I hate this year.
(This year was particularly tough.)
It was the worst.
(We'd like to let it go without feeling sorry.)
- Yes, it should end soon. - Yes.
I would rather turn 50. My goodness.
- You're right. - You're 50 soon.
(For Jae Suk who's almost 50...)
- Yes. - You'll be 50.
(and the other members, we have special year-end snacks.)
We'll enjoy the year-end with some chips.
It's red chili flavor.
It goes better with Coke.
(The texture)
Is it crisp both on the inside and outside?
Stupid both on the inside and outside.
Come on. This is an ad.
How could you say that?
(It becomes a commercial about Kwang Soo the actor.)
- You are... - How could you...
- How could you say that? - You said so yourself.
(Irritated)
I said it's crisp both on the inside and outside.
Yes, stupid both on the inside and outside.
Can I take this home with me?
(The one who's stupid both on the inside and outside won't stop.)
Just taste it first.
(Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo)
We're doing the ad on condition that you don't talk about this.
What are you talking about?
(What are you saying?)
(A cue card is given to the members.)
Please enjoy.
- Can someone take this card? - All right.
"Running Man Year-End Feelings Settlement".
"This is the last episode of 2020."
"Go into each booth that has each member's name tag on it..."
"and write what you were upset about each member this year."
- Gosh. - What I was upset about them?
I wasn't much upset about anything.
Do we have to write it in every booth?
No, you don't have to.
(They can write as much as they want...)
(to people they want to write to.)
- Only a few? - For the ones you were upset with.
- Only for those I was upset with? - You're right.
(They'll enter the booth of the person to write it.)
What should I write about?
Well, there's nothing much...
(Heartwarming)
- Right, there is nothing much. - There's nothing much.
- There's nothing to write about. - Right. Because...
(Grunting)
everything is understandable.
- There's nothing to write about. - Everything is understandable.
(Nothing much he's upset about but he goes to Suk Jin's booth.)
- Gosh. - What are you going to write about?
(Suk Jin's booth already has a waiting line.)
- Excuse me. - Hey!
Excuse me.
- Is someone in there? - What will you write about?
(He grabbed the pen without thinking much.)
- Someone is in here. - Oh, I see.
- Someone's in here. - I should write something.
(Looks like members will line up in front of Suk Jin's booth.)
My goodness.
I have some things to say to Se Chan.
I have some things to say to you too.
I have something for Se Chan.
(Scared already)
Really?
I even have something for Jae Suk too.
- What? - Me? What is it?
- I'm upset because of you. - Why?
(They're going to feel upset out of the blue today.)
Then I should write one for you too. What am I upset about?
(Remembering the grudges they have against each other)
Yang Se Can.
What is it, Jae Suk?
What is it?
I can't believe it. I just can't.
It's anonymous, right?
- Yes, just write down the content. - Kwang Soo.
(As they hear it's anonymous,)
(they all stand up.)
Right. There's one for Ji Hyo too.
Gosh, my legs.
I'm remembering things now that I've started.
(Waiting line)
My goodness. People are lined up.
Wait a minute. Is that my booth?
- You can't line up there. - I'm just here like everyone else.
(Waiting in front of Se Chan's booth)
- Then what should I do? - All right then.
(What is he so upset about Se Chan...)
- Someone's in there? - Yes.
I wrote for Haha.
(that he had to wait in line?)
(Ji Hyo said she's not upset about anything,)
I don't have to write one if there's nothing, right?
(but she's writing something down.)
(Mumbling for no reason)
Gosh, I don't have anything to write about.
Ji Hyo, were you upset with So Min?
What are you doing?
- Were you spying on me? - Why were you in there?
- I did nothing. - Ji Hyo, what were you doing?
(To me?)
I did nothing.
(She snoops around after saying she doesn't remember any.)
Why would you go in there?
No, I'm just checking something.
I mean, why would you go in there?
(They're all going rogue as if they've been waiting for it.)
I wrote something for Se Chan and...
They're writing all sorts of stuff now.
They're writing about their flaws.
They are...
(Now they started writing each other's flaws.)
Maybe there's nothing else to write about.
They're all writing about the members' flaws.
Not what they're upset about.
(2020 Year-End Feelings Settlement has lost its purpose.)
It's just a slander.
That's so funny. Our flaws?
(Before they hurt their feelings,)
It's not what they're upset about.
(we'll wrap it up here.)
- Excuse me. - Now everyone should come out.
All right.
(Sharing the things they were upset about with Jong Kook)
- It's what you wrote for Jong Kook. - All right.
I wonder what you're upset about me.
Here it goes.
(The person asked to remain anonymous.)
- It's completely anonymous. - All right.
"He doesn't know how to control his strength."
- It's something to be upset about. - I'm sure.
(Empathizing)
- It's possible. - Yes, everyone will agree.
I recognize the handwriting.
- I know who wrote that. - Really?
I'm not so sure though.
(The handwriting is especially poor to guarantee anonymity.)
- Why are you nervous? - You're not sure?
Why are you so nervous?
- Are you really sure? - Next.
"He gets dubious without thinking."
"I'm sick of it."
- This person's sick of it. - Sick of it?
I understand.
(Trying to look away)
Yes, it's understandable.
"Whenever I'm the spy,"
"I want to get rid of him."
(His excessive suspicious led the person to feel upset.)
It's getting dubious too.
He doubts too much.
(He suspects someone again when that's what caused this.)
It's not me.
- It's Haha. - It wasn't me.
Next.
"He only likes his daughter."
What's that?
Here we go.
This person wrote without thinking.
"He only spends money on his daughter."
(The source of his rumor about an American daughter)
People will think it's true.
The next one says,
"Se Chan speaks ill of you behind your back."
What?
(Is that so?)
What is this?
(Baffled)
- It's so obvious who wrote it. - It's So Min.
(Competing with their loyalty)
I think it's So Min.
Next says... This is funny.
"When he's the spy,"
"he uses his strength to prove otherwise."
(Everyone has an experience of it.)
(He admits it.)
- This is so true. - It's something to be upset about.
- He really does that. - So you've all been upset.
(There were 14 letters to Jong Kook.)
(Things they're upset with Suk Jin)
Here are the things Suk Jin did that made us upset.
"He doesn't speak to us unless the camera..."
"or the microphone is on."
(Kwang Soo wrote it as he experienced it this morning again.)
- "Even if we say hello," - It's something to be upset about.
"he doesn't speak to us."
- I'm really upset about it too. - Yes, you're right.
- It's so true. - Do I really do that?
Once I knocked on his car window to say hi,
but he didn't even lower the window.
- I guess he's a professional. - Yes, he's a pro.
(A true professional who spares his energy when there's no camera)
- He's a professional. - He acts when the camera rolls.
(Hilarious)
- This is the worst. - What is it?
"He pretends his family's precious."
(They're upset with Suk Jin's unnatural side.)
- Of course this upsets us. - Yes.
- It's the worst. - The worst.
- And it upsets us. - Gosh.
(Even Ji-rasoni gives in.)
- So Min, you did this. - It wasn't me.
- You wrote all three comments. - This is funny too.
"He pulls a string of hair that grows on his ear."
What was that again?
Don't pull it.
I don't have hair growing on my ear!
(They just want him around longer.)
- Yes, you do. - Let me see.
I don't!
You should water it.
- You wrote it, right? - I didn't.
(The person wishes him to live a long life.)
I don't have hair on the ear.
- Water the hair. - This is so funny.
Now, here are the things that Kwang Soo did that upset us.
(Things they're upset with Kwang Soo)
- "He's gotten ugly." - What?
- "His fashion sense is excessive." - Right, people ask me this a lot.
They ask me why you're getting ugly.
"He contacts me only when he's drunk."
"His back hair is too long."
"His forelock is too short compared to the back hair."
It's not like I can grow my forelock down here.
(Summary: We're upset because you only cherish your back hair.)
Isn't it natural to have...
- longer back hair? - Is it something to be upset about?
Of course the forelock is shorter than the back hair.
(A charge of having longer back hair)
I was serious, but this person wasn't.
Why is this person upset about my hair?
This is just a malicious comment.
Okay, next.
"I don't like his face especially when he smiles."
"His face is crooked."
- Wait a minute. - It's nothing to be upset about.
This person's upset because my face is crooked?
- This is too much. - Why does it make you upset?
(The person wants him to smile evenly.)
- What if that's my weak point? - This is...
- So funny. - Because my face isn't symmetrical,
this person is upset?
"He's gotten even taller."
"I think he's as tall as a two-story apartment."
"I think he can grow as high as 3m,"
"but he's not trying much."
Who wrote this?
(The person wants him to grow taller.)
What's this? This is ridiculous.
- This is so funny. - How can this person say that?
Yes, you can be upset about it.
- You can grow up to 3m. - That's right.
- You can, so why aren't you trying? - We're upset about it.
How should I try harder?
(They're upset he doesn't work hard enough in terms of height.)
We're upset, so work harder.
Why aren't you trying harder? You can be taller.
- Why should I be taller? - Work harder.
Okay, next.
"When you had drinks with the younger members,"
"you hesitated to pay for it."
Seriously, he makes it too obvious.
(It was you, wasn't it?)
- Come on. It wasn't me. - Hey, hey.
(Shaking her head)
It wasn't like that.
- I had my reasons. - Hey, you're so stingy.
(The 3-meter-tall giant becomes smaller only in front of a counter.)
- I didn't hesitate. - He never spends money.
- Seriously. - I didn't hesitate.
(Kwang Soo has 14 letters including various malicious comments.)
I do spend money. And I didn't hesitate.
- Things you're upset with me. - All right.
(Followed by things they're upset with Jae Suk)
"You always try to hang up the phone."
"I'm bored of your hairstyle." "Your mouth protruded even more."
"Too bad you're not handsome enough."
(There are as many malicious comments as Kwang Soo's.)
- Gosh. - What is this?
Too bad that I'm not handsome enough?
You could be upset about it.
"I'm upset that your teeth aren't even."
Yes, I'm also upset that your teeth aren't even.
- This person really meant it. - Yes, you could be upset.
(They're upset about his set of teeth.)
This upsets me. My teeth aren't even?
- Yes, it upsets me. - Right.
It'd be funnier if I get some braces.
- No, you'll look better. - My goodness.
Look at Se Chan.
- He straightened his teeth. - Yes.
(Surprisingly, he already had braces.)
You'll look better.
Well, I don't look better though.
Yours are straightened, but they're still protruding.
- Yes, they're protruding. - Right.
- Straightened but protruding. - Yes, straightened but protruding.
(Kwang Soo doesn't miss the opportunity...)
- Straightened but protruding. - Gosh.
(to promote the chips.)
Gosh, straightened but protruding.
- Both on the outside and inside? - Yes, stupid on the inside.
Next is Song Ji Hyo.
(Next is Ji Hyo.)
"After my first filming, I texted that she did a good job..."
"and that I hope to be good friends with her."
"But she still hasn't replied."
Since the first filming?
(He's been waiting for 10 years.)
- You should reply to people. - Isn't that 10 years ago?
- Ji Hyo. - Gosh, this is upsetting.
No, Jae Suk. That's not true.
(It's like a time capsule.)
"I can never reach her."
"I want to see your clear eyes at least once."
(We want Song Ji Hyo, not Cavewoman Ji Hyo nor Zoned-out Ji Hyo.)
It's because she's Song Sleepy.
"An ad to shoot together. But she wrote her name first on the card."
What does this mean?
It's nothing. Just pass.
- What is it? - What does it mean?
(The hyenas are after Ji-rasoni.)
Well, it's...
This is no fun.
- What is it? - Gosh.
(Yawning)
(Feeling sleepy)
- What is it? - It's nothing. Let's move on.
- Really? - It's a joke. It means nothing.
It's a joke, but it's not funny at all.
(Straightforward)
Be easy on him.
- Don't be so mean. Be easy on him. - Hey.
(The Ji Suk Jin Show never seems to end.)
- Are you upset? - You don't know what's it about.
Are you upset?
I'm not upset, but you don't even know what it's about.
(Ji-rasoni keeps fighting back.)
You're not upset, right?
You don't know what it's about.
It sure isn't funny.
What we're upset with Haha.
(Followed by things they're upset with Haha)
"He said we should get together sometime,"
"but he never called. I guess it was a formality."
(This is embarrassing.)
Yes, that's what he does.
- He does that. - Hey, let's get together sometime.
- He asks to have a drink. - Hey.
- It's been years. - Let's have a drink.
- I've never had a drink with him. - Yes, he does that.
(Loyal Haha only makes empty promises.)
- He asks to have a drink. - He does that all the time.
- Why would he ask then? - So don't ask us.
- A drink and half-dried herring? - He does that all the time.
- He wasn't like that in the past. - Seriously.
(Poor Haha.)
- Come on, Haha. - You can't help it.
He doesn't talk casually on the phone.
He always says this when I answer. "Hello, Mr. Lee Kwang Soo."
(Haha's always filming YouTube whenever he calls Kwang Soo.)
It's just business.
It's all about work.
"Mr. Lee Kwang Soo, please say hello to our viewers."
- He's always like that. - Seriously.
"When I was a spy, he said he'd let me off if I told him the truth..."
"when there was no camera around."
"So I told him, but he spread it everywhere and removed my name tag."
That's so pathetic.
(Haha receives 10 complaints along with his superficial loyalty.)
He's unbelievable.
- We should have a drink together. - It's not me.
There he goes again.
(Haha will open another useless group chat today.)
- This is the worst part. - He just opens a group chat room.
This is for Se Chan.
(Next is about Se Chan.)
"He says he's at a meeting for 'Comedy Big League'..."
"and never calls me back for over two hours."
He's being strange these days. I think he's seeing someone.
- I know. - Exactly.
"When we went climbing together,"
"he obviously gave me the wrong directions..."
"and told me to go before him."
Isn't it that he tried to kill you?
(Feeling hurt)
I bet it's So Min.
- Really? - He tried to kill you.
(Se Chan almost guided Kwang Soo to death.)
It was really close. It could've been dangerous.
"He looks like cuttlefish."
Hey, what's that? Cuttlefish?
(His lacking appearance is brought up now and then.)
- Cuttlefish. - This is just a slander.
Cuttlefish is expensive.
Gosh, this one is quite straightforward.
"He likes So Min, but he never tells her about his feelings."
(Glaring)
I'm sure it's Haha. It's definitely him.
I was very disappointed.
- Why? - Why didn't you tell her?
(He's the only serious one in this relationship.)
This is why I come to Running Man.
Okay.
(It's finally about So Min.)
This is about So Min.
"She lies a lot."
- Who wrote that? - "She doesn't trust me."
She keeps questioning me.
I think this is Haha.
(It's clearly from Haha.)
- It's Haha. - I really meant it.
- Because you always lie to me. - That's not true.
"She promised not to do it,"
"but she doubts me every time we get a new mission."
Why do you keep doubting me?
"It's been six months since the promise, but she hasn't changed."
"I will never trust you again." Isn't this a letter to her?
Is that from one person?
"She keeps trying to make things look romantic."
- You spelled it wrong though. - Se Chan.
(It's not the correct spelling.)
(This is the correct spelling.)
- It's wrong. - Did you write it?
- Se Chan. - You spelled it wrong.
(It's not from me.)
(Ji Hyo is the one who spelled it wrong.)
It's really embarrassing.
There's a hidden secret...
- behind those messages. - What?
Each message you got today...
is converted to minus 100 points.
What are you doing?
And your scores will be accumulated.
Kwang Soo got a lot of messages.
(He already senses his disadvantage.)
We all wrote a message to him.
The more messages you have,
(The more messages, the more disadvantageous it gets.)
the more points you will lose.
(The results of 2020 Year-End Feelings Settlement)
(So Min: 800, Ji Hyo: 900, Jae Suk: 1,000, Haha: 1000)
(Se Chan: 1,100, Suk Jin: 1,200, Jong Kook: 1,400, Kwang Soo: 1,400)
(The scores are all in negative numbers.)
But members who lost a lot of points still can turn the game around.
- I see. - That's good.
While you were writing down your complaints,
- our guests for today wrote down... - Guests?
good things about you.
Good things about us?
(And each message will be converted to 100 points.)
I guess they are someone we know.
- This is hard. What should I say? - What should I say?
(It's the four main actors of "New Year Blues".)
- Their merits? - Their merits.
(Lee Yeon Hee, Yoo Yeon Seok)
We should be honest.
Right.
(Yoo Teo, Choi Sooyoung)
(What does Kwang Soo's best friend think Kwang Soo's merit is?)
Kwang Soo?
He's tall.
(What're the merits of the members that the four guests think?)
(They're excited to hear about their good characters.)
Everyone, we will bring in our guests...
who wrote about your merits.
Please come on in.
(The 4 special actors are here in Running Man.)
Who are they?
- Oh, hello. - Hey.
(Their entrance gives an impression of a warm year-end party.)
There's Sooyoung.
(They are glad to see the guests.)
- What? - Hello.
(They're here to introduce their new movie for 2021, "New Year Blues".)
- There's Sooyoung. - Hello.
It's hopeless.
(The movie is about four couples...)
Have you never dated anyone?
(who want to be happier in the coming new year.)
When I'm with you, I feel so small.
(Today's special guests, Yeon Seok, Yeon Hee, Sooyoung, and Teo)
Have you been feeling that way the whole time?
("New Year Blues")
We have four actors from the movie, "New Year Blues".
(They came to promote the movie.)
- It's "New Year Blues". - "New Year Blues".
Are you starring in the movie?
- No. - How do you know it then?
Then stay quiet.
(Don't pretend that you know.)
What did I do?
(He gets scolded for stepping out of his line.)
People would think you starred in the movie too.
Kwang Soo knows the movie.
Yeon Seok, this is your first time...
to join our show officially, right?
This is my first official appearance.
(It's his first official appearance.)
- With Haha... - He was Kwang Soo's...
(But he appeared unofficially with Haha?)
That's right.
I had to shave my beard as soon as I met him.
(Running Man Episode 293 in 2016)
Is it your wish that I shave my beard?
It's not shaved here.
(He asked Haha to shave his beard on their first meeting.)
Oh, no. You're bleeding.
(He even saw Haha's blood on their first meeting.)
- I'm sorry. - It's all right.
Right.
- But... - Kwang Soo made me do it back then.
(The main culprit: Lee Kwang Soo)
- Right. He did. - I did.
On our first meeting.
He just shaved my beard while laughing.
I even bled.
He was bleeding here.
(After the first meeting that only left scars,)
- Right. - Now I remember that.
(he's back in Running Man after 4 years.)
It was really...
(Yeon Seok and Yeon Hee prepared a tango.)
What? Did Yeon Seok and Yeon Hee prepare a tango performance?
(The staff is promoting something with the sketchbook.)
- Are we doing it already? - Really?
(What? Tango?)
- Is it from your movie? - Are they dancing the tango?
(Wait. Are we doing it already?)
- Are we doing it already? - Really?
Are they dancing the tango?
- No. - This is crazy.
(Shocked)
Did you prepare a tango performance?
Why are you being like this?
(Yeon Seok is embarrassed at the sudden request.)
The tango I know?
No, in our movie...
- Thank you for doing this. - It's not like that.
We should watch it then.
(Proceeding quickly)
- No, it's just... - Go ahead and show us.
(You should do it if you want to do it so badly.)
- We prepared... - Show us what you prepared.
I'm so grateful that they want to perform for us.
(Thankful)
Go ahead and do it.
(His face turns red because he can't wait to dance.)
- They did it in the movie. - I've never seen tango before.
All of a sudden?
Actually, this is what we thought.
"Did Yeon Hee and Yeon Seok dance tango in the movie?"
(They all thought it'd be mentioned very naturally.)
"Then can you show us a little?" I thought it would go like this.
- We wouldn't do that. - That's not what we do.
We don't say things like that.
- We get to the point right away. - To the point.
Do you dance the tango? Show us.
(Straight to the point)
- Right away? - Yes.
(A very straightforward host without any introduction.)
So this is Yeon Seok and Yeon Hee's tango performance.
(Let's see the tango you've prepared.)
Hang on.
This is...
- Can you make it look less abrupt? - So...
The thing is, they really want to show us.
(If that's what you want..)
- It's not like that. - You want to talk more.
(Please listen to me.)
Let me tell you. In Argentina...
(Trying to explain about the movie)
Boo, just go ahead and dance.
Just show us.
(He gives up.)
Let's just do it.
(He accepts the request as he realizes there's no other way.)
We will make it short.
- Then we can talk about it. - Just dance first.
We'll talk after you dance.
(Very focused on the main point)
With no explanation.
- I want you to lead. - I don't know what to do.
(I don't know.)
- Let's go. - But...
(But they pose right away.)
They strike the pose right away.
(Excited)
Gosh, this is tango.
(Extremely excited)
But Yeon Hee...
(What would their tango dance look like?)
(Wriggling)
(They wriggle together for a while.)
(Then they start to dance.)
(It's just the basic steps from the beginner's tango class.)
(They don't know how to react.)
(But the two actors are dancing seriously.)
(Crossing at a crosswalk?)
(Laughing)
(What is this?)
(A sudden finish)
(Sad thoughts)
Oh, no.
(They clap their hands anyway.)
You haven't done this for a long time, right?
(I can tell.)
I just told you.
It's not that we prepared this.
- I can tell it's been a long time. - We didn't prepare it.
I get it.
It's not that they were unbelievably good.
They looked good together though.
(He tries hard to wrap it up nicely.)
(He replays the crosswalk step.)
The movie has a scene where we dance the tango together.
(The stage was a bit too simple to be prepared.)
We did it a year ago.
Ask him this question.
Why did he want to dance?
(Why did you want to show us the dance?)
Will you stay quiet?
(He denies it fervently.)
- I'm just curious. - Will you stay quiet?
I'm just curious. Aren't you curious?
- I didn't want to dance. - So this is...
(Please hear me out.)
(Suk Jin ignores him.)
an important scene. I see.
(Teasing)
But why?
Why did you want that so much?
Gosh, no one would want to watch our movie.
So you wanted to dance.
- So it has the tango scene. - I see.
(He's about to become an avid tango dancer.)
I bet it looks different in the movie.
It's not easy to show something that you did a year ago.
(Jae Suk tries to speak on Yeon Seok's behalf.)
- I know. - But why did you want to do it?
(A twist)
(Speechless)
- I was... - I guess he was really determined.
Yeon Seok, you must love tango a lot.
(Confident)
He loves to tango.
(A shy tango lover gets his wish come true.)
I heard you are still taking tango lessons.
Next up is Yoo Teo.
(Next up is an actor of proven ability, Yoo Teo.)
He looks amazing.
I heard you were born in Germany.
(Teo was born and raised in Germany.)
- He was born in Germany too. - Really?
- Were you born in Germany? - Yes.
(Happy)
(Haha was born in Stuttgart.)
- In Stuttgart. - Really?
- Which part? - Cologne.
- Where? - Cologne.
- He doesn't know it. - Really?
So Cologne is in Germany.
- You don't know where it is. - Speak some German.
(He just filed his birth certificate in Germany.)
Do you speak German?
I'm fluent.
You should ask Haha some questions then.
- Ask him questions. - You're from the same country.
(Yes.)
(Have a talk in German.)
- Say things like this. - Ask him a question.
(Speaking German)
(Right.)
He's really good.
(The German kid answers with his body language.)
- What? Why? - Answer the question.
I know.
(He proudly replies back in Korean.)
What do you know?
His German is really good.
So he's from Germany.
I lived in Germany until I was 21.
(He lived in Germany until he turned 21 years old.)
- His German is really good. - He's a native.
That's why you have an accent.
(Teo's still learning Korean.)
I see.
He speaks good English too.
- Does he speak English as well? - English?
(Impressed)
Gosh.
Stop asking me to speak foreign languages.
- They weren't going to ask you. - There's more.
- No one was going to. - Because we don't...
(He acts defensive due to the previous tango trauma.)
get to see someone who speaks German a lot.
Right. This is my first time.
(Embarrassed)
Please give the four actors a big hand then.
(We'd like to welcome you all.)
It's so good to see you.
As I told you before,
the guests wrote down your merits.
(The guests wrote down the members' merits.)
They wrote about our merits.
Those who know you wrote the merits they know.
(They wrote down even for members they don't know.)
And those who don't know you just wrote what they thought.
- I might not have anything. - It's 100 points per merit.
(100 points for each merit.)
- 100 points. - We wrote about flaws.
Let's see what they wrote.
I don't think they wrote about me because we're not acquainted.
(Feeling uneasy)
- Right. We're not acquainted. - Me neither.
(Everyone's nervous as their early scores are at stake.)
This is empty.
- Right? This is... - Gosh.
Hang on. What is this?
What does this mean?
"It hurts"?
Please read it for us.
(A spelling error by Teo.)
I often spell things wrong.
- I got it wrong again. - I know what it means.
(Please understand.)
Okay.
This is for me.
"He's always thoughtful and considerate toward his guests."
- "He's the best." - My gosh.
(Not satisfied)
"He takes good care of himself."
(It's filled with reverence for Jae Suk.)
"He's the best variety show host. He's cool."
Jong Kook. "He's very thrifty and frugal,"
(It's now Jong Kook's turn.)
(Satisfied)
"so he makes me reflect on myself."
"He looks scary even when he's standing still during a race."
(Most compliments come from his image on TV.)
"He seems to be good at sports."
- "Will you be my training partner?" - I know who wrote it.
(Suddenly talking informally)
One of the messages sounds like it's automatically translated.
- This is Suk Jin's. - Like a translation device.
(Teo's identity is always revealed.)
This is for Suk Jin.
"He's an experienced veteran."
- "He's warm." - "He's warm."
(It's obviously Teo's message.)
Yeon Seok.
"I worry about him both when I see him on TV..."
"and when I shoot a TV show with him."
(He's worried about shooting a TV show with Suk Jin.)
Who was that?
It's supposed to be a compliment.
(They voice their concerns instead of compliments.)
Who was that? Is that a compliment?
(Is this...)
- He worries about you. - I guess it's Sooyoung.
(Very worried)
Haha's. "He greets me with excessive reactions,"
"but I'm not sure if he really means it."
Why would you say that?
It must be someone you know.
We should have a drink together. Who is it?
You should reflect on yourself.
- It's someone who knows Haha. - Let's drink together.
There you go again.
"He has a loud voice, so I can hear him well."
Who is it?
They are forcing themselves to say something good.
Gosh, this feels really good.
The compliments...
(Forced compliments)
You all will end up in paradise.
I guess it was really hard for them to find something meritorious.
- Someone squeezed out the comment. - It's easy to hear his voice.
(He squeezed himself out to compliment.)
- They reluctantly wrote these. - They had no choice.
- They saw us on TV... - The compliments of Ji Hyo.
"She's so good at games. She's both charismatic and pretty."
These also sound...
- half-hearted. Don't you think? - Absolutely.
- Because they don't know us well. - They were just being polite.
(It's a meaningless compliment.)
- It means they're not close to us. - Exactly.
Right? Let's move on to Kwang Soo.
(Next is Kwang Soo.)
"He's a superstar in Southeast Asia."
- In Southeast Asia? - Yes.
- Who wrote that? - Specifically in Southeast Asia?
(The prince's influence is limited only in Southeast Asia.)
I suppose this person saw Kwang Soo only on TV.
(Not interested in Kwang Soo)
- But... Why... - So they're not acquainted.
(They think they heard the nickname on news articles.)
- Why am I disappointed? - Not a superstar in Asia?
- Let's move on to So Min. - That's weird.
(Next is So Min's strength.)
"I found out that she goes to the same beauty parlor as me."
"I guess she has good taste."
Is this supposed to be sarcastic?
It sounds a little sarcastic.
- Is it sarcasm? - It means they have similar tastes.
(It's the killing point.)
- It sounds like... - Oh, I see.
He's just not good at writing Korean.
(I wasn't being sarcastic.)
These are about Se Chan. "He's as funny as his teeth."
- "I don't know him. Who is he?" - "I don't know him. Who is he?"
(The interrogative compliment shows the laziness.)
- That's so funny. - It sounds so half-hearted.
- There was nothing to write. - None whatsoever.
- Okay. I won't forget this. - Jae Suk...
It seems to me that they wrote in this order from here.
- So they were tired at the end. - They got tired.
(Last turn)
- Their comments got much shorter. - They still had to write something.
("I don't know him. Who is he?" comes from fatigue.)
- Okay. - The handwriting...
But he's getting more famous as So Min's boyfriend.
(Today's race is full of heartwarming compliments.)
He's getting more famous as So Min's boyfriend.
Today, it's the 2020 Year-End Feelings Settlement Race.
(2020 Year-End Feelings Settlement Race)
We tallied the scores you received from the other members and guests...
(The complaints and compliments are calculated.)
from the complaint and compliment surveys.
- I'll announce your scores now. - Okay.
(The sum is announced.)
The members in the first place are...
Ji Hyo and So Min with 500 points.
(So Min and Ji Hyo place 1st.)
- Really? - Nice.
(Haha in 3rd place, Jae Suk in 4th place, Se Chan in 5th place)
Kwang Soo's score is minus 1,100 points.
Minus 1,100 points?
(Suk Jin in 6th place, Jong Kook in 7th place, Kwang Soo in 8th place)
Now, you'll be divided into 4 teams of 3 people.
(You'll be divided into a group of 3.)
The tallied score of team members will be your team score.
(The tallied score of team members will be your team score.)
You will receive scores according to the result of the mission.
(Through missions,)
(2 teams that score 2,020 points win.)
The 1st 2 teams that gain 2,020 points will win.
- 2,020 points? - Yes.
(When two teams score 2,020 points, the race ends.)
If 2 members have minus 100 and minus 300 points,
their team score is minus 400 points.
(However, if there is no team with 2,020 points,)
When your team score is 2,020 points, the race ends.
(two teams with the highest score win.)
Oh, 2,020 points. I see.
The 2 winning teams will receive 1,000 dollars as New Year's gift.
(The 2 winning teams will receive 1,000 dollars as New Year's gift.)
- Really? - 1,000 dollars?
And the team with the lowest score will receive a penalty.
(The team with the lowest score will receive a penalty.)
(The teams are decided based on the gift draw.)
Let's decide teams now. Bring the gifts here.
(The teams)
We'll begin the first mission after you change your clothes.
(Team Teo, Team Yeon Hee, Team Sooyoung, Team Yeon Seok)
- Okay. - Okay.
(They're gathering at the place for the 1st mission 1 by 1.)
- Gosh. It's so cold. - It's really cold here.
You're shaking because of the mere cold.
- Jae Suk. - You're cringing your fingers.
You seem to be feeling very cold.
(He cringes his fingers due to coldness.)
He's so cool. He looks cool even when doing his warm-ups.
(Teo fights the coldness with stretching.)
You can tell he works out regularly.
- Whom are you talking about? - Teo.
I didn't realize earlier, but he...
(Exclaiming)
He has such a muscular body.
Teo, how old are you?
- I'm 40. - I'm sorry.
Are you serious?
(He was being rude to a man who is 5 years older than him.)
He's 40.
- Teo, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. - My goodness.
I'm sorry. I thought you were younger than me. I'm sorry.
(He didn't hear Se Chan.)
- Why? - I didn't know.
I asked him, "How old are you?"
Teo, I'm really sorry.
(He keeps bowing as he's embarrassed.)
- Pardon me? - I apologize.
- He thought he was older than you. - I thought I was older than you.
- That's why talked like that. - That's okay. Don't worry.
- It's a good thing. - I thought he was younger than you.
(Teo is generous and also looks young.)
He looks much younger than his actual age.
- Teo is 40. - I thought he was younger than me.
- He's 40. - He has a babyface.
(Se Chan made one embarrassing memory by checking Teo's age.)
- I thought the same as Se Chan. - Me too.
- Right? - Please sit down.
This will be fun.
(They'll begin the first mission before the new year.)
- Yutnori is easy. - We'll play yutnori.
- Okay. One of them is different. - Yutnori!
(They're familiar with this yutnori set.)
Yutnori requires some skills.
(But there's one yut with a different color.)
- I'm good at yutnori. - You need good sense.
Exactly.
- The first mission is... - I'm really good at this.
(The first mission of 2020 Year-End Feelings Settlement Race)
Bomb Yutnori, the upgraded yutnori.
(Bomb Yutnori)
- What is it? - It sounds fun.
(It has the same basic rules as regular yutnori.)
It has the same basic rules as regular yutnori.
However, each team will receive one normal piece...
(Each team will receive 1 normal piece and 1 bomb piece.)
and one bomb piece.
When your normal piece is back at the starting point, you're done.
(You'll get points according to the arrival of piece.)
And you'll receive different scores according to the result of the game.
As you can see, we have five yut-sticks.
(The yut stick with a different color is...)
- What's the extra stick? - The dark brown stick is...
the bomb yut-stick.
There are bombs drawn on the other side.
(When you get the bomb side, it performs the bomb yut role.)
- So? - If that side is up,
(If that side is up,)
you get to place your bomb piece anywhere you want.
(you get to place the bomb piece anywhere you want.)
- Anywhere we want? - It's like a landmine.
- It explodes when we stop there. - It's like a landmine.
(The team that stops at the bomb goes back to the starting point.)
The bomb explodes,
and the team that placed the bomb gains 100 points.
(The team that placed the bomb gains 100 points.)
- We should place it wisely. - Okay.
(The bomb piece is to hold the opponent's piece in check.)
- It's good. - It's like the famous board game.
Instead, you can't catch other teams' pieces with your piece.
(You can't catch other teams' pieces with your piece.)
You can only catch them with your bomb.
(Even if they land on the same spot, they move on their own.)
- Even if you stop at the same spot. - Okay.
(You can only catch the other teams' piece with the bomb.)
When you get yut or mo, you get to throw sticks again.
(When you get yut or mo,)
But you must move your piece before throwing the sticks again.
(you must move your piece before throwing the sticks again.)
If you stop where there's a bomb is, you lose the chance.
(If you stop where there's a bomb,)
- Okay. - We must move our piece first?
Correct. You can't move your piece after throwing the sticks again.
(you must go back to the starting point.)
- We can't add the moves later. - We must stick to the order, right?
- You must move it right away. - Okay.
Yeon Seok stands out so much.
Come on. Don't be like that.
(Special seat arrangement for teammates that make Yeon Seok shine)
It's not because of me.
- It's not just Yeon Seok. - It's not because of me.
(Yeon Seok stands out, and Kwang Soo denies it.)
Suk Jin also...
- I think... - Jae Suk,
Yeon Seok stands out among them,
but Suk Jin also stands out.
He stands out so much.
He's our grandfather.
Team Green.
He wants to blend in by any means.
He put on a pink cap to blend in with his team members.
(He put on a pink cap to harmonize with the team.)
He looks like an old man with his grandchildren.
(They look like grandchildren who came to see their grandpa.)
- In my entire life... - Grandpa, happy New Year.
Stop it. Gosh.
(Good daughter 1 and 2)
- I wish you a long, healthy life. - They look like good grandchildren.
He stands out too.
The same goes for your team.
(Team Teo stands out strongly.)
Teo stands out so much.
- Who? - Teo.
- Teo looks even more handsome. - Teo stands out?
He looks even younger.
Jae Suk, don't act like you didn't expect that answer.
Did you think she referred to you?
Okay. I admit it.
(Jae Suk who's become brazen picked the draw first.)
He became so shameless.
- Okay. - Shall we decide the order?
Let's do that.
(The game order)
Let's sit in the order. 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Team Sooyoung, Team Yeon Hee, Team Yeon Seok, Team Teo)
How about you sit in the order? The first team should sit here.
- We're the 3rd team. - The 1st team should sit there.
(They sit in the order.)
The first team is here.
The first team, sit over there. Team Mint Green.
This is the worst.
That side...
- looks so gloomy. - The atmosphere is so bad.
Hey, you look like braised monkfish.
- Braised monkfish? - Yes, braised monkfish.
(Se Chan's face reminds them of all sorts of things.)
- You look just like it. - I have all sorts of nicknames.
That's too mean.
- He looks like braised monkfish. - Father, that's enough.
You look like braised monkfish, not even monkfish soup.
Stop it.
I can see how different we all look.
(There are all kinds of facial features in Running Man.)
Now that I saw you closely,
I realized your gums are so pink and pretty.
- I can't believe him. - He has pretty pink gums.
(He gets to watch Se Chan's pork belly color gum up front.)
- I'm surprised. - It's pretty pink.
- It's the color of pork belly. - The color is so pretty.
I know, right? I'll give you some later.
No wonder why I craved soju when I saw his face.
(Se Chan makes them crave soju.)
His gums are pretty pink.
- Let's begin. - This team goes first.
(The game begins.)
- Okay. - Sooyoung, throw the sticks.
- Me? - The yut-sticks.
- Team Mint Green will go first. - Go ahead.
(Team Sooyoung throws yut sticks first.)
- Shouldn't we spread it properly? - He's right.
(They spread the blanket and set up the yut zone.)
Is it out if only part of a stick goes out of the mat?
Of course, it's out.
- No. - Isn't it okay to be partially out?
It's in as long as a part of it is on the mat.
(If half of the stick lands on the blanket, it counts.)
- It's in if a part of it is on it. - Like this?
- Well... - We can stand in the front.
(Staring)
You can throw the sticks over there.
No. Let's draw a line here.
- Everyone should stand here. - She sounded so firm.
- We should throw the sticks there? - No.
- It's too far. - I can't throw them there.
(From that far?)
- All of them will go out. - That's not necessary.
- But... I mean... - Don't people...
throw the sticks over the mat?
(Why doesn't she just throw them?)
- You don't know the rules, do you? - Listen.
- I mean... - The game won't end that way.
- We draw a line in my neighborhood. - Where is it?
Cheongdam-dong.
Do they have such a rule in Cheongdam-dong?
(He's never heard of it.)
- Many of us live there. - There's no such rule there.
(They've never heard of the new regional rule.)
Is that how they play this in Cheongdam-dong?
Everyone throws from a different distance.
(Everyone should throw from a different distance.)
- That's up to you. - That doesn't matter.
What if I throw them right in front of the mat?
- That's okay. - That's how it's done.
(There has never been a line.)
- Really? Is it okay? - But you must throw them high.
(It counts as long as she throws higher than her sitting height.)
- You shouldn't roll the sticks. - Above your head.
- When you're in a sitting position. - Above your head.
Then the lower your body is, the easier it gets.
(2nd question)
- Go ahead and try it. - Why must this be so complicated?
- Have you never played it before? - Just try it.
(They deal with the rules before throwing.)
That's not the point of the game, Sooyoung.
Just relax.
I was afraid you might complain about how I throw them.
(She has Running Man experience.)
- We won't. - I promise we won't.
(They promise not to blame her.)
- Okay. I'll do it as I want. - Yes. Go ahead.
What if it falls like this?
(3rd question)
- It's in. - That's okay.
- It's in? - Yes, it's in.
- Okay. - It's out if more than half is out.
(They can throw the sticks anywhere they want.)
- You're quite meticulous. - More than half?
(If more than half of the stick is out of the blanket, it's out.)
Whom have you been playing this game with?
(Cheongdam-dong yutnori clique's brutal detail negotiation)
It always causes a fight in my family.
(If you play yutnori without rules, it causes a fight in the family.)
- It happens a lot. - Exactly.
- Your family fights over this? - It happens a lot.
You're taking too much time.
(She finally throws the sticks as bystanders rush her.)
Okay. I'll do it now. 1, 2, 3.
- Good. - That's good.
(It's out.)
- It's out. - It's out.
- It's out. - Look at Jong Kook's face.
(The detailed negotiator's shabby result)
Look at Jong Kook's face.
Look at Jong Kook's face. Look at his face.
(It went out?)
- It's out. - He's so excited.
(Very happy)
Jong Kook is in shock.
(The bystanders with cheerful faces are annoying.)
You're so cheeky. I hate you the most.
- Jong Kook is shocked. - I'm happy.
- Good job, Sooyoung. - Yeon Hee.
- Gosh. She wouldn't stop talking. - Yeon Hee.
(Team Sooyoung's turn ended poorly after arguing.)
That stick went completely out of the mat.
Hey, Yeon Hee. Yeon Hee.
(Next is Team Yeon Hee's turn.)
You should throw them high so we can see your hands move.
- I'll throw them like this. - Good. That's acceptable.
- That's how it should be done. - That's good.
- It's out. - I knew it.
(It's out again.)
- It's quite hard. - Move.
(The first throw was awkward.)
- Come on out. - It goes out if you throw high.
(I guess it's hard.)
Both of them failed. I get it now.
(It's Team Yeon Seok's turn.)
Here comes a handsome man.
We just have to move our piece.
- That's right. - Because they all failed.
- Let's see. - Anything would do.
- Can I begin now? - Of course. Go ahead.
- Let's move our piece. - Throw them high.
- It's out. - It's out.
(He can't move the piece as it went out.)
- Throw them high. - It's out.
- What was that? - This is a mess.
- Why did you throw them there? - Why did you do that?
- Why did everyone fail? - I don't believe this.
(Scratching)
He practically threw the sticks on the floor.
- I didn't know it was so hard. - I think the mat should be larger.
(The blanket looks small after failing.)
- Let's spread it a little. - Is it hard?
Let's spread the blanket a little wider.
Yeon Seok came out,
and confidently said, "We just have to move our piece."
(He's ashamed of what he said in 30 seconds.)
You shouldn't have been so confident.
What they did wrong was...
- You should throw from a distance. - Exactly.
Don't act like you're good at it.
You failed so many times the last time we played this game.
(Jae Suk's addicted to show off.)
(He has many out experiences from the last yutnori.)
- Shut it. - You failed so many times.
You just have to throw as high as your eyes lying on the side.
- Good. That's a good stance. - Like this.
He reminds me of an uncle who hasn't gotten married...
that you meet when your relatives gather on holidays.
(The weird uncle shows off by posing.)
- Wearing sweatpants... - Exactly.
- It's the only time they can brag. - and picking a fight with everyone.
Watch me.
(He shows off while playing yutnori.)
- Only on holidays, - What are you doing?
- they meet other people. - Shut it, will you?
(Team Teo tries to set out with a weird pose.)
- Watch me. - It's the only time they show off.
- Just as high as your eyes. - I'm 100 percent sure it'll be out.
- Out. - It's out.
- It's still in. Oh, gosh. - It's out.
(One stick completely went out.)
The mat is too small.
- No one got them on the mat. - It's too small.
(The first turn ends with no one getting out.)
- It's out. - Let's spread it.
- Shall we? - Let's spread it.
(They want to expand the yut zone.)
- Okay. - It's too small.
- It's too small. - Why can't we do this?
Hey, we can discuss things and move on like this.
(Rationalizing)
This is why... Can I say something?
- Go ahead. - It's too small.
- I told you earlier. - About what?
If we draw a line and...
(The Cheongdam-dong line lover interferes.)
- We already refused to do that. - We won't do it in your style.
- Why would you do it like that? - Let's just do it normally.
- Wait. I'll show you. - Let's just follow normal rules.
If we throw the sticks here, we'll keep failing.
(Everyone's stick went out because they sat down to throw.)
- It'll be out. - Okay. Show us.
(So they must stand before a line and throw.)
- We draw a line and throw them... - Here?
- The tone of your voice... - in our own ways.
- I see. - In our own ways?
(That does work.)
- Just as you want to do it. - Okay. I like it.
- It seems better. - Shall we fold a little?
- Yes, just a little. - Okay.
- And then... - Wait. You should flip it over.
- If it goes out of here, it's out. - Flip it over.
- Fold it and flip it over. - Fold it and flip it over.
(They have an argument over how to fold the blanket.)
- Gosh. Why is this... - When are we going to begin?
Gosh, seriously.
(He kicked the blanket.)
(The frustrated bystander ends up kicking the blanket.)
Go. Get out.
- Everyone, just go home. - Leave. Get lost.
- You go first. - Get out of my house.
- This is my house. - You go first.
I'll watch a movie, so all of you, get out.
(I'll watch "New Year Blues", so get out.)
(He promises to watch the movie and kicks the guest out.)
It might take us three hours to set up the rules.
- As expected... - Gosh. This is just a game.
(They reorganize the mat after a quarrel.)
- The couple... - We're good.
- And now... - Just do as Sooyoung says.
- Right. - She'll state the rules.
We'll follow Sooyoung's Cheongdam-dong Rule.
(They finally adopt the Cheongdam-dong Rule.)
- Right. - Of course.
Okay, 1, 2, 3.
(Using the Cheongdam-dong Rule,)
Okay, good.
(Sooyoung gets a geol.)
- Geol. - It's a geol.
(A geol without the bomb)
- Geol with no bomb. - Geol.
- Here. - Geol.
(A smooth start)
Let's go catch that.
Yeon Hee, let's get them.
(Next is Yeon Hee.)
Hey, look.
- Nice one. - Nice.
We caught that team.
(A geol and a bomb!)
- No. - It's not like regular yutnori.
(They can't catch Team Sooyoung's piece,)
- You'll be placing a bomb. - We can't catch the others?
(and the bomb can be placed anywhere they want.)
- So we move alongside them? - We occupy the same spot?
- The bomb. - Where should we place it?
It should be where they might land.
How about here?
That's not a bad idea.
- Yeon Seok, don't roll a gae. - Don't roll a gae.
- Because of the bomb? - Just don't roll a gae.
(Team Yeon Seok can avoid the bomb if it's not a gae.)
- Geol would be ideal. - You'll roll a gae.
A gae, gae, gae...
- Hold on a second. - Gae, gae, gae...
You're Yoo Yeon Gae.
- Yoo Yeon Gae? - Seriously?
(Then...)
- Then Gae Yeon Seok. - Are you kidding me?
Gae Yeon Seok?
(Complaining)
I'm wishing for him to roll a gae.
(Yeon Seok is flustered by the vulgar prefix.)
- Don't mind him. - Gae...
- I mean... - Suk Jin even shocked himself.
- He keeps saying "gae." - Gae Yeon Seok.
- Gae Yeon Seok. - Gosh.
(Suffering from the noise attack,)
Yoo Yeon Gae.
Roll a gae. Come on.
(he throws the sticks.)
- Geol. - Gosh.
(A geol and a bomb!)
- And a bomb. - It's a gae!
- It's a gae. - No, a geol.
Gae. How is this a geol?
(And Suk Jin claims it's a gae?)
- Of course, it's a geol. - It's a geol.
This should be ignored.
- What do you mean? - Just look at it.
(Do, gae, geol)
- It's a geol. - Shouldn't this be ignored?
(It's obviously a geol.)
- It's a geol. - Do, gae, geol.
- How is this a geol? - How is it not?
- It's a geol for sure. - Unbelievable.
My eyes have been deceiving me lately.
So do, gae, geol.
(Team Yeon Seok discusses where they should put the bomb.)
- This is the turning point. - It's easy to land here.
- Like this. - See?
- But we could land on it too. - A turning point.
- Is it possible to set off ours? - Of course.
(They can step on their own bomb.)
So we shouldn't do that.
Since it's your turn, you choose where to put it.
(They let Yeon Seok decide where to place the bomb.)
Sure.
But...
(Yeon Seok hesitates...)
- Hurry up. - You're placing it up there?
(and places the bomb ahead of his team's piece.)
- He placed it. - You're placing it up there?
(Yeon Seok decided to block all 3 teams.)
- You can't move it. - But what about us?
You can't take it back.
(Yeon Seok attacks aggressively by taking the risk.)
But we could land on it instead.
- We'll just not land there. - We're doomed.
Let's roll a geol!
Can you move? It's our turn now.
(Team Teo is still at the starting line.)
Gae Teo.
(They step on the bomb if it's a gae.)
- Gae Teo. - No, Geol Teo.
- Gae Teo. - Just roll them.
- Don't mind him. - Gae Teo.
He rolled a gae!
(It's a gae!)
- It's a gae. - A gae.
- Gae. - Yes, this is a gae.
(They step on the bomb, and the piece goes back.)
We're the only team still at the starting line.
- Nice. - Okay.
- So we get 100 points? - Let's speed things up.
(Team Yeon Hee gets 100 points for placing the bomb.)
Is this allowed?
- Next is So Min. - So Min!
Gosh.
- It's a gae. - A gae.
(So Min rolled a gae.)
Okay, that's good.
- It's a gae. - A gae.
- Okay, that's good. - I didn't roll a bomb though.
We made it.
- Where do we go? - No, we landed on a bomb.
You landed on a bomb.
- We made it. - No, we landed on a bomb.
(They landed on a bomb.)
(Their piece goes back.)
Nice, it's our bomb!
(Team Yeon Seok receives 100 points.)
It's the bomb that I placed.
Right.
(Yeon Seok's offense fortunately worked.)
- It was a great choice. - Geol and gae mostly get rolled.
- Right. - Okay.
(Now they're in the lead along with Team Yeon Hee.)
Gae... We can roll just about anything.
- Another bomb would be nice. - Life's all about one lucky punch.
(Ji Hyo throws a gae and a bomb.)
A bomb and a geol.
- No, a gae. - A gae.
We'll move two steps.
- Today... - They get to turn directions.
Let's place it here.
They could make a run for it.
Just don't roll a do.
(Team Yeon Seok only has to avoid throwing a do.)
- Braised monkfish. - Just don't roll a do.
- Go for it. - Roll a do.
Nice!
(The sticks roll out of the cloth.)
- Nice! - One rolled out.
It doesn't count.
- Kwang Soo... - You just killed our momentum.
- I'm sorry. - Haha.
(Team Yeon Seok puts on the brake.)
- Are you kidding me? - Haha.
- What now? - That's what he rolled.
Let's do this!
(Haha throws next.)
You just killed our momentum.
- A gae. - Gae!
Nice one. It's not bad.
(They start going forward with a gae.)
- Darn it. - Here.
- We were on a roll. - Is ours in black?
- Next is... - Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - There are bombs everywhere.
If only we were able to place a bomb.
(Team Sooyoung's piece was reset.)
- There... - You get your wish.
I know, you're getting your wish.
- What do we need? - A yut.
(They can get out of the starting line if it's not a yut.)
- Anything will be great. - Except a yut?
- Right. - Roll a yut.
It's a yut!
He rolled a yut!
(Back to the starting line, plus 100 points)
(Their piece is reset for the second time.)
- Nice! - He rolled a yut.
- Everyone, he rolled a yut. - A yut!
- Yut, yut. - Yut, yut.
(Let's celebrate.)
Yut, yut.
It's a yut.
(Shoving)
You can still place a bomb though.
(They can still place the bomb.)
- Can we place a bomb though? - Yes, you can.
So much for rolling a big one.
(They must place it where it'll hurt the others the most.)
Pick a different spot than the last time.
This line wouldn't be bad.
- How about right here? - Okay.
- So Min, good choice. - If they roll a geol...
- That's right. - We can roll anything but that.
(They put the bomb at the center where Team Yeon Hee might go to.)
How about we place it at the center?
Sure, the center.
Sure, roll a geol.
I can roll anything but that.
Geol Suk Jin.
- Roll a geol. - Geol Suk Jin.
(They start interrupting him.)
Geol Suk Jin.
(The chant's childish but addictive.)
Does the "geol" mean beggar in his case?
- Geol Suk Jin. - Geol Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin wants to avoid a geol,)
- Ji Seok Geol. - Geol Suk Jin.
- Ji Seok Geol. - Okay!
(and he throws a do.)
- It's a do. - A do.
- Do. - A do at this part of the game?
Do.
They just have to roll a gae next.
You're right. It's better this way.
We'll place bombs in its path.
- They could still roll a geol. - Go, go!
(They'll target Team Yeon Hee by making a minefield.)
- Let's do this. - Gae.
You...
- Roll a gae. - Just roll a bomb.
You talk a lot for someone who only rolled a gae.
- You are so talkative. - I've been the best on this team.
Are you good at yutnori?
(Childish)
- Yes, I'm a professional. - Get back here.
The Young Master of Mapo-gu.
(Kwang Soo's turn to throw, and he really needs a bomb.)
- Just don't let it roll out. - Come on!
- Nice! - One rolled off!
(One rolled off the mat once again.)
(These three keep letting the sticks roll off.)
- Move. - It doesn't count.
- Nice! - Seriously?
- The mat's not even far away. - Kwang Soo failed!
- Kwang Soo Out! - I didn't mean to.
(After their sad turn...)
- Kwang Soo Out! - Just watch.
- Watch how I get it done. - Okay.
Okay.
- He tossed them forward. - Nice!
- A yut. - I rolled a yut!
(Team Teo throws a yut.)
- Okay. - You get another roll.
Does he get another roll?
- Give me a yut. - Must he be so sly?
- Good. - Nice one!
(A gae and a bomb!)
- Gae. - Gae and a bomb.
- Gae and a bomb. - Right, a gae and a bomb.
(Team Teo members finally get their hands on the bomb.)
We need to catch this team, so this is where it should go.
- Do, gae, geol. - Target the team in the lead.
(They want to obstruct Team Yeon Hee's way.)
They'll land on a bomb if they roll a gae or a geol.
- Gae. - Darn, we're doomed this time.
They're doomed.
We're in big trouble.
(They make a minefield that blocks Team Yeon Hee's way.)
- Let's do this! - It's a minefield.
Yeon Hee, you're next.
- No... - The bombs are in one line.
No, you should do it...
(Nervous)
- since this is an important moment. - Look at all those bombs.
(Team Yeon Hee's piece will be reset if she throws a gae or a geol.)
Yeon Hee.
Yeon Hee, look.
You can't roll a gae or a geol.
All right, a gae or a geol.
(Will they be able to avoid the bombs?)
- Gae or geol. - Gae or geol.
One rolled out!
- What on earth? - It's a yut!
(Thanks to Yeon Hee,)
- Seriously? - It's a yut.
(they jump over the bombs.)
- It's a yut. - How is she so good at this?
- How can this be? - It's a yut.
- They jumped over them. - All of them.
- No way. - You get another roll.
(They're almost at the finishing line.)
The game's nearly over then.
- No way. - Go ahead.
(They get another chance after throwing a yut.)
They're masters at this.
- Please go out. - One went out!
- Okay. - One went out.
One rolled out.
(Yeon Hee prevented the team from being reset.)
It would've been another yut.
Yeon Seok, we need to block them by placing a bomb.
(Team Yeon Seok wants to get more bombs to block other teams.)
- What... - This is our last chance.
- Come on. - We need to move forward too.
- We mostly need a bomb. - Right, we need a bomb.
We need to stop the other team.
I bet one will roll out.
(Team Yeon Seok is falling behind. Will he throw a bomb?)
- I'm sure of it. - Please roll a gae.
- One will go out. - I agree.
One will roll off the mat!
(It's their 4th time already.)
You guys are good at missing the mat.
Seriously?
(Demotivated)
- Yeon Seok. - You're the worst.
- Yutnori... - He's the weakest link.
(Yeon Seok's sticks keep rolling off the mat.)
- He's terrible at this. - It isn't even funny anymore.
- Yeon Seok's the weakest link. - It's our third time already.
(The leader of the dud brothers, Yeon Seok)
It's their third time.
- It doesn't matter though. - It's their third time.
(They still haven't gone far from the starting line.)
- Lower your torso. - Get out of his way!
Lower your torso.
- What do they need? - Just throw them.
(Team Teo is right behind Team Sooyoung.)
- Let's go. - Let it roll off the mat.
- Geol. No, it's a yut. - It's a yut!
(They roll a yut with no bomb.)
- Yut pops up often. - It's a yut.
(They already make it past Team Sooyoung.)
Yut, yut, yut.
We'll be strict with the rules from now on.
(They get another throw thanks to the yut.)
Okay, I'm loving the stance.
- Good. - That's how we all do it.
Go ahead.
- Let's see. - All right.
- It's not bad. - A gae and a bomb.
(A gae and a bomb!)
This is actually better.
A gae and a bomb.
(They're both in the lead thanks to Teo.)
Where...
Let's make sure they won't follow us.
Following us along this line will lead to their demise.
(A bomb to hinder Team Sooyoung's course)
Do, gae...
We're not your enemy at the moment!
(Not there!)
Guys, just look.
(The Cheongdam-dong yut player steps up.)
- Take a look at this. - We rolled a gae.
Nice. No one's bothering to block our way.
Let's just stay quiet.
(Team Yeon Hee decides to keep still.)
It might end up blocking their way too.
That team will roll before you do, right?
(Since Team Yeon Hee will throw before you guys,)
(place a bomb where it can stop them, not us.)
It's better to target them first.
Sooyoung's right.
- What if we land on it? - Yes, I'm right.
Still...
(But the bomb goes here.)
- A gae? - Yes.
(The bomb ended up in Team Sooyoung's way.)
- Let's roll a geol. - It's all right.
- Geol. - Gae is rolled most often.
- Gae. - Gae is rolled most often.
We can't even take part in the conversation.
- We are not even close to them. - How many times has he done this?
(Team Yeon Seok seems to be on the sidelines.)
It's like we're invisible.
I've lost interest in the game.
- Gae. - Roll a gae!
(So Min will land on Team Teo's bomb if she rolls a gae.)
- Gae So Min. - Gae So Min.
(Yippee!)
- Roll gae and you're done for. - Gae So Min.
- Woof, woof! - Did you hear that?
Why on earth are you excited by that nickname?
Being so will prevent me from rolling a gae.
- Woof. - Jeon So Gae.
(So Min accepts the tease.)
- Get a bomb too while you're at it. - Jeon So Gae.
At least set up a bomb.
- Out, out, out, out - Out!
(She lets the rhythm sink in.)
- Hold on a second. - Out, out, out, out
Just keep quiet so that she can roll them.
- All right. - I'm begging you.
(He asks them to stop to continue with the game.)
- Don't excite her like this. - Got it.
- But I want to have fun. - All right.
(Make some noise!)
- But you... - I can't believe Yeon Seok sang it.
Out, out, out.
(Ji Suk Jin, Wants to join them)
I want one to roll off the mat!
- Just let her be. - I want one to roll off the mat!
Don't provoke her.
Out So Min.
- Jeon So Out. - Stay put, will you?
Why can't I do what I want?
I just...
(He's sad that he can't make any sound.)
- They're at it again. - It's just something I want to do.
- Suk Jin's upset. - Their show has begun.
- But So Min was enjoying it. - Still...
She was having fun,
but so was I.
We were all having fun, right?
Jong Kook, just let the two have some fun.
(They decide to neglect the two excited members.)
- He's right. - Roll a gae
Gae So Min rolls a gae
(So Min only has to avoid rolling a gae.)
A bomb and a geol.
(A geol and a bomb!)
- A geol! - A bomb and a geol.
- Okay, good. - She rolled a bomb.
I said we should assume that they'd roll a geol.
(They jump past Team Teo's bomb.)
- Nicely done. - Nice!
- Is it good for us? - Of course.
(Team Sooyoung discusses where they should put the bomb.)
Geol or a gae?
- What do we do next? - A gae or...
- What's better for us? - A gae.
(They'll place it in front of the pieces ahead of them.)
- Exactly. - So here.
- I agree. - Me too.
We're finally joining the game, right?
(These three are still on the sidelines.)
- Let's move forward now. - At least roll a bomb.
- You can do it. - Yeon Seok, don't worry.
(They prepare for their turn together.)
- We need to roll a bomb at least. - Right.
We at least need a bomb.
Just make sure they stay on the mat.
(Yeon Seok solemnly straightens out the mat.)
Look at Yeon Seok.
(He struggles to not roll the sticks out of the mat.)
You're straightening out the mat.
I'll just make sure none rolls out of the mat.
- It's actually our turn. - What?
Our team's next.
(It's not their turn yet.)
I see.
- What... - Yeon Seok, it's not our turn.
(He's straightening out the mat.)
- It's not our turn. - It isn't?
- It's not our turn yet. - It isn't?
- It's not our turn? - Yeon Hee said...
- Yeon Hee said... - Get it together.
When will our turn come?
- Let's keep it together. - Is it Yeon Hee's turn?
(He's even impatient compared to his performance.)
- I see. - It's not hers either.
- Okay. - Where's Ji Hyo?
Here comes Jeoktoma
(It's actually Ji Hyo's turn.)
- She'll crush you all - Jeoktoma! Jeoktoma!
- No! - It's out.
- It's in. - It's on the mat.
We'll call this as out.
(It's out that wasn't seen in a while.)
- Okay. It's out. - It's out.
- Me? - Yes.
(Now it's really Team Yeon Seok's turn.)
- If it goes out this time... - Make sure it won't happen.
- I'll do that. - Just avoid getting out.
(They hope for everything else but out.)
- Stay focused. - Okay.
- Out, out, out - Team Gray is still there?
(They're still in the same place due to continued outs.)
The sticks rolled out of the mat repeatedly.
- We couldn't move our piece. - We never got a bomb.
- Out, out, out - Earlier...
Out Se Chan, Out Se Chan
(Everyone is cheering for them to get out again.)
Out Se Chan
- Out Se Chan! - I am braised monkfish
Gosh, seriously.
The small serving, 25 dollars
I am braised monkfish, monkfish, monkfish
(He sings a monkfish song to distract him.)
- All right. - "The small serving, 25 dollars"?
- Out Se Chan ate an octopus again - Out Se Chan
- I hope the sticks will slide out - Out Se Chan
("Out Se Chan" song is an embarrassing song...)
- I just have to avoid getting out. - Out Se Chan
(composed by the men born in 1966 and 1972.)
Se Chan never let any sticks roll off the mat.
- Out Se Chan - Out, out, out, out, out
(Team Out Brothers suffered from many distraction tactics.)
- Out Se Chan - Focus.
- Out Se Chan - Throw them high
- It'll go out - It's out!
It's out.
(The team failed to move forward for the 5th time in a row.)
(We're in trouble.)
- It's out, it's out, it's out - Gosh.
- I'm sorry. - What's wrong with you?
- I don't know. I couldn't do it. - I know you can do better.
- They keep getting out. - I'm sorry.
(It's an otherworldly streak of outs.)
- Move. - Okay!
Gosh. This is annoying.
- That was... - Even I'm annoyed too.
- This is so boring. - They're really bad at this.
- It's not fun anymore. - It's not fun at all.
- I'm frustrated. What are we doing? - My gosh.
(Was this game of yut supposed to be this fun?)
I hope we get 1 yut. No, 2 yut.
- Yut, yut. - It doesn't match the drawing.
(Team Teo is likely to win as long as they avoid a geol.)
- Geol, geol. - Yut, yut.
- Geol, geol, geol. - Please stop there.
- Geolster, Geolster. - Geolster.
(What?)
- Geolster. - Hey.
- I thought I misheard it. - I didn't know you'd say that.
- It sounds fun. - That was unexpected.
(Jong Kook takes part in this childish song-making.)
- It suits him. - It suits him well.
- Geolster? - Haha.
- Geolster. - Yut.
(Haha throws his yut after the geol-begging curse.)
- Yut, yut. - Geolster, Geolster.
(The game will reset if Haha gets a geol.)
- Please get a geol. - Geol.
- Get a geol. - Geol.
- Yut, yut. - Geolster, Geolster.
(Haha's team will lead the game if he gets anything but a geol.)
- Please get a geol. - Geol.
- Geol. - Geolster.
(Is it a geol?)
- It's a geol. - It's out.
(Swarming)
- It's a geol. - No, it's not.
(The general yuts are a geol.)
- It's a geol. - It's out.
- You're wrong. It's a geol. - It's a geol.
(But it's hard to tell for the bomb yut-stick.)
- It's a geol. - It's a geol.
(If it's a geol, Team Sooyoung gets 100 points from the bomb.)
- It's a geol. - It's out.
- It's out. It's out. Say it. - It's definitely a geol.
(Team Teo will only survive if it's out.)
- It's out. - No, it's a geol.
- Check the camera. - It's definitely out.
(A detailed review of the video says...)
- We came to a conclusion. - We discussed it.
(that it's a geol because more than half of the stick is in.)
- It's in. - We concluded it's in.
- It's a geol. - All right.
(Let's celebrate.)
- It's a geol. - Okay.
- They stopped here. - They landed on the bomb.
(They return to the starting point after hitting a bomb.)
There's a team behind us now.
(There's someone behind us.)
- There's a team behind us. - Let's stay alert.
- Okay. - Thank you.
(Team Sooyoung gets 100 points.)
We still have a chance.
Gosh, that brat.
Jae Suk.
(He sighs out loud.)
- They don't jibe with each other. - It's not like you did well.
- They can't be on the same team. - Did you do well?
- Just break up already. - You didn't do well either.
(Internal dispute)
- We're back at the starting point. - You didn't do well either.
- They never jibe with each other. - Gosh, that brat.
(The two will never get along.)
- They never jibe with each other. - I've been too nice to you.
(They became too sensitive as they got too into it.)
We never jibe with each other.
(It's Team Sooyoung's turn again.)
She knows much about variety shows as she has a lot of experience.
She knows much about variety shows.
- Good. - It's a yut.
(It's a yut with the bomb.)
- Let's move our piece. - It's a yut.
- How does she throw the sticks? - It's a yut.
(Why are they so good?)
- We can move four steps. - We're almost there.
That team is almost done.
(Team Sooyoung is on a roll.)
- They're almost done. - We're done for.
(She gets another chance.)
- We're done for. - Okay.
(Lightly putting)
- Wait. She just put them down. - What?
(You didn't throw.)
She just put them down instead of throwing them.
- This doesn't count. - People at Cheongdam-dong are...
- so underhanded. - Fine.
(Goodness.)
- She didn't throw them. - She never throw them properly.
I'll throw them properly this time.
- I guess after the shoot, - Make sure to bend your arm.
we won't see each other for a while.
(Everyone's very into the game.)
- I'm so upset right now. - Bend your arm.
This will be my last appearance on Running Man.
(She's too focused that she gives up her reappearance in the show.)
- So I'll throw them hard. - Sounds good.
- That's good enough. - It's a yut.
It's a yut!
(It's another yut with the bomb.)
- That's great. - Oh, yes.
Didn't she throw them too lightly?
(They're about to complete.)
- Go ahead. - She threw them properly.
- They're almost there. - We'll end it.
(They'll win even with a do.)
- It was acceptable. - We'll end it.
- It's a do. - It's a do.
(They get a do with the bomb.)
- Do and a bomb. - We got a do and a bomb.
- We passed the finishing point. - Okay.
(Team Sooyoung completes the route.)
And then...
- They passed it. - Where should we place the bomb?
(That's a shame.)
Where shall we place it?
(The remaining teams must fight over the 2nd place.)
- We finished it. - We won fairly.
- Fair and square. - I've never won fairly before.
(Team Sooyoung wins 1st place fair and square.)
(Current Yut Board Status)
Fair and square.
Let's get 2 yut and 3 mo.
- Let's move on. - Okay.
(It's now Se Chan's turn.)
- Yang Gae Chan. - You can do it.
Yang Gae Chan.
- It's a yut! - Yut!
Yut!
(He gets his first yut.)
- Let's go. - It's a yut.
- They might land on a bomb. - Exactly.
You can land on a bomb anytime.
- A do would be perfect. - Right.
(He goes again.)
A bomb would be nice too.
- Where is it? - A bomb, please.
- A bomb! And a yut! - It's a yut! It's a yut!
(He gets another yut.)
(It's two lucky throws in a row.)
- A bomb! - It's a yut! It's a yut!
- It's a yut. - He just drooled.
Yeon Seok drooled.
(After checking the yut sticks,)
- A bomb! And a yut! - It's a yut! It's a yut!
He just drooled.
(he drools slightly.)
Yeon Seok drooled.
(Out Yeon Seok salivates only after two yuts.)
- He drooled. - Yeon Seok.
Yeon Seok.
- My gosh. - Stop it already.
(He's very serious about this game that his face turns red.)
- I'm so happy. - He drooled!
- Yeon Seok, are you that excited? - Hey, pretend you didn't see it.
Pretend you didn't see it!
- Yeon Seok just drooled. - I'm so happy.
This is so sweet.
- Getting 2 yut is so sweet. - He got too excited.
- Drooling Yeon Seok. - My gosh.
- I can't believe he drooled. - Drooling Yeon Seok.
- Are you that happy? - Yes.
(Drool Yeon Seok reveals his humane side.)
- Yeon Seok is so funny. - Are you excited?
This is so sweet.
(Team Yeon Seok is leading.)
- He's so down-to-earth. - My goodness.
- We should avoid a geol. - I hope you get a geol.
(Team Yeon Seok gets to throw again.)
- Is it Yeon Seok's turn? - Yes, he'll throw them.
- Throw them hard. - Geol, geol.
(They just need to avoid a geol.)
- It will be a disaster - Geol, geol.
- What's that song? - It's "Girl" by Aspirin.
(The childish chant evolves.)
(Yeon Seok can avoid the bomb if he avoids getting a geol.)
- Geol, geol, geol. - Mo, mo.
- Geol. - Good.
- Oh, yes! - It's a geol.
Oh, yes.
(He meets Team Teo's bomb...)
What is wrong with him?
(and returns to the starting point.)
- He's so bad at this. - We were so close.
He made me lose interest in the game.
(The worst combination of yut, yut, and geol.)
We were so close.
- Yeon Seok is so bad at this. - Okay.
(Yeon Seok made the worst move.)
We could be in second place.
(His face lightens up.)
- You see... - Save it.
I don't know what the penalty will be.
You'll most likely receive the penalty.
Anyway, you will...
get the penalty.
(After a series of Yeon Seok's bad plays...)
- We won! - Oh, yes!
(Team Yeon Hee secures 2nd place 10 minutes later.)
- My goodness. - We're in second place.
(Team Teo wins 3rd place, Team Yeon Seok wins the last place.)
Gosh. It's not working out well for us.
It's okay.
- I'll announce your scores. - Okay.
(It's time to announce the result.)
The team in first place received 1,000 points.
(Team Sooyoung gets 1,000 points for winning 1st place.)
- And the 2nd place? - The team in 2nd place gained 500,
the 3rd place gained 300, and the 4th place gained 100 points.
(2nd place gets 500 points, 3rd place gets 300 points.)
(4th place gets 100 points.)
- We gained 300 points. - We gained 100 points.
500, 300, and 100 points?
- There aren't large differences. - Okay.
(The points for bombs will be calculated separately.)
- We'll move to the next location. - Okay.
Gosh. I'm so upset.
(Team Sooyoung and Team Yeon Hee are in 1st place with 400 points.)
(Team Teo is in 3rd place, Team Yeon Seok is in 4th place.)
(They head out for the next mission.)
I didn't know Yeon Seok was so bad at the game.
It turns out he's not good at yutnori.
(Yeon Seok emerges as the new unlucky hands.)
He was so bad at it.
He did even worse than we did.
I shouldn't have teased Kwang Soo...
for being lousy at games.
(Yeon Seok didn't know the unlucky side of him.)
I only got humiliated.
Yeon Seok got so excited that he drooled.
- Just because we got a yut... - That was unforgettable.
(His excitement made him drool his humane side.)
- We got 2 yut in a row. - He drooled...
I got so excited when we got our second yut.
- He was exhilarated. - He rarely drools like that.
Exactly.
(His saliva leaked from getting too into the game.)
- Everyone. - Yes?
- We'll do the last mission shortly. - Yes.
- And we'll play a simple game now. - Okay.
(A short game during the ride.)
To celebrate the year-end, we'll reflect upon ourselves...
(With the new year approaching, it's time to look back.)
at the age of 20 when we were full of hopes and dreams.
(When I was 20 Years Old)
It's When I Was 20 Years Old.
When I Was 20 Years Old.
(Nostalgic)
- It makes me tear up. - Okay.
We prepared the 10 songs that were popular when you were 20.
(They prepared the top 10 songs from when the members were 20 years old.)
And we'll play one of the songs randomly.
You'll listen to the song for three seconds,
(After listening to the song for 3 seconds,)
and guess who was 20 when the song was popular,
(they must guess the member and the song's title and artist.)
- the song title, and the singer. - Okay.
For example, you can say, "Jae Suk, the singer, the song title".
(Yoo Jae Suk, "My Love By My Side" by Kim Hyun Sik)
- I see. - I feel emotional.
- It's touching. - I get it.
How do we know the songs that were popular when Suk Jin was 20?
- It's Suk Jin if it's a folk song. - Exactly.
(It's Ji Suk Jin as soon as they hear janggu.)
I think it's disadvantageous to you.
Se Chan, are you and Kwang Soo the same age?
- I don't remember. - He's the same age as So Min.
I'm one year younger than Kwang Soo.
(I didn't know.)
- You're one year younger than him? - Yes.
You appeared on many variety shows, right?
- It's because you're rude. - No, that's not it.
(Their friendship is easy for others to misunderstand.)
When people who don't know us see us, they think...
It's because I look older than my age.
Kwang Soo is one year younger than me.
(Se Chan was born in 1986, Yeon Seok was born in 1984.)
- You were born in 1984. - Yes.
How much older are you than me, Yeon Hee?
- I was born in 1988. - She's younger than you.
(He asked Yeon Hee if she's older when she's 2 years younger.)
- She's younger than you. - She's...
- She's younger than you. - Really?
You speak casually to people who are older than you.
- I thought she was older than me. - You talk formally to younger ones.
(Se Chan's conversation style has no prejudice.)
That was discourteous of you.
- I thought she was older than me. - Right. It was so rude of you.
(I'm sorry, Yeon Hee.)
- I'm sorry. - Se Chan.
(Just now, to Teo, who's 5 years older...)
- Earlier, you asked Teo... - I did the same thing Teo.
- "Teo, how old are you?" - "Teo, how old are you?"
And he said, "I'm 40."
(An unexpected rudeness to a 40-year-old man.)
Teo, I'm sorry again.
- What's with you? - I keep guessing wrong.
- "How much older are you than me?" - Exactly.
(She looks very young.)
Yeon Hee looks like she's only 23.
- Suk Jin, that's enough. - That's enough.
(That's enough.)
- Suk Jin must feel uncomfortable. - You're making her uncomfortable.
(Everyone complains about Suk Jin's excessiveness.)
- You should know when to stop. - She's on my team.
They're arguing again.
I'll meet Jong Kook privately later.
I've been waiting for the day when you call me out.
(Please call me.)
Suk Jin, if you are to roll on the ground, go to a snowy field.
(I recommend when it snows a lot.)
- After it snowed a lot. - I'll treat him to a nice meal.
Let's hear from our correspondent. Se Chan.
(Yang Se Chan, Running Journalist)
Yes, this is Yang Se Chan.
Tell us what happened.
Something absolutely shocking happened here.
- He's good at it. - Comedian Ji Suk Jin...
was rolling on the ground without wearing trousers.
(Ji Suk Jin, found tumbling in the snow without pants)
in the snowy field.
He wasn't wearing trousers?
- He wasn't wearing trousers? - No, he wasn't.
(Yang Se Chan, Running Journalist)
It doesn't seem like he did it of his own accord.
It seems that someone else robbed them from him.
That's all.
(The likely suspect is Kim.)
All right. Here's your first question. Cue.
(The game starts after a short skit.)
Cue.
(The first music plays.)
- Haha. - So Min.
(They're all familiar with the intro of the song.)
(Everyone is excited.)
- Haha. - So Min.
- So Min. - Haha, say the answer.
So Min, S.E.S, "Dreams Come True".
She wasn't 20 at the time.
- Wrong. - Let me answer.
Yeon Seong...
- "Yeon Seong"? - Wrong.
(Yoo Yeon Seok is not acceptable.)
- Wrong. - That's wrong.
- What was that? - Let me answer.
- Go ahead. - How could you not know his name?
Ji Hyo, S.E.S, "Dreams Come True".
- Wrong. - Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo was faster. - Kwang Soo, go ahead.
(Kwang Soo gets the chance.)
Haha, S.E.S, "Dreams Come True".
- Correct. - Okay!
(Was it when I was 20 years old?)
- Really? I didn't realize it. - Haha.
- "Dreams Come True". - My gosh.
(Team Yeon Seok earns 1 point.)
What a shame.
- It was when you were 20. - Dreams come true
(He's traveling back the time.)
Was he exactly 20 years old?
(The mega-hit "Dreams Come True" song came out in 1998.)
(It made all men excited, including the 20-year-old Haha.)
So it was when Haha was 20.
(Haha fails to connect with the 20-year-old himself.)
- What a shame. - The song was very popular.
- Here's the second question. - It was Haha.
(It's the second question.)
Cue.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
The answer is...
(He goes for it.)
- Suk Jin... - Oh, right.
(Suk Jin's name comes up due to the retro introduction.)
- Suk Jin, Kim Wan Sun... - That's correct.
- Wait. - 3, 2, 1.
(Time's up.)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer.
- I said it first. - So Min, go ahead.
Suk Jin, Kim Wan Sun, "The Pierrot Smiles at Us".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
(She was certain, but her answer was incorrect.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(Haha barely gets the chance.)
- Go ahead. - Suk Jin,
Kim Wan Sun, "The Piroro Always Smiles at Us".
- Piroro? - Let me answer.
(What? Piroro?)
- "At Us". - Piroro?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Piroro? - Let me answer.
- What is Piroro? - Let me answer.
(You mean Pororo?)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Suk Jin, Kim Wan Sun, "The Pierrot Smiles at Us".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
(What?)
- The answer was correct. - Is it me?
(Not me.)
- It must be you. - Jae Suk,
Kim Wan Sun, "The Pierrot Smiles at Us".
- Correct. - Okay!
(Team Yeon Seok got 2 questions right in a row!)
- Whose song is it? - Yours.
Is it mine?
Is it his? Isn't it mine?
(Everyone thought it was Suk Jin's song.)
- You were 20 years old. - Did the song come out in 1991?
(But it was actually Jae Suk's.)
(The masterpiece caused a sensation when Jae Suk was 20 years old.)
Team Yeon Seok got two questions right.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo's performance, Team Yeon Seok's running 1st.)
This is a team competition, right?
- Yes, it is. - All right.
(Yeon Seok's going along without any contribution.)
Good job. Yeon Seok.
- They got two questions right. - Good job.
Kwang Soo keeps stealing answers.
Here comes the next question.
(It's the third question.)
Se Chan!
What is this song?
(I know this song!)
Se Chan, Buzz, "Coward".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- So Min. - You are right.
- Kwang Soo, Buzz, "Thorn". - It must be Kwang Soo.
No.
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
Yeon Seok.
(What? It's not?)
- 5, 4, - Buzz,
- three... - "Coward"...
(Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo.)
- Is it Yeon Seok? - So Min.
- Incorrect. - I told you it's incorrect!
I told you it's incorrect!
(He explodes.)
What is wrong with him?
(He only changes the name to the wrong answer.)
- He drives me crazy. - What are you doing?
Did you tell me it's incorrect?
- Ji Hyo. - Yeon Seok,
- Buzz, "Coward". - Is it me?
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
Yeon Seok, Buzz, "Coward".
- Incorrect. - Is it wrong?
(She copies Ji Hyo's wrong answer.)
Let's listen to the song a bit more.
It's "Coward".
(This time, it will be played a bit longer.)
Maybe it isn't Yeon Seok.
- It's a song by Buzz. - That's right.
Yes.
(Everyone sings along naturally.)
The sky is bright
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo, Buzz, "Thorn".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
Kwang Soo, Buzz, "Thorn". It's correct, isn't it?
- I tried that answer. - Jae Suk tried that answer.
(She's proud even though it's a wrong answer.)
Is it "Thorn"?
- He gave the exact same answer. - Se Chan, did you try "Thorn"?
I tried "Thorn".
(This song is...)
(is "Thorn" by Buzz which was released in 2005.)
(Every man must have copied Min Kyung Hoon's head voice.)
The right combination hasn't come up yet.
- Really? - Let me answer.
- Jong Kook, Buzz, "Thorn". - No.
- Incorrect. - Yeon Seok, Buzz, "Thorn".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
(Only So Min and Se Chan avoid the wrong answers.)
Yeon Seok, Buzz, "Coward".
- Incorrect. - It isn't "Coward".
Maybe it isn't "Coward" or "Thorn".
(Reaching the climax)
- Isn't it "Thorn"? - "Thorn".
- Is it a song by Buzz? - Let me answer.
- Jae Suk. - Is it "Thorn"?
- Yeon Seok. - So Min, Buzz, "Thorn".
- Correct. - What?
(He got it after many turns.)
- No one said it. - Didn't someone say my name?
(Did I say Se Chan?)
No one said it with Buzz and "Thorn".
Did no one say "Se Chan, Buzz, 'Thorn'"?
- Didn't you say it? - I thought I did.
(He didn't know his song of life when he was 20.)
- "Thorn". - I thought it was "Coward".
(Suk Jin is singing "Coward".)
"Thorn".
- I am a coward - It becomes a thorn
- Please go away - Please go away
(This is the answer.)
- Go away for good - Go away for good
(They loudly sing the song everyone sang at the karaoke.)
- Next question, cue. - Okay.
(It's the fourth question.)
- I will answer it. - Let me answer.
- 3, 2. - Teo.
Teo, Uhm Jung Hwa, "Pupil".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
Ji Hyo, Uhm Jung Hwa, "Poison".
- Incorrect. - Yeon Seok, Uhm Jung Hwa, "Poison".
(As it gets harder,)
Incorrect. Let's listen to it some more.
(it's played for some more.)
It isn't "Poison".
(Oh, I know this song.)
All right.
- Let me answer. - I figured it out!
Yeon Hee! Yeon Hee!
- BoA. - "Atlantis Princess".
"Atlantis Princess".
- Incorrect. - It is a song by BoA.
- Sooyoung! - All right.
Yeon Seok, BoA, "Atlantis Princess".
- Correct! - Yes!
Yes!
(Nice!)
She pronounced it strangely.
- No, I didn't. - She said "Tiramisu Princess".
(Nitpicking)
- She said "Tiramisu Princess". - "Tiramisu Princess".
(Unbelievable)
Sooyoung, say the answer clearly.
- Atlantis. - Atlantis.
(Clear pronunciation)
- "Atlantis Princess". - I was so close.
(That was close.)
- It gets confusing. - I know.
- She got it right. - "Atlantis Princess".
(Yeon Seok was 20 years old in 2003.)
(The star of Asia, BoA released this masterpiece.)
(There are only two questions left.)
- We will have two more questions. - Okay.
- Yeon Seok, answer one. - Okay.
(Spacing out)
- Let's go. - Look at Yeon Seok.
- I will answer. - Yeon Seok, concentrate!
(Get a grip.)
Don't look outside the window.
Figure out who was 20 years old. Song title and singer too.
(He yells at Yeon Seok and cheers everyone up.)
Let's go.
Let me answer.
god, "Lies"... Hold on. Who was 20 years old then?
- 3, 2... - So Min.
- So Min. - Incorrect.
Let me answer. Kwang Soo, god, "Lies".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
Yeon Seok, god, "Lies".
(It's a series of incorrect answers.)
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
- So Min. - Ji Hyo, god, "Lies".
- Correct. - It was Ji Hyo.
It was Ji Hyo.
(Was it me?)
Really?
- Was it me? - "Lies" came out a long time ago.
(Teo and Ji Hyo were 20 in 2000.)
(The song made god the national idol group...)
(and made everyone sing, "Goodbye, don't go.")
They were young back then.
(She had no idea.)
- I had no idea. - god.
- Now comes the last question. - Okay.
That was close.
- Yeon Seok, get it right. - Yeon Seok,
(Please)
just yell, "Let me answer."
- Yeon Seok, help out your team. - Okay.
(Ashamed)
Let's go. Music, cue.
(The last song plays.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Okay. - The answer is...
3, 2, 1.
(He raises his hand first, but he never gets the answer.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Hold on. Yeon Hee should go first.
Kwang Soo, Kim Hyun Jung, "Bruise".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Yeon Seok.
(Now is the time.)
- Hold on. - Let me answer.
- "Bruise"? - Kim Hyun Jung...
(Flustered)
Hold on. Yeon Seok said it first.
- Yeon Seok. - Okay.
(He doesn't sound confident.)
Jong Kook, Kim Hyun Jung,
- "Bruise". - "Bruise".
(Copying)
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - What?
(What an idiot.)
Jong Kook.
(No one knows when Yeon Seok will start contributing.)
I will play it again.
- What is it? - It sounds familiar.
(The melody sounds familiar.)
I can't hear it.
- "Farewell Again". - Let me answer.
- What? - I think it's "Tears".
- Jong Kook. - That isn't it.
- R.ef... - That isn't it.
- 3, 2, 1. - He only knows his songs.
- Incorrect. - It goes like this.
(The song has a familiar melody.)
Listen to the lyrics.
(The hint is in the lyrics.)
How do the lyrics go?
It's an old song.
(From your ex-girlfriend)
- Let me answer. - Okay.
- Haha, Kim Hyun Jung, - Go ahead.
- "Breaking up Alone". - Incorrect.
The lyrics contained the title.
(The lyric just had the hint.)
- Sooyoung. - Go ahead.
Who was it? Haha, Kim Hyun Jung, "Breakup with Her".
- Correct! - That's right. "Breakup with Her"!
"Breakup with Her".
That's right. "Breakup with Her"!
(She succeeded to get the last question right.)
That's right.
- "Breakup with Her". - We were so close.
(What a bummer. They almost had it.)
We messed up from the start.
- It was Haha. - It was me.
(When Haha was having storm and gale...)
- "Breakup with Her". - That's right.
(People who could hit high notes attempted to sing this song.)
(The song with high notes in which her belting cleansed the eardrums)
"It was my fault." That's the song, right?
"I didn't forget."
(No, it's not.)
(Really?)
- Everyone... - Here is the result.
(Here's the result of the second mission.)
- Team Sooyoung took first place. - Yes!
- Did they take first place again? - We got many questions right.
(Jealous)
(Feeling proud)
Team Yeon Seok took 2nd place with 2 questions right.
(Team Yeon Seok placed 2nd by answering 2 questions.)
- Okay! - Okay!
The other two teams are at the bottom.
(Team Teo and Team Yeon Hee placed last.)
We will give 500, 300, and 100 points.
(They get 500, 300, and 100 points each.)
- Okay, okay. - In that case,
- we won points. - Do we have plus 100 points now?
(Team Sooyoung's the only team with positive points.)
Is there a game that uses the body?
The next mission uses the body.
(They set out for the last mission.)
(The final mission)
Before we begin the last mission, I will announce the current points.
(Each team's current score)
In first place is Team Sooyoung with plus 100 points.
(Team Sooyoung's in 1st place with 100 points.)
- Plus? - They placed first in both games.
They placed first in both games.
(They're winning because they won the two previous games.)
- Every member is good at games. - Yes.
(Oh, yes.)
Team Yeon Hee, minus 300 points.
Team Teo, minus 800 points.
- Are we still in the last place? - Team Yeon Seok,
minus 1,100 points.
- But we... - We...
- We received points. - The current score reflects that.
(Why are we in the last place?)
Are we still in the last place?
- I mean... - From minus 1,400 points...
From minus 1,400 points...
(Why are we still in the last place when we worked so hard?)
Why are we still in the last place when we worked so hard?
Do you guys keep receiving minus points?
(Their negative score doesn't seem to decrease.)
- I don't know. - The thing is, Yeon Seok...
- isn't contributing at all. - Seriously.
The thing is, Yeon Seok isn't contributing at all.
Seriously.
We started at minus 900 points.
(Defending himself)
You should have written down more merits.
Yeon Seok really is bad at games.
(Joining)
- You are right. - He is the worst.
(Everyone's blaming Yeon Seok.)
- I wasn't going to complain, but... - He is suited for variety shows.
If Yeon Seok ages well,
he will become Suk Jin.
(He was doing well,)
- That's right. - He hates it.
(but he ends up drooping his head.)
- Yeon Seok hates it. - He is devastated.
- He hates it. - It's true, Yeon Seok.
(He feels sympathetic.)
Suk Jin loves games, but he is bad at them.
(He likes playing games, but he's not good at it.)
Oh, no.
"Oh, no."
I am sorry, Suk Jin.
I mean...
(He gets it off his chest.)
- Suk Jin became sullen for real. - It's okay.
He became sullen for real.
It's just that I want to be at games.
(Trying to make it up)
Suk Jin met the right team.
(Suk Jin met good teammates.)
He didn't do anything,
(Although Suk Jin's bad at games,)
but his teammates saved him. Yeon Hee was really good.
(Yeon Hee's leading the team.)
Yeon Hee played diligently.
- I didn't know she was so cheerful. - Seriously.
- She is competitive too. - My throat hurts.
(Side effect)
The last mission...
(It's the last mission to determine the result.)
is the Push and Pull Car Racer for 2021.
(Push and Pull Car Racer)
While wearing a blindfold,
(While wearing a blindfold, you will come down a slope in a car.)
you will come down a slope in a car.
You succeed...
(You succeed if you stop before the slope ends.)
if you step on the brake and stop the car...
as close as you can to the edge.
Before you go,
(You bet points before playing.)
you can bet points.
- Your points? - Yes.
Let's say you bet 100 points.
(I'm betting 100 points.)
It can become minus 200, minus 100 points, etc.
(Minus 2 times, minus 1 times, 0 times, 1 times, 5 times)
You can win up to five times the points.
No matter how many points you bet,
we will give you 300 points if you fall into starch.
(If you fall into starch, you get 300 points.)
We win 300 points if we fall into starch.
You can press the brake only once.
(You can press the brake only once.)
Teammates can yell, "Stop."
(Teammates can yell, "Stop.")
The 1st and 2nd teams that get 2,020 points will win.
(First 2 teams that get 2,020 points will win.)
If no team gets 2,020 points...
(If no team gets 2,020 points even after the 4th round,)
even after the fourth round,
the final scores will determine the rankings.
(the final scores will determine the rankings.)
- This is our only chance. - Okay, okay.
(Even the low-rank teams can win depending on the bet.)
- This is our only chance. - Let's go.
The first player of each team should go up.
(The 1st player of each team on standby)
Be careful.
(The king of curiosity checks out the cart.)
- It doesn't fit. - I see.
(He gets on the cart.)
You can't practice.
You can't do it.
- Why are you practicing? - Catch him.
(He goes down...)
- You can't practice. - You can't do it.
(the slope.)
- Why are you practicing? - Catch him.
(Flustered)
- Stop. - No, no.
(You must stop.)
- Jae Suk, stop. - Catch him.
- He is at the bottom. - Why are you practicing?
(He fails to hit the brake.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
(He falls off the edge.)
Stop.
(He went down unexpectedly and dove into the starch.)
What are you doing?
- What was that? - Why is he so flippant?
What was that?
(Jae Suk's covered in starch.)
Hey, hey.
I wasn't going to go down.
You are so mischievous.
(His mischievous instinct always gets him in trouble.)
He always breaks the rules.
He is a comedian through and through.
(He's the biggest troublemaker in the name of a comedian.)
- It wasn't intentional. - He is the best.
- It wasn't intentional. - Gosh.
(Embarrassed)
I will go fourth.
(Once you pick up the speed, it's hard to stop.)
Once it speeds it...
It takes time for the cart to stop.
(It's important to step on the brake at the right timing.)
Let's go!
So Min, tell us how many points you will bet.
How many points will you bet?
(So Min bets first.)
Do I choose?
Bet 1,000 points.
Shall I add 1,000 more points to that?
(She bets like there is no tomorrow.)
Get a hold of yourself, So Min.
- Put on a blindfold. - Let's go.
(So Min sets off after betting 1,000 points.)
Let's go.
(She could win 5,000 points...)
I am so scared. Hold on.
(or lose 2,000 points.)
Push gently.
- Let's go. - Push gently.
I'm pushing.
- So Min, are you ready? - Okay.
(How will she do?)
Not yet. Not yet. Not yet.
(It's a tense moment.)
Not yet. Not yet.
It won't go down.
(What?)
- Did you hit the brake? - I didn't.
(The cart stops before it picks up the speed.)
- Hold on, hold on. - Oh, no. So Min.
So Min, press it!
It won't go down.
(Kwang Soo pushes the cart.)
- Did you hit the brake? - I didn't.
- Hold on, hold on. - Oh, no. So Min.
- So Min, press it! - Stop!
(Despite her teammates' cries,)
(she lands in starch.)
- So Min, press it! - Stop!
- Hey! - She should have pressed...
- the brake. - You jerk!
- It's your fault! - The cart had stopped.
I only helped her.
- You shouldn't have done that. - I only helped her.
- I only helped her. - This is hilarious.
(She looks like a fried frog covered in white frying mix.)
I only helped her.
So Min, are you okay?
So Min, it's a ski resort.
- Are you okay? - So Min, it's a ski resort.
(She got snowed.)
Kwang Soo.
(Sneezing)
Who pushed me?
- Kwang Soo. - It wasn't like that.
It wasn't like that.
(So Min fell into starch and receives 300 points.)
The cart had come to a full stop.
- Fine. - I had to help.
- Kwang Soo. - Let's go.
(Next is Kwang Soo, the culprit of the accelerator.)
Kwang Soo, how many points will you bet?
- I will bet 1,000 points. - Okay.
Okay. 1,000 points.
(Team Yeon Seok needs a twist because they're in the last place.)
Kwang Soo, we will tell you when to stop.
- Where should he stop? - Hold on.
(Leader Yeon Seok is getting ready thoroughly.)
Shall we tell him to stop at the "multiply by minus one" mark?
Let's tell him to stop at the "multiply by zero" mark.
1,000 points.
(They couldn't escape from the minus points.)
I am in the right position, right?
Okay.
- Let's go. - I am in the right position, right?
(How about this time?)
- Yes. - Am I...
(Kwang Soo sets off with hopes to escape from the minus points!)
- Stop! - Stop!
(Will Kwang Soo be able to stop in time?)
(He crashes into starch!)
- Stop! - Stop!
(He fiddled with the brake belatedly...)
(and crashed.)
Is this how it's done?
- No one is succeeding to stop. - Hey.
- Did you run a simulation? - Yes.
Were you able to stop?
(They think the brake is broken as they continue to fail.)
We were able to stop.
- I don't think the brake works. - The teammates should help.
(Express train to starch with a broken brake)
You know...
The teammates should help.
He flew off like KTX.
It's impossible to stop.
(The one with experience)
I don't think the brake works.
- Shall we give a demonstration? - Yes.
Why would you give a demonstration at this point?
- You should have done it sooner. - You are done.
(He gets angry with a pale face.)
(They put the cart back in place for demonstration.)
Suk Jin, help me with this.
Don't just leave.
(He asks for help while moving it.)
Carry this with me.
(The production crew decide to show a demonstration.)
- We will give a demonstration. - Okay.
Let's see a demonstration.
(The representative of the production crew comes up.)
- Try it. - Okay.
Try it with this cart.
(He checks the brake expertly.)
(The simulation team has gone through countless games.)
Stop before you go off the edge.
(To make a safe and fun game,)
(the best driver has ridden the cart dozens of times.)
(The ace member sets off to quell their complaints.)
Let's see it.
Will he succeed?
(Crashing)
Come on. Come on!
(He stops the cart in less than 1m.)
Hey!
Come on. Come on!
(He should be embarrassed about the distance.)
Hey!
Why did you send a coward?
He is a coward! He didn't even go halfway down.
(Being under pressure made him stop...)
- He is a coward! - This is impossible.
(as soon as he began.)
Even a staff member can't do it.
(A moment ago,)
Okay.
(the simulation team could stop as they wanted.)
(Proud)
(After checking the brake, it's Jae Suk's turn.)
- Let's go. - Let's bet 1,000 points.
1,000 points. He is confident.
(Jae Suk bets 1,000 points.)
1,000 points.
- Here we go. - Stop him.
(The cart moves before he gets into position.)
(In a rush)
Hey.
(He pressed the brake as hard as he could.)
What was that?
- Hey. - What was that?
(He got thrown into starch.)
What was that?
This game is no fun.
(The flippant man had it coming.)
- Hey! - The brake is broken!
He pressed it early on, but it didn't stop!
(The braking distance is quite long.)
- Hey! - The brake is broken!
- He pressed it right away. - It doesn't work!
(They complain out loud...)
He pressed it right away, but it didn't stop!
(in starch.)
What is this nonsense?
(The passengers are complaining.)
Listen.
After it speeds up,
(They need to pull the brake hard at once.)
it should be halted halfway down the slope.
Why are you running a simulation with us?
- Why? - We tried it many times.
(For the members who can't get used to Running Man's brake system,)
Can we take off our blindfolds?
We did wear blindfolds, but...
- Let's start over... - From the next round,
(they play without a blindfold from the next round.)
- without the blindfolds. - we will take out the blindfolds.
- All right. - Teo is determined.
(The 2nd round begins.)
He studied everyone carefully.
(Teo doesn't want to lose when it comes to cars.)
He is serious.
Jong Kook tends to succeed when he plays games like this.
(And)
(The Grand Award winner does what others can't.)
I bet Jong Kook will succeed. I bet Jong Kook will succeed.
(He checks the cart.)
How many points will you bet?
(Which team will be the first to succeed?)
- Bet 1,000 points. 1,000 points. - 1,000 points.
- 1,000 points? - Yes.
(The first player Jong Kook...)
- Let's go. - 1,000 points.
(bets 1,000 points.)
- I will push you. - Okay.
(He refuses to be covered in what isn't even protein powder.)
(The protein monster sets off with determination!)
(Screeching)
What?
(After 2.5m,)
- Yes! - Yes!
(the cart stops.)
- "Multiply by minus two". - Okay.
(It's minus 2 times.)
- Yes! - Yes!
(Team Sooyoung loses 2,000 points.)
- "Multiply by minus two". - Minus 2,000 points.
- "Multiply by minus two". - What?
- It works! - "Multiply by minus two".
(Yelling)
- "Multiply by minus two". - The brake works well!
(The protein monster gets angry when he is embarrassed.)
- Nice! - Okay!
(What's up with him?)
- Minus 2,000 points. - Minus 2,000 points.
- Yes! - Okay!
(The cart halted quickly because he used his muscles.)
- Okay. This cart stops well. - They are at the bottom now.
- Listen. - They are at the bottom now.
(It stops too well.)
We could wear blindfolds. The brake works well.
- Minus 2,000 points. - We could wear blindfolds.
(The man with a big build's timid driving)
We could wear blindfolds. The brake works well.
It's a party!
Jong Kook, you are a coward.
Had you gone off the edge, you would have gotten 300 points.
The cart moved this much when the others hit the brake.
(Giving excuses)
- So I did it early on. - Jong Kook, it was fun.
- The sound was so petty. - It was fun.
It was fun.
(The petty ASMR)
Yeon Seok, you saw how it's done.
(The petty driving ends.)
Hit the brake around here.
- Let's go. - My goodness.
(It's the new loophole Yeon Seok's turn.)
- Wear the helmet. - Yeon Seok, you must do this.
Okay. 2,000 points.
I won't play around this time.
- I will do it with seriousness. - Yeon Seok.
- You failed all day, okay? - Succeed just this once.
(Yeon Seok showed poor performance all day long.)
- Show us your cool side. - Okay.
We don't know what the penalty will be.
(I won't fail anymore!)
Even if you stop at yellow, we will be set.
Okay.
I will succeed.
- I will put an end to failures. - Okay.
(He gives his words of resolution.)
I will put an end to failures.
Hold on. No!
What is he doing?
- What is he doing? - No one pushed him.
(No one pushed him.)
No one pushed him.
(What is he doing?)
What is he doing? What is he doing?
- No one pushed him. - What is he doing?
(After an unimpressive ride, he falls in a fancy way.)
- What is he doing? - What was that?
- What is up with him? - What are you doing?
(Instead of escaping, he falls straight into the starch field.)
- You're talking nonsense. - Hey...
What is wrong with him?
Why did you look back when no one pushed you?
- What is wrong with him? - What is wrong with him?
(He proves himself as a successor of Suk Jin.)
- Did you see a ghost? - Gosh.
- What is wrong with him? - What did he do?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - What is wrong with him?
(Was it an illusion?)
- What are you doing? - I thought someone pushed me.
Who would push you?
- Who would push you? - There was no one behind you.
(He didn't put a stop to failing, he extended his life of failing.)
- I just... - No one paid attention to you.
I thought Jong Kook pushed me.
(Failing Yeon Seok became covered in starch.)
That was so funny, Yeon Seok.
Yeon Seok, it's okay since you were funny.
- Gosh. - It's okay since you were funny.
(Slapping)
It's better to brush it hard.
(Lee Kwang Soo, Starch expert, It's better to brush it hard.)
I brushed hard to brush the starch off.
(I'll also brush it off you then.)
What are you doing?
(Altruistic cheek-slapping that's impatient...)
(to brush starch off each other)
(They're affirming their brotherhood by producing fine dust.)
That's heartwarming. The year-end is so heartwarming.
- Yes. - You can help each other out.
- That's right. - Our company is running...
(She's in the same company.)
so darn well.
Yes, your company is really...
(Heartwarming)
Our company is running so darn well.
(The two starch King Kongs are showing off a special friendship.)
- Hey. - Oh, my.
(I think good things will happen in 2021.)
We're starting again.
- It's Teo's turn. - Teo!
(It's Teo's turn to bet on 1,000 points.)
- Let's go. - You can do it.
(Teo might be good at it since he's from Germany.)
I think he can do it for some reason.
You only have to do it once.
It's 10,000 dollars.
There's a ghost next to Ji Hyo.
- What? - Me?
(A 2.4m tall ghost that looks pale)
- He's just standing like that. - Me?
- Yes. - Why is he standing there?
(He looks like a ghost in the middle of the winter.)
He's just standing like that.
- He's scary. - What's happening?
He's taking off. He accepted the challenge.
(Teo takes off.)
He accepted the challenge. Do your best.
He's taking off. He accepted the challenge.
(Think of the Autobahn you experienced when you were young.)
Okay, go.
- No way. - Nice!
(It's a cowardly riding...)
(that you can't see in Germany.)
- Okay! - Okay!
Nice! That's double minus points!
- What are you... - I'm not in last place anymore!.
(What's wrong with him?)
- He's a coward. - He's a coward.
(Team Teo loses 2,000 points due to his cowardly riding.)
- Gosh. - He's a coward.
- This is... - Yoo Teo, "Coward" by Buzz.
Teo.
Give this to me again.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
- That's it. - It's not locked completely.
(They're trying hard to fix the brake.)
Kwang Soo, just come out if you can't do it.
(Struggling)
It's going to break.
(He succeeds at once.)
- He did it. - It's working now.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
(The tall white ghost likes to step out of his line.)
It's over if I just press this once.
- Wait a minute. - Just go.
(He's getting ready.)
- Wait a minute. - Wait a minute.
(But Jae Suk forces him to take off.)
What is wrong with you?
What is wrong with him?
- You need to take off quickly. - I'm getting ready.
(Jae Suk is acting playful because he wants to ride it.)
- During the test... - Lean to the back.
- From here... - No.
I'm going to go fast.
- He's going to go fast. - I'm going to go fast.
Look. I will stop when I lock the brake around "multiply by two".
(He must brake here.)
(His goal)
- Will you speed? - I will.
- He's heavy, so... - So now...
- Let's go. - Let go after you tell me.
(The speed helper forces a fast take off.)
- Here. - Let go after you tell me.
(Creaking)
Wait, it's broken.
(He fell forward after making a lot of noise from the brake.)
You said you would go fast.
- You... - This is impossible.
(He only earns 300 points without any speeding.)
- I'm going to take off. - Just go.
- Haha. Teo. - Do your best!
(It's now the troublemaker's turn.)
I'm going to aim for 2,000 points.
- 2,000 points. Deal! - Take it and double it.
(He relentlessly bets on 2,000 points.)
He's voluntarily going to the underworld.
(Would it be the highway to paradise or fire pit?)
Okay, I'll take off.
(The fate of their team depends on the fingertips of the troublemaker.)
Good.
(Creaking)
He did it!
(He succeeded at multiplying it by 1.)
- It's "multiply by one". - Okay.
(The troublemaker older brother always caused trouble.)
- He did it. It's "multiply by one". - Okay.
(He caused a giant accident this time.)
- "Multiply by one". - I should've gone a little further.
(He gained 2,000 points with an otherworldly control.)
- You were really awesome! - I should've gone a little further.
- I should've gone a little further. - Yes.
You gained 2,000 points!
- I should've gone a little further. - We could've gotten 4,000 points.
(Bitter)
- Okay, then. This team won. - Gosh.
(Team Teo wins.)
- We won? - Yes.
- We won? - We won!
Yes, but we will continue until we have a team in second place.
(Even the winners are puzzled by the news of winning.)
(We did it!)
- What are they doing? - I think we will be in last place.
(They celebrate with all kinds of gestures.)
- This is unbelievable. - After that...
- This is incredible. - Didn't they have any minus points?
Didn't they have any minus points?
Weren't they in last place?
(Are you sure that team is in 1st place?)
They didn't win, did they?
(Murmuring)
They were?
- Everyone. - Look at this.
I'm sorry.
You have 1,820 points right now. You need 200 more points.
(They need 200 more points to get the winning score of 2,020 points.)
- Come on. - 1,820?
You need more points.
(They retract the announcement due to miscalculation.)
- 1,820 points? - You need more points.
- Tell us why you did that. - Hey.
The atmosphere was nice just now.
- We did ceremonies like crazy. - You should've kept it going.
(There's an exchange of joy and sorrow because of the reversal.)
- It's not over yet. - We need more points.
It's not over yet.
If I just land in the starch and receive 300 points...
- You will succeed then. - Okay.
- Teo. - Yes?
- Just land in the starch. - Just land in the starch.
(Team Teo is still at an advantage.)
We get 300 points if we land in there. You'll look cool.
- Just land in the starch. - Okay.
(They start to murmur again.)
Everyone, I'm really sorry,
but you had minus 2,200 points.
That's right. They had a lot of minus points.
So you have minus 200 points now.
- I'm sorry. - What is he talking about?
I'm sorry.
There's still a long way to go.
Why are you causing such a fuss?
Goodness.
(The staff continues to make...)
- I'm sorry. - There's still a long way to go.
(embarrassing calculation mistakes in front of the guests.)
Why are you causing such a fuss?
- I'm sorry. - You should get beaten up first.
(Team Teo approaches to appeal to the staff members.)
I'm really sorry.
- What are you doing? - Hey.
I thought the game was over.
(He thought the game was over because they caused such a fuss.)
Did they just reach minus 200 points?
Are you kidding me?
- You didn't win yet. - Gosh.
(We finished celebrating but now we have minus 200 points?)
- Hey. - We're even done doing ceremonies.
- Did you just reach minus 200? - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - What is happening?
(He's about to refute using logic.)
- We're even done doing ceremonies. - Okay.
(They gained 2,000 points from minus 2,200 points.)
You had minus 2,200 points earlier because of Yoo Teo.
You earned 2,000 points just now.
(His logic is in full operation.)
We bet 2,000 points though.
- So you earned that. - And they got "multiply by one".
- You ended up with that. - Will we get minus zero...
if we get "multiply by 0"?
No, it's just zero.
Just cut it out.
(His logic runs out quickly.)
What's the difference between 0 and 1?
(His teammate ditches him really quickly too.)
Zero means that you won't earn anything.
- We gave you 2,000 points. - He can't even win.
- Hey. - Haha.
Dumb Haha, just come here.
2,000 times 0 is 0.
Why do you keep complaining to him when he's highly educated?
(Haha's angry but he can't refute logically.)
- He said you're highly educated. - Why do you keep acting up?
- He will lose just like that. - Gosh.
(He makes a U-turn acknowledging defeat.)
- He lost. - He's returning.
I'm sorry for the confusion.
(We once again apologize for the confusion.)
Multiplying it by zero obviously give them zero points.
(Times by 1 means they earn as much as they bet.)
Doesn't he know how to multiply?
This is the last round.
(Each time has one turn left.)
- It's Jae Suk's turn then. - Will Jae Suk do it?
- Me? - We're in second place now.
(This turn will determine the final outcome.)
How many points do we have right now?
- Please tell us exactly. - Aren't we in second place?
(1st place Team Yeon Hee 300, 2nd place Team Yeon Seok minus 100)
(3rd place Team Teo minus 200, 4th place Team Sooyoung minus 2200)
I think Jae Suk will do it.
(Jae Suk aims for 1st place while betting 1,000 points.)
But this is...
I think Jae Suk will do it.
(Jae Suk has the highest record, and it's his last try.)
We will prepare a ceremony.
Do your best.
(Will Jae Suk be able to repeat the miracle that happened earlier?)
That's it.
Trust your instincts.
(He pushed the brake.)
- It's a minus. - It's a minus.
(Times by minus 1)
It's a minus.
(Times by minus 1 equals a 1,000 point deduction)
You're in last place then.
- Earlier... - You're in last place.
- What happened? - Since it's multiply by minus one.
(The possibility of being in the last place...)
Jae Suk.
(happened with the deduction.)
Seriously...
(Team Sooyoung has the chance to avoid being in the last place.)
- Try pushing it in the beginning. - Okay.
- Will you bet 2,000 points? - Yes.
(She's in the last place anyway. She daringly bets 2,000 points.)
(If she gets plus 5 times, her team will end up in 1st place.)
(If she gets a minus, her team will end up in the last place.)
Sooyoung, you can do it.
(It's her last chance to make up for Jong Kook's mistake.)
Do your best, Sooyoung.
Sooyoung, you can do it.
(Choi Sooyoung takes off.)
You can do it.
I think you should push the brake. Push it.
(Sooyoung pushes the brake after safely passing the minuses.)
- Push it. - Push it.
- Gosh. - That's it.
(She falls.)
Sooyoung, good job.
(She ends the game after earning just 300 points.)
I pushed it.
- Good job. - It was too late.
Why do I keep going backward?
(It's now Ji Hyo's turn from Team Yeon Hee.)
- That's not how you do it. - Push with one foot.
- We will push it for you. - Hey.
(They extend their fake helping hand.)
No, you can't do that.
- Stop. - What happened?
(But...)
- It's "multiply by one"! - What?
Stop.
- What happened? - Yes!
(She stopped for now.)
It's "multiply by zero".
(She stopped exactly in the middle of plus 1 times and 0 times.)
- It's "multiply by zero"! - No, it's "multiply by zero".
(The score is determined based on the front wheel.)
- Isn't it "multiply by one"? - No, it's "multiply by zero".
- It's "multiply by zero". - It's "multiply by zero".
(It's judged as 0 times.)
The front wheel is on "multiply by zero".
- I'm certain. - It is, judging from the sideline.
(Team Yeon Hee remains in 1st place with 300 points.)
- Right here. - It's "multiply by zero".
- It's "multiply by zero". - It's "multiply by zero".
(They confirm at least 2nd place.)
- "Multiply by zero". - How is this "multiply by zero"?
- It is "multiply by zero". - The wheels...
(There's only 1 more team left.)
It's based on the wheels.
Yeon Seok, just land in the starch.
(It's Yeon Seok's turn.)
Yeon Seok.
(Team Yeon Seok bets 1,000 points.)
- Yeon Seok. - Push it when you're here.
If you succeed here, you will win.
- If he succeeds? - Yes.
(Team Yeon Hee is currently in 1st place with 300 points.)
(Team Sooyoung is currently in the last place with minus 1,900 points.)
(Team Yeon Seok can also become 1st or last place.)
You need to go a little fast.
That's good. That look in your eyes is good.
Okay, let the best man win.
Let the best man win.
(The last cart took off heroically.)
- This is a match. - He keeps asking that.
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
(What?)
Why?
- What are you doing? - What is wrong with you?
(He gets minus 2 times.)
(He said, "This is the match.")
(He stops cowardly after 1m.)
- What are you doing? - What is wrong with you?
Hey, you...
(His younger brothers are exploding from their pent-up anger all day.)
- The slope isn't even that steep. - You should've at least come here.
(His cowardly breaks blow away the last chance.)
Hey.
(Team Yeon Seok gets minus 2,000 points.)
- You're in last place. - He was so serious though.
Gosh.
That's what happens when he does it seriously.
(The match Yeon Seok's been calling for remains mysterious.)
You're showing a lot of different sides of you today.
- This stops too easily. - Yeon Seok.
(He's also the type who makes excuses.)
- What is wrong with you? - You've been doing this all day.
(The last mission is over after Yeon Seok's heroic act.)
I told you to push it here.
- Everyone, we have the result. - Yes.
(The final result is out.)
The team in first place is...
Team Yeon Hee.
(Team Yeon Hee is in 1st place with 300 points.)
- Yes. - Did we win?
The team in second place is Team Teo.
(Team Teo ended up in 2nd place by luck with minus 1,200 points.)
- This is unbelievable. - Gosh.
3rd place and 4th place have a 200-point difference.
(3rd and 4th place are only different by 200 points.)
200 points? Then we still have a chance.
- I think we're in last place. - That was so close though.
(With a 200 point difference,)
(4th place will receive the penalty.)
Okay, third place is...
(3rd place avoided the penalty with a 200 point difference.)
Third place...
It can't be...
- Team Sooyoung. - Wow!
Fourth place is Team Yeon Seok.
3rd place is Team Sooyoung and 4th place is Team Yeon Seok.
(These three men will receive the penalty.)
Why would you make us expectant?
Yoo Yeon Seok...
(Yeon Seok is the lucky charm for the other teams.)
- He made them lose at one go. - Hey.
Yeon Seok did everything today.
(Yeon Seok's miracle started with the tango.)
Was the game turned around because of Yeon Seok?
(They lost due to Yeon Seok's cowardly stop.)
- Really? - Yes, with "multiply by minus two".
That's incredible.
It's our first time having a guest ruin their team like this.
- I'm serious. - He's terrible at games.
I've never seen anyone this terrible at games.
He's really...
He even beat Kwang Soo and Se Chan.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan look relatively normal.)
- This is driving me crazy. - He really...
For the teams in 1st place and 2nd place,
we will give you gift certificates to use at traditional markets...
worth 1,000 dollars as a new year's gift.
- I can't believe it. - You can share them now.
(A meaningful prize for the upcoming new year)
- Take these. - 1,000 dollars?
- Yes. - That's nice.
They're traditional market gift certificates.
It's my 1st time being in 1st place.
You can use this like cash.
- This is like cash. - Okay.
(Two families share the money.)
Divide them among yourselves.
What is the penalty for today and who is in the last place?
(Revealing Team Yeon Seok's penalty)
The penalty is...
for you to get rid of the old grime of 2020...
and have a fresh start in 2021.
You will make a copy of your face by applying ink on your face.
- Yes, that's good. - What are you talking about?
(It's basically rubbing ink on their faces.)
- Bring in the materials. - This is the worst.
You must apply it completely.
(The rubbing of three men's faces begins.)
You forgot his nose. Apply more on the lips.
- Gosh. - It's really...
(It's assumed to be Yang Se Chan.)
You really look like a fish.
(One plump rockfish...)
- It turned out well. - What is that?
- Do it for Kwang Soo too. - It turned out well.
- Right now... - Do it now.
(and one penis fish are captured.)
- Should I press it? - It really looks...
(They even completed Yeon Seok's copy that's unique for some reason.)
2021 is the Year of the Ox. We will see you then.
(Running Man will continue to run hard in 2021.)
- It's the Year of the Ox. - Yes, it is.
See you next year. Thank you.
(Thanks to the four actors of "New Year Blues".)
- Thank you - Thank you.
Life always...
makes you stand in front of a crossroad of choices.
Just die if you're scared.
We have a good chance right now, so we should just continue.
Let's start the game now.
Okay, lock the door.
In the new year...
(The new year, 2021)
I'm Carlos.
(President candidate 1, Carlos, Ex-president)
- Kim Grand Award. - Kim Grand Award.
(President candidate 2, Kim Grand Award)
He's Cho Kka Chi.
(President candidate 3, Yang Kka Chi)
- His name is Ribeye. - Kwang Soo is Ribeye.
(President candidate 4, Year of the Ox, Lee Ribeye)
You could call me a hoodwinker.
(President candidate 5, Elder Woodwinker)
- She's Sally. - My world is wide.
(President candidate 6, Sally)
I'm Song Jeoktoma.
(President candidate 7, Song To Ma)
- What is he? - He's a petty thief.
(President candidate 8, Petty Thief)
Only the best has remained now.
(Variety Show Hoodwinkers, The Return of Gamblers)
All in.
(It's the final single round match among hoodwinkers...)
(who only know about going all in.)
We will end up in the final round.
I'll choose number eight.
(They can only trust luck and power.)
I will do everything.
(The world of professionals...)
I'm a beggar now.
(became more desperate and venomous.)
You're going bankrupt.
You're going to end up on the streets.
Breaking news. Ji Suk Jin is rolling in the snow.
(Breaking news, "Bankrupt hoodwinker Ji rolling in snow")
- He has no tomorrow anyway. - What are you doing?
(Did the ragged hoodwinkers even visit a pawnshop?)
- I have no place else to go now. - I'm giving my everything.
(The war among gamblers who have no place else to go will start.)
I'm going to bet my life on this.
(2021 Hoodwinker Association New Year's Party)
(The Return of Gamblers)