What is this?
- They are bowling pins.
- It's bowling.
(What's the first game they are
playing with bowling pins?)
It's bowling.
I'm good at bowling.
My score is 100.
Aren't you just a fool?
What? That means you are...
chonggak kimchi?
It sounds just about right.
I know. It sounds right.
This is the first mission
for the team match.
It's Human Bowling: Sticky Guys.
A player from each team
will take turns.
A player will roll
to the bowling pins...
wearing a sleep shade
within one minute.
But the surface of
the bowling set is very sticky.
If you end up on the sticky part
at the end of the time limit,
you will stay put
at where you are stuck.
If you're outside the sticker,
you will be eliminated.
Then the next player will
take part in the mission.
The team that knocks down
the most pins will win.
We'll put on a sleep shade
and roll forward?
Exactly.
But you can't go out of the lines.
If you roll to the side,
you will be eliminated.
Can I roll over and over again?
You are given one minute.
We should hurry. It will take
a long time to get there.
I'm in trouble.
I can't roll forward.
You keep rolling aside.
Anyway, I'd like you to decide
which team will go first.
Jae Suk, shall we
play Race of Wits?
Let's play Race of Wits.
- Race of Wits?
- Do you know Race of Wits?
Okay.
- Let's begin.
- One.
- We should sit down.
- Is it wrong?
- Did I do it wrong?
- Hae Sun, what are you doing?
- What should I do?
- Say one as you sit down.
- Ready...
- One.
(Ready...)
(She makes a false start
feeling highly motivated.)
You should wait until I say start.
(While Hae Sun feels motivated...)
(What? I don't know how to play.)
(Jong Ok gets coached
on how to play.)
Ready...
Even if you don't know the game,
you should go along with it.
Jong Ok, you can just stand still.
- Someone will lose anyway.
- I'll just wait standing still.
All right. Ready, set, go.
- 1.
- 1. Gosh.
(A bad example
of excessive ambition)
- So the two of us are out.
- You two are out.
Again. Ready, set, go.
One.
Two.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
(Shouting 5 loudly)
Go again with the two of us out.
One of us loses every time.
Ready, set, go.
- 1.
- 2.
(She remembers the advice
from her colleague.)
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
Jong Ok.
(Don't I win if I stay standing?)
- 1.
- 2.
(She just stood still until the end
as Suk Jin advised.)
- Nice!
- Okay!
- You go first.
- She's a big senior.
Oh no.
- She's cute.
- She was like this at the end.
You told me to stand still.
Suk Jin did.
- I'm sorry.
- You should've told her to sit.
I trusted him.
- All right. Suk Jin, you go first.
- Why should I go first?
- All right.
- Our team goes first.
Show us how it's done.
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
You are very important.
You saw that, right? You shouldn't
touch the sticky part.
- Let's go.
- I should roll straight.
Ready, set, go.
(Surprised)
He's really good.
(He's really good.)
(He rolls straight forward
without veering off.)
(He uses his arm
to help himself navigate.)
How did he know that?
- He has a good sense of direction.
- Is there a time limit?
It's one minute.
- My gosh.
- You should do it in one minute.
That's amazing.
(The arm compass is
shaking a little.)
(He sits on the sticky part.)
You have to do it in one minute.
(He's stuck.)
Oh no. What now?
(What should we do about him?)
This is...
He wears red thermal
underwear like that.
Is he doing that on purpose?
(Sticky)
(The gloves are stuck too.)
He's like a fly.
He lost his gloves and socks.
(He flounders with the spirit
of non-possession.)
He's like a fly.
(He looks like a fly on flypaper.)
He's like a fly on flypaper.
(A fly with a big nose)
(They laugh...)
(and cry at the same time.)
Hae Sun finds it really funny.
Suk Jin might
take off all his clothes.
(He's still struggling.)
(The more they watch him,)
(the worse they feel for the fly.)
(Time's up.)
- Oh no. I feel really bad.
- He should stay like that.
He's not listening.
- Stay.
- Stay. Stop it.
You should stop.
Oh no.
You should stay there.
You may take off the sleep shade.
Can't you even do this?
- You should give it a try.
- You shouldn't move.
- Stay still.
- You should stay there.
(He should stay on the sticker
until the game ends.)
My goodness.
Should he stay there like that?
Take off the sleep shade.
It's okay to take it off.
You should think.
You can't move like that.
Hey, you give it a try.
Do you think it's easy?
You should either make it funny
or hit the pins.
It was so boring.
- You should pick one.
- You made it look so boring.
I'll wait and see how good you are.
The yellow team will go next as is.
Team Hae Sun.
- It's better to go first.
- But he's right there.
We have to keep trying like this?
It's good
that you closed off the path.
- Really? I did a good job.
- Right.
Suk Jin, you should stay still.
- What did you say?
- You should stay still.
There's nothing else I can do.
(He's cute.)
When Jong Ok laughs,
she sounds like a character...
from an animated movie.
What?
(Laughing)
It's her real laugh.
(Jong Ok's 2D laughter)
She laughs exactly like "Ha-ha."
She keeps calling my name.
Who's next?
- Kwang Soo, do you want to try?
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo.
- You should block the way.
Kwang Soo, go block the way.
Kwang Soo is very tall.
- I will make it long.
- Good.
I wouldn't have gone first if I knew
I'd stay here like this.
No, you did a good job.
Did I? I love you, Jong Ok.
(What did you say?)
- Good luck.
- All of a sudden?
- He sounds like a romanticist.
- He's a romanticist.
(He rarely says that to his wife.)
He rarely says that to his wife.
- What?
- That's why I hate him.
That's too brutal.
- It's a fatal blow.
- But I had to say it.
I just know what he's like.
- Kwang Soo, do it right.
- Okay.
You sound like you are
older than Kwang Soo.
- Oh, really?
- Be careful.
It's strange
that I don't feel offended.
Meanwhile, Hae Sun looks
like an audience.
This is fun.
I'm glad to hear that.
This isn't something you can
experience in your daily life.
- Right.
- That's true.
Even celebrities don't
have a chance to do this...
unless they appear on variety shows.
I don't even know where I can
get these tight suits from.
I know.
It's so funny.
- Ready...
- He's very feisty.
He's in trouble.
He looks like the longest tentacle
of a dried squid.
The longest tentacle
You can buy it
at a department store.
Ready, set, go.
(He starts with his long leg.)
Good.
Good. He's doing good
because he's tall.
(Speeding up)
(Flipping down)
He's doing good
because he's tall.
(Welcome to the sticky world.)
Gosh, look at that.
(Giggling)
- He's stuck.
- That's good.
- This is good.
- It looks so funny.
Oh no.
Good.
You have only one minute.
(He's like a chick
hatching from its egg.)
- Is it that hard to go straight?
- It looks so hard.
Can't you go straight?
- Good.
- There you go.
- That's good.
- Well done.
You got one minute.
(The time is coming to an end.)
(Struggling)
Where is he going?
- Oh no.
(Laughing)
- I guess it's extremely sticky.
- It's really sticky.
Take off the sleep shade.
- Take it off.
- Oh no.
(Is that it?)
I should've rolled one more time.
Gosh, it's really sticky.
This isn't easy.
Let me show you how it's done.
He's stepping up.
- Jae Suk is stepping up.
- We should help you.
This is all about experience.
- There's the 3, 7 guy.
- 3, 7 guy?
- Jae Suk, 3.
- Strawberry...
- Jae Suk, seven.
- My gosh.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- The 3, 7 guy.
Jong Ok and Hae Sun, watch me.
Watch me carefully.
Jae Suk, just make sure
not to put us to shame.
Watch me, Jong Kook.
For this,
I should roll myself up.
- Okay.
- And I shouldn't move a lot.
You will see how bad he is.
(On his honor as an entertainer)
(Excited)
Ready, set...
We're doomed.
(He charges toward the sticker
as soon as the whistle is blown.)
(He's done for already.)
Look at his head.
(Groaning)
Oh no.
(He's stuck with a single cry.)
- He's stuck.
- Jae Suk, three.
Jae Suk, seven.
- Jae Suk.
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- What is this...
- What are you doing there?
(He's trying
to overcome the sticky slump.)
You don't need pants now.
That's right. Take them off.
Take off your socks.
(He takes off his pants
and charges forward.)
It looks like a metamorphosis
of a pupa.
Why are you taking off your pants?
(Goodbye, my pants. I should go.)
That's good.
That's right.
Take off your shirt. My gosh.
(The time is up
while he rolls forward.)
(It's so funny.)
It's gross.
Don't you dare move.
- Stay still.
I can't move.
You went the wrong way
from the beginning.
Why are you spreading your legs?
(Spread wide)
Why...
It's so funny. What should we do?
It looks really ugly from here.
Why are you spreading
your legs in front of the camera?
My posture is...
(As he gets a lot of criticism,)
(they put a tray on him.)
What are you doing...
What's that?
(It's taken care of.)
Hey.
What are you doing?
Hey, what do you think
you're doing now?
(He's highly satisfied.)
- Who's next?
- My goodness.
I will get there like a bulldozer.
I'm worried about him.
You should overcome the sticker.
Hey, my face is here.
My face is in the middle of it.
I'll just go through it.
You should be careful.
Ready, set...
(Start)
- Here I go.
- How is possible?
He's going straight.
Is it even possible?
(He rolls forward in the right
direction with tireless momentum.)
Is it even possible?
(Stop coming.)
Gosh, he's going straight.
(He does look like a bulldozer.)
(And the sticker No. 1
meets with the bulldozer.)
Stop him.
(Will it be blocked or penetrated?)
(He defeats Suk Jin immediately.)
Stop him.
(Jong Kook has reached
the bowling pins.)
(Is he hitting a strike like that?)
(He hits only 1 pin.)
No.
(He gets eliminated
after hitting only 1 pin.)
What was that?
It was going really well.
- What's that?
- It was so close.
What was that?
- Jong Kook suddenly turned left.
- Since you're not on the sticker,
you can come out of it.
I was in a rush
at the last moment.
It's become less sticky now,
so we will cut down
the time to 30 seconds.
So Min will go next.
(Team Jong Ok's next player
is Jeon So Min.)
Let me try.
You should hit 1 pin, So Min.
Only 2 pins.
I can't roll forward to begin with.
Just do it.
Gosh, what's Jae Suk doing?
- My goodness.
- Why are you being like that?
- It's embarrassing.
- My gosh.
Aren't you going to get rid of this?
Ready, set...
(Start)
- So Min, just do it.
- It's all about speed.
Don't go that way.
Gosh, where are you going?
- Hey, where are you going?
- I'm here.
- Good.
- Good. You're doing it well.
- My gosh.
- Keep rolling.
- I think she's almost there.
- Good.
Good.
(Making a deep bow)
(After making a bow,
she heads to the pins again.)
- Keep rolling.
- Looking good.
Good.
(My goodness)
That's good.
Oh no. That was close.
Gosh, what's this?
- She was going well.
- What is this?
- What are you doing here?
- I got you at the last moment.
This is...
- 30 seconds?
- I get only 30 seconds?
- Who should go next?
- I'll go next.
(Ji Hyo of Team Hae Sun
is going next.)
All you need to do is go straight.
I just saw what they did.
I'm scared.
Ji Hyo is good.
You should go between
Suk Jin and So Min.
- Okay. I will try.
- So Min, make sure to block her.
They have good defense.
What should we do about him?
(Me?)
(He can't believe
what's happening to him.)
I can cover your face with the sleep
shade if you feel embarrassed.
- Hey.
- Do you want to cover your face?
My gosh.
Do you have a death wish?
Let's begin. Ready, set...
(Ji Hyo starts.)
- What's she doing?
- She's the ace player.
(She's got the instinct
of the ace player.)
Good.
(I have to stop her.)
(Groaning)
(She breaks through Suk Jin.)
Keep going.
(This is a good chance.)
Ji Hyo, good.
You're going the right way.
- No.
- Hey!
Let me go!
(Ji Hyo punishes her.)
(What is going on?)
Let go of me.
Ji Hyo.
- Get off me.
- Keep rolling.
No, not that way.
(She totally missed the pins.)
(Laughing)
This is amazing.
Where am I? Hey!
- Who was that?
- It was so close.
Ji Hyo poked me in the butt.
Good defense.
She was going straight.
- She was almost there.
- I lost my direction...
- trying to avoid them.
- Jae Suk.
You should watch this on TV.
- It was fun.
- Let's just get this over with.
Jae Suk. Jae Suk is
having a lonely battle.
The 3, 7 guy.
Why am I feeling so lonely
on TV shows these days?
I feel lonely
in TV shows these days.
- Is Jong Ok going next?
- Jong Ok.
You should roll straight.
So Min and I will move over.
- Good luck.
- We'll get out of the way.
I can defend.
I should block Kwang Soo.
Ready, set...
(Jong Ok starts rolling forward.)
- My gosh.
- Good.
(Jong Ok can't avoid...)
Jong Ok, gosh.
(the sticky swamp.)
- Jong Ok, gosh.
- Jong Ok. You should...
Jong Ok.
Wait.
- Jong Ok.
Jong Ok!
That's good.
Jong Ok, you're good.
Jong Ok, it's good. Very good.
Move over.
(Team Jong Ok is
blocking the way now.)
Good. We should move over.
(The gate of Suk Jin is open.)
- Good.
- Stop her.
You're almost there.
(So Min blocks Kwang Soo
as he tries to interrupt.)
You're almost there. Good.
(She hit 7 pins.)
- Nice, Jong Ok.
- She's the ace player.
- That was nice.
- She's the ace.
That was amazing.
(Excited)
That was great.
It's unbelievable.
(Well done, Suk Jin.)
My gosh. I have a cramp
in my toes.
- Are you having a cramp?
- Yes.
- Take him off of it.
- Relax his muscles.
- What's wrong?
- I have a cramp on my toes.
- Are you having a cramp?
- Yes.
- Massage his toes.
- It's gone.
- Do it a little more.
- A little more?
Good.
- Is it good?
- Okay.
He seems to like this.
- Are you feeling better?
- It feels better.
You're here to work.
What are you doing now?
You are just getting a massage
lying down here.
It's not like you're on vacation.
Hey, it's not that I want
to be on vacation.
(Is he enjoying
the relaxing moment?)
That was good. Hey.
Jong Ok did a very good job.
- I hit seven pins.
- Okay, Jong Ok.
Nice.
- Who's next? Hae Sun?
- Yes.
Okay.
- You can go like that.
- Ready, set...
Go, Hae Sun!
- Start.
- Just go like that.
- To the left. Good.
- Keep rolling.
I bet Hae Sun never imagined...
she'd play this game.
Good. Keep rolling like that.
- A little to the right.
- Good.
- You should hurry.
- You don't have much time.
- You have only 30 seconds.
- To the right.
- You're almost there.
- You should listen to them.
Roll one more time.
(She just needs to overcome
the defensive wall.)
(So Min's defense makes her
lose her bearing.)
Keep rolling!
- Keep rolling!
- Just keep rolling.
- Go straight.
- One more time.
- Okay.
- She did it.
She did it. It's good.
- Seven pins.
- Okay.
- It's not bad.
- She did it.
Good. That was nice.
Haha, you should do this.
- Haha, good luck.
- Good luck.
If Haha fails to hit a pin,
- wouldn't it be over?
- Of course, he'll get some.
He'll get 10.
(She's watching.)
- Haha, you're our only hope.
- Okay.
Bring out the Ant-Man.
So Min is a good defensive player.
Kwang Soo, block her.
(Come at me!)
(She's like Bruce Lee.)
What was that?
What are you doing?
This is how I'll be defending...
- when Se Chan comes.
- What?
- Good luck, Haha.
- Good luck!
Jong Ok thinks of him as the ace.
- Let's go.
- Go.
- All right.
- Here he goes.
That's good.
- Good job.
- You're fast.
- You're good.
- Go to your right.
- You're fast.
- He's fast.
- Go to your right.
- No, no!
- No, no! Not that way!
(She's very into this.)
Go to your left.
This way.
Hey, hey.
Do it one more time!
(He needs to roll once more.)
Good job!
(He hits the jackpot.)
Hold on.
- How many were they?
- Nine.
- Did I do well?
- Okay.
You did.
(He's the best.)
Nine?
(Team Jong Ok: 16,
Team Hae Sun: 8)
He did that?
The score is 16 to 8.
No way!
- We're doing well.
- You need to defend well.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- Block them for me.
- I will.
- You can do it Se Chan.
- Got it.
It's easy.
Are you going to roll over me?
- Of course.
- Why?
Good luck.
- Ready, set...
- You need to block him.
(Se Chan sets out.)
Jae Suk, block him.
- Okay. Hey, hey.
- Throw the tray.
- That's good.
- Se Chan.
Grab him.
(He's out of reach.)
That's good.
- Go to the slippery part. No, no!
- That's it!
That's great.
(He rolls toward the sticky part.)
That's great! That's great!
You're doing well.
Get out of there.
- You need to block him.
- Get out.
- Good.
- You need to hold out.
- Good! Se Chan!
- No!
(He just needs to evade So Min.)
- You're almost there!
- Don't block me!
Grab him!
Go, go!
(He grabs Se Chan's pants.)
(He takes them off.)
That's not the way!
(He fights against them...)
(in his long johns.)
Go back!
(The game ends
with him in his long johns.)
Not there!
(The score stays the same.)
Where did you go?
Like so, Team Jong Ok wins.
(Team Jong Ok wins.)
(It's time for them
to pick their bags.)
As you can see,
there are 30 bags each...
in the good zone and the bad zone.
In the good zone, there are
19 plus values,
nine minus values,
1 switch chance,
and 1 double chance.
In the bad zone,
there are nine plus values,
19 minus values,
and one switch chance
and double chance each.
There's a total of 30.
(Team Jong Ok will each choose
from the good zone.)
We'll pick from the good zone.
(Team Hae Sun will pick
from the bad zone.)
The plus values range
from 1 dollar to 100 dollars.
It'd be awesome to get 100 dollars.
The minus values range
from 10 dollars to 200 dollars.
Who should go first?
- Should we go first?
- Sure.
You said they had
nine minus values, right?
- Yes.
Let's see... Okay.
(They have a 30-percent chance
of getting a minus value.)
I can't pick.
- Pick whatever.
- Okay.
(Most of them are good anyway.)
I pick number 17.
Okay.
No.
Number 17.
There are 9 minus values
and 19 good values.
All right!
(What?)
(It's minus 50 dollars.)
- Darn it!
- What is that?
Is that a minus value?
- It's a minus value.
That's great.
(He's placed
in the 9th, 10th ranks.)
I can't believe this.
- My gosh.
- The tables could be flipped.
Jong Ok.
I can't believe it.
(Which one will she pick?)
Okay.
- Jae Suk will pick one next.
- Right.
I'm not lucky
with these types of things.
It's Michael Jordan's number.
1, 2, 3.
(She picks
Michael Jordan's number.)
70 dollars.
(She gets 70 dollars.)
(She receives 70 dollars.)
(She reaps the benefit
of choosing from the good zone.)
(She's in 1st place.)
She got 70 dollars.
All right, Suk Jin.
- Hey.
- I pick three.
- Goodness.
- Why?
No, open it from the bottom.
Not there.
This black one.
He doesn't know how to open it.
(Look at him.)
(He's been a member for years now.)
You saw how to open it.
Be quiet.
- Be quiet.
- He doesn't know how to open it.
How could you not know?
(This time, he's determined
to open it.)
- What is it?
- It must be a minus value.
- Is it a chance card?
- Minus 20 dollars.
- No, it's 30 dollars.
- The probability is quite high.
What's wrong with me?
That really wasn't likely.
So Min.
I doubt they've aligned
two minuses together.
- Right. I picked that as well.
- I pick number one.
(Me too.)
- You did? Never mind.
- Yes.
- I wanted number 1.
- Then never mind.
- I pick number 30.
- Pick number 8.
I pick number 30.
(She picks number 30 instead.)
(What has she picked?)
- What is it?
(Minus 100 dollars)
(She picks minus 100 dollars.)
- Minus 100 dollars?
- Goodness.
- What was that?
- I was lucky!
Minus 100 dollars?
(Is that seriously the good zone?)
How is this possible?
- My goodness.
- What did you say?
We can beat them for sure.
What's wrong with us?
I'll pick the one from before.
- So Min, why did you discard this?
- Let me see.
It felt ominous
that you had picked it.
That's not it. Wait.
(Plus 20 dollars)
It's 20 dollars.
- It's not a lot.
- He's not extremely lucky.
I thought this was the good zone.
But three of us got minus values.
If we win next round...
- We'll get the good ones.
- We'll beat them for sure.
- Go on.
- Who's first? Kwang Soo?
Okay. I pick number 13.
(Kwang Soo goes 1st
and picks number 13.)
This is so annoying.
I'm sure Kwang Soo
got a minus value.
- Of course.
- 70 dollars!
What's gotten into him?
(It's the bad zone.)
(But he receives 70 dollars.)
70 dollars!
Seriously?
- 70 dollars.
- What's going on?
What's going on?
- Our situations have changed.
- This is strange.
Are you sure
you got the zones right?
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
They only have nine plus values.
- That's odd.
- It doesn't make any sense.
Are you sure you didn't make
a mistake?
Yes, we're sure.
- That one seems good.
- How is this possible?
This is meaningless.
We'll find out this time for sure.
(Everyone is focused
on Jong Kook's bag.)
- What?
- Darn it.
- Gosh.
- It's a minus value.
What is it?
- Gosh.
- It's a minus value.
(His eyes are wide open.)
How much is it?
(What is the amount?)
I think it's minus 200 dollars.
It is.
(The probability was 1 out of 30.)
- Minus 200 dollars.
- Minus 200 dollars!
- Minus 200 dollars?
- Nice.
- Yes!
- He got minus 200 dollars.
This one really caught my eye.
- 20 dollars.
- 30 dollars.
(Hae Sun and Ji Hyo got plus,
and Se Chan got minus.)
I didn't beat them?
(Final result for round 1)
(Jong Ok and Kwang Soo
are leading.)
(So Min, Se Chan, and Jong Kook
are the last ones.)
Sit here, Suk Jin.
(After their first game)
I'm in first place.
Jong Ok and Kwang Soo
are at the top.
I can't believe he's up there.
I doubt I'll come last today.
- Okay, okay.
- I should do better.
I should avoid the penalty.
For the second team mission,
your lunch menu is on the line.
It's called Calculated Auction.
- Calculated?
- Auction?
- It's calculated?
- After seeing the lunch menu,
both teams will auction.
There will be
a total of five rounds.
For this round, you won't use
your R money.
We will give you fake cash
just for this mission.
Each of you will receive
10 dollars each.
Each team will have 50 dollars.
You can bid as much
as you want for each dish.
The team with the higher amount
of money will get the dish.
(The food goes to the highest bid.)
If you think the other team
will spend 10 dollars,
you can agree to spend
more than that.
That's how you'll play.
If both teams pay the same amount,
the dish and your money
will both disappear.
The team that wins
3 dishes 1st wins.
The winning team will get...
- to eat them.
- Really?
Even if the losing team
has won 1 or 2 dishes,
they will only be given
laver and rice.
Laver and rice would be...
However, the member
with the most amount...
of remaining cash
in the losing team...
will have the chance
to eat the dishes...
and pick a bag from the good zone.
There's always a catch.
They're preventing us
from spending as much as we want.
They're playing smart.
You'll get to eat for sure
if you don't spend any money.
Kwang Soo.
I'm so glad that they have you.
(He's the epitome of betrayal.)
Not at all.
- If we all win, we'll get to eat.
- Right.
- Why are you stuttering?
- I'm sick and tired of hearing it.
- I'm serious.
- "Not at all."
- "If we all win, we'll get to eat."
- We need to work together.
Here's your first menu.
All right.
- Let's hear it.
- Your first dish...
is gim-tteok-sun set.
(They're the 3 most popular
snack foods.)
- Gimbap, tteokbokki, and sundae.
- Hey.
- I'm going to spend three dollars.
- This one's nice.
I'm going to splurge.
You can discuss
with your team members.
I think we should spend a little
first and see how they spend theirs.
We should at least spend
a dollar each and see.
- Should we do that?
- We need to feel them out.
(A dollar?)
Kwang Soo, wake up.
- Kwang Soo, no.
- It's a dollar.
(Kwang Soo, wake up. It's a dollar.)
You'll still have nine dollars left.
It's only fake money,
so why am I being stingy?
- Kwang Soo.
- Only a dollar.
I think we could eat it
with five dollars.
Let's have it.
Should we spend a dollar each?
- A dollar each?
- Yes.
We might win just with
a dollar each.
It's not something
worth investing in.
Even though we don't want it,
we should obtain it as insurance.
Jong Ok, pay up a dollar.
Shall we go ahead?
Write down your name and amount.
There's nothing to be upset about.
We'll only bid a small amount.
- How about this much?
- That much?
- Sure.
- Okay.
It's only the first one.
How much did you pay?
(Did they all pay a dollar
as they agreed to?)
(Kwang Soo's paper is clean.)
By the way...
Kwang Soo, write it down.
- I did.
- Let me see.
- Hold on.
- I will once you write down yours.
I'll do it once you do.
- You go first.
- Why did you lie to me then?
- Okay, go ahead.
- It's only the first round.
Right, okay.
- I wrote it down.
- It needs to be a whole number.
- I wrote down a dollar.
- Make it a whole number.
- But I did.
- Why would you write 0.6 dollars?
(Why would you write 0.6 dollars?)
Why would you write down
0.6 dollars?
- But I did.
- I saw 0.6 dollars.
(Glancing)
- Get over here.
- Make it a whole number.
He wrote down 0.6 dollars.
Must you be that dirty?
Beats me.
- We kept it anonymous.
- Us too.
They put down the same amount as us.
What we have left...
- Exactly.
- They don't get...
what we have left,
so it's important to win.
Yes, the objective
is to win the dish.
I wrote it down.
You shouldn't be showing me that.
You're the one who looked.
There's no need to.
But you looked.
- This isn't me doubting you.
- I think it's a tie.
Suk Jin saw what I wrote down.
- I did.
- He saw what I wrote down.
We should do this.
- Hold on.
- I'm so disappointed in Suk Jin.
(Jae Suk doesn't trust him.)
We don't believe him.
(Both teams agreed
to bid 5 dollars.)
The team that won
the gim-tteok-sun set is...
- Which team is it?
- Is there a winner?
- It should be ours.
I bet it's ours.
The team that won
the gim-tteok-sun set is...
Both teams...
(Both teams?)
You bid the same amount,
so no one gets the food.
- What?
- You bid the same amount...
(No one won the food.)
Really? Everyone
must've bid something.
You all bid the same amount?
(Did both teams bid 5 dollars?)
Both teams...
bid four dollars.
(Both teams bid 4 dollars.)
(But we agreed on 5 dollars.)
Which one of you betrayed us?
Who betrayed us?
I said five dollars was enough!
- I told you to write down a dollar.
- It was just a dollar.
- Unbelievable.
- Who was it?
- You saw me write it down.
- You!
- I saw you write it down.
- It was Suk Jin...
- who acted strangely.
- I saw Jong Ok write hers down.
- We can vouch for each other.
- That's right.
You could've sent in
a different piece of paper.
You turned around
and wrote something down.
You're unbelievable.
What did I tell you?
I said that five dollars was enough.
- He's right.
- Viewers know the truth, right?
You know I'm innocent.
- So Min...
- Jae Suk, come on.
- Right, I saw So Min's.
- That's right.
Everyone saw what I wrote down.
- It's him.
- You're all a bunch of jerks.
Except you, of course, Jong Ok.
(Laughing)
I can't believe this.
Both teams bid four dollars.
(What?)
(Why is she suddenly yelling?)
It was you, wasn't it?
Unbelievable.
I bet it was Hae Sun.
You wrote it down, right?
You saw it. I showed you.
But still...
Didn't you write it down?
I wrote the amount down in Korean.
- You saw mine.
- Hold on.
She wouldn't suspect you
if she wasn't the traitor.
- Her expression...
- I wrote it down.
- Unbelievable.
- This is how it'll be?
- Okay.
- Will this be revealed?
- Don't know.
- It will be, right?
I'm certain it was her.
Does this mean that
we lost the dollar we wrote down?
- Yes, it's gone.
- You've got to be kidding me.
(Yes, it's gone.)
Jong Kook, it's Kwang Soo.
You're actually checking
if we lost the money?
You checked if
your money was intact.
- That's not it.
- Save it.
You're the worst.
- I didn't betray you.
- Don't you dare eat anything.
Wait, come on. If I could...
You're not allowed to eat anything.
Don't you dare eat.
Let's move on to the next menu.
It's one whole pizza and coke.
- Coke.
- I really want that.
We must have this.
We can't pass up on this.
- All right.
- Was it Jae Suk then?
Jong Ok, how about seven dollars?
Why was it not five dollars then?
- Did you write it down?
- I did.
- Stop arguing.
- Really?
I did nothing to be ashamed of.
- Me too.
- Let's curse one another.
If I am lying about this,
my family will go broke.
(He's dead serious.)
- That's a strong one.
- Must you go that far?
I'm that serious.
- I'm serious.
- Why go that far?
Because I'm dead serious.
If I am lying about this,
my family will live as slaves
for generations.
(My family will live as slaves
for generations.)
- What?
- I'm dead serious.
Me too!
Let's not go that far.
Why not?
- Just don't.
- It was you, wasn't it?
- So Min, go ahead.
- Must we go this far?
- We've narrowed it down.
- Exactly.
- How about it?
- All right.
We have our suspects.
- Suk Jin, be honest.
- It's your last chance...
to apologize.
We'll forget about it then.
- Apologize.
- We won't hold it against you.
- Consider your future.
- Just apologize.
- Apologize.
- See?
(She turns herself in.)
(She wasn't able to lie.)
- Apologize.
- Just apologize.
(While everyone
was looking the other way,)
(she changed her number to 0.)
(If anyone asks about
the future of con artists,)
(tell them about So Min.)
- I'm sorry.
- We'll forgive you but...
- From here on out...
- Let's try this.
(He shows mercy.)
- From here on out...
- Let's try this.
Wait, hear me out.
- Gather around.
- Don't upset me again.
Did you have to take it that far?
This time, I'll write this.
- You?
- We should eat this dish.
Me too?
- Jong Kook, me too.
- I'll pay this much.
- Me too.
It's like this. Here.
But then in the next round...
Can't you see
we're discussing something?
- Hey.
- Stop butting in.
Mister, look here.
- Get away from us.
- But I paid!
Stay put.
(Yelling in desperation)
(Is he truly being
wrongfully accused?)
(A second before he turned his in,)
(he changed his number.)
(0 dollars)
(Don't worry. The hand
is quicker than the eye.)
- Kwang Soo betrayed us.
- I knew it!
What a weasel you are!
He's incorrigible.
(Kwang Soo's team members
already assume it's him.)
We're not going to consider
you a team member,
so go over there.
We're not going to consider
you a team member,
so go over there.
Go. Leave.
- What?
- Get lost.
You can't do this to me.
All right,
let's decide on an amount.
(His history of betrayal
is what caused this.)
Let me say this one thing.
She'll pay three dollars,
- and we'll pay a dollar.
- Okay.
(Jong Ok's plan)
- I'll pay two dollars.
- Okay.
- Gosh, you're the best.
- Jong Ok...
- It's all right.
- Hold on.
If that's the case,
I'll only pay two dollars.
- What?
- Why you...
Seriously?
You're the reason why
we lost the first round!
If you don't pay up this time,
Jong Ok will slap you.
I'll slap you hard.
(If you betray us again...)
(She taught So Min a lesson
with her strong pronunciation.)
- "I'll slap you hard."
- She'll slap you hard.
- As if she's acting.
- I'm good at slapping people.
- She means it.
- I never hesitate.
- She's serious.
I already feel like
I've been slapped.
- It hurts.
- If you don't pay up this time...
- She'll slap me hard.
- Exactly.
- Where though?
- If we win this dish,
Kwang Soo can pay
the entire amount in the next round.
- It's a team game.
- But if we win...
Yes, he could do that.
- He can.
- So this time...
There could be an opportunity.
- Right.
- So stay put.
Kwang Soo...
Stay put? Must you talk to me
like I'm your pet dog?
- Sorry.
- That's what you say to dogs.
So stay put.
(She gave him the order
people give to dogs.)
Gosh, I'm sorry.
We'll be fools
not to use him though.
Yes, you're right.
That makes you Chil Deuk.
- Then...
- You're Chil Deuk.
- Right.
- Then...
Will you be Chil Deuk?
- What do I write down?
- Just answer the question.
- Chil Deuk?
- Will you be Chil Deuk?
I've been Chil Deuk
for a long time now.
- Even I think we look alike.
- Right?
She'll slap you hard.
(The estimated price of both teams:
unknown versus 8 dollars)
- So in this round...
- No way.
The team that'll win
the pizza and coke set is...
(Which team will win
the one whole pizza and coke?)
Congratulations.
(Team Hae Sun wins!)
- Team Hae Sun.
- Nice!
Nice. How much was it?
- How much?
- What was the price?
- How much was it?
- Let me reveal the price.
It was 12 dollars to 8 dollars.
- What did I say?
- No way.
Weren't I on point?
- You were right.
- I knew they wouldn't pay up.
They...
This is what we'll pay.
(They agreed on 3 dollars each.)
(Except for Kwang Soo,
they paid 3 dollars each.)
(They will utilize what Kwang Soo
has in the next round.)
(I have nothing to lose then.)
(They put their trust in one another
and bet 3 dollars.)
(Kwang Soo bet 0 dollars
just like they planned.)
- Nice!
- That was so clever.
- See?
- Amazing.
- We would've lost anyway.
- I told you...
that they would bet 12 dollars.
I paid up this time.
I really did.
The next is jjajangmyeon
and jjamppong.
This we must eat.
- All right.
- The set will go to...
- Team Hae Sun.
- Okay!
Team Jong Ok has 31 dollars left...
while Team Hae Sun has 26 dollars.
(Team Jong Ok, 0 wins,
Team Hae Sun, 2 wins)
The next set...
is cake and iced coffee.
Desserts.
Kwang Soo, you're up.
Meet our expectations.
- You can do it.
- Even if we lose,
you can save face with what you bet.
- I won't call you Chil Deuk.
- Me neither.
Don't call me Chil Deuk...
and Hae Sun will stop nodding at me.
- We won't.
- I promise not to.
- I promise.
- If you...
don't win these desserts
for us though,
we'll all call you Chil Deuk...
until the show is over.
We need to win
the two rounds now.
That's right.
We're at a disadvantage though.
- I know.
- This time,
they'll bet a large amount.
Yes, but not as much as us.
We're going all-in this time.
How about this, Jong Kook?
Let's not bid a single dollar...
and bet our chances
on the final round.
Or...
- That sounds like a good plan.
- If you think about it...
So then...
They could skip this round
and let us win this time.
It'd be stupid for us
to bid a lot in this round.
We need to read their minds.
They might not choose this round.
They might skip this round.
We have to choose
either this round...
or the final round.
(They have to choose either
this round or the final round.)
Let's go.
What are we going to do?
Let's decide after they make a bid.
Let's see what they do.
(What will the two teams do?)
Let's start.
- Okay.
Let's win this.
It's our last chance.
This might be our last chance.
(All-in or 0 dollars)
(What did Team Hae Sun
decide to do?)
(All of the members bid 0 dollars.)
Why are we taking the risk...
of waiting until the final round
though?
It might be a good idea
to bid nothing in this round.
The ones who have been bidding
in every round...
Even if they don't bid
in this round,
- They can't win anyway.
- they know they can't win anyway,
so they'll definitely make a bid.
(If the other team bids a large
amount, they'll automatically win.)
Chil Deuk.
This might be our last chance.
Why...
- Chil Deuk.
- There's no point in saving money.
- We can't keep it anyway.
Chil Deuk.
(Will Team Hae Sun's
0-dollar strategy pay off?)
Kwang Soo, it all depends on you.
(Fall for it.)
Please, Kwang Soo.
Se Chan doesn't sound confident.
(Fall for it.)
- Why would he say "please"?
- He said "please."
He doesn't sound confident.
(Please fall for it.)
- Give us a second.
- Come here.
Why did he say "please"?
- This is not fair.
- Just a second.
- This might be our last round.
- There are two possibilities.
- I think they fell for it.
- I think so.
They fell for your reaction.
If they made a bid
without any tricks...
It seems they did, right?
It seems like
they didn't come up with any tricks.
They either found us out...
or fell for us.
That's why they're changing
their strategy.
Let's make a choice.
We either bid 27 dollars...
- or...
- About four dollars?
- Four dollars each?
- What if we lose?
- Then we'll definitely lose.
- No, in total.
I mean...
Then we'll be left with 26 dollars.
That's not what I meant.
We have to gamble now.
- They want us to bid a lot.
- Right.
(They can't come to an agreement.)
- I'm starving.
- They're so serious.
This is driving me crazy.
Make a bid one by one.
Make sure no one can see.
(Team Jong Ok makes a decision
after a long discussion.)
(What did Team Jong Ok
decide to do?)
This is giving me a headache.
(Are they bidding
27 dollars or 4 dollars?)
(Actor Lee Kwang Soo,
specialty: conveying emotions)
- All right.
- We have to gamble.
- The cake and coffee go to...
- Us, definitely.
Let's go!
- Go to...
- Let's go!
Congratulations, Team Jong Ok.
(Team Jong Ok wins.)
- How much did they bid?
- What happened?
Let me tell you the amount
each team bid.
For the cake...
(The amount is important.)
The two teams bid
25 dollars and 0 dollars.
- I told you.
- They bid 0 dollars.
- 25 dollars and 0 dollars.
- Okay!
- Yes!
- We made a good call.
You didn't expect this, did you?
- I'm so happy.
- We can't play the next round...
because Team Jong Ok
doesn't have enough money.
As a result, Team Hae Sun wins.
(Team Hae Sun automatically wins.)
They had to gamble.
So this is why it's so fun.
We fell for "please".
- Let's bid a lot in this round.
- Let's do that.
Whether it works or not...
(We'll give it a try anyway.)
Let's bid 27 dollars.
- I'll bid all I have.
- Me too.
(They completely fell
for the other team.)
- "Please" is what made us fall.
- Who said it?
We fell for "please."
Anyway,
the pizza and coke set,
jjajangmyeon, and jjamppong...
go to Team Hae Sun.
(The final winner is Team Hae Sun.)
Meanwhile, one of us
bid two dollars less.
One member of the losing team
gets to eat with Team Jong Ok...
and pick a bag from the good zone.
- Who is it?
- I bid it's So Min.
- No, I bid all I had.
(Who betrayed his or her teammates
and saved money?)
Congratulations, Haha.
He has four dollars left.
(Haha, with four dollars left,
is saved.)
See? It's not me.
(He is the one
who bid 2 dollars less.)
- See? It's not me.
- I knew it.
Hi, Chil Deuk.
(This man sitting on
Chil Deuk's lap...)
(had promised to bid 5 dollars...)
(but in the end bid only 3 dollars.)
(By saving his money,
he gets to sit on Chil Deuk's lap.)
It was our last round.
Suk Jin and Jong Ok
have a dollar left each.
Jae Suk and So Min
have no money left.
- I have nothing left.
- That's so cool.
Before we eat,
let's pick bags first.
(The second bag-picking)
(Team Hae Sun and Haha
pick from the good zone.)
This is the problem.
Our team won, right?
There are chances.
So you really didn't bid.
(He is just like
what he looks like on TV.)
That's not true.
In the last round...
He has 10 dollars left.
I didn't know you'd do that.
- Call him Chil Deuk once.
- I saved it for the last round.
Chil Deuk.
(Gosh, Chil Deuk.)
(Kwang Soo's official nickname
is now Chil Deuk.)
I'm sorry.
Jong Ok said to So Min,
"I'll slap you hard."
That made So Min come to her senses.
That's why I bid all I had.
For So Min to do that,
she must have been really scared.
(Even So Min bid all she had.)
So Min bid all she had.
- Team Hae Sun, please pick bags.
- This is not good.
Most of them are good ones.
Really?
- Bad ones...
- There aren't many bad ones.
There are some bad ones left,
but not many.
There are only six bad ones left.
I wish they'd pick all the bad ones.
(Hae Sun picks bag number 16.)
Okay.
I hope it's a really bad one.
- Minus 100 dollars.
- Minus 200 dollars.
(Hae Sun is currently in 3rd place
with 70 dollars.)
- How much is it?
- Plus 50 dollars.
That's not bad.
(Plus 50 dollars)
Hae Sun is now in first place.
She has 120 dollars.
(The other members pick
plus values too.)
- Gosh.
- Plus 10 dollars.
- At least...
- It was close though.
I'm not at the bottom at least.
(It's Jong Kook's turn,
who is way behind the others.)
Wait, I have minus 150 dollars.
How much do I have to get?
Jong Kook is most likely
to end up being at the bottom.
Probably.
Don't forget there are
a switch chance and a double chance.
There are?
If Jong Kook picks a double chance,
will Jong Kook be left with
minus 300 dollars?
- What?
- Minus...
I can't wait.
This number two left alone here
is bothering me.
You should pick
one of those lonely ones.
We, the unlucky ones, are like that.
- We don't want them to be lonely.
- Right?
You guys are too nice.
They're too nice?
I would have picked that one too.
- Really? Okay.
- Yes.
I trust you then.
(Jong Kook, who is at the bottom,
recklessly trusts Jae Suk.)
(What will be the result?)
(What?)
(Only a dollar?)
(Jong Kook,
who has minus 150 dollars,)
(miraculously wins a dollar.)
You have minus 149 dollars now.
Unlucky ones don't want anything
to be lonely.
I somehow feel so relieved now.
Right?
I feel so relieved.
(With an additional dollar,
he starts chasing the others.)
I hope Kwang Soo gets
minus 200 dollars.
I pick bag number 12.
- Bag number 12.
- No, bag number 5.
No, I'll choose bag number 12.
Bag number 12.
It's been bothering me
the whole time.
- I want him to get a minus value.
- A big minus.
- Here we go.
- Red letters, please.
Let's go!
(There are only 6 minus values left
out of 21.)
(What's the result?)
(Minus 70 dollars)
- He's wearing a red cap too.
- Let's go!
(She's laughing for real.)
Jong Ok looks genuinely happy.
(Our Kwang Soo is back.)
Chil Deuk picked minus 70 dollars
because "Chil" means 7.
He sure is Chil Deuk.
- Chil Deuk.
- It was for my team.
Chil Deuk picked minus 70 dollars.
(The other team picks
from the bad zone.)
Minus 50 dollars.
- That's not bad.
- Minus 30 dollars.
That's not too bad.
I was going to pick this one,
but the other team
recommended this one.
It's a double chance.
- You have 60 dollars now.
- I have 60 dollars now.
(He has 30 dollars times 2 now.)
The letters are blue.
In this situation?
In this situation...
(Jong Ok picks plus 30 dollars.)
Hae Sun is in 1st place, and Jong Ok
is in 2nd, only 10 dollars apart.
(Current Amount)
Thank you for the food.
- Is the pizza warm?
- Yes.
(They enjoy pizza
after the exciting mind game.)
Who's that guy wearing
his jacket inside out?
(Perfectly camouflaged)
I can't believe Haha.
- I know.
- He's sitting with the other team.
It feels like I'm eating sand.
I feel so uncomfortable.
By the way, his jjajangmyeon...
- doesn't look good.
- I know.
(His jjajangmyeon tastes like sand.)
Jong Ok, you say such mean words.
The noodles look all soggy.
She's glaring at us the whole time.
Why do you keep looking
at the other team?
I just took a look.
Our food is so simple.
I'd share the food with you,
but it's against the rules.
I'd give all of it to her.
You're lying.
The noodles actually are soggy.
- I told you. I can see it.
- Right.
(Kwang Soo takes a sip of coke.)
(Spitting)
- What's wrong?
- What's going on?
(What happened?)
Did you drink coke
with ice cream in your mouth?
Hey.
(The combination of
carbon dioxide and ice cream)
- What's with him?
- What happened?
If you drink coke
with ice cream in your mouth...
He's so stupid.
He deserves to be called Chil Deuk.
He really is Chil Deuk.
They even handled it
on "Curious Paradise."
Why did he drink the coke?
(Children and immature adults,
don't try this at home.)
The final mission will be
an individual game,
Mafia War: The Innocent Ones.
A team of five will play
the Mafia Game.
After all the members draw
a cue card,
one member will be chosen
as the mafia at random.
The mafia's cue card has...
a mission word he or she must say.
- This is hard.
- I am good at a game like this.
- Really?
- He is getting revved up.
- He is the king of ad-libs.
- He is good.
Weren't you channeling
a dead frog earlier?
I am good at a game like this.
Don't call him a frog.
That's my nickname.
For 20 minutes,
talk among yourselves.
What do we need to talk about?
You can share a funny story
or an aspiration.
You just need to talk...
- comfortably.
- Can we talk about a dream?
Yes, you can.
You just need to talk comfortably.
However, the mafia must use...
his or her mission word.
The failure to use the mission word
will result in the mafia's loss.
After the talk,
you will discuss among yourselves
and decide who the mafia is.
If you succeed to catch the mafia,
the citizens win.
Otherwise, the mafia wins.
Please don't pretend to be
the mafia.
Can I pretend to be the mafia?
Please don't do that.
But I seek attention.
(He is honest.)
(He loves screen time
and attention.)
- He loves screen time.
- In summary,
we need to prove our innocence.
- My goodness.
- Right?
If the mafia says
the mission word...
in response
to someone else's words,
- does it count?
- Yes.
You will play the game
as a team of five.
- A team of 5.
- There are 5 of us.
- Will the five of us play the game?
- Yes.
We will play the Mafia Game
by ourselves.
You should go first.
Why? Why should we go first?
- Can't you do it?
- What?
Can't you listen to an older member?
- No.
- No?
- Jong Kook.
- That's just unfair.
- I will teach you a lesson one day.
- Jong Kook.
I have watched their interactions
for the past few weeks.
Nothing ever goes Suk Jin's way.
- Nothing.
- Listen.
- In 2020,
- Okay.
I will teach you a lesson.
Please teach me a lesson.
I don't like to second-guess.
The mafia will be chosen at random.
The mafia's cue card will have
a mission word.
Don't show your cue card
to the others.
The citizens can talk comfortably.
The mafia must incorporate
his or her mission word...
into the reaction
or the overall conversation.
If the word is too outrageous...
That's right.
Then it will be obvious.
Let's start the conversation.
Where do we begin?
Se Chan, you can share
your first impression of Hae Sun.
I made a mistake earlier.
- I didn't know your age.
- That's right.
I thought you were older than me.
I am so sorry.
- I thought you were older than me.
- It's okay.
She doesn't look older than you.
I got confused...
because she was much taller
than I expected.
- She is tall.
- Hae Sun is tall.
- She is 174cm tall.
- That's right.
Height has nothing to do with age.
- Since I was looking up at her,
- Are you an elementary schooler?
she seemed older.
Does that make Jang Do Yeon
as old as your mother?
(What kind of logic is that?)
(Godmother Jang Do Yeon)
You should call Kwang Soo "Grandpa."
That's ridiculous.
You should treat me
as an older member.
Kwang Soo has an old man's butt.
Hey!
(Kwang Soo has an old man's butt.)
- It's true.
- What are you talking about?
- I don't have an old man's butt.
Didn't you watch
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks"?
Make sure you do.
- He is like Dooly's grandpa.
- His butt makes an appearance.
- Dooly's grandpa!
- "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks"?
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
"Butt" can't be the mission word,
right?
- "Butt."
- It could be "Butt."
No, no.
That came up pretty naturally.
If you have a story,
you should share it with us.
I want to talk about
the dream I had the other day.
- That's good.
- That's suspicious. Okay.
- I really had this dream.
- A dream is the perfect starter...
for any word because
they're outrageous.
- They are imaginary.
- That's right.
In the dream, Se Chan and I went...
to Lee Da Hee's house.
This is quite sudden.
- Da Hee.
- Keep going.
- Okay. Da Hee.
In the parking lot...
we were washing the car.
- "Washing the car"?
"Washing the car" is suspicious.
I am serious.
- We were washing the car.
- "Washing the car"?
- "Washing the car" is suspicious.
- You know what a BB gun is, right?
Someone stayed hidden
in the forest...
and shot at the two of us.
- At us?
- Yes.
Let's keep listening.
Let's see how the story ends.
Se Chan ran away first.
I was packing up...
when the shooter approached me...
and pushed my cap down.
"Cap."
Then the shooter tapped on my head.
When I woke up,
I felt the tap on my back.
- You felt it when you woke up.
- Yes.
(When he woke up,
he felt the tap on his back.)
- This happened for real.
- My goodness.
I was so startled
that I started sweating profusely.
And when I looked back,
no one was there.
What?
- His story...
- It's suspicious.
- It can't be a story he prepared.
- "BB gun" must be the word.
- "BB gun."
- I really had that dream.
- Hey.
- I told you about the dream.
- He did,
but he didn't talk about
the parking lot.
Kwang Soo told me about the dream,
but...
- I told you the story the same.
- No.
There were a few words
he didn't mention before.
He said BB gun before,
but Se Chan, Da Hee,
and washing the car didn't.
Those three words were missing.
Here is what I think.
He intentionally retold the story
you have heard.
- The parking lot.
- This is driving me crazy.
I am a citizen.
"Washing the car" must be
his mission word.
He only mentioned
the underground parking lot before.
I told the story before.
I told the story
to Se Chan and So Min before.
Ji Hyo is awfully quiet.
I was thinking about a dream I had.
Tell us about it.
I was having
a shoot for Running Man.
In the dream, we had the Speed Quiz.
"Talk about four-character idioms.
Talk about mathematical functions."
- Mathematical functions!
- I was so lost.
- This happened in a dream, right?
- So...
I suffered so much
due to four-character idioms...
that I downloaded an app.
- You downloaded an app.
- That's right.
- This happened in a dream, right?
- I see.
The wallpaper
of Ji Hyo's phone is...
- January, February...
- Yes.
It has all the months in English.
So I began to study
four-character idioms.
Why don't you give us one?
Well...
Gyeolchoboeun.
(She confidently says
a four-character idiom.)
What does "Gyeolchoboeun" mean?
(What does "Gyeolchoboeun" mean?)
- I can't believe her.
- My goodness.
- You should know the meaning.
- She dug her own grave.
When you memorize
four-character idioms,
- you should know the meaning.
- You should know...
- what the characters mean.
- There are easier ones.
Ji Hyo, exactly how do you study?
You should know the meaning.
Nothing was suspicious
about Ji Hyo's story.
I think "Four-character idiom"
is suspicious.
- "Four-character idiom."
- Suddenly...
- Hold on.
- Her story was flawless.
- It's suspicious.
- You know,
I don't think the real mafia made
an attempt yet.
- I agree.
- I think Jong Kook is the mafia.
- Jong Kook hasn't said anything.
- He never makes the first move.
- Jong Kook...
- I will share...
something ridiculous
that happened in my life.
One time, I went to a swimming pool
with Haha and Kwang Soo.
- "A swimming pool."
- We went to a swimming pool.
That day,
we were talking about
how we should meet someone...
- and get married.
- He is telling that story again.
Suddenly, Haha said,
"Why don't we have lunch together?"
- "It's my father's 80th birthday."
- 70th birthday.
"It's my father's 80th birthday."
I said, "Okay, let's go."
I went with him.
At a round table,
I didn't see his father,
but Byul and Jae Suk.
I thought,
"What is Byul doing here?"
I was going through the same thing.
I sat down. Then, Haha...
who shared my worries about
marriage and such a moment ago...
suddenly said,
"Jong Kook, I am getting married."
(Haha said that to Jong Kook.)
- What a shocking statement!
- You must have been flustered.
He suddenly said...
- that he will marry...
- Jong Kook is ridiculous.
Byul, who I don't know.
- You know,
- Isn't it ridiculous?
that happened eight years ago.
Are you still holding grudges?
- Seriously.
- I was so flustered.
- Do you know what he said to me?
- Listen.
"When I get married,"
"you will find out through the news
on a search engine."
I will make sure he finds out
through the news.
Jong Kook is dead serious.
- You know,
- Isn't it ridiculous?
- it was ridiculous.
- It was indeed.
We found out at
his father's 70th birthday party.
You saw something that was
even more ridiculous...
than how I broke the news.
My father didn't attend
his 70th birthday party.
(His father didn't attend
his 70th birthday party.)
- That's true.
- Seriously.
- He didn't come.
It was one ridiculous thing
after another.
"Father, where are you?"
"The traffic is heavy."
"What?"
"I won't go. The traffic is heavy."
"I won't go."
- He really didn't show up?
- No.
He is a free-spirited man.
Then did his 70th birthday party
get canceled?
We photoshopped him
on an empty chair later.
We had it by ourselves.
What's more ridiculous is that
Jae Suk picked up the bill.
What?
- You paid the bill?
- Yes.
- Why?
- Jae Suk picked up the bill.
Why did you do that?
It's because I announced my wedding
without doing my father's party.
That makes sense.
Se Chan, you should talk too.
I will talk about the time...
- I got flustered.
- Go ahead.
I recently got a medical checkup.
You said you will get it with me.
I can't believe it.
I haven't gotten it yet!
(You said you will get it with me.
I can't believe it.)
(Se Chan's betrayal annoys
Jong Kook.)
- Se Chan betrayed him.
- You said you will get it with me.
- I haven't gotten it yet!
- It actually happened in the past.
- For goodness' sake.
Why would you get
a medical checkup together?
I thought we were friends.
- Listen.
- Kwang Soo got it with me.
- I am talking about...
- That's right.
last year.
I will get it with you this year.
- Really? Okay.
- Yes.
- I'm talking about last year.
- I was almost shocked.
This flustered me.
Colonoscopy is...
kind of embarrassing, right?
It is embarrassing.
I was kind of...
embarrassed about it,
so I covered up my face.
When I got there, I took off my mask
and they drew my blood.
They called my name.
- "Yang Se Chan".
- Yes, that was fine.
First thing you do is...
- lie down,
- Right.
and they ask you your name.
Then they put you to sleep,
- uncover you, and proceed.
- Yes.
What I was flustered about was...
after I lied down and said my name,
they uncovered me.
"What?
I think this is the wrong order."
("What?
I think this is the wrong order.")
"The order is..."
That was very flustering for me.
- I could imagine.
- That order got messed up.
- That's flustering.
- He told me this before.
This is true.
- I was flustered.
- I could imagine.
- This is a fact.
- Too bad though.
If they uncovered you before asking
your name, it would be funnier.
They uncover you first
and then ask your name.
This then, "What's your name?"
I know.
("What's your name?")
(You would hear the echo
in the crease of his butt.)
Don't do that.
- What was that about?
- Haha, I was very flustered.
What was that?
I was very flustered.
There were no odd words
in his story.
- Look.
- But Hae Sun...
wasn't listening to him
while he was talking.
- She was deep in thought.
- No.
- She was thinking of her story.
No, that's not why.
Can I say this?
When I was talking
to the writer earlier,
- I said something about masks.
- Okay.
He, on the other hand,
went to the hospital,
but he didn't have to
mention the masks.
When he said that,
I got distracted by it.
Masks.
(In the beginning of his story,)
(he said he took off his mask.)
(Why masks all of a sudden?)
You're all framing me.
It's your turn, Hae Sun.
(It's Hae Sun's turn to talk.)
I don't really have fun stories...
- like that in my life.
- Me too.
There was an incident
that confused me though.
I was on the elevator,
and I was wearing a mask.
- She keeps on talking about masks.
- I know.
I was wearing a mask,
and I had my cap on.
I got on the elevator,
and this lady got on as well.
She recognized me...
and said, "You look much prettier
in real life," before she got off.
- When you covered yourself up?
- Exactly.
So I was confused.
- When you covered yourself up?
- How did she know?
She said I look better in person.
- Is that your story?
- That's it.
(The end)
(That ended in vain.)
What is her score?
She has to try again.
(He's stern.)
(Her part will get edited out.)
- She has to try again.
- It's Hae Sun's turn.
I could see that happening.
That happens.
Everybody told their stories
including Hae Sun,
and I can't tell at all.
- I have no clue.
- I have no idea.
I'm most suspicious about Kwang Soo.
- He's most suspicious.
- It's him.
How many mafias are there?
- One.
- See?
- That was strange.
- I swear it's not me.
- That was strange. You caught that.
- You caught that.
- I swear.
Time over.
- I have no idea.
- I think the mafia won.
The mafia accomplished
their mission.
Who was it?
Five of you, please write down
who the mafia is.
Do they not vote?
They don't.
It's just the five of you.
Will you hear my final statement?
Is it over once we vote?
See? Kwang Soo keeps on talking.
- I personally think it's Hae Sun.
- I'm not sure where's he's going.
- Who?
- I personally think it's Hae Sun.
- She kept saying "mask."
- She did.
- It's the mask.
- Right?
- I think.
- He's right.
No, I swear it's not me.
- It's the mask because...
- Earlier,
- we played the game together.
- before she started her story,
she pointed out his mask.
That's true.
- It's Hae Sun.
- True.
No...
If she mentioned it only once,
- we wouldn't have noticed.
- It wasn't weird at all.
She got caught because of her story.
- She mentioned it first.
- You got caught.
I think it's Kwang Soo.
- What if...
- You're too...
Kwang Soo planned this out?
I heard about this dream yesterday.
- No, I don't think...
- No.
it's Kwang Soo.
You have 10 seconds.
Please write a name down.
- Jong Kook, I swear it's not me.
- Nine,
- eight,
- Write a name down.
seven,
6, 5, 4,
- I told you this story.
- 3, 2, 1. Hand in your vote.
- I have no idea.
- I'm going to follow my instinct.
What if it's Jong Kook?
There was nothing odd about
his story though.
There was nothing. I had nothing.
I had nothing too.
Wasn't my story clean?
I guess it wasn't a unique word.
- I guess not.
- Here's the result.
3 votes for Hae Sun,
1 for Kwang Soo, and 1 for Se Chan.
Who voted for me?
The votes are anonymous,
so I'm not sure.
- Hae Sun wrote your name.
- I did.
She wrote your name.
- It was me.
- So...
- the mafia...
- We caught her.
was not arrested.
See?
(The mafia was not arrested.)
(Hae Sun was not the mafia.)
- Who was it?
- Oh, gosh.
- The mafia...
- I didn't think it was her.
- It's Jong Kook.
- It wasn't me.
I guess it's him.
It wasn't Hae Sun?
The mafia was...
(From the four of them,
the mafia was...)
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo.)
(Ji Hyo was the mafia!)
- What was that?
- Oh, my goodness.
(Everybody is shocked.)
Her word was "Gyeolchoboeun."
(Mafia Ji Hyo's mission word was
"Gyeolchoboeun.")
- What?
- Really?
You asked her to say
a four-character idiom.
Why did you ask her to say it?
She's not even on your team.
(She had to say, "Gyeolchoboeun.")
(How do I say it?)
(At that moment)
(That was easy.)
(She kept a poker face...)
(and said, "Gyeolchoboeun".)
(Jae Suk saved her.)
(He deeply criticizes Jae Suk.)
(He gets criticized more.)
- I kept on thinking about it.
- Weren't you so happy?
- He told you to say it.
- I totally took it.
"Gyeolchoboeun"!
Why do you think she said it
when she didn't know its meaning?
- You talk too much.
- I did it.
Why did you ask her?
He always wants to lead.
- I'm sorry.
- My gosh.
He's the type...
- who turns the table upside down.
- Exactly.
He turned
everybody's table upside down.
He's the problem.
That was a difficult word.
That was difficult.
She couldn't have done it
without Jae Suk.
Only Ji Hyo will choose from
the good zone on this team.
Everybody else will choose
from the bad zone.
- She did really well.
- That was so hard.
Four of them were fine.
I'm amazed by Ji Hyo's ability.
We know she's studying hard
these days.
I know. It's true.
Once she gets married,
she'll trick her husband too.
- I will?
- What are you talking about?
- You completely got me.
- Why would you say that?
Why would she trick her husband?
(Laughing)
If this is going to go like this,
- We have the disadvantage.
- our team's in trouble.
- It can't be me.
- Let's pick.
- Please check your cards alone.
- This is a challenge.
(It's Team Jong Ok turn.)
This is so...
You're supposed to not say anything.
- Suk Jin looks anxious.
- Suk Jin.
(He sees that Suk Jin is tense.)
- I already caught you.
- Why?
Suk Jin, look at your legs.
- Hey.
- It's so obvious.
- Don't...
- I caught him.
- Listen.
- I caught you.
Don't get swayed by this.
Fine. You can pick me.
- He's really tense.
- He kept on looking at his card.
- That's true.
- Really?
He saw it,
- and this was his face.
- He kept on doing this.
He squinted...
and had this peculiar smile.
Who would like to talk first?
So Min.
This is not a funny story.
I went home a couple of days ago...
for the Korean New Year.
My dad and mom drove in one car,
while my brother and I were
in another car.
We parked and got off.
I helped my dad park too.
All of a sudden, my dad sighed...
- after looking at my brother's car.
- My mom's like,
"Wook Min! That punk,"
and she ran to him.
He hit another car
while he was parking.
- It was a collision.
- My dad got mad at him...
and opened his car door,
but there was a middle-aged man
sitting inside.
It was somebody else.
- It wasn't your brother?
- It wasn't his car.
(It wasn't her brother's car.)
He got mad at a stranger?
My dad apologized.
Oddly, it was the same car
and color.
Good thing it wasn't him.
That person was probably upset
already, and he opened the door.
It can't be "middle-aged man."
It's not. It can't be that easy.
- Nothing really stood out.
- Right?
It was "Gyeolchoboeun" earlier,
- so it has to be an unusual word.
- True.
They assign words...
- that sound awkward.
- I agree.
- That wasn't odd at all.
- Not at all.
- I used simple words.
- Car type and color.
This happened earlier today.
It wasn't surprising or anything.
When we had to wear tights...
and roll ourselves
to the bowling pins,
Suk Jin said this
in the waiting room.
"Do I have to wear this
at my age..."
"and play this game?
This has to change."
"Variety shows have to change.
They think this is funny,"
"but they should
seriously reconsider."
"I feel sorry for the guests."
As soon as we start filming...
(As soon as they started filming...)
Good story.
- Good story.
- Did you see him roll?
(He's going to cross the ocean
doing a somersault.)
That was fun though.
The tights weren't bad.
Why did you say that then?
Because tights are old style.
- I see.
- That's why I said it.
I see.
- Should I go?
- Sure, go ahead.
- I said this on a different show.
- Go ahead.
I was really flustered by this.
You sound weird already.
- Go ahead.
- Spy.
- Go, mafia.
- Go ahead.
- Let's hear it.
- Hey, don't do this.
Don't do this. Don't trust him.
Don't trust him.
Fine, go ahead.
- Listen carefully.
- Okay.
- My friend...
- Your friend.
said this to me
because I'm playing golf again.
- You're playing golf.
- He has a driver...
A driver?
- It's a driver.
- Fine.
- I said this on "Men on a Mission."
- Sure.
He has a driver
that can hit over 300m,
but it's really expensive.
It's around 2,000 dollars.
- 2,000 dollars?
- Yes, 2,000 dollars.
That's three.
How's this 2,000 dollars?
Right?
- Hey!
- He had three fingers.
- How's this 2,000 dollars?
He pretended to be relaxed.
- He held up three fingers.
- Do I seem like the mafia?
He simply made an observation.
We still have time.
It must be his mission word.
It makes no sense.
It's not like it's a goblin's club.
- 300m? Come on.
- "Goblin's club"?
Did he mention "Goblin's club"
on "Men on a Mission"?
- I don't think he did.
- He didn't, right?
"Goblin's club."
That word is totally suspicious.
- It's not a golf word.
- Seriously.
- It's not a word you usually use.
- In any case,
he said it costs
about 2,000 dollars.
I went home
and told my wife about it.
She searched on the internet...
and found one
that costs 400 dollars.
A goblin's club
that costs 400 dollars?
A driver!
(Frustrated)
I ordered it.
When I received the parcel,
I saw that it was this big.
- Was it a screwdriver?
- No, it wasn't a screwdriver.
- I only got the head.
- The head.
I know this story.
He told the exact same story.
I even texted him
after watching "Men on a Mission"...
because it was so funny.
- "Goblin's club."
- That was a new addition.
That's right.
(Suk Jin's story was
a bit suspicious.)
If you turn out to be a citizen,
that means you are a weirdo.
I am a citizen!
- Maybe he did it for attention.
- I have never heard him...
use a word like "Goblin's club."
You guys keep making me
look suspicious.
Stop giving us a strange reaction
if you are a citizen.
You should be upset.
"Goblin's club" is...
Keep in mind that the last time
we focused on one word,
- the actual mafia get away.
- That's right.
I think we are right
about "Goblin's club."
- All right. Who is next?
- Haha.
A few weeks ago,
Se Chan, Jong Kook,
and I had a shoot.
The topic of So Min came up
for some reason...
and we talked about her.
That night,
Se Chan got very drunk.
I don't know if he remembers this.
He called me.
He said he doesn't know
how he feels.
- Did Se Chan say that?
- Yes.
He said he has never dated
a same-aged woman.
- For goodness' sake.
- "A woman his age."
(The story is a bit suspicious.)
Keep going. Keep making things up.
"I have only dated women
who are younger or older."
"Have you dated women
who are older than you?"
"I see."
"How much older was she?"
He wanted to say, "One year older."
I guess he was too drunk.
He said, "First year older."
(First year older)
Listen.
I am not that dumb.
I didn't say that to him.
I didn't call him.
- You are the worst.
- Did you say,
- "First year older"?
- You are the worst.
- You were totally wasted.
- You are...
- You are a piece of trash!
You were totally wasted.
We did talk about So Min
throughout the shoot that day.
- For goodness' sake.
- "First year older"? Unbelievable.
I didn't call him.
It's a blatant lie. He is the mafia!
I relayed the story to So Min.
I even talked with her mom.
That's right.
- I was with my mom.
- She wants to see you, Se Chan.
By the way, Se Chan,
you should have called me.
Why did you call Haha?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Hey.
Her book is titled,
"You Can Call Me After a Drink."
Haha is ridiculous.
But Haha doesn't usually say
"Same-aged."
- No, he doesn't.
- "A woman his age" is more natural.
"First year older" is
more suspicious.
Let's move on...
- to Jong Ok's story first.
- Okay. Let's go.
"Goblin's club" and "Same-aged"...
- were suspicious.
- "Same-aged."
- "Same-aged" sounds strange.
- No, it isn't. It's used often.
Jong Ok, you are up.
This is something ridiculous
I experienced a long time ago.
Back then, I was starring in
"Men of the Bath House."
- I enjoyed it a lot.
- I loved that drama.
I was dining at a hotel...
when a middle-aged man told me
that he is a big fan.
I talked to him briefly
and we parted.
I don't know how, but he called me
after getting a hold of my number.
- Really?
- Yes.
"I am the man who said hello to you
at the hotel."
I was like, "Okay."
"I called you to help you..."
"because I have seen you work hard
at the set."
"If you buy the stocks
of a such-and-such company,"
"the price will go up.
So please buy them."
"You can trust me."
"Please buy them."
For a second, I got tempted
because I am easily swayed.
- I am easily swayed.
- You are easily swayed.
I am easily swayed.
After consideration,
I bought a bit of stock.
A week later,
the bank went bankrupt.
- Really?
- Yes.
He was a swindler.
And you had no idea who he was.
How did he get your number?
It's insane.
I am telling this story
so that he would see it.
- You know,
- That swindler.
- I have a similar story.
- He does.
- Let me tell you the story.
- Okay.
I was very lonely.
I didn't have a girlfriend.
I was single.
You know Broadway Theater, right?
Is it still there?
I know the theater.
I visited it often in the past.
- You know the theater, right?
- That's right.
- I went there and...
- It's near Sinsa Station.
Do you know the movie,
"The Contact"?
Of course, I do.
You know the movie, right?
"The Contact" is a movie about
realizing love.
Since I was very lonely,
my eyes wandered to women.
In front of me,
I saw a pink tracksuit.
- Pink goblin's club.
- Wasn't it a pink goblin's club?
- A pink tracksuit.
- You saw a pink goblin's club.
"Give me gold!"
- It can hit over 300m.
- Go on.
I saw a really fine woman
in a tracksuit.
I was too shy back then,
so I sat a few seats away from her.
About three days later,
I got a call.
- How...
- The caller was a woman.
"Hello?"
"Didn't you recently watch a movie
at Broadway Theater?"
"Do you remember a woman
in a pink tracksuit?"
She said that.
I said, "Yes, I remember."
- "I am that woman."
- That's scary.
- Was she a ghost?
- That's so scary.
This is a true story.
Did she get your number by using
a goblin's club?
(Give me the number!)
Did she get your number by using
a goblin's club?
- No! I didn't bring it up.
- A goblin's club.
- Keep going.
- For goodness' sake.
- "Give me the number!"
I still remember what she said.
She will recognize me
if she sees this.
Do you want to find her?
- "Love on the Air."
- Do this on "Love on the Air."
Listen.
I know every single story
about Suk Jin.
- Is this story new?
- It must be new to him.
- This story is new.
- Was it a red tracksuit?
Maybe the mission word is
"Pink tracksuit."
- It must be "Tracksuit."
- "Tracksuit."
- This story is new.
- You can vote for me,
but think about
why they are attacking me.
If you vote for me, we will lose.
Do you know why Suk Jin told
two stories?
He couldn't use his mission word
when he told the first one.
- That's what I think too.
- That's why...
- he told another story.
- That's what I find suspicious.
Ji Hyo followed up
with her story in a natural way.
This is the same thing.
- The mission word is "Tracksuit."
- That's right.
What do you think, Jong Ok?
What?
Who are you suspicious of?
You become really distant at times.
Just when I think we are close,
you become really distant.
"What?"
That sounded so cold.
She is friendly.
(Was I too cold?)
Haha didn't have to use
the word, "Same-aged."
So the mafia is
either Suk Jin or me.
But I really am not the mafia.
- I really am not the mafia.
- My story was natural.
Fine! Vote for me!
Vote for me and lose.
The most eccentric word
we heard was...
- "Goblin's club."
That's right.
"Pink tracksuit" too.
I thought about how things were
back in the days.
When "The Contact" was released,
a pink tracksuit wasn't something
women wore.
A tracksuit with the word "Pink."
- A tracksuit with the word "Pink."
- That's right.
It only became popular after 2000.
- Jong Ok.
- It became trendy later.
When "The Contact" was released,
didn't women wear pink tracksuits?
I don't remember.
(She refuses to help him.)
Jong Ok.
She became distant, right?
- I thought we were close.
- She is icy.
- She became distant.
- She is like that.
She becomes distant at times.
Jong Ok, vote for me if you want.
- But we'll lose.
- All right.
- For some reason,
- You know...
I always say strange things.
This team made it had.
- I think it's Suk Jin.
- I am not the mafia.
- "Pink tracksuit" is just...
- It's confusing.
It just sounded strange.
I am not the mafia.
For goodness' sake.
It's "Same-aged."
Think about it again.
Otherwise, we will lose.
- It's one of them.
- This is driving me crazy.
The result is out.
- All right.
- Out of five votes,
Suk Jin received three votes...
and Haha received two votes.
- 2 votes.
- A difference of 1 vote.
Jong Ok, I bet you voted for me.
All right.
Please tell us right away.
The mafia...
(Suk Jin was the most suspicious.)
(Is Suk Jin the mafia?)
was arrested.
(The mafia was arrested.)
The mission word was...
- "Goblin's club."
- I knew it.
(The mission word was
"Goblin's club.")
Hey! I almost died
from the suspense...
because of you guys.
My mouth went dry.
I was like,
"Did he say 'Goblin's club'?"
- The two of them ruined it for me.
- 2,000 dollars.
- "Did he say 'Goblin's club'?"
(He held up three fingers.)
The two of them ruined it for me.
It became obvious
because of "Goblin's club."
Thus,
everyone except for Suk Jin
will choose...
- from the good zone.
- I will still pick a good bag.
This is the last round
of picking the bags.
- Bring in the bags.
- My goodness.
- This is the last round.
- This will finalize the result.
(The last round
will finalize the ranking.)
We will now begin Round Three...
and pick the bags.
Shall we start with the good zone?
- Okay.
- Suk Jin, go over there.
- That's right.
- Goblin, come over here.
- Ji Hyo picks from the good zone.
- Goblin.
You know,
I am in eighth place.
I am too close to the penalty.
- This is bad.
- Now,
which zone goes first?
- The good zone.
- That's us.
Not all bags in the good zone
are good.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- Which one should I pick?
- You are in second place.
Jong Ok, you will be
in first place...
- if you pick well.
- That's right.
It's time to make a choice.
- Number 15.
It would be incredible
if she gets the switch chance.
(Jong Ok picks number 15)
- 20 dollars.
- She's currently in first place.
- Really?
- She's in 1st place.
- 130 dollars.
- I pick number 18.
- It's So Min, Jong Kook, and me.
Number 21.
Please.
(Ji Hyo gets plus 1 dollar,
and So Min gets plus 10 dollars.)
I got 10 dollars.
- As long as you're not last.
- I'm in trouble. This won't work.
So Min is getting the penalty.
There's still Suk Jin.
Me.
- You need to pick a minus card.
- Whose turn is it?
- Can I go?
- Sure.
I'll pick an uncertain number.
- Lucky...
- Seven?
- Okay.
- Number 22.
(Jae Suk picked number 7,
and Haha picked number 22.)
This one.
- All right. 10 dollars.
- I knew it.
- 10 dollars.
- Why is it all the same?
- That's all there is.
- That's interesting.
Haha has minus 10 dollars now.
There are still switch
and double chances in the good zone.
- Was this our last chance?
- Yes, it was.
Hae Sun and Kwang Soo,
- go first.
- Of course.
There are blue ones too, right?
There's some left.
There are five good cards left.
Five?
If you pick a good one,
you'll be first place.
- True.
- There are many bad ones.
Hae Sun is currently
in second place.
- Exactly.
- I want first place.
You have to pick a good one.
Help me.
As long as it's less than
minus five.
- No.
- Or plus.
- She got it.
- Lucky seven.
- I don't have a good feeling.
It's going to be really bad.
It's going to be minus 15.
- Right?
- Oh, dear.
Minus 70 dollars.
(Minus 70 dollars)
- Jae Suk is in second place now.
- I told you.
- I'll pick this one then.
- Oh, gosh.
- Second place gets a prize too.
- Really?
1st and 2nd places.
- Kwang Soo.
- There has to be a good one here.
We didn't open any of them.
- I hope you get 200 dollars.
- I pick number 19.
Number 10.
(Kwang Soo picked number 19,
and Se Chan picked number 10.)
1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo gets plus 50 dollars,
and Se Chan gets minus 30 dollars.)
- 30 dollars?
- 50 dollars.
Okay, nice.
Okay, I won.
Minus 30 dollars.
(10th place Jong Kook or 9th place
So Min is likely last place.)
Shouldn't there be a plus
next to a minus?
- True.
- Like this one?
Suk Jin,
I was going to pick number nine.
- Okay, go.
- He has to lose for me to win.
- I'm fine...
- I hope it's red.
- as long as I'm not last place.
- Let's go.
(Switch chance)
(Switch chance?)
- What?
- Switch chance?
- Gosh, what's that?
- What? What's this?
(Suk Jin picked...)
(the switch chance.)
- What's this?
- You picked the switch chance,
so you'll switch with somebody
excluding yourself.
(He'll pick a random name
and switch the amounts with them.)
You'll pick excluding yourself.
He might pick Jong Kook then.
That's possible.
This is not good then.
He might pick me?
This is not good.
He might save me.
- How did I pick this?
- I have hope for the first time.
I wanted to pick something stable.
If you pick Jong Kook,
that would be insane.
I hope you pick me or So Min.
Please pick me.
It's because of the goblin's club.
Mr. Club.
Mr. Goblin.
(Goblin Suk Jin is sad
because he messed up his story.)
I don't know!
- I picked a random one.
- I hope it's me.
Jong Kook.
- I'm fine...
- Jong Kook.
as long as
it's not Jong Kook or So Min.
If it's 1st or 2nd place,
it'd be amazing.
Jong Kook.
- As long as it's not those two.
- Right. What are the chances?
One...
(Will he end up switching
with either of the last two...)
(or dramatically win a prize?)
2, 3.
(Yoo Jae Suk!)
- It's Jae Suk.
- Three.
(7th place Suk Jin switches with
2nd place Jae Suk.)
(Their places switch.)
You're in second place now.
- Am I in second place?
- That's not good.
- I'm in second place.
- You win a prize.
- This is the worst.
- You're in trouble.
- That was insane.
- It depends on Jong Kook.
This is the worst.
- I have no way to move up.
- Really?
What if you get plus 10?
- There's plus 100 dollars.
- There is?
- If you pick plus 100 dollars,
you'll be in seventh place.
- Really?
- True.
If you pick plus 100 dollars,
So Min and Se Chan will be in last.
- Really? Will I survive?
- Is it not Jae Suk?
- Is it Se Chan and So Min?
- Yes.
Really?
It won't be easy though.
(8th place Se Chan has minus 90,
and 9th place So Min has minus 110.)
Stop following me.
I pick number five.
- It's not easy to get plus 100.
- What is it?
Number five.
(Will Jong Kook pick
plus 100 dollars...)
(and avoid the penalty?)
(50 dollars)
That's a lot.
Your total is close to 100 dollars.
That was a lot.
Only if I was lucky earlier.
- That was a lot.
- It's too bad.
50 dollars.
(So Min and Jong Kook will
receive the penalty!)
Jong Ok and Suk Jin got
1st and 2nd places.
You get the R rings.
- They get R rings?
- Thank you.
It's been a while seeing those.
(She's satisfied and happy.)
You usually...
I hope "Innocence" does well.
- This is for Hae Sun.
- It's okay.
(This is the 1st time in 10 years
he's done something heartwarming.)
I've never seen him do this
in 10 years.
Thank you.
Everything is working out for him
this year.
Along that line,
can the two of you say a few words?
Right.
Jong Ok, say a few words.
- I was looking at my ring.
- Stop looking at it.
I fell in love with this ring.
Thank you for treating us so nicely.
It was fun having you.
- I hope your movie "Innocence"...
- Thank you.
- is widely loved.
- Let's go, "Intruder."
"You Can Call Me
When You Are Drunk,"
- let's go!
- Let's go!
(That's nice.)
Great. 1, 2, 3.
(Whipped cream is launched.)
Goodness.
Look at So Min.
(Who is this?)
- Me?
- Jong Kook.
- I'm bleeding.
- That was strong.
I know.
Great work.
- Great work everyone.
(Na Eun of April and
Yura of Girl's Day are here.)
(Emotional actor Kang Tae Oh and
trot angel Kim Na Hee show synergy.)
(Se Chan and Yura show
new chemistry.)
(So Min bans dating.)
(However,)
(they spot suspicious movements
when they open the door.)
(They must brace themselves!)
(A single mistake...)
(leads to a deadly result.)
I won't sit back and watch
this time.
(If you behave impulsively,)
(your suffering doubles
without question.)
(Everybody turns cruel.)
(There's only one word
that will save you.)
(And there's the die of fate!)
(If you hesitate,
punishment awaits.)
What are you doing? What's wrong?
(There's no mercy.)
(Who's the hidden mastermind?)
(Fate Betting Race:
Throw Double or Nothing)