(Sanjicheon on Jeju Island with the blue sea and blue sky)
(There's Sanjitmul Park next to Sanjicheon.)
My gosh.
(The members are gathering at the park.)
Hello, guys.
Seok Sam.
- Excuse me. - Seok Sam.
(Seok Sam follows as he grumbles.)
- Excuse me. - Come here, Seok Sam.
(What's this skit?)
You haven't taught me anything for the past 15 years.
(Human Cultural Asset Jae Suk, and his pupil, Seok Sam)
- Do you want me to leave? - Stay quiet, Seok Sam.
(Immersed)
- This is just... - Don't talk too much.
You just let me do the laundry.
(Seok Sam's stopped from talking for 15 years.)
So you're Seok Sam.
(And these two are...)
- He's Ji Seok Sam. - Hello.
(Assistant Manager Haha, new recruit Jong Kook)
Hello.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo say hi politely.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Math Olympiad winner Ji Hyo, Math Olympiad runner-up Kwang Soo)
Nice to meet you.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Se Chan and So Min are wearing matching outfits.)
Nice to meet you.
(A newlywed couple, Se Chan and So Min)
Nice to meet you. I guess you are married.
(Nosy)
- Right. - We've been married for a year.
So you're on a trip to Jeju Island.
(The skit experts have gathered.)
But the husband...
Is the husband rich?
Is he rich?
What's that supposed to mean?
He's a rich man with a lot of teeth.
(Se Chan is always rich in a couple skit.)
I do have many teeth.
- So... - What did you do for a living?
- I ran my own business. - What business?
I used to handle big money.
What did you do?
He runs a restaurant.
- A restaurant? - Spicy catfish stew.
- Spicy catfish stew. - A restaurant.
(Mr. Yang sells fish that look like him.)
- Do you live in Paju? - Yes. How did you know?
(He sells catfish and Korean bullhead.)
He sells spicy catfish and Korean bullhead stew.
- It tastes really good. - You should visit my restaurant.
(This couple owns a big restaurant.)
I'll offer a discount of 15 percent.
(The husband made a lot of money from selling freshwater fish.)
So what brings you two here?
(What brings the newlywed couple to Jeju Island?)
I said I didn't want to come to Jeju Island.
Don't raise your voice when there are people around.
- Honey... - My goodness.
- I mean... - Don't embarrass me.
I'm sorry, but who picked out your sunglasses?
Why? Aren't they nice? I picked them.
(He picked cyborg sunglasses.)
- You look pretty. - Honey.
You look great.
(The husband loves his wife.)
- You two... - You're so pretty.
Don't make fun of her. She looks pretty.
Why did you marry him?
(Out of nowhere)
- Seok Sam. - Yes?
- Don't be nosy. - What? Hey.
(The human cultural asset stops Seok Sam from being nosy.)
I like their skit.
Seok Sam is too nosy.
(Complaining)
- I'm sorry. - You should talk to him.
Sir, I just said 1 word while you said 5.
Seok Sam, just stay quiet.
- Seok Sam. - Watch your language.
- Is his name Seok Sam? - Yes.
(Is the student's name Seok Sam?)
- Like how you count numbers. - I see.
(Korean style naming)
- Seok Sam means three. - That's what it means.
I've never seen him paint.
(Conspiracy theory)
- I've never seen his work. - I do an ink-and-wash painting.
(He's an ink-and-wash painting human cultural asset.)
- An ink painting. - I just saw him draw a mustache.
Sure. It's a kind of ink painting.
(He drew a painting on top of his protruding mouth.)
- He does draw pictures. - Sure.
- Are you sure? - Don't worry.
(Title: Petty)
Are you Math Olympiad winners? It sounds far-fetched.
- I was a runner-up. - I was the winner.
(1st place, 2nd place)
I know this is a skit, but it should be plausible.
(It's not realistic at all.)
- What's wrong about this? - All right then.
(Putting on a smart face)
Since you are the Math Olympiad winners,
(Tell us about the Pythagorean theorem.)
please tell us about the Pythagorean theorem.
Or the quadratic formula. Just anything.
It's not something anyone can understand.
- What is she talking about? - It's not easy.
She says things that aren't relevant to the question.
Do you know what an equation is?
You should make it more convincing.
- This is far-fetched. - I know.
(She can't proceed with her theme.)
And all we can say about math is an equation and...
- And quadratic formula. - Quadratic formula.
(Bringing all math principles)
What is 3.14?
- Pi. - That's enough.
- Stop it. - Root.
He's acting as if he knows a lot. My goodness.
- What did you say? - I was talking to myself.
(What?)
- What was that? - Well...
You should speak clearly.
(He keeps scuffling without teaching anything for 15 years.)
- It's my bad. I'm sorry. - You understand?
- Are you a new recruit? - Yes, I'm a newbie.
(They're from Running Trading Company.)
So he's your superior.
- That's right. He's my subordinate. - He's an assistant manager.
(Disciplined assistant manager and swaggering new employee)
And I'm a newbie.
But what kind of assistant manager are you?
- Do you have other work experience? - With your hands in your pockets.
I guess you used to be in a different business.
- Right. I made a career change. - I knew it.
I was in a different business.
That's right. Our company is known for giving a second chance.
(Assistant Manager Ha, the King of insurance)
He has broad shoulders.
(The new employee)
His shoulders look different.
That's right. We are gangsters.
- But he looks so nice and kind. - He's nice.
- He seems good-natured. - They're not intimidating.
We're in charge of debt collection.
(In charge of naiveness, in charge of sinister face)
(We can help you with debt collection.)
Today, you guys are here for a package tour.
(Why did people with different jobs gather?)
(Package tour to Jeju Island)
You are groups of two, and you guys don't know each other.
Now you will take a Running package tour around Jeju Island.
(They will take a package tour around Jeju Island.)
So you should pay for the tour package.
(They have to pay for the tour package.)
You have 50 dollars in your mission bags now.
(They all have 50 dollars each.)
- 50 dollars? - You will scatter...
(They can pay as much as they want for the tour package.)
and put the amount you are willing to pay in an envelope secretly.
The mission fund is very important for today's race.
(The mission fee matters in the race.)
So you should think carefully before you pay.
Is there the minimum amount we have to pay?
(They can pay as much as they want.)
Can I not pay at all?
It's up to you. Just put the amount you want in an envelope.
He's not telling us if we should pay a lot or not.
(A lot or little? That is the question.)
I guess we should pay a reasonable amount.
- It might be better to pay a lot. - That might be better.
I think we should pay a lot.
- Make it big. - I was going to do that.
(The newlyweds decided to pay a lot.)
Gosh, I should put some money in here.
(Passing by)
- It's very thin. - For this once, I should...
Why did you pay so much?
- Do you know something? - Well...
I thought about it, and if you calculate it mathematically,
multiplying it by 2 or 3 should work best.
- That's nonsense. - "That's nonsense"?
Why would a human cultural asset...
(The human cultural asset speaks in a rough manner.)
I paid a moderate amount.
(All 8 travelers have paid their entry fees.)
I also paid a moderate amount.
(People who paid a little, People who paid a lot)
You paid a lot.
I thought we should pay a lot.
- We collected all entry fees. - Yes.
(Which team will have the upper hand?)
Today is the You Must Do Everything...
If You Get Caught Package Option Trip Race
(You Must Do Everything If You Get Caught Package Option Trip Race)
The two people who are on the same package trip are a team today.
(The 2 members joining a package will make a team.)
The entry fee you just submitted...
(The entry fee they just submitted...)
will be your team money.
(will be their team money.)
(People who paid a little, People who paid a lot)
You will start your trip with the total amount submitted.
(They must travel today only with the entry fee they submitted.)
- Yes! - Nice! How much did you pay?
You must return the rest of the money.
(In other words, it's advantageous to pay a lot.)
(Honey, you did a good job!)
I'm in trouble. I didn't pay a lot.
(It's unfavorable for Team Human Cultural Asset...)
How much did you pay?
(and Team Running Trading Company from the start.)
- I'm worried. - I also paid quite a bit.
The team with the most money is...
the newlyweds, So Min and Se Chan, who paid 60 dollars.
Why did you pay so much? Did you pay 40 dollars?
Next are Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo with 41 dollars.
(Team Olympiad, 41 dollars)
- You almost paid nothing. - They paid 36 and 5 dollars.
I paid a little.
Team Asst. Manager Ha and the New Recruit...
paid 5 dollars each, and have a total of 10 dollars.
(Team Running Trading Company, 10 dollars)
- Gosh. - Look at that.
Hey High Schooler, I'll be in your debt after today.
What are you talking about?
Team Ink-and-Wash Painting Human Cultural Asset and pupil...
paid 5 dollars and 2 dollars and have a total of 7 dollars.
(Team Human Cultural Asset, 7 dollars)
Oh, my.
That's...
- That's cutting it close. - That's amazing.
(They're amazing in many ways.)
You suit each other.
- I'm going to owe you a favor. - He's a real human cultural asset.
(Crawling)
- He's a human cultural asset. - I'm going to owe you a favor.
(Dumbfounded)
What kind of human cultural asset...
brings seven dollars to Jeju Island?
- I'm a human cultural asset. - I'm...
(The human cultural asset suffering from the hardships of life)
I'm going to owe you a favor.
I brought much more money with me when I was in high school.
You could have a bowl of pork and rice soup each, and leave.
(They might have to share a bowl of pork and rice soup.)
Today,
(The mission funds have been given.)
you can go back to Seoul...
after taking the course our travel agency has prepared for you.
(They will travel the course prepared by the staff.)
There will be all kinds of options and extra fees.
(There are all kinds of options and extra fees.)
First, each course has...
a set number of people that can go sightseeing.
(Each course has a set number of people that can take it.)
Regardless of the teams, that number will be decided...
- after playing games. - Okay.
(The number will be decided by the games.)
The people who get the chance to go sightseeing...
(The members who are going on the trip...)
will be able to enjoy all the course offers limitlessly...
which includes buying food, gifts, and extra options.
(will enjoy all of the course and get a stamp.)
They will get a stamp each during that course.
However, for the people excluded from going sightseeing,
one loser will be decided after playing a simple game each time.
(Those who were excluded from losing a game...)
Also, the loser will cover the entire cost of that course...
(will play a game to choose who pays for the course.)
using their team money.
(The chosen one will pay the whole price with the team money.)
- They will pay up the whole amount. - We should do our best then.
- Your team might end up in debt. - Yes.
The teams who don't have a lot of money should join forces.
(They have different amounts of team money.)
- Okay. - Let's join forces.
- Let's target them. - This is good.
(But the funds will grow larger...)
- We should also join forces. - Okay.
(to the point in which the difference means nothing.)
The top three people who have the most stamps...
(The top 3 people who have the most stamps...)
when the package trip is over will get a prize.
(will get a prize after the 4 courses.)
- This is regardless of teams. - Really?
There will be a penalty for the team that has the least team money.
(The 2 members of the team with the least team money get a penalty.)
- Okay. - Okay.
You could also get the prize and penalty at the same time.
Starting now,
you will have to even pay for the water you drink.
(Even a bottle of water will be included in the package fee.)
- That's too harsh. - You're tight.
(Running Tour's cheapest package that's known for ripping people off)
I should have drunk some water beforehand.
The fee you use in the car on the way to the course...
(All charges throughout the day will be included in the expense.)
will also be counted.
I will give each team their team money and individual stamp passport.
(Team Newlyweds, 60 dollars, Team Olympiad, 41 dollars)
(Team Running Trading Company, 10 dollars,)
- Okay. - Oh, my.
(Team Human Cultural Asset, 7 dollars)
The first schedule is...
- Yes? - the highlight of package trips.
(The first schedule)
(Forced shopping)
It's forced shopping.
- Shopping? - Forced shopping?
- Okay. - Forced shopping?
- They disappeared a lot these days. - Shop with seven dollars?
(Human cultural asset with the total fortune of 7 dollars)
We will go to a shopping street, a Jeju Island tourist attraction.
(They'll visit Chilseongro Shopping Street.)
Only three people can participate.
(The number of Forced Shopping participants: 3 people)
The first game is...
Noise Complaint Apartment, which we played last time.
(The first game of Package Option Trip Race)
(Noise Complaint Apartment)
For each round, one team leader must come out,
(1 member of each team will come out and pile a hand tower.)
and a total of four team leaders will play the game.
They will shout the game chant at the same time,
(They take the bottom hand to slap the top hand.)
and they will use both hands to pile a hand tower after the chant.
(If one makes a sound, he or she loses.)
If you make a sound while getting slapped, you will be out.
(If no one is eliminated,)
One person must come from each team.
(the one caught at the predetermined floor will be eliminated.)
- You must go unconditionally. - Gosh.
(Jong Kook competes for Team Running Trading Company.)
So Min, you should go first since Jong Kook is there.
You should go after Jong Kook.
(The new groom pushes his wife into the deadly game.)
- It hurts. - Jong Kook won't slap you hard.
Jong Kook won't slap you hard.
- He won't let me off. - No, he will let you off this time.
Kwang Soo, do you want to go?
(He has no intention on playing it.)
It doesn't matter.
(The Palm Tyson says, "Welcome.")
Gosh...
- You can do it. - Come out.
(The catfish new groom saves himself.)
Shop as much as you want.
You're really despicable.
New Recruit Kim, you can do it!
(Jong Kook, Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, and So Min will start Round 1.)
While you sing, I will...
- 1, 2. - 1, 2.
(They must win to take the shopping course.)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Cross the starry bridge - Cross the starry bridge
(The package trip participants know how to have fun.)
- Let's go - Let's go
(Tiger Moth bounce and catfish bounce)
- Pass by the windy reed field - Pass by the windy reed field
- Let's go - Let's go
(The new bride had plenty of trips on a tourist bus.)
- Seok Sam is energetic. - You always
- You always - He's energetic.
(Seok Sam is an energetic cultural asset.)
Seok Sam is energetic.
- Waited for me at your apartment - Waited for me at your apartment
(Seok Sam's back hunches whenever he's excited.)
- Let's go - Let's go
- 12th floor! - 12th floor!
- Okay. - Okay.
(If no one makes a sound, the one on the 12th floor is eliminated.)
I'm in trouble. My hand is underneath her hand.
(1st floor, Suk Jin will slap So Min.)
- We will start from the bottom. - Will we start...
- from the bottom? - Start from the 12th floor.
(The person at the bottom slaps the hand at the top.)
You will be eliminated if you make a sound from now on.
So Min, endure it.
(They will be eliminated if they make a sound from now on.)
(So Min must endure Suk Jin's smashing.)
- Gosh, So Min took it. - What happened?
(Holding it in)
(So Min passed.)
- Who's next? - Second floor.
(2nd floor, Ji Hyo will slap Suk Jin.)
- It's my turn to slap, right? - Yes.
Ji Hyo, let's send him away this time.
Don't make any sounds.
- Good job. - Second floor.
(The Pupil passed.)
It's his turn.
(And here it comes.)
(3rd floor, Jong Kook will slap Ji Hyo.)
It's his turn.
- Is it Jong Kook's turn? - It's Jong Kook's turn.
- It's over. - Why did you put your hand there?
(She miscalculated.)
- I didn't know. - Take it.
Ji Hyo is shrewd, so she's good at holding it in.
(He succeeded at changing jobs with his sole palm strength.)
(Will Ji Hyo be able to endure his monstrous smashing?)
(Smash)
(Enduring)
- Other people... - I'm in pain.
(The impact was delivered to the hand below that.)
- will also be eliminated. - No.
- So Min, you must endure it. - How could the pain...
(She held it in.)
also reach me when Ji Hyo was slapped?
Fourth floor.
(Among 12 floors)
We have 10 floors left now.
We have eight floors left.
He's really bad at math.
- Weren't you in second place? - I was mistaken.
How could you be mistaken?
(It's obvious that Ji Hyo couldn't tell the mistake either.)
- Are you a foreigner? - I just got this problem wrong.
- That's why. - You can't do addition.
Endure it. Let's go!
(The math geniuses are especially weak when it comes to subtraction.)
- Send him away. - It's So Min. That was...
(5th floor, Jong Kook will slap So Min.)
(It's the new employee's turn again.)
My palm hurts.
- It's Jong Kook's right hand. - Jong Kook...
- Your... - Yes?
(The Tiger Moth bride could be eliminated.)
wife will be eliminated now.
No, she can endure it.
- Endure it. - Two people must be eliminated.
- It can't be helped. - Of course, it's a game.
(I have no choice. It's a game.)
(Avoiding)
- She avoided him. - She's eliminated.
(So Min is out.)
- She's eliminated. - She's eliminated.
Why did you make a sound when you weren't even slapped?
(Sobbing)
Good job.
(Being kind)
- Did you see the look in his eyes? - Yes?
(If you get to know him, the catfish husband is a romanticist.)
- Did you see the look in his eyes? - I thought you were going to die.
- Just endure it this once. - I can't watch this.
(It's Jong Kook's attack and Ji Hyo's defense.)
- I will also... - It will just smart once.
No. Your bone might break, Ji Hyo.
(She's the olympiad winner who has the most patience.)
It will just hurt once, and it will be over.
(The Palm Tyson is controlling his breathing.)
The new recruit is angry.
(She took her hand out.)
(Shouting)
(The math genius took her hand out at the crucial moment.)
I think you made a sound.
- He made a sound. - Can you take your hand out?
(Murmuring)
She...
She took her hand out.
(Asking to play the video)
Can you take your hand out?
She...
(Seok Sam moaned as it was unexpected.)
- Isn't that cheating? - Can you take your hand out?
- Can you take your hand out? - She took out her hand.
(She's not good at subtracting, but she's good at taking her hand out.)
My fingers aren't moving "automatically".
(Saying he twisted his finger and it's moving on its own)
- Do you mean "automatically"? - What?
- Do you mean "automatically"? - I'm sorry.
(So Min, Ji Hyo, and Suk Jin got eliminated in the first round.)
Okay, the next group should go.
(Haha, Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan will play in Round 2.)
The people who didn't play should come out.
- Okay, three people should go. - Se Chan, I can only trust you.
(They have a chance as they're all weaker members.)
- Don't worry. - Okay.
- You need to do a good job. - You need to do a good job.
(Their excitement engine is starting.)
- It's doable. - Go
(Go!)
- Let's go - Let's go
- Pass by the windy reed field - Pass by the windy reed field
(Insurance king Assistant Manager Ha is showing off his karaoke skills.)
- Let's go - Let's go
(Bounce)
- You always... - You always...
- 9th floor. - 9th floor. That's it.
- Let's go. - No, come here.
(The game of quick hands)
- Come here. - Come here.
- Let's do it quickly. - Do it quickly.
(Hurry up and play.)
- Let's do it quickly. - Okay.
- Okay. - Haha.
(1st floor, Kwang Soo will slap Haha.)
- Who is on the bottom? - It's me.
- Hurry up. - Haha's a scardy cat.
(They will get eliminated right away if they make a sound.)
Isn't this school violence?
- Hurry up. - It won't hurt at all.
It doesn't hurt. It didn't hurt, did it?
(He uses his long arm to gain momentum.)
(Enduring)
- Didn't you make a sound? - You're a man.
- It's okay, Assistant Manager Ha. - It's okay.
(Ordering)
Wait a minute, Recruit Kim,
are you the owner?
- It's okay, Assistant Manager Ha. - Okay.
(The new recruit is full of a sense of ownership.)
I thought you were the owner.
(2nd floor, Jae Suk will slap Kwang Soo.)
- Do it. - Okay, the second floor should go.
(Now, it's for the human cultural asset to smash.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
At first, I had no idea how it will be.
(He's really scared of the thought of getting slapped.)
Is it still the third floor? Whose turn is it? Who will slap now?
(The representative scaredy-cats are gathered, so the game's quite slow.)
- He's the human cultural asset. - Of course.
(Should I slap him or not?)
- He has a different rhythm. - He's rhythmical.
(Along with his wrist movements trained from...)
They became really close to each other.
(ink-and-wash paintings, everyone is bouncing along with his rhythm.)
The four of them became really close to each other.
- Bam - Bam
(The hip-hop waterwheel is suddenly turning.)
- Beat everyone - Beat everyone
- Bam - Bam
(The 4 scaredy-cats are using all kinds of methods to buy time.)
- Beat everyone - Beat everyone
- Let's go. - They're finally doing it.
(He starts slapping after preparing for a long time.)
(In pain)
(Frowning)
That was intense.
(He succeeds at defending while giving his face up.)
- That was intense. - It didn't hurt at all.
- What floor are we on? - You have six floors left.
- What floor are we on? - You're on the sixth floor.
(They have 6 floors left among 9 floors.)
- Se Chan. - Endure it.
(Se Chan smashes his hand on Jae Suk's hand.)
That's it. You can endure it.
It doesn't hurt.
(Let's endure it.)
Everyone is so well-behaved.
- Okay, next. - Seventh floor.
It's Kwang Soo's right hand this time.
(Se Chan must endure Kwang Soo's right hand.)
He's going to use his right hand.
Se Chan, endure it.
- He's merciless. - Let's fly away.
(The math genius high school student is merciless.)
You can't lose to a high school student.
(Be proud.)
You must endure it.
(The sound is extraordinary.)
(Kwang Soo just slapped Se Chan using his fist.)
He slapped with his fist.
(He doesn't want to lose, so he endured it with clenched teeth.)
- You're going to be eliminated. - Why did you slap with your first?
(Upset)
When did I?
- Young punk! - Why?
How dare you slap me...
(He got slapped by a high school student on his honeymoon.)
- Why are you hitting me? - with your fist?
How dare you slap me with your fist?
- Right now, you... - Is that not allowed?
(The high school student's character hasn't developed completely yet.)
Shouldn't he be eliminated?
- He's eliminated. - He's eliminated.
(Kwang Soo is eliminated from offending people by using his fist.)
Why?
- No wonder, even I was hurting. - He's eliminated.
Even I was hurting.
If Jae Suk makes a sound, Haha will win.
(The last 9th floor, Haha will slap Jae Suk.)
(If Jae Suk makes a sound, Jae Suk will be eliminated.)
If Jae Suk doesn't make a sound, Jae Suk will win.
(If Jae Suk endures it, Haha will be eliminated.)
- Oh, I will be okay then. - That's right.
- You will be okay. - You did a good job.
(He smiles while showing his gums.)
Look at Jae Suk right now.
Look at the face of the human cultural asset.
(No Pain Master Yoo is summoned.)
You should slap him hard.
- I do not know pain. - Lay it down hard.
He might wet himself.
(The result depends on the final slap.)
- Just do it already. - Get it over with.
I can't watch!
- Darn it hurts. - It wasn't a direct hit.
Haha, you're out.
(Haha slaps and gets eliminated.)
- It wasn't a direct hit. - He only hurt his own hand.
(The human cultural asset endured the pain with willpower.)
- Haha, you're out. - It wasn't a direct hit.
- He only hurt his own hand. - It slipped.
(It's over, right?)
Unbelievable.
(Foul language)
(Thankfully, the airplane flies over them at the right time.)
- It wasn't a direct hit. - A plane is flying over us.
(Everyone's happy to film near an airport.)
I'm good now.
(They're able to resolve their anger at any time.)
He's good.
Perfect timing.
(Jeju Airport honors the human cultural asset's status.)
Nice timing!
- It was nothing. - We couldn't hear a thing.
You heard wrong.
(Call us when you're angry.)
The three will go shopping...
(Jong Kook, Jae Suk, and Se Chan will go to the shopping course.)
and one out of the rest...
(1 of these 5 members...)
will pay for the expenses from the team's budget.
(will pay for it using the team money.)
Just so you know, Jong Kook is quite the spender.
I'm unleashing my shopaholic side.
(Let's head off to see Jong Kook waste money.)
Let's get going then.
Sure, let's head to the van.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hello.
(The highlight of a package tour, forced shopping)
- It's good to see you. - Shopping...
While on the trip,
(The service on the bus for a pleasant package trip)
- you could get hungry or thirsty. - Right.
That's why we prepared coffee, beverages, and water.
(Various drinks and snacks are available.)
- Coffee too? - Chips, chocolate, jelly...
are prepared for you too.
Beverages will cost three dollars...
while the snacks are five dollars.
Whatever you buy will be added to the tab...
(What they eat will be accumulated,)
which will be paid by the one paying...
(and the person to pay for the first course will pay for it.)
- for the first schedule. - Really?
- Hold on. - Which will be paid...
- Really? - Yes.
(One will pay for everything.)
That means the three of us can eat whatever we want.
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and Se Chan)
If your teammate has to pay,
(But one of their teammates might have to pay.)
then it'll take a toll on you too.
There's nothing more to life anyway.
(Ji Seok Sam, Pupil, spends more money than he has)
We'll think of the consequences later.
- We'll get going then. - Sure.
Can I get a bag of chips?
How about some coffee?
(Starting)
- Should we have some coffee? - Please get So Min some coffee.
I'd like a refreshing beverage too.
- Coffee... - That'll be three dollars each.
- Sure. - They're not cheap.
(Adding 3 dollars each)
Is there a cup too?
- One with ice. - Nice.
This will be three dollars too.
- Sure thing. - This too?
(It's 3 dollars for a cup of ice?)
- Just hand it out. - Can I get some jelly too?
- I'd like some ice too. - Black coffee.
(Enjoying the service)
A cup of ice, please!
Black coffee.
- Unbelievable. - This chance might not come again.
(Adding 3 dollars each)
(The payments are added as they keep order.)
That's for me.
- This... - Go ahead.
Thank you.
Can you get that for me?
We shouldn't be stingy when on a vacation.
(Team Human Cultural Asset has 7 dollars.)
- Exactly. - Nicely said.
This is the reason we save money up.
Everyone's spending money like crazy.
(Worried)
Are there any chips?
I'll get some to you.
You're eating a lot today.
Shouldn't you stop?
(He spends like he has 700 million dollars.)
- All right! - Can we stop eating now?
One team might start off as bankrupt.
We don't know who'll have to pay, so let's eat.
- Unbelievable. - This is wrong.
You've spent 63 dollars.
(They've spent 63 dollars.)
One team will go bankrupt.
(Not worrying about the amount)
- For sure. - No matter which team pays,
- it will be a lot. - One team will go bankrupt.
Any team will go bankrupt.
As long as it's not our team.
(Seok Sam spends like it's gambling.)
That's just how it is.
Don't you have any sweet or savory snacks?
(Unique taste)
So tell me. What's your dream?
(Out of the blue)
That's right. What's your dream?
- It's to be a scientist. - A scientist?
Whose your favorite scientist?
Nobel?
- Einstein. - Who?
- Nobel. - Einstein.
Honey, what was your dream growing up?
- Me? - He's my mentor.
My dream was to meet a pretty lady...
- Then your dream came true. - and live with her forever.
No, not quite.
(Darn it.)
- So we're at our first location. - Right.
(As they eat, they arrive at the first course.)
Yes, let's spend some money!
(Chilseongro, a shopping district in Jeju with a long history)
I'm going to buy you a few things.
This is life, I guess.
(Including Sanjicheon and Jejumok Government Office,)
- Right. - I'll spend at least 1,000 dollars.
(the shopping district connects us to various tourist attractions.)
The three of you...
(They're given 10 minutes to shop.)
will have 10 minutes to shop...
for yourself or your teammate.
(They can shop freely to vitalize the local economy.)
The three of you will get off now.
(The 3 members will get off.)
- Can we go shopping now? - Yes.
Please put on your masks.
- Mr. Kim. - Yes?
Buy something for my daughter, will you?
Your daughter?
Human cultural asset,
- can you get me something too? - Okay.
Let's go shopping then.
(They head out after receiving various requests.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello, everyone!
I'm here to spend some money.
(Big spender Mr. Yang arrives at the shopping district.)
I'm here to spend money.
I need to buy clothes for Haha's daughter.
(The human cultural asset...)
Hello.
(has ladies coming up to greet him in a heartbeat.)
- Hello, everyone. - Hi!
(The human cultural asset pleases his fans.)
Hello.
Hi.
(He's warmly welcomed into a clothing store.)
Hold on a second.
Hello.
(He picks a cardigan that suits the modernized hanbok.)
Is it for your pupil?
Can you get me something too?
No, it's for me.
Why would I get my pupil anything?
(The pupil is trained under harsh circumstances.)
- Guys. - Yes?
We will now see...
(They will choose who will pay for everything.)
- who pays for everything. - Sure.
You'll play a series of random silent games.
(Random silent games)
Quite a few of them actually.
(They will play a variety of silent games.)
Silent 007,
(Silent 007)
Silent 3, 6, 9,
(Silent 3, 6, 9)
or Silent Word Chain.
(Silent Word Chain)
You will choose the game you wish to play.
- How do you play Silent Word Chain? - Silent Word Chain?
You'll explain the words with body language.
(In Silent Word Chain, body language will be used.)
- Nice. - Like "bicycle"...
This sounds like fun.
If you lose the round or get it wrong,
(One gets a point if one loses or makes a sound.)
you'll be met with a punishment.
The one with the highest number of points will pay.
(The person with the highest points will pay.)
You'll now fall silent.
And go.
(Silent random games begin.)
Starting with Kwang Soo, you'll play your desired game.
(Kwang Soo will go first.)
(Silent 3, 6, 9)
(Clap)
(Silent 3, 6, 9 isn't that difficult.)
(There aren't any hitches so far.)
(Clap, Clap)
(Clap!)
Wrong!
(We knew the pupil would mess up first.)
Pound on his back.
Suk Jin receives a point.
(He doesn't know what he got wrong.)
(They switch it up to Silent 007 next.)
(0)
(07 bang!)
(Argh! Argh!)
(0)
(07 bang!)
(Argh! Argh!)
(0)
(07 bang!)
(Argh! Argh! Argh?)
(Why would the pupil raise his hands?)
Suk Jin got it wrong.
(Seok Sam gets it wrong twice in a row.)
Suk Jin now has two points.
(Let's slow down a bit.)
Slowly.
(The speed is too fast for the pupil.)
(Seok Sam needs time to adjust.)
(We'll go with Silent Word Chain.)
(We'll go this way.)
(Hopping)
(Frog noted.)
(Frog)
(A word that starts with the Korean syllable "ri")
(He's delicately describing a ribbon.)
(Ribbon noted.)
(Easy, right?)
(What on earth was that?)
(You didn't get it?)
Ji Hyo.
(Blinking)
3, 2, 1.
(Come on!)
(Time's up and Ji Hyo receives a point.)
Ji Hyo receives a point too.
The three already spent 400 dollars while shopping.
(They already spent 400 dollars.)
(Se Chan takes his time.)
Can a woman wear this too?
I'll buy one for So Min.
(The newlywed buys an item for his wife.)
Meanwhile, I'll buy this for myself.
(A couple's sweatshirts)
I'll take this one.
Sure.
(A familiar song plays.)
Seriously?
("Hapjeong Station, Exit Five" by the human cultural asset)
(Chorus by newlywed Yangsebari)
All right, come on!
I'll take two!
I'm here to spend money, people.
(He seems to have an experience of being in a chorus.)
How much have I spent so far?
Your total is at 180 dollars.
180 dollars? I'll take one that 20 dollars then!
I'll spend a total of 200 dollars.
(Receipt, a total of 200 dollars)
(He goes big by spending 200 dollars.)
Since it's winter, I should get something warm.
(Jong Kook picks a gift for Haha's daughter.)
How adorable.
(He repeats, "It's cute.")
I'll take this one. Look how cute it is.
(He isn't even checking the price.)
How adorable.
I'm glad I have all these gifts for Haha's daughter.
(Uncle Jong Kook goes big to help small businesses.)
(Receipt, jumper, woolen hat, and boots for Haha's daughter)
This is great.
(A total of 200 dollars)
Let me see.
(The human cultural asset values the fit of clothes.)
- I'll take this then. - Sure thing.
(He's also finished shopping.)
- Can I get an unopened one? - Sure.
So everything we buy...
(He bought some products, and he gets worried.)
will be paid for by the losing team?
Oh, dear.
The points are 2, 1, and 1.
(Suk Jin 2 points, So Min 1 point, and Ji Hyo 1 point)
This will be the last game you play.
If the two don't get it wrong, will I end up paying?
That's right.
(He might have to pay 600 dollars when he only has 7.)
- I'll kick off the word chain. - Sure.
So Min will go first.
(Silent Word Chain Given word: Jean)
The first word is "jean."
(A Korean word that starts with the syllable "ji")
(Worm)
(A Korean word that starts with the syllable "yi")
(Teeth)
(Teeth noted.)
(A Korean word that starts with the syllable "bbal")
Suk Jin, you're up.
(- Let's act dumb. - Sure thing.)
(The Korean word that starts with the syllable "bbal"!)
(I don't get it.)
(Being as frustrated as he is,)
(he starts rubbing his clothes.)
(Poor Suk Jin)
(Kwang Soo still acts dumb.)
(Are you still going to play dumb?)
Noted.
(Laundry noted.)
(The Korean word that starts with the syllable "rae")
(He calmly starts expressing the word that begins with "rae.")
(Haha gets it right away.)
(This seems to be what he's describing.)
(Everyone seems to get it.)
Kwang Soo, you're out.
That begins with the Korean syllable "re."
("Re" not "Rae)
(Embarrassed)
It wasn't the correct syllable.
(It serves you right for teasing others!)
- "Rae" was the correct syllable. - "Rae" not "re."
(The math genius lacks in the language department.)
- It's "rae." - Really?
What you described starts with "re."
(Final score: Suk Jin 2, So Min 1, Ji Hyo 1, Kwang Soo 1)
And my word ended with "rae."
- It was the wrong syllable? - Goodness.
(Jong Kook finished shopping.)
- Rae. - It was "rae."
- We'll conclude the game. - Okay.
- Sure. - You're back.
- Look. - You bought a lot.
(New Recruit Kim spent a lot on the presents for Haha's daughter.)
- Sure. - You bought a lot.
I bought a full set.
My gosh, that's heavy.
(Running Trading Company is harmonious.)
- Are you serious? - Sure. I bought a full set.
- He's open-handed. - I also bought shoes.
(The shopping list makes them smile.)
- My goodness. - That looks great.
- It's adorable. - It's so pretty.
I wonder what the human cultural asset bought.
(Anticipating)
Is this enough?
(Jae Suk and Se Chan finish shopping.)
- He also bought something good. - Show us.
Thank you.
- This is crazy. - I appreciate it.
- I bought a cardigan. - For who? Is it for me?
It's for me.
(Blocking)
I bought a cardigan which was 199 dollars.
Good. That's the exact amount.
(Seok Sam wants clothes from the secular world.)
You bought one expensive item.
Sure. I got a good one.
- Honey, what did you buy? - I bought a lot.
You should buy things for me.
(A lot of goods)
He bought them for real.
You should wear this.
You should buy things only for me.
(He bought grey sweatsuit...)
- And this is... - A sweatsuit? My gosh.
(for the honeymoon.)
How could he buy...
- Just wear it. - But this is...
- This is... - Is this a team uniform?
(It's a newlywed couple rally uniform.)
A team uniform? And this is for the pupil.
Thank you.
Did you buy something for Seok Sam?
(As he receives the unexpected gift,)
(he can't stop smiling.)
This is...
- Seok Sam must be happy. - Seok Sam, that's cute.
I bought a shirt for him.
- That's nice. - I need something that's worth...
(He bought a cute shirt for 20 dollars.)
- 20 dollars. - It's a shirt.
This is nice.
- It's pretty. - I love this shirt. It's cute.
(That's how he speaks when he doesn't like something.)
I'll tell you about the amount.
(63 dollars for the bus, 599 dollars for shopping)
The transportation cost is 63 dollars.
And the amount spent on shopping is 599 dollars.
- So it's 662 dollars in total. - My goodness.
The person who will pay 662 dollars is...
What do we do?
- Ji Suk Jin. - My gosh.
(Ji Suk Jin)
(Staring at him sharply)
We can do better next time.
- We can do better next time. - That's a lot of money.
Let me tell you about the second course.
(The second course begins immediately.)
- Okay. - Good.
Why are you so bad at playing games?
(Blaming)
You should try it yourself. They are so good.
- "You should try it yourself." - They play games so quickly.
There's no way I can beat them.
(From painting to 007 game, Seok Sam has a lot to learn.)
The second course is the best photo zone on Jeju Island.
(The second course is...)
(the photo zone for the photo of a lifetime.)
That sounds great.
It has a lovely view.
(There are spots for the photo of a lifetime...)
(along the beach.)
That's nice.
We've found many good places.
(They have to play well this time to take the photo of a lifetime.)
- I want to see rapeseed flowers. - Okay.
And the next game is...
(The second game, Hello, It's Me)
- Hello, It's Me. - What?
- Hello, it's me - Is it about this song?
(Is the game about making a phone call?)
- How are you doing there - How are you doing there
(She's tearing up.)
It's a team game.
(A chance to take the photo of a lifetime depends on this game.)
Each team will select a player to make a phone call.
(Each team will select a player to make a phone call.)
- And? - You can make a call...
- To a friend? - to your family or friend.
(You can make a call to your family or friend.)
And one of you will talk on the phone pretending to be the player.
(The other person will talk on the phone for 3 minutes.)
- I'm in trouble. - And you shouldn't get caught.
(Estimate the time until the person on the line realizes it.)
- If I get caught quickly, I lose? - Right.
(If your acquaintance realizes that it's not you, it's the best.)
So if they say, "What's wrong? Is it really you?"
- Then I lose. - Exactly.
- "Who is this?" - I should call my brother.
(If the person on the phone sounds suspicious, you fail.)
If the person on the phone sounds suspicious, you fail.
First, you need to decide whom to call.
(They decide whom to call.)
- I should call my dad. - I'll call Se Hyeong.
- One from each team will call. - How do you call your dad?
(Listening)
- "Dad." I just do this. - Who should we call?
(So Min's going to call her dad who knows her voice.)
Hang on. Who should we call?
Who should it be?
Should I call my wife?
- She will notice it immediately. - She will.
(Shall we?)
When we tried, we got caught in less than a minute.
(They're all thinking about whom to call.)
Really? How did they know?
But...
(Then he receives a call.)
- Hey. - I wasn't like that.
My wife is calling me. Do you want to try talking to her?
- Really? - Just talk to her. Don't whisper.
(He got a call from Chaser.)
- Just talk to her. Don't whisper. - Let me try.
(For a practice, Jae Suk answers Chaser's call.)
You don't have to whisper. Stay quiet.
Where are you, honey?
- Suk Jin? - Where are you?
I was surprised by your voice.
(Was she surprised?)
I thought it was someone else. I'm on my way home now.
- Where are you going? - Home.
(Upon the start, Jae Suk overcomes the crisis.)
Did you have a nice day?
Gosh, you're Jae Suk.
(He gets caught only in 10 seconds.)
(Happy)
Jae Suk, my gosh.
(After a few words, she catches the altered voice.)
- How did she know? - How did she know?
How did she know? Su Jung, how did you know?
He sounded just like you.
(Jae Suk sounds just like you.)
(It was a low-quality voice alteration.)
I know. So you like your husband's voice better, right?
- Sure. - I knew it.
My gosh.
(Suk Jin's couple is sweet.)
But why is your wife saved as Chaser?
Su Jung.
(It's a sweet but scary name.)
- I didn't know that. - Don't say that.
- Why is your wife a chaser? - It's just...
(His lone chase got caught.)
- Okay. - Su Jung.
- She's saved as Chaser. - You should change it to runaway.
(I can't believe it's Chaser.)
Su Jung.
Why are you with them? Are you shooting the show?
- We're filming... - She didn't know we were shooting.
(She didn't know about the shoot.)
- We're filming - She didn't know.
She didn't know that. My gosh.
- She thought you were home. - We're shooting Running Man now.
(Giving update)
- She thought Suk Jin was at home. - Su Jung.
(He came to Jeju Island on the day of the shoot.)
Let's stop talking.
Hey.
Are they separated or what?
The more we talk, the more I feel hurt.
(The longer the call gets, the deeper he's wounded.)
- Okay. - Bye.
I'll see you later, Su Jung.
(He ends the call with his wife...)
- Bye. - Bye.
(by telling her about his business trip to Jeju Island.)
Drive safely.
- She fell for it at first. - She didn't know.
(It was a practice, but it's a bummer.)
But she recognized you right away.
(The faster the acquaintance notices, the better.)
- Only in three seconds. - That was funny.
- Who should we call? - She has quick wits.
I'll call my dad, and Ji Hyo will talk to him.
(So Min will call her dad.)
Ji Hyo.
But Ji Hyo's voice is...
(The faster her dad notices, the better for Team Newlyweds.)
- Ji Hyo has a unique voice. - Gosh, this is...
There's no one in the world who sounds like Ji Hyo.
(Will Ji Hyo be able to talk on the phone for a long time?)
Are you making a call right away? Don't you need to practice?
(Calling So Min's dad)
- Ji Hyo is doing it. - I rarely call my dad.
Hello, So Min.
Mom?
(Playing by ear)
Yes. Why did you call?
(Her mom answered the phone instead of her dad.)
Mom, where's Dad?
Your dad? Why?
Well...
Is this a mission?
(A mission?)
(She doesn't know it's not So Min. She just thinks it's a mission.)
Yes, it's a mission. You need to answer my question.
(You should answer my question.)
No, let your dad do it.
(She turns it over to her husband.)
- Hello? - Dad.
- Yes. - Dad, what's my nickname?
- Your nickname? - My nickname.
- You have many. Parrot. - Parrot?
(He's talking to the fake parrot with no doubt.)
- Why? - Ask him about his blood type.
What's your blood type?
Type AB.
What about me?
Yours is also type AB. You take after me.
- I can't believe this. - What?
(So Min's anxious by his conversation with a fake daughter.)
Dad.
Who's your favorite member in Running Man?
I like Song Ji Hyo.
(Song Ji Hyo?)
It's her.
(He likes Ji Hyo, but he doesn't recognize her voice.)
He doesn't know.
(The fake mission call continues.)
What a coincidence.
I think she can talk to him for three hours.
- She can do it for three hours. - You know I like her.
(It's way past 3 minutes.)
All right. It's been nine minutes.
(Team Newlyweds fails as it's over 3 minutes.)
Dad, it wasn't me. It was Ji Hyo.
- Hello, sir. - Dad.
(So Min's dad finishes his lone mission.)
I guess he wanted to be in our show for a long time.
- I mean... - He wanted to be on TV.
("Is this a mission" works well.)
- He was so excited to be on TV. - I think...
he was too excited to notice her voice.
(To be on TV, he didn't focus on her voice.)
- I can't believe this. - I didn't see this coming.
(He did his best to respond to complete the mission.)
If she kept talking, it would last for an hour.
It wasn't me. It was Ji Hyo.
I see. She sounded just like you.
What?
- Sir. - I thought it would end right away.
(He talked to Ji Hyo for a long time whom he wanted to meet.)
- Hello, sir. - How is it possible?
That was unbelievable.
You must be proud of your daughter.
I'm always proud of her whether she's successful or not.
(Touched)
That's so nice.
I know. You're so proud of her, but you don't recognize her voice.
I hope we will meet someday. Thank you, sir.
(They could feel the love from the call with So Min's dad.)
- Thank you. Bye. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
That was really good.
(Other teams are relieved thanks to Ji Hyo.)
- Is it that Ji Hyo did a good job? - I'm disappointed.
- I'm disappointed with Dad. - That was fun.
(Sad)
It's important not to get caught at first.
(Ji Hyo soothes So Min.)
Then it goes well. Shall we call Sae Ho?
- Sae Ho? - Let's call Sae Ho. Who'll speak?
Who wants to try? Who will talk to Sae Ho?
(Jae Suk's calling Sae Ho.)
- You'll call Sae Ho? - Yes.
- Hang on. - Or we could try this.
"Hello?" As if he's pulling a joke.
- "Hello." - As if he inhaled helium.
(Kwang Soo plans to pull a petty trick with his voice.)
- Good idea. - "Hello?"
So who will talk to him?
(Kwang Soo will talk to Sae Ho.)
- Kwang Soo, you should try. - Kwang Soo?
I think he'll notice it right away.
- I think he will. - I think so.
(Will Sae Ho notice that it's not Jae Suk?)
- We don't know it yet. - It's okay.
- Hello, Jae Suk. - Where are you, Sae Ho?
I'm shooting a TV show now.
Really? Are you on a break now?
(He tries to confuse him with a whispering voice.)
- Pardon? - Can you talk now?
Yes. I can talk now.
You should go outside now.
- Okay. - Hurry.
(Sae Ho's manipulated by Kwang Soo's whisper.)
- I'm out. - I'm going to...
give you a quiz, so you should answer.
- What? - I'm shooting Running Man now.
Okay.
First, say hello to our viewers.
(He asks Sae Ho to say hello to viewers.)
- To viewers? - Yes. Say hello to them.
Hello, nice to meet you. Thank you so much.
(Sae Ho says what he always says.)
I'm Cho Sae Ho, and I was shooting a TV show.
I'm on a break now.
(Naive Sae Ho completely fell for the voice alteration.)
- I'm glad to talk to... - Lower your voice.
- Sae Ho. - Yes?
(Pretending to be in a rush)
Lower your voice.
Okay. Nice to meet you. Thank you so much.
(Obedient)
I'm Comedian Cho Sae Ho. I'm glad to talk to you.
(Sae Ho says hello as he's ordered.)
Sae Ho, make an acrostic poem with my name.
- What? - An acrostic poem with my name.
(Asking for an acrostic poem to kill time)
- An acrostic poem with your name? - Yes. Yu.
(Out of nowhere)
Yu.
You are so
You are so beautiful
(He starts singing right away.)
Where are you now?
(He sings a serenade of an acrostic poem moanfully.)
You should stop him. It's over.
I must say he succeeded.
(Time is up and Jae Suk fails.)
- Hey, Sae Ho. - Yes.
- How did you not know my voice? - I can't believe this.
- It was Kwang Soo. - Hello, I'm Kwang Soo.
That's not it. You suddenly called me. What is going on?
- Do you not know what's going on? - Sae Ho.
(Sae Ho is blamed even after doing everything he was asked.)
How could you not recognize my voice?
- Well done, Sae Ho. - Good job.
(Other teams are satisfied by Sae Ho's terrible hunch.)
Sae Ho, you weren't so funny today.
It's not easy to be funny while getting a perm.
- Okay. Thank you anyway. - Sae Ho.
(He still said hello to viewers and made an acrostic poem.)
- Have a nice day. - Thank you.
- Sae Ho. - Nice.
- I'll call you again, Sae Ho. - Good job.
(Due to Kwang Soo's whisper,)
- Thanks. - So who won?
(Jae Suk from Team Human Cultural Asset fails.)
- Who will win this game? - My gosh.
- And So Min... - Do you want to call Hyuk?
(Jong Kook will call Actor Jang Hyuk.)
- Let's call Hyuk. - Do you want to try?
What do you usually say to him?
I won't tell you.
(Why not?)
Why not? Hey.
You should tell me what to do.
- "What are you doing?" - "What are you doing?"
(Jong Kook tends to talk nonchalantly over the phone.)
- "What's up?" - "What's up? Where are you?"
- "Hello? Where are you?" - "It's me."
"Hey, where are you? Where are you now?"
Don't do that.
- Don't you sound too sly? - Wait a minute.
- Is that how you think of me? - No, it's not like that.
(Are you saying that's how you will impersonate me?)
- No, I don't think he's mean. - How dare you.
Were you imitating Jong Kook?
(Se Chan is cornered because of the low-quality impersonation.)
- I was just focusing on your tone. - Okay, try it again.
"Hello? Hey, where are you?"
(He was born to sound vulgar.)
- Aren't you mad, Jong Kook? - "Did you eat?"
Do I sound that vulgar?
(Jong Kook's angry to hear his vulgar tone.)
- No, it wasn't vulgar. - What?
- Se Chan, you try calling Hyuk. - All right.
(Se Chan will try calling Jang Hyuk.)
- "Hello?" - I think you can fake his voice.
Here's the ring tone.
(Calling him)
Put it on speakerphone.
Look at it shaking.
Hey, Jong Kook.
Hyuk, where are you?
Me?
I'm on Olympic Boulevard Expressway right now.
Where are you headed?
(He naturally finds out where he is.)
I just dropped the kid off.
I need to go home first then I have to go to Gangneung.
So you're going to Gangneung?
Yes.
Have you eaten?
I will on my way to Gangneung.
(Not doubting at all)
You will on the way?
- Yes. - Gosh.
I'm on Jeju Island. The weather is great here.
(Presenting a topic)
You're in Jeju Island?
Yes, I finished filming. The weather is so good.
Hey, doesn't Tae Hyun call you these days?
Gosh, he keeps calling me. I'm going out of my mind.
(The subject changes.)
Why is he talking so much?
(He starts having small talk.)
Why does he call me whenever he's drunk?
That's what he does these days.
(He starts to spin a yarn.)
I think he's obsessed with it.
Because I'm not answering his calls.
(Summary: "He keeps calling you because you're not picking up.")
Is that right?
It's just making me go crazy.
(Se Chan makes a few rejoinders,)
I was dragged by him a couple of times though.
(and Hyuk starts talking.)
- Gosh, he dragged you? - He sure did.
(Sloppy response)
Hyuk, where are you?
- Who is this? - "Who is this?"
(There's no way they're going to complete the mission anyway.)
Who is this?
(Where's Jong Kook?)
I'm Jae Suk.
(Jong Kook fails his mission.)
- He didn't know it was me. - Hey.
- He really didn't know. - Gosh, Hyuk.
- Even when I talked in my tone. - I can't believe it.
(Hyuk completely believed the crappy impersonation.)
- He really didn't know. - Hyuk.
- It's so funny. - Yes.
You've been talking to Se Chan.
(Hyuk.)
There's no way he sounded like Jong Kook.
I talked in my own tone.
(He's really naive without prejudice or doubt.)
- A voice he's never heard before. - Hyuk.
- Hyuk. - It's hilarious.
- Yes. - How can he not know?
How can you not know it's someone else?
(He still thinks it's Jong Kook.)
So who was I talking to?
- You were talking to Se Chan. - I think he thinks you're me.
(He thinks...)
And you're talking to Jae Suk right now.
Hyuk, please get it together!
(Hyuk is still in confusion.)
- Hyuk! - Hyuk!
(Laughing)
Hyuk.
How can you not recognize Jong Kook's voice?
The truth is we're not that close.
What?
(He forces an excuse as he feels embarrassed.)
- Hey, you ruined my mission. - I did?
It's not you, is it?
It is me!
It's me, you fool!
(He's all confused now and still can't recognize his voice.)
He can't trust anyone now.
Hyuk, you're so funny.
- Thanks. I'll talk to you soon. - Thank you, Hyuk.
(Though he can't recognize the voice, they're still good friends.)
- All right. Bye. - Thank you!
Take care of yourself.
(Jong Kook fails his mission as Se Chan talked to Hyuk instead.)
I can't believe him.
- This is so funny. - He talked so smoothly.
It's so easy to fool him.
Se Chan, call someone you know.
Yes, you should pick one of your friends too
(Se Chan of Team Newlyweds will try calling his celebrity friend.)
Who should I call?
How about calling Jae Joon?
(The comedian)
- Kang Jae Joon? - Yes.
- Jae Joon will notice it's not me. - All right.
(Se Chan will call Jae Joon.)
- Why don't Jong Kook call him? - What do you usually call him?
(How does Se Chan speak when he's on the phone with Jae Joon?)
- Do you speak casually with him? - No, I speak formally.
- "Hello, sir?" Like this? - As soon as he answers...
(First...)
he says, "My goodness."
- "My goodness." - "My goodness."
- "Where are you?" - "Where are you?"
- "I'm off work now." - "My goodness."
(Se Chan likes to drag the politest expression.)
- "I'm off work now." - "Where are you?"
Jong Kook, sounds like him.
- "Jong Kook." - Oh, that's it.
(Like this?)
- You're good. - That's good.
Then you should try calling him.
(Jong Kook will talk to Jae Joon as he sounds similar.)
- Yes, you try it. - Yes.
It's on speaker.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
- Where are you? - Where are you?
Are you home?
(It's a smooth start.)
I'm somewhere I don't want to be.
Oh, gosh.
You mean you're home?
I'm at the office of Comedy Big League.
I see.
- Wait a minute. - I...
- Your voice is... Is this Se Chan? - My gosh.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
(The original "My goodness")
- It wasn't Se Chan. - It wasn't him.
(Jae Joon noticed it in 15 seconds.)
- It's me. I'm Jong Kook. - Hey.
- Jong Kook, how have you been? - Good.
We're on a mission right now.
Jae Joon, you recognized it too fast so our mission is ruined.
(He explains to Jae Joon that it was a mission.)
(Put me on.)
I'll let you talk to Se Chan. Just a minute.
- All right. - Bye.
My goodness.
Wait. This isn't him either.
(It's not so easy to fool him.)
- He noticed again. - It's so hard to fool him.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
Hey, it's me. It's Se Chan.
Stop lying to me!
No, it's really is me!
(Still doubting)
- Come on. It's me! - He doesn't...
- It's me! - recognize the real one either.
(After the brief call with Jae Joon,)
- Jae Joon. - He's suspicious of everyone.
Pottery.
(So Min called Ji Hyo's brother to play Word Chain.)
Greasing.
How can her family member not notice her voice?
- I'll talk to you later. - Thank you, Sung Moon.
(Ji Hyo's brother didn't recognize it for a while.)
- Here's the result of the mission. - Okay.
Se Chan and So Min's team completed the mission in 15 seconds.
(Only Team Newlyweds succeeded once in 15 seconds.)
But the others failed.
One more team can join them.
So pick one team to take them with you.
(They can choose a team to go on the course.)
This is good.
We won so we don't have to pay for it though, right?
(They're saving money as they're both getting off.)
- Yes, you can save your money. - That's right.
Then you should take...
these penniless guys with you.
- Yes, the old guys. - These guys?
Yes, we should take the old guys with us.
(Giving the chance to the ones that came to Jeju with 7 dollars)
- Take pity on them. - Yes, take them.
- Yes, take us. - All right.
(Team Newlyweds and Team Human Cultural Asset...)
(will go on the Photo of a Lifetime Course.)
All right then.
- Chosen members should get off. - All right.
(They'll go to take photos of their lifetime near the shore.)
- It's pretty. - Wear your masks.
All right.
- The four can get off the bus. - All right.
(The photo spot of Jeju with the entrancing sunset)
Have fun, guys.
We'll go take some pictures.
- See you. - This is so nice.
So Min, it's this way.
Gosh, this is nice.
(The newlyweds are excited to see such beautiful scenery.)
- It's amazing. - It's so pretty.
(With the sunset painting the sea red in the background...)
I think it's this spot. Photo of A Lifetime Course.
- Where? - There.
(and cute little chairs lined up)
Yes, this is it.
- There's something to eat too. - We should take photos here.
(Any photo will turn into a photo of a lifetime here.)
Gosh, that's tangerine juice.
(There are also things to enjoy.)
It's really delicious.
There's a Polaroid camera too.
(And a Polaroid camera)
Gosh, what's this?
You may choose the services. The prices are listed on the menu.
(There are different props prepared.)
So Min, you can buy that. But come here first.
(Childlike innocence)
It's tangerine bread, isn't it?
- Let's buy the couples' bracelets. - Okay.
- Choose one. - Okay. It's pretty.
(The newlyweds get couple's bracelets.)
It costs 30 dollars.
I'll take two for me and my wife.
You said you're not married.
(Seok Sam also buys a present for his wife.)
- I have a wife. - Now he was a wife.
I'll buy these for Ji Hyo and Na Eun.
(Jae Suk buys postcards for his children.)
- Then take two. Three? - I will buy...
photo of your lifetime taken by Chan Hee. It’s 50 dollars.
(The highest price on the menu is 50 dollars.)
That's good.
We will take the immortal photo of...
- The Polaroid camera. - your lifetime taken by Chan Hee.
- Yes, I'd like that. - I want photos from Chan Hee.
("Immortal Chan Hee" is...)
(Kang Chan Hee the cameraman with years of experience...)
(who has worked...)
(for numerous other shows.)
- Yes, Chan Hee will take photos. - Okay.
(The living legend will take their photos.)
Here we go.
Shouldn't the apprentice be stand up?
Gosh, sit here then.
(A human cultural asset and a teacher who is strict)
Shouldn't the apprentice be standing up?
(If only he wasn't my teacher...)
- I'll hold up the reflector. - Okay.
What's with these two shots?
Smile at least.
(The serious and strict teacher and the old pupil)
What is this?
Is it done?
(So Min in charge of bubbles)
1, 2, 3.
(Click)
- You take one alone. - All right.
(Teacher.)
- You need one for your funeral. - For his funeral?
(Random words)
(The pupil looks for a chance to get rid of his teacher.)
- Here it is. - Yes.
I wonder how it came out. I wish my bubbles are in it.
(What will the photos by "Immortal Chan Hee" look like?)
Here.
This looks like...
(What's wrong?)
they're going to die soon.
Is it a photo of their spirits?
("Ascension" by Kang Chan Hee)
- Are we ghosts? - Why did it come out like this?
It looks like we're going to die soon.
(What is this?)
- And it costs 50 dollars? - Gosh.
(It's quite low in quality for a 50-dollar service.)
Gosh, Chan Hee.
- Immortal photo? - Where's your immortal photo?
What is this?
(Restless)
How can you make us look like we're about to die?
(The customer explodes after seeing a psychic photo.)
Let me see it.
(Kang Chan Hee, cameraman, specializing in videos)
Gosh, this makes me sad.
- You two get a photo. - Yes, we should.
(The newlweds)
- Hold up the reflector. - All right. The reflector.
(Next are the newlyweds.)
- Blow some bubbles too. - Okay.
Blow some bubbles, please.
Hey, Mr. Human Cultural Asset.
- Help us out. - All right.
(A generous human cultural asset)
- Seok Sam. - Yes, sir.
(Take this.)
(He's strict only toward his pupil.)
"Seok Sam."
- "Hold this up." - Okay.
(The human reflector is docile.)
Here we go.
Se Chan, move towards So Min.
("Immortal Chan Hee" helps them with the pose.)
- Okay. - Look towards her.
(Turning)
Look towards her.
Wait a minute.
(Flustered)
(His face got as red as his gums.)
Just do it.
Can't you take off your sunglasses?
- That looks nice. - Gosh, the bubbles.
(He can't even look her in the eye.)
1, 2...
- Wait. - Do you usually press on two?
1, 2.
(Clicking on two)
- Wait. - Do you usually press on two?
- Do you usually do that? - You should press on three.
Is it normal to go on two?
(Nervous)
Again.
(He tries again.)
- Here we go. - Suk Jin, you're too close.
(Get out of the angle.)
- I am? - Get out of the way.
- Suk Jin, you're too close. - Okay.
Only two of us should be in the picture.
(The human reflector tried to get in the shot.)
Suk Jin.
- Here we go. - Ready.
(They try again without the unwelcome guest.)
1, 2, 3.
(Clicking)
- This one will be good. - Great.
(It was taken well this time.)
- I'm sure of it. - Yes, I'm sure.
- So Min. - Yes?
I think you're really enjoying this.
(Look at this.)
This is too...
- Let me see. - Look at the photo.
- What is this? - What's this?
This looks really weird. What do I do?
(It looks like an actual honeymoon photo.)
It's weird.
We look too close.
- It's like you're really on a trip. - Yes, this looks real.
(Seok Sam gets excited.)
- Come on. This isn't right. - You two look real.
(Embarrassed)
- Looks like you're really in love. - Yes, they're in love.
You two look like a couple on a honeymoon trip.
(The couple's photo crosses the line between role-playing and reality.)
And you took a photo of us looking like we're about to die?
(Enraged again)
- Come on. - What's with our photo?
("The Boatmen of Jordan River" by Kang Chan Hee)
How can you make it look like it's the end of our world?
- Their picture is so much nicer. - What about our photo?
(Complaining)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Sorry.)
- This photo's so funny. - The photo is...
(They wasted 250 dollars because of "Immortal Chan Hee".)
We spent 250 dollars on photos.
- How much did we spend? - We can...
(While the four members are spending a lot of money,)
- How much? - We can spend more.
Everyone, please get off.
(the rest of the members are somewhere they can't see the ocean.)
Four of you can't take photos here.
(One of them will have to pay without even watching the ocean.)
But one of you will have to pay for the photos.
You'll play Tumbling Tug-of-War to decide who will pay.
(Photo of a Lifetime Course)
(Waving Tug of War)
- Tug-of-war? - Tug-of-war?
It's a one on one tournament.
(It's a 1-on-1 tournament.)
Two members will wear...
(2 players will wear a belt connected by a string.)
belts attached at each end of the spring.
You have one minute...
(Within 1 minute, they must send...)
to make the CD in the middle move towards your opponent.
(the CD across without using their hands.)
- Towards your opponent's side? - Yes.
You lose if the CD is close to you.
(The loser's team will pay for the expenses.)
The one who loses until the end...
will pay for the photos.
(Send the CD away to avoid paying.)
So the CD should be far away from me?
- That's right. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo, Haha, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo)
Let's start with Lee Kwang Soo and Haha.
(Round 1, Kwang Soo versus Haha)
- Ready. - How do I do this?
- The black mark is the middle. - Set.
(Nervous)
(The game starts.)
Haha, you're doing great.
(The CD moves toward Kwang Soo as soon as the game begins.)
That's it! Great!
Haha, you're doing great.
(Fancy hip movements)
Okay! That's great.
(The CD won't seem to leave Kwang Soo.)
You're doing great.
You're doing great. Great!
(The Math prodigy learned how to play games from a book.)
Haha, you're doing great.
(This is fun.)
Gosh, Kwang Soo!
Great. Swing it more.
Great!
(This won't do.)
You're doing great!
(Doing the nasty hip dance)
Here he goes. Great.
(With his vulgar hip movements,)
No, you can't let him win.
(he succeeds in pushing the CD away.)
Okay. There you go.
(The Pythagorean pelvis that makes use of the x-axis and y-axis)
You can't use your wrists like that.
Okay. Again.
- No. - You can do this.
We need to go!
(Use your energy, Assistant Manager Haha.)
- We need to go! - 3, 2...
(Will Kwang Soo win like this?)
(Game over)
(The whistle was blown.)
- What is happening? - We win!
(Centerline)
Hey!
(The CD moved toward Kwang Soo beyond the centerline.)
- What is happening? - We win!
- What? Why is it coming toward me? - We win!
(Assistant Manager Haha won after an unexpected buzzer-beater.)
- It passed the centerline. - But this is...
- The finishing point matters. - Yes.
(How could this happen?)
- Kwang Soo. - Gosh.
(As a runner-up at the Olympiad, he lacks persistence.)
- Gosh, this is... - This is so funny.
- This is so funny. - Why am I dizzy?
- Should I go? - Ji Hyo, you must win.
(Round 2, Jong Kook versus Ji Hyo)
This is amazing, Jong Kook. We just have to win this round.
(If Jong Kook wins, Team Olympiad has to pay.)
- Let's do this. - Okay.
It's over for us if you lose this round, Ji Hyo.
Let's win.
- Ready. - Move your hand away from it.
(The game on the edge of a cliff...)
(starts.)
We must win.
- Do it the other way. - That's it.
(The CD moves toward Ji Hyo as soon as it begins.)
Do it the other way.
- Ji Hyo. - Gosh.
- Jong Kook. - Do it the other way.
(He's clenching his molars hard.)
Jong Kook, don't use your strength too much from the beginning.
- Ji Hyo, you're doing a good job. - What!
(He ignores her and moves forward.)
- Don't come toward me! - Ji Hyo!
(You're scaring me.)
- Don't come toward me! - Go the other way! You got this!
(Ji Hyo retreats and looks for a chance.)
No.
(New Recruit Kim only moves forward.)
- Don't come toward me. - The other way!
That's right.
(Neck-and-neck)
End it now.
Ji Hyo, endure it.
Endure it. You're winning right now!
(Moving forward for the 2nd time)
- Don't come toward me. - You can do it!
Don't come toward me!
(What's wrong with him?)
- Ji Hyo. - Endure it until we win.
(If Ji Hyo loses, Team Olympiad has to pay.)
Please...
Four...
- 3, 2. - Ji Hyo, don't give up.
That's it!
(Game over)
Why did you keep coming at me?
(The recruit who kept pushing won.)
- Okay! - Okay!
(Running Trading Company is exempted from paying.)
That's it.
- New Recruit Kim! - He did it on purpose.
Our company's name is actually "New Recruit".
Team Olympiad lost.
(Team Olympiad will have to pay.)
You will have to pay for everything.
- Okay. - We're going to win.
- We might come in first. - I know.
I think it will cost a lot of money.
(It would cost a lot.)
- We lost. - That's right.
We will take everything like family and group photos.
(They spent money for no reason without even seeing the sea.)
- Come here, let's take a photo. - Okay.
(They're posing like partners.)
Come here.
(Ji Hyo also joined the selfie.)
Kwang Soo.
Aren't you going to join them?
- Let Lee Kwang Soo in the photo. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(Ignoring)
We're done. We're done taking photos.
- Let's go. - We're done.
We're done taking photos.
We took a lovely photo.
(Even his teammate abandoned him.)
- The sky is lovely. - Hurry up.
- There's no airplane passing by? - No.
Kwang Soo, hurry up and leave.
(He just spits out harsh words.)
(They heard everything.)
An airplane passed by.
- It was an airplane. - Where?
- There's an airplane over there. - Kwang Soo.
It already passed by far away.
(The course ended by just leaving several wounds on Kwang Soo.)
- Okay. - Please get in the car.
(They completed the course.)
- This is so funny. - That's right.
- Did you take photos? - It's so funny. What should I do?
(The 4 returned after enjoying.)
- Take a look. - You should try one of these.
- This is so... - But you look really...
- close and lovely in the photo. - Who wants some tangerine juice?
(Newlywed couple)
(They check out the photos.)
- Me. - I want some.
- Try this. - This is funny. "Newlyweds."
(Meanwhile, Se Chan smiles as he looks at the photos.)
We'll get going now.
This is really good.
- It looks good. - You gave him the good picture.
(Assistant Manager Ha loves make-believe relationships.)
- The total fee we used is... - Yes?
(The newlywed couple makes Assistant Manager Ha smile.)
We spent a lot.
You became sentimental.
Take a look at that.
Look at the horizon.
(Jeju's sunset induces exclamation.)
Look at the sunset.
Look.
(While everyone is immersed in the scenery,)
(Suk Jin is stealing snacks.)
Look at the horizon.
(Gosh, Suk Jin.)
(The pupil is not romantic since he's worn out from the hardships.)
The sky is really beautiful.
We're on our way to eat something good.
- Really? You should eat this. - Yes.
This time...
- You should eat this. - Yes.
(He returns the snack right away.)
(He can't believe it.)
- Suk Jin... - Are you serious?
- His tone was... - "You should eat this."
(Seok Sam threw the snack to his teacher to have delicacy.)
so detestable.
It's obvious that he was serious.
But he's...
- being serious. - I was joking.
(Shocked)
- Were you joking? - You were serious.
(Seok Sam's too honest.)
- He wasn't trying to be funny. - "You should eat this."
- "You should eat this." - He's serious.
He's being real.
(Embarrassed)
I'm dumbfounded by the timing I said that.
I'm sorry.
(Sulking)
"You should eat this."
(A restaurant in Jeju)
- Look at this view. - Gosh,
look at this panorama. It's so nice.
Since the sun is setting, it's making me slightly sentimental.
(They're excited...)
(to enjoy the meal with the sunset on the horizon.)
- Yes, my heart is... - Do you know that?
- This is the third schedule. - Yes.
(The third schedule in the tour package)
We will enjoy playing Jeju Island Full Course Feast...
(Jeju Island Full Course Feast...)
with a clear ocean view as the background.
(with the clear ocean view as the background)
Braised hairtail, which is a dish that represents Jeju Island,
(Braised hairtail, which is a dish that represents Jeju Island,)
and all kinds of fresh seafood have been prepared.
(and all kinds of fresh seafood will be served.)
I'm going to eat this.
The number of people who will enjoy the feast is five people.
(Only 5 people can enjoy the feast.)
- Let's eat. - The number is too little.
(5 out of 8...)
- Five people... - That's a lot.
(is not bad.)
It's out of eight people.
- Five people are doable. - Yes, it is.
(Enthusiastic)
This game is Half Proverb Quiz.
(Package Option Trip Race, third mission)
(Half Proverb Quiz)
It will be an individual match.
- It's not a team match. - We shouldn't do proverbs.
It's advantageous to Team Olympiad.
(Team Olympiad looks worried.)
That's possible.
- That's right. - Proverbs are...
Five questions will be given to each person continuously.
(5 questions will be given to each person continuously.)
Listen to the last part of the sentence...
- of the proverb we say. - Okay.
(Listen to the last part of the proverb...)
Complete the front part within three seconds.
(and complete the front part within 3 seconds.)
- That's hard. - Proverbs.
- You'll tell us the last part only? - Only the last part?
(They have to answer the front part.)
If we say the last part, you have the get the first part.
- The front part? - There are a lot of hard proverbs.
- We will start right away. - Okay.
(The game order)
- Let's start with this side. - Let's start with this side.
If you can't say it after we say "1, 2, 3.",
(If you can't answer in 3 seconds, you fail.)
- you will be out. - Okay.
Ready,
(Ji Hyo will try first.)
go!
It's better to get beaten...
1, 2, 3.
Okay.
(Timeout)
- "It's better to get beaten"? - "It's better to get beaten"?
(What's "It's better to get beaten"?)
It's better to get beaten first.
- "It's better to get beaten first." - I couldn't think of it.
This is confusing though.
(It's confusing.)
- I'm not sure about this. - This is hard.
- It's better to get beaten... - This is the second question.
"The best side dish..."
1, 2, 3.
- Quail eggs! - Hunger!
- "Quail eggs"? - What do you mean by "quail eggs"?
(The best side dish is quail eggs?)
- Is it "quail eggs"? - It was "Hunger."
(Quail eggs are the best side dish.)
- Quail eggs... - Quail eggs are also a side dish.
(When you think about it, it's not exactly wrong.)
Quail eggs are a side dish.
- Please give us a little more. - This is hard.
It's too far back.
(The Olympiad winner isn't good at anything aside from math.)
- This is the third question. - Okay.
This is hard though.
Spraying ashes on...
Cooked rice.
(The members figured out the answer right away.)
Spraying ashes on...
(What about Ji Hyo?)
- Spraying ashes on cooked rice. - No way.
(Timeout)
She said it too late.
(It was close, but she failed.)
How could we not answer even one question?
But I think this is doable.
(Feeling confident)
- Okay. - We got zero points.
(Ji Hyo got 0.)
- I really don't know what it is... - In my opinion...
- If we just get two right, we win. - Here we go.
(If they can get at least 2, they can eat.)
It's Lee Kwang Soo's turn.
I can't think of anything.
(Kwang Soo will try.)
Don't even look at...
Trees you can't climb.
(Correct!)
(What happened to Kwang Soo?)
Even dogs won't catch...
Winter colds.
Summer colds.
Winter colds!
- Summer colds. - It's "summer".
(Incorrect)
- Summer colds. - Winter colds?
A lot of people catch colds in the winter.
- Winter colds - Okay.
- I was close, but I got it wrong. - Okay.
(Rationalizing himself)
They say it's rustling...
(It's a question that's even hard for proverb expert Jae Suk.)
Effortlessly?
What is that?
(They say it's rustling effortlessly?)
- That's not it. - What is it?
What was it? It was something related to sound.
(What's the first part?)
The oak leaf says that the pine leaf is rustling.
- That's right. - That's it.
- I knew it. - This is important.
(It's a mix of hard and easy questions.)
- That's right. - This difficulty will be intense.
This is hard.
- This is hard. - This is the last question.
The sister-in-law is more irritating...
Than the mother-in-law who hits you.
- That's not it. - It's "who stops the fight is..."
The sister-in-law who stops the fight is...
The mother-in-law who hits you.
In my opinion, we will get to eat if we get one question right.
(Kwang Soo got 1.)
- You will get to eat. - You will get to eat.
- It's Kim Jong Kook's turn. - Okay, I'll try.
(Jong Kook will try.)
- It's really hard. - I think Jong Kook will be good.
(Jong Kook is unexpectedly good at this type of question.)
- I'm not sure. - It's hard.
- It's hard. - Let's get going.
Your crotch will get ripped...
Crane legs will also...
It's "storks".
(Jong Kook can't do it either.)
The crotch of crow-tits will get ripped if they follow storks.
- It's "storks". - Storks.
(He got it wrong, but he pretends to know it.)
Crow-tits were following storks.
- I get what you're talking about. - Crane legs.
(He said a crane, the long-legged bird, in a rush.)
- Crane legs. - Crane legs.
I knew what it was.
(It's really confusing.)
- This is the second question. - This is hard.
You can't see through someone's mind...
Even if you know 1,000 fathoms of water,
you can't see through someone's mind.
- It's "10 fathoms of water". - 10 fathoms of water.
(It was close, but it's a wrong answer.)
Even if you know 1,000 fathoms of water,
you can't see through someone's mind.
- It's "10 fathoms of water". - It's "10 fathoms of water".
(It wasn't 1,000 but 10.)
- It's confusing. - Gosh.
Please be quiet by his side.
(Stop acting like you know.)
I said it after the bell was struck.
(Speaking in Jeju dialect)
"I said it after..."
- It's "10 fathoms of water". - It's "10 fathoms of water".
(Jong Kook is struggling unexpectedly.)
This is the last question.
Jong Kook's proverbs are hard.
We will get to eat if we get one question right.
(Kwang Soo who got 1 is currently in the lead.)
You will get first place if you get two questions right.
Rice cakes...
Give one more rice cake to the child you hate? That's not it.
(Incorrect)
- Rice cakes you can't eat... - Rice cakes in drawings.
(He couldn't answer such an easy question.)
Rice cakes in drawings.
But this is...
- They just gave this to you. - Gosh.
(Once they hear the answer, they know.)
- The last part is not enough. - It's hard. I can't think of it.
It's easy after you hear the answer.
You don't know what it is.
(Jong Kook got 0.)
I'm currently in first place.
- It's Haha's turn. - Haha.
(Haha will try.)
I'm getting confident though.
To sow the wind...
And reap the whirlwind!
(Correct!)
He's going to eat.
There will be a hole to survive...
Needle.
(Gibberish)
Needle!
(Because of So Min's distraction, he says "needle".)
- Did you say that? - Even mouse holes...
Even if the sky collapses, there will be a hole to survive.
(Embarrassed)
- It's not "mouse hole". - Gosh.
- I'm angry. - How could you not know this?
- This is a famous proverb. - How could you not know this?
This is the third question.
To deceive yourself...
- Cover your eyes! - This was easy.
(Correct!)
Cover your eyes!
- This was easy. - Cover your eyes...
- Haha is in first place. - to deceive yourself.
(Haha's in the lead after getting 2 right.)
To be honest, his questions are too easy.
(Angry)
- My questions were too hard. - That's right.
- Ji Hyo's was tough too. - Okay, I got two.
(The level of difficulty reflects their level of intelligence.)
The difficulty is too...
(Because Haha did well, they complain.)
- There's too much of a difference. - How hard it will be for me?
- Yes, it's like that. - Yes.
(Feeling proud)
Haha, you're in first place.
Whose turn is it now? Se Chan or So Min?
- It's So Min's turn. - That's right.
(So Min will try.)
Junsobari.
(She doesn't feel confident.)
- I don't think I'll get it right. - So Min.
They will go on top of the stove first...
A whimsical calf!
(Whimsical So Min said the wrong answer.)
It's "well-behaved cat".
So Min, you...
(Embarrassed)
- I... - What did she say?
I suddenly didn't remember it.
- A whimsical calf? - She's really whimsical.
(The relaxed man who answered 2 questions)
Wait a minute. Yes.
This is the second question.
A well-behaved cat?
You will survive if you recover your senses...
- A crazy man... - What?
(She throws wrong answers unhesitantly.)
- It's "if you're in a tiger's den". - Wait a minute.
- It's "a tiger's den", isn't it? - A tiger's den.
- This was too easy. - This was too easy.
(How can you get this wrong?)
(They all raise their voices when it's someone else's question.)
- How could you not know this? - Even if you're in a tiger's den...
This is the third question.
(It's the next question.)
You can't give it to dogs...
- Someone else's habits! - What is this?
- It's "your habits". - It's "your habits".
(Incorrect)
- Your habits. - This was too easy.
- To someone else? - To dogs.
- In my opinion, the meanings... - It's easy when you hear it.
- of what I said are similar. - That's right.
(Giving a lame excuse in front of her husband)
- Only the details were wrong. - "A well-behaved cat"...
(Still, "An eccentric cow" was...)
and "An eccentric cow" are entirely different.
I said the first thing that came to my mind.
(So Min got 0.)
- Let's go. - You become dazed.
- Se Chan. - Here I go.
(Se Chan will try next.)
- Let's go. - Try to get one right.
Out of the blue.
(He just needs to get one question right in order to eat!)
- A squid. - A bolt!
- A bolt. - Hey, it was a really easy one.
(It's the easiest question so far.)
I will have no expectations. I have zero expectations.
I can't tease him because it's unbelievable.
You know how it is.
(The pencil squid's lame excuse)
I couldn't say what I know due to nerves.
A goby also jumps.
When a pencil squid jumps, a goby also jumps.
(He sounds like a pencil squid that is upset.)
- When a gray mullet jumps... - Is it a gray mullet?
- Yes, it's a gray mullet. - It isn't a pencil squid.
I thought it was a pencil squid.
(When a gray mullet jumps, a goby also jumps.)
This is the last question.
(One who copies someone better than him without realizing his situation)
He didn't get a single question right.
With acorns.
(He must get this question right in order to eat!)
Comparing the heights!
- That's wrong. - It's "With acorns".
(You must get the first half.)
Dog food.
- It's so embarrassing. - The production crew is laughing.
(Se Chan didn't get anything.)
Comparing the heights!
- The newlyweds are out. - That was hilarious.
(The wife is embarrassed of her husband.)
- Excuse me. - Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin will try next.)
I will show you the perfect score.
(He seems like an expert from his outfit.)
- Suk Jin. - Okay.
Suk Jin knows a lot of proverbs.
(He's an old man.)
- Let's begin. - Okay.
Looks at the roof.
Dog... Dr. Dog.
- Dr. Dog? - Dr. Dog?
He said he can get all the proverbs right.
(He was condescending.)
Hold on. Gosh.
(Master Ji is embarrassed.)
I knew it had something to do with "Dog".
I couldn't think of it.
- I didn't know... - A dog that was chasing a chicken.
- what kind of dog it was. - Let's go.
You glare at the Han River.
After scowling.
- Isn't it "After getting slapped"? - After getting slapped at Jongno.
Is that it?
Where did "After scowling" come from?
(Seok Sam's common knowledge is low despite his experience.)
I couldn't think of it.
You kept going, "How could you not know that?"
(He kept showing off.)
- "After scowling"? - After scowling.
I suddenly couldn't remember it.
(Embarrassed)
- Let's resume. - Okay.
- A chicken. - A dog that was chasing a chicken!
A dog that was chasing a chicken!
- My goodness. - What is it?
What is the answer?
- Not a pheasant, but a chicken. - Not a pheasant, but a chicken.
(He was just laughing at "comparing the heights with acorns".)
- What is up with you? - You should try it!
You shouldn't have been so snobby.
(Blaming)
- You should try it. - After getting the same proverb,
(He's dressed as a proverb master,)
you went, "A dog that was chasing a chicken!"
(but he's actually a dog that was chasing a chicken.)
This is the last question. To Gangnam.
(Will he be able to get the first part right?)
- You follow your friend. - That was easy.
Hold on!
(Correct)
- You follow your friend. - This is easy.
Hold on! Why did he get such an easy one?
(That was so easy.)
- Okay. - It was too easy.
(I would've got that too.)
- It was too easy. - Seriously.
- I mean... - It was too easy.
(Suk Jin got 1 question right.)
I will go next.
(Lastly, Jae Suk will try.)
- Jae Suk. - All right.
- Let's see how well you can do. - You know,
(You yelled at me.)
I need to get 1 or 2 questions right.
(If he answers at least one right,)
You only get three seconds.
(he gets to eat and exempted from the tour cost.)
You just need to get one question right.
Let's begin.
And meat is for chewing.
(He often flaunted his knowledge to other members.)
(Will the human cultural asset get it right?)
(What will be Jae Suk's answer?)
- What? - Song Dae Kwan.
- Insadol. - What?
(Time's up.)
- Song Dae Kwan. - Insadol.
You need strong teeth.
(Chew, bite, taste, and enjoy.)
Which proverb ends with "And meat is for chewing"?
- What is that? - What is that?
Words are for talking and meat is for chewing.
- That sounds familiar. - It's so difficult.
(Groaning)
Why is it so difficult? The difficulty level is too high.
(The human cultural asset couldn't say anything from the start.)
Gets no wind.
This one is easy.
- It's easy. - What was it? A household?
A household?
You were being so cocky earlier.
(A household with no wind)
- What is it? - A tree with many branches.
- A tree with many branches. - A tree with many branches.
Gosh, I knew this proverb. I have to get one right.
You only remember it after you hear the answer.
- Okay. - That was funny.
He might not be able to eat.
Keep you awake all night long.
- This one is easy. - Late-learned thieving skills...
keep you awake all night long.
(Correct)
I thought it was "Thieving for the first time".
Who came in last?
There must be many people.
- We came in last. - 4 people got 0 questions right.
(The 4 who didn't get anything)
- 4 people? - There is space for 1 more person.
(One of them can eat.)
Why don't the four of you play rock-paper-scissors?
Why don't you give us the same question?
(Whoever answers the question will get to eat.)
- The one who answers should eat. - Shall we do that?
Let's go.
And he asks to give you his bag.
Talk to a porter and he asks to give you his bag.
(Se Chan is out.)
- Gosh, it's so easy. - Do you know it?
(Jae Suk has a problem remembering someone else's question.)
You spare a man and he asks to give you his bag.
(Incorrect)
Save a man from drowning and he asks to give you his bag.
- There you go. - That's right.
(Jong Kook gets it right.)
Save a man from drowning and he asks to give you his bag.
- Okay. - Is that the first part?
(They place last.)
- The first part. - Save a man from drowning.
(Retrieving his reputation)
- That's right. - Jong Kook succeeded.
Why isn't it about a porter?
Save a man from drowning and he asks to give you his bag.
(Third mission result)
It's about a drowning man.
Thus,
five members except for Ji Hyo, So Min, and Se Chan will eat.
(The familiar three placed last.)
Okay.
(They acquire a stamp.)
- The cutoff line... - What is this?
(They enjoy a course meal with a sunset.)
Oh, my goodness!
- It's the braised hairtail. - What is this?
- What is this? - What is this?
(It's full of fresh ingredients of Jeju Island.)
This is a meal you must eat.
It's tasty.
(Running Tour provides a proper meal.)
Order me some food too.
- It's so tasty. - Thank you.
Thank you for the meal.
- We got this dish. - Let's mix it with rice.
(The bottom 3 can only have seafood pastes.)
Do you want some hairtail?
(Do you want some hairtail?)
- Yes! - Do you want some hairtail?
(Interested)
Please give us some.
(We want hairtail.)
Please give us a piece.
Then you should get a question right.
(Suk Jin will ask a question...)
What question?
(and whoever answers it will get hairtail.)
I will give you three seconds. Can I decide on a member?
- Devotion will touch the sky. - I mean...
- Can I decide on a member? - Devotion...
- will touch the sky. - I mean...
(The proverb quiz left Se Chan traumatized.)
He asked if he can decide on the member.
- I will decide on Ji Hyo. - Okay.
Travels 400km.
A foot without words...
- A word without feet... - A foot without words!
- I am sorry. - A word without feet.
(I shouldn't have done that.)
I am sorry.
(She can't laugh because Ji Hyo tried her best.)
I can't believe she said, "A foot without words".
- A word without feet... - A foot without words!
- A foot without words! - She was in a hurry.
(Still confused)
The wrong proverb suits Ji Hyo.
The losers will play a game to decide who will pay.
(It's time to pick who will pay among the losers.)
- Yes. - That's right.
(Team Asst. Manager Ha and the Recruit is safe.)
- Thank goodness both of us won. - I know.
- I will give you the game. - Okay.
(After playing the game to pick the person to pay,)
Se Chan will pay.
(Se Chan will pay.)
Okay!
- You lost. - That was pretty far.
- The total of the meal is... - How much is it?
(The course meal costs...)
- 374 dollars. - What?
It isn't as expensive as I thought.
(Sad)
The first place was the most expensive.
(This is bad.)
You ate a lot. The total is 370 dollars.
We will get coffee to go...
(They will move to the last mission place.)
- and move on to the last mission. - Okay.
- We should turn the tables. - Let's do that.
(They completed the course.)
What comes now isn't a mission.
(Now that they're full, it's time to get some coffee.)
You just need to go to the cafe and order coffee to go.
- Really? - Who wants to go?
We will go.
(We will go.)
No, no. My pupil is here.
- Your pupil. - Seok Sam can go.
(Student and slave at the same time)
- Your pupil. - Listen.
I have a few pupils too.
- Like who? - What?
Didn't you say you were born in 2002?
- He was born in 2004. - 2004.
(It's hard to believe, but he's in Grade 10.)
In which year were you born?
2001.
- He is older. - You are older.
Why are you speaking so casually to an older boy?
(How rude.)
- Seok Sam. - Why do I need to...
(Seok Sam hasn't learned manners yet.)
Why did I become someone who was born in 2004?
(Angry)
Seok Sam, I can't believe you!
(You'll be scolded.)
Do you want me to whip your legs?
What about my legs?
- He is polite to Jae Suk. - Listen.
(Meanwhile)
(Changing the target)
You look young. Why don't you go?
Are you interested in me?
(Are you interested in me?)
(Laughing)
He is happy.
(She attacks Seok Sam's heart, who never had a girlfriend before.)
- He is happy. - He is single.
He said earlier that he is single.
Since I am going through puberty, I am interested.
(She's mine.)
- Seok Sam, stay in your lane. - He is going through puberty!
- He is going through puberty! - This is insane.
(Shy Seok Sam is going through puberty.)
The newlyweds and Seok Sam should go.
(Anyway, the newlywed couple and Seok Sam will get a takeout.)
That's a good idea.
We will go together.
Seok Sam, let's go together.
Okay, Seok Sam.
(Why did I become a boy who was born in 2004?)
Why did I become a boy who was born in 2004?
(Seok Sam.)
- Wait for us. - Seok Sam, wait for us.
(Moving fast)
Okay.
(Seok Sam listens to So Min well.)
- How pretty! - Seom and Some.
- Hello. - Hello.
(A view where you can see the ocean at a glance...)
- How pretty! It's pretty here. - Hello.
I really like this.
Let's buy some bread too.
(with mouthwatering desserts)
- Let's do that. - Shall we get the corn sticks?
Two cups of iced chamomile tea.
(They place an order first excitedly.)
The bread is incredible.
This is where you take photos.
(They check out the cafe after placing an order.)
Where?
- My goodness. - Hey.
- How pretty! - Shall I take a photo of you guys?
It would look really beautiful during the day.
(You can enjoy the night in Jeju here.)
This is where you take photos.
I will take a photo of you guys.
- Okay. - My goodness.
(Seok Sam takes photos of them.)
This is an amazing spot.
1, 2, 3.
(We are newlyweds for the day. Seok Sam, take nice photos.)
- Give me the phone now. - You should get your photos taken.
(It's time to take Seok Sam's photos.)
Should I keep my mask on?
- Smile. - 1, 2, 3.
(He poses like he went to college in the 80s and 90s,)
1, 2, 3. Let's do this.
Smile.
(Are you taking good photos of me?)
- Smile. - 1, 2, 3.
(He is taking selfies.)
1, 2, 3. Let's move a bit here.
(The swindler couple is busy taking selfies.)
- Let's take it like this. - It's prettier.
1, 2, 3.
(Seok Sam is excited.)
- Let's take it like this. - It's prettier.
1, 2, 3.
(Making a V-sign)
It came out really well.
(He is excited to see the photos.)
(Se Chan runs away after fooling him.)
- This is nice. - When you come to Jeju Island,
you should take a lot of photos.
(He sees the newlywed couple.)
Hold on. Hey.
Did you guys take selfies?
(It's okay.)
You took selfies. Okay.
It's okay. It's okay to take selfies like that.
(Seok Sam is a bit foolish,)
That's what you do when you are newlyweds.
(but he's kind.)
This place is the best.
The two of you should sit here.
(Seok Sam's going to take photos of them again.)
Here?
What a shot!
Make a heart over your heads.
- That's so old. - Go ahead and make a heart.
- That's so old. - Come on.
One... Go ahead and do it.
(They soon make a heart after complaining.)
1, 2, 3.
- I should work with cameras. - Why?
(Look at this.)
Are you good at taking photos?
This is a work of art.
(Another best photo with the beautiful night view of Jeju)
- You take good photos. - That's a nice photo.
- You take good photos of your wife. - Yes, I do.
- I will take your photos for real. - No.
(This time)
- I am serious. - Suk Jin.
- I don't need photos. - I am serious.
(You can't fool me.)
I will take them for real.
(He heads to the photo zone forcibly.)
- You need photos from here. - I don't want to do that.
I don't like what I am wearing.
(Despite the complaints, he poses in an old-fashioned way.)
- It's a good shot. - One...
(He zoomed in on Suk Jin's face.)
I will focus on your face.
(This photographer eliminated the background.)
One...
I feel bad for him.
(You can't tell if he is in Jeju Island or Yeouido.)
Okay. You don't need to take many photos.
He is handsome.
He is handsome. Suk Jin is handsome, isn't he?
I focus on the face when I take photos.
I see.
(He checks the photo excitedly.)
- I don't focus on the background. - It's nice.
(Chuckling)
(Zoomed in)
- What do you think? - You...
You zoomed in too much.
I focused on the face.
- I focused on the face. - You zoomed in too much.
(The background only assists.)
Be careful.
(While the three enjoy their time,)
Let's get going now. Is our order ready?
(others are waiting inside the bus.)
- Five years? - Yes.
That must be nice.
(Wriggling)
(He is distracted.)
You aren't a human cultural asset, are you?
(He is too unfocused to be a human cultural asset.)
What do you do for a living?
Aren't you a human problem?
(Not a human cultural asset)
(The human cultural asset seems to have a lot of issues.)
- I am a human cultural asset. - A human problem.
My drawing of an orchid...
costs 20,000 to 30,000 dollars.
You are an artist.
(Then)
- Do you have a nickname? - What?
- A pen name? - Something like a pen name.
(That's a pen name.)
How could you call it a nickname?
(It's suspicious how he joined Running Trading Company.)
A nickname?
You make it sound like a nickname from school days.
Something like a silly goose.
A nickname! A nickname!
(The recruit is embarrassed of his boss.)
What's your pen name?
(He doesn't want to talk to Haha.)
Do I really need to reveal it to someone like him?
I am not sure if you would know, but...
Do you know who Johns Hopkins is?
(American businessman who founded Johns Hopkins University)
- That came out of nowhere. - Johns Hopkins.
- He is a famous painter. - That's right, I respect him a lot.
(Reading the room)
That's right, I respect him a lot.
Did you just say Johns Hopkins is a famous painter?
(What are you talking about?)
- This is insane. - This is insane.
(No ordinary person understands the Olympiad level of knowledge.)
I can't have a conversation with them.
- What? - Johns Hopkins.
(I've heard about it before.)
- Johns Hopkins. - He is a famous painter, right?
- Is he a stock investor? - What?
He asked if he is a stock investor.
(Not John Lee)
Seriously.
Johns Hopkins.
(Favorite painter)
(Then)
Do you have a favorite work of his?
- Yes. - What is it?
(Gibberish)
"Deviation".
My favorite is "Jonathan's River".
(Gibberish)
(Saying everything they know)
"Jonathan's River".
- "Jonathan's River". - It draws you in.
(Brazen)
It's so frustrating to talk to them.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you laughing because you understand it?
Of course.
- I respect him. - You respect him.
(Respect it if you don't know.)
All right. Make light work.
(A sudden quiz)
Let's.
(That's ingenious.)
(It's incorrect, but it's not exactly wrong.)
That works too.
- She is witty. - She is witty.
(The Olympiad winner also has a sense of humor.)
She is witty.
- That cafe is a work of art. - Why?
It's so nice.
(Meanwhile, the 3 ordered the takeout.)
Is it by the sea?
It's more than that. It's so big.
Here you go.
The packaging is pretty.
Thank you.
- Okay. - Who is paying for this?
Seok Sam, thank you for the coffee.
(Half formal, half informal)
- Okay. - Is Seok Sam paying for this?
It will be included in the total.
(They go to the location of the last mission!)
The total wasn't that big.
Do you see the powder here?
Are you satisfied with the trip?
(So far, the customers are satisfied with Running Tour's package trip.)
- Yes. - It's perfect.
I will now explain which course remains.
(It's finally the last course.)
Give us a chance to turn the tables.
- You can turn the tables. - Really?
(They can turn the tables in the final course.)
All right. The best part of flying is...
(If there's an inflight duty-free shop in the plane,)
- the in-flight duty-free shop. - Yes.
On the bus,
(there's an inside-the-car duty-free shop in the bus.)
- you can purchase a souvenir. - Really?
(Each team can buy 1 souvenir.)
- Each team can choose 1 souvenir. - 1?
There is something I need to tell you in advance.
(They were supposed to stop somewhere for the souvenirs.)
Since we don't have time to visit a souvenir shop,
So Min will sacrifice her free time and go with us tomorrow.
(Due to tight schedule,)
(So Min will buy their souvenirs for them.)
- Good job. - If you agree, we will give her...
(It's a gift from staff for So Min who cares about the show.)
- a penalty exemption card. - I will go tomorrow.
- So Min? - Yes.
(If everyone agrees, So Min will get a penalty exemption card.)
- She is staying another day. - We will give it to her.
- Okay. - A penalty exemption card.
(Since she's spending more time for them, they all agree.)
- Really? - You will have a shoot tomorrow.
- Thank you. - If you don't want it...
(A penalty exemption card is given to So Min for future.)
- I want it. Give it to me. - It's yours.
Choose a souvenir So Min will buy it tomorrow.
(They'll choose the souvenirs that So Min will buy the next day.)
- Okay. - Let's see.
Let's see.
(Jeju Island souvenir menu)
- The hairtail set. - It's expensive.
(Seafood products, agricultural products)
It's the real deal.
I want to buy wine.
(Industrial products)
- I like tilefish. - Tilefish is the best.
(Alcohol)
- It has a long face. - Then...
you should take a hairtail set to your parents.
Thank you.
(A lesson from the human cultural asset...)
- It's for you, Seok Sam. - The hairtail.
(for Seok Sam who isn't a good son)
Yes, the hairtail.
We want tangerine wine.
(The newlywed couple chooses Jeju tangerine wine.)
- Tangerine wine. - Let's drink wine.
We also want tangerine wine.
- Let's eat cheonhyehyang. - Aren't you a student?
- Seriously. - That's wrong.
- Hey, hey. - Get the hairtail set.
(The human cultural asset is mad at the delinquent.)
Get the hairtail set.
- Seaweed chips. - Eat hairtail.
He looks like seaweed chips, so that should be his souvenir.
- Hairtail. - How could you say that?
(Angry)
- You look like seaweed chips. - It's your hair.
- I will get the hairtail set. - Hairtail.
(Kwang Soo ends up choosing a hairtail.)
The total cost of the coffee...
(Team Running Trading Company made a choice too.)
and the expensive souvenirs you have chosen is...
(The coffee and souvenirs...)
- 773 dollars. - What?
(cost 773 dollars.)
That's the worst.
(The team that pays 773 dollars...)
I forgot about the coffee.
(is guaranteed to lose.)
The last mission will change the rankings.
- I will explain the last mission. - Okay.
(The final mission to determine the loser)
- Soon, we will arrive at a cafe. - Okay.
(Soon, they will arrive at a cafe.)
Two team members will decide on the order...
(Each team will enter the cafe every 1 minute.)
and enter the cafe every one minute.
It's your mission to stay without getting recognized.
(If they stay unrecognized, they win.)
- By whom? - Only the cafe owner knows.
(Aside from the cafe owner,)
The part-timers and customers don't know about the shoot.
(the part-timers and customers don't know about the shoot.)
- I have an advantage. - How about the cameras?
(The staff members are ready to film!)
The staff members are already hiding in the cafe.
Two members will enter the cafe at a time.
(Each team will enter the cafe every 1 minute.)
The 2nd team will enter after 1 minute.
(The team that gets the name called first loses and pays for the cost.)
If your name gets called, you are out.
- That team will get the penalty. - What if...
("You are so-and-so, right?")
What if someone says, "You look familiar?"
(Their exact names have to be called to lose.)
- No, your name has to be called. - Your name.
Wait until everyone enters the cafe.
(If it doesn't end after all four teams enter,)
If all eight members enter without any names being called,
then you need to take turns to order the drinks too.
(they will take turns to order drinks.)
- Can I take off my glasses? - Of course.
- People don't recognize me. - We are allowed...
(They're allowed to wear a hat and a mask.)
- to cover our faces, right? - Can we wear...
- a hat? - You can wear a mask and a hat.
Can we wear sunglasses?
(Glancing)
But I am wearing modern hanbok.
But I am wearing modern hanbok. It will catch people's eyes.
(Stealing attention)
- You should wear a jacket. - This is bad.
Let's play Race of Wits for the order.
(They'll play Race of Wits for the order.)
- The losers go first. - Yes.
(It's disadvantageous to enter early.)
- It's Race of Wits. - Race of Wits.
(Who will enter first?)
Don't stand up. Call out the number.
- Get ready. - Set.
(Race of Wits begins.)
- Set. - I will go first.
- I will go fourth. - Go.
One.
- 2. - 3.
- 4. - 5.
- 6. - 2.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 6.
- 7. - 7.
- Okay. - 5.
- 6. - 7.
(Seok Sam and Kwang Soo lose.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Sam loses every game.)
He is so cute.
- Kwang Soo is cute. - Kwang Soo is cute.
(Teasing)
- Kwang Soo is cute. - He is cute.
(Seok Sam and Kwang Soo somehow became rivals.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Team Olympiad will go first.)
- Okay. - What happens if Kwang Soo goes...
and gets caught?
(If they get caught as soon as they enter, it's over.)
- Then it's game over. - Is it game over?
That won't do. Don't send in Kwang Soo first.
(Team Olympiad is expected to end the mission fast.)
No, no. You just need to hang in for a minute.
(The order of entrance)
Okay.
A hat and a mask, right?
(A cafe in Jeju)
Let's do this.
My hair at the back of my head is too long.
Kwang Soo, you look suspicious already.
(They even turned off the light.)
Should I put on a cap?
You look suspicious.
(They look suspicious even in darkness.)
People will recognize you as soon as you enter.
Kwang Soo, it's game over.
(They're glad that the 1st player is Kwang Soo.)
- You should know that. - No.
- I will show you. - Don't get your hopes up.
- Do you have a cap? - Where is it?
(The 1st team, Team Olympiad gets off.)
People rarely recognize me,
but you are too recognizable.
(Anyone will be able to tell that he is Lee Kwang Soo.)
I am wearing a school uniform too.
I am too tall to be a high schooler.
(Even to me)
You are too tall to be a high schooler.
(Team Olympiad is already nervous.)
We need to go that way. Isn't that the cafe?
(They act natural and approach the cafe.)
(However)
Why are there so many people?
(Since it's 7:30pm on a weekday, the cafe is packed...)
(with students and office workers.)
(This footage was filmed safely and in accordance...)
Let's sit down first.
(with COVID-19 prevention guidelines.)
(The two students enter.)
Let's sit down first.
(The cafe is packed with customers.)
(A customer looks at Kwang Soo as soon as he enters.)
(Thankfully, he didn't recognize Kwang Soo.)
(A staff member's cell phone)
(They walk past the customers without ordering.)
(The direction Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo went)
Let's sit over there.
(They arrive at a secluded place.)
This table is perfect.
(Whispering)
No one will look at us.
(At that moment,)
(a customer looks at Ji Hyo!)
(She turns her head away.)
We look natural.
(Team Olympiad sneaked in pretty well.)
(Staring)
I see more seats over there.
(More secluded)
(What?)
(Is she looking at Kwang Soo?)
(Kwang Soo was looking for a more secluded spot...)
(when a female customer looked in his direction!)
If your name gets called, you are out.
(Did she recognize Kwang Soo?)
(Uninterested)
(She resumes talking to her friend.)
Let's not move.
(Nervous)
(This high school student who is 2m tall can't even stand up.)
Let's not move.
(While Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo overcome many crises,)
- What? - That's too obvious. I'm not lying.
(Team Running Trading Company gets ready to enter.)
Really?
(Jong Kook and Haha can't cover themselves.)
Go.
- We need to cover the mic. - What?
(They look like they're here to take over the cafe.)
Is it here?
- Hello. - They're here.
(A staff member's cell phone)
- Jong Kook and Haha are here. - They're here?
Hello.
(Humming)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Jong Kook tries to act normal by humming.)
(To be safe, they must grab a seat first.)
(A staff member's cell phone)
(Jong Kook sits down.)
(Haha moves to the other side.)
(They're going to split up to avoid suspicion.)
(Jong Kook, Haha)
(They safely grab a seat.)
- Haha. - Thank you. Bye.
(After 1 minute, Team Human Cultural Asset enters.)
- What? - Hey.
Don't worry.
- Is it here? - Look at our pants.
(Chuckling)
(Flapping)
Our pants are...
- Is it here? - I think so.
(Two men enter flapping their pants.)
- It's here. - Seriously.
Hello.
(A staff member's cell phone)
(2 people in a weird hanbok appear in a cafe full of young people)
Welcome.
Your pants are embarrassing.
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk is here.)
That's so weird.
That's obviously Jae Suk.
He looks weird.
(They steal people's attention.)
- Welcome. - Your pants are embarrassing.
(As they walk, they can feel people looking at them.)
This is wrong.
Let's go somewhere else.
(Embarrassed)
I didn't know it was this bright.
- Hurry up. - Let's sit.
(People in the cafe are stirred.)
Why is it so bright?
(They move in a rush.)
Hurry up.
(What?)
(They enter a room.)
What are we doing?
What's this place?
(The human cultural asset and Seok Sam aren't used to a cafe.)
- Why is it so bright? - What's this room?
I didn't expect it to be this bright.
- What's this room? - What's this?
I think some people recognized us.
(They look suspicious even from behind.)
(A staff member's cell phone)
- What? - Some people recognized us.
I think they recognized us.
I noticed my pants...
(People stare at them...)
I saw you from the back.
(because of their flapping pants.)
You look like a martial arts player.
(No one has called their names yet.)
You should go place an order.
- I was so flustered. - People here don't know.
(Someone's approaching them.)
She's looking at Jae Suk.
- Okay. - I think she's looking at us.
(The customer grabs her phone...)
(staring at Jae Suk and Suk Jin.)
This is bad.
(Glancing)
(Please don't come.)
(Jong Kook's glancing at them.)
People here don't know yet.
(She passes them.)
Should I sit somewhere else?
(Relieved)
I think some people noticed.
They're here.
Who are they?
(After 1 minute,)
Se Chan and So Min.
Welcome.
(Team Newlyweds enters.)
They're here. They covered their faces perfectly.
- Hello. - Hello.
Don't they look weird?
- They look suspicious. - They're wearing matching.
(They look very suspicious.)
- They look so weird. - My goodness.
They're wearing matching clothes. That's so weird.
(The newlywed couple doesn't look sweet at all.)
- They're wearing matching clothes. - What's up with them?
Are they placing an order?
Are they?
(A staff member's cell phone)
What are you having?
I'll sit over there.
Well...
(So Min's going to place an order to avoid suspicion.)
What would you like?
(While So Min's ordering,)
Well...
(Se Chan sits in the corner.)
They're ordering something.
Well...
I'll have two iced tea.
(The employee raises his head...)
(upon hearing So Min's voice.)
The part-timers and customers have no idea.
(Will he notice that it's So Min?)
(Very kind)
- Two iced tea? - Yes.
- For here? - Yes.
(He focuses on his job with So Min in front of him.)
- Yes. - That's 5.8 dollars.
I got so nervous that I ordered iced tea.
- Good job. - Because I was so nervous.
(They successfully grab a seat with iced tea.)
I was so nervous. I didn't know what to order.
- Let's go over there. Let's move. - Is there a table?
- Is there a table? - Let's move over there.
(Team Human Cultural Asset aims at the partitioned area.)
Okay.
- Over there. - Let's go.
(They feel pressured since it's open.)
(They quietly move to the partitioned area.)
(What? A glass wall?)
There's a glass wall.
(Flustered)
Why is there glass?
(He almost broke a glass for trusting Seok Sam.)
There's glass.
You said there's a door.
(Because of two brothers who came to the dead end,)
It's glass.
There's a table. We have to go now.
(Jong Kook will be suspected.)
We have to go now.
- We have to go. - Let's go.
(They try to move to the partitioned area again.)
(Running Man members think...)
Hello.
(they look natural if they put their hands in the pockets.)
(They all grabbed a seat.)
You have to place an order.
(Whispering)
We have to order.
(Since all 4 teams are here, Team 1 has to place an order first.)
He's ordering something.
Kwang Soo is too obvious.
He's too obvious.
(2m-tall giant appeared in the cafe again.)
Do I look weird?
Look at me. Do I look weird?
Do we look weird?
Your order.
Do you have money?
Hello. What would you like?
- Peppermint... - Hot chocolate...
(Altering his voice)
(Despite altering his voice,)
- Peppermint... - Hot chocolate...
(people focus on 2m-tall high school student.)
- Thank you. - Is it just one drink?
We're going to share.
Just one, please.
(When two students barely place an order,)
(one customer gets up and approaches them.)
(He approaches Kwang Soo.)
Excuse me.
(He tries to talk to Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.)
(If a customer says their names, they fail.)
Excuse me.
Are you Lee Kwang Soo?
(Careful)
(Pretending not to hear him)
Are you Song Ji Hyo?
You failed the mission. Come back.
(The producer appears.)
(Team Olympiad fails the mission.)
(Oh, it's Lee Kwang Soo and Song Ji Hyo.)
Kwang Soo got caught.
(Laughing)
Right. He got caught.
(Despite various suspicious couples, Kwang Soo got caught.)
- They got caught. - Their mission is over.
They got caught.
Hello.
(Hello.)
- Kwang Soo got caught. - He got caught.
(I'm your fan.)
My goodness.
Kwang Soo. Did you get caught?
(Teasing)
(2m-tall high school student is down after failing the mission.)
(V for victory)
Hey.
I told you not to open your eyes like that.
(Delinquent Ji Hyo appears.)
Lee Kwang Soo got caught.
(Letting Jong Kook know)
(The news about Kwang Soo's arrest is delivered to suspicious people.)
Is it over?
- It's over. - Is it over?
- Did someone get caught? - Yes.
(It's a surprise that they didn't get caught.)
Did Kwang Soo get caught?
(They cheer as the nervous mission ends.)
- He did. - I saw it.
Who got caught?
Kwang Soo got caught.
(Light steps)
- Okay, okay. - That's a relief.
I was wrong to think...
(They survived from the edge of the cliff.)
- Where were you? - I didn't see you. Where were you?
- I didn't see you. - But...
- We were in a room. - You don't know,
(You know what?)
- but you all looked weird. - Really?
- It's really suspicious. - You were really weird.
(All eight of them looked suspicious.)
When you walked in,
I almost called the police.
They looked so weird.
We were surprised.
It was so bright.
(Bright light and crowd were worst conditions.)
We were like, "My goodness."
- And our pants were flapping. - That's funny.
(Thanks to the cafe and customers for cooperation.)
- We all looked weird. - We were all suspicious.
- Let's get in the car. - Get in the car.
It's worth calling the police.
Here's the result of the last mission.
(Announcing the race result)
- I will announce three winners. - Who are they?
(3 winners who will win a prize will be announced first.)
It's based on the number of stamps.
(Among 8 people, the person who collected the most stamps is...)
- Okay. - Oh, stamps.
First place goes to...
(1st place completed 4 courses.)
Yoo Jae Suk.
(It's Yoo Jae Suk.)
- Really? You placed first? - That's amazing.
(The human cultural asset participated in all courses.)
- Me? - Is it an individual play?
- He played a lot. - Yes.
(2nd place who will also receive a prize with 1st place is...)
Second place goes to...
Ji Suk Jin, Kim Jong Kook and Yang Se Chan.
(Suk Jin, Se Chan, and Jong Kook placed 2nd.)
- Oh, really? - Me too?
- That's awesome. - I didn't know.
We'll give these four people a prize.
(All 4 people will receive a prize.)
So Min will purchase the prize tomorrow.
(So Min will buy the prize at the duty-free shop.)
- Am I buying them tomorrow? - Yes.
- Okay. - Goodness.
Now, I have to announce the penalty.
(Announcing the penalty team)
Do we receive the penalty as a team?
(While only one team is nervous, the penalty is revealed.)
Yes.
It's an opening penalty.
(There will be an opening related penalty in a month.)
Lately, the opening penalty's getting weird.
(The opening penalty which they hate the most will be carried out.)
It's getting weird.
- It's getting really weird. - It's very childish.
(They're complaining.)
- You have to come early. - You have to come early.
- It's a hassle. - It's troublesome.
(It's ruined.)
- It's such a hassle. - It's troublesome.
Jae Suk and Suk Jin's Team Human Cultural Asset...
(Announcing the team money to determine the penalty)
has negative 655 dollars.
We spent a lot.
Team Asst. Manager Ha and the New Recruit...
kept 10 dollars.
(Team Running Trading Company didn't spend at all.)
Team Newlyweds has negative 314 dollars.
Next, Team Olympiad...
has negative 1,212 dollars.
So they will have the opening penalty.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo will receive a penalty.)
- Lee Kwang Soo. Seriously... - Come on.
That's the end of Part Two of Jeju Island Special.
(The happy Jeju Island trip is over.)
Thank you.
(The next day)
This place is really big.
(Duty free shop in Jungmun, Seogwipo)
I didn't know there was a duty free in south of Jeju Island.
(Shopping completes the trip.)
I should pick what best suits them.
(So Min chooses the prize for the winners.)
I heard lately Suk Jin enjoys wine.
(Wine for Suk Jin who finally opened his eyes for alcohol)
This is perfect for Jae Suk.
(Sweet snacks for Jae Suk who loves snacks)
Well...
I'll get cosmetics for Se Chan and Jong Kook.
(With gift shopping, Jeju Island Special ends.)
I'll make sure to deliver them to Seoul.
- Fall, the season for food... - It's food.
(It's fall, the season of delicacies.)
- Okay! - Nice.
- Old restaurants. - Old restaurants.
(Old restaurant tour in Seoul)
- Bo Mi! - It's Nam Joo.
(Famous food lover idols, Bo Mi and Nam Joo)
- They eat so much. - It's SEVENTEEN.
(People you want to eat with, Hoshi and Mingyu)
- Nam Chang Hee. - It's Soo Dragon!
(People you want to feed, Kim Soo Yong and Nam Chang Hee)
(Find the real old restaurant in Seoul with history.)
It shows their history.
If Soo Yong and Suk Jin go, it's an old restaurant.
It's 200 years old.
We have to go to Jongno.
(No area...)
(or menu...)
- 50 years in Myeongdong. - It's here.
(is set.)
- I love Pyongyang naengmyeon. - How old is it?
Excuse me. How old is your restaurant?
(They must cast the place themselves.)
When did you open the restaurant?
We should go here.
(Hangover soup with 84 years of history)
We must try the gukbap with history.
It's 100 years old.
This is 49-year-old ramyeon, So Min.
(Ramyeon with 49 years of history)
- It's younger than me? - Wait a minute.
(The older the restaurant is, the younger they become.)
(They fight to eat...)
- Hey! - Are you opening mine?
(and to reduce their ages.)
Stop it.
(What's the result of the old restaurant tour in Seoul?)
- Awesome. - Let's go!
(Journal of Old Restaurant)