(It's a summer day with a heatwave.)
(Oil Tank Culture Park)
Hello.
- Hello.
Good morning.
- Wang Soo.
- What?
I heard Wang Soo was Kwang Soo's
childhood nickname.
I just told you about it in private.
Why would you say that?
Were you called Wang Soo?
- My family called me like that.
- Why?
Today's about superpowers.
Welcome to the entrance ceremony
of Running Man Superpower School.
All right.
Today, you are the seniors
of Superpower School.
I want you to be good mentors for
the freshmen who are joining soon.
- So this is the entrance ceremony.
- We are mentors indeed.
I'm not sure
what our superpowers are yet.
(A few hours ago,
Room of Superpowers)
(Kwang Soo walks into the Room of
Superpowers, full of expectation.)
This is just too cool.
Just open it.
(What is my superpower?)
What is my superpower?
"You are an invisible man."
"Doing mosquito dance..."
(You're an invisible man.
Doing mosquito dance...)
(Mosquito dance?)
"You are an invisible man."
"Doing mosquito dance,"
"sing, 'You didn't see me,
you didn't see me'."
"Sing, 'You didn't see me,
(I'm supposed to do this?)
"And put on the invisibility cloak."
"Then you will stay invisible
until you take off the cloak."
A giant mosquito bit my foot
(I'm supposed to do this
in the Superpower School Race?)
It was itchy, but I put up with it
I give up.
(He decides to give up
after much consideration.)
(He drinks the potion
that gives him a superpower.)
(Once he sings,
he gets his superpower.)
Do I have to sing now?
Yes, please.
This is humiliating.
I feel like I'm standing here naked.
It's been over 10 years.
(He shudders thinking about
his specialty from 10 years ago.)
(He pulls himself together
and tries to focus.)
This is crazy.
(This is crazy.)
- I will give you the cloak.
- What?
- This is the cloak?
- It's an invisibility cloak.
(This is the invisibility cloak?)
(I'm an invisible man.
Please pretend you didn't see me.)
(The cloak has an earnest request
of an invisible man on it.)
(What's this?)
I thought it'd be something cool.
(Even though it's not very cool...)
You didn't see me, you didn't see me
(Once he becomes invisible, he is
protected from all superpowers.)
(Kwang Soo is invisible now.)
(Invisible Man)
(The cloak makes him invisible and
protects him from all superpowers.)
(- That was so cool.
- You deserve your award.)
(His superpower comes with
embarrassment.)
You deserve your award.
"Your superpower lets you
summon a bodyguard."
"Raise your arms overhead..."
(She laughs.)
(Embarrassment comes
before a bodyguard does.)
Hold on.
This is... Hold on.
This...
(This is why the members fear
Superpower Special.)
This is driving me crazy.
I'm supposed to do this
in front of many people?
- Yes.
- For three minutes?
(She drinks her potion,
fighting embarrassment.)
(Summon a bodyguard by raising
your arms overhead and singing.)
(However, bodyguards are only
for defense purposes.)
Ta-da.
(Bodyguard Summoner)
(Your superpower allows you
to summon a person.)
This is embarrassing.
I'll leave.
See you later.
(Here comes...)
(Haha, the perfect member
for this theme.)
(He is already immersed.)
(He looks like
he is in his element.)
(No one beats him
when it comes to themes like this.)
"You are Captain Gravity."
"To attack a member
out of your sight,"
"drop two apples..."
"and shout, 'Gravity!'"
"It'll put 5kg sandbags..."
"around the wrists and ankles
of the member,"
"which will hinder his or her
movement for three minutes."
Gravity, gravity...
This word is hard to remember.
Gravity.
What does it mean?
- It's a pulling force.
- What?
Exactly.
(His vocabulary can't keep up with
his enthusiasm.)
I see. That's what it means.
To gravity.
(He drinks to the word
he just learned.)
(Groaning)
(Gravity fills my body.)
Gravity!
(Captain Gravity)
(It gives a member of your choice
20kg of sandbags.)
"You are the Sorcerer
of Five Senses."
"Hold up your hands
to your mouth..."
"and shout, 'Jong Kook has
donkey ears!'"
"It will let you eavesdrop
for three minutes..."
"and find out
a member's superpower."
I always get a useless superpower.
Why did you give me this?
It's completely useless.
"You are Ttuk-nos."
"Snap your fingers..."
(Snap your fingers and sing to make
3 members freeze for a minute.)
Completely turn me over
Like that?
All right. Let's welcome
our freshmen.
I heard their voices,
and it seems like...
Suk Jin is one of them.
I'm not sure if he's okay
with being a freshman.
Congratulations.
(Congratulations
on entering our school!)
(One of the freshmen is
a bit too excited.)
Hey, we're not doing that.
(Their superpowers make them
even sillier.)
- We're your seniors.
- We're not doing that.
(Someone definitely looks
more like a senior.)
I'll never get used to this.
(Running Man's 10th anniversary
is celebrated with two guests.)
Hello.
Hello, Seniors.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- It's been a long time.
- They're so cute.
- They're really cute.
- Hello.
- Welcome to the school.
- Thank you.
Han Na, come over here.
What am I?
Sang Yeob, come over here.
- What am I?
- Love your classmates!
- Come here.
- I asked, what am I?
- One, two.
You're an old man
with a passion for studying.
- Why am I a freshman?
- You're a returning student.
These five are freshmen
at Superpower School.
According to Suk Jin's
superpower evaluation results,
he failed to move on
to the next grade and is held back.
(Suk Jin is held back.)
(Even with his phoenix superpower,)
(he got eliminated
three times in a row.)
(No matter how good
his superpower is,)
(he always ends up
being a race starter.)
(He has bad
superpower using skills.)
(In the end, he gets held back.)
He is held back?
That's why you're a freshman.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
He's held back.
As the freshman representative,
- Suk Jin will recite a pledge.
- It feels real.
Seniors, please sit down.
It feels more like
a principal's speech.
It feels...
Here.
- Love your classmates!
- Get the chairs.
- Love your school!
- Here.
- Hello.
- Hi, Sang Yeob.
Here's one more.
- Take a seat.
- Let's sit down.
All right.
The freshman pledge.
- We don't have to do it.
- It's what we have to do.
- Please look at us.
- We'll repeat after you.
- It's what we have to do.
(The repeater already
makes a mistake.)
All right. You guys don't know
how to use magic, do you?
(Arrogant)
- What?
- Superpowers...
- Is it superpowers?
- It's superpowers.
He doesn't know anything.
Let Sang Yeob do it instead.
He can't do anything right.
He knows even less than I do.
- So it's superpowers.
- Just read out what's written.
- He's blushing.
- Just do what you're told to do.
Just recite the pledge.
- What's wrong with him?
- Why did he say, "magic"?
The freshman pledge.
- The freshman pledge.
"As the new students entering
Superpower School in 2020,"
"we will learn from
our seniors' ambitions..."
"and work hard to develop
our own superpowers,"
"so that we can use
our superpowers..."
"in an autonomous way."
All right.
"Freshman representative
Ji Suk Jin."
Lee Sang Yeob.
Yang Se Chan.
Kang Han Na.
Jeon So Min.
That's our freshman pledge.
(We will work hard.)
- We'll work hard.
- All right.
- This is touching.
Salute.
I used to be like them too.
- I used my superpower well.
- Good job.
(The freshmen are given
superpowers too.)
Hello.
(Freshman Se Chan enters.)
(Excited)
I should drink my potion first.
I've been waiting for this moment.
"You are the Poison Needle
Sorcerer."
"Shoot a member's name tag,"
"and he or she will be paralyzed
after 15 seconds."
(The paralysis lasts
for 30 seconds,)
(preventing the member
from any action except rolling.)
(The computer graphics
are not in yet.)
(The freshman is too excited
to wait for the computer graphics.)
(Here come the computer graphics.)
(He enjoys the graphics
to the fullest.)
My name is Se Chan.
I'm a shooter.
(Poison Needle Sorcerer)
(A poison needle paralyzes you
after 15 seconds,)
(only allowing you to roll
for 30 seconds.)
(The next freshman is So Min.)
"You are the Wizard
of Push and Pull."
(Giggling)
Is this really a superpower?
"Shout, 'Go, go, push!'"
"at a member,"
"and he or she will be pushed away."
"Shout, 'Come, come, pull!'"
"and he or she will be
pulled toward you."
"As soon as you breathe,
the member can move freely."
"So try to hold your breath
as long as you can."
(Enthusiastic)
Go, go, push!
Like that? Or...
(After fancy preparatory moves...)
Come, come, come!
(The spell is wrong.)
Oh, is it "pull"?
- It's "push" and "pull".
- Right. "Push" and "pull".
Okay. This is nice.
Will this give me a superpower?
(She drinks her potion to become
the Witch of Push and Pull.)
Go, go,
push!
(The cameraman is pushed away.)
(Her superpower is so effective
that it even affects the cameramen.)
Okay, I like it.
Can I try it one more time?
Come, come,
pull!
(Push or pull a member
by saying spells.)
"You are..."
"the Past Life Summoner."
"When you're eliminated,"
"lift the bundle..."
This is it.
I still...
have a death.
(His spell is wrong.)
(Past Life Summoner)
(You can be born again
in the form of your past life.)
Mirror, mirror,
who do I look like?
"Is it wrong to fall in love?"
(Doing an impression turns you into
him or her for three minutes.)
Drop the beat.
(After saying, "Drop the beat",
dance for 30 seconds.)
(Everyone who sees you dance
will go blind...)
(and have trouble seeing
for a minute.)
- You've all been given superpowers.
- Yes.
Running Man's 10th anniversary
special is only 3 weeks away.
That day,
we will go live...
- at the end of the race.
- On a Sunday?
What?
(A live broadcast
to celebrate the 10th anniversary)
A live broadcast?
For the next two weeks,
to decide who will be penalized live
on our 10th anniversary special,
we will have two races chosen
by our viewers as their favorites.
Our viewers' number one favorite
turns out to be...
War of Superpowers.
- This was a fun one.
- I enjoyed it too.
The Keeper of Time!
(The Superhero Race
led the show into glory.)
(It was probably too childish
for the average viewer.)
(The race featured
B-rated computer graphics.)
(The viewers asked,
and we answered.)
(10th Anniversary Specials)
(It will lead to a live show
on July 12.)
Therefore, we welcome you
to the Superpower School Race.
The last man standing
will become the final winner.
The one chosen by the winner
will receive the penalty...
during the live show.
(The winner will choose 1 person
to receive the penalty.)
(Then we need to win
no matter what.)
The guests will receive a prize
if they win...
or a penalty if they lose.
The details will be revealed
at the end of the race.
Before we begin the actual race,
you'll compete in
a preliminary mission.
You will split into 5 teams of 2...
that consist of
a mentor and mentee.
Points will be handed out
depending on how you do.
The points you receive...
will affect the number of times...
you'll be allowed
to use your superpowers.
So doing well in this mission
will be crucial.
- Got it.
- The mentors must do well.
- How about this?
- It's all down to the mentors.
We've already
chosen your teams for you.
- What?
- Really?
Team One.
Yoo Jae Suk...
and Kang Han Na.
- Han Na.
- I hope we get along.
- Be good to him.
- Strong Han Na, Weak Han Na.
Han Na, come this way.
She seems like an excellent student.
Han Na's finally moving out
from under my shadow.
I should use this chance
to learn from the best.
- She was always...
- Team Two.
We have a good chance of winning.
I'm partnered with a true mentor.
(Superpower School)
We're playing the limbo game.
- I'm not good at that.
- We're not on the flexible side.
My mentor, come this way.
Your mentor?
Who's the mentor?
- Kwang Soo is.
- We...
He's not directly above us though.
- But...
- I remember my freshman years.
He's the senior
because he joined before us.
Does that look like
an ordinary pole to you?
- Kwang-tor.
- Kwang-tor?
(He's the easiest type to tease.)
- Kwang-tor.
- Are you saying...
that this is no ordinary limbo game?
Please let us know.
If you tell us in advance...
Consider the bigger picture here.
- As in what?
- See the paint over there?
(There are five colors of paint
on the other side of the room.)
Will we be playing the game
with paint on our faces?
(No way.)
- I see you don't know.
- Are you sure?
- We'll be holding the paint.
But someone could slip and get hurt.
That's the fun of it.
(Getting injured is fun?)
He's a clueless mentor.
- Ji Hyo.
- That's the fun of it.
- I bet she's clueless.
- Ji Hyo.
- She won't know a thing.
- What? Of course, I know.
- She doesn't know anything.
- She's clueless.
- Then...
Ji Hyo, do you know
the rule of this game?
- The rule? It's a limbo game.
- She doesn't know.
See? She doesn't know a thing.
- It's a limbo game.
- That's right.
You will compete in a mission...
to earn more chances
to use your superpower.
The game is called
Walking with a Third Eye.
The runner will put on gloves
and a blindfold.
After spinning
five times on the spot,
he or she will try...
and plant handprints
beyond the limbo pole.
Each team will start
with five points.
You will earn an extra point
for every 2m,
but a point will be deducted...
if you fail to move past
the starting line.
You will earn two points
for a handprint on the floor.
Two points will be deducted though
if you place them elsewhere.
The points you receive
will determine...
the number of times
you can use your superpower.
- Right.
- Can we help our teammates?
No, you must not talk.
You're not allowed
to guide your teammate.
What's there to worry about
when we have superpowers?
You idiots.
But what's with the third eye?
(The game begins with Haha
fully absorbed in his character.)
- Not both hands?
- No, just the one.
And you have to spin on the spot.
- In university...
- Gosh.
- So Min, you're up.
- You've got this.
- You're ready.
- Put on your blindfold.
You can do this.
Do I put this on her?
Do you guys major in sports?
- Is this comfortable?
- He must major in sports.
- Are you good?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Ready!
- So Min, your hair looks nice.
- Get set.
(The goal is to place a handprint
the furthest as possible.)
- It's better to speed up.
- That's right.
- One.
- Faster.
- Faster!
- Two.
- Three.
- Faster.
- Pick up the pace.
- Faster, So Min.
- Five.
- Off you go.
Go ahead.
- Get going already!
- The game ends with a handprint.
(So Min takes cautious steps.)
Watch out for the camera.
(Watch out for the camera.)
Beware of the camera.
(Is it this way?)
12, 13.
(Why is she headed this way?)
Who's there?
(Swipe!)
(Jae Suk let her hand
touch his face.)
This is the spot.
She touched Jae Suk's face
right here.
- Over here.
- You smacked a mentor.
Place your handprint here.
- Go on.
- How dare you smack a mentor.
So where her handprint landed...
That was hilarious.
She came a long way though.
What's fascinating is that
I touched something sharp.
Something sharp?
- It was his protruding teeth.
- It was really sharp.
- His protruding teeth.
- What do you mean it was sharp?
You look like Young Gu or Ppak Gu.
- Ppak Gu.
- Ppak Gu?
Yes, Ppak Gu.
- This isn't at all pleasant.
- I know.
Haha, please let go of him.
- Let's go!
- You can't say anything.
I'm dizzy.
It does make you dizzy.
(After spinning just once?)
- Two.
- Gosh, I'm dizzy.
- Five.
- My head's spinning.
- I'm too dizzy.
- Off he goes.
There he goes.
- He's off.
- Gosh, I'm dizzy.
(Where is he headed?)
- He's off.
- Gosh, I'm dizzy.
(He's completely off course.)
My world's spinning.
- What now?
- He's going that way.
I thought he'd come this way.
I'm too dizzy.
- What's this?
- You made contact!
(His turn ends
under the flashy light.)
- The light.
- Over there.
What on earth?
- I thought I was walking forward.
- I mean...
The Keeper of Time!
The mentees look like
they need guidance.
- I can't believe I headed that way.
- You did well.
And go.
Guys, please step back.
- Gosh.
- That's fast. Go for it.
Three.
- Four.
- Goodness.
You can't clap.
(After five quick spins,
she heads off.)
(Searching route)
(How she does will decide...)
(the number of times Jae Suk
can use his superpower.)
(What?)
She has a good balance.
(Is she already
playing the limbo game?)
(You're not quite there yet.)
She's already playing
the limbo game.
(An error has occurred.)
No way.
She's doing a great job.
Right there.
(She can feel where the mat ends.)
Just a little to the side.
To the side.
(She thinks she's
at the end of the mat.)
- Han Na, no!
- How did I do?
- Is she done?
- Tell me how I did.
- Why did you stop there?
- Where am I?
That was awesome.
- Why...
- I knew she'd fail.
Flimsy as always.
You failed.
(Jae Suk and Han Na
score 9 points in total.)
The mentees can't seem
to do this right.
Unbelievable.
I should show them how it's done.
I bet he'll do a good job.
Why are you all bad at this game?
Get ready.
(Se Chan will represent
and show them how it's done.)
Three.
(Se Chan is good
when it comes to games.)
(It's why everyone
watches silently.)
Unbelievable.
I should show them how it's done.
(Will he able to proudly
represent the mentees?)
(What?)
(He bows down to his seniors.)
(It serves you right
for being overly confident.)
Oh, no. He fell there.
I was too dizzy.
My world is spinning.
(Are you kidding me?)
I was too dizzy.
I'm not kidding.
(He was able
to make them laugh though.)
Good.
- It's all good.
- I was too dizzy.
It was like
that comedy skit, "Master".
"Get out of here!"
- What on earth was that?
- You looked cool though.
Se Chan, seriously?
(The teams that were tied
played again.)
Jae Suk and Han Na...
- earned nine points.
- Okay!
With the points you earned,
you can buy how many times
you can use your superpower.
The rule of distribution is simple.
Distribute the numbers
on three cards.
What your mentee picks
will be the mentee's points.
The next card chosen
will be discarded.
- The last one is the mentor's.
- Got it.
Per two points,
you will get an extra chance
to use your superpower.
(4 points equal to 2 extra chances.)
- So Han Na...
- Yes?
You know I never play dirty.
Let's share it fairly.
I'll write 5 and 4.
- 5 and 4.
- 5, 4, and 0?
- I mean...
- Betrayal isn't all that bad.
We have enough points to go around,
- so there's no need to play dirty.
- Right.
- He plays dirty too.
- 5, 4, and 0.
That's right.
5, 4, 0. Which one has 0?
Zero?
Card number one.
Then 5 and 4 respectively.
Card number 1 has 0 written on it?
You seem nervous though.
- Card number 1 has 0?
- You shouldn't choose it.
- Then...
- Yes?
- Please don't.
- Let him have that instead.
She hasn't seen it yet.
She hasn't looked.
I wrote zero on that.
But...
Really?
(Han Na choose card number 1.)
You're really taking that?
- Don't you trust me?
- Take a look.
(Han Na trusted
her instincts instead.)
(9 points!)
(I'm doomed!)
Seriously?
(Jae Suk ends up with 0 points.)
- It's her superpower!
- That leaves him with nothing.
Han Na, you're unbelievable.
- That was insane.
- Did she understand the rule?
Jae Suk, I've got
to hand it to you too.
He has zero points then.
Of course, I trust Jong Kook.
- How can you not?
- I trust you completely.
Just do as I say.
I'll write 0 on card number 2.
On card number 3, I'll write down 4.
- He'll write down four.
- What? Wait. Hold on a second.
4 on card number 3?
I saw him write a zero.
I'll write two on the last one.
- See? It's just like I said.
- You can't show her.
- Wait and see what So Min does.
- "Wait and see."
(We all look forward
to So Min's choice.)
- Is this four?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
You promised, remember?
(Thanks to Jong Kook's honesty,
So Min received 4 points.)
- Please choose the next one.
- You guys are all nice.
This is how we normally are.
- Of course.
- We're one big team here.
Look at her eyes.
Come on.
Choose the right one for me.
- Did you write two on this?
- Yes.
- 0?
- 0. Yes.
You can throw one away.
You really are...
(He said number 1 was 2 points,
but she threw away number 1.)
(His anger explodes.)
- That's right.
- He's really angry.
Run away, So Min.
That's how So Min is.
This is what you meant.
She's like a poison mushroom.
- I told you.
- The strongest member came out.
I should've done this.
My head hurts already.
All of them are zero, but...
All of them are?
- He's going to do 4, 0, 0 for sure.
- Can I see it?
Yes. Take 2 and leave 2.
I'll show it to you.
- Seriously.
- You're going to write 2 and 2?
You're going to let him see you
write it down?
You're going to let me
see you write it. Show me.
(He will write it down
in front of him.)
- It's true.
- He's writing 2, 0, 2.
Seriously.
(Did he keep his promise?)
- And then he's mixing it.
- He's mixing it up.
- It's like he's doing magic.
(It looks like he's mixing them up.)
Are you mixing them up?
- Hey, you fool.
- Hey.
- There are numbers in the back.
- There are numbers in the back?
- There are...
You fool. Stop mixing them.
I showed it to you.
Then...
I really showed it to you.
What's wrong?
Really? He's telling the truth.
- I'm telling the truth.
- I thought he had other cards...
hidden in his pocket.
- No way.
- Then it's 2, 0, 2.
- Yes.
- It's 2, 0, 2.
I saw him write 2, 0, 2.
- That's what he wrote.
- I showed it to you.
I saw it too.
I'll take 2 then.
- I'll take 2.
- Okay.
(What?)
(Why does it say 4 points here?)
Okay!
- You are...
- Seriously.
- You're too much.
- He overthought it.
He overthought it.
My goodness.
(The results of the other teams'
distributions)
(Han Na can use it 5 times.)
(So Min, Suk Jin, Haha,
Se Chan can use it 3 times.)
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Kwang Soo,
Sang Yeob, Ji Hyo can use it once.)
The results are interesting...
because all the seniors have
zero points except for Haha.
You guys have really good juniors.
- They are really...
- That's right.
Let's continue to overcome them!
- This is the worst.
- Let's go, juniors!
The seniors need to work harder.
As a result,
Han Na has received four more...
and has a total of five chances.
The remaining members have 3 chances
or 1 chance.
- I only have 1 chance.
- We'll move on...
- to the location for the race.
- Yes!
Goodness, Kang Han Na.
(Let's go to the location
for the final race.)
- Good job.
- Goodness.
Good job, Han Na.
- Who, me?
- It's nice and cool here.
- You did a good job.
- Oh, for getting 9 to 0?
You did well.
Jae Suk had a weird look
on his face.
- I see.
- It was a good game.
We need to choose a representative
among the second years.
- The rules are...
- What are they?
When you get off the bus,
the juniors will...
write down the name
of their favorite senior...
and give us the ballot.
- The juniors will do that?
- Yes.
The juniors will do that.
Is there some type of benefit
to the senior?
- The senior chosen...
- A benefit.
as the representative will be given
another chance.
- Okay.
- Yes.
We should hear the reasons why
we need to choose them.
- If we look at it like this...
- Really?
- That's right.
- Kwang Soo, I choose you.
As you all know, I gave Han Na...
nine points.
- That's right. Wait.
- You tried to fake it.
- You were trying to fool me.
- I'm talking about the results.
Guys. Hey, everyone.
- Who should be the representative?
- It's the representative.
- Let's vote for one person.
- I agree.
The way that I see it,
I think that
the votes should go to...
Excuse me.
Are you the leader of the juniors?
- Yes, I am.
- Did they choose you?
- Yes, they did.
- I'm sorry,
but the principal
should stay out of it.
Stop speaking nonsense.
- The students are talking.
- The way that I see it...
- Everyone.
- Yes?
Choose someone who's a bit slow.
- Someone who's slow?
- Someone slow?
- Someone who's easy to manipulate.
- Hey.
- They should have good character.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes? Did you call me?
- Honestly,
you debuted after me
as a comedian, right?
- That's right.
- Right.
- Keep that in mind.
- Who's the junior?
- Pardon?
Why are you speaking casually
to your senior?
- Suk Jin.
- Who's the junior?
Suk Jin, don't write my name down.
(Suk Jin,
don't write my name down.)
- Oh, my.
- Excuse me.
Let's do it together.
Hang out with us.
- Hey!
- Let's play together.
- I choose Ji Hyo.
Don't you know that the juniors
have come together?
- I'm leading them.
- We haven't done so yet.
Who are you leading?
We aren't being led yet.
- We aren't being led yet.
- Who said we are?
Juniors, raise your hand
if you will join me!
- He's making me feel uncomfortable.
- What surprises me...
is that he's a junior like us.
- It's uncomfortable, right?
- But...
- It surprises me.
- It's for our benefit.
If you know my superpower,
- First off,
- will you support me?
- we must choose someone weak.
- Tell us.
- I can help you.
- How?
- I can give you more power.
- Power?
- Stop lying.
- It's a lie.
- Has there ever been...
- I'm telling the truth.
something like that on Running Man?
- He's going to be a burden.
- No, that's not true.
- He's talking nonsense.
- I'm telling the truth.
- Show us a motion about your power.
- A motion.
- A motion about your power.
- I'll show you something.
- A motion related to it.
- Here.
- Your superpower.
- This is... Goodness.
- What is that?
- Is it Thanos?
- It must be Thanos.
- It's an offensive power.
- This is...
- He must kill at least half of us.
- Can he get rid of us?
- Show us a motion.
- This is mine.
I say something and do this
to the other person.
(I will help you.)
Forget it. Forget about it.
- This is yours?
- Lee Kwang Soo, out!
- Take him out.
- Can you tell he's a liar now?
- I don't believe him.
- Did you see that?
- Forget him.
- How can you not believe me?
- Let's ignore that one.
- Yes, of course.
(Thudding)
- Gosh, that surprised me.
- Me too.
Did you see that? Everyone was
surprised, but I kept my cool.
- Hold on.
- You were the one to stay cool.
We need some tissues.
Jae Suk peed his pants.
(The elections for the class
representative is filled with lies.)
- Am I wrong?
- Gosh, Kwang Soo.
I found out something important.
- He's trying to promote himself.
- Among the superpowers,
there are some
that will help others and...
- some that will help themselves.
- I have a power...
that will help everyone.
Don't you think our conversation
is really funny?
He has a great superpower.
(They suddenly broke out
of character.)
- When he's 45.
- We're all being so serious.
- We're wearing the same outfits.
- Some of us are in our 50s.
- Han Na, I'm telling you...
- What superpower?
- What R Coin?
- if I help you, you'll win.
- Really?
- Of course.
- You have to fill in your votes.
- Did you write it down?
- Yes.
- Are you done?
- Yes. Should we hand it in?
- Write it down.
Here. I wrote it down.
- Okay. I will announce the results.
- Okay.
The first vote goes to...
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes!
- Who voted for him?
- Who chose Jae Suk?
- Thank you.
- It must've been Han Na.
- Who voted for him?
- The second vote goes to...
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Okay!
- Who chose him?
- I will help whoever chose me.
- Who chose Kwang Soo?
- I'll do this for them.
- He can't be the representative.
- My goodness.
- The third vote goes to...
Haha.
- Someone voted for Haha?
- Who did?
The fourth vote goes to...
Yoo Jae Suk.
(Yoo Jae Suk, 2 votes)
The fifth vote goes to Yoo Jae Suk.
- I knew it.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Who voted for him?
- Please help us.
- Han Na.
I didn't expect more than two votes.
Jong Kook's
true feelings just came out.
Not a single person voted for me.
(Not a single person voted for me.)
You're right.
My voice is coming back.
I'm glad you're so in character
right now.
- My goodness.
- It's like we really have powers.
My goodness.
We're going someplace far.
Aren't we going to Ilsan?
The venue we had intended to go to
got canceled because of COVID-19,
so we'll have our race at
Tanhyeon SBS.
(Tanhyeon SBS has become the mecca
of superpowers through many races.)
(The Superpower Race
will be held here.)
During our 10 years, the fans chose
this as something they want to see.
It's meaningful.
- Yes.
- We finally get to use our powers.
It will be meaningful to win today.
It is the War of Superpowers:
The End Game.
- The End Game.
It will be a huge honor
to be the winner this week.
- It's an honor.
- Seriously.
Use your powers to rip off
the other members' name tags.
The winner will be
the last man standing.
However, you are unaware
of the other members' powers,
so you have to be careful
while doing the race.
I'm sure there will be a power
that lets you reflect.
You can use your power according
to how many chances you got earlier.
Also, there are tickets for
the Room of Reinforcement...
hidden all around the venue.
(Room of Reinforcement Ticket)
(Choose 1 member
and bring him or her with you.)
If you find these tickets,
you can choose one person
to go into the room with...
and forcibly summon them.
Then you can use the room
in a group of two.
- In groups of two.
- Both of them must get stronger.
If you succeed in
the hit-or-miss mission in the room,
both members can add more chances
to use their superpower.
Even if you fail, you don't lose
the chances you already have.
- You have to go.
- However,
you can't rip off another member's
name tag while in this room.
- In the Room of Reinforcement?
- Yes.
Please go to the location
of the race.
- Let's go!
- I'm getting excited.
I should try to win.
- It's been 10 years.
- Let's try to win.
Oh, my gosh.
(The Number of Times
They Can Use Their Superpower)
I really want to win this one.
It's been 10 years since we had
a superpower race.
If it wasn't for
our 10th anniversary,
I wouldn't want to win as much.
(Bodyguard Summoner)
I'm so curious as to what
the other members' superpowers are.
So Min.
You have a cape on.
(So Min. You have a cape on.)
Yoo Jae Suk. Yoo Jae Suk.
Jae Suk. I can really...
bring anyone you'd like
in front of you.
Can you see this?
You can figure out what kind of
superpower I have, right?
(Ttuk-nos, Witch of Push and Pull)
Is that a ring?
(Is that a ring?)
Is he really Thanos?
He must really be Thanos.
You kind of...
Oh, are you Gollum?
(Oh, are you Gollum?)
- What?
- Are you Gollum?
You must be Gollum.
My gosh. That brat.
He's Gollum. I should run away.
Back in the day,
if you had one of these, you'd be
the most popular kid in town.
My name is Se Chan. I'm a shooter.
(Serious)
Excuse me.
(He sees an employee passing by.)
I'm doing something cool.
You're looking at me
like I'm childish,
but I'm focusing
on what I have to do today.
- I see.
- You look the coolest.
Thank you.
We'll start the race now.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Race start.
(Superpower School Race,
War of Superpowers: The End Game)
Don't I look cool?
Don't I look like Sailor Moon?
(Don't I look like Sailor Moon?)
(Transformation)
(A side-effect of superpowers:
You get too into character.)
(In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!)
Don't I look like Sailor Moon?
(In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!)
I'm going to use my superpower
like this.
What are you carrying around
with you?
What?
What are you carrying?
I found something.
(Exclaiming)
Hey.
(Another patient suffering from
the side-effects of superpowers)
- What is that?
- It's a strong weapon.
I can get rid of you in one shot.
What is that? You really
have some type of gadget.
It must be a bomb.
(It must be a bomb.)
- A bomb?
- It's a bomb.
Does he have a bomb on his wrist?
- Do you know what this is?
- It's a water gun.
(Now he sees what it is.)
A water gun?
It's a water gun.
(They are being cautious as they
don't know about the superpowers.)
Once you're shot,
- Gosh, what's that?
- you'll be eliminated immediately.
- What's your superpower?
- What's that, Suk Jin?
- Is it some kind of device?
- Are you a peddler?
- What?
Hey, once I open this,
you guys will die.
- I think he's a vendor.
- No.
- You're a vendor, right?
He's a peddler.
- I'm not here to sell stuff.
- I think...
- he will sell this later.
- Are you a peddler?
(Sang Yeob shows up
with something in his hand.)
- Hey.
- Wait. He has a mirror.
He has a mirror.
(Sang Yeob is caught with the mirror
for his superpower.)
- I just used it to check my face.
- What is it for?
Don't be ridiculous.
Once I open this...
and throw it down, you all will die.
Are you Spider-Man?
Do you want me to open this?
I'm going to open this.
Do you want me to do it?
I guess he has
packed lunch in there.
- Should I open it?
- Go ahead.
- I will...
- I'm going to open it.
I'll buy two.
- I want 2.
- Do you want 2?
- It's not something you can buy.
- I'll buy two books.
Once you touch it, you will die.
- I'm sure Suk Jin is a vendor.
- He's a vendor.
- Your superpower is selling.
- Why is my weapon so heavy?
His superpower requires
a lot of work.
I think I'm the coolest one here.
(Satisfied)
I should find the ticket
to the Room of Reinforcement.
(I should find the ticket
to the Room of Reinforcement.)
- Suk Jin. What's that?
- Hey.
- Feeling!
- Intuition!
- Cross!
What's that?
Honestly, my superpower
isn't that cool.
But it looks perfect on you.
Wish me good luck.
- It's not so cool.
- You know it, right?
- It's not cool, but my power...
- There's Jong Kook.
- He's wearing gloves.
- Why is he wearing gloves?
(He looks charismatic
with the gloves on.)
Are you upset?
What are the gloves for?
My superpower is...
beating people to death.
- It's not a superpower.
- Hey.
You can do that
even without a superpower.
My superpower is
beating people to death.
- He has a package.
- Drop the beat!
(Drop the beat!)
Drop the beat!
- What was that?
- Did you use your superpower?
(Did she use her superpower?)
(She suddenly starts to dance.)
- What is she doing?
- It has something to do with dance.
(Feeling nervous)
- What? Did she use her power?
- I guess there's something.
(She uses her superpower
of Charming Dancer.)
"You're Charming Dancer."
"If you shout, 'Drop the beat'..."
"and dance to music for 30 seconds,"
"all the members who watch it..."
"will be blinded."
"And their vision becomes narrow
for one minute."
(Charming Dancer)
(Suk Jin who watched her dance...)
(has to wear swimming goggles
for 1 minute for narrow vision.)
(Charming Dancer blinds them all
with her dance moves.)
(They all get narrow vision.)
- What?
- I can't see.
- I can see just a little.
- I can barely see.
What is this?
One minute?
(Right at that moment)
(Han Na is attacking?)
What was that?
(She rips off Suk Jin's
name tag immediately.)
- Who was that?
- What just happened? Suk Jin.
- What?
- The race starter is back.
- Hey!
- Already?
- This is...
- Who took off my name tag?
Suk Jin, you're out.
I'm out?
Hey, we've just started.
- Is it over?
- You're so mean.
- Hey! Han Na!
- Seriously?
Is it really over for him?
What was that?
It's been less than five minutes.
Suk Jin, put down your bundle
and get some rest.
But this is for our
10th year anniversary.
My goodness.
Kang Han Na.
Han Na, I'll get back
at you for this.
This is nice.
(Charming Dancer feels proud
after eliminating him.)
What's your superpower?
(The four superheroes are
in front of the cafeteria.)
- You're Thanos.
- Right. He's Thanos.
- He can eliminate us immediately.
- You will snap your fingers.
With a snap.
It's a random choice. Once he snaps
his fingers, one of us will die.
Go ahead and try it.
Let's see what happens.
No. I can't use it now.
My superpower is just too strong.
- You might get hurt.
- Before I rip off your name tag.
Come here, guys. Are you ready?
- Are you ready?
- We're ready.
Shall we begin?
(What?)
(Shrieking)
You're...
- Hey, you're...
- We are three superheroes.
Do you really want to do that
to fight against me?
- We are three superheroes.
- Are you ready?
Let's go!
(Thump)
- It must hurt.
- Are you all right?
(Thump)
- It must hurt.
- Are you all right?
- Cut.
- Are you okay?
Okay.
If you're being like this,
I'll use my strong superpower.
- Okay?
- Jae Suk.
Se Chan.
- You're going to take his side?
- Se Chan!
Se Chan!
(Combined)
Let's go, So Min.
(They don't want to lose.)
What is she doing?
(Embarrassed)
- We are very strong.
- Okay.
- We can do this. Haha, we can win.
- You should give up.
Se Chan betrayed us. All right.
I'll remember that.
(Bodyguard Summoner Ji Hyo
shows up right at the moment.)
- We should form an alliance.
- Seriously.
I bet you have
an amazing superpower.
(Right at the moment...)
- What?
- What is that?
What's going on?
(Something shows up
all of a sudden.)
- What's going on?
- What is it?
(Suk Jin has become a king?)
(His superpower is...)
(Past Life Summoner)
(If you shout "I still have a life"
lifting up a bundle,)
(you will be born again
in the form of your past life.)
(Suk Jin can be born again
in the form of his past life.)
(Suk Jin got eliminated
by Charming Dancer,)
(but he had a faint smile on
for a reason.)
I still...
have a life.
I'm born again.
(He's reincarnated
as a king of the Joseon Dynasty.)
- What's going on?
- You brats.
What's all this?
- What is he doing?
- What's going on?
Did you not watch the movie
that features Jang Dong Gun?
Jae Suk.
Poison Needle Sorcerer
used his superpower against you.
You will be paralyzed in 15 seconds.
(Did Jae Suk get
a poisonous sting?)
- Who used it against me?
- 15, 14, 13...
Hurry. Let's follow Jae Suk!
- Ji Hyo, hurry. Ji Hyo, come here.
- I'm coming.
- 11.
- Ji Hyo, hurry and run.
5, 4,
- 3, 2...
- I will use it.
Completely turn me over
(Completely turn me over!)
(Jae Suk used his superpower
before he got paralyzed.)
All right. Pause for a moment.
Jae Suk used his superpower.
What is it?
(Jae Suk's superpower is...)
(Ttuk-nos)
(Snap your fingers and sing,
"Completely turn me over,")
(to make 3 members
freeze for a minute.)
Completely turn you over?
(He picks 3 members to freeze.)
(Please don't pick me.)
Good. It's done.
(Jae Suk uses his superpower
to freeze 3 members for a minute.)
- What? I can't move?
- What?
- How long does he stay paralyzed?
- 30 seconds.
There's Ji Hyo.
I can't do anything?
(While all three
of them are frozen...)
What are you doing? What is it?
- What are you doing now?
- Stay still. Attention.
- What do you want?
- What?
- What's going on?
- What is he doing?
You should shoot
a period drama somewhere else.
We're shooting Running Man here.
What are you doing?
- Wait.
- Just stay still.
- Why would he say "attention"?
- Stay put.
Isn't it over yet?
- Stay still!
- Jae Suk is relieved now.
Hang on. I should go to Ji Hyo.
And I will
You can't use your superpower
when you're frozen.
Gosh, no!
- Come here!
- No.
Stop singing.
- Stop it.
- No!
- I have to get rid of you.
No! You can't do this to me.
- Ji Hyo!
- No!
I said no!
- Ji Hyo.
- And I will
- What's happening, Ji Hyo?
And I will!
Hey! I called you!
(Right at the moment!)
- And I will!
- What is this now?
Hey! I called you!
(Her bodyguard shows up
as soon as the pause is over.)
(Your superpower lets you
summon a bodyguard.)
(Summon a bodyguard by raising
your arms overhead and singing.)
(Her bodyguard seems
somewhat weak and timid though.)
Is he her bodyguard?
What's going on?
- What's that song about?
- And I will!
- Hey, my superpower is...
- What's going on?
- What was that?
- What was all that?
- She got a bodyguard.
(While her bodyguard
protects her...)
- Hey!
- I mean...
What was the song about?
(Bodyguard Summoner Ji Hyo
runs away as fast as she can.)
Why did you not come?
I almost got eliminated!
(Despite his looks,
he managed to protect Ji Hyo.)
He protects Ji Hyo.
So our superpowers are
like a comedy.
They are not afraid of me at all.
(He charges towards Suk Jin.)
- Come here.
- Your Majesty.
- What?
- Please leave.
Where would I go? I just got back.
What? What is it?
I guess Suk Jin is nothing.
What is Suk Jin doing?
What are you doing?
What is it? Is it a diaper?
Come here.
- Is it your diaper?
- Hey.
Why is he running around like that?
Let's get rid of the king.
- Let's do that.
- Let him put on his name tag.
Come here. I'll get rid of you.
Look at you. How dare you...
(Screaming)
He's got nothing.
(They don't fall for his trick.)
(He gets caught immediately.)
(The king has lost his dignity.)
- He's got nothing.
- I shot him.
(Poison Needle Sorcerer
used his superpower.)
- Am I paralyzed?
- 14.
- You should run away.
- 13.
You'll be paralyzed in 14 seconds.
- Me? Okay.
- 10, 9...
(His diaper is slipping down.)
This is slipping down.
(He can't run so far.)
You're paralyzed now.
(He's paralyzed for 30 seconds.)
- You should lie down.
- Lie down.
- What is he, by the way?
- You're paralyzed.
(King Suk Jin got poisoned
and fell ill.)
How dare you!
- Forgive me, Your Majesty.
- I told you to stop.
Suk Jin is out.
- Forgive me, Your Majesty.
- I told you to stop.
Suk Jin is out.
- What is up with Suk Jin?
- Seriously.
- Why is he so weak?
- I couldn't use my superpower.
Why didn't you use your superpower?
(Frustrated)
Why didn't you use...
Watch the episode when it airs.
You will see why I didn't use it.
Why didn't you use your superpower?
Who used the poison needle on me?
I did.
(Honest)
(You did?)
What is up with him?
(While his attention was
on King Suk Jin,)
(he secretly shot
the poison needle.)
What?
I am the Poison Needle Sorcerer.
(He was attacked by someone
he thought was on his side.)
You are less than human.
Your back was
right in front of my face,
so I tested my superpower,
and it worked so well.
I had to figure out
what your superpower is.
Now I know.
You know my superpower too.
- We are even.
- Okay.
Do you know
that they joined forces?
- Who did?
- They joined forces.
- Jae Suk and Se Chan.
- Se Chan betrayed us.
Why don't the three of us
join forces?
- I need to be in a team.
- What's your superpower?
It's meaningless for me
to be by myself.
- Me too.
- I need to be in a team.
Even if you get attacked,
I can turn the tables.
I can help you rip off
someone's name tag.
- You just need to rip it off.
- That's right.
- Thus, we should join forces.
- Really?
- Will you join the team?
- Let's join forces.
- Yes, I will join the team.
- Let's do that.
Hold on.
How did I think to do something
with these two?
The two of you are
just as untrustworthy.
Out of all people, it's you two.
I really like this idea.
- I like it too.
You can use it many times, right?
Three times.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
- Keep your promise.
- I'm going to use my superpower...
as soon as someone appears.
Let's go. So Min, don't betray us.
I won't.
If you rip off my name tag...
For goodness' sake!
I didn't do anything.
- It was a cameraman.
- A cameraman.
I will use my superpower!
I will use it!
Come on.
(Startled)
I didn't do anything.
(The smallest movement
puts them on edge.)
I could use my superpower
right away.
Do you want to see me turn my wrist?
Let's keep going.
(Clearing her throat)
(They are nervous as they don't know
each other's superpower.)
(Clearing her throat)
Come, come, pull!
(So Min uses her superpower.)
"You are the Witch
of Push and Pull."
(Say "Push" to push
the others away from you.)
Go, go, push!
(Say "Pull" to pull
the others toward you.)
Come, come, pull!
(The Witch of Push and Pull
uses her superpower.)
(Haha, An actor
who specializes in superpowers)
What is going on?
(His realistic performance
calls for computer graphics.)
(What is going on?)
(Come on and remove his name tag!)
Hey, don't do that!
(While Kwang Soo is in a daze)
It's over.
You should have ripped it off!
- What?
- Why didn't you rip it off?
You should've told me the rules!
You should've told me how!
(The alliance falls apart
in 5 minutes.)
I can't believe it.
So the effect ends
when she can't go on.
(Kwang Soo gets the plan.)
What are you guys doing?
- You ruined our alliance.
- What are you guys doing?
What are you guys doing? Stop it!
No! This is my first time
to have a superpower.
Go, go, push!
Is it a different skill?
My goodness.
(The actor who specializes
in superpowers puts on a show.)
(The Witch of Push and Pull
creates a hassle for everyone.)
You ruined our alliance.
(Meanwhile,
So Min runs away quickly.)
(She manages to escape.)
Gosh, So Min.
- Kwang Soo, did you see that?
- Haha.
Let's stay together
until the very end.
I will keep my promise today.
Let's go.
I can't believe So Min.
How could she betray me?
You have only one chance left.
I need to find
the Room of Reinforcement.
(Sang Yeob was wandering
by himself.)
Jae Suk.
- It's Sang Yeob.
- What's his superpower?
He has a mirror.
It's just my mirror.
(Sang Yeob seems to be flustered.)
(Jae Suk notices something!)
Lee Tae Oh? What is that?
- What?
- Why does it say Lee Tae Oh?
What do you mean?
Why does it say Lee Tae Oh?
Lee Tae Oh?
Is there another guest?
(Why does his name tag say
Lee Tae Oh, not Lee Sang Yeob?)
You are the Celebrity Copier.
If you do a voice impression
of a celebrity,
you can become that celebrity
for three minutes.
(Sang Yeob can gain a new name tag
through a voice impression.)
Mirror, mirror,
who do I look like?
It's not a sin to fall in love!
Ji Sun Woo!
(He used his superpower...)
(and transformed into Lee Tae Oh.)
(Even if the name tag gets removed,
Lee Sang Yeob will survive.)
(Meanwhile, Han Na
was walking around by herself.)
Sang Yeob!
(He is on guard.)
Drop the beat!
(She blinds him
with a charming dance.)
(Lee Tae Oh is blinded.)
What is this?
Do I walk around like this?
That's right.
(Now is my chance!)
(She attacks right away.)
(He can't defend himself
due to his narrow field of vision.)
Lee Tae Oh!
(Lee Tae Oh is out.)
Lee Tae Oh is out.
- Lee Tae Oh is out.
- Why does it say Lee Tae Oh?
Why does it say Lee Tae Oh?
Lee Tae Oh is out.
- Who?
- Lee Tae Oh is out.
Who?
Lee Tae Oh is out.
- Lee Tae Woo?
- Lee Tae Oh.
- Lee Tae Oh is out.
- Who is Lee Tae Oh?
It must be Suk Jin.
(Everyone is confused about
Lee Tae Oh.)
Lee Tae Oh from
"A World of Married Couple"?
(Lee Tae Oh who was eliminated
disappears.)
Lee Sang Yeob is back.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo used up
her superpower.)
This is driving me crazy.
(She is searching for a ticket
for the Room of Reinforcement.)
I am the only one
without a superpower.
Ji Hyo is over there.
I will go over to her and use
my superpower.
You are Captain Gravity.
(It gives a member of your choice
20kg sandbags.)
(Ji Hyo doesn't know this.)
(Captain Gravity is out to get her.)
Gravity!
(Haha uses his superpower!)
(Haha's superpower affects Ji Hyo.)
(Gravity pulls Ji Hyo down.)
(Walking slowly)
Let's go.
(Ji Hyo couldn't run away
due to the sandbags.)
(Ripping)
(He ripped off her name tag!)
(Ji Hyo gets eliminated...)
(without a chance
to use her strength.)
(Laughing)
(Captain Gravity's superpower
worked well.)
- Ji Hyo is out.
- Are these sandbags?
Are these sandbags?
Who used this power on me?
Haha is watching from there.
He isn't even surprised.
- I can't even run.
- Haha used his superpower on her.
(This is the charm
of the War of Superpowers.)
Your superpower is incredible.
(He gives a ceremony.)
What did you do to me?
(Ji Hyo became his first victim.)
(Current Situation)
(Ji Hyo is out.)
This is funny indeed.
(Suk Jin is out, but he can use
his superpower 2 more times.)
(It's his time to summon
his second past life.)
I still have a life.
(What's Suk Jin's
second past life?)
(Ji Suk Jin)
(He comes back as a commoner
of the Joseon Dynasty.)
The Korean language is different
from the Chinese language,
and the written words
and the spoken words don't match.
The Korean language is different
from the Chinese language,
and the written words
and the spoken words don't match.
(Jong Kook bursts out laughing.)
If I can save the country,
I will sacrifice...
"If I can save the country..."
I will sacrifice myself readily.
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin,
- are you filming something?
- What?
I need to keep saying that.
Otherwise, I die.
The Korean language is different
from the Chinese language,
and the written words
and the spoken words don't match.
- In any case,
- Suk Jin.
be careful.
Don't make me recite
"Hunminjeongeum".
The Korean language is different
from the Chinese language...
- Do you need to memorize that?
- I can't recite what comes next.
I can't make a mistake.
For goodness' sake.
Suk Jin, you are so funny here.
Why aren't you funny
on your YouTube channel?
I want to act normal on my channel.
I want to act cool.
Don't do that.
- I want to act cool.
- It's better when you look foolish.
Where is everyone? Come on out!
You jerks!
- Suk Jin, you are so funny.
- You...
You are so funny.
Once I recite "Hunminjeongeum",
you are done for.
- All right.
- You jerks!
- Okay.
- The Korean language...
is different
from the Chinese language...
(That's insane.)
Thank goodness
I managed to fool Jong Kook.
Thank goodness.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Wasn't I right about Suk Jin?
Suk Jin is so funny.
He became a zombie, right?
Today,
Suk Jin will have a costume show.
He can keep coming back to life.
The bundle contains costumes.
- That's right.
- It seems that way.
We should go and eliminate him.
Why didn't you take him out?
(When Jae Suk lowers his guard,)
(the Poison Needle Sorcerer
uses his superpower.)
(Jae Suk fell for the same trick.)
Jong Kook, hurry up.
For goodness' sake.
Jong Kook,
let's eliminate him together.
11, 10...
You should take him out.
(Jae Suk is about to be paralyzed.)
Hey.
What is going on?
(Time left until the poison needle
comes into effect)
One. You are paralyzed.
You are paralyzed.
(Jae Suk is paralyzed.)
One. You are paralyzed.
(The poison spreads
in Jae Suk's body.)
(Time left until the effect
is lifted)
You dirty jerk.
I will survive...
I will survive and take you out.
Jong Kook, help me!
- I will survive...
- Over here!
Over here!
Why can't he take out
a paralyzed person?
You...
(Bouncing)
(But Jae Suk perseveres.)
- Hey!
He is too strong.
2, 1,
- zero.
- Come here.
- You are no longer paralyzed.
- Jae Suk, I am sorry.
Jae Suk, I betrayed you...
because I was blinded
by the idea of winning.
- Jae Suk, I am sorry.
- Hey.
I was blinded
by the idea of winning,
- so I took my chance.
- How could you do this to me?
How could you use
2 out of 3 poison needles on me?
I am sorry.
How could you use
2 out of 3 poison needles...
on me?
I saw a lot of openings.
Jae Suk, I don't have
any poison needles now.
I am done for.
I will stay by your side.
(By the way)
Gosh, I can't do anything.
(Now, the result of the race depends
on the number of chances left.)
(She finds a ticket
for the Room of Reinforcement!)
(She looks around
so that no one will take it.)
(Commoner Ji appears.)
(So Min doesn't notice him.)
(He chases after her
with the bouncing bundle.)
(Startled)
Suk Jin, Suk Jin. Let's go
to the Room of Reinforcement.
The Room of Reinforcement?
- I have a ticket.
- It's time to choose.
- What?
With whom will you go
to the Room of Reinforcement?
- Hurry up. Who will it be?
- Ji Suk Jin.
Okay. Let's go.
- Hurry up. Who will it be?
- Ji Suk Jin.
Okay. Let's go.
This is great.
- You found the ticket.
- Can we use the ticket...
- right away?
- Yes.
- Hello.
Hello.
You entered
the Room of Reinforcement.
Please choose a random mission.
I can't fail.
- Do we choose one each?
- This is bad.
"Random Vinegar Yogurt Drink".
"Pick 1 out of 3
yogurt drinks each."
"You succeed if both members drink
a regular yogurt drink."
My goodness.
We can drink a vinegar yogurt drink
as if it's a regular one, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Please pick one each...
- and drink.
Let's do this.
- You must endure it.
- Please drink it in one go.
- In one go?
- Yes.
Please drink it in one go.
- Cheers. For reinforcement!
- For reinforcement!
(Will they succeed the mission...)
(and obtain more chances
to use the superpower?)
(Throwing up)
(He picked
the vinegar yogurt drink.)
Suk Jin,
you should have endured it.
It was impossible.
(Bumping into the wall)
Suk Jin.
It was so hard for me
to find the ticket.
Would you give us another chance?
You failed the mission.
Please exit the room
and resume with the race.
What? The race?
Yes.
Gosh, why did I pick
the one in the middle?
(Someone is there!)
Let's take out that man.
Suk Jin is weak.
Why does he keep coming back
to life?
What are you doing?
Are you filming a period drama?
If you touch my clothing,
you will go straight to your grave.
Is it a costume show or what?
No, no.
Don't make me recite
"Hunminjeongeum".
- What?
- Don't make me recite it.
Okay?
(They ignore his warning.)
Shall we have Suk Jin change
into another costume?
(Let's rip off his name tag.)
(What?)
- Is there another costume?
- If we rip off his name tag,
he will change into another costume.
I am sick and tired of that costume.
- Okay. Come on.
- Let's see a different costume.
- Okay.
- But...
- What?
(Everyone figured out
Suk Jin's superpower.)
The Korean language is different...
- from the Chinese language...
- He has nothing.
(He has nothing.)
And the written words...
Suk Jin.
And the spoken words...
Should I complete the sentence?
Should I?
- Should I complete the sentence?
- Let's take him out.
- Should I?
- What was that?
Was he just saying things?
(His act doesn't work.)
Just rip it off. Rip it off.
- I will help.
- Just rip it off. Rip it off.
- Rip it off.
- I helped.
- I did it.
(Commoner Ji is out.)
Suk Jin is out.
I helped.
- Is that all?
- Yes.
Wasn't he using his superpower?
Is that all?
Why did you pretend to be scary?
- I helped.
- Is that all?
Suk Jin is out.
(Laughing)
Didn't he get eliminated earlier?
I thought I heard the same thing
earlier. What's going on?
Go and change into another costume.
We are sick and tired of this one.
- Does he have another costume?
- It's a costume show.
Can he keep coming back that way?
- He has costumes in that bundle.
- What's his superpower?
He has costumes.
Is that all?
Is he out?
For goodness' sake.
It's about time
I wear a different costume.
Where on earth is Jong Kook?
(Jong Kook is wandering by himself.)
I should step away.
Suk Jin is out.
After half of them get eliminated,
my time will come.
(After half of them get eliminated,
my time will come.)
(Jong Kook makes
a mysterious comment.)
(Kwang Soo is looking for a ticket
for the Room of Reinforcement.)
(He spots the cameraman.)
(Someone must be there.)
(He approaches carefully.)
(Peek-a-boo.)
(His third past life is a beggar
from the Goryeo Dynasty.)
(Laughing)
I am a beggar.
What is up with this getup?
- I am a beggar.
- How did this happen?
I don't even have a bundle now.
This is my last life.
It's over. Are you by yourself?
Yes.
Why didn't you team up with someone?
I didn't team up with anyone
because you are the only one left.
Would you team up with yourself?
You are a beggar.
Han Na is coming.
Why is she walking towards us?
- She is coming.
- It's Se Chan.
(Se Chan approaches them quickly
as well.)
Se Chan is coming.
Jae Suk is coming too.
(Jae Suk joins as well.)
Jae Suk.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Is Suk Jin still in the race?
Listen, everyone.
Listen.
Jae Suk, make an announcement.
An announcement?
No, no. I won't hear it.
What?
What's your superpower?
(He still doesn't know
what Jae Suk's superpower is.)
What is it?
(What should I say
to appear strong?)
What's your superpower?
Will you use your superpower on me?
(What's your superpower?)
(While they have
a war of nerves...)
What's your superpower?
I am sorry. You can pass through.
I am sorry.
(Polite)
- He was waiting.
- I am sorry.
We were too absorbed. I am sorry.
I am so embarrassed.
I am so embarrassed!
I am sorry.
That was so...
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
He was watching us.
His line was the worst.
- His line was the worst.
- Why didn't you tell me sooner?
- Seriously.
- He asked,
"What's your superpower?"
(Jae Suk's words
were cringeworthy.)
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
He seemed flustered.
He was like, "Who are these guys?"
Completely...
(Completely)
turn me over.
- That's your superpower?
- What is that?
- That's fascinating.
It must be Jae Suk's superpower.
Who will be the three people?
Please.
(3 members of his choice
will pause for 1 minute.)
(Which three members will be forced
to pause?)
Once the three members
are announced,
they will need to pause for 1 minute
after 5 seconds.
- Do you mean the three members?
- Hold on.
(Hold on.)
- These people freeze?
- Yes.
What's wrong?
- Did you pick your name?
- Yes.
(Nodding)
(He has to freeze himself.)
Okay!
(You need luck
to use your superpower.)
- Come on!
- I mean...
Han Na, Kwang Soo,
and Jae Suk freeze.
(Han Na, Kwang Soo,
and Jae Suk freeze.)
- Do it.
- Han Na, Kwang Soo, and Jae Suk...
- Who?
- The three of you freeze.
- Gosh.
- You didn't see me
(After picking his own name,
Jae Suk runs as fast as he can.)
You didn't see me, you didn't see me
(Kwang Soo finally uses
his superpower.)
(Invisible Man)
(The cloak makes him invisible and
protects him from all superpowers.)
(The cloak protects him
from all superpowers.)
(Hurrying)
(After a bit of a hassle,)
(he finally puts on
the invisibility cloak.)
- What's going on?
- What happened?
What's going on?
- What's going on?
So Min, Kwang Soo is
invisible right now.
- You can't see him.
- I can't see him?
Read what's written on my cloak!
(Viewers, please pretend
you don't see him.)
(So Min bumps into him.)
I can't see him?
You can't see him.
How can you hit me
when you can't see me?
- Gosh, that was close.
- Is Han Na out?
(Jae Suk uses his superpower
on himself.)
Jae Suk, freeze.
(He freezes for a minute.)
- Can I rip her name tag off?
- Han Na, freeze.
- Yes, you can.
- What's going on?
- Really?
Me?
- Hey!
- Han Na is out.
Hey! Han Na!
How could you do this, Se Chan?
- Hey!
- Han Na is out.
- Hey, Han Na!
- How could you...
- Eliminate Kwang Soo.
- How...
How could you do this?
Se Chan, this is not okay.
I used my superpower for you.
I used it for you.
Jae Suk, you can move again.
- Come here.
- Just a second.
Jae Suk, you can move again.
- Come here.
- Just a second.
Hold on.
Come here.
- Is Han Na out? Come here.
- Hold on.
- Come here.
- Can you move again?
Go, go...
- So Min is out.
(The Witch of Push and Pull is out.)
- She's finally out.
- What's with him?
He's invisible.
What?
(We skipped the computer graphics
because it's too much work.)
(Current Situation)
(So Min is out.)
That's a shame.
I wish I'd gotten a chance
to dance in front of everyone.
(By the way...)
Is Jong Kook hiding somewhere?
(Jong Kook has been on his own
a lot today.)
What...
(It looks like he found
something again.)
(The list of lost items?)
(It's a list of items
missing from the property room.)
(He stares at the list
for a moment.)
This...
This is dangerous.
(He tears the lower part
of the paper.)
This...
(And he heads somewhere.)
(There is a mysterious gem.)
(What is this place?)
So Min and Han Na,
who have superpowers, are out.
Thank you.
(Along with the news of
the two members' elimination,)
(he receives two gems.)
Okay.
(What's the secret of Jong Kook,
who is collecting gems secretly?)
(Yesterday, Mok-dong SBS)
(Jong Kook meets the staff alone.)
Why only me?
There's only me for real?
(He suddenly feels uncomfortable.)
Only me?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
Normally, you're the strongest
at Name Tag Elimination.
But once superpowers are involved,
- you always struggle.
- Right.
You and Suk Jin are
the only ones who have never won...
- War of Superpowers.
- That's right.
Actually, you did even worse
than Suk Jin did.
(He tells the harsh truth calmly.)
I was given a useless superpower
every time.
It only got in my way.
(One of the superpowers
he had was Wi-Fi.)
(But the information he got
was not very useful.)
(Wi-Fi only got in his way.)
(His true superpower
comes from his muscles.)
(All his superpowers were useless.)
(Every time, he just ended up
being cute.)
All of them were useless.
So...
we've concluded that you're
not good with superpowers...
and deprived you of all superpowers.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
You've never given me
any superpowers anyway.
- But you'd still want to fight.
- Right.
Tomorrow,
you'll be a human weapon
hidden among those with superpowers.
You'll use your physical strength
to rip off others' name tags.
(Eliminate those with superpowers
using your physical strength.)
(It's his chance to get back at them
and crush their confidence.)
(The human weapon, Jong Kook,
snuck into Superpower School.)
(Seniors, please sit down.)
(But there were only 4 chairs
for seniors.)
(He gets his own chair.)
(As he was not invited, he made
all the preparations himself.)
(Jong Kook pretended to be
a senior at the school.)
(When the War of Superpowers began,)
(he damaged the list of lost items
of the school.)
(1 superpower cloak and
1 communication device are missing.)
(The lost communication device
was the walkie-talkie he's using.)
(The lost superpower cloak was
what he wore at the ceremony.)
(The human weapon has been
waiting for his moment.)
- There's one condition.
- What is it?
Every time a person with
a superpower is eliminated,
you'll receive a gem.
The gems you receive will be
kept in the human weapon's room.
Okay.
Once you've collected five gems,
you can start eliminating
those with superpowers.
Once I've collected five?
(He can get into action
when 5 members are out.)
(He gave away superpower points
because he didn't need them.)
(He won everyone's trust
by pretending to be generous.)
(Even when his prey came near...)
(Let's eliminate him together!)
(He waited for his moment.)
(I can't eliminate him anyway.)
(When everyone else
was given a superpower...)
Please read out
your fake superpower.
(He pretended...)
(that his superpower was Wi-Fi.)
I don't have to eavesdrop.
There's no point.
I'm only human.
Why can't they eliminate
each other faster?
Gosh.
Hey.
Let's eliminate Suk Jin first.
Let's eliminate him.
(Se Chan can use
his superpower only once now.)
- We're a team now.
- Yes.
Let's go.
(Their target is
the Goryeo beggar, Suk Jin.)
You should be more into it.
(But...)
(Jae Suk is shot
with a poison needle again.)
(It's almost like he collects them.)
You've been shot
by the Poison Needle Sorcerer.
In 15 seconds,
you'll freeze for 30 seconds.
- 15, 14, 13...
- Again?
- You...
- Let's run!
(Seeing him run away
is getting old.)
(Time left until the poison needle
comes into effect)
- This is my last chance.
- How could you do this?
- I have to eliminate him.
- How could you?
- How could you...
- Now.
- Se Chan...
- This is my last chance.
Lift him. 1, 2, 3.
Lift him. We have to.
1, 2, 3. This is my last chance.
- He's out.
- It's over.
(Jae Suk is out.)
You filthy jerks.
You little...
- Jae Suk is out.
Hey, how could you do this?
I shot you three times.
Hey.
Gosh.
Can you see me?
Yes, I can.
You can't see me.
- You can't see me.
- Gosh.
(This is so annoying.)
This is unbelievable.
You shot 3 out of 4 needles at me?
Jae Suk, I had no choice.
Where should I go?
(The news makes someone happy.)
Wait a minute,
I'm starting to have hope.
I'm starting to...
(It's time to get ready.)
I'm starting to have hope.
(With Jae Suk out,)
(he receives the fourth gem.)
Okay.
There you go.
(Once he receives another gem,)
(the human weapon
can get into action.)
(Just then...)
Sang Yeob is out.
(Sang Yeob is out?)
You'll be given one more gem
and a ring.
(Finally, five members are out.)
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo
eliminated Sang Yeob together.)
Kwang Soo!
Sang Yeob is out.
(While those with superpowers
are distracted...)
Sang Yeob is out.
(The human weapon is
about to get into action.)
Finally.
(Jong Kook's goal is to win
without any superpowers.)
Finally.
(He is given the fifth gem.)
All right.
(The human weapon is in action.)
(He can now hunt down
those with superpowers.)
(The school's intruder alarm
goes off.)
What's going on?
There's an intruder in the school.
- There's an intruder in the school.
- An intruder?
There's another person?
- Kwang Soo.
- What's going on?
- Who's the intruder?
There's an intruder.
Did someone use a superpower
to bring someone in?
- No.
- Or did someone just show up?
Someone broke into the school.
There's an intruder in the school.
- What does that mean?
- There's another person?
- Is it someone new?
- I know. Who could it be?
Should I get ready
to go back out there?
What are you talking about?
Why are you preparing to go out,
Han Na?
Is it time for us to step up?
There's no place for us to go.
Oh, so we're completely done.
(Meanwhile, Haha is...)
I'm sorry, sir.
They're looking at me.
(Haha takes a look around.)
(He finds the list of lost items
that Jong Kook ripped.)
Someone ripped this, right?
(Superpower cloak,
19 in stock, 1 lost)
There is an intruder.
An intruder. There's an intruder.
Who is the intruder?
Hold on. How can I use this?
Hold on.
From my head to my toes
(Suk Jin is enjoying
his last past life.)
Kwang Soo has
an invisibility cloak.
You've been summoned...
- to the Room of Reinforcement.
- I have?
You've been summoned...
- to the Room of Reinforcement.
- I have?
- Okay.
- Please follow us to the room.
Where is the Room of Reinforcement?
It's in the main building.
The cafeteria?
How nice.
I should go first.
(He enters the Room of Reinforcement
in hopes for a better past life.)
(Soon after, the person who invited
him to the room enters.)
(The person who invited him was...)
- Okay.
- Okay. Thank you.
Suk Jin.
(The human weapon summoned Suk Jin
with the ticket he found...)
(in the beginning.)
(The reason why he called Suk Jin
to the Room of Reinforcement is...)
(the Room of Reinforcement is
a safe zone for them.)
(Warning:
This is the Room of Reinforcement.)
(Those with superpowers cannot
rip name tags here.)
(However, the human weapon,
Jong Kook,)
(can rip off name tags as
he doesn't have superpowers.)
(That's why Suk Jin,
who dreams of a new life...)
- Did you get it?
- No, not yet.
- Okay.
- Yes!
What was that?
- Did you get it?
- No, not yet.
(was eliminated in
the Room of Reinforcement.)
Okay.
- Why?
- He's out.
Okay.
But this is
the Room of Reinforcement.
You can't rip off name tags here.
The intruder of Superpower School,
the human weapon,
- has started to move.
- What?
The intruder of Superpower School,
the human weapon,
- has started to move.
- What?
(The human weapon?)
(Frozen)
He must be the human weapon.
I'm the human weapon.
I'm a human being
who doesn't have a superpower.
You're a human being,
who defeats...
- those with superpowers?
- Yes.
The intruder of Superpower School,
the human weapon,
has started to move.
Who's the human weapon?
I have a feeling they'll know
that it's me.
Because nobody knows
my superpower.
Jong Kook.
I found the list of lost items.
- What is that?
- Come down here.
- What?
- You have to trust me.
I'm the original. Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- We're brothers, remember?
- Come down.
- Okay. Just wait.
I have chills.
My gosh.
This is dangerous.
- Jong Kook.
- What's going on?
Your superpower is...
- You have superpowers, right?
- Right.
- Take a look.
- Okay.
Remember how we all wore
cloaks during the opening?
- Right.
- Take a look.
One of the cloaks is missing.
It says one is lost.
What did they say about
the human weapon?
- They said they intruded, right?
- Right.
There's a human among us.
(Haha, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan,
who have powers, are left.)
(Jong Kook is in trouble
if he gets caught now.)
This punk... Oh, my.
I mean, this person.
I'm sorry. I got overexcited.
I felt victimized.
This young, little kid...
stole a cloak and entered the school
while pretending he has powers.
- But look.
- Who could it be?
- You have superpowers, right?
- Honestly...
- Right.
- I have superpowers too.
What was my chant again?
Was it "Tiramisu"?
What was it again? Anyways.
- I have this, my superpower.
- Okay.
- And Kwang Soo is invisible.
- Right.
Then who's left?
- Does the last person have a power?
- Se Chan?
- Se Chan has a water gun.
- All he has is a water gun.
- That's just a gun.
- Okay.
All he has is that water gun,
but we were fighting
among ourselves.
And you were won over by him!
He's fake!
Let's eliminate him.
What is this?
This isn't it. What is it?
(He finds something with
an R Sticker on it.)
It's a certificate of admission.
(Is it a 2019 Superpower School
certificate of admissions?)
(Name: Haha)
Haha.
(It looks like the certificate
of admissions for the 2nd years.)
Ji Hyo.
Jae Suk.
(Certificate of Admissions)
(Name: Kim Jong Kook)
What?
Jong Kook's certificate
doesn't have a stamp on it.
(There is a stamp marked on
four of the certificates.)
(However, Jong Kook's certificate
does not have a stamp on it.)
I just got chills.
Jong Kook is the human weapon.
I have to let the others know...
before anyone else gets eliminated.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Come here.
- Hey, Yang Se Chan.
- Come here.
- Yes?
- My goodness, Yang Se Chan.
Come here. Stand right here.
- Are you starting again?
- I said, stand over there!
Why? What's wrong?
You were entrusted with something
big after 10 years, weren't you?
Who was?
They're going to entrust
someone like me...
with a big project like this?
That makes no sense.
- Do you know why you're fake?
- Why is that?
Jong Kook and I...
have been friends for over 20 years,
you punk.
You fake punk.
(You're the fake intruder
who came in between us.)
- Big brother!
- Okay.
Do you want to go?
(Do you want a taste
of my poison needles?)
Do you want to go?
Se Chan, if you've enjoyed yourself,
it's time to sacrifice yourself.
But Jong Kook, seriously...
I will sacrifice myself. I will.
- I'll make it quick.
- Do it so there will be a CG on it.
Please put some graphics
on my name tag.
(Yang Se Chan)
(Due to the work overload
of the CG team,)
(we couldn't fulfill
Se Chan's dying wish.)
(Poison Needle Sorcerer is out.)
- Let me see.
- I'm nothing.
Then you should've told us
that you weren't more aggressively.
- I told you I wasn't.
- What is going on here?
Are you saying
it's the Invisible Man?
(He's making a wrong guess.)
- It must be Kwang Soo.
- The human weapon is on the move.
(It must be Kwang Soo.)
Jong Kook. Hold on.
- Hold on.
- Be careful.
Hold on. Is it you?
Are you insane?
He just said that the human
is on the move!
Haha.
(Kwang Soo appears at that moment.)
- Do you know who the intruder is?
- Who is it?
Do you know who the intruder is?
(Flustered)
It's Jong Kook.
What are you saying?
- It's Jong Kook.
- What are you saying?
You're really...
(Completely flustered)
- I found a hint.
- Let me see.
- What hint?
- I took a picture of it...
because I knew
you wouldn't believe me.
Haha, get ready.
(The battle will look very different
according to Haha's choice.)
(Who will be the final winner?)
I will tell you the results.
The 10th anniversary
War of Superpowers: The End Game...
was a chance for Jong Kook,
who always got low rankings...
- during superpower races,
- Right.
to have no superpowers
and participate in the race.
- He was just a human?
- But...
- I didn't have anything today,
- Really?
and I had to wait until
five members were eliminated.
You didn't have anything, but you
were terrifying with the gloves on.
- I was at a serious disadvantage.
- In the end,
Haha and Kwang Soo...
(Jong Kook worked among those
with superpowers.)
In the end, Haha and Kwang Soo...
(What were the results of the final
match between the three of them?)
ripped off Jong Kook's name tag,
and those with superpowers won.
We won because we didn't
betray each other.
ripped off Jong Kook's name tag...
Seriously?
(Team Superpowers won
thanks to Haha and Kwang Soo.)
- I feel like...
- I'm so touched.
I'm going to cry.
(Earlier, Haha and Kwang Soo
were facing off with Jong Kook.)
Kim Jong Kook, Gravity!
(Haha used his last chance.)
(The 2 scaredy cats joined forces.)
Grab him!
(However, the human weapon
is a strong match.)
(The two of them just barely
ripped off his name tag.)
(They're overly emotional
and praising themselves.)
- These weasels...
- I'm serious...
I'm serious today.
- What about me?
- You used 3 of your 4 powers on me?
So the punishment that Jong Kook
must do for losing the race...
during the 10th anniversary
live broadcast is...
What is it?
(What is the punishment that must
be done during the live broadcast?)
He must put on a costume.
Oh, my.
During a live broadcast?
He will be joined by another member
who will be chosen next week,
and the two of them must put on
a costume for the live broadcast.
Two people?
So someone else will also do it.
Thank goodness for now.
- I had no idea.
- Okay.
Over the course of 10 years,
the eight of you... I'm sorry.
He was yawning.
- Why are you yawning now?
- What are you doing?
(He just yawned
for everyone to see.)
- Why are you yawning now?
- What are you doing?
- But...
- Why are you yawning?
I know I need to put on a costume
as a penalty,
but what about Suk Jin, who had
to dress up four times today?
I'm exhausted
after living three lifetimes.
The candidates for Jong Kook's
costume punishment are...
one of each of your costumes
in the past, which you will suggest,
and four new ones suggested by
the crew.
You must choose 1 of the 12.
- I think they'll be bad.
- Suggest one of your past costumes.
- Something that Jong Kook could do.
- Okay.
The doll? That's too weak.
- A giraffe is too weak.
- A mummy's not good enough.
I'll choose the llama.
- What about the beggar?
- I chose the llama.
I choose Kaonashi.
I choose Yondu.
Yondu is a good one.
(The costumes chosen by the members,
the costumes chosen by the staff)
Okay. Jong Kook, please choose one.
Okay.
Are you going to do
the one you choose?
What is it?
(This is the big data of costumes
accumulated over 10 years.)
(Among the many costumes, which one
will be chosen by Jong Kook?)
It's Kaonashi.
- What is it?
- It's Kaonashi.
(This is the best one
out of all of them.)
This is it. Okay!
This one is not that bad.
- This is not that bad.
Kaonashi.
- Okay.
- Kaonashi is cute.
I wanted to do something cute.
Are we choosing another person
next week?
- Yes, that's right.
- Okay. Good.
Please say something, Sang Yeob.
It's been a while since I came,
and I had a lot of fun.
Please invite me more often.
Okay.
Okay, Kang Han Na.
I'm sad because I couldn't dance
two more times.
- But thanks for letting me dance.
- Dance before we end.
- Go for it.
- Can I do that?
- If you want to, go ahead.
- Do it.
- It's your last chance.
- I hope you trust me
This was it.
- This is her superpower.
- Her moves are loose.
Does it make sense that one would
go blind from watching this?
- Her moves are loose.
- Of course, you'd go blind.
Her moves are loose.
Congratulations on
your 10th anniversary, Running Man.
(We thank Lee Sang Yeob
and Kang Han Na for joining us...)
(on our 10th anniversary.)
(The return of
the 2020 Reincarnation Race)
(Welcome to
the 1st Reincarnation Camp.)
(Part 2 of the race that viewers
wanted to see,)
(the Reincarnation Episode)
(ZICO, Lee Do Hyun,
SUNMI, Cho Sae Ho)
(The members are reincarnated
at different time periods.)
(While they enjoy
camping at peace,)
(a mystery siren goes off.)
(There's a secret...)
(behind the reincarnation camp?)
(Doubt and fear keep growing up
with mysterious accidents.)
You better be careful.
(The number of survivors
keeps decreasing.)
(They've got a limited time.)
(They have to find out
the secret of reincarnation.)
(The reincarnation special is back.)
(How would it end?)
(2020 Reincarnation Camp)