(KINTEX in Ilsan)
(2021 Running League Rookie Draft)
Hello. I'm Announcer Bae Sung Jae
who will host...
2021 Running League Rookie Draft.
We have a lot of
outstanding rookies this year,
so all eyes are on this draft.
First, the team owners
who are here to discover rookies...
will enter first.
Please come on in.
(The two dignified team owners
are walking in.)
He's got outstanding agility
and intelligence.
- Nice to meet you.
- He's the owner of Team Yang,
Yang Se Chan.
He's got the leadership
for the whole country.
He's the owner of Team Yu,
Yoo Jae Suk.
(Bursting into laughter)
Aren't we taking a photo?
- What?
- Aren't we taking a photo?
- A photo? What photo?
- Yes, let's take one.
- Let's take a photo together.
- I didn't know it was you.
(2021 Rookies Are Ours!)
(Team Owner Yang Se Chan
and Yoo Jae Suk)
Mr. Yoo and Mr. Yang,
it's nice to meet you.
The draft is very important
for the victory of your team.
Is there any player you have
your eye on for this draft?
Any player you like?
- There are about 2 players.
- 2 players.
Yes. I'm interested in two players.
- I see.
- Can you tell us who they are?
Yes. They are Ryu Hyun Jin
and Kim Kwang Hyun.
(He announces
that he will take them all.)
Will you take them all?
- You're taking them all.
- Other than these two,
I'm not so interested.
Players like Ji Suk Jin...
shouldn't be here for the draft.
- He will be kicked out right away.
- Right.
Now the rookies will enter.
2021 Running League Rookie Draft.
- Entry number one.
- Do we have to do this?
Is this necessary?
(Shinil High School song)
(All players are entering
with their school songs.)
(Booing)
I will never pick him.
- I'm telling you.
- I'll kick him out.
He's been in the hot stove league
for the past 30 years.
He's a rookie who will show
the power of a veteran.
(Fizzing)
He can't be a pitcher.
He has weak shoulders.
I don't understand why he's trying
to become a pitcher.
(Groaning)
See? He can barely come up here.
He barely climbed up here.
- He's exhausted already.
- See?
He doesn't even have
the right pitching form.
- He's out.
- He's discharged.
Here comes the next player.
Entry number two.
(Entry No. 2, Kim Jong Kook)
Bench-clearing brawl is my thing.
He's unbeatable All Mighty.
- This is my school song.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Gosh, he's a headache.
- He really is.
I'm exhausted already.
He plays soccer well,
- but he's bad at baseball.
- He's a terrible baseball player.
He's like a scarecrow
when it comes to baseball.
- Compared to his body...
- Gosh, what was that?
(The real monster rookie
threatens the two team owners.)
- Why are you being like this?
- He was...
- about to throw a ball at us.
- Don't threaten us.
- He knows nothing about baseball.
- He's a scarecrow.
This is the ball...
used in the seventh game
of the World Series.
- He's bragging about it.
- Are you serious?
Yes. It even has some dirt on it.
And it has Ryu Hyun Jin's autograph.
He's bragging
about knowing him again.
I went to watch the game.
I will never pick him.
- He's condescending.
- Condescending?
- What did you say?
- You're condescending.
He brags about
knowing Ryu Hyun Jin.
- I will never pick him.
- I'll be sure to start a fight.
I will never pick you.
I will straighten your teeth
with a bench-clearing brawl.
- What?
- I'm wearing braces.
- Straighten my teeth?
- Yes.
- What are you talking about?
- I'll make them even.
Okay. I get it.
Let's move on to the next player.
Entry number three.
He's a super rookie
from Osan High School.
- It's him.
- It's Haha.
He can barely play baseball.
Is he a junior player?
"Don't make fun of my height.
I'm a player with a quick wit."
Rookie player, Haha.
Isn't he from the little league
baseball team?
He is. He's a junior player.
All right. Shall we move on?
- Yes.
- You've gained a lot of weight.
- Right.
(He points out his weight.)
- Why would you say that?
- That wasn't necessary.
You are bulking up.
Why are you...
I was told there would be
no cross talk.
- Just continue.
- You look like...
- You look like a baseball player.
- I didn't know you'd be so close.
You can keep going.
- I was surprised to see him.
- All right.
Entry number four.
- He's good.
- It feels like...
She's the ace player who's
come out of the cave for today.
- That's a good swing.
- Song Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, I like your swing.
Doing this after a swing
is the worst.
We don't do this.
Why are you looking away like this?
I should do this. Am I wrong?
She lacks basic skills for batting.
Is that so?
Let's move on to the next player.
Entry number five.
There's no one to pick.
I'm bored already.
He's bored already.
He's the assassin on the field
who attacks even his team.
He's Lee Kwang Soo.
(They let out a deep-drawn sigh
as soon as Kwang Soo shows up.)
- He's the worst.
- He looks like a Japanese player.
We don't warm up like that.
And he needs to get a haircut first.
His back hair. It's too...
He looks like
an amateur Japanese baseball player.
An amateur Japanese baseball player.
Hello.
(It turns out he's
a baseball player from Japan.)
Does your cap have the hair?
It's not a wig.
- You need a haircut.
- It's fake.
No, I can't.
This player has...
a lot of issues about teamwork.
- Exactly.
- He has a lot of problems.
- He muddies the water.
- Exactly.
He's not so good,
but he negotiates
his salary for a long time.
- He thinks he's popular.
All right.
Entry number six.
Her batting average
for romance is 100 percent.
She's Love Frog who throws
a breaking ball for love.
She's Jeon So Min.
(She's a national athlete
for romance.)
I'm sure we should
pass on her today.
- We have to pass on her.
- Pass on her.
She knows nothing about baseball.
She knows nothing.
- She's not interested in baseball.
- She's here to hit on the owners.
- Look at her.
- She's here to seduce the owners.
Who knows? She might have
dated some baseball players.
- Right.
- Yes.
She might have dated some.
That's possible. She might have
dated baseball players.
- So it's finally time.
- It's the main event.
It's the main event.
This is the beginning.
Lastly, we have monstrous rookies
who are the talk of the town...
- in the baseball world.
- They're different.
Entry number seven.
Everything he does wins
Korea's first titles.
Gosh, this is...
Korean Monster, Ryu Hyun Jin.
(Korean Monster, Ryu Hyun Jin)
(He conquered the Major League
with his skills since his debut.)
("Ryu Hyun Jin Ranked 2nd
for the CY Young Award")
("Ryu Hyun Jin Proved
that he's the Best Pitcher")
(With his outstanding performance,)
(he moved to Toronto Blue Jays.)
("Ryu Hyun Jin Receives
80 Million Dollars")
("Ryu Hyun Jin Moves to Toronto
for 80 Million Dollars for 4 Years")
(He's not just Korean Monster,
but World Monster.)
My goodness.
We are wearing baseball uniforms.
He's not wearing uniforms.
This isn't an award ceremony.
- He's tall.
- He is...
Gosh, he's become handsome.
Hello.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- You look great.
- Why are you looking so handsome?
Hello.
Like I said before,
you should be tall like him.
Not like Kwang Soo.
- He looks so cool.
- This is how you should look.
- Well...
- He looks amazing.
- Good.
- He's our team.
I'll have him on our team.
Entry number eight.
(There's another monstrous rookie.)
(The cheerful music
raises the expectation.)
What's this song?
He dominates the mound
with his amazing slider.
The so-called, KK.
He's Kim Kwang Hyun.
(He led SK Wyverns to victory
in the Korean Series 4 times.)
(He's the living legend of KBO,
Kim Kwang Hyun.)
(After he conquered
the Korean league,)
(he joined Saint Louis
with uniform number 33.)
(He moved to the Saint Louis
Cardinals in the MLB.)
("The Best MLB Star Picked by
Baseball Card Companies")
("Kim Kwang Hyun Selected as
the Left Hand Pitcher of the Year")
(He will now become the legend
of the Major League.)
- He's a rookie.
- This is so cool.
What are you doing?
This is what he did.
He's the real ace player.
- This is amazing.
- Kwang Hyun, please come on up.
Right?
Nice to meet you.
I'm the team owner.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- You're so handsome.
(Suk Jin gives Kwang Hyun
a pat on the back like a coach.)
You look great.
- Please stand here.
- My gosh.
We finally have good players.
- They're finally here.
- Right.
(They've been looking forward
to meet the rookies.)
They are the ace players
for this draft.
- These two.
- They're finally here.
We have Ryu Hyun Jin
and Kim Kwang Hyun.
- Thank you for joining us today.
- Thank you.
(Thank you for joining us.)
Let me explain today's rules then.
- We should begin the draft.
- Okay. Let's go.
This is the Fiery Stove League Race.
Yoo Jae Suk and Yang Se Chan
are team owners.
- That sounds cool.
- And the rest of you are rookies.
He's wearing the coach's uniform.
The team owners were selected
by Ryu Hyun Jin and Kim Kwang Hyun.
They picked
the least favorite members...
for the team owners.
- What?
- They got selected.
What did you say?
They got selected by them.
- This is very offensive.
- They got selected.
- Well done.
- Good job.
That's good.
So does that mean
we're the worst team owners?
I wondered why
these two were team owners.
- I know.
- I was curious the whole time.
- Now I understand.
- This is ridiculous.
- My gosh.
- Okay. Let's continue.
Okay. Good.
The two teams will get...
different amounts of money
for their teams after each mission.
And the team owners will...
negotiate a salary
with each player in each round...
and pay them accordingly
with the money they won.
There are only two players
whom I want to negotiate with.
I'll kick the rest of them out.
I won't buy the rest of them...
- even if I get paid.
- No.
Aren't we having
a bench-clearing brawl?
- What?
- Bench-clearing.
Why do you want to fight?
If we lose, we should
turn things upside down.
(A player who used to be a bully
and likes to bust up everything)
The team owners will compete
against each other.
And the team owner who earned
more money will win the race...
and receive a prize.
The team owner who loses the race
will receive a penalty.
The players will compete
against each other as well.
Among 8 players, the top 3
with more money will win...
and receive prizes.
The player with the least money...
will receive a penalty.
(Today's race is both team
and individual competition.)
Now we'll hold the draft,
so each team can allocate
new players to their teams.
- Yes, here we go!
- Let's do this.
(2021 Running League Rookie Draft
begins now!)
Gosh, I'm nervous.
(Team Owner Yu, Team Owner Yang)
We can use only 500 dollars
to negotiate...
the two players' annual salaries.
It's so unrealistic.
It doesn't have
the same value as dollars.
All right.
Each team can allocate four players.
- Okay, four players.
- The rookies...
- must choose a team.
- Four players?
- If I choose one, I go all the way.
- Well, anyway,
I can't say which players...
but I won't spend more than
two dollars for some of them.
(He announced
a salary cap of two dollars.)
- I'm limiting it to a few cents.
- Oh, come on.
I'll spend only a few cents...
so that I can spend all the money
on one particular player.
All right then.
Before the owners
negotiate their salaries,
the players are going to
throw balls at a target...
to show them their abilities.
Oh, I like that.
If needed, the owners can
ask the players anytime...
to test their skills.
(Staring)
Hyun Jin,
he's bulking up these days.
Bulking up?
(They said
there won't be a cross talk.)
- Okay.
- No wonder.
Actually, Sung Jae
agreed to do this...
on one condition today.
He doesn't want a cross talk,
got that?
He won't have conversations.
- He'll only say what he needs to.
- All right.
Only the bust shot and no cross talk
are in the contract.
- So how much weight did you gain?
- What?
(So how much weight did you gain?)
- Why would you ask that?
- Don't ask him that.
- How can you ask him that?
- You can ask him in person.
I'm trying to gain weight.
(Suk Jin's question interrupted
Sung Jae from hosting the show.)
All right then.
We will begin the draft now.
- You're not going to answer?
- My goodness.
I can't tell you my weight.
- You don't have to talk with him.
- All right.
- Just stop talking about it.
- My weight is a secret.
- You don't have talk with him.
- You're asking too many questions.
You don't have to answer.
Now we'll introduce two players.
The first two candidates are
Kim Jong Kook and Lee Kwang Soo!
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
(Frowning)
I'm competing against a Japanese
player from the Yomiuri Giants.
(A player from a gang and a player
from a neighboring country)
What are your positions?
I'm a batter. I love to hit.
Can we see your batting stance?
- My stance?
- Yes.
(Flinching)
(He grabs the bat
like a gang member.)
What about...
- What about you, Kka Chi?
- Kka Chi?
Yes.
- Jo Kka Chi?
- Well, yes.
(Suddenly he talks about
Kwang Soo's character in a movie.)
- I'm not that Jo Kka Chi.
- No?
- No.
- Isn't it Sul Kka Chi?
Are you talking about Sul Kka Chi?
I played Jo Kka Chi,
not Sul Kka Chi.
(So what's Jo Kka Chi's
baseball position?)
What about you, Kka Chi?
Something like a pitcher.
Something like a pitcher?
- Something like a pitcher?
- What does that mean?
- Can you show us what you can do?
- Yes, show us your pose.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
- Kwang Soo, hold on.
- Yes?
You're supposed to
pull back your left foot.
(Changing the pose in a hurry)
Your left foot. That's it.
(The foreign player tried
to look cool, but got embarrassed.)
- All right.
- No, I was faking it.
- My goodness.
- I was going to fool them.
All right then.
It was just a fake.
What are you, a fool?
You're like this.
I didn't want you
to know if I'm right or left handed.
So I tried to fool you
by pulling the wrong leg.
(Brazen)
All right.
You're all rookie players.
So don't point out
the styles of others.
All right. I won't.
Now the owners will
decide their salary range.
The two owners.
But I don't want to leave my team.
I love batting.
- You're giving him that much?
- For me...
- I'm going to pass on him.
- I love batting.
- You're sorting Jong Kook out?
- Yes.
You can't say his name out loud.
- You're sorting Jong Kook out?
- Yes.
- What?
- You can't say his name out loud.
You should whisper.
Why would you say it out loud?
- You're sorting me out?
- No, we're having a meeting here.
All right. I understand.
Now the two owners will announce
the players' salaries.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Right away?
(Kwang Soo 10 cents, 2 dollars,
Jong Kook 50 cents, 1 dollar)
This is our last offer.
(He can't believe this.)
We can't give them
a higher salary than this.
Would you accept their terms?
Mr. Yang's prices
are more than double.
You may choose a team.
They should pick Se Chan.
What should I do?
I can't take 10 cents.
(Holding back their laughter)
10 cents? Are you kidding me?
- He's cruel.
- Maybe the team is poor.
- Gosh.
- 10 cents.
- I feel really bad about this.
- 10 cents? Is he joking?
You can't buy anything
with 10 cents these days.
- Sung Jae.
- You're too mean.
I can't give
more than 10 cents for him.
- He's very stingy.
- It's final.
We have great benefits.
So choose us.
Jong Kook can't choose Mr. Yang
to get only one dollar.
- You're right.
- He offered Kwang Soo two dollars.
- Okay, you brat.
- Look over here.
Brat? I'm the owner of the team.
The salary I'm offering you is
five times bigger than Kwang Soo's.
- All right. I choose you.
- Okay.
He's a proud man.
So you're getting 50 cents?
- He values me more than Kwang Soo.
- Yes, that's right.
He's worth five times bigger
than Kwang Soo.
I will choose Yang Se Chan's team.
Thank you for joining our team
at 2 dollars.
- I will choose Mr. Yu.
- Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
- This is great.
- This is it.
I offered you a salary that's
five times higher than his.
(Bumping)
- Thank you in advance.
- Thank you.
Now we'll introduce
two more players for you.
Ryu Hyun Jin and Kim Kwang Hyun!
(Ryu Hyun Jin and Kim Kwang Hyun)
- You're calling them right away?
- Here they are.
(As Sung Jae calls out their names,)
(the team owners instantly stand up
and give a big round of applause.)
- Here they are.
- What's this?
- Thank you in advance.
- I'm going to spend big money.
- Mr. Ryu.
- I'll spend big.
- Don't spend too much on them!
Don't spend too much on them!
- All right.
- There are still many players.
He's right.
(The owners are ignoring Suk Jin.)
- It's good to see you.
- Let's hear them out.
The money I can spend on them is...
I have more than 400 dollars.
We have two players for you.
Would you like to
see their abilities?
- Sure, sure.
- Of course.
I know what they're good at.
But I still need to
see their skills.
They've already proved
their abilities in Major League.
- But we will have them...
- Can I refuse to do this?
throw balls at a target 7m away.
I can't believe I'm about
to see this here.
They only have one chance
so they must be nervous.
Will you throw a fastball
or a slide ball?
- Whatever you want.
- Okay, then can you...
- throw a change-up ball?
- Sure.
(His specialty, change-up ball)
He's going to hit the target
with a change-up ball?
We're about to see
his change-up ball?
It's a change-up ball.
- Yes, a change-up ball.
- Okay, it's Ryu Hyun Jin!
It's Ryu Hyun Jin!
What was that?
- Hey.
- Wait a minute.
- It didn't hit the center.
- Gosh.
- What was that?
- You didn't hit it.
- Hey.
- Wait a minute.
The ball didn't hit the center.
It was far away from the center.
Kwang Soo, it turns out
we're not that bad.
I told you it's hard to hit it.
Yes, it is. It's too far away.
(This is how they did
a minute ago during the draft.)
(They did their best to throw...)
- What was that?
- Mine hit closer.
My gosh, that was pathetic.
(Korean Monster laughed at them
not knowing what was about to come.)
(Now he's become
the laughing stock.)
- What was that?
- It hit far away!
- It's totally a ball.
- It is a ball.
Anchor Bae, can you say
that it is a ball?
- It's a perfect strike.
- It went over two rows.
- This is a strike?
- Yes, a perfect strike.
(That's a perfect strike?)
- That's a strike?
- Come on.
He's playing favorites with him.
It was a dead ball
if it hit someone.
Anchor Bae,
your suit is about to burst.
Come on, it's a ball.
- That wasn't a strike.
- It's a ball.
- It went way beyond the target.
- That was a ball.
Kim Kwang Hyun,
can we see your slide ball?
- I'll throw a fastball.
- A fastball?
Should I make it fun or serious?
- Throw it seriously.
- Yes, be serious.
(Will Kim Kwang Hyun throw
a serious fastball?)
I told you it's hard to throw.
See?
- See?
- We were better!
(He couldn't even hit the target.)
(What on earth was that?)
- See?
- We were better!
Yes, we were better.
(He threw the ball seriously,
but gave them a big laugh.)
(After Se Chan sees
Kim Kwang Hyun's terrible throw,)
(he writes down a salary for him
right away.)
- What was that?
- Hey.
We were better.
Here's the result.
10 dollars for Ryu Hyun Jin
and 5 dollars for Kim Kwang Hyun.
(Their value plummets.)
Gosh, you're terrible.
It's so funny
how they're so embarrassed.
- There are metal bars behind.
- Yes.
I guess this is good
for the rest of us.
- Yes, you're right.
- We can get some money.
- This isn't over for us.
- My goodness.
(The two owners
are seriously worried.)
Gosh, I was going to
put all the money.
It might be better
to be called up after them.
(The major leaguers
seem humbler than before.)
Okay. Here's my number.
Show us your numbers. 1, 2, 3!
Mine is 165 dollars and 160 dollars.
- 160 dollars and 180 dollars.
- Since they are...
(They don't know how to react
to their poor hospitality.)
Since they're
both famous major league players,
I put a premium for that.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
Make it 250 dollars.
- Make it 250 dollars.
- My goodness.
Wait a minute. He's the team owner.
A player can't force the team owner.
(He didn't do well as a player
so he wants to be a sports agent?)
What do you think you're doing?
- Make it 250 dollars.
- Excuse me.
Didn't you get 50 cents
when you joined the team?
My goodness.
- Just sit down.
- What are you doing?
- I changed my job.
- What?
If I make it 250 dollars,
I won't have any left.
- Mr. 50 Cents, please step aside.
- Go away.
- Mr. 50 Cents.
- Make it 250 dollars.
I could even kick you
out of the team.
This is why I didn't
want to sign him.
Just make it 250 dollars.
If you make it,
I want five percent of that money.
- Jong Kook.
- What?
That pants make you
look like a gang member.
Now the players
will choose the team they want.
(It's time for the players
to choose the team.)
Hyun Jin might feel bad
about the price.
Yes, since his price is lower
than Kwang Hyun's.
Why don't you negotiate?
Wait a minute.
- Mr. Yang.
- Yes.
I think you're trying to get
a player you can control better.
- You're right.
- Right?
- Hyun Jin is older than me, so...
- He wants to control them.
- it'll be harder for me to handle.
- My goodness.
So Kwang Hyun would be better even
if it's my first time seeing him.
Yes, it seemed like you set
their salaries based on that.
You're right. I'd like to
control them easily.
- I want to feel comfortable.
- So what are you going to do?
I will choose Mr. Yang's team.
- Oh, okay.
- Mr. Yang.
- You made up your mind?
- Yes.
And I don't need to negotiate.
That is neat.
He only has 300 dollars,
and he offered more than half.
(Faltering)
Wait. I want to give him
another 10 dollars.
Wait, Kwang Hyun.
- He sounds nice.
- I'll give you another 10 dollars.
Hang on. I get it.
My offer is 190 dollars.
- Why would you give him a raise...
- Hang on a second.
just because he sounds nice?
He's a good negotiator.
I'll add another 50 dollars
and make it 200 dollars.
I guess all we need to do here
is be nice.
I want to give him a compliment.
- I made it 200 dollars.
- Good.
You wrote 10 cents for me,
and now it's 200 dollars?
- How much is it? 190 dollars?
- 190 dollars.
Okay. My offer is 200 dollars.
I'm giving you another 10 dollars.
That's quite high.
I'm satisfied with the amount.
- Really?
- I'll gladly accept the offer.
- Okay. Good.
- Okay.
Kim Kwang Hyun joins Team Yang,
and Ryu Hyun Jin joins Team Yu.
Thank you.
- Our team...
- We should take a photo.
- Let's take a photo together.
- Take a photo?
("Kim Kwang Hyun Joins Team Yang
for 190 Dollars")
("Kim Kwang Hyun is Satisfied
with His Salary of 190 Dollars")
Okay!
- They didn't do it with us.
- We should take a photo too.
You didn't take photos with us.
- 50 Cents, stay out of this.
- I will...
Hey, mister!
- Why did you not do it with us?
- 50 Cents, stay out of this.
Come here.
- It's a secret that I bought you.
- Come here.
Smile. Go ahead and smile.
(The rookie shows his love toward
his team in an aggressive way.)
- Done.
- I'm really disappointed.
I was holding Se Chan's hand
to take a photo, but he was like...
(Grasping his hand)
He pushed my hand away.
The third candidates are...
Song Ji Hyo and Jeon So Min.
Please come on out.
I guess I should pass on them.
Gosh, hang on.
I have no plan to spend a lot.
Can I ask how much
you know about baseball?
I'm a cheerleader.
- Really?
- All of a sudden?
She's changing her stance.
It's a new plan.
(She changes her position and
tries to win the owners over.)
Hey.
She's changed her plans.
She's good.
- Okay.
- She's funny.
Hey, it's like...
Ji Hyo, is there anything you can do
regarding baseball?
She is good at drinking beer.
- Right.
- She drinks beer quickly.
She's good at
having a beer with chicken.
Beer killer.
- I once threw the ceremonial pitch.
- I know.
- She threw the ceremonial pitch.
- She did?
I did it twice.
Really?
If you throw it to the center,
it means you're better than them.
Song Ji Hyo is up.
(Ji Hyo is trained with chicken
and beer. How will she throw?)
(Hurling it down to the ground)
Thank you for showing how you hurl
the ball to the ground.
(She flung it to the ground.)
(Maybe she enjoyed
too much chicken and beer.)
Thank you for showing how you hurl
the ball to the ground.
- This happens a lot.
- Right.
- Who's up next?
- It's not easy.
- So Min.
- Yes.
Throw the ball.
Don't pick your nose.
(She tries all the stuff
she's seen before.)
- Her face is really funny.
- What's wrong with your face?
She should be a comedienne.
Good. Hang on.
(She didn't expect herself
to throw a fastball.)
That was good.
(Flustered)
What happened?
- That's enough.
- That was good.
What's going on?
She's better than Ryu Hyun Jin.
- So Min.
- She's better than both of them.
What kind of cheerleader
is so good at baseball?
I'm 100 percent sure
she played catch with her boyfriend.
- Let's continue.
- Show us.
- I didn't think about this.
- The problem is,
we have the minimum amount.
- I want to negotiate.
- I should've offered more...
- to Hyun Jin and Kwang Hyun.
- I know.
- Let's start the negotiation.
- Congratulations.
- She joined Team Yang.
- It's a deal.
Now, we'll carry out the last round.
- They are Ji Suk Jin and Haha.
- All right.
- Hello.
- To check their capabilities,
- I want to see them dance.
- First...
(He starts dancing right away.)
I'd like to see you dance.
Good. You're good.
You're really good.
- I don't like him.
- I like him.
He's my style.
(He shows off
his old dance moves too.)
(They show off their talent
to negotiate their salary.)
Excuse me.
My ERA is 0.2.
I should spend all my money anyway.
(They offer high salaries
even though they don't want to.)
It's 58 dollars.
Gosh, it's zero.
I just wrote it because
I have to spend all the money.
I get only 2 dollars
while Suk Jin gets 49.5 dollars?
I'll play as much as 50 cents today.
This is the result of
2021 Running League Rookie Draft.
Team Yoo will take a photo together.
1, 2, and 3.
("Team Yoo Signed New Contracts with
Ryu Hyun Jin and 3 Other Players")
Now it's Team Yang.
- The players of Team Yang are...
- I'll stand in the middle.
- He's being serious.
- Lee Kwang Soo, Kim Kwang Hyun,
Song Ji Hyo, and Haha.
(The owner bought
only the obedient players.)
("Team Yang Signed New Contracts
with Kim Kwang Hyun and 3 players")
This is it for
2021 Running League Rookie Draft.
- I'm Bae Sung Jae. Thank you.
- Thank you.
(We'd like to thank Bae Sung Jae
for the draft and cross talk.)
(All the team owners
and players are satisfied.)
- Please gather around.
- Okay.
- It's so pretty.
- Jong Kook is not here.
- What?
- Jong Kook isn't here.
I'm going to sell him...
in the next season anyway.
How dare he tell me...
to offer 300 dollars to Hyun Jin?
I'm only as good as 50 cents.
Nice going.
If I got a dollar,
I would've been here on time.
- Good one.
- Nice tantrum.
He's throwing a tantrum. Good one.
- Mr. Loser.
That was a good one.
- Okay.
- Hey.
How can you be sitting here...
- when your seniors are around?
- Come on, get up.
We have many players
who are more expensive than you.
- Look at him.
- What's wrong with you?
I was paid 50 cents,
so I'm doing only this much.
He got 10 cents,
but he's standing up.
Let's line up
in the order of salary.
With the pandemic, we had to stop...
our daily lives this year, and
we couldn't go to baseball games.
That's really sad.
To make you feel better,
we prepared some snacks...
that we usually eat
at baseball stadiums.
- Good.
- What's all this?
- Hot dogs.
- I'm hungry.
The hot dog looks good.
It looks great.
Hey, this is New York hot dog.
This isn't for product placement.
- It's not for product placement.
- We paid for them.
- It's not product placement, right?
- No.
I was going to eat it
in front of the cameras.
You should put it on here.
- This one?
- The ketchup.
Should I turn it?
You can turn it.
When I went to watch Hyun Jin's
game, I had a beer with a hot dog.
(It reminds them of the old days.)
Jong Kook is like
the fairy of victory.
I won every time Jong Kook
came to watch my game.
- Really?
- It was 100 percent.
This is good.
The staff got us some snacks because
the major-leaguers are here.
Are we really eating it like this?
We will explain the rules
for the next mission while you eat.
The first mission is
Bunt Foot Volleyball.
This is how baseball players are
trained to improve bunt performance.
- Seriously?
- Instead of using a tennis racket,
you will hit the dodge ball
using baseball bats.
If you fail to hit the ball over
the net, you lose a point.
Okay. I get it.
I'll give you some time to practice.
We should send it over the net
within three attempts.
Good.
- Like this?
- That was good.
Nice.
It's still in.
- Hit it.
- Okay!
- Nice shot.
- What?
(He spiked the dodge ball.)
- Yes!
- Nice.
Okay.
Do you have to hit it so hard?
Let's start.
Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- Good luck.
Hold the bat short.
Good.
My ball.
Okay.
- Two.
- Where is it going?
- Hit it.
- Okay.
(Team Yoo lost a point.)
- Nice. It's 1 to 0.
It's okay.
"Nice. It's 1 to 0"? Okay.
- There will be bench-clearing.
- "Nice. It's 1 to 0"?
- There might be bench-clearing.
- Hey.
- Okay.
Okay. You gangling fool.
Do it right.
You gangling fool, okay.
Here we go.
Kwang Soo, you shouldn't
touch the black part.
You should hold it like this.
Did he grab the black part?
- That's against the rule.
- No.
Did you grab the black part?
That's a foul.
- I just did it for a moment.
- Don't tell him.
Don't you dare do it again.
Do you have to say that
holding a bat?
- I'm holding a bat for the game.
- He's scary.
- Okay.
- All right. Let's continue.
Okay, go. Let's go.
- Okay. Good.
- That's good.
- Kwang Hyun.
- Nice serve.
- That's it.
- It's coming.
It's okay, it's okay!
(Is he passing the ball
to the floor?)
- Hey.
- Jong Kook.
- My gosh.
- Jong Kook!
Darn it!
I can't believe this.
Jong Kook.
(Laughing at him)
Hey, 50 Cents.
50 Cents.
- That 50 Cents.
- What's okay?
(Imitating Jong Kook)
Hey. You should use 49.5 Dollars
instead of 50 Cents.
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
(He's approaching the net.)
Do you think this is a wall?
- All right.
- What is he doing with the bat?
- Mr. 50 Cents.
- Just be as good as your salary.
- 50 Cents...
- Okay.
- All right.
- It wasn't close enough.
Mr. 50 Cents. Go back to your spot.
Jong Kook is so attractive
when he plays the foot volleyball.
- Here we go.
- Go, Kwang Hyun!
What's wrong with you?
- Okay!
- What's wrong with you, Kwang Hyun?
What's wrong with you?
(He hurls himself down.)
- Okay.
- What was that?
What were you doing?
What was that, Kwang Hyun?
What are you doing?
- Why...
- It was a short slapstick comedy.
Good.
- Let's go.
- We can do this.
- That's it.
- Mine.
This one is pretty.
- Good.
- This one is pretty.
- This is a good one.
- Hey.
My goodness.
(He said it was pretty.)
(But he sent the ball
straight to the net.)
(Shouting)
Go back there. Come over here.
(They start to laugh at him.)
(He makes fun of Jong Kook
walking on his knees.)
So Min, you were supposed to hit it.
(He's hammering with a bat.)
I love Jong Kook
when he plays foot volleyball.
(The player looks humane
when he plays foot volleyball.)
- He's humane.
- He's making a fuss, but he's bad.
Hey, 50 Cents.
He got 50 cents for a reason.
Here I go.
- Make it low.
- Good.
- All right.
- Kwang Hyun.
- Hit it lightly. Good.
- Move over.
(Kwang Soo's serve
is a little too long.)
- It's in.
Move over.
- No.
- We're so lucky.
Move over.
(The ball hit the bat
right in the middle.)
(The ball flew back.)
No.
Hit it.
(And he missed the ball.)
(Team Yang scored another point
thanks to Kwang Hyun.)
What happened?
The ball went in that direction.
- The ball hit his bat.
- It hit his bat. Gosh.
- I didn't expect that.
- I got so lucky.
It hit his bat and came to our side.
Hey, 50 Cents, come out.
Come out of the court.
Will you play?
(As the team lost a few points,
Suk Jin will replace Jong Kook.)
- Okay.
- Haha, it's already a won game.
- Got it.
- We already won.
- We can do this.
- It's hard to hit it.
- Okay. Nice.
- That'll be hard to hit.
- He has good skills.
- Oh, no. Hey.
Kwang Hyun, hit it over the net.
- Good job.
- Hit it over the net.
(He hit the ball backward.)
(Hyun Jin received the ball.)
- No!
- Darn it.
(But Jae Suk failed.)
You should've hit it upward.
We're doing so well.
Then it would've flown over the net.
Okay.
We're doing so well.
- Good job.
- We have such a large skill gap.
- Exactly.
- True.
- Kwang Soo.
- Are you going to do it?
- It's okay. You can keep playing.
- Go and play.
- That's okay.
- We're winning by a huge margin.
That's ridiculous. Hey, hold on.
- Wait. Hold on.
- Gosh.
Kwang Hyun told me to replace him
saying we're winning.
I'm a little offended.
How large is the margin?
It is now a set point.
It'll end if we score a point.
How about Jong Kook replaces So Min?
What do you think?
- Jong Kook.
- Let's...
Let's win this game.
Let's go.
I'll make our team win.
- I'll stand in the front.
- Where will you stand?
I won't go easy on them
from now on.
- Jong Kook, receive the ball.
- I'll defend the attacks.
Jong Kook, will you receive it?
Okay. Stay there. I'll receive it.
Okay. Let's do this.
(It's a set point,
and Haha will serve.)
Okay.
(The ball fell in a good spot.)
(Okay!)
(Why won't you... Darn.)
- Okay.
- Why won't you... Darn.
(They didn't know who should hit it
and ended up missing it.)
Gosh. You should've received it.
- Why did you... Hold on.
- You should've hit it.
- Why do we have such poor teamwork?
- You said you'd hit it.
(Team Yang won Round 1.)
Let's switch sides.
I moved aside
so you could receive it.
- So Min, you play this time.
- Gosh.
- This is driving me nuts.
- I'll sit this one out.
Suk Jin ruined the game.
Here we go.
- Nice!
- Okay. That's good.
(Tossing it to Suk Jin)
- Hit it upward.
- Run, Suk Jin. Move your body.
(Big Nose's feet are
stuck on the floor.)
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- Run. Move your body, will you?
Suk Jin, that was your ball.
You were closer to the ball.
No. She was closer to the ball.
No. You were much closer
to the ball.
He wouldn't even bother running.
- Suk Jin.
- Hey, why didn't you run to it?
- I ran to it.
- Do what you're paid to do.
- Suk Jin. Suk Jin.
- She's so annoying. Hey!
- You should be ready to run.
- Suk Jin, listen.
This is a mess.
Understood.
I'll hit it toward Suk Jin.
No, don't do that.
- Hit it in this direction.
- Good.
- Receive it. That's good.
- Good job.
- Why did you hit it like that?
- So Min.
- Hit it.
- There you go.
(She hit it backward!)
Okay. He received it. Kwang Hyun.
Hey, wait.
Nice!
(Nice shot!)
(He hit it accurately
to make it fall inside the court.)
- Great job.
- That was amazing.
You did a great job.
- Good job, Kwang Hyun.
- That was incredible.
- It was like a scene from a movie.
- It was incredible.
Let's watch it again.
- Okay. He received it. Kwang Hyun.
- Hey, wait.
Nice!
- My goodness.
- He couldn't do any better.
If this were an actual game,
- he'd be a national team player.
- I can't deny that.
It was incredible.
Listen to me, guys.
However great it may have looked,
they scored only one point.
- True.
- Don't be discouraged.
- 50 Cents.
- They scored only one point.
You should do better than that
because you got paid 50 dollars.
- Suk Jin.
- That's funny.
Don't be disrespectful to her.
- You should've turned around...
- Wait. Hang on.
- and hit the ball.
- Listen, Suk Jin.
- It's okay.
- Yes, sir.
You don't have much time left
to play for our team anyway.
So do whatever you want.
(Big Nose will be
kicked out very soon.)
Go ahead and play the game
however you want.
- I don't think you'll play...
- I'll do my best.
- for our team for so long.
- I love Team Yu.
- Hyun Jin will serve.
- Stay focused.
We have such poor teamwork, Mr. Yu.
- Yes, sir.
- Wait. Hyun Jin.
You're the highest-paid player
on our team. Don't let me down.
Right. You're doing well, but...
Understood? Don't let me down.
Hyun Jin is doing well.
Hyun Jin is undeniably
the best player on your team.
Go.
(Team Yu's last hope
Hyun Jin will serve.)
Okay. Good.
- We need Hyun Jin to step it up.
- Ji Hyo.
- Nice! Good job.
- Okay.
- This is your last chance.
- It's my ball.
(It's my ball!)
- Gosh.
- All right.
- It's my ball.
- Come on.
(The ball hit the net.)
- What was that?
- Hey!
- You got paid 200 dollars.
- Gosh, you brat.
What's wrong with you?
- What was that? You brat.
- Okay.
- It was a mistake.
- Hey.
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Yes?
You seem overly passionate
about the team.
It's not like that.
- Try to be a bit less passionate.
- All right.
- I thought you were the team owner.
- I feel bad I can't pay you more.
- He's acting like the team owner.
- You're overly passionate.
- You know what I mean, right?
- You should be more passionate...
- about our team. I'll try.
- Try to think of yourself more.
- Give me some slack, will you?
- Cheer up.
- He's actually not that good.
- I'm his fan.
I bet he will make a mistake.
- Okay. Toss it.
- Nice.
Okay. So Min, it's your ball.
Hit it.
- That's good.
- Okay.
- Didn't you hit it over the net?
- No, I failed.
- She's lousy at this.
- Hey.
She doesn't have basic skills.
Mr. Yu. Mr. Yu, will you...
let So Min keep playing?
I think we need a substitution.
Suk Jin, come out.
(I think we need a substitution.
Suk Jin, come out.)
- Wait. You can't...
- You made the right decision.
- Wait.
- I'm glad you made the decision.
- You're too distracting.
- Please.
- Right. He's too distracting.
- Hey!
She's the one who made a mistake.
Come on out.
Will you keep running your team
like this?
You shouldn't run the team
like this.
- Suk Jin, step off the court.
- I mean...
- Leave the court.
- Okay.
- Can I talk to you briefly?
- Of course, Mr. Yang.
He called him "Mr. Yang".
Gosh, seriously.
Okay. This time, I'll make sure...
Nice serve.
(Screaming)
Move.
(He hit it with a monstrous scream
and strength.)
- That was unexpected.
- Good job.
- That was a back attack.
- It was unexpected.
- What was that?
- He suddenly screamed and hit it.
- Great job.
- How was my back attack?
- That was great.
- It was good, right?
- Yes.
- My back attack.
- That was too much.
- Why did you do that?
- What's wrong with you?
- It was too much.
- Don't hit it too hard.
- Be careful. You saw that, right?
- Gosh.
- You saw that, right?
He has some mental issues.
He's scaring us.
He must keep it together
during a game.
My player has some issues.
He should improve
his mental strength.
- I'm sorry.
- They're complaining.
- We can do this!
- Focus!
(After he pulled himself together,
the game resumed.)
- That's good.
- Okay. Good.
Okay. Good.
Just hit it over the net.
- Hey!
- Gosh, seriously.
(Gosh, seriously.)
- This won't work.
- Okay.
- Why did you...
- You stand...
- You stand in the front.
Stand in the front.
- Gosh, I...
- We almost scored a point.
They're too scary to play with.
- You idiot.
- Out, out.
(Out?)
- It went out.
- They're too scary to play with.
(While Jae Suk was being scolded
for his mistake...)
Haha.
Now is the time. Let's do it.
(He hit the ball toward the wall.)
(He got caught right away.)
- It went out.
- What was that?
- You're so bad at this.
- What did you do?
- Gosh. Why...
- Don't go.
- Why can't you do it?
That was funny.
- It went out.
- Why did you do that?
That was ridiculous.
I'll do better this time.
I won't be too greedy.
- You tried to pull a trick.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, hey.
- Oh, gosh.
(Hyun Jin launches
a surprise attack.)
- Hey, hey.
- Oh, gosh.
- Oh, yes.
- Okay.
- Gosh, Hyun Jin.
- Hey!
(He made a mistake
while trying to use the same trick.)
(It serves you right.)
(It was even funnier
because he tried a sly strategy.)
- He made the same mistake.
- My gosh.
- No need to rush.
- Why...
Why did he learn sly tricks
from them?
Gosh. Why did he learn such a thing?
Incoming.
Okay.
- Good. That was great.
- Nice.
- Up, up. Good.
- Good job.
(Screaming)
Why?
(He screamed again.)
My goodness.
- That's enough.
- Mr. Yu!
- I saw him...
- I barely got a chance...
- I saw Suk Jin hesitating.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Hey. Come on.
- I was surprised too.
- What is wrong with him?
- This is driving me crazy.
- I'm just passionate...
- Please don't do that.
- I'm just passionate. That's all.
- It's good to be passionate, but...
- It's a good thing, but...
- Calm down.
Okay. I understand.
- What's the score?
- It's a set point.
- I see.
- If we score a point, we'll win.
Yes. The match will end
if you lose in this round.
- Let's end it.
- Go, Team Yu!
(Could Team Yoo be able to
win this round?)
- Gosh.
- That was really good.
- Haha.
- He received it.
Here. Hit it, Kwang Soo.
- Nice.
- Good.
(He tossed it.)
(Kwang Hyun ducked quickly.)
(The ball fell on Team Yu's side
of the court.)
- Move.
- Kwang Hyun, get up.
You must pull this off.
(He hit the ball right in the net.)
(Jong Kook lost his temper
as the team owner made a mistake.)
Gosh. Don't be greedy.
- What a shame.
- Don't be greedy.
(Team Yang won.)
- I was surprised.
- Gosh.
- How did you dodge it?
- You were amazing.
It was incredible.
(Screaming)
It was amazing.
Why did you do that?
- Why did you do that?
- Exactly.
I can't believe you.
It was a good chance.
- There was no one to block it.
- You could get it over the net.
I'm the team owner. Gosh.
How dare you use violence
against your team owner?
My gosh. What was that?
If Jong Kook gets kicked out,
I'll transfer to that team.
- We almost won.
- He's invincible.
That team's owner must have
a lot to think about.
Maybe I should quit
running this stupid team.
They always argue with one another.
As a result of the match,
Team Yang that won the match
will receive 500 dollars.
Yes!
And Team Yoo will receive
300 dollars.
It's time for
the first salary negotiation.
The team owners...
should decide the order
of the players to meet.
Also,
You have 200 dollars left
on top of the money you just got.
You can use that money.
700 dollars in total?
Each player will meet
their team owner,
and if the negotiation
falls through,
- meet with the other team owner.
- I see.
If both teams refuse to draft you,
you'll be paid half the amount
the first team offered.
- Really?
- You need to impress us,
the team owners.
If you're offered 10 cents,
you'll get paid only 5 cents.
- That's right.
- Okay. Got it.
Okay. Then please move to
the negotiation site.
(The 1st salary negotiation!)
(Unlike how they may look,
these are the team owners' offices.)
(The players are waiting
in front of the offices.)
I have no choice.
The salary negotiation
will be brutal.
I wanted to let you know in advance.
Why did you tell us that
when some of us aren't here?
To be honest, I'm in a very bad mood
right now.
How dare you torture me
when I'm your team owner?
(How dare you torture me
when I'm your team owner?)
- He did that.
- Gosh. I'm speechless.
- Drop them from the team.
- I mean...
I'm the team owner, you know.
- I bet you're thirsty.
- I mean...
Please take a sip.
(He pretends to be loyal.)
- Hold on.
- I just want to say...
- Watch your health.
- The team's a mess because of you.
- I see.
- Is that so?
For someone worth only 50 cents,
I showed a lot of love for the team.
- He...
- Who else is better than me?
- I know.
- You should give him 50 cents more.
- That's why he's complaining.
- Jong Kook...
- It's to save money for others.
- A loyal teammate is worth having.
- Yes, having you on the team...
- Of course.
I prevent conflicts
from bubbling over.
Where's the door?
They're all tied up.
- I'll make you one!
- Sure, I get it.
- Let me make one for you.
- Gosh.
Unbelievable.
- Let me go over the rules.
- Sure.
- Each team has its own budget.
- Right.
The former 200 dollars plus what
you earned in the previous game.
You may utilize it
at your discretion.
So they can do whatever they want?
The teams still need
to be balanced out though.
Why on earth do they get
so much authority?
The team owners are
in a league of their own anyway.
After deciding on the order,
each player will get
two minutes to negotiate.
Renew the contract by that time
or the deal is off.
That means you'll have to negotiate
with the other team owner.
If a contract with
the other team falls through,
you'll be forced to resign
with your former team...
at half the original rate.
(The final option
is a pay-cut of 50 percent.)
Could the team owners
offer us less money?
They could, but then
they'll lose key players.
Our team owner has
nearly twice his budget.
(Who will hit the jackpot
in the first salary negotiation?)
Please begin
your first negotiations.
You have two minutes.
- Suk Jin, it's good to see you.
- You too.
You've been working hard
for this team.
I only have a love for this team...
- and...
- Hold on.
What's your current salary?
- It's 49.5 dollars.
- 49.5 dollars, I see.
You got lucky last season,
didn't you?
So the salary I propose is this.
Well...
- May I say something though?
- Sure.
There's a team that wants me.
(There's a team that wants me.)
I hope you consider that.
(Jae Suk snorts
at Suk Jin's intentions.)
- I hate switching teams.
- Is that so?
That's not what I want.
I want to set down roots.
- I grew attached to the team.
- Then...
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk
offers him a new salary.)
What?
(20 dollars)
- I...
- Are you kidding me?
I cut 50 percent.
- You cut my salary?
- I guess...
I could add five more dollars.
Is this the "maxi"?
The maximum, you mean?
What on earth is "maxi"?
Is that a sausage brand?
(Suk Jin's lost for words
at the salary proposal.)
All right, then.
- Okay, I get it.
- Right.
- You're not signing the contract?
- I'm disappointed.
- I won't.
- I see.
Please get going then.
You heard my offer,
so you may leave.
Darn, that's cheap of you. So cheap.
Hello.
This is so that I won't
have to look you in the eyes.
It could sway my decision.
I understand how it can
weaken someone.
Yang Se Chan...
How much do you think
you should receive?
During my first season as a rookie,
I started off
at too low of a salary.
- How much was it?
- Two dollars.
- Two dollars?
- Yes.
- If you want to win...
- Yes?
- You'll have to be more generous.
- Right.
I have 700 dollars to spend,
so tell me the amount...
you think you should receive.
- About 150 dollars.
- Wait. What did you just say?
- 150 dollars.
- Well...
- What?
- 150 dollars.
- I...
- I'll be loyal forever.
But even 15 dollars
seems like too much.
(The air is stiff
around the negotiation table.)
- Mr. Yang, please hear me out.
- Sure.
Se Chan, I say this as your friend.
- But I'm the team owner.
- I say this as your friend.
Go ahead.
The amount you offer me...
will be wired into your account...
once the next game is over.
That's absurd!
Anyway,
I don't think I can spend
more than 20 dollars on you.
(20 dollars out of 700?)
- I mean...
- 20 dollars?
- I'm afraid so.
You're going from 2 to 20 dollars,
which is a 1,000 percent raise.
- Here's your last chance. 5, 4...
- 4...
- 3...
- I'll sign for 100 dollars then.
- No, even 60 is too much.
- 2, 1.
Leave.
(The petty friend explodes.)
Hold on. He's beating up
his team owner!
He's beating up the team owner.
Stop hitting me!
(Is this how negotiations go?)
(A dirty negotiation process
you'd never see in the big league)
He's beating up his team owner!
He's beating up the team owner.
He's kicking me!
(The team owner's wishy-washy
attitude makes him explode.)
You're kicking your team owner.
(Spitting)
How crazy must one be
to beat up his team owner?
(Kwang Soo's negotiation
falls through.)
What a piece of trash.
(Each team is looking
at serious pay-cuts.)
30 dollars. So Min, you see...
I hear that the other team owner...
- is an ex.
- No way.
No, there must be
a misunderstanding.
- Will you sign with this team?
- Sure.
(So Min signs a contract
at 40 dollars.)
He cut my salary.
Since you did a good job,
I'm going to give you a raise.
Please sign.
(He offers 80 dollars to Ji Hyo,
which is a slight increase.)
This I'll remember.
(She's the first
to receive a raise!)
I have no intention
of leaving this team.
- Great.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
- Haha, it's you.
- Hello.
- I saw you doing a great job.
- Thanks.
You see,
I'm working with a tight budget.
What do you mean?
We earned a lot for you earlier.
You already sound annoyed.
Hardly. I find you admirable.
Let's take a look
at your previous salary.
It's 58 dollars.
Next will be a round of quizzes,
which means
I can't possibly sign you.
- You see, Mr. Yang...
- Yes?
I'm smarter than the majority here.
- Is that so?
- Of course.
- I'll ask you a question then.
- Sure.
- If you answer correctly,
- Yes?
I'll consider...
- 100 dollars.
- 100 dollars it is.
This was once asked on the show.
What is the full name
of the president of Russia?
If you get this right...
(A correct answer will get him
a salary of 150 dollars!)
- 150 dollars?
- Yes, 150 dollars.
Yes, because that's an ability
I'll need in the next round.
(He wants to answer it correctly,
but his lips won't move.)
You don't know it, do you?
I do!
I'm digging the name up
from my memory. The five syllables.
- Putin.
- Right.
What's his first name?
(His first name?)
(His eyes dash from side to side.)
This is hilarious!
- What is it?
- Siba...
Siba... What?
- Is that your answer?
- No.
- Then...
- Wait a second.
- That is incorrect.
- Escobar.
What?
Escobar.
(Haha has a talent for
coming up with foreign names.)
What's the answer?
- So...
- What's his name?
- You're out.
- What is it?
Did you renew your contract?
(Haha's lack of knowledge
resulted in a pay-cut.)
- I forgot my contract.
- He signed one.
- Jong Kook.
- I'm the team's franchise player...
who has nothing but love
for his team.
What's your current salary?
My salary?
I see you don't remember.
I don't get how that is possible.
- Are you here to argue?
- Of course not.
But it's something
you should remember.
I mean, just think about it.
Kwang Soo signed his contract
for two dollars...
while I did for 50 cents.
(An annual salary of 50 cents)
All hope has been
taken away from me.
Do you know what happens
when one loses hope?
- Who's most terrifying?
- Hold on.
The one who has no tomorrow
is the scariest.
- I mean...
- Why are you so angry all the time?
- How can I not be?
- Why are you so angry?
It seems like
the roles are reversed.
Jong Kook looks like the team owner.
- You're not the owner, you know.
- How can I not be angry?
- Why did you grab that?
- Come on.
- Mr. Yu,
hear me out.
- Still...
- Let me be somewhat motivated.
I'm the team's franchise player.
A franchise player?
Aren't I the team's
franchise player?
- Then...
- I...
How about 30 dollars?
- 30 dollars?
- It's a big raise.
What's going on in here?
You should come out.
- Hey!
- Your time is up.
What is he doing? Seriously?
- What is he doing?
- Kwang Soo...
Never have I seen...
He's forcing the team owner
to write a contract.
(The love for his team
manifested into a forced contract.)
Hey!
- 80 dollars.
- Hold on.
I only offered 30 dollars.
- He forced Jae Suk to write 80.
- 80 dollars is ridiculous.
He loves his team so much...
that it made him
want to get revenge on it.
That's the love he has for his team.
I mean...
You can't force me to sign this!
We're good.
Okay, 80 dollars.
(Team Yang's top player
Kim Kwang Hyun enters.)
- First of all...
- How much do you have left?
I spent quite a lot already.
Is there an amount in mind?
- Your previous salary was 190.
- Yes, 190 dollars.
Is there an amount
you personally want?
Not really.
I'll take what you give me.
Unbelievable.
- This team made more money.
- Right.
We earned 500 dollars
while they only earned 300.
That's a 200-dollar difference.
Hyun Jin will be worth
at least 200 dollars.
So to match that...
- My salary should match his.
- Of course.
You should receive more, is that it?
- Yes, about 250 dollars.
- How much?
- 250 dollars.
(Brazen)
Still...
- I'm liking this.
- Still,
we have 200 dollars more to spare.
- Hi, Hyun Jin.
- Hello.
You see...
A player just now...
literally stole money...
from the team's budget.
Well, that's...
only the team's problem.
- Then...
- This negotiation...
involves just me.
That's good and all,
but let me tell you this.
The team isn't in
a good place financially.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
How much are you willing
to offer me then?
Out of all the players,
you receive the most at 200 dollars.
By my calculations though,
I can only offer you...
about 110 dollars.
(I can only offer you
about 110 dollars.)
You're cutting my salary?
That's not how I'd call it.
The team isn't doing
so well financially.
So I'm going from
200 dollars to 110 dollars?
If you put it like that,
- it could seem like a pay cut.
- No way.
You're leaving?
Wait. Hold on a second. Hyun Jin!
- Hyun Jin didn't sign on.
- The deal fell through?
- He left the team.
- Hyun Jin left his team!
Kwang Hyun,
maybe you should do the same.
Wait...
It seems like Jae Suk
didn't manage to sign Hyun Jin.
Hyun Jin's deal falling through
had them moving fast.
(Se Chan quickly
offers the desired amount.)
(I'm good!)
Here.
- See?
- Got it.
- I'll sign the contract.
- That's 250 dollars.
I'll sign it.
Mr. Yang, Hyun Jin
didn't renew his contract.
This is your chance
to sign both players.
- All right.
- Kim Kwang Hyun and Ryu Hyun Jin.
- Kwang Hyun renewed his contract.
- He sure did.
(Kwang Hyun signs the contract
for the highest salary yet.)
- Let's work hard.
- Sure.
Hyun Jin's deal falling through
had them moving fast.
- Exactly.
- He immediately signed on.
- You should head inside.
- What...
All right.
(Team Yu's budget: 380 dollars)
What are you doing here?
My deal with the other team
fell through.
There was a bit of a mishap.
- You refused to sign with them?
- That's right.
By the looks of it,
I'm the last one
you can negotiate with.
Right.
How much did the other team offer?
He offered me 20 dollars.
That team has 700 dollars.
- So I...
- His team has enough money.
Exactly. I slapped him in the face
and left.
- I have a short temper.
- 20 dollars...
I slapped him in the face
and spat in his face.
- You have a bad personality.
- No, that's not true.
I'm a little bit short-tempered,
but I'm not a bad person.
Would you get a haircut
if I draft you?
(That's... Well...)
- It might bring me bad luck.
- I'll give you five dollars for it.
(Team Yu's condition is
to maintain a tidy hairstyle.)
- 5 dollars for a new haircut.
- You'll give me 5 dollars?
- On top of my salary?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Just for a new haircut.
But I'll only trim it a little bit.
- I can do that.
- I see.
- Let me think.
- Thank you.
(Kwang Soo signs a contract
at 33 dollars...)
(including 5 dollars
for a new haircut.)
- Did you sign with this team?
- Yes, I did.
You should bring your contract.
- Really?
- Jong Kook, come back with yours.
We need to negotiate again.
80 dollars is too much.
- 80 dollars?
- That's nonsense.
What are you talking about?
I already signed the contract.
That's not reasonable.
Wait, Kwang Soo. This is yours.
- Wait.
- Whose is that?
This is So Min's.
You agreed to pay her 40 dollars.
Wait. Hold on.
(Kwang Soo is furious
because of the low salary!)
I gave you the wrong one. Stop it.
(He lost his temper
and started a fight as always.)
(The post-negotiation process is
revealed transparently.)
Hold on.
I'll be the last one
to join this team.
(Suk Jin who hasn't signed
a contract entered.)
How much did he offer?
- The thing is...
- I don't have much money left now.
I paid the other players a lot.
- Pardon?
- How much did he offer?
Five bills.
You mean, five dollars?
- 50 dollars. Yes.
- 50 dollars?
No. I can never spend 50 dollars
to draft you.
- But...
- Even if you do well this time...
I mean... Listen.
I deserve much more than 20 dollars,
you brat.
I'm the team owner. How dare you?
Leave now.
If you keep acting like this,
I'll drag you out.
How can you say that?
Do you want to give up
and move to a deserted island?
Hey, Haha is...
Get out!
- Get out!
- I won't leave!
How dare you behave so rudely?
- Gosh.
- This is absurd.
How much will you pay me?
For a mere 10 dollars...
I was offered 50 dollars.
Leave!
- "Leave!"
(The owner's voice resonates
out of his office.)
- "Leave!"
- You let...
your greed for money sway you.
Even 20 dollars is too much for you!
Please come out.
- I won't draft you. Leave!
- That's so funny.
- I don't want to see you. Leave!
- I'll leave of my own accord!
Leave now.
I've never seen anyone
that greedy for money like him.
Gosh. I'm so upset.
He offered me only 20 dollars
when I used to be paid 50 dollars?
He's insane.
- Oh, my.
- Hello.
We meet again here.
You see, I want to draft
a skilled, trustworthy player.
I used to be paid 200 dollars.
- 200 dollars?
- Yes.
200 dollars...
Mr. Yang, please remember...
that if the deal falls through,
he has to sign with them for half.
If you offer 10 dollars
on top of the half,
- you can draft him.
- Really?
Hyun Jin, what are you doing here?
Why did you come here?
What's with you?
- Please leave.
- Hey, listen to me.
Leave!
- Did Hyun Jin sign with that team?
- Time's up.
You should leave now.
- What?
- Go on.
- "Go on."
- You should leave now.
Hyun Jin is in trouble.
(Hyun Jin failed to sign
with Team Yang as well.)
What happens to Hyun Jin now?
Please send them all away.
Both of them have to sign
a contract...
for half of what Jae Suk offered.
And Jae Suk can choose one of them.
At least one of them has to
join Team Yu...
for half of what he was
first offered.
Of course, I choose...
Half of what I offered...
Then I can draft him at 60 dollars.
- What?
- Have you made up your mind?
Yes. I choose Hyun Jin.
60 dollars?
- I will quit.
- Who?
How much did you offer Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin? I offered 25 dollars.
- Yes.
Then Suk Jin will transfer to
Team Yang at 12.50 dollars.
12 dollars and 50 cents?
I offered him 25 dollars earlier.
- You should've accepted it.
- Okay.
It's all been sorted out.
Hyun Jin,
let's forget about any hard feelings
against each other.
I'll stay on the team.
He cut my salary. I'm speechless.
After all I've done?
(The 1st salary negotiation ended
with hurt feelings.)
(Team Yu, 287 dollars,
Team Yang, 322.50 dollars)
(Hyun Jin, 260, So Min, 90,
Jong Kook, 80.50, Kwang Soo, 35)
(Kwang Hyun, 440, Ji Hyo, 130,
Haha, 93, Suk Jin, 62)
Kwang Hyun signed
the largest contract.
Hyun Jin stormed out
even before the negotiation began.
Hyun Jin, I think you should
work on that negotiation style.
Think about it.
You offered him only 120 dollars
when he used to be paid 200 dollars.
Mister.
- You're not on our team anymore.
- That's why I'm telling you.
- He transferred to that team?
- Oh, right. He's on the other team.
- Yes, he did.
- We drafted him for a low salary.
Of course, he's an old man.
I want to ask you about something,
Jong Kook.
Why do you love your team so much?
- Me?
- Yes.
What's the reason?
Since I belong to this team,
- I don't need a reason...
- It's unconditional love.
But he twisted my arm
to make me sign the contract...
- Pardon?
- for the amount he wanted. Gosh.
- Did he force you to sign?
- That's not true.
He wanted to pay me that much,
but he had no justification for it.
So I helped him a little.
- He's so scary.
- He was...
- acting shy.
- I'm speechless.
- But he was actually happy.
- He wrote the number.
He wrote it by himself.
I'm utterly speechless.
He wrote all those zeroes
of his own accord.
Also, I'm the franchise player.
I told you, you're French fries.
He's the franchise player.
- On our team...
- Hyun Jin is the franchise player.
That's not true.
You know, the same goes for
Mr. Yang.
- I offered you...
- Hold on a second.
- Actually, there are...
- Yes?
so many questions I want to
ask Hyun Jin and Kwang Hyun.
- Of course.
- Mister, please be quiet.
I'm very sorry, but...
Will you stay quiet?
Or should we make you?
Nice.
I have a question.
When you play in a Korean league...
and when you play in MLB,
do you work harder
in one of the leagues?
Are you saying
he plays halfheartedly in Korea?
- That's not what I mean.
- No way.
- Not halfheartedly.
- Of course, I'm not halfhearted.
- But maybe...
- He pays more attention?
I don't want to relate it to our
race, but if you get paid more...
- You feel pressured.
- There's a higher expectation.
See? I knew it.
- It's true.
- I knew it.
I even dived to live up
to his expectation,
- but he cut my salary.
- Gosh. That's enough.
- Gosh. He's still holding a grudge.
- He's the type that holds grudges.
I'm sorry. I didn't...
Real baseball players
react exactly like this.
- It hurts your feelings.
- If they get a pay cut in winter,
they don't even look at the staff.
- Wait.
- Of course.
But why would you react
the same way on this show?
This isn't a real baseball team.
Hyun Jin was immersed in
his role too much.
Honestly, I thought you would
give me a 10 dollar raise.
Gosh. Don't be so petty.
I think we'll do something
like "Metal Tray Karaoke Room".
Through this game, you can check
your common knowledge and teamwork.
It's Loyal Chinese Idiom.
What?
- Chinese idioms?
- I can't do this.
- I'm done for.
- Chinese idioms?
All members have to participate.
We tell you the meaning.
- The meaning?
- And you say the idiom.
But one member can skip
his or her turn.
For example,
the question is one crane
among a flock of chickens.
If the first member doesn't know,
he or she can skip the turn.
The other members should say
"flower", "of", "the", and "flock".
(Any member can skip a turn,
but it's allowed only once.)
("Flower", "of", "the",
pass, "flock")
You should've told us
about this game.
I wouldn't have drafted
some of them.
That team will fail
because of those in the middle.
These two are hopeless.
- They're hopeless.
- Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo is the third player.
Would that be okay?
We can skip her turn.
There's no way we'll lose.
We won't lose.
We'll start from this side.
Here's the first question.
This means you say something
to please someone else...
or to persuade the person
to do something.
Let us answer.
Sweet.
(Team Yang failed.)
- Let us answer. Sweet.
- Talk.
- In.
- Pass.
(What could be the last word?)
- Gosh, you punks.
(Gosh, you punks.)
(Yelling)
(We almost got it right.)
Darn it.
- Let us answer.
- Sweet.
- Talk.
- In.
- Whisper.
- Okay.
- Oh, yes.
(Team Yang won 1 point
thanks to Hyun Jin.)
We pulled it off.
(He's trying not to
say harsh things.)
- You see...
- My gosh.
- It was our plan.
- Wait.
All right.
- Are you serious?
- I bought him some time.
We know how this works now.
- Even Se Chan knew the answer.
- Yes, I knew it.
- Now, we know. Don't worry.
- He'll skip his turn again.
Kwang Hyun, did you know
the answer or not?
Of course, I knew it.
Here's the second question.
This literally means there's no one
under the eyes.
- It means an arrogant, rude...
- Let us answer.
- Go ahead.
- This one is easy.
- Captain.
- Eyes.
- Darn.
- Let us answer.
- Go ahead.
Captain.
Mouth.
- Gosh.
- Let us answer.
(Team Yoo remembered
the right answer.)
- Captain.
- Snobby.
Ego.
Mouth.
(Wrong)
No?
(Frustrated)
- Isn't the last word "mouth"?
- Let us answer.
(They got another chance
thanks to Hyun Jin.)
- Let us answer.
- Captain.
- Snobby.
- Ego.
- Pass.
- Mania.
(Team Yang got the right answer!)
(Thanks to Hyun Jin,
the score is now 0 to 2.)
It's "captain snobby ego-mania".
It's "mania", not "mouth".
(He's so cheerful
that they can't get mad at him.)
This is driving me nuts.
Why...
Do you have any medicine?
Any medicine?
How about you?
My chest feels so stuffy.
(This is so much fun.)
- I thought we'd win.
- Let's keep going.
- We could've got both right.
- Listen.
Everyone.
- We can do this.
Team Yang?
- Let's just relax.
- It's okay.
Here's the third question.
This literally means to replace
a bone structure to change a shape.
It means to become a completely
different person in a good way.
I'm upset.
He's upset.
Let us answer.
- Pass.
- Make.
- A.
- Fresh.
- Skill.
- Okay.
(Make a fresh skill?)
- Okay. Let us answer.
- Isn't the last word "skill"?
- Make.
- A.
- Fresh.
- Start.
- All right.
- We are set.
Do you want to leave the team?
- For goodness' sake.
- "Skill".
- Do you want to leave the team?
- "Make a fresh skill."
This is driving me crazy.
- How could you get it wrong?
- I need medicine.
- "Make a fresh skill."
- Let me answer. Study.
- Despite.
- The.
- Odds.
All right!
Suk Jin used the idiom
so many times.
How did you get me for 12 dollars?
All right. I will raise your salary
the next time.
Raise my salary the next time.
I should give him a lot of money.
- Come on.
- All right.
- I think I am making the team lose.
- That's not true.
- I should leave the team.
- Thus, Team Yang won.
- We lost again.
Team Yang will get 500 dollars
and Team Yoo will get 300 dollars.
- Now, the last salary negotiation.
- Okay.
Team owners, please make decisions
in your respective room.
(The second salary negotiation
gives them a headache!)
Now, the last salary negotiation.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hello.
(So Min enters 1st.)
So Min, how much
did you get earlier?
- 40 dollars.
- Sit down.
(There is a high chance
she will receive a salary cut.)
You know,
(You know...)
I just would like to say...
All right. Take a look first.
- Did you write it down already?
- Yes.
When did you... Gosh!
Give me the same amount.
Don't cut the salary.
I just ask for the same amount.
Are you going to sign it or not?
(The team owner's stern behavior...)
(results in a breakdown.)
- Are you leaving?
- You return evil for good.
Okay. Leave. Leave!
(Hesitant)
I want to use an idiom,
but I don't know any.
- You return evil for good.
- Leave.
- You are too strict.
- Leave!
- I won't lose!
(It was her secret weapon.)
If you treat me this way,
- I will...
- Leave, leave.
All right. Here I come.
- I am in a good mood.
- Jong Kook.
I am not greedy.
Just give me a moderate amount,
- and I will be loyal.
- I will give you 70 dollars.
- What?
- 70 dollars.
- It's more than I expected.
- Right?
(My goodness!)
- It's because you have done well.
- Really?
You have a love for the team.
That's good. I am satisfied.
I am very satisfied.
It's nice. Okay.
I pay handsomely
to those who deserve it.
How nice is that?
My goodness.
That went smoothly.
- You can go now.
- Okay.
- Do I take it?
- You take it.
I will take it as proof.
That wasn't half bad.
There is no reason
to raise this person's salary.
(He writes down a low salary
and waits.)
All right. Come on in.
(The long-haired pitcher,
Lee Kwang Soo)
I will be blunt with you.
This is my last chance.
I am at the bottom of the ranking.
If I don't get a higher salary
than Jong Kook, I am over.
This is the most I can offer.
Take a look.
(20 dollars?)
20 dollars?
(He is a player who never gets
the salary he wants.)
- Leave.
- Is that the best you can do?
Get lost. Get lost.
- 20 dollars?
- Is that the best you can do?
You don't even deserve
a salary of 20 dollars.
- Okay.
- Leave! Leave!
Okay. I got it.
- Hello.
- My goodness.
(He bows in 90 degrees.)
(Hyun Jin became modest
after the four-word idioms.)
- You became very modest.
- Gosh.
- You are working hard.
- You became very modest.
The salary negotiation
didn't go well the last time.
You became friendlier.
I had many struggles.
- All right.
- Welcome.
You remember how well I did
in the last season, right?
- Yes.
- All right.
- I am ready to sign the contract.
- What's your name?
Suk Jin.
What are you doing?
"Stay healthy."
- Here.
- What are you doing?
You can go on your way.
Take my autograph.
You can join another team.
The salary negotiation is over.
(The salary negotiation ends
before he gets to say anything.)
You use me and discard me.
Don't say it like that.
Let's go with 170 dollars.
Gosh. Be more generous.
I will show you what I can do.
Okay. It's my duty as a team owner
to keep the players satisfied.
180 dollars.
Okay. Let's sign the contract.
All right.
Let's sign the contract.
(Jae Suk used a big amount of money
to lift up a player's spirits.)
- We need to win this time.
- Of course.
Okay. Take the contract with you.
(Kwang Soo barges into the room!)
(The long-haired pitcher
was watching in secret.)
(The friendly atmosphere
made him lose his senses.)
How could you give this much
to Hyun Jin...
when you offered 20 dollars to me?
(You offered 20 dollars to me.)
- I mean...
- I will work hard.
Okay. Okay.
I got Kwang Soo for the price
of five hot dogs.
How is it possible
that I only collected 35 dollars?
(The result
of the 2nd salary negotiation)
(The last mission)
My goodness.
- Gosh.
What is this place?
- What will we do?
- It's a baseball park.
- What is this place?
- Please stand with your teammates.
(What will be the last match?)
This is the last mission
of Stove League.
We will test the team owners'
skills and strategies...
with the Rich and Poor Play Ball.
- Rich and Poor.
From a regular baseball match,
only the scoring system is tweaked.
After the batter hits the ball,
he or she can pick up half cones
while advancing.
When the batter returns
to the home plate,
the number of half cones
will decide the score.
- Really?
- Do we need to pick them up?
- Let's pick up one.
- Yellow ones are one point.
Green ones are 3 points,
red ones are 5 points,
- and the blue ones are 10 points.
- Where are the blue ones?
They are right behind the pitcher.
Are the red ones three points?
Here it is.
We will play three innings.
All players...
will start off with poor equipment.
The team owners can use
the team money...
to upgrade the equipment
for the players of their choice.
It's nice to be a team owner.
Oh, you purchase the equipment.
You should use the money.
You can purchase the equipment
at any time.
The umpire who will help us today
is Song Ho Yeon.
The pitcher is in 11th grade...
of Hyun Jin's high school,
Dongsan High School.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Dongsan High School.
- Thank you.
You can pick the equipment
of your choice.
(They move to the team's dugout
before the game begins!)
- What should I choose?
- What are these?
These are bad equipment.
- How about this?
- What is this?
- These are the basic equipment.
It will be easy to use.
What are these?
- Acupressure shoes.
- Acupressure shoes?
Let's buy shoes.
- Okay.
- We will buy shoes.
Let's buy shoes for the key players.
- Me and...
- Hey.
- Hey! I might be a key player.
- I don't have money.
I don't have money.
- Three players.
- Hey!
- Hold on.
- I don't have money.
The team isn't well-off.
- Okay.
- See how they are.
- They don't fit.
- They fit.
- They don't fit!
- What do you want me to do?
Just wear the swimming fins.
(Kwang Soo gains swimming fins...)
(after the team owner
invests 10 dollars.)
- All right.
- This makes no sense.
- Just the basics.
- Kwang Soo, that's good.
How are we supposed
to play baseball this way?
That's good.
I will buy the toy bat.
It's 10 dollars.
There is no need to use 10 dollars.
Save up on the money.
I think I can hit a tennis ball
with this.
- I will use this.
- The toy bat.
Do you want one?
These shoes will make me healthy.
That's...
- Let's buy shoes.
- Jae Suk.
- I can't walk in them.
- Me neither.
Let's buy the 20-dollar shoes.
- That's right. Buy me shoes.
- My goodness.
This is the basic glove.
- A boxing glove.
- Do we wear it at first?
This is insane.
- Do we wear it on one hand?
- That won't do.
How much is the glove?
Let's buy a new one.
Start with the basic items.
Can't you buy a glove
for a major leaguer?
Seriously.
- We can use this one.
- Hyun Jin...
Let's play ball.
Hyun Jin can throw the ball.
One toy bat.
So Min is the first batter.
I will show everyone.
- It's important to start well.
- Let's go.
Make sure you reach the first base.
So Min, let's go!
- Let's go!
- All right!
Come forward.
(Hyun Jin will take her on
from the start.)
(The unexpected match,
Hyun Jin versus So MIn)
Play.
(Will So Min be able
to hit the ball?)
(She misses big time.)
(She swung the bat
to hit Hyun Jin's ball.)
Hyun Jin, go easy on her.
It's her first time
to play baseball.
(The 1st batter has
no batting eye whatsoever.)
Don't throw so fast.
(Two strikes)
- I can't do it!
- Hyun Jin, you threw too hard.
- What is this?
- I touched the ball.
Okay.
- Two strikes.
- I touched the ball.
So Min.
Okay.
- Foul.
- Time out!
Hit by pitch!
She swung the bat!
(A dead ball)
What do you mean?
She swung the bat!
What?
(So Min succeeded to get on base.)
You did it!
Did the ball hit her?
She swung the bat!
No, no. You need to be polite.
- It will be bad if you get ejected.
- You might get ejected.
It will be bad if you get ejected.
Are they related?
The second hitter,
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Send the ball far.
- Okay.
- Pick up any half cones.
Send the ball far.
Kwang Soo, send the ball far.
Time out.
You can't step on the line.
Step back. Step back.
But the swimming fins...
You can't step on the line.
- The swimming fins touch the line.
- Step back.
Fold your toes.
Kwang Soo.
Position your feet differently.
But to hit the ball...
- No. You can't step on the line.
- Kwang Soo.
- Turn them outward.
My toes aren't touching the line.
That won't do.
You can't step on the line.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Play.
- Hold on.
How am I supposed to hit the ball?
I need different shoes!
(Se Chan has no intention
to make more investment.)
(Kwang Soo finally gets
in position.)
Okay.
(He misses the ball!)
Okay. That's good.
- He can't reach the outside.
He can't reach the outside.
(Hyun Jin found his weakness.)
(He sends the ball outward again.)
- Strike.
- Come on.
- I mean...
- Kwang Soo!
I can't even hit it straight!
Hold on, hold on.
Two strikes.
Wait.
Run, run!
- Did he hit it?
- Run, run!
Run, run! You need to run!
(Kwang Soo gets tagged.)
- You need to run!
- Out!
Run! Suk Jin!
(At the 2nd base,
So Min gets eliminated.)
- Out!
Good job.
What are we doing?
- So Min, don't you know the rules?
- You didn't tell me to run.
(The clueless 1st batter
and the slow 2nd batter)
- You need to get the half cones.
- The ball went over.
- Hey, buy me shoes!
- For goodness' sake.
Wait.
(At that moment)
I can't believe I will see this.
Hyun Jin will pitch
and Kwang Hyun will hit.
- Let's do this.
- The next batter...
You need to get on the base.
If you are out, we are done.
We have no hope.
(It's the best friend's first time
to go against each other.)
(How will Hyun Jin pitch
against Kwang Hyun?)
I feel like I am watching TV.
They are going against each other.
(Pitcher Ryu Hyun Jin
versus Batter Kwang Hyun)
Kwang Hyun, hit the ball.
Kwang Hyun, let's go!
(They are desperate
for Kwang Hyun's hit.)
(It's a face-off
that won't happen again.)
Won't the scratcher break?
See?
- See?
- Kwang Hyun!
- Buy him a bat!
(Kwang Hyun?)
- Kwang Hyun!
- Buy him a bat!
I can't hit with this.
- Buy him a bat.
- You can buy it now.
- Kwang Hyun said he will try it.
Let's buy a frying pan.
(Hyun Jin succeeded
to seize control of the situation.)
Good job.
(The 2nd pitch)
Run!
(He hits the ball
with the back scratcher.)
- He did it.
- He hit the ball.
- Okay!
- Hey!
(But the ball goes straight
to the pitcher.)
(and he is out at 1st base.)
- Out!
- Good job.
He is like an iron wall.
Out.
- Come on.
- Maybe next time.
You can do it the next time.
- Hurry up.
- Hey.
- These shoes hurt.
- Hurry up.
- This one.
- Let's buy it.
(It's Team Yu's turn to attack.)
Let's buy a bat.
- This one.
- Let's buy it.
Firstly,
let's get a 20-dollar bat
for everyone.
- Okay.
Why is there a story-telling glove?
- Hey.
- Can you catch a ball with it?
What is up
with the story-telling glove?
Everyone will wear
the story-telling glove.
(Se Chan likes
the story-telling glove.)
- The story-telling glove.
- Why should we wear it?
Why should we wear them?
This is ridiculous.
We can't catch a ball like this.
Let's take out one.
This is the basic glove.
Wear the basic glove.
Why does it have to be me?
You already have the swimming fins.
- Hello.
- So Min should take it.
- Hello, we are animal friends.
- I can't do anything like this.
- It hurts.
- This is...
(Everyone except for Kwang Soo
gets a story-telling glove.)
(After making preparations,
Team Yoo attacks.)
- I am in your care.
- Is Ji Hyo the first batter?
Here I go.
- Move to the front.
- Okay, okay.
You can do it, Ji Hyo.
- I can do it.
- You can hit it.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
(Kwang Hyun will take her on
with a story-telling glove.)
(Will Ji Hyo succeed
to get on the base?)
Okay, okay! Go! Run!
(She hit Kwang Hyun's curveball.)
- Run!
- Throw it! Catch it!
- Out.
- Gosh, it hurts.
- Nice.
- This is no joke!
- It was a nice hit.
(The acupressure shoes
brought health and elimination.)
(The bad equipment
is the problem.)
Ji Hyo would have made it
if it weren't for the shoes.
Nice pitching!
- The second batter, Ryu Hyun Jin.
- Here is what I think.
- That's the weak spot.
- That's right.
(Hyun Jin aims for the one
in the swimming fins.)
That's the weak spot.
Let's catch him.
(Who will win in the second match?)
It will go that way. Be careful.
- Okay!
- Catch it!
- Kwang Soo! First base!
- Okay!
- Pick up the half cones.
- Go to the second base.
- Hey!
- Second base.
Catch it.
- Third base.
- Hyun Jin, get the half cones.
Throw it.
(He bodyslams the base
without any half cones.)
Catch it!
Throw it!
Move, you jerk!
Hey.
- You need to get the half cones!
- He can do it on his way back.
- I will stay here.
- Okay.
- Why didn't you get them?
- You need to get the half cones!
- He missed them.
- You went all the way there.
Listen to the coach!
(Jong Kook ends up teaching baseball
to Hyun Jin.)
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
These are terrible shoes
for an important moment.
- Get him out.
- The third batter,
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Let's go for a double play.
(Meanwhile)
Hyun Jin! A stolen base!
Okay. A stolen base.
Good job.
Kwang Hyun.
(They must go for a strikeout
with Suk Jin.)
Kwang Hyun.
(It's a hit to the left-center gap.)
Come on! Run!
Suk Jin, what are you doing?
(Limping)
(Suk Jin is out.)
For goodness' sake!
- Hey!
- Why did the atmosphere turn loose?
Why are you so slow?
Buy me shoes!
(The oldest member has been asking
for shoes for 20 minutes.)
The entire stadium
suddenly turned quiet.
- I am in pain.
- He can't run.
- It's funny to see him walk.
- Check the back.
(The oldest player's hit ends
without gains.)
- Jong Kook!
- Okay.
- You must hit the ball well.
- Kwang Hyun, go for a strikeout.
- Okay.
Time out. Time out.
We will change the bat.
(Hyun Jin is close
to scoring points.)
Right now?
- Really?
- Send the ball in the air.
- Let's go.
- This is the strategy.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
This is bad. This is bad.
(It will be easy to hit
with a frying pan.)
Let's move back.
(Will Jae Suk's big investment
pay off?)
A foul ball.
(He hit it, but...)
- My goodness.
- Kwang Hyun!
Go for a strikeout!
Let's get him. Just one more.
(Kwang Hyun increased the speed
since he was nervous.)
My goodness.
Thank goodness I hit it.
We need to do this.
Show them that you can throw.
- Hit it.
- Kwang Hyun, we need a strike.
- There you go.
- He hit it!
Second base!
(The man in the swimming fins
already made 3 mistakes.)
(While Kwang Soo struggles,
Jong Kook runs to the 1st base.)
- Okay!
- Okay.
(Hyun Jin succeeded
to reach the home base.)
It's a success!
You should have caught it.
I couldn't catch it!
You could have caught it.
Nice!
The frying pan did its job.
(Team Yoo scores 3 points.)
- You are the best.
- Good job.
The frying pan was the best.
It would have been cool
to catch the ball.
I know. It's a shame.
- Jae Suk is good.
- Really?
Kwang Soo, move back.
(It's time to see Kwang Hyun's
crisis management skills.)
- Catch it!
There you go.
(The animals
of the story-telling glove helped.)
Okay. Nice defense!
This broke.
My hands hurt.
- My hands hurt so much.
- Good work.
This glove is the worst.
That's too bad.
- Go.
- You need to hit hard.
- Seriously.
- How do you hit it?
Here comes the man
who can't reach the outside.
Hold on.
How far can I go?
- Hey.
- How far can I go?
He is the man
who can't reach the outside.
Even if I stretch out my arm,
I can only reach up to here.
- I feel bad for him.
- You can do it.
(Kwang Soo is growing strong due
to the team owner's indifference.)
Run!
(He hit the ball!)
Hey, you got him.
For goodness' sake!
(After taking a few steps,
his anger explodes.)
Hey.
(A discord occurs
in just 2 innings.)
- What?
- You should buy me...
a bat or shoes!
- I will buy you shoes.
- Three outs.
I will buy you shoes.
(Se Chan promises to buy him shoes.)
I feel bad for him.
- I am sorry.
- I feel bad for him.
Se Chan, do you want straw shoes?
- Buy him straw shoes.
- Okay.
A pitcher change.
I'll pitch some balls,
and Hyun Jin must come in
when there's an emergency.
I think we should get
a frying pan for now.
Who is next? Is it me?
- I'll get a frying pan.
- Let's get five frying pans.
- Let's get 3 for now.
- Let's get 4.
Let's get three.
- Why?
- What is wrong with him?
If you're out, we won't have
any chances left.
Throw hard, Jae Suk.
Play.
- Strike.
- Yes.
(The strike zone is slightly large.
He hit strike to the outer course.)
How is this a strike
when the ball fell out over here?
- How is this a strike?
- It's a strike.
- Okay.
- Good.
- I know what it feels like now.
- You're good.
The ball fell out over here.
You should follow the ball
and hit it.
(The long hit
cut through the crowd.)
- It's a hit.
- Okay, Mr. Yang.
- Hurry up. Run.
- Good job.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- This is unbelievable.
(They must send Se Chan
to home base no matter what.)
We're in trouble.
(Kim Kwang Hyun is at bat.)
- Hit a home run.
- Let's go, Kwang Hyun.
(Can Yoo Jae Suk
overcome this crisis?)
He threw a breaking ball.
Did he throw a breaking ball?
- He threw it like this.
- He suddenly threw it.
- Really?
- That's surprising.
Jae Suk is good at baseball.
(He continues to throw
the 2nd ball.)
- That's good.
- That's it.
- Safe.
(Se Chan touched 2nd base.)
(Ryu Hyun Jin fell down.)
- Safe.
- Hey.
- You're out.
- Oh, my.
- Are you okay?
Hey, do you know how much you cost?
- Hey.
- Don't do that.
- Don't try to do a slide.
- Hyun Jin.
- Are you crazy?
- What is wrong with him?
- Wait a minute.
- That's right.
They crashed into each other,
but everyone ran to Hyun Jin.
- I even scraped my arm.
- Are you okay?
He's okay.
Let's take a look at the video
for a moment.
- Okay.
- Let's take a look at the video.
- He touched it before the whistle.
- Okay.
- Okay, before the whistle.
(Se Chan who got 12 points
succeeded at landing on 2nd base.)
Kwang Soo, I'll buy a frying pan.
Okay.
Kwang Soo.
- You must get it in this time.
- Okay.
You must get it in this time
unconditionally.
- It has to go in.
- That's right.
He's like Ma Dong Tak.
- Grab it.
- Suk Jin.
(It's a neat heavy hit.)
Suk Jin, gosh.
Grab it.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo succeeded
at picking up a 5 point cone.)
- Safe.
- Gosh.
(Kwang Soo is safe by a close call.)
- Okay.
- Grab it.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Hyun and Se Chan
were the lead runners.)
- Grab it.
- Just get in for now.
Just get in for now.
Get in quickly.
- Safe.
Okay.
Nice.
(Kwang Soo got 23 points
with only 1 hit.)
- Nice.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- What's the score?
Kwang Soo, nice.
- He got a lot of points.
I think he got about 30.
Kwang Soo, get ready to run.
Okay.
(Kwang Soo's aiming for extra points
with teasing base running.)
We need to get Kwang Soo
no matter what so he doesn't go in.
Jae Suk.
- Gosh.
- Strike.
Jae Suk, you should start
looking over here.
(Jae Suk's really bothered by
the 1st base runner Kwang Soo.)
(He does a motion
to keep Kwang Soo in check.)
What is he doing?
What is this?
I think you will get hit
in between there.
- This is...
- It means you shouldn't throw.
It's not time to throw yet.
- Oh, my.
- Hey.
- Grab it.
- He's really good.
- Good job.
Go to third base.
- Hurry up.
- That's right.
Kwang Hyun, it's your turn.
Good, frying pans are good.
- I need to change my shoes.
- We need to get going.
- Hyun Jin must throw this time.
Pitcher change.
I'm in trouble.
I can't help it anymore.
Hyun Jin, you should throw
instead of me.
(Kim Kwang Hyun versus Ryu Hyun Jin,
The 3rd match)
- I need to hit it this time.
- It's a head-on match.
Good.
I need to hit it this time.
Hey, Hyun Jin.
(Straw Shoe Kwang Soo
doesn't miss a chance.)
- Gosh.
- He's really good.
He's the best at stealing
in the world.
- He's the best. He's number 1.
- He's number 1 at stealing.
(The ball speed suddenly
became faster.)
(Gosh...)
- Nice.
- Good job.
Good.
We can't give them any more points.
We can't give them points now.
We can't. Hyun Jin,
you must stop him.
- Okay.
- Good.
Gosh...
- Okay.
- Good.
(Gosh...)
(A little league player
suddenly rushes onto the mound.)
You punk...
What are you doing?
(The bench-clearing expert is
running toward them like a bull.)
- Who won?
- What are you doing?
(The franchise star exploded like
he was waiting for this moment.)
- I wondered why you weren't coming.
- Go away.
- Who won?
- What are you doing?
(Falling down)
(He approached them to stop them,)
(but he fell down.)
(Unexpected physical contact)
(The umpire finally got back
to his senses,)
(and left to stop
the franchise star.)
- Where?
- You punk.
(They're even venting their personal
feelings unrelated to baseball.)
It's mine. Oh, my.
(The two groups are playing baseball
to do bench-clearings.)
- How dare you...
- Okay.
- I left it.
- Are the bases loaded?
- Yes, the bases are loaded.
- Bases are loaded.
- Gosh, the frying pan...
- Play.
- Why did you fight?
- Let's go.
We just have to get one more.
(Hyun Jin's goal is to strike Haha
out in this desperate situation.)
What are you doing?
He's crazy.
(Lee Kwang Soo, Has supernatural
powers, The man who rules bases)
You!
- This is an out.
- Gosh.
- He took the base away with him.
- Safe.
Safe.
Gosh, I can't help it
if this happened then.
Okay.
- Nice.
Haha, keep your eyes
on the ball to the end.
- Okay.
- Strike.
(He succeeded at focusing on
throwing the ball higher.)
- Okay.
What is that?
I ended it with three balls.
I had no other choice.
- He's incredible.
- Yes.
They got a lot of points, right?
- What is he doing?
- Gosh.
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
(The end of the second inning,
Yang 23 to Yoo 0)
- I'll also get a frying pan.
- Okay.
Everyone got a frying pan.
- Do they all have frying pans?
- Yes.
(The victory group pitcher is
Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo, who are you nodding to?
(He's staring into the air while
sending a secret code to somewhere.)
Who are you talking to?
Throw it quickly.
Nice.
(Perfect strike)
Kwang Soo's good at pitching.
- He's like Kershaw.
- Kwang Soo's ball is too fast.
- That's so unfair.
- How could you throw a fastball...
to Ji Hyo?
She swung.
(He threw it even faster.)
- Safe.
- That's right.
(He doesn't care about Ji Hyo. He's
busy showing off his ball speed.)
(Gosh, he's so annoying.)
Gosh, he threw
a fastball to Ji Hyo.
That's right, make her frying pan
feel useless.
Make her swing.
- Nice.
- Am I out?
- He's just a bully. If that's so...
He's a bully.
Make him swing.
Kwang Soo, that's right.
Kim Jong Kook.
Look, he's going to hit it
no matter what.
He's showing us
all of his directions.
It means that he will throw
toward the inner side.
- Will he throw it to that side?
- Gosh.
Wait a minute.
(He does a mysterious hand signal
and throws the ball.)
- Gosh.
- Strike.
- What?
(Is the ball that flew above
Jong Kook's head a strike?)
Okay.
(Everyone is surprised because they
never saw this strike zone before.)
- Was that a strike?
- Kwang Soo,
- say thank you.
- Okay.
That's right.
(Bowing)
- Gosh.
- Was that a strike?
(Team Yu's franchise started
to get excited.)
(What?)
Why?
Why are you upset?
Gosh, wait a minute.
(The second physical fight
broke out.)
(This affectionate player is
merciless to dirty players.)
Come back for now, Jong Kook.
- But this is...
- How could you do this to a human?
This is a little...
- unfair.
- This is really unfair.
He deserved to get hit.
"He deserved to get hit"?
Okay.
It's interesting though.
Let's win this thing.
Kwang Hyun came again.
We need to win at least once,
Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- We need to win at least once.
Gosh.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Kim Kwang Hyun!
- I'm sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Seriously, that's unfair.
- I'm sorry.
- I thought it was the major league.
- Okay.
Are you a bully?
We need to strike him out.
Make a short backswing,
and head to the bottom.
- Okay.
- That's it.
(He hit it.)
- End it.
- Stop.
- No.
- It's not over?
- Just push through.
- They attacked from there.
- To the end?
Okay.
(Next at bat: So Min,
Haha, and Kwang Soo)
(2020 Running Series
Innings Change)
Please give a frying pan to So Min.
Jeon So Min, you can do it!
So Min, let's go.
This is the last turn.
(If the last pitcher Ji Hyo defends
within 3 points, Team Yoo will win.)
- Run.
- Oh, my.
(It's a straightforward hit.)
- Run.
(An exciting swing to continue
the spark of a come-from-behind win)
(But it's a fly out.)
- Out.
- I hit it really well.
- You did a good job.
- Let's do it one more time.
- I did a good job.
- You did a good job.
- This is too hard for me.
- No, you did a good job.
- Ji Hyo's ball won't fall far away.
It's hard. How am I going to hit it?
(Pitcher Ji Hyo's ball is
hard to predict.)
You can do it.
(Falling down)
- Strike.
- Mister.
- Mister, you're being unfair.
- Good.
(The strike zone is like the Pacific
only for Ji Hyo.)
- I'm being consistent.
- Consistent...
(This is the secret of
her special ending.)
Mister.
He must want to go home quickly.
He's the best umpire.
How can I hit this?
Who can hit this?
Play.
(She concentrates and throws again.)
- Gosh.
- Okay.
(He jumped with all his might.)
(The strike zone is too high for
the little league player.)
- Okay.
- He's bad.
A frying pan is too good for him
Why did you give him a frying pan?
Kwang Soo, we need to do it this
time for a come-from-behind win.
That's right.
Your posture is good.
Wait a minute.
- Foul!
- But...
(Ji Hyo's ball flew in suddenly.)
- It's a swing and miss.
- Is it a foul?
- That's not it.
- You hit it.
- You hit it. Foul.
- I was doing a performance.
- Foul.
- You did a good job.
The ball hit you
when you were swinging.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Kwang Soo, focus.
- Ji Hyo is actually talented.
(He focuses
and tries again properly.)
(Putting his foot forward)
It's a ball.
(The ball brushed against his foot
that he held out on purpose.)
- Nice.
- Gosh.
(He's pretending that he got hit
by accident.)
- It's a ball.
- That was good.
You can do it.
It's okay. Good job, Ji Hyo.
A slightly annoying person
came out, but...
(He's stealing cones while crawling
after advancing to 1st base.)
- He's slightly annoying.
- He really is.
- Gosh.
- Here he goes.
- Don't keep him in check.
- Ji Hyo, just throw the ball.
Leave him alone.
(Ji Hyo missed the ball
just at that moment.)
Hey, that's not it.
(This is his chance.)
Good.
(Team Yang is behind by 3 points.)
(It's their chance to turn the game
around and earn more points.)
(But the player who is throwing
the ball is Ryu Hyun Jin.)
(A crucial moment came to them
in the 1st half of the 3rd inning.)
(Will they survive with a save and
dream about a come-from-behind win?)
(Or will they end the game with
a misfortunate out count?)
- Out.
- Safe.
(Both of them touched the base
almost at the same time.)
(What is the decision of
the professional umpire?)
- Out!
(The game ended with three outs.)
You're out.
(He turned in the last out count
with a greedy base running play.)
Out.
- Okay.
- Go.
- Just go.
- We have two left.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Yes.
(Team Yoo won.)
- This is the ending.
- It's a good ending.
(Discouraged)
Okay.
(Wait, what happened?)
- Kwang Soo, nice ending.
- Hey.
- I never even won once.
- That's right.
Seriously. I was
the icon of misfortune.
Everyone, according to the result
of the last game,
- Team Yoo won.
- Okay.
You will each receive 700 dollars
and 300 dollars.
- 700 dollars?
- That's a large amount.
- 700 and 300 dollars.
- This is the long-awaited ending.
I'll announce the current amount
of the team owners.
Se Chan has minus 459.7 dollars.
- Minus?
- Yes.
- He spent a lot of money.
- Minus?
Yoo Jae Suk has minus 539 dollars.
- Oh, my.
- Why is it a minus?
- They spent all of their money.
- There's an 80-dollar difference.
- We spent a lot.
- There's an 80-dollar difference,
and it will end like this.
Divide 700 dollars and 300 dollars
among 5 baseballs...
however you want.
Can I divide them however I want?
- You'll have to divide it up.
- After that, take a ball each.
- Okay.
- Right.
- If so, I could beat Jae Suk.
- I think Se Chan...
will put 300 dollars on one ball.
- There's an 80-dollar difference?
- Yes, an 80-dollar difference.
- I think Se Chan will do that.
- Exactly 80 dollars?
- You just have to beat Se Chan.
- That's right.
He won't put all of the money...
- on one ball.
- No, he won't.
You should just put
all 300 dollars on 1 ball.
- Yes.
- Just put 300 dollars on 1 ball.
- 300 dollars and the rest are 0.
- Make it 300 and the rest 0.
- It's for you.
- What's the current score?
If Kwang Soo picks 300 dollars,
it will be a come-from-behind win.
I got 100 dollars.
Why did you give all of the money
to rich people?
Hey, gosh.
Me?
- Zero.
- Me...
- Wait a minute.
- I can't believe it.
- Please!
(Current number of cases:
1. If Kwang Soo picked 300 dollars,)
(he will be exempt from the penalty
by avoiding the last place.)
- I only wore pants today.
- It's one of the two.
(2. If Se Chan picked 300 dollars,
the entire team will be exempt.)
Okay, one...
(Se Chan only thought about himself
amid the cold negotiation.)
Two...
(Kwang Soo dreamed of exemption
while receiving the lowest salary.)
Three.
(Only the person who picked
300 dollars will be exempt.)
(What will be the result?)
Okay!
(Lee Kwang Soo acquired
300 dollars.)
(The misfortunate Team Owner Yang
will receive a penalty.)
Jae Suk won.
(Team Owner Yoo Jae Suk's
come-from-behind win)
Jae Suk won.
Jae Suk is really lucky today.
(He covers his mouth
as he's overwhelmed.)
- It was so close.
- So Min was amazing.
I was almost there.
- Kwang Soo won.
- The result is dramatic.
Ryu Hyun Jin won with 641 dollars.
(Ryu Hyun Jin won with 641 dollars.)
Kim Kwang Hyun is in 2nd place
with 640 dollars.
- Is there a 1-dollar difference?
- There's a 1-dollar difference.
- Third place is...
- It could be Kwang Soo.
Song Ji Hyo.
(The last person to receive a prize
as 3rd place is Ji Hyo.)
Yang Se Chan lost as a team owner.
- Yes.
- I spent too much money.
So the person who will receive
the penalty as last place is...
Jeon So Min.
- Is that it?
- The ex-lovers got together.
- 5 dollars and...
- They suit each other so well.
Will the two of us
receive the penalty?
So Ryu Hyun Jin, Kim Kwang Hyun, and
Song Ji Hyo will receive prizes.
They are the highest grade
abalone sets.
- Are they abalones?
- They're really big.
The penalty is...
organizing the remaining cones
and baseballs.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
It's perfect. The two of you can
do it in a romantic way.
If I had picked 300 dollars,
I wouldn't have been in last place.
That was so close, So Min.
If I was on the same team
as So Min, I would have lost.
Everyone on my team lost today.
Gosh.
(After picking up balls for
15 minutes, they were done.)
(We would like to thank
major leaguers Ryu Hyun Jin and...)
(Kim Kwang Hyun for doing their best
without sparing themselves.)