(One spring day in May)
There's something.
- What's that?
- I guess we're sitting there.
- Hello.
Bo Pil, you're wearing a shirt.
- Why do you even care?
- We all are wearing shirts.
Why would you even care about that?
You're wearing two shirts.
It's one shirt.
- You're wearing 2 shirts.
- No, it's 1.
Are you wearing
one of them inside out?
No, it's one shirt.
Ji Hyo, it's winter again for you.
She's wearing winter clothes.
- It's a grandma's vest.
- That's what my grandma wears.
It's a grandma's vest.
- It's winter for Ji Hyo.
- Grandma's vest.
Jong Kook said he doesn't believe
in fortune, but he wears pink a lot.
I know.
He wears pink in TV shows.
(Jong Kook has been
wearing pink a lot is...)
(because he was recommended
to do it by a fortune teller.)
(He didn't seem
to care about it back then.)
He's wearing pink again.
- He's all pink.
- I just want...
Jong Kook to be honest.
Just say you are affected.
It's not like you don't care at all.
You can say it bothers you a little.
You better not do things
that are bad for you.
(He's being honest.)
- Okay.
- You know what I mean.
- I get it.
- It's done.
I understand.
Kwang Soo, you fell in the mud.
Did you apply paint or something?
- No.
- He spilled paint on his pants.
I heard something about it.
It's not official though.
Thankfully, we are sponsored
by some apparel companies.
But Kwang Soo pays for it.
(A rumor has it that Kwang Soo
pays for his clothes.)
- What are you talking about?
- Isn't it true?
I thought you were
a popular celebrity.
- Isn't it true?
- My gosh.
I don't pay money for that.
Really? Isn't it true?
A rumor has it that
you pay for your outfit.
Ji Hyo's new movie, "Intruder"
is finally being released.
(Ji Hyo's new movie, "Intruder"
is being released on June 4.)
"Intruder".
You should promote your movie.
Where do you intrude on?
What kind of promotion is that?
You don't have to
force yourself to do this.
What are you talking about?
I'm trying to help her.
She must intrude on something.
After he started running
his own YouTube channel,
I realized that he's not good
for TV shows.
I'm telling you.
- Is it too raw?
- Don't you think so?
Is he too unrefined?
I should get my part cut.
I know.
I just wish you good luck.
All right. It's being...
released in rough times.
But I hope it will be loved
by a lot of people.
Me too.
- Watch it wearing a mask.
- It will go well.
- Sure.
- And So Min is...
- finally coming back next week.
- Yes.
She can't wait to join us again.
I thought she'd come today.
(So Min is wearing a microphone.)
(The daily life of So Min who's
coming back after a long break...)
(will be revealed soon.)
Today, you are having Dilemma Race
where you should choose...
between personal gain and
your team's victory with R coins.
- Dilemma Race?
- Gosh.
- Before...
- Already?
- He's sighing already.
- Before we start the race,
I will introduce today's guests.
- Really?
- That's nice.
Behind the shade,
we have three guests
who faced acute dilemmas...
in their dramas.
- Acute dilemmas?
- Yes.
The guests randomly picked...
10, 20, and 30 coins beforehand.
Gosh, this is hard.
You will talk to the guests
and pick a number you want.
Then the guests you pick will
share their coins with you.
We better be separated.
We should pick a guest
with more R coins.
But the guest can lie
about the R coins...
they have.
The members should try
not to fall for their lies...
and pick a guest
without gathering all together...
in order to get more coins.
We should get as many
coins as possible.
Please say hello to the guests then.
(The shadows of the 3 guests
are revealed.)
- We have two female guests.
- First...
- Female guests.
- And we have one man.
Number two...
looks handsome. Even his shadow
is good-looking.
Just take a look at him.
Look at the silhouette.
He has a long neck.
He looks handsome.
His shadow is good-looking.
Imagine that Se Chan
is sitting there.
Even his shadow looks ugly.
(Imagine that Se Chan is sitting
there. Even his shadow looks ugly.)
You will notice that
my mouth is sticking out.
You'll be able to tell
it's my shadow.
Even the shadow looks handsome.
Look at the neckline.
His neckline is so...
So they faced
dilemmas in their dramas.
- Dilemmas.
- I wonder what dilemma it was.
- Number one.
- Yes?
What dilemma it was that
you went through in your drama?
I couldn't...
get away from...
the dating violence of my boyfriend.
(Dating violence?)
Dating violence?
Whenever I tried to avoid it,
he got me a ring,
- money, and...
- Hang on.
(Hang on.)
Jae Suk, I think I know her.
I know this voice.
I think I know her.
If you say it,
we all know will know who she is.
- She's...
- Who is she?
- Why? Who is she?
- "A World of Married Couple".
- Kim Hee Ae's...
- The bobbed-hair.
Right. Hee Ae's assistant.
Exactly.
I didn't watch
"A World of Married Couple".
- I watched it.
- No way.
She must be really busy.
It might not be her.
- Is the drama over?
- Hang on.
Number one, have you ever met
one of us before?
No.
I think it's her.
- Then...
- It's her.
Number two, have you ever met...
one of us before?
- Yes, I have.
- What? Who?
Se Chan.
- Is he younger than Se Chan?
- Se Chan?
- Am I older than him?
Let me ask you this question.
How many coins did you get? Number
one, how many coins do you have?
- This is important.
- Would they tell us the truth?
I got 10 coins.
I don't think she's lying.
- She sounds honest.
- I guess it's true.
What about you, number two?
I got 10 coins.
They are lying.
- They should share them with us.
- I think number two is lying.
- He's lying.
- He pretends to be poor.
Because they don't
want to share coins with us.
- What about number three?
- I'm...
rich at heart.
So how many coins do you have?
- I'm rich.
- My gosh.
- She's...
- She's changing the subject.
- How many coins?
- She's been in many variety shows.
- My gosh.
- She's not telling us the truth.
She doesn't give us
the exact answer.
Wait. I can't pick one.
- Did you make your decision?
- Yes.
- All right.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- I'm picking number 1.
- Me too.
- I picked number one.
- What?
- She doesn't lie.
- 4 people picked number 1.
2 people picked number 2,
and 1 person picked number 3.
Let's have them here now.
Please open the shade.
(Who are the 3 guests...)
(who put the members in a dilemma?)
- It's her.
- We were right.
(A rising star, Sim Eun Woo)
(She's a scene-stealer who
mesmerized viewers with her acting.)
(She's Actress Sim Eun Woo
with a promising future.)
- It's her.
- Who's number two?
Who are you?
It's Min Gue.
- And Jaekyung.
- She's Jaekyung.
I knew it.
Jaekyung and Min Gue.
(Kim Jae Hyung played a detective
who has a criminal father.)
(And she gives fans an unavoidable
dilemma with her charm.)
(Kim Min Gue played a king who faces
a dilemma with precognitive dreams.)
(He also gives off his charm
in many variety shows.)
I didn't know it was Jaekyung.
- Hello.
Hello, Eun Woo.
It was you, Eun Woo.
Nice to meet you.
- I really liked your drama.
- Jaekyung.
- Hello.
- It's you, Min Gue.
- You were amazing in the drama.
- Jaekyung, long time no see.
I know.
Come over here.
Let me introduce them one by one.
We have Kim Jaekyung here.
- Jaekyung.
- It's good to have you here.
This is her first appearance
in Running Man.
- I'm back in 6 years.
- It's been 6 years.
It's her second time.
(It's been 6 years.
It's her second time.)
Don't be so presumptuous.
Why are you twisting your legs?
Don't pretend to be handsome.
Jaekyung, do you
think he's fashionable?
- He's my style.
- Are you serious?
(Unexpectedly, he happens
to be her type.)
Do you like the pants
covered with mud?
Isn't it cool?
It's covered with paints.
It looks like he sat
on a painted bench.
He looks like a guy
with a free spirit.
Are you serious?
- He's happy.
- My goodness.
Jaekyung is back in our show
after six years.
Last time she joined our show,
- we had Gary here.
- That's right.
- Gary was here.
- He was my partner.
- I see.
- Really?
We moved around
provinces cooking.
- Exactly.
- I see.
You have a good memory.
My throat is choked.
- All of a sudden?
- Is it because of Gary?
Ji Hyo.
She still remembers it
while we don't.
- And...
- She doesn't remember yesterday.
Ji Hyo suddenly weighed in.
That doesn't happen a lot.
I know.
Next up is... Gosh, I really liked
"A World of Married Couple".
- I was really...
- Gosh.
I couldn't believe my ears.
- She made me cry.
- She's Sim Eun Woo.
Hello.
You started studying classics?
What does that mean?
I really like your show,
- "Hangout with Yoo".
- I see.
You played the harp...
- That's right.
- in the show.
And I was very impressed by that.
So that's when I...
- Harp?
- Did you learn to play the harp?
- Do you play the harp?
- No, that's my dream.
I listen to classical music.
- You listen to classical music.
- Classical music.
It's not that
surprising news though.
- She just listens to music.
- Why would you put it in here?
What's the big deal?
I thought it was something amazing.
I thought she bought the harp.
I listen to trot songs
because of his show.
Is there any song...
you'd like to recommend us?
Gustav Mahler.
Gustav Mahler?
"Adagietto" by Gustav Mahler.
"Adagietto"? Can you hum the song?
For us to see what it's like.
It's quite majestic.
If it's a lie, just tell us now.
- Is it a lie?
- Hey!
- Just to make sure.
- She said "Adagietto".
She can't hum the song.
How dare you talk
to a big star like that?
No, it's not like that.
- She's a star.
- I'm a star too.
I'm a star.
You're not a star.
You're a burner.
What? A burner?
So what's "Adagietto"?
It's my fault.
(It's my fault.)
She's good.
- Okay.
- You're good at this.
- It's nice that she's being honest.
- You're good.
- This feels a lot better.
- All right.
Eun Woo, do you realize...
how popular you've become?
Well, I'm on Running Man.
(Well, I'm on Running Man.)
She's so witty.
- That makes me so happy.
- She's a good talker.
- She's so kind.
- She's a really good talker.
- What's your major? Singing?
- I majored in...
musical theater.
- Really?
- You must be a great singer.
- You do have an amazing voice.
Then you must be...
- Please give her a big hand.
- Yes!
She starts acting right away.
("Hopelessly Devoted To You"
from the musical, "Grease")
(She sings confidently...)
(with a pure and clean voice.)
(Since the moment
I fell in love with you)
- She's an amazing singer.
- She has a beautiful voice.
- Right?
- Unbelievable.
(I've been only thinking of you)
- She's really good.
- She's incredible.
(I only think of you)
(She finishes off with
impressive, clean high notes.)
She's so good.
- She's amazing.
- I didn't expect this.
(We haven't seen such
a nice performance in a while.)
Are you interested in
joining a mixed-gender group?
- Hold on.
- Oh, wait.
I saw it.
- She's an incredible singer.
- Why do you bring up that show?
I'm sorry.
Do that when you hang out.
(You're on Running Man right now.)
Next up is...
- Se Chan's good friend.
- He's a good friend of mine.
- Min Gue!
- Hello.
- He's so good-looking.
We're friends too.
Why didn't you mention it?
But we're not that close.
(Min Gue sounds so cold.)
- Still...
- Just say that you're close.
- You're in trouble now.
- Jong Kook...
- Just say that you're close.
- Jong Kook seems hurt.
- You're in trouble now.
- How...
- Talk to Jong Kook.
- We do know each other.
- Jong Kook made a friendly gesture,
- We know each other.
- but Min Gue drew a line.
- He sounds serious.
We do know each other,
- but we didn't...
- Take this away. I quit.
(Jong Kook is already
throwing a tantrum.)
- Why?
- Just go down on your knees.
- You're in trouble now.
- We never exchanged our numbers.
(He didn't want to be rude.)
- Okay.
- He didn't want to be rude.
If Min Gue doesn't
put this right today...
It'll stay this way forever.
It might take a long time.
What's worse,
Jong Kook chose number two.
Really?
I chose number two.
Min Gue has appeared in...
the dramas, "Queen: Love and War"
and "Perfume".
He was in that drama too.
Was it "Signal"?
- He played a detective.
- That's right.
- He was in "Signal"?
- Yes.
- Jong Kook knows a lot.
- "I Can See Your Voice" too.
- He became famous from that show.
- He was on that show too.
- He became famous.
- Thanks to Jong Kook,
I received a lot of attention.
Forget it. It's too late.
I'm doomed.
To solve this,
you have to start from a ball boy.
Seriously.
He's an amazing singer.
- Really?
- You're a good singer?
- He is.
- I'd love to hear it.
- Min Gue, can you sing for us?
- Please go ahead.
- Eun Woo sang for us too.
- All right.
- Should I sing without any music?
- Yes, please sing just a little.
He has dimples too.
- That's his charm.
- He has dimples.
I have them too.
- Where?
- No, you don't.
You do have them.
(Here they are.)
Isn't that an ax cut?
"An ax cut"?
- Isn't that just a scar?
- Did you make it with your finger?
It's a dimple.
- That's not a dimple.
- I haven't seen dimples in a while.
- Thank you.
- I'll sing just a little.
- Okay.
I love Jong Kook's songs.
I'll sing one of them.
Jong Kook is not angry anymore.
He's smiling. Good job!
Congratulations.
Good job.
It's from the album he released
right after his military service.
- You remember that?
- You have a good memory.
Jong Kook is not angry at all
anymore.
(Jong Kook forgives Min Gue
completely.)
- I'll just sing the climax.
- Sure.
(I love you more today
than yesterday)
(Both Min Gue and the song
make him happy.)
(The song is nearing its climax.)
(What?)
What are you doing?
- That was so random.
- Look at your face.
That was nice.
- He's a great singer.
- His dimple is so deep.
- I'm sorry, Min Gue.
- That was really nice.
- You couldn't help it.
- I loved it.
It's time to distribute the coins
within the teams.
Eun Woo was chosen by most people.
We're a group of idiots.
(Jae Suk, Haha, Kwang Soo,
and Se Chan chose Eun Woo.)
It's going to be fierce.
- Eun Woo.
- Like this?
(Team Eun Woo has...)
- Show us.
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh.
- Okay!
- You were...
- You were being too honest.
- She really has 10 coins.
- I mean...
- I thought...
She was emphasizing so much
that she has 10 coins,
so I thought she'd have 30.
The rest of you
will become one team.
- Who chose Min Gue?
- I did.
- Ji Hyo and Jong Kook did.
Show us how many coins you have.
(Team Min Gue has 20 coins.)
The 3 of you get 6 coins each.
The remaining two coins will be
distributed by Min Gue.
- There are 2 coins left.
- There are 2 coins left?
If I give you the coins,
can we end our relationship?
(Can we end our relationship?)
What do you mean?
That's not what I mean.
He means...
You want me to take the coins...
- and get lost?
- That's not it.
He did make it sound that way.
- You want me to get lost?
- That's not what he means.
I mean, can we end
our misunderstanding?
Don't worry. You can take the coins
if you want.
- Jong Kook is hurt again.
- It's up to you.
Both of them?
I'll give one to each of you.
Really? You're so kind.
- Jong Kook is happy again.
- And...
Jaekyung and Suk Jin get
15 coins each.
Like I said earlier,
today you'll compete for coins
in Too Much Dilemma Race.
After every mission,
there will be Coin Dilemma.
At the end of each round,
each of you will hand in
as many coins as you want secretly.
The team that hands in
the most coins wins a point.
- Really? That's simple.
- The team that wins...
2 rounds out of 3
will be the final winner.
The two people with the most coins
in the winning team will win prizes,
and the bottom two in the losing
team will be penalized.
Considering the people on my team,
- we'll only play for ourselves.
- Seriously.
None of them would sacrifice
themselves for their team.
After each mission,
the winning team and losing team...
will receive different amounts
of coins.
So pay attention
to the mission results.
Now please change
and go to the first mission spot.
(Let's start the dilemma mission.)
(Team Eun Woo, Team Min Gue)
Eun Woo, please come here.
1, 2, 3.
(With a clap,
everyone is ready for shooting.)
I hope it goes well.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- Are you at a cafe?
- Have we started?
(Are you at a cafe?)
(Suk Jin is still relaxing.)
Jong Kook is having coffee too.
Why do you only talk to me?
Jong Kook is...
Also, you should have hidden
the logo.
- I got rid of it.
- Listen.
I didn't know we'd started.
Of course we did. Everyone's here.
Suk Jin acts differently
on camera...
more than anyone I know.
(Suk Jin can't deny it.)
Jaekyung, you look...
- a lot like Kim Ji Won.
- Who?
- From "Descendants of the Sun".
- Kim Ji Won.
She looks a lot like Ji Won, right?
- Do people ever tell you that?
- At restaurants,
- they give me more food.
- I knew it.
Do you tell them you're not her?
I just smile.
(I just smile.)
(The smile explains everything.)
You accept all the food
they give you?
- She should.
- She couldn't tell them.
- Right.
- It'd embarrass them.
Eun Woo, do people tell you
you look like anyone?
They tell me I look like Android 18.
- From "Dragon Ball"?
- Yes.
- I get it.
- She does look like her.
She looks exactly like her.
- She looks exactly like Android 18.
- They look the same.
I don't know how "Dragon Ball" ends.
- I never finished it.
- I should.
- Did it end?
- It ended very sadly.
What?
It ended?
It did about 30 years ago.
(It did about 30 years ago.)
(It ended back in 1995,
which is 25 years ago.)
It's true that Ji Hyo is
a little isolated from the world,
- but how could you say that?
- It ended 30 years ago.
Why couldn't you just say,
"Yes, it ended."
Do you know Porori?
- Porori?
- Yes, I think you look like Porori.
Do you know Porori?
(The two suddenly start talking
about Porori.)
Did she just do an impression?
- Did you just do an impression?
- Why did you do that?
- Did you two plan this?
- Was it a comedy sketch?
- Did you plan this?
- Did you do an impression?
- Poroporo...
- She suddenly asked me...
- What about you, Min Gue?
- I look like Ji Suk Jin.
- What?
(Min Gue looks like Suk Jin?)
(What?)
Suk Jin?
Oh, that came out wrong.
I mean Ji Jin Hee.
(Their names are similar,
but they look completely different.)
Why did you do that?
Min Gue.
- I almost got angry.
- Thanks.
- Thanks anyway.
- I was so surprised.
I was like, what is he saying?
I thought...
- You do look like Ji Jin Hee.
- I meant Ji Jin Hee.
I thought...
- he must be really ambitious.
- He's determined.
Now I get it.
Show us 3 ways to look cute. In 1...
- Sorry, what did you say?
- Three ways to look cute.
- What does that mean?
- Hey!
Three ways to look cute!
(Because of Min Gue, Suk Jin's face
is slammed with cream.)
(Here and here too.)
You practically punched him.
Team Eun Woo wins.
(Team Eun Woo wins
the warm-up mission.)
The coins will be distributed
according to the results.
The winning team gets cards with
0, 5, 6, 7, and 8 written on them.
The losing team gets cards with
0, 1, 2, 3, and 4 written on them.
Each of you gets as many coins
as the number you pick.
- 7.
- 6.
- Eight.
- Gosh.
Five.
- Who picked zero?
- Haha.
- 4.
- I picked 0.
(Jaekyung 4, Min Gue 3,
Jong Kook 2, Ji Hyo 1, Suk Jin 0)
Gosh, how did this...
This is unbelievable.
The Coin Dilemma starts now.
First, the members of
the losing team will...
hand in coins at the booth
over there one by one.
The team that hands in
more coins will win...
and receive one point.
Guys, let's do this.
We have to win.
We should try to meet
the minimum winning number.
- We should hand in more than 6.
- At least 5 or 6.
We'll definitely win if we get
a total of five coins.
- Most definitely.
- That team will have less.
- That's from each.
- Who'll go first?
- Right, go ahead.
- Sure.
(Will everyone keep their promise?)
(Min Gue hands in one as promised.)
(Jong Kook also hands in one.)
(Their other teammates
hand in theirs as well.)
The winning team can...
ask one from the losing team
how many he or she handed in.
- Really?
- Name the person and I'll tell you.
- Do we all get to hear it?
- Yes.
- Suk Jin...
- He's too obvious.
- I agree.
- He probably didn't hand in any.
How about Jaekyung or Min Gue?
- Right.
- Let's get a feel for them.
(They don't know if Jaekyung
and Min Gue are the betraying type.)
- Jaekyung?
- Yes, Jaekyung.
- We choose Jaekyung.
- I heard a rattling sound.
- Jaekyung?
- Yes.
Jaekyung...
I'm sure she handed in at least one.
(Team Min Gue agreed
to hand in 1 coin each.)
- She handed in seven.
- She handed in that many?
What?
(Jaekyung, 7 coins)
(Jaekyung handed in 7 coins?)
You'll hand in at least 1, right?
You could spare even 2.
I'm rich with coins.
(Rich Jaekyung handed in 7 coins
for her team!)
You didn't have to!
- That's a bit too much.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk, how about this?
- You didn't have to!
- Let's give up the first round.
- No way.
If you think about it...
You're right.
We should save our coins.
Jaekyung handed in too many coins.
It's not a bad choice
to let them win this round.
We can win the next round instead.
Winning the next round
will make us even.
Winning the first round
is important though.
- But we can't.
- How can we?
Jae Suk, who says
we can win the next round?
You just need to hand in
3, 3, 3, and 2 coins.
- I'll contribute a coin too.
- How much is that in total?
- What?
- What's our total then?
That's 9 plus 2, so 11.
- But they...
- It won't be enough.
- 11 will be enough.
- No, it won't.
- They handed in more than 11.
- Jaekyung handed in 7.
The rest wouldn't
have handed in any.
- They handed in more than 11.
- Won't you hand in any?
- Hold on.
- I'll hand in one.
Can you butt out?
We're trying to work here.
Me too!
(Can you butt out?
We're trying to work here.)
(Me too!)
I'm trying to work here too.
How else do you explain
what I have on my face?
- Just listen to Jae Suk.
- What?
- Where am I supposed to go?
- Also...
Who thinks we should
make a play for the first round?
We should.
I agree.
(Thud)
(Groaning)
- He lowered his hand.
- Why?
(Kwang Soo suddenly
withdrew his vote.)
We should go all-in
in the second round.
Who thinks we should
aim for the second round?
- It's settled then.
- It's 3 to 2.
- We'll let them win.
- Sure.
(Giving up the first round
was forced upon them.)
They wouldn't have given up
had they not heard about her coins.
- Exactly.
- We would've played.
- Let me reveal the result.
- Sure.
(The result)
I can't believe
she handed in seven coins.
Team Eun Woo handed in...
- zero coins.
- That's right.
Team Min Gue handed in
a total of 10 coins...
which makes them the winning team.
(Team Min Gue wins with 10 coins.)
- One didn't hand in a coin.
- One didn't hand in.
Who betrayed us?
Suk Jin, of course.
You can't seem
to hold a straight face.
We were going to lose anyway.
I can't believe him.
They didn't hand in a whole lot.
- I thought it'd be 13 coins.
- In the second round...
- Sure.
- Let's wish us luck.
- 1, 2, 3. Go, team!
- We need to win this round.
- Exactly.
It was my son's birthday recently,
and I was shocked.
Someone rang the doorbell...
- at midnight.
- Really?
Four of his friends
came by as a surprise...
- with a cake.
- Those are some good friends.
He must be popular in school.
- Didn't you say anything?
- What?
"Go home!"
Gosh, you startled me.
- Actually...
- "Do you know how late it is?"
We think...
that it's rude to come by that late,
- but that's not how kids think.
- Of course not.
- He has some great friends.
- Exactly.
I don't know if you remember this,
but Suk Jin...
had an English name
known as Cody IV Drop.
- Kwang Soo's was Dung Perry.
- Right.
Do the others
have English names too?
- Jong Kook has one.
- I'm JK.
- I'm JK too.
- Really?
- Those are her initials.
My nickname in high school...
- was Kim Jong Kook.
- Why?
Because I'd write my initials KJK
on my books.
- That's right.
- Hold on!
Jong Kook has finally found someone!
Look at them.
- This must be fate.
- Guys, stop it.
- They're also sitting together.
- Look at you, Jaekyung.
- Why are they side by side?
- Your initials are the same.
- No way.
- They have matching bags too.
(No way!)
They have matching bags too.
(All members of the team
have the same bag.)
Haha's ruining things once again.
Get over here, you two.
You ruin everything!
Are you kidding me?
- We'll dial it down.
- Must you force it?
They're doing it
to please themselves.
- It's one amazing coincidence.
- I'm fascinated.
- What about the others?
- Mine is Jimmy.
- What?
- Jimmy?
- As in baggage?
- Baggage?
- Are you kidding me?
- Jimmy?
- Why Jimmy?
- Is that what they call you?
- Gosh.
Min Gue, what about you?
I let people call me Ming.
- Ming?
Isn't that Chinese?
- It sounds Chinese.
- M-I-N-G.
I see.
- Ming.
- Ji Hyo, what about you?
I don't have one.
Isn't yours Dam?
- Dam.
- What about Wall?
- Yes, Dam.
- Dam!
- Dam, sure.
I'll go with Dam. So Dam!
Eun Woo, what about you?
I don't have an English name,
but I have one in Sanskrit.
- What?
- Sanskrit?
You've been odd
since the opening, you know.
- What's "Sanskri"?
- Sanskrit.
- What's that?
- It's an ancient Indic language.
- Prana.
- Is that the name?
Why do you have a name in Sanskrit?
I practice yoga,
and it's the name...
my instructor gave me.
(A unique Sanskrit name)
- I see.
- They give you names too?
Why did you ask
about our English names?
You will be facing
a dilemma in name-calling...
in this game called
What's Your Name.
With those names,
you'll play the Frying Pan Game.
I hope you recall
all the others' names.
The team to reach
10 points first wins.
- What about us then?
- Do we go with something else?
Your nickname is Loser.
- Loser!
- That's not in English.
- Then Large.
- How about Large?
- Large.
- As in x-large.
- Loser as in Go Large?
- That's the one.
- Go Large.
- What's Suk Jin's?
- IV Drop.
- IV Drop?
- From Cody IV Drop.
- I'm Perry.
- As in Dung Perry.
- Jimmy?
- Yes, Jimmy.
- I'm just Perry.
- No, Dung Perry.
- Sebastian.
- Quanninomalisquare.
- What?
Are you kidding me?
- Seriously?
- What?
- Keep it simple.
- Is this a joke?
- You've got to be kidding me.
- I'm Double Ha.
We'll begin with Double Ha then.
- Okay, Double Ha.
- We're playing offense.
- I'm IV Drop.
- Ready, set, go.
Ting, ting, ting, ting,
tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
- Four Prana.
- Prana, Prana, Prana, Prana.
Four Dam.
Dam, Dam, Dam, Dam.
(She missed the beat.)
Hold on a second though.
Ming doesn't know
how to play this game.
- You got it wrong though.
- I'm just saying.
You're making excuses.
- You're stalling.
- Hear me out.
Don't try to buy some time.
- He doesn't know the beat.
- Aren't you aware of the game?
- Really?
- I don't know how to play it.
- He doesn't know.
- Frying Pan Game!
- I don't know how to play the game.
- Not Prada.
- It's in four counts.
- It's Prana.
- I still don't get it.
- Ming...
(Just like Ji Hyo said,
he doesn't know the rules.)
He's just as clueless.
He hasn't got a clue.
- We'll start with Go Large.
- And go.
Ting, ting, ting, ting,
tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
Perry, three.
Perry, Perry, Perry.
- JK, four.
- JK, JK, JK, JK.
- Prana, four.
- Prana, Prana, Prana, Prana.
Ming, two.
(Will Ming be able to survive?)
Ming, Ming.
(He managed to survive.)
- He's good.
- Mole, one.
- Mole?
(They can't believe
what they heard.)
How can you call her that?
- A mole?
- Seriously?
- Can you believe it?
- Hey!
- What?
- She's a mole?
- Is there one among us?
- There's a spy?
- A mole?
- He's ditsy in a way.
I haven't heard that term
in a while.
- He must've been nervous.
- Prana, right.
It's Prana.
Sebastian will
kick us off this time.
- Sebastian, you're up.
- And go.
Ting, ting, ting, ting,
tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
- IV Drop, three.
- IV Drop...
(I-V Drop)
- What was that?
- Seriously?
- What on earth was that?
- I was caught off guard.
You addressed me
when your eyes were on him.
- That's how you play the game.
- My gosh.
It's like a no-look pass.
You're a clever one, aren't you?
It's a basic move.
Are you all familiar
with the game now?
- Sure.
- Right.
You'll now have to say the name
of the one that attacked you.
If I say "Ming, three,"
you'll go "Perry, Perry, Perry."
You have to say the name
of the one that called you.
You need to say
the other person's name.
- And go.
- Tang, tang, tang, tang
(Out of the blue)
Tang, tang, tang, tang,
ting, ting, ting, ting
- He messed up.
- You forgot a step.
- You missed it.
- Does that even matter?
Tang, tang, tang, tang
- We'll start with Dam.
- All right.
Ting, ting, ting, ting,
tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
- Double Ha, three.
- Dam, Dem, Darn...
Dam, Dam, Dam!
Dam, Dam, Dam, Dam,
Dam, Dam, Dam, Dam
- Dam, Dam...
- What are you doing?
This is humiliating.
He's trying to seem trendy.
Unbelievable.
- Dam, Dam, Dam!
- Let's see how Jae Suk does.
- Target Jae Suk.
- What's so hard about this?
Guys, don't be fazed.
- Look at him.
- Your palms are sweaty.
- Target Jimmy next.
- Don't be flustered.
- Okay.
- Why would you be caught off guard?
- Let's all target Jimmy.
- Unbelievable.
- Tell me about it.
- We're coming for you.
Are you guys kidding me?
- Here we go.
- Let's go.
- Ting, ting, ting, ting
- It's my turn, right?
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
- Prana, three.
- Ming, Ming, Ming.
- Ming, four.
- Pra, Pra, Pra, Pra.
What on earth was that?
(Pra, Pra, Pra, Pra)
(They all stand up.)
- Seriously?
- What's wrong with him?
- He's doing whatever he wants.
- What was that?
(The reggae lover is happy.)
What's with the sudden reggae vibe?
Why would he say it
when it's not his turn?
- Do you like reggae music?
- I...
- What on earth was that?
- I'm new at this game.
- He wasn't even targeted.
- Tell me about it.
- I mean...
- I was scared for a second.
You shocked me.
Is it Ming again?
Ready, set, go.
Ting, ting, ting, ting
(Min Gue's drumming
to a beat of his own.)
Ming...
If you're not going to clap on time,
don't do it.
- Ting, ting, tang, tang
- Frying Pan Game
- Jimmy, four.
- Jimmy, Jimmy Jimmy, wow.
(Jimmy, Jimmy Jimmy, wow.)
Ming...
He's unbelievable.
He's so bad.
For 10 minutes you were
criticizing somebody and you failed.
Last part was the worst.
- What did you do?
- Wow.
It's his English name,
so the gesture is in English too.
Okay, okay.
You're out.
It's Jimmy.
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
- Dam, three.
- Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy.
Dam, four.
(Did she attack herself?)
- "Dam, four."?
- Why?
Gosh, you guys.
Such fools!
- Hold on.
- This is not fun.
What's wrong with Dam Dam?
- Is she bad?
- Let's go once around.
What is this?
I thought he was Dam for a second.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
You and I are shouldn't
attack each other.
It gets weird when we play together.
- Sure.
- Okay?
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
- Perry, four.
- Dam, Dam, Dam, Dam.
- Good.
- JK, three.
Perry, Perry, Perry. Jimmy, four.
Perry, Perry, Perry.
(He shouts confidently.)
(I'm Perry.)
- What's wrong with you?
- She's JK.
- Come on.
- Is this okay?
- My bad.
- He's so bad in games.
- This is so difficult.
- What's the matter with you?
I'm blushing for you.
Founder!
Hey, hey.
Pay attention.
Pay attention to what?
You pay attention.
- What are you talking about?
- Pay attention.
- To what?
- You're next to me.
- I really enjoyed watching...
this game when I was young.
What is all this?
Okay, let's go.
Ting, ting, ting, ting,
tang, tang, tang, tang
- Who's going?
- Ting, ting, tang, tang
- Frying Pan Game
- Jeerinae, three.
- "Jeerinae"?
(Jeerinae, three.)
(Don't you smell urine somewhere?)
Is that a stench?
- Hey.
- What was that?
What is this?
- Should I throw up a white cloth?
- I'm offended.
We can't play this game.
- What's "Jeerinae"?
- "Jeerinae"?
- That was so rude.
- You should know his name.
"Jeerinae" is a stench.
- "Jeerinae".
- My bad.
I'm sorry. Can you cancel that?
- Cancel what?
- You can't do that.
- You don't want to?
- Kwang Soo.
- Would you like some water?
It's okay.
- I don't need water.
- Let's keep playing.
- Why would you want water now?
- She wants some.
Drink some water.
That was just too...
- Jaekyung, do you want water?
- Mister.
- Okay, here.
- You keep getting the beat wrong.
No, don't worry.
If you attack your own team
and accumulate points,
we'll give you what you lost
on your next successful attack.
I get what he means.
- For example,
- You defend.
you go back and forth
within your team.
Then you accumulate two points.
You have to attack next.
Let's don't do that.
- Within our team.
- We should do that, Ming.
- This is dangerous.
- But it's dangerous.
- Let's just keep it the same.
- No, it's not dangerous.
- JK is good.
- It'll be confusing.
We should plan this out.
Let's go with JK. Okay.
(JK, I'll go with 3.)
- Let's get started.
- Let's go.
- Go with JK. She's good.
- Start.
Ting, ting, ting, ting,
tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang,
Frying Pan Game
- Frying Pan Game
Jimmy, three.
(All of a sudden?)
- Jimmy, three.
- Ming, Ming, Ming, Ming.
- He's wrong.
- It's three!
- Take it.
- Ming, Ming, Ming, Ming.
(What a relief.)
It's three!
I was supposed to call your name.
Good job.
What's wrong with you?
He's so weird.
- Jaekyung was waiting.
- He's the weakest link.
She was waiting
and he goes, "Jimmy, three."
Jimmy is like,
"Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy."
He can only do four.
- Did I do four?
- Yes.
- This is a mess.
- Don't do it on the first beat.
- We won anyhow.
- We did.
We won anyhow.
- Okay, go.
- Nice.
- Let's start with Double Ha.
- Let's go.
- Double Ha.
- This is not easy.
Double Ha.
I don't like my name.
- Answer with "Double Ha".
- Suk Jin.
- Start.
- I get the order confused.
Ting, ting, ting, ting,
tang, tang, tang, tang
Ting, ting, tang, tang
Frying Pan Game
Ming, three.
(He attacks Ming,
who's the weakest.)
Ming, three.
Double Ha, Double Ha, Double Ha...
(Double Ha, Double Ha,
Double Ha, Double Ha...)
(Team Eun Woo wins
the first mission.)
We survived because of Min Gue.
We survived because of Ming.
Ming.
- Team Eun Woo won.
- He can't play.
We'll do Coin Dilemma again.
- They'll be taking a lot.
- Okay.
Winning team,
please pick the cards first.
- It's 5, 6, 7, 8.
- 5, 6, 7, 8?
In 1, 2, 3.
- I got 8.
- I got 6.
- Se Chan got zero.
- Don't switch.
Kwang Soo got 5, and Haha got 6.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- 3.
- 1.
Min Gue got zero.
- Rest got 1, 2, 3, and 4 in order.
- Okay.
Losing team,
hand in the coins first.
- Is it losing team first?
- Yes, that's what we did earlier.
Can we ask after?
Yes, you can.
It'll be better for you
to give up the coins.
How many?
- Hand in four coins.
- Okay, and then?
We'll hand in one each.
Do you think we have a chance?
Look at those people.
Look at their eyes.
Look at Kwang Soo.
(Eyes of a traitor)
- Hurry up.
- Okay, we'll go.
(Suk Jin promised
to hand in 2 coins.)
(Will he hand in 2 as promised?)
(Submission complete)
Our team has to win.
"Our team has to win."
Think about what he just said.
- Did I confuse you?
- He handed in one at most.
Right?
I don't like what he said.
(I don't like what he said.)
Did I confuse you?
- Here.
- Are they done?
Yes, you can ask about one person.
What did Suk Jin say?
He said he's doing it for the team.
- Should we ask about him?
- Let's ask him.
It'll be better for their team too.
- I agree.
- Really?
If it's zero, that means
they barely handed in any.
- Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin has a mysterious smile.
How many coins did he hand in?)
- My gosh.
- Suk Jin...
(Suk Jin has a mysterious smile.
How many coins did he hand in?)
No.
Suk Jin handed in two.
(He handed in 2 coins as promised.)
(He handed in 2?)
- He took the safe route.
- Really?
Really?
They all handed in two.
- 10.
- It is 10.
I'm sure they handed in two each.
Minimum is 10.
- We have to go larger than that.
- Okay.
Let's do 11.
- Sure.
- How many do you have?
- 12?
- You have 13.
- Oh, right.
(Stop lying.)
Why would you ask if you know?
- I know.
- You already know.
- Why would you lie?
- Why won't you tell us?
Why did you lie?
- We know, so why did you lie?
- Don't test me.
- Why would you ask if you know?
- Why did you lie?
- You know.
- I got confused. 13.
What about you, Eun Woo?
- 14.
- Why are you not saying anything?
You have more than me.
Prana has to hand in four.
Prana should hand in four.
We'll lose otherwise.
I don't think he'll hand in any.
- I will.
- We'll lose then.
- We'll lose.
- I'll let you hear the sound.
- Really?
- 3 so 9.
Just calculate and hand it in.
What's the matter?
- Wait until you come here.
- We have to win this round?
Just hand in...
- as many as you need.
- It's a mess.
3, 3, 2.
- 1 and 1.
- Right.
- You have to hand in a coin.
- We're a team.
- Of course.
- If we don't hand in coins,
- We'll lose.
we'll lose.
If we don't make 11, we lose.
- We'll lose otherwise.
- I'll let you hear it.
- You go first.
- You can hear it.
Please come up.
(Kwang Soo promised to hand in 3.)
(Rattling)
- We'll lose.
- It's in his gene.
He submitted three. I heard it.
(He's certain.)
Did you hear that?
Hey.
Why? You heard it.
- I think that was something else.
- Something else?
Like what?
- Stand up.
- What else?
What are you doing?
- The caps are gone.
- They're all gone.
Hey!
(The caps are all gone.
They're all gone.)
(Hey!)
- Kwang Soo.
- Come here.
That was legendary.
- Kwang Soo.
- Come here.
- Hey.
- That was legendary.
- He can't go back.
- Hey.
- It's over after one time.
- It's over.
(How did he do it?)
(He opened the water bottle
in the middle of a discussion...)
(and put it in his bag.)
(He collected 3 bottle caps
in various ways.)
(He tries to hand in more coins.)
- It's over.
- Right.
- He handed in zero.
(He acts like he's sorry.)
It's over.
Rest of you have to hand in more.
He's unbelievable.
Rest of you have to make up for it.
- For real?
- Is he human?
- For real.
Don't you think
this can be a strategy?
During the next round...
You handed in none.
We'll lose.
(He gets slapped with water.)
Strategy... Is this a team?
Did you just say that to us?
This is driving me crazy.
Let's do it among us.
We should give him up.
- We have to get rid of him.
- Kwang Soo.
You look like a drunkard
sitting like that.
(He has a new English name
from today.)
You look like a drunkard.
Kwang Soo is cool. He's on our side.
(Jae Suk promised to hand in 3.)
I'll hand in four.
(I'll hand in 4!)
Why is he saying that out loud?
- He said it out loud?
- He did.
Why is he saying that out loud?
- He's all talk.
- Who were you talking to?
I said it out loud. I'm confident.
That sound is fake.
(Haha promised to hand in 1.)
(He does as promised.)
Where are you going? No!
What?
Eun Woo handed in a lot.
- Did you hand in one?
- Who is it?
Let me announce the results.
I did it.
I'm curious.
Team Min Gue lost.
(Team Min Gue lost!)
- Team Min Gue handed in four.
- What?
- You handed in 4.
- 4?
- What?
- I handed in 2.
What? We handed in four?
I handed in 2, but 4?
- We handed in 4?
- 4?
What's wrong with you guys?
I think they'll check
how many I handed in.
(0 coin)
(Jaekyung...)
(handed in 0.)
No.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook handed in 1
each as promised.)
Team Eun Woo won.
- How many did we hand in?
(Team Eun Woo won,
and they handed in...)
Five coins.
- By one.
- See?
- You didn't hand in any.
- Who did?
Jae Suk didn't hand in any.
- He didn't.
- Four?
I handed in one. I swear.
- Did you?
- Only we did.
I did.
(Haha handed in 1.)
(I'll hand in 4!)
(He pretended like
he was going to hand in some...)
(and took them back.)
He did.
The sound tells me
that he is faking.
There is no need to make the sound.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan
didn't hand in any coins.)
Eun Woo handed in multiple coins.
How many coins did she hand in?
(Eun Woo handed in 4 coins!)
We won thanks to you
with a difference of one coin.
We won thanks to you.
We will hand in the coins
the next time.
We will do that.
You don't need to hand in anything.
We won economically.
- It was a great win.
- We won with one more coin.
It was a great win.
- Gosh, this is unbelievable.
- It's time for a fight!
- Don't live that way.
- Okay!
- What is this?
- Gosh, this is...
(The soccer goalposts
and foam-filled field)
- This is...
- It will be fun.
My goodness.
I guess we will play soccer.
It will be fun.
We need to win.
This is the last mission.
- It will be fun.
- We need to win.
(Expectant)
Will we determine the winning team
with this game?
All right.
(Enthusiastic)
Jong Kook, come here.
- You are right.
- Yes.
Jong Kook, you shouldn't be here.
He was standing
next to his close friends.
He is like that.
You know that, right?
- His close friends.
- He was standing next to them.
His close friends
- The 1st, 2nd, and 3rd are here.
- The suck-ups.
- The suck-ups are here.
- The 1st, 2nd, and 3rd suck-ups.
- All of the suck-ups are there.
This is the last mission.
The dilemma
will be choosing between...
being funny and securing screen time
with slapstick comedy...
and making sure your team wins.
- I Want to Be the King of Soccer.
- Slapstick comedy.
2 players and 1 goalie will come up
from each team...
and play a 3-on-3 match.
The goalies must stay inside
the wheeled washbowl.
They can use their hands
only within the penalty line.
The team that scores more goals
in the 1st and 2nd half wins.
- The rules are simple.
- Yes.
Other rules of soccer apply.
A foul results in a free-kick.
- That's nice.
- Handling results in a warning.
- Please come up with the lineup.
- What should we do?
- Eun Woo, be an offensive player.
- Shall I be a goalie then?
(The players stretch on the field
before the game starts.)
The ball...
- Is the ball hard or soft?
- It's soft.
- Is the floor slippery?
- It's very slippery.
- There are foams.
- If I run, I will slip.
(You won't get hurt
even if you fall down.)
(Kicking)
My goodness.
(Eun Woo warms up
with a fierce shoot.)
That was great. Good job, Eun Woo.
- That was great.
- You are intense.
(Carefree)
In the first half,
this team will have a kick-off.
- Get ready.
- Let's go!
Eun Woo, are you ready?
- Let's go.
Set.
- Eun Woo.
- That's good.
- Eun Woo, kick.
That's good.
Kick, kick. Eun Woo. Eun Woo.
(Eun Woo shoots.)
- Min Gue.
- That was a good pass.
Eun Woo, that was good.
I see that Min Gue isn't athletic.
Min Gue. Min Gue.
Min Gue!
- Min Gue!
Min Gue, you hit me here.
You hit me here.
That was good, Eun Woo.
- That was good.
- That was a good pass.
- That was good, Eun Woo.
Are you okay?
- Block them.
- Eun Woo.
My goodness.
- Block them.
- Get close to them.
- Pass the ball behind you.
- Eun Woo.
- Eun Woo, kick.
- Eun Woo!
(Falling down)
- Get the ball!
You are playing defense.
- Throw it!
- Give it to Jae Suk.
(It's your first time
at a foam-filled field, right?)
I can't believe him.
- Min Gue, it's your chance!
- Min Gue!
Eun Woo, go.
- This is fun.
- Go, go. Here.
- Jae Suk, block them.
- Hey.
Tackle her!
Good job.
- Tackle her!
- Shoot!
(Falling down)
(The slapstick comedy is as fierce
as the soccer match.)
Hey!
- Get it.
- Eun Woo, kick it.
- Kick it.
- Eun Woo.
(Slipping)
- Eun Woo, kick it. Kick it.
- Eun Woo.
My goodness.
(That's so funny.)
No!
What was that?
Is it that slippery?
Keep calm.
Suk Jin is being weird.
- Don't miss this chance.
- Tackle.
- Kick it.
- There you go.
Head the ball!
It's a goal.
Okay.
(This goal resembled...)
(Park Ji Sung's goal
that brought down Portugal in 2002.)
(Everyone went crazy.)
(Min Gue recreated the moment
in the foam-filled field.)
(It's a goal!)
He is incredible.
- Yes!
- Nice!
Okay!
- That was great.
- Good job.
- Nice.
- It's okay.
- Let's go. You can score a goal.
All right.
It's okay.
Eun Woo, watch out
for the open space.
Score a goal right away.
- Shoot!
- That's good.
- It's a chance!
- It's your chance.
- Kick!
- It's open.
Nice save.
Okay.
(Kwang Soo's superb save)
Throw it right away.
Give it to me! Give it to me!
Come on!
(His pass was too long.)
(Suk Jin tosses the ball back!)
- Good job.
- What was that?
- Hey.
- Jaekyung. Jaekyung.
(Jaekyung makes a long shot,)
(but Kwang Soo blocks it easily.)
(Grunting)
Eun Woo. There you go.
- Move it to the front. Jae Suk.
- Pass.
Keep going.
Suk Jin is good at saving.
(What?)
Kwang Soo, you need to stay
at the goalpost!
Jae Suk, center the ball!
- Eun Woo, get in there.
- Jae Suk.
(He leaves the goalpost
because he wants to score a goal.)
- Eun Woo, get in there.
- Eun Woo.
(Ouch!)
Hey!
This is bad. Tackle!
The goalpost is empty!
(The goalpost is empty!)
- Hurry up.
- The goalpost is empty!
Tackle.
- Get it away from the goalpost.
- No!
Kwang Soo, you need to stay
at the goalpost!
Hurry up!
No!
(Jae Suk kicks the ball away,)
(but Min Gue shoots
and scores a goal.)
Good job!
- Kwang Soo.
- My goodness.
Why did you come on out?
What are you, Kim Byung Ji?
Three minutes remain.
Let's go!
- Eun Woo!
- Shoo!
(Kung fu shoot)
Eun Woo.
Eun Woo, please.
- Eun Woo.
- Go.
- Dribble.
- No!
- Block the ball.
- You need to score a goal!
(Jae Suk gets a 1-on-1 chance.)
(Will Jae Suk score
or will Suk Jin block?)
Yes!
(The score goes from 2 to 0...)
(to 2 to 1.)
Jae Suk, that was great.
- You looked cool.
- Good job.
Eun Woo, good job.
- Two minutes remain.
- Let's go.
(Team Eun Woo is on a roll
with 2 minutes remaining.)
Here is the ball.
- Suk Jin, please throw the ball.
- What?
- Just take it.
- Okay.
(Suk Jin
makes teamwork impossible.)
- What is up with you?
- You are the goalie.
What is up with you?
It's hard to stand.
You could kick right away.
- Right away?
- Yes.
- That's good.
- Okay.
- Throw it right away.
- Throw it.
(What?)
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
It's a foul.
You can't do that. It's a foul.
- Kwang Soo!
- The other team gets a free-kick.
Is there a free-kick?
- Nice!
- Is there a free-kick in this game?
- Why did you do that?
- Let's go.
- Why...
I will block it.
Come on.
- I will block it.
- Stay at the front.
Only one person can stand
in the wall.
- Jaekyung.
- Go.
- You can kick well, right?
- Stay at the front.
Jae Suk,
why are your hands up there?
They should be down here, right?
I am embarrassed.
Jaekyung...
Jaekyung is in front of me,
so I am embarrassed.
I was so surprised for a second.
(A war of nerves ensues.)
- There you go.
- That's good.
That's good, Jaekyung.
Nice!
(With the inside of her foot,)
(Jaekyung kicked the ball
to the open spot.)
That was incredible.
You kicked so well.
(The shy wall was useless
in front of the sharp kick.)
That was wild. That was amazing.
(The score is 3 to 1.)
What was that?
(Disheartened)
Why did you move up?
How can there be a free-kick?
(He still doesn't understand.)
He said
the official rules will apply.
One minute remains.
- That's good.
- Jae Suk, you need to score.
(Jae Suk, please.)
You need to score.
Good job. Jaekyung, nice tackle.
- Nice tackle.
- How is she so good at this?
My knees... Gosh, that startled...
(Grunting)
(With Suk Jin, the goalie,)
It's a goal.
(the ball goes past the goal line.)
My knees... Gosh, that startled...
(Suk Jin scores an own goal!)
- It's a goal.
- What are you doing?
He scored an own goal!
- How is this a goal?
- The score is 3 to 2.
Okay. Okay.
Jaekyung, be the goalie.
40 seconds before end.
- Hurry up and go.
- Then you should just play.
No. Hurry up and go.
- Come here.
- Play the game.
- For goodness' sake.
Sir.
Why are you putting shampoo
in your hair?
Why are you washing your hair?
(Why are you washing your hair?)
(Suk Jin shampoos his hair
during the soccer match.)
- What is up with him?
- What are you doing?
What is he doing?
What is up with him?
What are you doing?
- What is wrong with you?
- He is trying to be funny.
What?
He keeps ruining the atmosphere.
Suk Jin.
- Why is the foam turning dark?
- I don't know.
It's turning dark.
- Why is the foam turning dark?
- It's turning dark.
Right now...
Hurry up and play.
- Why is the foam turning dark?
- Come on.
(Suk Jin distracts people
and passes the ball.)
- Grab it.
- Throw it.
Grab it. No, no.
You are too far from the goalpost.
(Grabbing)
What was that?
- Hey.
- Handling! It's a foul!
- Is handling a thing in this game?
- For goodness' sake.
Kwang Soo, there are lines.
- Go back.
- Is handling a thing in this game?
The other team gets a penalty kick.
- A penalty kick.
- A penalty kick?
- That's ridiculous.
- Does that exist in this game?
Don't you know
what a penalty kick is?
- Suk Jin isn't that good.
- There is no space.
It will spin
and go past the goal line.
I will aim for your face.
Okay.
It was weak. It was nowhere close.
How could you be worse
than Jaekyung?
The first half is over.
(The 1st half ends
with a score of 3 to 2.)
- I should stay a goalie.
- You did an amazing job.
- Let's go. Good job.
- We aren't too far behind.
Haha, let's go in.
- Good luck.
I know Jong Kook's strategies.
Don't be scared.
I can read Jong Kook
like an open book.
I can bet my left hand
that he will use a feint.
You look the most scared.
- You shouldn't enter the circle.
- Okay.
You don't know much
about soccer, do you?
Whistle.
Why do you even watch soccer?
- Get ready. Set.
- It doesn't matter.
There isn't enough space.
- Block him.
- Go, go.
- Come on.
- He is good.
(Here comes the tyrant
of the foam-filled field.)
Make it a 1-on-1 match.
- Block him.
- Go.
(He continues to move the ball
despite the blocking.)
- It's out of the field.
- Okay.
- We were close.
- Tackle Jong Kook.
- Okay, okay.
A throw-in.
Hold on. We haven't begun yet.
- Really?
- Move back 1m.
- Why are you being so strict?
- This isn't real soccer.
- Move back 1m.
- The entire field is 3m long, okay?
- What?
- This isn't real soccer.
Okay!
(The magician of the right foot
scores a goal!)
(The score goes from 3 to 2...)
(to 4 to 2.)
It's okay.
- You need to do a better job.
- It's okay.
If you keep being that way,
I will switch you out with Eun Woo.
Haha, I am close
to switching you out.
Kick it right away.
Haha, this spot is empty.
Here.
Get it.
Use the tip of your feet.
Are you a fool?
(Give me the ball!)
That's good.
Are you a fool?
Nice!
(He flies like a butterfly
and heads the ball like a bee!)
- It's back-header.
- Nice!
Ahn Jung Hwan moves in...
and heads the ball.
- It hit the back of his head.
- Yes.
- Ahn Jung Hwan heads the ball!
- It was like...
(Dreams come true.)
No way.
(Team Eun Woo almost caught up
with Team Min Gue.)
You scored a goal.
(The score is 4 to 3.)
You are doing great.
- We need to score a goal.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
This team has two men playing.
- That's right.
- What about it?
- Two men...
- Then have Suk Jin come in.
I am not a man.
- You aren't a woman.
- Okay. Ji Hyo, step out.
(Like a man, he slips!)
- What are you doing?
- You need to rest.
Go to the bench.
Come on out when I call you.
Why did you enter the field
as you wanted?
- You need to score a goal!
- Let's go!
Watch the wall.
Haha. That's good.
Kick.
That's good.
(He kicks powerfully
twice in a row.)
Good job.
(That was close.)
- It was like a real sport.
- It was cool.
Score a goal!
- That's good.
- There you go.
They are good.
- It's 2 against 1.
- Run, run!
- Come on.
- Tackle.
- It's 2 against 1.
- Come on.
- Go, go.
Nice.
- Nice tackling.
- Nice defense.
- That was good.
That was good.
I see that Jong Kook just likes
soccer.
Jong Kook isn't that great.
The foams make him weak.
- Eun Woo, go. Do you want to play?
- Okay. Go.
- Go ahead.
- Eun Woo, go.
- You can switch out the players.
- Let's switch out the players.
I entered the field
when Jong Kook is angry.
(He laughs loudly
to hide his anger.)
- Jong Kook isn't that great.
- Hey.
- Jong Kook is angry.
- His body is heavy.
Eun Woo and I entered...
- The foams made his body heavy.
- Really?
Stand at the front. It's okay.
I am scared.
Stand at the front, Eun Woo.
(Play ball!)
Let's score another goal.
Eun Woo, it would be cool
if you score a goal.
Move. You need to move.
- That was good.
- How did he dribble the ball?
(Jong Kook uses a feint.)
- That was good.
- How did he dribble the ball?
Defense. Defense.
Eun Woo, get close to Jong Kook.
Kwang Soo!
(This is the beginning!)
Pass the ball this way.
(When the ball comes to him,)
(he kicks.)
Jong Kook isn't that great.
The foams make him weak.
(He will put an end to that rumor.)
Pass the ball this way.
(The ball goes over the goalpost.)
- That was close.
While you have the power,
the shoot...
(The foams make you weak.)
The shoot was unsuccessful.
I know Jong Kook's strategies.
You don't need to be scared.
One minute remains.
- Eun Woo.
- We need to score one more goal.
Eun Woo, that's good.
- Eun Woo, that's good.
- I heard something.
Don't touch it.
Don't touch it, Kwang Soo.
Keep going, Eun Woo.
How is Eun Woo blocking Jong Kook?
Don't touch it, Kwang Soo.
Keep going, Eun Woo.
- Jae Suk, run forward.
- You are doing great.
- I am exhausted.
- Don't make it go out.
- Jae Suk is fast.
- Kick.
(Determined to win,)
(he makes a foul!)
- This way.
- Kick it!
That's great!
(It was a goal like a lightning!)
Eun Woo!
What was that?
(She aimed for the open spot...)
(and made the net shake.)
(Eun Woo's perfect goal
shakes up Running Man!)
(Eun Woo created a drama
without a script!)
What was that?
She is good.
Eun Woo was like Messi.
- Eun Woo is really good at soccer.
- We won!
- We did a good job.
- We won.
- Good job.
- One goal made a difference.
Eun Woo, good job.
- Eun Woo did well.
- You are really good at soccer.
After a great match,
Team Eun Woo won.
The last goal was really regretful.
- The other team did well too.
- I agree.
They didn't do badly.
Instead of drawing cards,
- we will play Name Tag Elimination.
- Okay.
The winning team will choose
a member of the same sex...
from the losing team.
The winner receives two coins...
and the loser
gets two coins taken away.
Do you understand?
You can choose your partner.
You can pick someone
who was picked before.
Why don't you go against Ji Hyo?
You said you wanted to meet her.
I pick Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
- Rip off Ji Hyo's name tag.
We pick Suk Jin.
Not all of you picked me, right?
- All of us picked you.
- All of us did.
(Not all of you picked me, right?)
(All men picked Suk Jin.)
- Really? Why? What's the reason?
- All of us picked you.
- There is no reason...
- I don't understand.
There is no reason
to pick someone else.
The first match will be
between Jae Suk and Suk Jin.
- Let's go.
- I will be exhausted.
It will be over if you fall down.
- I might win if that happens.
- That's right.
Get ready.
(Suk Jin and Jae Suk)
(Catch the Tail starts.)
You are too far from the wall.
- What?
- Stay close to the wall.
Suk Jin, if you run fast,
you will rip off his name tag.
I know. I am running fast.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Their speed is about the same.
- It's...
It's so slippery.
Suk Jin keeps getting off track.
(His breath quickens
after two laps.)
Suk Jin, you need to go against
three more people after this.
Until when will we run?
Suk Jin's speed fell drastically.
Suk Jin, you need to do this
three more times.
I can't close the distance.
My goodness.
- It's so slippery.
- Let's finish it this way.
- We should use the centerline.
- Shall we do that?
The match will end faster that way.
Let's start over.
"Let's start over."
- Suk Jin, let's start over.
- Let's start over.
- Three more times.
- This is the real match.
The real match.
Three more times.
You can't enter the circle.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
Take small steps. That's right.
- Take small steps.
- What...
What is this?
Are you doing your best?
Suk Jin, don't force yourself.
I am doing my best!
- Run! Run!
- What is this?
I am doing this with gritted teeth.
(The match between
the two proud geniuses)
My back hurts.
- Jae Suk is losing.
- Seriously.
I feel like I am going to puke.
Let's change directions.
- Let's change directions.
- Okay.
Okay.
Jae Suk, you were so close
to catching him.
- Jae Suk.
- He was right in front of you!
(Why did you change direction?)
- This is hilarious.
- Is this a show for the elders?
He is nearly there.
Suk Jin is playing it
in a strange way.
You're almost there.
(Suk Jin suddenly falls down.)
We don't know it yet, Suk Jin.
No, we don't know it yet.
Keep running.
(Struggling)
They are cute. They are so lovely.
Keep running.
Go.
He's right here.
He's right in front of me.
This is working.
(It's a close match.)
- Okay.
- All right.
Okay.
All right. One more time.
I want to go next.
You guys do it.
- Let's move on.
- So Min should go next.
Where's So Min?
What? Is he seeing things?
- Suk Jin.
- So Min is not here.
No, Suk Jin.
- It's not So Min.
- Suk Jin
What's wrong with you?
- I'll do it with Suk Jin.
- Okay. Se Chan goes first.
- What?
- I'm doing this with you.
(Laughing)
You jerk.
- Why...
- Okay.
Start.
You should walk in big steps.
Good. That's great.
You're doing a good job.
Good.
(Slipping)
Just take it off.
Don't go easy on him.
Why would you do that?
(He's getting exhausted.)
Are you all right, Grandpa?
(He struggles to hold out
with shampoo.)
Look at him.
Suk Jin is fast.
(Se Chan keeps walking
right behind him.)
Suk Jin, just make sure
you're one step ahead of him.
Just rip it off.
(Go ahead and
rip it off, you punk.)
Here. Just rip it off.
(Despite his struggle,
he's losing 2 times in a row.)
Suk Jin, this is fun.
You should try it.
- You can't go back.
- Wait in line.
This game is really fun.
What is it like?
I can't wait to try it.
You should wait in line.
Ready.
(The 3rd match starts.)
Wait. Haha has big feet.
I can't do this.
- My gosh.
- Good.
That's nice.
Good one.
(But...)
He's slow though.
Why is it hard? Why am I slow?
Haha is losing.
He's right in front of you.
- Gosh, this is hard.
- He's right in front of you.
- Hang on.
- Something's not right.
This is too hard.
Hang on. What's going on?
Gosh. What is he doing?
- What's going on?
- Hey.
- I can't believe this.
- This is called know-how.
(This is called know-how.)
(Throwing it away)
How did you do it?
This is my know-how.
This is so funny.
- What happened?
- Show me.
You looked so cool
when you threw it away.
- Was it cool?
- Yes.
Eun Woo and Jaekyung.
No, is it Ji Hyo?
- Ready.
- Be careful.
(The last match between Eun Woo
and Ji Hyo starts.)
Ji Hyo is fast.
You should hurry.
Eun Woo, walk faster.
Good.
- Walk with big strides.
- Ji Hyo is really fast.
- Eun Woo.
- Ji Hyo looks like a giant.
I know. Why is she so tall?
Is she a giant or what?
How can you walk
with such big strides?
(Eun Woo is in a rush,
but Ji Hyo seems relaxed.)
Eun Woo...
She's right in front of you,
but it's not easy to catch her.
- I know. It's not easy.
- Keep trying.
(Slipping)
- I know. It's not easy.
- Keep trying.
She's letting it go.
- Eun Woo, go.
- Hurry.
(She just looks at Eun Woo
with a smile.)
- Eun Woo, go.
- Hurry.
Run away from the giant.
Ji Hyo is just walking nonchalantly.
- That's even scarier.
- She's brutal.
She's so cruel.
She's almost there.
Go ahead and do it.
Hurry.
(What?)
(Is she letting it go again?)
She will rip it off
once you start to move.
Hurry and go.
What was that?
Just kill her.
- Ji Hyo is so...
- Ji Hyo, you...
- She's unbelievable.
- This is like "I Saw the Devil".
She's scary.
She's playing with Eun Woo.
She's having so much fun.
This is really fun.
Ji Hyo, gosh.
Go closer to the circle.
Where are you going?
What is going on?
(Eun Woo is exhausted.)
(She's out.)
- She's really good.
- I know.
How can you be so good, Ji Hyo?
This isn't easy.
(Current Number of Coins)
(Jae Suk 17, Kwang Soo 10,
Suk Jin 14, Jae Hyung 14)
We will have the last Coin Dilemma.
Since Team Min Gue lost,
they will turn in their coins first.
If we go all in,
we are going to win.
- We can win, right?
- Sure.
Let's do this.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
Please turn in your coins
one by one.
I'll go first.
I'll do it first.
For your information,
the winner will...
get the Bluetooth earphones
of A company.
- Really?
- Yes. The new model.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
(They should have their team win and
make the top 2 to win the prize.)
I'm going all in.
(Jong Kook hands in all his coins.)
(The rest of his team members
are done handing in their coins.)
Now the winning team can
choose one member.
Who should we pick?
What about Suk Jin?
- Let's pick Ji Hyo.
- What about Ji Hyo.
Let's go with Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo?
- Yes.
She has a subtle smile.
Hey, you...
You'll be in serious trouble.
Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo has changed.
Ji Hyo handed in...
(How many coins did Ji Hyo hand in?)
- 10 coins.
- What?
Seriously?
(Did she hand in 10 coins?)
It's done, Ji Hyo.
That's good enough.
See? We should hand in
all coins we have.
Hand in all the coins you have.
We picked the right person.
- It's 10 coins.
- We should hand in all of them.
You should remember this.
If we lose, you won't
get the prize anyway.
- He's right.
- Seriously,
we will lose if you don't do this.
If you keep the coins,
- they will be useless.
- I know.
- But...
- Make sure to hand them in.
I will. Why would I keep them?
Kwang Soo, if your team loses,
you'll get a penalty.
Even if your team win,
you're not going to get the prize.
Kwang Soo, I would say differently
if there was a chance to win.
But to be honest, I don't know.
We can still win.
- We can win.
- We all have to do this.
We have to hand in the coins
and win the game.
You can just keep one coin.
- If you win, give him the prize.
- I will.
Is this good enough for you?
Why do we have to do this though?
Calm down.
This is really upsetting.
Why do we have to do this?
- Why are you being like this?
- I didn't ask for it.
I have 14 coins, and I'll
hand in all my coins.
- Just do it.
- I will.
You can't watch it.
- Don't look.
- Kwang Soo, you...
- Hey, don't drop them.
- You dropped the coins.
(Dropping coins)
- Hey, don't drop them.
- You dropped the coins.
You dropped the coins.
You're not supposed to look.
I'm just sick of this.
- What's wrong with him?
- We should win.
It's a disease.
I'm having a hard time today...
because of you, not this show.
- Just do it.
- What's the problem?
What is it you want?
Just keep one coin
and hand in the rest.
Okay. We will hand it
all our coins. We will lose.
Just keep one coin with you.
- Can I keep one coin?
- Yes.
- Happy now?
- Do you believe them?
I'm sure someone keeps two coins.
I'm pretty sure. Some of them...
- will keep two coins.
- Let's do this, Kwang Soo.
I'm doing it. I will keep one coin.
Okay.
Kwang Soo, think carefully about it.
My gosh.
(However...)
Kwang Soo, can I ask
what's taking you so long?
(Kwang Soo, can I ask
what's taking you so long?)
What's taking so long?
Just put the coins down. Hey.
- Darn it.
- Just do it.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
So Min is coming tomorrow.
(The female Lee Kwang Soo
is coming next week.)
I'll be more tired from tomorrow.
(Kwang Soo has been fighting
against himself for quite long.)
Okay. Just one coin.
- Did you do it?
- Kwang Soo is done.
- I did it.
- Who's next?
(Jae Suk currently has 17 coins.)
- 17 coins?
- Yes.
Were you talking to me?
Hang on. What's taking him so long?
(Hang on.
What's taking him so long?)
Wait.
What are you doing there?
- He says...
- What are you talking about?
He asked me something.
- About life?
- Yes.
He asked me something.
(Is he getting counsel
in the middle of the shoot?)
- All of a sudden?
- About that,
I'll tell you after the shoot.
He needs some life advice.
This is crazy.
I'll hand in all my coins.
It's simple.
Let me announce the results.
- I don't expect anything.
- No.
- I handed in all my coins.
- I think we will win.
We don't know it yet.
The winner of the final round is...
We should win.
Hang on. Why do you
even expect to win?
Seriously, I handed in all my coins.
(The top two members
will win a prize.)
The winner of the final round is...
(And the last two members
will get a penalty.)
Team Min Gue won
with the score of 14 to 47.
- What?
- 14?
Team Min Gue won
with the score of 14 to 47.
(They turned in only 14 coins?)
What did they do?
- Only 14 coins?
- 14?
14? Do you mean 14 coins?
- Seriously?
- 14?
Is it 14?
Do you call yourselves
a human being?
This is just unbelievable.
- Only 14 coins.
- Guys.
We will give the penalty first.
Please bring it in.
Is it 47 to 14?
What's the penalty?
- It's cold water.
- The penalty is...
lower-body bathing in iced water...
- It has ice in it.
- for you to have cool summer.
(They feel cold already.)
During the closing,
you will soak in the tub.
- My gosh.
- Does that mean...
two of us will get the penalty?
Yes, there will be two people.
- 14 coins?
- Darn it.
Let's see. We don't know it yet.
I could've been in big trouble.
I saw this coming.
- I knew it.
- 14 coins.
The two players...
with the least coins
in Team Eun Woo is...
Who is it?
- Let me announce the bottom first.
- Okay.
Eun Woo?
It's Kwang Soo
who turned in nine coins.
My gosh.
(It's Kwang Soo
who turned in nine coins.)
(Kwang Soo explodes with anger.)
(Startled)
Seriously? Is it true?
(She struggles to survive.)
Is it true?
Why did you hit her?
What are you doing?
Don't hit her.
(Eun Woo is surprised.)
Hey.
He's mad at her.
(They all feel bad for Kwang Soo
who turned in 9 coins.)
Hey.
- Hey.
- Did you turn in your coins?
(I'll keep one coin as I promised.)
(It was his first time to keep
his promise for the past 10 years.)
Did you do it? Did you turn in
your coins, Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo did it.
- Did Kwang Soo hand in nine coins?
- Did he?
- Then...
- Why did you do that?
Kwang Soo handed in 9 coins,
and now he has only 1 coin.
- Please get into the tub.
- You have only one left?
- Hey, you were too naive.
- That's so nice of you.
I'm touched.
- You were too naive.
- Kwang Soo.
- You were naive.
- He kept his promise.
- That's amazing.
- He kept his words.
- I'm going to cry.
If we had handed in 10,
we would have won.
Kwang Soo, please go into the water.
The other person
who will be penalized is...
(It's the person
in second-to-last place.)
Haha, who has 4 left
after handing in 0.
- Gosh.
- I'm sorry.
You handed in nothing?
(Haha goes into the water
right away.)
(I'm going into the water.)
Gosh. I'm sorry.
He handed in nothing?
He handed in nothing at the end?
(He didn't have many coins
in the first place.)
- Gosh.
- Unbelievable.
That will teach you a lesson.
- Jae Suk handed in five.
- He did?
Se Chan and Eun Woo
handed in nothing.
You didn't hand in anything?
Good job.
Hurry up!
(The cold bath makes you scream.)
Please bring in the prizes.
(Screaming)
Okay.
Kwang Soo.
You were amazing.
Let me announce
the two prize winners.
Jaekyung, who has 3 left after
handing in 11, is in 1st place.
(Jaekyung, who has 3 left after
handing in 11, is in 1st place.)
Min Gue, who handed in eight,
and Suk Jin, who handed in 12, are
in 2nd place.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Hurry up!
All right.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Just a second.
If you don't play, you lose.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Calm down.
If you don't play, you lose.
I mean it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Here we go.
- Let's go.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Suk Jin wins 2nd place.)
- I win.
- The second prize is...
a car fridge.
(1st prize: Bluetooth earphones
2nd prize: a car fridge)
- Let's...
- Thank you.
Let's ask our guests how they feel.
I bet they're happy!
Of course, they're happy.
Come on the show again!
Jaekyung, it was nice seeing you.
(Haha wants the shooting to end.)
I had so much fun.
Thank you for the prize.
Please invite me again!
Thank you.
- Yes!
- Thank you!
(The shooting is finally over.
There's someone we should meet.)
(One sunny day)
(The man with flowers is Se Chan.)
Kwang Soo.
I mean...
- You won the game...
- This is not a penalty.
You won a prize, right?
(Se Chan won the race
in the 500th episode.)
(As a prize, he gets to do
house chores at So Min's place.)
(Se Chan has to go then.)
(Se Chan was forced to visit
So Min's place.)
So what am I doing here?
- This is our chance...
- Why am I wearing a microphone?
This is our chance to get together
as the younger members.
If I had to come here alone,
it would have been embarrassing.
Why are you using me like this?
I feel like I'm being used.
Who's the leader of
the younger members? It's you.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
This way.
(Kwang Soo is forced
to follow Se Chan.)
(Sighing)
But you'll do the house chores,
right?
- Yes, we'll do them together.
- Right.
(They arrive at her place
with heavy steps.)
Gosh.
This is apparently a big project.
How many cameras are there?
I feel burdened.
Are there cameras inside too?
(They feel
both burdened and excited.)
(It's finally time to meet her.)
Hey.
- I'm already tired.
- Why am I here?
- Already...
- I feel uncomfortable.
She sounds too excited.
So Min.
Hi, So Min.
Hi. What's that?
So Min.
Hi, So Min.
Hi. What's that?
Are you wearing makeup?
I just put on some lipstick.
Why did you bring flowers?
It's for you.
She's not even looking at me.
Come here.
- It's not like that.
- What is this?
Why did you bring flowers?
The note said
I should bring flowers.
(I miss Mom.)
Come here.
- Forget it. Go inside.
- Come here.
Why didn't you just bring
a cardboard cutout of me?
- Why is he here?
- Who?
That guy.
(I mean you.)
He's the leader
of the younger members.
I thought you were coming alone.
- He dragged me here.
- Let's go in.
Don't make it look like
I'm forcing you.
Just go inside.
(They finally enter So Min's place.)
Don't you think this is too much?
They've always been there.
You want your apartment
to look pretty?
Have a seat.
- Have a seat.
- Okay. Let's sit down.
(Awkward)
(He sits on the floor
instead of the sofa.)
Why are you sitting on the floor?
This is more comfortable.
It would look weird
if we all sit next to each other.
You look super awkward right now.
When there's so much space here,
you sat on the floor.
I think I'd feel more uncomfortable
if I sit on the sofa.
He hesitated at the door too.
- "Should I go in or not?"
- You should relax.
- It's not like that.
- Also, when So Min came out,
Se Chan stayed so close to the wall.
(Close to the wall)
As if to show us
that he's never been here before.
Why are you doing this?
You lie on this sofa all the time.
Cut it out. Stop lying.
- I'm leaving. I've had enough.
- No!
- No.
- I'm leaving.
You're our leader. Stay here.
- I mean...
- Sit back down.
What do you mean,
I lie here all the time?
Give me a camera or something.
I need something to do.
Give us some work.
I have some towels to fold.
They're in the dryer right now.
You can do the dishes too.
I'm sorry,
but can you look at Kwang Soo
just once?
I gave up at some point.
- Why do you only look at me?
- At some point...
Look at Kwang Soo too.
To be honest,
I don't care if they decide to
completely edit me out.
Look at Kwang Soo too.
Why do you only look at me?
So Min, you haven't put on
a microphone in a while.
Put on your microphone.
It's been so long.
- This is such an honor.
- Exactly.
Kwang Soo and I get to watch this.
Should I help you?
I can do it myself.
I haven't worn two microphones
in a while.
So Min is putting on microphones.
(Congratulations
on putting on microphones.)
I'm happy to be here.
- Running Man...
- You wear...
You wear jeans at home?
That's too much.
- Stop it. Just think to yourself.
- You...
I just thought it was strange.
"She wears jeans at home?"
She probably got a pedicure too.
(She painted her toenails
to be on the show.)
Good job, So Min.
Order some food. It'd take too long
to make something.
- Order something.
- You don't have any food at home?
I thought you'd bring something.
You don't even have any ramyeon?
I do have some different ramyeons,
but you can't mix them.
- These are all I have.
- These three?
- We could mix them.
- Then it'd taste weird.
It'll be fine.
(An invisible wall)
Is it expired?
(Kwang Soo leaves the kitchen.)
(Kwang Soo becomes invisible again.)
- Come back here.
- What?
- Where are you going?
It expired on May 4?
(They leave Kwang Soo out again.)
I think it should be okay.
It only expired a few weeks ago.
I'll just watch TV or something.
I have some lunchboxes too.
(They find lunchboxes
in the fridge.)
We could microwave them.
(What do you think?)
Hey, this is not an escape room.
(Escape So Min's apartment.)
- I mean...
- Why would you...
Do you want to eat those
and escape from here?
- You want to microwave them?
- We have nothing else to eat.
- What are they anyway?
- They're low-calorie lunchboxes.
- I feel uncomfortable.
- I mean...
You want to eat microwaved
chicken breasts and leave?
We could have ramyeon too.
Or get some takeaway food
from the restaurant near here.
That would be faster.
(You're telling me to go?)
- What are you waiting for?
- Kwang Soo,
go get some takeaway food.
- Just imagine I'm not here.
- Hurry up.
I have to do the dishes
and get takeaway food?
Should we play rock-paper-scissors?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- The winner decides who should go.
- The winner decides.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min wins.)
- I just...
- Go.
Go, Kwang Soo.
(It's always Kwang Soo
who gets penalized.)
That'd be best.
(It was decided from the beginning.)
Go now.
What are you going to get?
What should I get?
If she had chosen me,
I would have gone.
- See you.
- Should I just get ramyeon?
Yes, just get ramyeon.
(Sighing)
(Kwang Soo leaves.)
So Min, the thing is,
I feel so uncomfortable.
- Why?
- I don't know.
There's nothing much
for you to do here.
Why are you laughing?
You feel uncomfortable too, right?
I do.
But this is better.
If Kwang Soo wasn't here today,
it would have been bad.
I would have blushed the whole time
without doing anything.
- Why would you blush?
- I don't know.
It's not like
you have a crush on me.
That's not...
That's not what I meant. The whole
thing would have been awkward.
(So Min loves teasing Se Chan.)
Should I do the dishes?
Tell me what to do.
- What's that?
- Put on an apron. You'll get wet.
- I never wear an apron.
- But you'll get soaked.
I mean it.
(What's going on here?)
We're not shooting
"We Got Married" here.
So Min, this isn't "We Got Married".
This is Running Man.
- I mean...
- I never wear an apron.
You'll get completely soaked.
Really? I don't usually
wear an apron.
Put it on yourself.
This is too awkward.
Should I tie it for you?
- This isn't "We Got Married".
- I know.
I feel uncomfortable too.
I don't like it either.
But what can I do?
(We haven't seen their chemistry
in a while.)
Don't worry. And I dry them
with this afterwards?
- Yes.
- Okay.
You're the first guy
who has done the dishes at my place.
(So Min takes a picture.)
(The atmosphere is getting weird.)
This feels weird.
Doing the dishes...
- "What am I doing here?"
- How did you feel?
It's just work for me.
Are you really here for work?
- I'm here to do the dishes.
- I mean...
Did you come here...
to visit me or...
I don't have to ask Kwang Soo...
because he came here
even though he didn't have to.
Kwang Soo came back
just at the right moment.
Kwang Soo, help me!
- What?
- I feel suffocated.
- Kwang Soo.
- Why?
- Should we eat here?
- Did you do the dishes?
I did the dishes.
Explain.
What did you get?
I have non-alcoholic beer.
Sit down.
I have a family problem.
I have to go.
Don't go. Stay for a bit.
- What did you get?
- Dumplings.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Kwang Soo.
- No problem.
Try sundae. It's good.
It's good.
Dumplings are good too.
Do you know I became a new person?
Your attitude changes
after you're sick.
What changed?
I want to be nicer.
I was nice all this time...
- Why are you glancing around?
- I'm not.
Didn't you say
you're going to be nice? Continue.
- Yes.
- I was just asking.
I'll be considerate of others,
respect the elderly,
- and love my friends.
- Try the soup.
Try the soup.
- Eat and shut my mouth?
- This is really good.
- No.
- Eat and shut my mouth?
What changed?
When did I tell you
to shut your mouth?
The soup is really good,
so I told you to try some.
Are you all right?
Are you back to normal?
Do you talk a lot
when you're home alone?
I rarely did.
- Why?
- She's exploding right now.
Am I talking a lot?
- Can't you feel it?
- Don't you know?
Since I entered your house,
you talked nonstop.
I'm not talking a lot at all.
- You?
- Yes.
You're back. We don't have to worry.
We can leave.
You can't leave
until you finish this.
Hold on.
(It's white carpet. Be careful.)
Spill it.
(Chuckling)
(He spills fish cake soup.)
- Hey!
- No.
- No, no!
- Hey!
(No, no.)
- I don't know.
- You did.
- It's fish cake soup.
- I only got it on my pants.
- Look.
- I swear.
It's on the floor.
Did you spit it out?
What's this?
It's sundae.
It's the liver.
- It was chewed.
- No.
It is. Look. It's liver.
So Min, I caught him.
I told you first.
It's obvious like a dot
because it's white carpet.
(How dare he?)
Why? I'm right.
Right, So Min? It's like a dot.
Look. It won't get erased.
Once this dries up...
(He explodes.)
Why? Why?
I'm right.
Stop it.
(This is hilarious.)
Fold the towels.
(They had fun,
so it's time to fold the towels.)
You should fold the towels.
We can do it together.
(Sighing)
Pause and pull to open it.
Don't bring them if they're not dry.
Only bring them if they're dry.
(They went home
after they folded all the towels.)
They're here.
(Somebody is waiting
for the members.)
(So Min is back in good health.)
You're celebrities!
(The atmosphere boosts
thanks to So Min.)
(She has an invitation
to a village.)
You just have to dig for treasures.
(There's a golden village
where you can dig up treasures?)
(Everything starts going wrong.)
(They hear people screaming
inside the village.)
(They find people's name tags
one by one.)
Why are you being fooled?
- Where is he going?
- I saw him hiding something.
(Suspicious people
in a strange village)
(Mysterious serial eliminations)
(Don't trust anybody.)
(Find a clue
about this village's mystery.)
(There's somebody
who's behind everything.)
(What's the secret
surrounding this old village?)
(Eliminating Trespassers:
Secret of the Old Village)