- Okay. - Hello.
(One windy day in January)
- Hello. - Hi.
I heard Suk Jin has very good news.
(Suk Jin has good news?)
- I know. - What news?
- I don't know what it is. - You posted about our show...
on social media even before it was aired.
That's right.
(Feeling guilty)
You posted about our show...
(Suk Jin spoiled the losers on his social media before the show.)
on social media even before it was aired.
- That's right. - I saw that too.
How could he do that? My gosh.
(The ending of Episode 486 was spoiled by Suk Jin.)
I feel really bad, and I apologize to the production crew.
(He has no excuse.)
We shot it a while ago, so I thought it was already aired.
(He thought it was already aired.)
It's not like you're new to variety shows.
- So Min and I... - You're not supposed to say that.
(Startled)
You can't say that. It's the spoiler.
No, it's not. The episode is aired, so it doesn't matter.
(By the time this episode is aired, it doesn't matter.)
Oh, really?
(Is that it?)
Will you pull yourself together? You don't do things that you should do.
(Posting on social media)
And you do what you're not supposed to do.
- He never listens to others. - Is he a green frog or what?
(Suk Jin updates his social media when he's not supposed to.)
- Why did you do it? - You know what?
I completely had no idea.
But about 30,000 people read it immediately.
(He spoiled the show without thinking,)
(and 30,000 people liked it.)
A lot of people read the post.
(Many viewers complained on Suk Jin's posting.)
And they all said the same thing.
"Suk Jin, no!" "Spoiler alert."
(Ji Suk Jin, 384,264 people like this post.)
- Please... - They all said that.
"Suk Jin, no. Spoiler alert."
"Get it together, Suk Jin."
(Pull in your ears, Suk Jin.)
What's funnier is when I called him right away.
(The producer called Suk Jin after seeing his post.)
"Suk Jin." I said. And he answered, "Hey, Chul Min."
"I just saw your social media." I said.
"Did you? It's funny, isn't it?"
(Did you? It's funny, isn't it?)
Gosh, he's so tactless.
(Shocking)
- He has no wit. - My gosh.
(I thought he called me because he liked my post.)
My gosh. So I deleted it right away.
(And there's a rising star who's as popular as Suk Jin.)
Se Chan and Se Hyeong are doing something together...
(Jae Suk heard something)
- On YouTube. - on YouTube.
And it was categorized as a kids' channel.
That's right. They think it's a kids' channel.
- Really? - Why?
(They are in their 30s.)
- Why is that? - Se Hyeong and you?
Is it a kids' channel?
Those who are in charge watched their channel...
and thought it was for children.
- It's not like that. - They looked like kids.
(It wasn't done by human.)
Their faces were automatically recognized by the computer.
(After scanning the face,)
And it was categorized as a kids' channel.
(it was categorized as a kids' channel.)
So you can't write comments on their videos.
- Really? - You can't. It's blocked.
- You can't leave comments? - No.
(The video only contains childish mischief...)
(with a lot of screaming.)
(It's obviously a kids' channel.)
(So his way to make some income was blocked.)
So we are classified as kids.
Isn't it good?
(Take it as a compliment.)
- Why? - It's good. It sounds cute.
People say we look young.
They play pool in the video. How would they look like kids?
(Kids who play billiards eating some jjajangmyeon?)
I mean, just one video. You're right.
There's a vlog.
(Flustered)
- That's right. - I'm talking about the vlog.
It's cute though.
Before we start today's race,
I asked you to bring something meaningful to give someone...
(They were asked to bring a gift to someone...)
and something you couldn't throw out but wouldn't mind...
(and something they want to throw out.)
- if someone else did. - Yes.
Let's find out what you brought first.
(It's time to reveal the items they brought.)
I brought something that's really useful.
- Me too. - I brought something good.
- What's that? It's too big. - To be honest,
(The items they prepared are brought in.)
I wanted to bring a treadmill.
Gosh, what's this? It's so big.
(And among them,)
- This is so... - Gosh, what is this?
(what Ji Hyo brought stands out.)
Is this what Ji Hyo brought?
- Is there a person in it? - Is it a motorcycle?
- Isn't this a motorcycle? - No.
(You'll know once you see it.)
Is it a bicycle or what?
(Could it be...)
Hey.
(He just can't stop spoiling things.)
Is it a bicycle or what?
(Pretending to not know)
Can't you pretend not to know it?
(You're so slow-witted.)
What is this?
- Is it a bicycle? - I don't know.
(Taken aback)
He spoiled it again.
(He's ridiculous.)
He just did it again.
He spoiled it again.
Is it a bicycle for kids?
(He keeps going.)
(It's the birth of Spoiler Jee.)
- Spoiler alert. - He did it again.
I like that character.
- There's only one. - How did you bring a bicycle?
(Shaking her head)
- Let's take a look. - Okay.
(Haha will reveal his item first.)
- Please open it one by one. - What is it? I want that one.
- Open the meaningful gift first. - This is meaningful.
(He'll open the meaningful gift first.)
This is a meaningful gift. I've given it a lot of thought.
(What did he bring?)
I brought this with one person in mind.
(Especially...)
I have this in my restaurant.
(His meaningful gift is also in his restaurant.)
- It's so... - What is it?
(What is it that he had to put it in his restaurant?)
Let me tell you what it is.
(He thought of only one person while preparing it.)
(What would his gift be?)
What is it?
- This is it. - I knew it.
I like to drink alone these days.
What is that?
(What?)
That's...
I know what it is.
If you stick a bottle on it and put a glass under it,
(What did he bring?)
it pours you drinks.
(It's a companion for someone who's lonely.)
If you stick a bottle on it and put a glass under it,
(It's a drink dispenser.)
it pours you drinks.
(This isn't a product placement advertisement.)
It doesn't feel right to pour yourself a drink, right?
But this makes it feel like someone poured you one.
(It's like he came here to sell it.)
- That's right. - I don't feel lonely.
I brought this...
- thinking about So Min. - Me?
(Why did he bring a drink dispenser for So Min?)
I saw you were shaking hands drunk.
(Kwang Soo recited a poem for So Min in Episode 471.)
- I saw that too. - I saw...
(She has terrible drinking habits.)
you were rolling your eyes drunk.
(He revealed her terrible drinking habits.)
No.
You got it wrong.
- I don't like to drink alone. - I see.
(She's 100 percent lying.)
Shall we take a look at the meaningless gift?
- What is it? - Why is it so big?
(It's followed by something that Haha wants to throw away.)
- Isn't it a tent? - No. This is...
something I treasured.
(Why is it so big?)
- I didn't want to get rid of this. - You should...
pay money to throw out something like this.
That's why I brought this.
- You need to pay to throw that out. - You need a ticket.
(You need a waste sticker when you're dumping things like that.)
- That's right. - It's too big.
You're using our show to save money.
- To save 3 dollars? - It's only 3 dollars.
(You're trying to save that money.)
- Gosh, Haha. - Some people...
- might like it. - What is it?
It's very meaningful.
- What is it? - What's that?
(What would it be?)
- Gosh, what is this? - It's Kim Jong Kook and Haha.
(What?)
- There he goes again. - It's our restaurant.
(What Haha wanted to throw out is...)
This is Jong Kook and this is me.
(the cutout of Haha and Jong Kook that is in their restaurant.)
I just couldn't throw it away.
There he goes again.
(Why did he bring that?)
- He's promoting the restaurant. - This is PPL.
(Dumbfounded)
- Just throw it away. - Hey, what's that?
(That's too much.)
This is the worst.
(He brought something he wants to throw away.)
That's good.
Hey, it's nice.
(Here's 1 person who's satisfied.)
It looks cute. It's cute.
- It's so cute. - I know.
If you find it cute, scream.
(His business partner is satisfied.)
- My gosh. - It's cute.
(How others react)
- Is this Jong Kook? - Yes, it's Jong Kook.
Jong Kook doesn't have big eyes like this.
(It's photoshopped to distort the reality.)
Are they big?
This needs to get changed.
(The real version)
Gosh, it's so cute.
That's ridiculous.
(Booing)
Just throw it away.
- People are dying to have this. - Throw it away.
(Take it back!)
- It's so cute. - Throw it out.
If you put it on the wall and get an LED light,
(Meaningful item: Drink dispenser)
(Throwaway item: Cutout of Haha and Jong Kook)
- It's cute. - It makes a good mood light.
That's true.
I brought something that you would like.
(Jae Suk's meaningful item will be revealed.)
- That's right. - That sounds good.
Jae Suk brings something good at a time like this.
(Expectant)
This is also very meaningful and easy to carry around.
(Unlike Haha's cutout hardboard...)
It's not hard to take home.
All right.
You guys will love this. This is popular these days.
(They're looking forward to Jae Suk's gift.)
(I see.)
You guys will love this. This is popular these days.
(It's hot these days.)
(It's his album.)
(An assorted gift set of Yu San Seul's goods)
It's called the Yu San Seul set.
We all are trying to promote our business.
(He promotes himself.)
Why are you promoting yourself on Running Man?
(His second character of MBC)
No. My parents would want this.
(The good daughter is after Yu San Seul's goods.)
I can sign it for you.
Where's the bottle opener?
(Where is it?)
This isn't what you can buy.
- What did you say? - I said a bottle opener.
(Turning)
- Where's the bottle opener? - This isn't what you can buy.
What did you say?
(How dare you say that?)
I said a bottle opener.
Why are you being so sensitive?
(He's sensitive about talking about Yu San Seul.)
A bottle opener.
I'm sorry.
Those are hard to get.
(Some of them want the assorted gift set of Yu San Seul's goods.)
They are really popular.
All right, everyone.
I didn't bring anything useless...
- for what I want to get rid of. - Really?
(Jae Suk's throwaway item will be revealed.)
It's easy to carry around.
- Again? - And...
I brought what you'd find useful this season.
(They're looking forward to Jae Suk's item.)
(A must-have item for this season)
What is this?
(A Halloween bucket)
- What? - What's that?
(Unbelievable)
- What is that? - Halloween is...
in October.
You just brought what Ji Ho threw out.
(He's throwing out his son's item.)
What's that thing?
- Isn't it a chamber pot? - No.
It's so insignificant.
Why would you say that?
(The ultimate insincerity)
- My gosh. - I told you before.
(Dangling)
There must be something else.
(That can't be all.)
- There's nothing. That's it. - Is that it?
- That's it. - Unbelievable.
(Empty)
Isn't this nice?
You can use it when you paint.
(Pathetic)
To wash brushes.
(Laughing)
He's racking his brains.
And when you don't have much time...
(He squeezes out all the use of it he can think of.)
and you don't need to buy much, you can use this.
(Going too far)
It's like a shopper bag.
(Saying anything that comes across his mind)
You can use it as a shopper bag.
This isn't a shopper bag.
- It's plastic. - Stay quiet.
What if Ji Ho wants it back?
(What if it's your son's favorite?)
- Does he know about this? - To be honest,
Na Eun tried to take this back. So I had to hide it.
(He brought the precious item after struggling with his daughter.)
- I had to give her something else. - Seriously?
Yes.
I told Ji Ho about this.
(Meaningful item: Yu San Seul's goods)
(Throwaway item: Halloween bucket)
He said he doesn't need it anymore.
- Ji Hyo. - I'm curious about this. It's big.
(Ji Hyo's meaningful item will be revealed.)
- It's the biggest one. - It looks like a motorcycle.
(What would the huge item be?)
For a meaningful gift,
I brought this thinking about So Min and Suk Jin.
(Is it a gift specially for Suk Jin and So Min?)
Because Suk Jin is always...
(What is it?)
- jealous of Jong Kook's thighs. - Isn't this a motorcycle?
(Suk Jin is jealous of Jong Kook's thighs.)
He was always jealous.
(Everyone with thin legs stand up.)
- And... - It's really big.
- Wait. This is... - Gosh, this is...
- It's a bicycle. - This is nice. Are you sure?
(Suk Jin was right about that.)
- Is it a good one? - It's really good.
(The three brothers with skinny legs are interested.)
Ji Hyo, I want this. Hey, Ji Hyo.
- This is really good. - I want this.
(Ji Hyo's meaningful item is wanted by everyone.)
This is mine.
(Luxurious bicycle)
- I wanted to buy a bicycle. - This is expensive.
(I want this.)
Why would you give this to us?
Ji Hyo, did you steal it? It has a lock.
It has a lock.
(It has a lock on it.)
Ji Hyo, I want this bicycle.
No, wait.
(But it is my bicycle.)
- I will ride it. - Wait.
- It has her name on it. - I'll take this.
This is new.
(Are you sure it's your bicycle?)
I'm going to ride it.
This is a road bike.
Gosh, this is good.
(Passing by)
- Where are you going? - He's so mischievous.
- Where are you going? - Hey!
- This is a road bike. - Gosh, this is good.
(The mischievous boy steals the bicycle.)
Hold on a second.
He's so mischievous.
(He's like a little boy who wants to play.)
- Where are you going? - Hey!
(He leaves the set.)
- Jae Suk. - This is...
You might get hurt.
(You're going to get yourself hurt.)
It's perfect for your legs.
(It's perfect for the length of your legs.)
- Ji Hyo, when did you buy this? - This?
Ji Hyo, what's this number?
(The unit number of the apartment)
You stole it. I'm sure she stole it.
(A bicycle from another house)
Did she paint it?
- Does she still do that? - She stole and painted it.
(Cornering Ji Hyo)
- You can't do that. - This isn't right.
(She hasn't been able to say a word yet.)
- Now, she even steals things. - No.
(Old term)
- So did you paint it? - I didn't steal it.
- Do you know the combination? - No, I don't.
(If you're the owner...)
- What? - What do you mean?
- She stole it. - I don't know the combination.
(It's my bicycle, but I don't know the passcode.)
- What? - What do you mean?
(She's turning herself in.)
She stole it.
- I don't know the combination. - Why do you not know that?
After Ji Hyo turned 40,
- she started theft. - No.
(Ji Hyo earns 1 skill point in theft at the age of 40.)
No, it's not like that.
- This is... - Do you work two jobs?
(A celebrity and thief)
- Ji Hyo, I just rode it. - Yes.
It's not your size.
No. This is a pixie.
I guess her ex-boyfriend was your height.
(We got you.)
(They're suspicious that the bicycle belonged to her ex-boyfriend.)
- Can you prove that it's yours? - Try riding it.
(Prove that it belongs to you.)
- Ji Hyo, it's not your size. - It's dangerous.
No. I'll show you.
(I'll show you by riding it.)
Wait.
You can't even touch the ground.
(Struggling)
Do you ride it like that?
(Is she levitating?)
Ji Hyo, this isn't right.
(Why can't I ride it all of a sudden?)
You're standing on your tiptoes.
(Who rides a bicycle while levitating?)
I think she really stole it.
- I'm serious. - No.
(They're being certain that it's not her bicycle.)
She couldn't just throw it away.
(It's difficult to throw out your ex-boyfriend's item.)
To be honest,
I gave this to Seong Mun.
(Her little brother)
- You just made that up. - No, I'm serious.
I like that ad-libbing.
(We compliment your ad-lib.)
- That was nice. - Well done.
If it was Seong Mun's she would've said that sooner.
(There's no trust among them.)
But she tried to ride it as if it was hers.
I bought this for Seong Mun.
(Shaking his head)
He uses public transportation.
(She bought it for her younger brother who commutes by bus.)
- I felt bad so I bought him this. - Okay. That's enough.
Let's move on.
- I bought it for a gift. - Let's just say that.
(Okay. Let's move on.)
- Okay. - Let's just say that.
- Let's move on. - All right.
- Let's say that. - Okay.
(Let's laugh about it and move on.)
- Just move on. - Is Seong Mun okay about this?
Let's just move on.
I bought this for him,
- so it belongs to me. - I feel bad for you.
No, listen to me.
(It's a bicycle that holds her memories.)
She opened the door and took this.
No, I'm serious.
All right. What is the thing you want to get rid of, Ji Hyo?
(Ji Hyo's throwaway item will be revealed.)
It's also big.
- It's a bicycle too. - What? Is it a bicycle?
- She brought two bicycles. - Why do you have so many bicycles?
(Is she throwing away a bicycle?)
(Is she a bicycle thief or what?)
What?
- She really stole it. - What's this?
(Bursting into laughter)
Gosh, what is this?
- She really stole it. - What's this?
(A filthy bicycle)
She painted it.
It has a lot of dust on it.
(Spitting)
- Hey. - There are...
a lot of bicycles like this in my neighborhood.
- No. - Isn't this from "Um Bok Dong"?
No.
(Dirty)
(Um Bok Dong's old bicycle...)
(that he swept all the cycling competitions in the 1930s with)
(Is this the bicycle?)
- He said Um Bok Dong. - My gosh.
What is this?
(It's even got a flat tire.)
- The tire is flat. - This is horrible.
- I want to throw this away. - This is for the trash.
(Agreeing)
It's so obvious that she wants to get rid of it.
(It's obvious.)
You should've at least wiped it down. Look at the dust.
I received this as a present.
- When? - It was a gift.
It's a bit...
(Look at Suk Jin.)
- too small for me. - It's too dirty.
It's too small for me.
(He takes his hands off after he was about to touch it.)
(Suk Jin didn't touch it because he thought it was too dirty.)
He didn't touch it because it looked dirty.
- It's too... - He just pretended to touch it.
For some time, I rode this...
(Meaningful item: Expensive bicycle)
- from Ilsan to Gangnam. - You must be good at riding it.
(Throwaway item: Old bicycle)
Mine are not objects.
I wanted to bring good presents.
(It's time to reveal So Min's meaningful item.)
- We had to bring meaningful ones. - Right.
(So Min's meaningful item that she prepared all night.)
I couldn't sleep much because I had to prepare this.
- I made a lunchbox. - A lunchbox?
You're going to give these to Se Chan.
(She's blatant.)
(Was the food made for him?)
Look at that.
(So Min made a lunchbox for someone she doesn't know.)
- I... - She's very...
- She's very cute. - They're not for me.
(So Min's meaningful lunchbox)
I've prepared this.
It's rice mixed with butter and soy sauce.
(Rice mixed with butter and soy sauce,)
- There are sausages and gimbap. - They're heart-shaped.
(Heart-shaped sausages gimbap, and jangjorim)
- There's also jangjorim and eggs. - This is amazing.
This is potato stir-fried with roe.
(Heart-shaped sausages gimbap, potato stirred with roe,)
(and mini tomatoes)
Seeing how there are cup noodles,
(Even cup noodles for spiciness.)
- it's not for me. - It looks cute.
(It's definitely not for me.)
Look at this.
(This lunchbox prepared with so much effort...)
- Do you think this is for you? - No.
(doesn't belong to Suk Jin...)
Kwang Soo?
(or Kwang Soo.)
- She texted Se Chan this morning. - What did she say?
She took a photo of this lunchbox.
She wrote, "This is enough, right?"
(Would lunchbox be enough?)
Wait. That means you two...
(Does that mean it's for him?)
What's going on?
(Haha is too into it.)
There he goes again.
I asked him if this would be good to bring.
(That's not it.)
- That's all. - Why would you ask him?
You could've asked me.
What? It'd be weird to text the rest of you in the morning.
(So Min's excuses aren't good enough.)
- We were all up. - It's...
(Laughing)
What's wrong with him?
(What's with him?)
(There must be somgthing going on betweeen So Min and Se Chan.)
- What's wrong with him? - That's why I...
What's wrong with you?
(Haha feels butterflies in his stomach.)
(Was I like that too?)
Come on.
My heart is racing.
(Whispering)
Why would yours race?
(Why in the world...)
- I don't know, but it is. - Come on.
(This old man's heart starts to flutter at young people's love.)
This is an item I want to get rid of.
(So Min's throwaway item is revealed.)
Actually, I'd like to apologize beforehand.
I can't really say it's something I want to get rid of.
(Talking for a long time)
- It's... This is... - Hey, what are you doing?
(It's a t-shirt with a picture of Jong Kook.)
- Why do you have that? - Well...
(An unexpected encounter)
- That's not it. - Goodness.
Hear me out.
(Why does she have that?)
- Look. - That's...
Why would you get rid of that?
(If you want to get rid of it...)
- Just give it to me. - Hear me out.
(If I were to tell you about this t-shirt,)
For Jong Kook's concert,
(Se Chan made this t-shirt especially for Jong Kook's concert.)
Se Chan wanted to make it special,
- so he made 10 of these. - Right.
- He gave me one of them. - He made it.
(She took one shirt because it looked really nice.)
I really liked it, so I took one home.
But when I wore it at home,
it felt like there were just us two there.
(Feels like there is a man in the her room.)
- It really felt that way. - I can understand.
(Embarrassed)
- It seemed like we were together. - Right.
When I laid this on the table, it felt like he was watching me.
It was very frightening.
It seemed like we were together.
(It feels like someone else is home.)
When I laid this on the table...
it felt like he was watching me. It was very frightening.
(It feels like someone's watching me.)
Give it to me.
(What is the advantage of having the t-shirt?)
If you're mad at him, you could pinch his nose.
(Because of Jong Kook...)
Like this. Or...
(You can punish the shirt instead of Jong Kook.)
you could do this.
(This is good for these weak two who can't fight Jong Kook.)
- That's hilarious. - I like it.
- It's very meaningful. - It's really cute.
(Meaningful item: Lunchbox, Throwaway item: T-shirt)
- Next up is Suk Jin. - Should I go?
After receiving the text,
(Suk Jin introduces his meaningful item.)
I thought about the past 10 years.
- I... - How about you take it out first?
(Jae Suk cuts him off.)
- How about you take it out first? - I...
(Sure!)
Gosh, that was refreshing.
(Jae Suk preemptively blocks the old man's lecture.)
(It's given gift-wrapped!)
- You wrapped it? - I was happy...
to be able to give a present to a fellow member.
- Did you buy that? - So I went...
(To buy a gift)
- to the department store. - Seriously?
(He bought it at a department store.)
My wife came with me.
The moment I laid my eyes on it, I was reminded of Kwang Soo.
(Suk Jin thought of Kwang Soo as soon as he saw this item.)
Me? What is it?
(Is it for me?)
My wife got it for him.
- Thank you. - It was displayed,
(Suk Jin's wife thought that it was perfect for Kwang Soo.)
- and she pointed at it. - What is it?
- Thank you. - We really bought this.
They couldn't wrap it,
(It's gift-wrapped by Suk Jin's wife.)
- so my wife did. - Really?
(Kwang Soo is touched.)
- She did it? - We're so grateful.
Anyway, these are padded bottoms.
He needs this.
It's...
- She got it just for you. - It's real.
(Suk Jin's wife chose padded bottoms for Kwang Soo.)
- Let me see. - Suk Jin.
This won't do.
- It's enough. - He needs more.
(It's not enough for Kwang Soo's buttocks.)
- Goodness. - It's too thin.
- It's the best gift. - How nice of her.
- That means she saw the movie. - This is...
("Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks")
- This is... - Don't be ridiculous.
She watched it.
- That means she saw the movie. - Don't be ridiculous.
(She saw his bottom in that movie.)
She watched it.
(He'll be forever teased for his nude scene.)
(Cheer up, Kwang Soo.)
- All right. - We thought of each other.
(Very touched)
Thank you...
(Thank you for your gift. I will wear it well.)
Yes, thank you.
- Next up is... - Something to get rid of.
(Suk Jin reveals his throwaway item.)
For that category, I brought an electronic device.
- Really? - Does it still work?
(I want that electronic device.)
I want it.
We used this when we rented a car in the States over 10 years ago.
(It's from his trip with his wife to the United States 10 years ago.)
(This item holds memories from 10 years ago.)
- Is that a navigation device? - It's a navigation device.
(It's a GPS device for car from the US.)
(Laughing)
(Does it even work?)
Does it even work?
- We set this in our car. - That's...
(Suk Jin starts introducing the GPS device for car.)
(Suk Jin can't help himself from laughing.)
This is the device.
It looks very third rate.
(Another statement by a straightforward host.)
- That's because... - I can see it.
(Where can we use this GPS device in this country?)
When can we use that?
You can use this in the States.
In the States and Canada.
(So where can anyone use it in this country?)
- So who'll use that? - It's for Americans.
(Suk Jin keeps repeating.)
It's for the States and Canada, and it displays Korean too.
(That's the problem.)
If you say Niagara Falls, it'll take you there.
How can we go there from here?
You need to be there.
- Right. - But we got it here.
American rentals all have navigation devices.
(This GPS device is useless.)
You can't use this here.
- It's for the States and Canada. - It's useless.
It'd be insane to set that up on Ji Hyo's bike.
(It's a complete set of useless items.)
- And ride it in the States? - And ride it in the States.
You could visit the Niagara Falls.
(How to get to Niagara Falls)
It's for the States and Canada, and there's Korean language too.
(Turn the device on, ride the bike, and go to the Niagara Falls.)
It's nice.
(He doesn't sound that excited.)
- You don't sound too excited. - What?
What? It's nice.
(He disassembles it.)
I thought you were talking to me.
It's better than your Halloween bucket.
(Suk Jin attacks him.)
(How dare you call it so?)
"Halloween bucket"?
(His face turns red.)
- At least, his is useful. - Come on, now.
(Both GPS device and the Halloween bucket seem useless.)
How could you call this so?
It's so pretty.
(They are about the same.)
This is an electronic device.
This will be very popular when Halloween comes.
- This was expensive. - He's so harsh.
(Meaningful item: Padded bottoms)
You can fasten it like this.
(Throwaway item: GPS device from the US)
Next up is Kwang Soo.
- This is something you need. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo introduces his meaningful item.)
- That's important. - I brought one.
This is...
(Impressed)
You rarely use this at home.
(What is Kwang Soo's item that everyone is impressed?)
- This is more for restaurants. - What is that?
- Jong Kook would like that. - It's a blender.
(It's a big blender...)
- Isn't that a blender? - Oh, it's a blender.
(with a set of blades.)
There are various utensils inside such as knives.
- Those are good for athletes. - You're right.
(It's a must for people who work out and enjoy shakes.)
Wook Min would like it.
That's probably about 1,000 dollars.
(A blender expert)
- Really? - You're right.
- That's about 1,000 dollars. - Really?
(This big blender is worth around 1,000 dollars.)
- Am I right? - Are you serious?
(The blender's superior performance is on a par with its cost.)
- I want it. - It's expensive.
- It is. - Seriously?
Let's start off by grinding Suk Jin's navigation device.
(Let's find out how good it is.)
(What are you going to do to my GPS device?)
It can easily grind it.
(I can definitely do that.)
- Is that so? - Yes.
- You'll get brown-colored juice. - Let's grind...
This is full of memories.
Let's grind it first.
(Kwang Soo's introduction to his meaningful item is over...)
This was very expensive.
(right before Suk Jin's item gets mixed.)
And this is the item I want to get rid of.
(Kwang Soo reveals his throwaway item.)
Jong Kook and I traveled to the States before.
(It's an item he bought when he got sentimental...)
After having some drinks,
(after a drink with Jong Kook in the US.)
we became sentimental.
I bought this 300mm UGG boots then.
(It's 300mm UGG boots.)
These are fur boots.
Those are the worst.
(Is it an aircraft carrier?)
They look like ancient Joseon footwear.
- I just couldn't wear them here. - Why not?
(It's another useless item from the US.)
- What? - I wear them these days.
(Suk Jin is greedy.)
- But they're too big for me. - Try them on.
We should give them to Han Gi Beom.
(It's highly recommended for Ki Beom.)
Suk Jin loves these boots.
I love them.
(Kwang Soo's another throwaway item)
I brought something else.
I found this in my storage room.
What is that?
(They are curious.)
(Very dusty)
- What is that? - That looks familiar.
- It's a Halloween item. - It's a Halloween item.
(Jae Suk is happy to see an item from the same season.)
It looks familiar.
(That Ghost House seems very familiar.)
- What is that? - What could it be?
- Nine years ago, - Right?
Haha gifted this to me.
I knew it.
I remembered it.
Seriously?
(I remember it now.)
How was I able to remember that?
(It's an item that holds our memory from 9 years ago.)
- It's so dusty. - We were at your house that day.
- It was before you got married. - Right.
(They were hanging out at Haha's place.)
You told me...
to take whatever I needed from your house.
I picked a hat, but you said I couldn't have that.
Instead, you told me to take this.
(You can't take the hat.)
- You said this was a genuine gift. - Seriously?
(Haha gave him the useless item instead of a hat.)
- What's it for? - What do you do with that?
- I have no idea. - What's that for?
(Who cares?)
- I remembered. - I don't know what it's for.
(Then he forgot about it for the next 9 years.)
- It looked so familiar. - I think you lit a candle inside.
- You need to lit a candle inside. - I see.
(It's a lamp, and the candle should be put inside.)
I tossed this in the storage room nine years ago,
and I finally retrieved it today.
- It's the worst. - I had forgotten about this.
(It's the fruit of his selfishness that Haha meets after 9 years.)
Yes.
I feel bad for Haha but...
- How could you? - This was in your closet.
That haunted house is full of our memories!
That's why I couldn't throw it away.
- These could be a Halloween set. - You're right.
- Right. - Let's put them together.
(Halloween lamp and Halloween bucket must go together.)
We'll celebrate an early Halloween.
- Right. - It's a Halloween set.
It didn't look that nice on its own, but as a set,
(The two create synergy.)
- It looks nice, right? - it looks nice.
(It's a Halloween package.)
- You can hang it here. - They look nice.
All right.
(Meaningful item: Big blender)
I can totally remember that day.
(Throwaway item: UGG boots and Halloween package)
- You're right. - I'm feeling nostalgic.
- Who's up next? - It's me.
(Feeling sorrowful)
It's Se Chan's turn.
He's So Min's future boyfriend.
(So Min's future boyfriend will introduce his items.)
I'm talking in future tense. He'll become her boyfriend.
I think all of you will want this.
(It's an item that everyone would want.)
Did you have anyone specific in mind?
(Did Se Chan have anyone in mind?)
You wanted So Min to have yours.
(If So Min takes Haha's item,)
- I'd also like her to have this. - What is it?
(this item will go perfectly well together.)
They'd be a good collaboration.
- There are many items for her. - All right.
- What is it? - They'd be a good collaboration.
(What is this item that will work well with Haha's?)
- All right. - What is that?
It's a soda maker.
It's a soda maker. I'll give you the can of carbon dioxide as well.
(Sparkling water maker with carbon dioxide)
- It's a set. - That's really nice.
Put a glass of water here...
(Isn't it so easy, is it?)
- then press this. - It turns into a carbonated drink.
- The carbon dioxide enters it. - I know.
In what way is sparkling water good for you?
(Showing interest)
It has a kick.
(It has a kick.)
- The gas kicks your neck. - So Min,
it'll give your heart a kick.
(1st effect)
Love will surge from it.
(2nd effect)
Love will kick your heart.
(Two men are having fun making fun of Se Chan and So Min.)
Isn't this decent?
Yesterday, I asked Se Chan to join me for shaved ice...
(She asked Se Chan to join her for shaved ice yesterday.)
after church, but he just bolted.
- Right. - He ran away again.
(Se Chan's shy.)
He always does.
What a cold idiot.
(He's clueless when it comes to love.)
Unbelievable.
- She gave him an opportunity. - That idiot.
(They're frustrated.)
- Gosh. - I had no other choice.
(Se Chan couldn't take his chance.)
So Min officially made a move.
(They're upset.)
What's so hard about joining her for shaved ice?
(He draws a line.)
I was busy. All right then.
Here's the item I wish to discard. I received it as a gift recently,
(Here's the item Se Chan wishes to discard.)
and it's of a well-known brand.
(It's a well-known brand item from his acquaintance.)
However, I looked into it...
- and it was a fake. - Really?
(It turns out it was fake.)
And it was a fake.
(Someone gave him a replica.)
- Someone gave you an imitation? - It was a fake?
That's why...
Hey!
- Why? - You're throwing away our memory.
(The moment Kwang Soo sees it...)
- That's why... - Hey!
(Kick!)
(You'll throw away our memory?)
You're throwing away our memory.
- What is it? - Is it a memory?
Kwang Soo must've given it to Se Chan.
(It must be something Kwang Soo gave him.)
Is it a memory?
- It is. - Isn't that of...
(It's a replica speaker.)
- a famous brand? - It is.
- It's a speaker. - Isn't it a speaker?
- That's right. - It's a speaker.
Who on earth would give you an imitation?
(Pretending not to know)
- It's not. - It is.
- But... - You had no idea...
that this was an imitation of a well-known brand.
(Kwang Soo bought the speaker for Se Chan...)
I knew that, but...
(regardless of whether it is made by the real brand or an imitation.)
- It was just adorable. - I thought it'd suit him.
(How dare you throw away our memory?)
Still, how could you?
Once you hear how it sounds,
(Once you hear how it sounds,)
you'll understand why I want to give it up.
(you'll understand why I want to give it up.)
- Give us a demonstration. - Well...
(Unclear sounds)
(What's with the quality?)
Are we listening to a phone?
Are we hearing the speaker?
(Surprised)
Yes, the speaker. The music is coming from the speaker.
(Among the swaying flowers)
Did you turn on an LP record?
(The sound quality is worse than the speaker on a phone.)
- This... - Did you keep this underwater?
(It was always like this?)
The bass sound should be louder and clearer...
(You can smell my shampoo)
- Are the speakers wet? - Who knows?
(Is it just passing by)
No way.
What's wrong with this?
- It has an LP record option. - Beats me.
(The sound quality isn't good.)
It makes recent songs sound like oldies.
(It has an LP option that turns the latest songs into old songs.)
- You're right. - Right.
It sounded like Jang Beom June with a cold.
(The original singer)
The speaker comes with a stuffy nose option.
It sounded like Jang Beom June with a cold.
(The speaker has an LP option and a stuffy nose option.)
It'll sound incredible if you turn on old songs.
(A new way of thinking)
- Really? - Yes, old songs.
How much was this? Two dollars?
(Meaningful Item: Sparkling water maker, Throwaway Item: Speaker)
Still, someone might want it.
First, this is my meaningful gift.
(Next is Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook's meaningful gift is...)
I brought a massager.
(a massager.)
What's this?
It soothes any soreness you have and it can be used as a weapon.
(It's a massager, not a club.)
For a second,
(Scared)
I thought he was bringing out a weapon.
Your calves, thighs, and everywhere.
(You can rub anywhere with it.)
Even your backside.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Don't you use a massage gun powered by electricity?
(He's unbelievable.)
(Anyone can tell that a massage gun is better.)
But I use this too.
(He got caught.)
- I use this. - The massage gun.
How could you?
(The massage gun is better, but the manual one means more to him.)
- That's too loud though. - It requires manual labor.
- That's too loud. - You use a massage gun.
(Both Yu San Seul's CD and a massager are not that useful.)
- But this is better. - That feels good.
Unbelievable. So what's the next gift?
(There isn't much difference.)
I really want to throw this away.
(Next is the item Jong Kook wants to discard.)
- What is it? - I don't know what to do with it.
(What's that?)
I should've gotten rid of it back then.
- But back then... - Exactly.
How could you?
(He can't believe his eyes.)
Are you kidding me?
Yes, this.
It's a life-size cutout of Cristiano Ronaldo.
(A life-size cutout of Cristiano Ronaldo)
- Hold on. - Are you sure about this?
Can we air this on TV?
(Can this be on TV?)
- Well... - What can we do?
Please blur out his face.
He was supposed to visit my house for "Mom's Diary,"
(He's blurred.)
so I prepared this to make the event memorable.
(He was supposed to visit Jong Kook's house.)
- That's right. - But now...
(He became the most hated man.)
- he's the most hated man. - The whole nation hates him.
I don't want to leave it in my house anymore.
(Jong Kook doesn't know what to do with his cutout.)
I need to throw this away, but I haven't had the chance.
I can understand your trouble.
That's something...
(Astonished)
- I don't want it. - I don't want that at all.
- On your way home... - Gosh.
(They'd rather reject it even if they get 370 dollars.)
His and Haha's gifts are the worst.
Mine's perfectly fine.
(The 2 worst items)
It'll come with an autograph.
(Haha and Jong Kook's cutout is way better.)
Jong Kook's second gift is the worst of them all.
(Meaningful Item: Massager, Throwaway item: Cutout of Ronarldo)
It's really something he wishes to get rid of.
So you've all brought your gifts today.
(Where are these gifts going to be used?)
We asked you to bring them over...
to celebrate Suk Jin's birthday and the release of So Min's book.
(Suk Jin's birthday)
(Release of So Min's book)
It's the Double Celebration Race.
(Double Celebration Race)
Is it your birthday?
(He didn't understand it.)
What about my birthday?
It's your birthday.
(Don't you know what birthday is?)
Suk Jin, pull yourself together!
This must air around the time of my birthday.
(Tomorrow, February 10, is Suk Jin's birthday.)
- Happy birthday. - We asked you...
to prepare these gifts today...
(The real purpose of gifts they brought)
(To celebrate Suk Jin's birthday...)
so that we can celebrate Suk Jin's birthday...
(and So Min's debut as a writer)
and So Min's debut as a writer.
Writer Jeon! Goodness.
(The writer says hello.)
This is amazing.
(She became a real writer from a crazy poet.)
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
- Writer Jeon! - It's embarrassing.
- Gosh. - We also prepared a gift.
(Here's the gift from the crew for double celebration.)
- Really? - You guys prepared a gift?
(They can't believe that the crew prepared a gift.)
Really? There's a gift?
- No way. - What?
(Turbo's happy birthday song is played.)
(Expensive cake is prepared.)
My gosh.
- Goodness. - You're embarrassing us.
This embarrasses me, you know.
Gosh.
(Congratulations on becoming a writer. Happy 55th birthday.)
Stand in the center.
(He said it embarrasses him, but he puts on the cone hat.)
Look at this.
- Gosh. - They used honorifics.
(He's old enough to deserve honorifics.)
"Happy 55th birthday".
All right, Writer Jeon.
- "You Can Call Me..." - "After a Drink".
(So Min published the feelings she wrote down for a long time.)
I'm proud of her.
You heard that, right?
"You Can Call Me After a Drink".
A candle went out.
(Quietly)
- Right. - I guess I can call her.
A candle went out.
It feels like my life has just faded away.
Your life?
- What? - It's a birthday cake.
(Candle. You remind me of myself.)
A gush of wind blew, that's all.
- Wait, this went out too. - The other one...
(The last candle is about to go out too.)
- What? - It's back to normal again.
No!
(The other candle withered like Suk Jin's feeble legs.)
- What? - It's back to normal again.
No!
(Say goodbye to his life)
(Happy 55th birthday)
What's happening?
No!
(He identifies himself as the candle flames.)
The wick dropped completely.
Like this?
(The drooped wick has many meanings.)
- The wick... - Just like his chin drops.
- I mean... - I've never seen that happen.
- I'm perfectly fine, you know. - Just look at it.
(Denying)
- All right. - This is slightly embarrassing,
(A speech from Suk Jin)
but thank you so much.
(Thank you for celebrating my birthday.)
- Blow out the candles. - Happy birthday.
(We wish So Min and Suk Jin the best.)
- 1, 2, 3. - So Min, go ahead.
Congratulations!
This seems out of the blue though.
(Suddenly feeling anxious)
Tell me about it.
You will compete in two teams today.
(They will be divided into Team So Min and Team Suk Jin.)
So Min and Suk Jin will be team captains.
(They're team captains.)
Through the games prepared today,
(They can win gifts through a mission.)
So Min and Suk Jin will win gifts after each round.
(The team to win 2 rounds first will be the final winner.)
You will compete in three rounds...
and the team to win two rounds first will be the final winner.
(The winning team captain will be given two choices.)
The winning team captain...
(The captain can choose to obtain all the meaningful gifts.)
will win a chance to obtain all the meaningful gifts.
- That's nice. - They're in for a treat.
(The winning team captain will be lucky.)
Or, they will win a chance to choose between two curtains...
(Choose between a 100-inch TV or a dud behind the curtains.)
where one conceals a dud and the other one...
(Dud, latest 100-inch TV)
conceals a 100-inch TV that's worth 8,000 dollars.
(Will the winner get gifts from the members...)
- A 100-inch TV? - Really?
- That's worth 8,000 dollars? - You can choose...
(or get the 100-inch TV with a 50 percent chance?)
between two options.
A 100-inch TV that's worth 8,000 dollars...
(Their eyes open wide.)
- 8,000 dollars? - A 100-inch TV?
(If the captain chooses the dud, they will obtain one of the wastes.)
- A 100-inch TV? - No way!
The wall in your house isn't even 100 inches long.
It isn't.
If you don't want the TV,
(If TV is too much, the captain may swap it...)
you may swap it for a gift certificate of 8,000 dollars.
(for a gift certificate of 8,000 dollars.)
- A gift certificate? - My gosh.
- Then it's truly a gift. - All right.
(If the captain chooses the gifts that the members brought,)
If you choose the gifts that the members brought,
your teammates will all receive a prize badge.
(the teammates will all receive a prize badge.)
If you choose to gamble on the TV,
they will only win a prize badge...
(If the captain chooses to gamble on the TV,)
if you successfully choose the TV.
(they will only win a prize badge...)
- All our teammates. - Hold on.
(if the captain successfully chooses the TV.)
Isn't this the most expensive prize we've been offered?
(It's the most expensive prize that has ever been offered.)
That's right.
However, there's only a 50 percent chance.
You can easily choose the dud.
(Feeling competitive)
I really want to win today.
It'll be upsetting if the captain doesn't choose our gifts though.
(If the team captains are being greedy,)
I know.
(they could risk their teammates' chances too.)
The member with the fewest number of badges...
(The member with the fewest number of badges...)
will receive a penalty at the end.
(will receive a penalty at the end.)
Before we begin the race,
(They'll choose their team members.)
you two will choose your teams.
- Okay. - How will it be done?
(They'll play rock-paper-scissors.)
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Good.
- You'll choose your teammates. - We have to win for them.
(They're getting gifts their teammates brought.)
It'll be their gifts you'll be playing for.
(It's important to consider what their teammates brought.)
But the TV is too good not to gamble on.
- You'll have to win. - Exactly.
It's impossible for me to lose to Suk Jin.
(Feeling confident)
Don't be ridiculous.
(It's about the weakest members' pride.)
- Oh, please. - Come on.
(So how will the rock-paper-scissors go?)
Rock-paper-scissors!
(So Min wins.)
(He truly is the weakest Running Man member.)
Hold on a second. Which gift was the best?
If I had known, I would've brought a better gift.
(Who will So Min choose?)
Exactly. If only we knew in advance.
- Right. - Okay.
I choose the sparkling water maker.
(She first chooses the sparkling water maker.)
(So Min first chooses Se Chan who brought the sparkling water maker.)
I choose the sparkling water maker.
- All right. - Of course.
(Old men are getting excited again.)
The two youngest are on the same team again.
First of all...
It's the sparkling water I like, not Se Chan.
(Giving excuses)
- We get it! - We hear you.
(Happy)
I really need it.
(I really need sparkling water.)
Okay, fine.
Can't you take the calendar instead?
(Interrupting)
I want the sparkling water maker too.
(Suk Jin gets greedy.)
- Seriously? - Suk Jin...
(Don't be greedy.)
But I won. Wait, hold on.
- What is it? - Is this gray hair?
- What? - Let me see.
He'll die if you pluck that out.
(Don't do that.)
Won't he?
- It's not hair, is it? I'm glad. - Suk Jin,
- is that a udumbara flower? - I'm glad it's not hair.
- Udumbara? - What's a udumbara?
(Udumbara flower is an imaginary flower in Buddhism.)
- No way. - I thought of a goat.
(They've picked the teammates.)
Anyway, they're the weakest links.
(Team So Min: So Min, Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Se Chan)
I can't believe this.
(Team Suk Jin: Suk Jin, Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Haha)
The gifts are the worst too.
(Getting nervous already)
You never know though.
So you now have your teams.
You'll change clothes and begin the race.
(The race will start now.)
- Got it. - Okay.
- All right. - Today,
(Captain Jeon says...)
my teammates agreed to be considered as the same age.
(their teammates will drop honorifics.)
- Jong Kook, Kwang Soo... - There's something...
(So Min adds her rules in Running Man rules.)
called the Jeon So Min Rule.
- Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Se Chan... - What?
(He's never heard of it.)
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
(They become friends unexpectedly.)
I love calling just your names.
Just like the members of AOA,
(Team Suk Jin will call each other by name like AOA members do.)
- we'll stick to just the names. - Sounds good.
- Then can we... - Can I call you Kook?
- Of course. - Kook!
- Kook. - Kook.
- Look at him. - Just so you know,
friends get into fights while growing up.
What?
(Scared)
So Min, say that we can't argue or fight.
You see, it's mean to hit someone younger than you,
but it's okay to beat up your friends.
- Of course. - That's how...
(Jong Kook's friends are worried.)
we grow up and build our friendship.
- I'm sure you're all hungry. - Yes!
(All together)
The first game you'll be competing in...
is Name the Dish.
(The First Mission: Name the Dish)
- Name the Dish? - That's right.
You'll be given 100 minutes.
(Within 100 minutes of time limit,)
Among the dishes sold in Seoul,
(the team that finds the dish...)
find the dish with the longest name to win.
(with the longest name in Seoul wins.)
What is this?
Only the actual name on the menu counts.
(The number of letters on the menu will only be counted.)
If the other team finds a dish that has a longer name than you did,
(If the opposing team eats a dish that has a longer name,)
you'll get to try again within the given time.
(you're allowed to try again within the time limit.)
Does a set menu count?
- As long as it's on the menu. - Of course.
(It doesn't matter as long as it's on the menu.)
Does "something and something" count?
- That counts too. - It does?
(If it's on the menu, it's allowed.)
But you can only order...
one portion.
(They must order 1 serving only,)
The member who eats the dish wins a prize badge...
(and the person to eat the dish...)
regardless of the result.
(will be given a prize badge regardless of the result.)
We have to compete against each other.
(They must compete within the team to choose who will eat.)
- We compete against each other? - We compete against each other?
Only one member gets to eat.
Then it's a good thing that we're all weak.
(It's advantageous for me.)
- It's a good thing. - In that case,
(The weak are deeply satisfied.)
- we're lucky. - We have an advantage.
- It's not bad. - I mean...
(Joy and sorrow)
I have a chance.
You should have told us beforehand.
(So Min is upset.)
- You guys are so unlucky. - It's war.
(Jong Kook's teammates are depressed.)
Hey.
- You picked the wrong guys. - So Min is so unlucky.
(The worst team combination with Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan)
If I had known...
I love my team.
(The weaklings)
We can just pick one randomly.
(Don't worry, So Min.)
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - All right.
(They'll find their own way to choose who will eat.)
You can decide how you pick one member.
Please get on the cars now.
(I think I picked the wrong teammates.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - What should we have?
(All teams are on their vechicles.)
"A dish with a long name".
(They start searching the Internet right away.)
It's an Italian restaurant.
(She finds something right away.)
"Red wine oxtail stew and creamy barley risotto".
- That's perfect. - Where is that place?
(It's 17 letters!)
- Let's go there! - Hold on.
- Let me see. - Ji Hyo did it!
- I have to see where it is. - How many letters are there?
(Wait.)
"Red wine..."
It's in another country.
Gosh.
(What were we getting excited for?)
We can go there as long as we have a GPS.
(Don't worry.)
- Hey. - Get a GPS.
There are many restaurants like this in Itaewon.
(They can go anywhere in the US with Suk Jin's GPS device.)
- Hey, Suk Jin. - What?
(Haha found another menu.)
"Their dishes not only have long names but also taste amazing".
"Woo Seul's restorative chicken..."
"with abalone, mitten crabs, and small octopus".
- That's the place! - Hold on.
- Let's go there. - Where is that place?
(The name of the dish has 16 letters.)
- It's in Iksan. Gosh. - That's too far.
(North Jeolla Province)
That would have been perfect.
(Ji Hyo is counting something.)
- I found 16 letters. - Where is it?
(I found it.)
"Burgundy wine-marinated beef stew".
- Let's go there. - Where is it?
- It's in Itaewon. Hold on. - Let's go.
(In the same restaurant that Ji Hyo found,)
- There are even longer names. - They have really long names.
(they find a dish with a longer name.)
"Roasted pork tenderloin served with mustard sauce..."
"and grilled eggplants".
It has 22 letters.
- Unbelievable. - Unbelievable.
(It's 22 letters.)
- Ji Hyo! - It's not bad, right?
(The best at searching)
You did it!
Ji Hyo, good job. We have two masters...
(Thanks to Haha and Ji Hyo on Team Suk Jin,)
of Internet searching.
(they take off to find a dish with a 22-letter-long name.)
All right. I'll try searching the Internet.
(Meanwhile, they haven't even departed yet.)
(The four members of the thumb tribe)
Hold on. 1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
(The youngest member of the thumb tribe found something.)
- 11, 12, 13, 14... It's 17 letters. - What?
- It's 17 letters. - Can you find that?
- What is it called? - Hey.
"Wings marinated in Analog Kitchen's special soy sauce".
- Is that the name? - That's the name.
(But they don't know what Team Suk Jin has found.)
- Is it in Itaewon? - Yes, it is. It's not bad, right?
- I can't find anything. - Should we look some more?
(So they decide to keep looking.)
Let's look some more on our way.
(Searching)
Hey.
"The American mom's..."
"Beef meatballs and French fries made by American mom".
- Unbelievable. - Where is it?
- Where is that place? - The "American mom"?
(American mom)
It says, the "American mom".
Not the Korean mom, but the American mom?
- The "American mom"? - That's right.
Where is the place? It sounds nice.
(An American mom in Yeonnam-dong)
It's near Hongik University. It's in Yeonnam-dong.
Guys, let me tell you what we'll have.
(They find a dish...)
It's 18 letters.
(with a 18-letter-long name in the same restaurant.)
"Carbonara with rich cream sauce that fills your mouth".
- That sounds good. - I'm sure it tastes good too.
(The American mom can also cook carbonara.)
- Nice! - Nice!
- I finally found something. - Good job.
(Flattering)
- You did a good job. - Se Chan, you're the best.
(Complimenting Se Chan)
While Kwang Soo was checking his messages,
- I've been searching the Internet. - I can't find anything.
(He takes credit to himself for his achievement.)
I've been searching, but I can't find anything.
I found something.
(But...)
"Flavorful beef cream sauce risotto served with ginkgo nuts,"
"bell peppers, and mushrooms with a touch of lemon".
- How many letters is that? - Kim Jong Kook!
(All hail Jong Kook!)
- Kim Jong Kook! - Kim Jong Kook!
(It has 28 letters.)
- Where is it? - It's in Itaewon.
- Can you call them? It's closer. - It's in Itaewon.
(It's even closer than Yeonnam-dong.)
- It's even closer. - It's even closer.
- Hey. - Why couldn't you find this?
(Blaming)
Hey, what are you doing?
(Blaming too)
- You're useless. - I'm sorry.
(Tossed out into the cold all of a sudden)
Try calling them.
- Hold on. - It has more than 20 letters.
(Wait.)
(Getting proud)
- What? - What?
It's closed on Mondays.
(They shoot on Monday.)
- What? - Really?
Many restaurants in Itaewon are closed on Mondays.
- Yang Se Chan! - Yang Se Chan!
(All hail Se Chan!)
- Yang... - Seriously?
(Conceited)
I can't believe this.
(Instead of the dish with a 28-letter-long name...)
- Are they really closed? - They're closed on every Monday.
(that Jong Kook found,)
Please go to the previous place.
(they're going to the place Se Chan found in Yeonnam-dong.)
Yes. Jong Kook!
Okay.
That's so cute. "Okay".
(It's a good example of being muscular and cute.)
- Okay. - Jong Kook!
- "Okay. I admit it". - Jong Kook, you're so cute.
- Jong Kook! - Okay.
- You should work harder. - Okay.
(Let me try.)
Try it. You're so cute.
(They're all acting cute.)
- Okay. - Okay.
That's so cute.
(Cute)
I love everything that's cute.
(What's wrong with them?)
I respect everyone who's cute.
- What are you doing? - He's so stubborn.
(So Min thinks if you're not acting cute, you're younger.)
- I'm not good at it. - Kwang Soo.
Are you okay with Se Chan being rude to you?
Have you guys ever been polite to me?
(Irritated)
(Kwang Soo was born in 1985,)
Have you?
- They've never been polite. - Kwang Soo.
(Se Chan and So Min were born in 1986.)
Have you ever treated me with respect?
(Sad)
- Don't be like that. - Kwang Soo.
(Calm down, Soo.)
- Come on, you're good at this. - Right.
(Acting cute is difficult.)
- Do it just once. - Right.
He's so stubborn.
We've been begging him.
- Is it so hard to say, "Okay"? - Why is it so hard?
(Jong Kook joins them.)
Okay.
(Kwang Soo can be so cute in front of Jong Kook.)
Good job.
We're Team Okay now.
(The cute Team Okay is formed.)
We're Team Okay.
(Team Suk Jin goes to Itaewon, and Team So Min goes to Yeonnam-dong.)
I should take my wife to places like this.
(Abruptly)
- He's lying. - I know.
It's just something he says on camera.
(He pretends to be a good husband on camera.)
I'd tell her when and where we should meet.
And she'd wonder what's going on.
(Pretending)
He's lying.
We'd eat together.
We'd have steaks.
When Suk Jin says he'd do something,
(Jae Suk gives testimony.)
he never actually does it.
(Embarrassed)
I shouldn't have worn long johns.
- Did you think it'd be cold? - I took mine off.
I never wear long johns.
(Acting tough)
You did the other day.
It was exceptionally cold that day.
Why would you lie?
(So you wore them.)
I rarely wear them.
- I think we're here. - We are?
(They arrive at the restaurant.)
Good that we're here.
Otherwise, Suk Jin would have needed a special investigation.
(It looks like he is appearing before the prosecution.)
Where is it?
(They arrive at the restaurant that Ji Hyo found.)
- I think this is it. - This is it.
Can we shoot here for a minute?
(Excuse me.)
We're going to eat.
- Is that okay? - It won't take long.
(Asking for the owner's cooperation as it was a sudden visit)
Can we see a menu, please?
(Fortunately, the owner consents.)
We want the dish with the longest name.
- The dish with the longest name. - Here it is.
(They find the menu.)
- Let's see. - We came to the right place.
- Nice. - It smells so good too.
(They check if they have a dish with a 22-letter-long name first.)
- The food looks so good. - This is nice.
- Hold on. This is even longer. - What is it?
(But...)
But it's sold out.
(Sold out)
It's already sold out?
(We came all the way to taste this dish.)
- Truffle... - It runs out fast.
(They're out of ingredients.)
It must be going well for you.
I'll come back with my wife later.
(He doesn't mean it.)
(He's lying again.)
He's definitely not coming.
(Was it that obvious?)
Do you see that?
(Suk Jin is a celebrity for show.)
Suk Jin is embarrassed.
I can totally tell what he's thinking.
(Embarrassed)
Only the names on the menu count.
(The one on the menu will only be accepted.)
Can we order this?
"Roasted pork tenderloin served with mustard sauce..."
"and grilled eggplants".
- Can we order this? - Yes, you can.
(They find an available dish above the sold out dish.)
- Is that all you need? - Yes, please.
It has 22 letters.
(This one also has 22 letters.)
"Roasted..." It has 22 letters.
Please decide who is going to eat.
(It's time to choose who will eat the dish.)
- What should we do? - Well...
(Thinking)
How about...
we ask someone passing by...
who should eat...
(Asking)
among us?
That's not okay. It's unfair.
(They object as it's too favorable for Jae Suk.)
You have an advantage over us.
They'll pick you.
How about this?
- We'll all be assigned a number. - Right.
- Let's do that. - That sounds good.
(It's a deal.)
- Number 1, number 2... - That should work, right?
- What number do you want? - I want number one.
- No. I want number 2. - Number 2? I want number 3.
(Number 2, Ji Hyo)
(Number 3, Suk Jin)
- I'll be number 1. - I'll be number 4.
(Number 1, Jae Suk, and number 4, Haha)
Number three is nice.
We'll ask someone on the street.
(One of the production crew will go and ask a passer-by.)
- Just one person. - Just one person.
- Number 3 is nice. - When there are 4 options,
(Please say number 3.)
- people would choose number 3. - All Koreans choose number 3.
Each of the four is assigned...
(Asking randomly)
a number between 1 and 4.
Can you choose a number between 1 and 4?
(What number will the passer-by choose?)
To be honest, if we weren't shooting,
(They're chatting while waiting for the food they ordered.)
we could have come here with some friends...
(The owner brings water.)
- That would be really nice. - and eat together.
That sounds so nice.
(Suk Jin feels thirsty and pours himself a glass of water.)
(Staring)
(Suk Jin, the oldest member, fills his own glass first.)
That does sound nice.
(He puts the bottle back on the table...)
Aren't you going to fill our glasses?
That does sound nice.
(after filling his own glass.)
Aren't you going to fill our glasses?
- I was watching him. - Gosh.
(There's a proper order for everything according to their ages.)
(No, there's only proper order for me.)
- I knew it. - Unbelievable.
I knew what he'd do.
I'm okay with him filling his own glass first,
(Dumbfounded)
- but I thought he'd fill ours too. - I thought the same.
I was watching him.
(They were staring at him,)
I couldn't believe what I saw.
(and they hoped not.)
- I'm sorry. - He can fill his own glass first,
(He never falls short of their expectations.)
but he should fill the others' glasses too.
(Disappointed)
- I couldn't believe it. - You're the worst.
I'm disappointed.
I had no idea.
(I'm sorry, I was too thirsty.)
Here comes our food.
(Their food is served.)
- It looks delicious. - What's this?
(Mouth-watering)
- It's pork tenderloin. - It's pork tenderloin.
It looks fantastic.
Let me just try slicing it.
(Sous-vide pork tenderloin)
- Oh, my. - Was this cooked sous-vide?
(Sous-vide is a method of cooking in which it's cooked...)
Let me explain.
(in a water bath at consistent temperature.)
It's cooked at low temperature...
(It preserves the taste and scent, and the meat gets very tender.)
- for longer than 10 hours. - That's right.
Is that correct?
(It must be very delicious.)
Is the result out yet?
Please tell us.
(The passer-by has chosen.)
The person who gets to eat the roasted pork tenderloin...
served with mustard sauce and grilled eggplants is...
(The member to eat the dish and get the prize badge is...)
Please.
(Nervous)
- I'm nervous. - I'm so nervous.
(I want to eat it so badly.)
This is driving me crazy.
- Number 3. - Number 2, please.
(Between 1 and 4, what number did the passer-by choose?)
Congratulations, number one.
(Number 1 is Jae Suk.)
- Number one. - Okay. Thank you.
(The passer-by chose Number 1.)
No way.
(Devastated)
(Thank you for your time.)
I can't believe this. Number one?
(Jae Suk gets to eat the roasted pork tenderloin.)
- No way. - Unbelievable. Number one?
(Jealous)
I'll try it.
(He tries a big piece.)
- Does it taste good? - It tastes amazing.
(It's very delicious.)
- How does it taste? - It tastes like a sausage, right?
(I know what it tastes like.)
Does it taste like a sausage?
- You know how it tastes? - I do.
(It's a fantastic combination...)
- It tastes amazing. - I love it.
(of the juicy sausage and the mustard sauce.)
It's delicious.
- It looks so good. - Are you going to eat all of that?
We'll play rock-paper-scissors. Give one piece to the winner.
(Suggesting)
- Jae Suk. - Just one piece.
Rock-paper-scissors is boring.
Do a talent show.
- A talent show? - It tastes fantastic.
(What should I do?)
I'll improvise a song about mashed potatoes.
(Suk Jin will try first.)
That sounds good.
("Mashed Potato" written on the spot)
Let's eat mashed potatoes
Mashed, mashed potatoes
(Jae Suk doesn't look impressed.)
Tasty, soft mashed potatoes
It goes perfectly with pork tenderloin
It's French cuisine
(The lyrics are catchy and addictive.)
It's served with eggplants, mashed potatoes, and pork tenderloin
Please give me a bite, ooh
(Please give me a bite)
(Ooh)
(He ends the song in a seductive way.)
That wasn't half bad.
(Suk Jin is happy with himself.)
Gosh, Suk Jin.
(Haha, you should just have a bite.)
- Thank you. - My goodness.
Hey.
(Haha gladly accepts it.)
- You should just eat it. - Hey.
- You should just eat it. - Does it taste good?
(The piece of meat goes to the father of three children, Haha.)
- You should just eat it. - My goodness.
You should just eat it.
Jae Suk completed the dish, so he gets a prize badge.
(Jae Suk has finished the dish.)
(He earns the prize badge.)
With 22 letters, you currently hold the record.
(With 22 letters,)
(Jae Suk holds the record.)
- Currently? - Yes.
(They go to find a dish with a longer name.)
Let's hit the road again.
That was tasty.
- We are here. - This is the place.
(Team So Min arrives to eat a dish with a 18-letter-long name.)
- Let's hurry up and eat. - Let's go.
(They won't know what the other team ate until they finish.)
- All right. Let's go. - Let's go.
- Okay. - It's a matter of who eats it.
Jong Kook, there is a dish with a longer name.
(Longer than 18 letters...)
Cream-Sauce Pasta with a Whole Crab and Popping Flying Fish Roe.
- Paprika... - This is legit.
(They find a 19-letter-long name.)
- My goodness. - How many letters are there?
- 19 letters. - 19 letters.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 19...
(Why does 19 come after 16?)
- 17, 18, 19. - 17.
(Se Chan, 17 comes after 16.)
- 15, 16, 19... - 17.
(Dumbfounded)
What am I supposed to do with you if you can't even count?
- You can't count. - I got nervous.
(It's an unreasonable excuse.)
- Which name is longer? - Let's go in. There must be more.
(You can't say that 19 comes after 16.)
- Hello. Would it be okay... - Hello.
Would it be okay if we have a shoot at a corner?
(They carefully ask for cooperation.)
- It won't take long. - Thank you.
(They gladly approve.)
- Thank you. - Let's go in.
- This is the place. - Let's go.
(They start to read the menu.)
There is a dish with a name that contains 19 letters.
(My goodness!)
- 2, 4, 6, 8, 10... - Cream Pasta...
- Hold on. 12, 14, 16, 18... - Cream Pasta with Salted...
(While they were reading the menu, they discovered...)
- 22, 24, - My goodness.
26, 27!
(a dish with a 27-letter-long name!)
This is incredible.
We will surely win.
(It'll be hard to find a dish name that goes longer than 27 letters.)
Please decide which member will eat.
(They now have to pick who gets to eat.)
Shall we point to and eliminate one member?
(If that's the case...)
Let's play Go Away.
(They decide to eliminate 1 out of 4 by pointing.)
- Okay. - Go Away.
(That sounds good.)
Go Away.
- Point to one member. 1, 2... - 1, 2...
(Who will be eliminated first?)
- Three. - Go away.
(Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and So Min choose Jong Kook.)
What? Three.
- Go away. - What?
(He gets all the votes.)
(All three of them chose Jong Kook as if they planned it.)
Jong Kook.
- When I wasn't looking... - Jong Kook, I am sorry.
- No. - Jong Kook, I am sorry.
(He even tried to act cute.)
Why weren't you looking?
Okay.
(How did this happen?)
(You need to choose Jong Kook.)
Let's play Go Away.
(When Jong Kook was looking away)
(Tapping)
Let's play Go Away.
Go Away.
(You need to choose Jong Kook.)
- One person gets to eat, right? - That's right.
(It's So Min's scheme.)
- Okay. - Let's do this.
(Let's do this.)
Let's play the game Jong Kook suggests.
Okay. We will play the game you suggest.
(Okay.)
Do you know me?
Jong Kook.
(This is bad.)
- This is... - You have nothing to do with me.
(Jong Kook is upset.)
- This is the beginning. - It's okay.
(They messed with the sleeping tiger.)
Suit yourself.
Jong Kook, this is the beginning.
Are you going to ignore us?
I am going to have my own show.
- I will hold the camera. - No.
(It's a one-person broadcast by Jong Kook who is left alone.)
I am going to use Instagram Live.
(Jong Kook TV)
- Jong Kook. - It's okay. I am fine.
(I will get revenge on you guys.)
That was delicious.
(Team Suk Jin enjoyed the dish with a 22-letter-long name.)
- Everyone. - Yes?
(They are convinced that they won.)
You found a dish with 22 letters and only Jae Suk got a badge.
- Yes. - Yes.
The other team is eating a dish that's 27 letters long.
What?
(Is there a dish with a 27-letter-long name?)
How does it have 27 letters?
- How is it possible? - Really? 27 letters?
- What happens now? - You hit the road again.
(There are only 50 minutes left.)
(They must find a dish name that is longer than 27 letters.)
- We need to find another dish. - That's right.
Let's surf the Web again.
(We need to find it quickly.)
I don't think we will find a longer name.
Why don't we draw lots?
(Team So Min is still deciding on the game.)
Let's ask the owner to choose one.
When the dish gets served, we won't say anything.
(The one who is closest to the dish will be eliminated.)
The person who is closest to it gets eliminated.
- It's a good idea. - What do you think?
(Jong Kook is interested.)
The person who is closest to it gets eliminated.
- Let me answer a call from Haha. - You are getting a call.
(Se Chan gets a call from Haha.)
- Haha. - Which restaurant did you visit...
(Where did you guys go?)
to find a dish with 27 letters?
- Hold on. Hold on. - Hold on.
(At that moment...)
Hold on.
(The food is served.)
Hey.
(The one who is closest to the dish will be eliminated.)
The one who is closest to the dish will be eliminated.
Se Chan.
(The food is placed in front of Se Chan.)
(Se Chan, enjoy the dish.)
- Se Chan. - Yes?
(Yang Se Chan is eliminated.)
I hear you giggling with your girlfriend.
(Are you having fun?)
I think...
- you need a scolding. - Jae Suk.
(I am not in the mood.)
Jae Suk, I am done.
(Se Chan moves next to Jong Kook.)
You found a dish with 27 letters.
Do I know you?
(Anyang Loser isn't through with them.)
Sit here.
I am sorry,
but I don't want to share a table with a stranger.
(Docile)
There are other tables.
What?
Jong Kook is being the Anyang Loser. This is suffocating.
You just sat next to me.
(Who is he?)
(Se Chan lost the badge and Jong Kook.)
Okay. I am hanging up.
Okay, Jae Suk. See you later.
One person can eat, right?
(The final winner...)
- The one with a longer noodle... - The one with a longer noodle wins.
(will be determined by the length of the noodle.)
Okay.
(Writer Jeon carefully picks out noodle.)
- You picked one. Lift it up. - Okay.
(Pulling)
- It's long. - What? Is it buried underneath?
- It's long. - What is going on?
(It's really long!)
It's pretty long.
- It's long. - That's good.
(I am done for.)
- It's long. - Kwang Soo, it's your turn.
I don't know what they are doing, but it looks fun.
(They are having fun.)
- Yes. - It looks fun.
(Anyang Loser abruptly starts to act.)
I used to have fun with them.
- You can't change once you pick. - The noodles go deep.
(Kwang Soo's choice will determine the winner of the badge.)
- You can't change once you pick. - You know,
they are covered with cheese and cream.
You can only pick one.
(After much deliberation, Kwang Soo picks noddle.)
You are done.
It's this one. Please let it short.
(Very careful)
It's over if it breaks.
(Please!)
Please let it be short.
(What?)
(Is that it?)
(It's obvious that So Min won.)
(Kwang Soo, come here.)
Kwang Soo, come here.
Look at this. Yours is ridiculous.
(Goodness.)
You are done.
(So Min gets Cream Pasta with Salted Pollack Roe and Bacon.)
The dish is mine.
Come here.
(Satisfied)
(That looks really good just like the name suggests.)
- So Min, do you taste... - It looks delicious.
- all the ingredients... - It looks delicious.
(The food quality is on a par with the length of the name.)
in the name?
Yes. It's tasty, but there is a lot. I wish I could share.
(So Min gets to have both the food and the badge.)
It contains salted pollack roe, right?
- Yes, it does. - Salted pollack roe and cream.
I see.
You know,
(Team Suk Jin goes to find another food.)
it's hard to find a dish that's 28 letters long.
(They need to find a dish with a name...)
I can only find one that's 25 letters long.
(that is longer than 28 letters.)
Why are they so good at finding things?
This is bad.
- Jae Suk! - Let's surf the Web.
- What? - Jae Suk!
(When everyone is about to give up,)
- Let's surf the Web. - What?
(Haha finds something.)
- Hold on. - What?
- This one has 45 letters. - What?
(45 letters?)
- 45 letters? - Really?
(They check to see if it's true.)
Look.
(Then they all start to laugh.)
It actually exists. I can't believe it.
(My gosh)
This is unbelievable.
- Let's go. - It's bibim guksu.
- Bibim guksu has... - Bibim naengmyeon.
(Haha found a bibim naengmyeon with a name that is 45 letters long.)
- Let's go. - This is unbelievable.
- This is... - This is unbelievable.
(This is unbelievable!)
- This is incredible. - It actually exists.
I bet the production crew didn't expect this.
(They are confident after finding a 45-letter-long dish name.)
You can't beat...
- 45 letters. - Are they on the road again?
(While they're moving to the restaurant, Team So Min...)
- I think she is done. - That's good.
She ate with gusto.
(So Min enjoys the food all by herself with 30 minutes left.)
- She ate everything. - I know.
So Min's team succeeded to clear a dish...
(Team So Min finished having food with a 27-letter-long name.)
that's 27 letters long.
That's what matters.
We should hit the road again.
(Since we have 30 minutes, should we look for another dish?)
I don't think we should search on the street.
- Jong Kook. - What?
Sweet Melon, Parmesan, Prosciutto That Has Been Cured...
- for 24 Months, and... - And...
- Buffalo Mozzarella. - Okay.
- 30... 31 letters. - 31 letters.
(31 letters?)
Is that the name?
- Are you sure it's the name? - Hold on.
(They can't hear her.)
- It's the name. - This is the English name.
(Excuse me)
- This is the English name. - It's the name.
(Whispering)
- It's the name. - What is this dish?
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo join Anyang Loser.)
- A pizza? - Are you sure it's the name?
It's on the menu.
Are you sure it's the name?
(Can't you see me?)
The English name is...
They translated it into Korean.
(This is crazy.)
- You are right. - This is driving me crazy.
It's the name.
(Being a captain feels especially lonely today.)
- Where is the restaurant? - Where is it?
It's in Hongdae.
(Team So Min heads to try food with a 31-letter-long name nearby.)
- Hongdae? - It's near.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Shall we play rock-paper-scissors this time?
(They have to decide again on who gets to eat.)
So Min can choose...
a member to eliminate just like she did the last time.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
That's funny because it wasn't me.
(I did not plan it.)
- It wasn't me. - Listen.
- Even if someone else suggested it, - That's right.
the team captain makes the final decision.
- That's her responsibility. - That's the weight of her position.
(He's being annoying.)
"One who wears the crown must bear its weight."
That's her responsibility.
- I can tell that you are a writer. - Stop it.
Stop it.
- I am sorry, but it's a saying. - It's a saying.
(Don't you know the phrase?)
- It's a famous saying. - It's a saying.
(Since when?)
Is it a saying?
(He memorizes anything that sounds cool.)
"Must bear its weight."
Shall we play fair this time?
(Anyang Loser is now gone.)
- Okay. - Jong Kook isn't sullen anymore.
- That's good. - Shall we start anew...
(Everyone, clap to celebrate that Anyang Loser is now gone.)
- with a round of applause? - Okay.
Let's start anew with a round of applause.
(They start to shoot anew as if everything has been reset.)
Let's start anew. Let's clap the slate. 1, 2, 3.
This is good.
(It's hard to be the team captain.)
(Team Suk Jin arrives to try a dish with a 45-letter-long name.)
This is a familiar neighborhood.
(with 15 minutes left.)
We are in Hongdae.
(This looks very familiar.)
We will get off as soon as we turn left.
(Haha seems to know how to get there.)
It just needs to be on the menu.
- That's right. - It just needs to be on the menu.
(And they arrive...)
Please stop here. This is the place.
(at Haha and Jong Kook's barbecue restaurant?)
- The dish is... - Hold on.
(Flustered)
- It just needs to be on the menu. - It's on the menu.
(Confident)
- It's on the menu. - A dish with 45 letters?
There is a dish with 45 letters.
(Confident)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
(Once they open the door,)
(they find Geun Sik as if he was waiting for them?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Geun Sik pretends he doesn't know.)
- It's nice to meet you. - Hello.
You look familiar.
Let's sit down.
(Is there a dish with a 45-letter-long name...)
Sir, please give us the menu.
(at the crew members' favorite place?)
Please give us the menu.
Let me remind that it needs to be on the menu.
(It must be on the menu.)
- It's on the menu. - It's on the menu.
Why else would we be here?
I have been to this restaurant many times,
(It's the first time the crew members heard about the menu.)
- but I never saw such a thing. - It's on the menu.
- It really exists. - It came to be in 2020...
(Talking)
As an event.
(Ji Hyo is being shameless.)
Since it's a special dish, it's at the back of the menu.
- It's at the back. - It's on the wall too.
- Is it on the wall too? - It's on the wall too.
(Is there a 45-letter-long dish name on the wall of the restaurant?)
- There it is. - There it is.
(It counts if it has been sold.)
- Is it on the wall too? - It's on the wall too.
- There it is. - There it is.
(What's the dish?)
(Nino Maximus Keyser Soze Sonador Sparta and Jack Sparrow's...)
(Beloved Lutartha Sparta Kook's Lovely Bibim Naengmyeon)
- Nino Maximus Keyser Soze... - Keyser Soze...
Sonador Sparta and Jack Sparrow's...
Beloved Lutartha Sparta Kook's Lovely Bibim Naengmyeon.
(It's now 47 letters.)
- It actually exists. - Let's see if it's on the menu.
- Here it is. - Here it is.
(They check the official menu too.)
This is the menu, okay?
- It exists. - It exists.
(Is it even on the official menu?)
Look at this.
- It's obviously fake. - Nino Maximus...
It doesn't even have a price next to it.
(30 minutes ago)
What should we do?
We can't film in the restaurant.
(Geun Sik.)
(I'm on Running Man right now. Can you create a menu for me?)
(What do you mean?)
(Make a long name for bibim naengmyeon on the menu.)
- I found one with 45 letters. - What? Let's go.
(I'm on the way now. Do it now.)
- Let's go there. - They're noodles.
(That's how the dish with a 47-letter-long name got created.)
Nino Maximus Keyser Soze Sonador Sparta...
(Geun Sik tried to be creative.)
and Jack Sparrow's Beloved...
(It's hard to order food with a 45-letter-long name.)
- Lutartha Sparta Kook's Lovely... - Lutartha Sparta Kook's Lovely...
- Bibim Naengmyeon. - Bibim Naengmyeon.
How many letters is that?
It doesn't even have a price.
It shouldn't cost too much.
(Shameless)
It's the same as any other bibim naengmyeon.
Sir, how much is bibim naengmyeon?
- 5 dollars. - It's all 5 dollars.
(Saying anything that comes across his mind)
It's five dollars.
- That's cheap. - You can just tell.
(That naengmyeon is good.)
If this is different from the regular dish, I'll accept.
(The final decision)
(Find the difference from a regular bibim naengmyeon.)
Regular bibim naengmyeon is...
(What's the difference?)
Can you order a regular bibim naengmyeon?
The egg is...
It's essentially the same thing.
(He comes out of nowhere.)
(He interrupts tactlessly.)
What?
(Hey. You need to say it's different.)
- What did you say? - It's half-and-half.
It's half-and-half.
(Haha is trying to sort this out.)
The regular bibim naengmyeon...
(He means the shape of the egg is different.)
- True. - comes with a boiled egg...
- It's only a quarter. - that's only a quarter.
(Since there's controversy, 1 person will try it.)
This is the restaurant's...
- Right. - special menu.
- That's cheap. - You can just tell it's cheap.
(So, the legendary menu is served.)
(Ji Hyo who won the game in the car will taste it.)
Let me know if this is too much for you.
My mouth is getting watery.
(The taste of the dish with a 47-letter-long name)
It's impossible to find a dish...
- It's impossible. - that's over 40 letters long.
I'm done.
- She's done. - You have to approve.
(We won for sure.)
Ji Hyo finished it, so please take a prize badge.
(She finishes eating with 3 minutes left.)
They have no choice, right?
- What are they going to do? - It's on the menu.
It's on the menu.
(Ji Hyo finished eating, so she gets a prize badge.)
After some discussion,
we've decided to approve Ji Hyo's prize badge.
(Now the crew should decide...)
(whether they approve of the 47-letter-long dish name.)
(After a discussion,)
(Ji Hyo's prize badge is valid.)
(What about the result? Have they won?)
Mission failed.
(The 47-letter-long name got disapproved.)
If we approve this,
(It's to play fair.)
the other team will try to create a menu too.
- That's true. - We did think far enough.
It doesn't matter if we win today. We'll keep suffering.
(Jong Kook will make them suffer.)
We at least got a prize badge.
(They earn a prize badge and conclude the first mission.)
- That's at least comforting. - Let's get going.
Hey, weaklings.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan won a prize badge...)
- Here they are. - Oh, dear.
(for having a dish with a 31-letter-long name.)
- We heard. - Oh, dear.
(Teasing)
Was it that difficult to find?
You were so short on letters.
(They're annoying.)
(Only if bibim naengmyeon had been approved...)
So Team So Min won.
(Team So Min who had a dish with a 31-letter-long name...)
That was close.
(won the first mission.)
Round one is now over.
(Team So Min wins the 1st victory. They move on to the next round.)
Let's move onto round two.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(The 2nd round starts.)
Sit with your team.
Shall we?
(So Min grabbed it.)
Okay.
His name is Se Chan from now on.
- Sure. - Se Chan.
(So Min grabbed Se Chan's soaked speaker.)
Se Chan.
Sure, you can call it Se Chan.
(Puppy Se Chan with low sound quality)
Come here.
- Captain. - I think...
So Min has a strategy now.
(He's trying to setting something up again.)
- Oh, gosh. - My Se Chan.
(She's trying to seduce Se Chan.)
- What are you doing? - My Se Chan.
(She's unbelievable.)
What is she doing?
This second mission is a quiz related to memorable commercials.
Memorable commercials?
(Glad)
It's called Aged Commercials.
(The Second Mission: Aged Commercials)
- This is ours to take. - Good.
(We're at a disadvantage.)
We're at a disadvantage.
The team that guesses more out of the five commercials wins.
(The team that guesses more from the 5 commercials wins.)
Okay!
After getting the answer right,
(They must act out the commercial and fill in the missing line.)
you will act out the commercial and fill in the missing line.
- All right. - The line.
There are so many old people...
(Objection)
It's a gathering of the old fossils.
- They have so many old people. - They're the old fossils.
What are you saying?
(The group of old fossils in Running Man)
The youngest is 40 something.
They're the aged ones.
- They're the old fossils. - My gosh.
- We're all young. - Excuse me.
- You should join us. - Aren't you...
all old too?
(Controversy arises.)
We're not.
- You're not? - I'm old,
(He's flustered by the truth bomb.)
- but they're not. - They're old too.
(They're oil fossils too.)
- They're not. - They definitely are.
You're all over 40.
- No. - That's true.
There's 1 person who just turned 40.
- Still. - I'm a newbie.
(Ji Hyo is an infant in her 40s.)
- I'm a new 40. - Newbie.
- We're at a disadvantage. - We're going to lose.
We're at a disadvantage.
We're going to win for sure.
(Feeling confident)
- Let's do this. - Whoever calls out,
(It's important to remember the old commercials accurately.)
"Let me answer," will get to go first.
Here's the first question for Aged Commercials.
(Here's the first question.)
Play...
- I'm going to get this. - the first commercial.
(It's a beverage commercial from the 2000s with many catch phrases.)
In Sung.
(Zo In Sung and Jun Ji Hyun's emotional acting is the key.)
I thought you were busy with work.
- Is dating part of work too? - Don't jump to conclusions.
Why? Are you embarrassed of me? Do I look pathetic?
- Be quiet. - Are you sorry?
What's wrong with you? Who are you to yell at me?
I thought you were busy with work.
(They can almost remember it.)
What's this?
What's wrong with you? Who are you to yell at me?
Have you ever bought me dinner at a nice restaurant?
Have you ever dropped me off with your car like other people?
Does it make you mad that I lied and met some guy?
(She got caught on a date with somebody that's not her boyfriend.)
Is it driving you crazy seeing it firsthand?
(Commercials back then had stories.)
- Was there a commercial like this? - I've never seen it.
Is this a commercial?
I've never seen it.
Don't you have a sense of pride?
Get yourself together!
(This is the product.)
Liars...
Is love enough for love?
(The actors were amazing on the commercial.)
I don't remember the line, but I remember seeing it.
(Will they be able to remember the lines?)
- I don't know. I have no clue. - This is so long.
Wait.
(Their acting is too good for us.)
- We have to act this out? - This existed?
We have to do this?
(As long as it's similar, it counts.)
You just need to make it sound similar.
(Trying to set So Min with Se Chan again)
This is for So Min and Se Chan.
- They have to do it. - I'm looking forward to it.
(They look forward to seeing Se Chan and So Min acting.)
- They need to act. - I'm going to be Yang In Sung.
You'll become Yang In Sung.
Here comes Yang In Sung.
Personality controversy.
He said "personality controversy."
(It's a play on words.)
If I do this,
(Yang In Sung was a funny one.)
there'll be a personality controversy.
I saw that a lot when I was young.
(They remember the commercial, but they don't remember the lines.)
- This... - "Are you sorry?"
I don't remember.
The team that wants to go first can start.
(The team that wants to go first can start.)
If we go first, they'll copy us.
(On alert)
- I think I know. - They might copy us, so let's wait.
(Team So Min wants to wait, so the other team wouldn't copy.)
We can't get it on our first try.
- Right? - Isn't this right?
(Then)
- Go. - "Get yourself together."
(Ji Hyo remembers something.)
"I was never enough."
- That's right. - Okay. Go.
(Team Suk Jin will try first.)
- Let me answer. - Go.
You can start.
(Would they get it?)
- Please come up. - Suk Jin wants to do it.
(Team Suk Jin's first attempt!)
Go, Ji Hyo.
- Jee In Sung. - Jee In Sung?
(Suk Jin plays Zo In Sung.)
Gosh, Jee In Sung.
He has to worry about his personality.
His skin is oily.
Is he a Jee Rogue?
Jee In Sung.
- Go. - Come this way.
(They begin acting.)
Hey, you said you were busy at work, but you were dating another guy.
You said you were busy at work, but you were dating another guy.
(What?)
What are you doing?
(What's he doing?)
That's not the commercial.
- This is horrible acting. - Stop it.
(Suk Jin's acting is terrible.)
- I can't do Zo In Sung. - Just do the original.
- I can't do Zo In Sung. - Copy the lines.
(Just follow the script.)
I thought you were busy with work. Is dating part of work too?
(They try again without ad-libs.)
Don't jump to conclusions.
Why? Are you embarrassed of me? Do I look pathetic?
- He's yelling. - Be quiet.
(He should've followed the script in the first place.)
- Are you sorry? - Have you ever bought me dinner...
at a nice restaurant? Did you ever pour water for me?
(Ji Hyo's acting stands out after Suk Jin's terrible acting.)
Did you ever open the car door for me?
(She sure is an actress.)
You did nothing for me.
I guess you have a sense of pride. Do you have a sense of pride?
Get yourself together.
- Get yourself together. - This is the important part.
(This is the blank part.)
I was never enough.
Good!
- I was never enough. - Good!
Does she remember?
Liars...
I'll bury all of them.
(I'll bury all of them?)
- What? - What was that?
(Startled)
- What? - "I'll bury all of them?"
- I followed my instinct. - You don't say that...
(Was it a noir commercial?)
- in a commercial. - You'll bury them?
- Why would you bury me? - I stayed true to my emotions.
(Flustered)
- When will you stop? - Goodness.
(Obviously, both are incorrect.)
Number 1 and 2 were both wrong.
- They were wrong. - We were wrong?
Both?
- We're ready. - What's number one?
(Team So Min tries next.)
(They're excited to see Team So Min's acting.)
- Jun Ji Min. - I'm excited for them.
(So Min plays Jun Ji Hyun.)
Jun Ji Min.
- Personality controversy. - Yang In Sung.
(Se Chan plays Zo In Sung.)
Saeb In Sung.
- Please say, "ready, action." - Ready, action.
(Team So Min begins acting.)
I thought you were busy with work. Is dating part of work too?
Don't jump to conclusions.
Why? Are you embarrassed of me? Do I look pathetic?
Be quiet.
- Are you sorry? - What's wrong with you?
(The big fan is watching in the front row seat.)
Who are you to yell at me?
Have you ever bought me dinner at a nice restaurant?
Have you ever dropped me off with your car like other people?
Hey, does it drive you nuts that I'm dating somebody else?
(She's unnecessarily good.)
(Is it supposed to be like this?)
Does it make you mad to see me like this?
Does it make you mad? I guess you have a sense of pride.
(She even pulls his hair.)
Do you have a sense of pride?
I guess you have a sense of pride. Do you have a sense of pride?
(This couple is acting very well.)
Get yourself together. Do you know what love is? Do you?
"Do you know what love is? Do you?"
(After their passionate acting, they say the answer.)
"Do you know what love is?"
Liars...
don't get presents from Santa Claus.
Liars don't get presents from Santa Claus.
(He summoned Santa Claus.)
You know that?
(Is this a Christmas commercial?)
Liars don't get presents...
- from Santa Claus! - Your hair.
- Is number one wrong too? - I think it's right.
(Is number 1 wrong too?)
- It's incorrect. - Is it similar?
(Both are incorrect.)
- It's wrong? - Two?
I'll give you a hint for number one.
(Here's a hint on the 1st question.)
It starts with "Love is..."
(It starts with "Love is...")
"Love is amusing to you, right?"
- I'm right. - What is it?
(As soon as So Min hears the hint,)
- Is it right? - "Love is amusing to you, right?"
(she's got an idea.)
- Let's go. - Go.
We'll give it a try.
(Did they figure it out?)
I remembered.
- This is the answer. - I think you're right.
(Team So Min tries right away.)
- Let's do it. - I thought you were busy with work.
Is dating part of work too?
- Get yourself together. - Let's go!
Does love look like water to you?
- That's not right. - Lairs...
Liars...
have no right to love.
- For when you're 2 percent short. - For when you're 2 percent short.
(The acting is 2 percent short, but the ending is perfect.)
Only the second one is correct.
(Only the 2nd one is correct.)
I told you not to do it!
The tone was similar.
(The tone was similar for the 1st one.)
I told you not to do the second one.
(What a shame.)
They didn't know about that one.
Let me give you a hint. This is a poor couple.
(Additional hint: The couple is poor.)
This is a poor couple.
(They're listening to the hint.)
- The woman lied to this man. - A poor couple.
Despite...
(Why is Jae Suk on his phone?)
their financial difficulties, they loved each other.
(Fiddling with his phone)
It makes no sense.
Jae Suk, you can't look it up.
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
(He got caught cheating.)
- What is wrong with you? - What are you doing?
(How dare you look it up?)
- I didn't look it up. - How could you be so shameless?
I didn't look it up.
(Bench clearing is occurred by Jae Suk's cheat.)
- For goodness' sake. - This is...
He got a text.
(A ridiculous excuse)
There is no way he got a text.
(We're in the middle of shooting.)
Who was it? Who told on me?
(He yells at the production crew in embarrassment.)
This is something the elders say often.
(Additional hint)
Give it a try.
(Team Suk Jin got an idea after hearing the conclusive hint.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer. This is it.
- This is it. This is it. - Let me answer.
(Old fossils are certain that they got the answer.)
- This is it. - I don't think it's correct.
- It's correct. - It's too old-school.
(Certain)
It's what the elders say.
You should try it.
- Okay. - It's too old-school.
(Those old fossils must've figured it out.)
- Are you sure it's correct? - It's correct!
Does it drive you nuts that I am dating somebody else...
(Team Suk Jin tries.)
- and not working? - It drives me nuts!
Does it make you mad to see me like this?
- It makes me mad! - Does it make you mad?
I guess you have a sense of pride. Do you have a sense of pride?
- Yes, I do. - Get yourself together.
Okay. Check it out.
(The second answer has been revealed.)
- Love... - You're right.
(If they get the first answer correct, they will win.)
Love...
doesn't put food on the table.
- What? - Is that the answer?
(I think that's correct.)
Liars...
- have no right to love. - That sounds right.
(Team Suk Jin's answer is correct.)
"Love doesn't put food on the table."
We shouldn't have given away the second answer.
(We gave the answer for Number 2.)
I told you it's correct.
Gosh,
(Suk Jin sure is old.)
it's an expression old men use.
I guess you have a sense of pride.
(The answer)
Do you have a sense of pride?
Get yourself together.
Love doesn't put food on the table.
It's correct.
(Suk Jin really is an old man.)
Liars...
have no right to love.
Is love enough...
for love?
(We could have won.)
We revealed the second answer too early on.
- Seriously. - I remember the commercial now.
Their performance was incredible.
They filmed it hundreds of times.
(What's wrong with him?)
How would you know? That might not be the case.
- They are excellent actors. - They filmed it for a day...
(Suk Jin playing In Sung has sparked controversy.)
to get an okay from the director.
I had no idea about the first answer.
Here comes the second aged commercial...
(The current score, Team So Min 0 and Team Suk Jin 1)
- you barely remember. - Okay.
(Let's get it this time.)
We remember that period of time.
Let's go.
(Here's the second question.)
Here is the second question.
- Play. - But I don't remember...
(It's a coffee commercial from 2008 with the lovely lines and acting.)
Da In, are you wearing makeup?
(There were many parodies made.)
- She is wearing a skirt too! - Go away!
I know this one.
I auditioned for it.
(So Min auditioned for the commercial.)
Really?
- She is wearing a skirt too! - Go away!
She is wearing makeup!
(She is waiting for her crush.)
Sometimes, lies are necessary for love.
Hey,
I think I have a fever.
Of course, you need wits to fall for those lies.
I wish you luck.
(They've all seen it before, but they barely remember it.)
- This is... - Why...
It was a popular commercial.
It was incredibly popular.
I don't remember it.
(There were many parodies of the commercial.)
- People parodied it. - That's right.
I just remember the woman's line.
(Although I auditioned for it, I don't remember the whole thing.)
"I think I have a fever."
"Hey, I think I have a fever."
Maybe this is the answer.
(Is that it?)
"Do you like me feverishly?"
- For goodness' sake. - For goodness' sake.
(Sighing)
(The comedian's ad-lib makes them speechless.)
When the woman, Ryu Hyun Jin, spoke,
the man laughed.
When she spoke, the man laughed.
(Ryu Hyun Jin?)
Suk Jin, Ryu Hyun Jin is a baseball player.
Her name is Da In.
- Suk Jin. - Yoo Da In.
(The people on the commercial)
- The man's name is Lee Hyun Jin. - He mixed up the names.
- Suk Jin, you are unbelievable. - Lee Hyun Jin.
(Oh, it's not Ryu Hyun Jin.)
Don't you remember the man's line?
(You said you auditioned for it.)
- I don't remember it. - You auditioned for it.
(Frustrated)
- "Are you in a lot of pain?" - Let's try it.
(Although they don't remember,)
(Team Suk Jin tries first.)
Let's see what we come up with.
Let's see what we come up with. Ji Hyo, try it.
- "Hey, I think I have a fever." - "Hey, I think I have a fever."
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are getting ready to act.)
- This is... - Is this university for the elders?
(Is this college for elders?)
Is this university for the elders?
- The university... - The university for the elders.
(He looks like a university professor.)
(Team Suk Jin tries.)
Go.
- Hey. - Yes?
- What... - That was so late.
How could you address the principle that way?
- You should bow to him. - The president of the university.
(How rude.)
(Senior Suk Jin became a principal.)
- You should bow to him. - The president of the university.
- I can't do this. - How many years did he move down?
(Sorry I didn't say hello right away.)
(Suk Jin is the principal and a senior.)
I can't get immersed in it.
(His look distracts the audience.)
I have no idea what kind of commercial this is.
Let's do this one by one.
(Love between the principal and student is forbidden.)
"Hey, I think I have a fever."
"Hot water is pouring out!"
(Warm water commercial would be more appropriate for them.)
That's how this commercial should go.
(They go back to acting.)
Take my hand.
Hey, I think I have a fever.
You are burning up.
(The principal is worried about the student.)
That could be the answer.
- That was the worst. - That could be the answer.
- That was the worst. - What was that?
(Team Suk Jin fails obviously.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- We have an idea. - It's our turn.
(Team So Min tries.)
- Aren't you going to go? - Let me answer. We have an idea.
(Let's watch them.)
- Sit down. - Do this.
What a scary underclassman!
(Jong Kook isn't a gangster. He's the beauty queen of PE major.)
(Cute)
That's cute.
(I should've taken the other gate.)
- Hey, I think I have a fever. - Put his hand on your forehead.
(Please don't kill me.)
What are you doing?
(Can't you hear me?)
I think my hand is warmer.
(Wrong)
- What? Is it incorrect? - Is it incorrect?
- Was it close? - It's correct.
(Team So Min fails.)
- It's incorrect. - No, it's correct.
(Despite Jong Kook's good acting, Team So Min failed.)
Come on. It's incorrect.
- Let me answer. - Try it with Jae Suk.
(Did they figure it out?)
- Here we go. - Ready, set, go.
(Team Suk Jin tries again.)
- Hey. - Yes?
- I think I have a fever. - How hot!
Your forehead is boiling up!
(Gosh, it's hot.)
- What was that? - "Your forehead is boiling up"?
(What's with his speech?)
- What was that? - That sounds ridiculous.
- How hot! - What was that?
(It sounded like a heating pad commercial.)
- This isn't it. - Your forehead is boiling up!
- Did you turn on the boiler? - Come on.
(Team Suk Jin fails without a chance.)
Is it incorrect?
Come on, it's not a commercial for a boiler.
Give me a break.
- "Your forehead is boiling up"? - "Hey, I think I have a fever."
(Both teams have no clue.)
I will give you the first thing the man says.
(The production crew give a conclusive hint.)
"Hey, I think I have a fever."
(It starts with "It hurts...")
"Being sick..."
Let me answer. "Being sick is the sign of youth."
(Is it warm advice to a junior who is in pain?)
- "The sign of youth"? - Where did that come from?
"Being sick..."
"Makes you prettier."
(Team Suk Jin's deducting after hearing the hint.)
"Being sick makes you prettier."
Let's go.
(Then Team Suk Jin tries again.)
- Give it a go. Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Hey,
I think I have a fever.
Being sick...
makes you prettier.
Is it correct?
(Will they be able to get it right twice in a row?)
I think it's correct.
- It's correct. - I think it's correct.
"Being sick makes you look prettier."
- We did it. - My goodness.
- We did it. - Our answer was very close.
(Team Suk Jin gets close to it. They got it.)
That's good.
(The answer)
Hey,
I think I have a fever.
Of course, you need wits to fall for those lies.
Being sick makes you look prettier.
I wish you luck.
That makes my heart flutter.
(Getting excited)
If we get one more question right, we win.
(The current score, Team So Min 0 and Team Suk Jin 2)
- So Min, we are nearly there. - We need to do this.
(Team So Min answered the next 2 questions.)
I am Dongwon.
(The current score, Team So Min 2 and Team Suk Jin 2)
- This is the final round. - The final round.
(The team that answers the next question wins this round.)
We barely managed to catch up.
Let's go. We came this far.
- Let's get this right. - I had nearly given up.
(Let's keep this going.)
- This is the last question. - We will win.
- Here it comes. - This is the last question.
(Here's the last question.)
(Jang Na Ra, 18 years ago)
We're just friends.
I...
never loved you.
(Wait. That commercial is...)
- I know this commercial! - This is...
(He can barely remember it.)
- Kim Jae Won. - Jae Won.
I'm going to break you.
Oh, my.
Love is not...
"Love is not..."
"It's..."
That's the catchphrase.
Gosh, my memory is blurred.
(She can barely remember it too.)
Love is not a joke.
That's a song title.
- Love is not a joke - Love is not a joke
(Mission is not a joke either.)
(Giggling)
Love is not furniture.
- It's science. - It's science.
(His love for science never stops.)
It's a commercial for a green plum drink.
(Keep in mind that it's a plum beverage commercial.)
You have the right approach.
- The drink is called Green Plum. - Yes. Green Plum.
(Plum is green.)
"Love is not green"?
Love is green.
(Is it that love is green?)
Love is not yellow, it's green.
(Or is it that love is not yellow, but green?)
Love is not red, it's green.
(They're talking about colors.)
(Whispering)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer. This is it.
(Team Suk Jin tries.)
They might get it right.
(What is it?)
We're... We're just friends.
I never loved you.
I'm going to break you.
Okay.
That was good.
Love...
is not pink. It's green.
What?
- It's green. - What?
(Love is not pink, but green?)
Pink? Where did pink come from?
(Team Suk Jin fails.)
Try it. The two of you should try it.
(This time, Team So Min tries.)
Try it.
(I think our guess is right.)
I think this is it.
- I think this is it. - They might get it right.
(They become a couple that is breaking up.)
- But... - We're just friends.
(He's being harsh.)
I never loved you.
(Splashing water)
(That upsets me.)
That's so cold. That's so cold. I am sorry.
I am sorry.
(He wants to beg for forgiveness after getting splashed.)
I shouldn't have messed with you.
(Don't ever say that even for acting.)
I am sorry. You must be upset.
(He's using honorifics.)
That's a comment that would really anger So Min.
(The audience is loving it.)
I'm going to break you.
(She speaks what's on her mind.)
- Narration. - Female voice.
Love is...
not green.
It's a green plum.
(Plums?)
No?
(Team So Min, Incorrect)
- My bad. - It's okay.
(What is the answer?)
I never loved you.
"Love is not green. It's a green plum..."
sounds kind of immature.
This is it. This is it!
(Suk Jin has come up with an idea.)
- Go for it. - Go for it.
(Team Suk Jin tries.)
- Let me answer. - You be the woman.
- Be the woman. - Go for it.
Go.
We're just friends. I never loved you.
(Ji Hyo is a great actress indeed.)
I'm going to break you.
(Suk Jin uses his wrist to splash water.)
(He takes a peek.)
(Then he suddenly looks around.)
He's unbelievable. He looked at himself after splashing the water.
(He's in the middle of an act, but he still loves himself.)
How cruel.
(He splashes the water...)
(and scans himself.)
Did you see him?
(Ji Hyo is the one who got splashed.)
He splashed the water. He obviously splashed it on her,
- but he looked at himself. - In case he got water on it.
(It's not just tears that Suk Jin doesn't want on his body.)
That's sharp.
- I got goosebumps. - My bad.
- That's sharp. - You're the worst.
I always think this is the worst moment, and he surprises me.
He's the worst.
(He is making a record for 10 years.)
Love is not a fantasy.
It's reality.
Suk Jin?
(Is Suk Jin sharing what he really feels?)
- What was that? - Wasn't that it?
That's when you sign divorce papers.
We thought of "Love doesn't feed you."
Here's a hint. Haha and Ji Hyo's first try...
(It's very similar to "Love is not pink, but green.")
- was very close. - See?
I said so.
- Let me answer. - Let's go.
(I think I know.)
We'll go.
(Come back after you guess it right.)
- Do it. - We'll go.
(Kwang Soo sees the water bottle.)
Okay.
I'll be Jang Na Ra.
What are you talking about?
(What are you talking about?)
- Why? - What?
(I don't want to get wet.)
You're Jang Na Ra.
(It's a discussion among...)
I mean... Am I?
(two idiots.)
I'm the woman.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo is not the only idiot. Se Chan is an idiot too.)
(Se Chan wins and takes Jang Na Ra's part.)
He was late.
(Drinking)
Hurry up.
He has water in his mouth.
Are you going to do this?
(Quietly)
This is not the last game.
(Threatening)
We're just friends.
(Kwang Soo calmly starts to recite his lines.)
I never loved you.
(2 water strikes)
You got your face washed.
(He got to wash his face.)
I'm going to break you.
Love is not pink.
It's green.
- It's wrong. - Let me answer.
(Team So Min changed it into English, but it was wrong.)
- No. - Let's go for it.
(That's not it.)
I'm going to break you.
(Team Suk Jin guesses the answer.)
Pink is not the color of love.
- It's green. - That's the answer.
(Are pink and green colors correct?)
- You were 99 percent correct. - What?
(Incorrect, but very close.)
Let me answer!
What is it?
(He's certain.)
This is the last time,
(Kwang Soo grabs onto the water bottle.)
- so Jong Kook and I'll go. - Okay.
Jong Kook.
(Are you going to challenge me?)
Good.
(He gets a new water bottle.)
Use the old water, punk!
(This country has a water shortage.)
I drank from it.
(Intimidated)
This is the last time.
- Is it me? - Yes.
(This is the last question, so there's no next time.)
He loaded his gun.
(Loading a gun?)
Let's go. Ready, action.
(Water Sniper Kwang Soo is fully loaded.)
(Speechless)
We're just friends.
I never loved you.
(This is a water bomb.)
(It turns into a trashy drama.)
(The water slap follows the kimchi slap.)
This is improbable. Good ad-lib. This is ad-lib.
(This has no logic or context.)
(The male lead is mad because the story doesn't make any sense.)
(The female lead isn't scared because this is the last question.)
What are you going to do now?
(Haha had an experience of being ignored by Jong Kook.)
I understand why he's mad.
(The audience mode)
- I'll hit the other person. - I understand.
(The bulletin board will be flooded with complaints.)
- Me too. - I understand.
Pink is not the color of love.
It's green.
- That's exactly what we said. - That's what we said.
What was that? Let me answer.
(Team So Min blew their chance.)
- What was that? - Isn't that what we said?
(We couldn't even get it correct.)
(Anxious)
He's in deep trouble.
(How are you going to bear it?)
- Here's a hint. - What was that?
"Love is not the pink..."
(Hint: Love is not pink something.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(Team So Min knows the answer.)
(We missed our chance.)
Let me answer.
- Go, Jong Kook. - Can we go?
(To make the story more compelling)
What's he going to do?
- How many bullets do you need? - Give me all of them.
What do you mean?
- The answer is important. - Okay, good.
(If you know that so well, why did you do that?)
- You might forget the lines. - Fine.
Let's go.
(Everyone takes a step back knowing what will come.)
You'll get water on the cameras. Move back.
Something will happen.
(He doesn't know where to look.)
Say your line.
(He's petrified.)
We're just friends.
(Trembling)
- Next. - I...
(He predicted his fate.)
I never... I never loved...
(It's a super muscle mist for...)
(moisturizing the aged skin.)
I never... I never loved...
(Kwang Soo is becoming moisturized.)
I... I never...
I never loved... I never loved you.
(He's dripping tears and water.)
I'm going to break you.
Love is not the pink hue.
It's the green hue.
(Correct)
Good job.
- Good job. - Okay!
I didn't think my underwear would get wet.
(When you said we are doing quizzes...)
We did it.
My underwear got wet.
(The answer)
Love is no the pink hue.
It's the green hue.
Our team is amazing.
(The final score, Team So Min 3 and Team Suk Jin 2)
- That was too bad. - We turned it around.
(Team So Min turned it around!)
That was a drama without a script.
(So Min is happy.)
We have the final scores, but there are 1 to 2 funny commercials.
- Let's watch them. - Would you like to?
I'll give a prize badge to the winning team.
(The winner will take 1 prize badge.)
That's good.
Queen, would you like to dance?
(Two superstars, Shim Eun Ha and Han Seok Kyu, 20 years ago)
I remember this.
"Hello, I'm Han Seok Kyu."
If I'm a queen,
what are you?
I'm...
It's long.
That was so long.
It's so long. Why is it so long?
"I'm Dr. Romantic."
"I'm Dr. Romantic 2."
(MC Romantic, Master Yu)
Who's number two?
- Who's number 2? - I'm number 3.
(The answer to this question...)
If I'm a queen, who are you?
I'm accompanying the queen right now.
All right.
(Haha earns the prize badge.)
- "Accompanying"? - We were right.
Haha got the answer, so he gets a prize badge.
(Prize badge status, Team So Min, Team Suk Jin)
As I promised,
(Since So Min won 2 out of 3 rounds first,)
So Min can choose a gift.
(she gets to choose.)
Really?
(1. Choose gifts from all of her team members.)
You can choose the meaningful gifts brought by your team members...
or take a chance to win a 100-inch TV...
(2. A chance to win a 8,000-dollar TV through a game.)
that's worth 8,000 dollars.
Can I decide now?
(Is she going to play safe and choose the team members' gifts?)
(Or is she going for the chance to win 100 inch TV?)
Can I decide now?
(What will So Min choose?)
I'll try for the 8,000-dollar TV.
(100 inch TV)
(You are so greedy.)
- Think about it. - So Min.
- What are you doing? - We have nice gifts.
(How can you abandon our presents for a TV?)
There's nothing here worth 8,000 dollars.
(She speaks the truth.)
- I wouldn't hesitate. - Why?
You might get a dud. That's possible.
You'll get nothing.
(She might earn a dud, but she still wants to try.)
- Rather than getting those, - Is a dud better?
- I'd rather go for the TV. - Go for it.
That's your style. I agree with you.
(Sparkling water maker)
If I take this, will you install it at my house?
Will you install it at my house?
(Sparkling water maker dealer is flustered.)
You don't need to install anything. You just leave it there.
- You leave it. - "Will you install it at my house?"
(So Min is cute.)
- So Min, please choose. - Gosh, So Min.
I choose the TV.
(As she said first...)
Then switch spots with Ji Hyo.
(Now she has a 50-percent chance.)
Look towards it.
She might finish it.
I should have won!
(Suk Jin is jealous.)
If she wins the 100-inch TV,
everybody on this team gets a prize badge.
- Everybody? All of us? - Yes.
If she wins the TV, you all get a prize badge.
(If So Min wins TV, her teammates will have prize badges.)
I have a question.
What if both are duds?
(She is doubtful.)
- Jong Kook, can you check then? - Okay.
(Jong Kook checks for So Min who is full of doubt.)
You know what?
If I were you, I would have done the same.
All right.
(He checks.)
- Good. - Jong Kook checked.
(She whispers in front of the crew.)
If I win the TV and cash it in...
(I came here to make a deal.)
She's trying to make a deal with me.
I'll give you 5,000 dollars.
(Jeon So Min, gift certificate lobbyist,)
5,000 for you, and 3,000 for me.
(I'll give you 5,000 dollars.)
Go back immediately.
Everybody, let's vote.
Line up on either side.
Do I get something?
(The investment genius)
If I win the gift card,
(If I get the gift certificate, I'll give 3,000 dollars.)
- I will... - Will you give us some?
It's 8,000 dollars, right? I'll share 3,000 dollars.
Through a lottery. That's if I win.
(If she wins the TV.)
Please line up on either side.
I'm sure it's this one.
(They are divided into 3 versus 3.)
It's difficult when it's 3 on 3.
(She deliberates for a long time.)
I...
You're giving us 3,000 dollars.
will go with my team's choice and pick number one.
- Okay. - They're too blue.
(So Min chooses Number 1.)
- So Min chose... - Is she stupid?
number one.
(Would Number 1 have the 8,000-dollar TV?)
I wish you luck.
- I think it's this side. - Let me have some of it.
(Or is it a dud?)
- Is this her final decision? - This is her final decision.
(This is her last chance.)
One...
What will happen to the 100-inch TV?
(So Min didn't choose her team members' gifts.)
One,
(She chose the TV instead.)
two,
(What's the result?)
three.
- What's that? - Hey!
(It's a dud.)
Three.
- What's that? - Hey!
What was that? What's wrong with me?
(Dud)
Did you not switch it around?
(Did they switch it from the back?)
Did you not switch it?
(Phase 1: She gets annoyed.)
(Phase 2: She is in denial.)
- Did you not switch it? - Jong Kook checked.
- Really? - Was it like this earlier too?
And So Min,
we're the unlucky ones.
(She chose where most of her teammates are.)
I was going to choose this side, but they were all blue,
so I went for my team.
It's too early to give up because you have to choose...
(Look at me.)
- the useless gifts. - Take Ronaldo!
My billboard is pretty.
(This is the consequence of being too greedy.)
1, 2, 3.
(What is the useless item that So Min will take?)
- Suk Jin. - The navigation device.
(She got the GPS device from the US.)
Use it when you go to the States.
(It will be the navigator for her American dream.)
You should use it when you go to the States.
(Instead of 100-inch TV,)
- This one. - The navigation device.
Navigation of my life
(she got a 3-inch GPS that can be used only in the US.)
I guess I'm unlucky this year.
(What's the use of the GPS?)
Actually,
there was something...
that Suk Jin and So Min didn't know about today's race.
(Something we didn't know?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Before the shooting)
(A few members gathered.)
Is this a show in a show?
- Se Chan, come over here. - Hello.
So Min isn't here.
(That reminds them.)
As you know, two of the members aren't here.
Right.
Suk Jin isn't here too.
- Hey, why would you say that? - I'm sorry.
(They don't feel his absence.)
- I didn't know. - Right. Suk Jin isn't here.
(He's always in our hearts.)
We didn't know.
Today, we will have...
Double Celebration Race to celebrate...
(It's to celebrate Suk Jin's birthday...)
(and the release of So Min's book.)
Suk Jin's birth and So Min's book.
(Double Celebration Race)
But there's a secret that the two captains don't know.
There will be no 100-inch TV to win in the first place.
- I knew it. - My gosh.
- I saw this coming. - Really?
There's no TV?
All the choices are duds.
(They're both duds.)
But if the captains press their luck too hard,
whether they win games or not, they won't get any prizes today.
(If a captain's being greedy and chooses the TV,)
(regardless of the result, the captain won't get anything.)
That's good.
Actually, they both are greedy.
(Suk Jin and So Min)
That's true.
If they don't choose the gifts we prepared...
(If they don't choose the gifts from the members, they will get nothing.)
They will get nothing.
(And So Min doesn't know anything about it.)
Can I make my decision now?
I want the TV.
(I want the gift certificate worth 8,000 dollars.)
On three, we'll open them at the same time.
(And the crew members switched the prizes accordingly.)
- I choose number one. - So Min chose number one.
- I choose number one. - Okay.
(Jong Kook was hand in glove with the crew members too.)
- Okay. - Are you sure?
- So Min chose number one. - Okay.
We kept switching the places behind the curtains.
Jeong Mi kept going back and forth there.
(She remembers the time she was being greedy.)
Did you plan the whole thing?
So Min and Suk Jin were the captains of today's race.
If they pressed their luck too hard,
their team members wouldn't get any prizes.
And the members knew about it.
(They feel betrayed.)
What?
Why did you not tell me about it?
We kept telling you to pick this.
(I told you to pick this.)
I told you to pick this.
(You were the one being greedy.)
- I said that too. - Right.
I...
You were blinded by 8,000 dollars.
(The sparkling water maker dealer)
I knew it when I saw her eyes.
(The cutout agency)
She wouldn't listen to me anyway.
She seemed so greedy.
(Her eyes were burning with desire)
She would never listen to us. We should've given up sooner.
Her eyes were full of greed.
(Captain Jee)
You should've told... What about you?
If you were me, you would've made the same choice.
I would've been worse.
(Burning desire)
I'm so resentful that I didn't get to open it.
Guys, I'm so sorry.
(I won't be greedy next time.)
I'll be a nice person.
Let me announce the result of today's race.
(The result of prize badges)
Those who didn't win a single badge...
are Suk Jin, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo.
I didn't win a single badge.
They didn't lose the game, but they didn't get a badge.
Can you let one of us off the hook?
(Being pathetic)
- I'll do that. - Since it's my birthday.
(Special treatment for a birthday boy)
- Let's make it 2 people. - 2 people.
(Only 2 people will get the penalty.)
Okay.
The one who picks So Min's name will be excluded.
All right.
Open it as I count to three.
(Who will be lucky and excluded?)
(Kwang Soo and Suk Jin will face the penalty.)
- My gosh. - I picked it.
Gosh, Jong Kook picked her name.
- I got excluded. - You picked it.
- My gosh. - You're so lucky.
I didn't expect this.
You just got me a cake to celebrate my birthday.
(He got a birthday cake and the penalty.)
Let's do this.
1, 2, and 3.
My goodness.
(Cannon salute to celebrate his birthday)
It's so red.
(Kwang Soo with pink cheeks)
It's red today.
Kwang Soo got it just right.
Gosh, it looks so good.
(Blushing)
You look cute.
It's so cute.
(Everyone loves Kwang Soo who got the penalty.)
(Crowded and alienated)
Say something to Suk Jin.
(The producer feels bad for Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin doesn't look funny.
(Suk Jin doesn't look funny.)
(Funny and not funny)
Bye, Suk Jin.
My gosh.
Things are not going well for in 2020.
(Good things will come your way, Suk Jin.)
- You have no luck. - I'm so unlucky.
(Happy birthday to Suk Jin, and congratulations to So Min.)
- You don't look funny. - It's not funny at all.
- My gosh. - You got it right.
(Contestants of Running Man Dance Challenge)
(Creaking dance, Kang Han Na)
- What's that? - Kyeong Hwan.
(A humorous dancer, Heo Kyeong Hwan)
- It's become strange. - What's that?
(The ambiance suddenly turns cold.)
- It shows the time. - Kwang Soo, you should change here.
(The clock is ticking differently on their phones.)
(They should feed, lodge, and clothe themselves in the circle of time.)
- The time is ticking. - It's decreasing.
- You don't have much of it now. - Han Na!
(Time is fair.)
(Time is unfair.)
You have to hurry.
Those who don't have enough time are desperate.
(The same events repeat to everyone.)
This is crazy.
(Bad timing and the locked door of time)
- It's locked. - Where's So Min?
We have to find something.
(If you want to survive,)
(find the room of time and steal time.)
Let's go!
You don't have to do this. Just give me 10 minutes.
(Success and failure will be decided only in 10 minutes.)
Will you take my side?
(Join hands with someone you can trust.)
Watch yourselves. You have to give me a chance.
(However)
- Really? - Are they judges or what?
(There are time controllers in yellow jacket who are watching you.)
- Why are they being so serious? - Is it over?
Seriously? They are unbelievable.
(Who's the one to get away from the time circle?)
This is surprising.
(Running Countdown)