- Hello. - Hello.
(Chilly wind welcomes them...)
(under clear autumn sky.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Look at the fall leaves over there.
I think the fall foliage peaks this week.
(Autumn leaves reached its peak and shine brightly.)
I know. It's beautiful.
- It's chilly now. - They are the best this week.
- But it's quite warm. - It looks amazing.
Your boots are too much.
- Gosh, I knew you'd say that. - For this season.
It's too soon to wear boots like them.
(Her horseback riding boots are too much for autumn.)
The most awkward part of So Min's outfit is her boots.
I know. Why are you wearing them?
(They start commenting on her fashion.)
The edges of the boots are folded around her knees.
Around her knees,
(The horseback riding boots are rubbing against her knees.)
- they are wrinkled. - You're bleeding on your knees.
So Min is standing at the end for a reason.
So stop pointing that out.
(He asks them to stop commenting.)
- Why are you trying to stop us? - When a dog wears shoes,
it walks awkwardly.
I'm just like that. I feel awkward in the boots.
(Puppy So Min's nervous from wearing new shoes.)
You look like a kid at an elementary school entrance ceremony.
(Target changed)
That's right. I'm dressed like this to attend an entrance ceremony.
That's right.
I'm dressed like this to attend an entrance ceremony.
(He admits it.)
I see. That's good.
When he says that...
(He doesn't know what to do as Jae Suk admits it.)
- You should attack him. - I have nothing to say.
- I... By the way... - Say something to attack him.
(Suk Jin!)
- Suk Jin, you should hit back. - Is that what you're doing?
(The audience is angry as Suk Jin misses his good chance.)
Suk Jin! My gosh.
(What a bummer.)
That's what I thought when I put these on.
That's perfect.
I'm very grateful.
I was right about that. I got it right.
(The low-rank attacker pretends to be happy.)
Suk Jin read your mind.
Suk Jin is good.
(Thanks to Suk Jin, Jae Suk's school look shines.)
- Suk Jin... - This isn't what he wanted.
- Just let it go. - Hey, Se Chan.
(Jae Suk noticed something and giggles.)
Suk Jin is really mean.
He got flustered by what I said.
Then he checked Se Chan's outfit.
(He changed his target.)
Suk Jin is good.
(As soon as he failed to attack Jae Suk, )
(he glanced at Se Chan to pick on him.)
Suk Jin...
- He's flustered. - I'm not flustered.
(And he got caught right away.)
(He leered at Se Chan to change his target.)
Do you know why he didn't say anything?
His shirt is similar to mine.
- It has a similar pattern. - He's right.
(The red checkered twins aren't any different.)
I was going to say something, but it looked just like mine.
He wanted to criticize Se Chan instead.
(He knew suppressing Se Chan would only make fun of him.)
It's like looking into a mirror.
The weather is very nice today, isn't it?
(They're happy, and the weather is nice.)
- Yes. - Yes.
Since fall is the season of gastronomy,
(Since it's autumn, the season of gastronomy, )
you're going to enjoy tasty food today.
(they're going to enjoy tasty food today.)
- Okay. - Nice.
And we have six guests...
(There are 6 guests...)
whom we want to have a meal with.
(whom they want to have a meal with.)
- Gosh, six guests? - Yes.
(Anticipating)
- We will... - What? There's Bomi.
(Who's the first guest to enjoy the tasty food?)
I really wanted to eat with her.
Bomi.
- There's Namjoo. - Namjoo.
- Hello. - She's Namjoo.
(Namjoo, Bomi)
- Namjoo? - It's Apink!
(Running Man's family, Apink is here to have a meal together.)
(Namjoo got her wings with her solo, "Bird".)
(Bomi is a charming girl with a good appetite.)
- Namjoo? - It's Apink!
(Welcome, guys!)
- Hello. - Hello.
We just showed up out of nowhere, right?
That's why it's so good to see you.
(They haven't seen Apink for a while.)
- Namjoo. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - Namjoo.
- Bomi. - It's been a long time.
They are gourmets.
Bomi, don't you think this is too straight?
(Her hair is too flat.)
I've gained some weight, so I want to cover my face.
- I need to cover it. - It looks like you ironed it.
(She ironed her hair nicely for the show.)
How did you do that?
- Namjoo, how have you been? - A long time ago.
My solo album was released.
(Namjoo released her solo album, "Bird" in September.)
- That's right! - Oh, right.
- You didn't know. - I know. I watched it.
You had something on here. I saw you dance alone.
I didn't have anything on.
- You didn't? - Why would you make things up?
(Bitter)
Namjoo came to my gym once, but I didn't see her afterwards.
- Maybe you told her something. - You didn't go?
(He checks her gym attendance.)
- She said, - That's not true.
"I'll start working out." And she didn't come again.
(Trainer Kim is strict with Namjoo's attendance.)
She's here as a guest,
but she's being scolded that she didn't go to the gym.
Really?
I think people like her seem more humane.
Those who say they will work out and never come back.
(Namjoo feels humane because she's realistic.)
- I didn't see her again. - Isn't that humane?
- She is indeed humane. - Right.
(Along with Bomi and Namjoo who are here to eat, )
Here are our next guests.
I guess we're having guests with a good appetite.
(there are more guests whom they want to eat with.)
- It's Mingyu. - SEVENTEEN.
(Nice to meet you.)
Welcome. How have you been?
(Hoshi, Mingyu)
Have you been doing well?
(Hoshi and Mingyu of SEVENTEEN are back with "Home;Run".)
(SEVENTEEN is so popular that they have no time to eat.)
(So the two members are joining Running Man as representatives.)
It's SEVENTEEN.
- It's been a long time. - Have you been doing well?
(It's nice to see you.)
- All right. - Mingyu...
(Mingyu's been on the show before.)
- has been in our show many times. - Right.
(It's Hoshi's first time on the show.)
But this is the first time for Hoshi.
- Right? - Yes.
It's been so long since I met Hoshi in "Sugar Man".
- In "Sugar Man"... - I didn't appear in "Sugar Man".
- Gosh, he wasn't there. - Why are you confused?
(He already got one wrong.)
- Because... - He's becoming like Suk Jin.
(Laughing)
SEVENTEEN has a lot of members, so I thought I met Hoshi.
(Yoo Jae Suk keeps getting wrong today.)
But you weren't there.
Things are not going well for you today.
- It's okay. Cheer up! - Cheer up!
(He keeps making mistakes as he's very glad to meet them.)
- Good luck. - Get your energy up!
(Okay.)
It can happen.
(They'll meet their next guests.)
Let's bring in the next guests. They are the last team.
We have a lot of guests today.
(Who are the last guests to eat with the members?)
(Laughing)
What is it?
(They burst into laughter as soon as the guests show up.)
Hello.
- What are you doing here? - What's happening?
(Two people who they want to treat to a meal)
- Hello! - Hello.
(Kim Soo Yong, Nam Chang Hee)
It's Soo-DRAGON.
- What are you doing here? - Soo Yong is perfect for this.
(They all cheer at their appearance.)
- Chang Hee. - Okay.
Okay. He's here.
Gosh. As they showed up...
right after Mingyu and Hoshi, it's really...
- It feels heavy. - It is heavy.
(You can feel their heavy sense of existence.)
Soo Yong and I debuted together at "KBS College Comedy Contest".
(Jae Suk and Soo Yong debuted at "KBS College Comedy Contest".)
He was number one in Yeouido.
Right. He went to Yeouido High School.
(Soo Yong lived in Yeouido for a long time.)
- Yes. - He grabbed Jae Suk's shoulder.
It's not that he was number one at his school.
He says he was a good fighter,
but it's not like there's...
(But there is...)
a famous story about that.
(no legendary story.)
I think he was just a worthless scamp.
I didn't know that about Soo Yong.
(Kim Soo Yong, worthless scamp)
- All right. - My gosh.
(Pinching)
How could he do that to Jae Suk?
(Yeouido scamp pinches the national MC's ear.)
- To Jae Suk... - Actually,
he's always treated me like this since our debut.
- Because he's older. - When I talk a lot,
(He's been pinching Jae Suk's ear for 30 years.)
he always does this.
All right. Good.
If you don't have anything to say, we will move on.
(It's over after calling him the Yeouido scamp.)
I don't have much to say.
Okay.
(There's no news about him.)
- We're moving on. - All right then.
We've moved on.
All right. Every time...
(They're glad to meet Bomi as much as the Yeouido scamp.)
Bomi joined us, she showed her kicks.
(She showed her low kick every time she appeared.)
I don't know if she'd do it today.
I want her to kick Soo Yong.
(Supporting his friend)
I think Soo Yong is ready.
(He's helping his friend get more airtime.)
- Right. - He can give it a try.
(Approved)
Are you going to be okay?
Are you really okay?
(The scamp said yes without knowing what it is.)
- About getting kicked? - Yes.
- In the buttocks. - It's her signature.
It's her signature.
(Bomi is under a lot of pressure.)
All of a sudden?
- We all experienced it once. - I can do that.
(Confident)
- Are you okay with it? - Sure.
As far as I know, he's very strong.
(Since Soo Yong willingly said yes, )
(he gets to experience her kick on the spot.)
Sure. He looks strong.
(Even Jong Kook approves of strong Soo Yong.)
Are you really okay with this?
Yes. It's no problem.
(The legend of Yeouido High School willingly tries it.)
Can I hit you after you hit me?
(Dad joke)
(No one expected Soo Yong's dad joke.)
- What are you talking about? - What?
- That's not what we're doing. - How could you...
(The legend of Yeouido High School is punching with his dad joke.)
- How could you clench your fist? - That's not it.
- That's not it. - That's not what you're doing.
(He just needs to get over Bomi's kick.)
It won't take long.
- It just stings. - With your foot?
- Where? In the buttocks? - Look straight ahead.
Are you going to do this at full strength?
(Bomi's ready with an apologetic look.)
Yes.
Soo Yong was quite famous in Yeouido High School too.
(He seized Yeouido with his resilience.)
- I know. He really was. - All right.
(Will he be able to put up with Bomi's kick?)
(Groaning)
(The legend of Yeouido High School groans like a weak person.)
(A scamp from Yeouido collapses.)
(I'm really sorry.)
Did you hear his short holler?
Soo Yong doesn't usually react much to anyone.
- But not to this. - Yes, this is the first I've seen.
(She succeeded in making Soo Yong react.)
Thank you, Bomi.
Soo Yong doesn't react.
(Bomi's low kick restored his dull emotions.)
This is the first I've ever seen a reaction.
You're the only one who made him react.
Are you okay?
(Bomi's single blow made everyone laugh at Soo Yong's reaction.)
- That was good. - Yes, it was fun.
"Are you okay?"
Before I explain the rules to you,
(Introducing today's race)
- we'll decide on the teams. - All right.
(The teams will be decided first.)
- So there are teams. - We'll divide you into three teams.
(The guests have been assigned to their teams.)
Each guest has already teamed up with the person they came with.
- I see. - Oh, really?
Now they'll decide who's going to be on their teams.
(The guests will pick the members to join the three teams.)
Each team will pick a card...
(The guests of the 3 teams will choose the order first.)
to decide the order of picking their members.
They will take turns to choose one they want on their team.
(They will take turns to choose one they want on their team.)
(The result of fixing the order)
(1: Mingyu and Hoshi, 2: Bomi and Namjoo, 3: Soo Yong and Chang Hee)
1, 2, and 3.
Starting there, you will take turns...
(Mingyu and Hoshi will call out the name of the member they want.)
to choose a member for your team.
We will choose...
Jeon So Min.
(My goodness)
She's grinning.
(She smiles genuinely as Hoshi picks her.)
- She's smiling like this again. - Yes, because she's so excited.
She doesn't know how to hide her feelings.
(She can't help but feel happy every week.)
Yes, every week.
- Hoshi and Mingyu picked her. - She's excited.
(So Min joins a team 1st.)
Who's next?
We will choose...
(Who will be picked by Bomi and Namjoo of Apink?)
- Jong Kook! - Okay!
(They chose Jong Kook.)
- Jong Kook eats well. - Thank you.
(The Apink members choose a guy that eats well.)
- He eats a lot. - They want to win.
(Elated)
- Yes, they want to win. - I can eat a lot.
Okay, next.
I will pick...
(Soo Yong and Chang Hee will pick...)
(They're whispering to each other like it's difficult to decide.)
(They chose Jae Suk!)
- We choose Yoo Jae Suk! - Yoo Jae Suk!
(The bad boy kicks Jae Suk's butt to choose him.)
- Why would you pick me? - Jae Suk.
I'm not good at talking so we need you.
(They picked him for the talk.)
- This is crazy. - We need you.
Okay, next.
(It's Mingyu's turn again.)
We will choose Se Chan.
- Okay. - Se Chan!
(Se Chan joins them followed by So Min.)
She doesn't like it though.
- I don't want him. - You don't?
(Can't we just be a team by ourselves?)
I don't want to team up with him.
You don't want her being happy on their team, do you?
- Go get her. - I'll ruin everything for you.
- Come on. Why? - Just get lost!
(Guarding them)
- Why are you doing this to me? - Don't!
Hey, hey, hey. Don't!
(Mingyu and Hoshi gets a shield!)
Now it's Namjoo and Bomi's turn.
(She has to choose between Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, Haha, and Kwang Soo.)
We choose Haha.
(She chooses Haha.)
- Oh, yes! - Yes!
I wanted to team up with you!
(Haha leaves with a cheer.)
(It's Soo Yong and Chang Hee's turn to pick among the remaining three.)
- Who will you choose? - What?
We will choose Mr. Ji.
- Mr. Ji. - Hey, hey!
(They chose Suk Jin!)
- How could you choose Suk Jin? - Hey!
(Grumbling)
- If you choose me, - Is this a comedian team?
- we're 200 years old in total. - You should've chosen Ji Hyo.
(The members complain.)
What is this, "Old Gang is Back"?
Why did you do that?
(They become the team that brings back memories.)
- You're all so old. - What is it, a room for comedians?
Soo Yong isn't good at talking to strangers.
- He's too shy to talk to strangers. - Get along with the others too.
(They make a team of comedians as Soo Yong is shy.)
This is the worst team ever.
- Can I talk casually? - Sure.
(Hoshi.)
- No, you can't do that. - Why not?
- You can't talk casually. - Why not? Hoshi is younger than me.
(No talking casually)
- Don't talk casually. No. - Why not?
- We should talk formally. - Come on, why not?
(Se Chan wants to keep using the honorifics.)
Talk formally, all right?
These two keep fighting.
I don't want to be on this team.
(Telling on So Min)
She wanted to talk casually, so I said no.
We are going to talk formally to each other.
- Come on. - Be polite to each other.
- He's ruining everything. - Not today.
(Polite Se Chan interrupts her.)
- Do not speak casually. - Okay, now...
- Mingyu and Hoshi, your turn. - It's our turn.
(Mingyu and Hoshi's turn to choose)
I choose Ji Hyo.
(They picked Ji Hyo.)
- Give me a five, Ji Hyo. - This is great.
- You should try to stop Se Chan. - I should?
(While Ji Hyo's amicable team is being completed...)
- Yes, you should. - Kwang Soo...
- Hello. - Last time, he was...
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo leaves to join the team, )
- Give me a five, Ji Hyo. - You should try to stop Se Chan.
(and only one member is left.)
(Deserted)
Last time, he was picked first.
(Left all alone in the corner)
Last time, he was picked first but not today.
(He comes in last even before he joins a team.)
Hey.
Hey, Chalk.
- What? - Chalk.
- What chalk? - Blue chalk.
(A blue chalk)
Do you want to be hit by chalk?
Chalkboard eraser.
(A lonesome blue chalk)
Gosh, do we have to pick him?
(You don't want me?)
Why, because you don't have an option?
- You want to have an option? - No, we want you.
(Disappointed)
- Hey. - I really like you.
Is it okay not to pick him?
Oh, come on!
(The blue chalk joined them by itself.)
Can Kwang Soo eat alone?
- Why would I do that? - It'd be funny.
(Including the blue chalk, they're divided into three teams.)
So today,
you're going to visit old restaurants...
with more than 30 years of history...
("Nopo": An old restaurant that's passed on for generations)
to enjoy their food.
It's called Old Restaurant Race.
("Old Restaurant Race")
More than 30 years?
- We are the old ones. - If Suk Jin and Soo Yong...
enter a restaurant, that makes it an old restaurant.
- We are the old four. - We're like an old restaurant.
(The Old Four)
- What does it mean? - Old...
- Old restaurants. - Right.
Since these two were young comedians,
they were famous for eating unappetizingly.
- Yes, he eats unappetizingly. - I'm serious.
(They both eat unappetizingly.)
He also has a poor appetite.
These two eat like the food doesn't taste good.
(The two oldest members worry the team before the eating mission.)
- I feel bad for Chang Hee. - Serve them well.
When you look for old restaurants,
(When they look for old restaurants, they should follow special rules.)
you should follow special rules.
First, please add up every member's age.
(Add up the age of the teammates!)
- Seriously? Wait a minute. - Gosh.
Adding up the age of you two will make it 110 years old.
(Team Suk Jin's total age is...)
- I'm 39. - And I'm 49.
Then it's 70, 80...
- Then it's 98 and... - 198 in total.
- Our total age is 198. - 198.
Yes, it is 159.
(Ji Hyo 40, So Min 35, Se Chan 35, Hoshi 25, Mingyu 24)
- 159? 159. - Yes, 159.
- Se Chan. - It should be more than that.
(The total age is 159.)
- 159. - It's correct. 159.
I'm 26.
- Add up the age of you two. - You're only 26?
(Add up Bomi and Namjoo's age.)
(Bomi is 28 and Namjoo is 26, so the sum of their ages is 54.)
It's 54.
Okay, 54. I'm 36.
- I'm 45. - You're 36 years old?
54 and 36 is...
(Calculating)
- You can use your cell phone. - That's right.
- 54 and... - Yes.
- Add your age to 90. - 90?
(They end up using the calculator on the phone.)
135. Add it to 135.
I wish I could multiply by zero.
(Jong Kook's team has a hard time adding numbers of double figures.)
- You can't add up the numbers? - It's 95.
It's 42.
- You can't add up numbers? - It's 96.
(Finally done calculating! It's 177!)
It's 177.
- It's 177. - Okay.
We're the oldest.
(With the age of 198)
- We only have 4 members. - And our total age is 198.
(They lack 1 person but they're the oldest.)
Seriously?
It's 198, 177, and 159.
Until 3pm,
(Until 3pm today, )
you're going to have meals at old restaurants you find.
(when they find an old restaurant and eat 1 serving each, )
Subtract the years of the place's history from your team's number.
(the age of the restaurant will be deducted from their total.)
You win when your team's number goes down to zero.
(They win when their team's number goes down to 0.)
- What an original game. - We should visit many places.
(The point is to find restaurants with history quickly.)
- But for us... - It's tougher for us.
(They have to deduct 198 years.)
They should have at least five meals.
(Feeling hopeless)
Five meals.
You should subtract numbers according to the rules.
(First, they will find an old restaurant...)
First, you will find a restaurant with more than 30 years of history.
(with more than 30 years of history.)
(They go through a mission to set the order to subtract the years.)
You go through a mission to set the order to subtract your number.
Starting with the winner, you may subtract as much as you want.
(They will share the years of the restaurant.)
So everyone still has a way to win. Okay.
You will go through a simple mission...
(There will be a mission every time they go to a restaurant.)
to subtract the number of its age from the member's age.
(The order of subtracting the years will be decided then.)
Through the mission, you will decide who will subtract first.
(The 1st place winner of the mission...)
And you may subtract as many as you want.
(gets to subtract his or her years first.)
(A traditional restaurant with 50 years of history)
(Subtracting 15, 4, 1, and 30 years each)
You all start off with your real age.
I'll show you an example.
(They'll be given Age Boards with the age badges attached...)
This is Kim Soo Yong's Age Board.
You may return the badge to us as you subtract your number.
(based on the age of each person.)
- Okay, okay. - Until you're out of badges.
(When they subtract the years, they submit the age badges to the staff.)
This one is Mingyu's. Everyone has one.
Gosh, there are so many.
Their age difference shows a page full of badges.
(The oldest and the youngest have a whole page between them.)
A page full of badges.
- He's as old as his father. - We're at a disadvantage.
Except for the winning team, the other teams will get a penalty.
(The other two teams except for the winning team...)
Two members with most ages from the two teams will get a penalty.
(will have 2 oldest members from each team get the penalty.)
I know who will get a penalty.
(You should work hard to subtract your age to avoid penalty.)
So we're all competitors.
(Catching a glimpse)
Yes, Kwang Soo is on our team.
(The team with Kwang Soo worries.)
No, I won't betray.
Everyone, get in your team's van.
(Now they go to find old restaurants and subtract the years.)
- Let's go! - Yes, let's do this!
- I'm hungry. - Let's go, let's go!
(Team Suk Jin 198, Team Ji Hyo 159,)
- Let's have something delicious. - Let's go, let's go.
(and Team Jong Kook 177)
Ji Hyo.
(Team Ji Hyo gets ready to move.)
Jeon So Min, I'm sitting at the back.
So Min, you shouldn't sit at the back.
I know you want to sit at the back, but you can't.
(So Min wanted to sit at the back!)
- You can't. - Because of Hoshi and Mingyu?
You think I wanted to sit there because of Hoshi and Mingyu?
(Se Chan sits at the back to protect the SEVENTEEN members.)
- But you can't. - Thank you.
- What are you talking about? - You can't.
They should be as comfortable as they can.
I understand why you picked Ji Hyo.
But Hoshi and Mingyu, why did you pick Se Chan?
- It'll be easier when they have me. - He's funny.
- You think Se Chan's funny? - Yes.
(Smiling)
Yes, Hoshi thinks I'm funny.
Se Chan, you know a lot of old restaurants?
- Of course, Ji Hyo. - This is good.
- Here's the basic rule. - He's the best.
(Professor Yang Se Chan tells us how to find old restaurants.)
Hear me out.
If you want to find the oldest restaurants, here's where you go.
- You should go to Jongno. - That's right.
(Amazed at Se Chan)
And if you fail to find one there,
restaurants nearby have a history of 50, 60, and 70 years.
(They can't get their eyes off of Se Chan.)
- I can't believe you. - I'm serious.
How many years of history do Jokbal restaurants in Jangchung-dong have?
- Well, many years I guess. - 50 years, at least.
(They might believe anything that Se Chan tells them.)
And there are hangover soup places near there in Gwanghwamun.
- They have a history of 60 years. - How about kalguksu restaurants?
(Since we have Se Chan...)
- I think we will definitely win. - Kalguksu restaurants are old too.
Three meals will be enough for us.
(The youngest team is relaxed.)
- You're right. - We'll be done quickly.
Here's a list of restaurants that we prepared.
(They're handed the list of old restaurants.)
Please refer to the list.
(But it's up to them to choose where to go.)
- You may call them before you go. - Okay.
- Let's go find these places first. - This one looks good.
- Which place? - Give me a second.
(What is it?)
- What's the name? - Wait.
They serve hangover ramyeon. This is the one.
(H Restaurant, signature menu: tear gas ramyeon)
- Let's go there. - Why?
- They have 45 years of history. - Let's go.
Okay, let's get going.
Gosh, ramyeon restaurant with 45 years of history.
(The SEVENTEEN members burst out laughing whenever Se Chan speaks.)
My goodness.
It's good to have ramyeon as your first meal.
- I love ramyeon. - I love it too.
(They head for the restaurant with the history of immense years.)
So we're playing a game there and...
- the winner gets to subtract age? - You're right.
(They'll share the deducting years in the order of the winner.)
- If they have 35 years of history, - Yes.
you play a game...
(It's advantageous to decrease their individual ages...)
and the winner gets to subtract his or her age as many as 35.
(to avoid the penalty.)
- I got it. - But you should be...
- loyal to the team. - Yes, you're right.
(They have the highest chance to win since they are the youngest.)
I think we have a high chance of winning.
I'll show you how loyal I am to the team.
- It'll end soon. - I can't wait.
(They all promise their loyalty.)
So here's what we're going to do.
When we have meals at the first restaurant,
I think we should even out our ages.
Like I said, I will subtract Ji Hyo's age first.
Because Ji Hyo is the oldest.
(Old girl)
Ji Hyo, this is a game.
- I'm not saying you're old. - But you know what?
(Telling her the harsh truth sneakily)
You are old, but...
- I'm not trying to dis you. - He's a little...
(In this way...)
- condescending. - They're the rules.
If you keep being that way, three of us will team up.
(Se Chan is in high spirits with the SEVENTEEN members on his back)
- See? - I might text Hoshi and Mingyu...
secretly to team up with them.
- Within this team. - But you don't know my number.
- Who? - You.
- What are you doing? - I'm just saying.
You can just give me your number.
- But I don't know your number. - Come on, Mingyu.
(The younger members he trusted keep a distance.)
- Hoshi, will you give your number? - Sure, I will.
- Mingyu? - I will give it to you right now.
- You can, can't you? - I'll give it to you now.
(The three are exchanging numbers.)
- Okay. Let's exchange our numbers. - I'll give it to you.
- This is how we become friends. - Sure.
(Feeling left out)
So Min, why...
I need your number.
- Se Chan. - What?
- Do you like tigers? - What?
I really like tigers.
Thank you.
- Do you like tigers too? - Hoshi.
I was born in the Year of the Tiger.
(She uses her Chinese zodiac sign to win his favor.)
I have a tiger tattoo on here.
I have a tattoo.
(The two women are so into tigers.)
Okay. We all like tigers.
(The woman with tiger sign, The woman with a tiger picture.)
All right.
- Do you like to eat? - Yes.
- I love it. - I'm starving now.
I was talking to Hoshi.
Why are you being so mean to me, Se Chan?
- No, I'm not. - Do you really like me?
Hey.
Stop that!
(So Min blatantly brings up her reasonable doubts.)
Why would you say that in front them?
He's being strange these days. He's trying to avoid me.
- Is he playing hard to get? - Yes.
(Song Ji Hyo, 1st Monday Couple, Is it a change of heart?)
Is that because you have feelings for her?
I guess that's what it is.
(Reacting strongly)
We are close friends.
Why are you avoiding me?
(The woman with the tiger zodiac doesn't back down.)
- Why is that? Why? - Why is he avoiding her?
- So Min... - Ji Hyo, I'll stop making jokes.
- She can't. - When he's like that...
Hey, that's enough.
You can't say such things when the kids are around.
Why are you raising your voice?
That makes me raise my voice too.
Do you think I can't do that?
(Se Chan's patriarchal voice is perfect for the skit.)
If they become a couple, it will be really shocking.
I'll attend their wedding for sure.
I will throw feces at your wedding.
(Beware of the ugly guest.)
You will?
Once our age is reduced,
the hierarchy in our team will change accordingly.
If I get my age deducted,
- Then you'll become younger? - I'll become younger.
(You'll get younger as the numbers get deducted.)
- We become younger just as much. - Okay.
(The hierarchy can change according to the mission results.)
- Then we will... - Do you understand?
- You shouldn't feel bad about that. - Sure.
(Team Ji Hyo arrives at the mission site.)
- Is this it? - I know this restaurant.
- Let's go. - I know this place.
It must be delicious.
(What would the first old restaurant look like?)
It says tear gas ramyeon. It must be really spicy.
- Tear gas? - Yes.
(The restaurant opened in 1972.)
It must be very spicy.
Okay. Let's go!
- Okay. - It must taste good.
(Still retains the appearance of what it used to be.)
(Named as one of the oldest restaurants by Seoul City.)
- This is it. - It says "old restaurant".
It means this place is old.
(ORAEGAGE, Old and Historical Store)
It's been here since 1972.
- Hello. - Hello.
(ORAEGAGE, Old and Historical Store)
Compared to this restaurant, we're so young.
(The restaurant was loved by a lot of student activists.)
We are young.
- This place is older than us. - I know.
(It was like a safe house for them.)
(Its signature menu, tear gas ramyeon is...)
(spicy and refreshing with Cheongyang chili pepper, )
(bean sprouts, and clams.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(The filming was done in accordance with the health guidelines.)
- Hello. Ma'am. - Welcome.
How old is this restaurant?
(What is the history behind this restaurant?)
When did you open this restaurant?
This place looks pretty old.
I'm sorry for asking this all of a sudden.
This restaurant opened in 1972 or 1973.
(The boss)
- Then... - And you've been here all along?
So it's been 47, 48 years.
(It's 49 years old!)
Can we have some ramyeon here?
- What is popular here? - I didn't recognize you.
I'm Yang Se Chan.
What is the best menu?
(Dancing)
What's popular?
- The popular menu? - Yes.
- It must be ramyeon. - Hangover ramyeon.
(The popular menu is the hangover ramyeon.)
Hangover ramyeon?
- Where should we eat? - We will have hangover ramyeon.
- We'll take a seat. - Let's sit here.
I'll sit between the members of SEVENTEEN.
(The old restaurant in Sinchon shows the time of 49 years.)
I can tell this is a traditional place.
This restaurant was here even before I was born.
(The restaurant was here even before Ji Hyo was born.)
Was it 1973?
- In 1973... - It was even before I was born.
Right.
You're in the first restaurant now.
And you can order only one serving.
(You can only order for just one person.)
- Only 1 serving? - 1 serving?
- Can't we eat it all together? - We're done for.
- Only 1 serving? - 1 serving...
Is your signature menu hangover ramyeon?
(They order one hangover ramyeon first.)
- Yes. - We will have...
- 1 serving of hangover ramyeon. - 1 hangover ramyeon.
- Please make it good. - Please make it big.
(They'll be able to eat in accordance with the ranking.)
The winner gets to eat the food first, as much as they want.
Good.
- So this is like the loyalty game. - It's the loyalty game.
- I like that. - I'll show you...
what loyalty is. I'm serious.
I'll relieve my hangover here.
(Everyone can eat if they keep their team spirit.)
I can't do this though. I'm hungry now.
I'm hungry too.
Once you finish one serving,
you can deduct the age of this place from your team age.
(They'll deduct 49 years, which is equivalent to this place's age.)
This place is 49 years old.
This mission is called Rubber Band Game.
(First Mission: Rubber Band Game)
The person who gets more rubber bands on the face...
- in one minute wins the game. - On the face?
(The person who gets more rubber bands on the face...)
On the face?
(in 1 minute wins.)
This might snap.
It sounds difficult. I'm scared.
- Get ready. - I'm ready.
(The first player is Professor Yang Se Chan.)
It's not easy for Se Chan because of his mouth.
It might bounce off. He did it.
(He uses his protruded mouth as an advantage.)
This isn't about time.
Like this.
It hurts.
You're flustered, right?
(The rubber bands are getting tighter.)
It must hurt.
- It must hurt. - My gosh.
- It hurts. - He's got fat under his eyes.
Se Chan.
(The fats become pronounced thanks to the rubber bands.)
This is no joke.
This is...
This feels really strange.
You have 12 bands on your face.
(He breaks out in laughter.)
Should I keep going?
- It's been 30 seconds. - My gosh.
- Hey. - You look good.
- Your face... - No.
- Se Chan, you should stop it. - It hurts.
(They haven't seen anything so shocking for the past 49 years.)
My goodness.
(Se Chan's turn is over.)
- Gosh. - It must hurt a lot.
(It's not easy to get rid of the rubber bands.)
Hang on. I need to put these down.
Wait.
5 and 6.
How do I look? Do I look good?
- Am I handsome? - Yes.
- You look like Voldemort. - What about your chin?
(A handsome guy with the rubber band.)
I'm done.
This is good for blood circulation.
(Se Chan gets 30 bands on as he promotes his blood circulation.)
Good.
I can feel that my blood is circulating.
- Ji Hyo. - Yes.
(The second player is Ji Hyo.)
Ready.
- You have... - There she goes.
plenty of time anyway.
Does it hurt, Ji Hyo?
It must hurt.
This is tighter than I thought.
I know. It's tight.
(Ji Hyo does her best.)
- It looks painful. - You should spread them. Good.
- 15 seconds? - Yes.
That's the last one.
(Ji Hyo tries to wear multiple bands at once.)
Ji Hyo. You're being hasty.
Gosh, Ji Hyo. No!
- I want to eat ramyeon. - Two.
One. Time's up.
- It's done. - Take them off.
(Ji Hyo's turn is over.)
Time's up. Grab the bands.
- You should help her. - My gosh.
Ji Hyo, why are you trying so hard?
No. Please, Ji Hyo.
I think this is good for the text neck syndrome.
(Everyone discovers the benefits of rubber bands.)
Ji Hyo's record is 33.
- My gosh. - The margin is only three.
(Ji Hyo is in 1st place with 33 rubber bands.)
- Oh, no. - What's your record?
- It's 30. - I'm going to eat ramyeon.
She put on 33 bands.
(It's now Love Frog's turn.)
- So Min, get ready. - If you want to do it...
all at once, you should do it toward the end.
Should I do it slowly?
You can take your time for the first 15 pieces.
So Min isn't that pretty.
(Staring sharply at him)
(Se Chan's biting remark upsets the Rubber Band Frog.)
So Min isn't that pretty.
So Min, you look like a painting by Picasso.
I've seen a person who looks just like her.
(She looks like the famous painting.)
There's a comedienne who looks like her.
Stop that.
- I won't let this slide. - She looks artistic.
I think So Min will win this game.
(She proceeds relentlessly even in front of SEVENTEEN.)
You have 10 seconds left.
It hurts!
My goodness. This is crazy.
(You'll go this far?)
Her eyes look funny.
- 5, 4... - So Min, stop it. Please.
(She can't even open her eyes as she wears more rubber bands.)
Two.
- That's it. Take them off. - Time's up.
(So Min's turn is over.)
It counts.
Help me.
Help me!
My gosh. I thought my eyes would pop out.
You thought your eyes would pop out?
(Rubber Band Frog is wailing at an old restaurant.)
It hurts.
- It hurts really bad. - That's true.
Do I have to go this far to eat ramyeon?
How many?
(Rubber Band Frog is leading with her record of 36.)
Seriously, my eyes almost popped out.
I can't do this.
(Hoshi, 18, Mingyu, 22)
- I think I did it wrong. - It really hurts.
Did I win first place?
(1st place, 2nd place, 5th place, 3rd place, 4th place, )
Starting from first place,
you will get rid of your age.
(The age will be deducted according to the rank.)
- I'll... - Are we...
- doing this openly? - No, you should tell me.
(They can deduct a total of 49 years.)
Really?
- I'll... - Okay, So Min.
Let me tell you one thing.
(They'll need to deduct ages to avoid the penalty.)
This isn't the last place.
- This is the beginning. - I'll show you...
what loyalty is.
(Loyalty)
I can give you my age here.
Okay. Go ahead.
I'll show you what loyalty is.
(Tiger Moth is insisting on loyalty today.)
- Ji Hyo, trust me. - Okay.
- Seriously... - I believe you.
- I'll... - I wonder what she's like.
- I'm excited, So Min. - Seriously.
We have 49 years.
(Of 49 years...)
- So I'll... - 30 years?
No. I'll remove only 10 years.
- Are you serious? - Sure.
What's with So Min?
(The fairness spirit only comes out in front of male guests.)
- Okay. - Hey.
I can't betray you guys forever.
(Shouting)
- It's not... - This is nice. I like the peace.
Hang on. I can get rid of a lot of my age then.
- What? - 30?
Here's 10.
(So Min deducts 10 years.)
So Min deducted 10 years.
Of course. This is...
(So Min, 35 years, minus 10 years, 25 years)
Ji Hyo, you're up.
- Deduct as many as you can. - You have 39 years left.
(The age that's left is 39.)
Okay. I'll deduct 20 years.
If I deduct 20 years, and if he deducts 10...
Then we have only 19 years left.
(Ji Hyo, 40 years, minus 20 years, 20 years)
Ji Hyo is 20 now.
Then Ji Hyo is the youngest one here.
I'll be harsh on the youngest member.
I've warned you.
We've already talked about the age and hierarchy.
(The hierarchy will change in accordance with the new age.)
- I'm shaking. - I'll scold her.
If I don't do this,
I'm 100 percent sure Se Chan will do it.
I'm sure Se Chan will use up all the age.
(The Tiger Sisters do not trust Se Chan.)
- I'm very positive. - I won't do that.
So I tried to show you. You wouldn't believe me.
I want to do this in secret.
(He's doing it secretly after talking about loyalty.)
Se Chan, it's your turn.
- I know what's going on. - Even if you do it secretly...
(Everyone knows Se Chan's secret strategy.)
I can tell what's going on.
Hoshi and Mingyu are next.
(The age he can deduct is 19 years.)
He wouldn't do that to SEVENTEEN.
(How many years will he deduct?)
He's just mean to us. Right?
See? Do you hear the sound?
He's busy taking them off.
(Flustered)
I'm just counting them.
- See? He's like a rat. - Hey. You rat.
- I'm done. - Okay.
(Se Chan finished his deduction. Did he keep his loyalty?)
I did it with my conscience. I figured out what to do.
I did this openly on purpose.
- I wasn't supposed to do that. - You have four years left.
Really?
(Se Chan deducted 15 out of 19 years.)
- I wasn't supposed to do that. - Really?
I did it so you'd believe me.
(Hoshi's age depends on Mingyu's choice.)
You should remember that Hoshi is up next.
I'll just do this.
(This is real loyalty. Mingyu deducted only 1 year.)
(Mingyu, 24 years, minus 1 year, 23 years)
You're the last one, Hoshi.
(Hoshi, 25 years, minus 3 years, 22 years)
- You have 3 years left. - 3 years?
Good.
- This is huge. - Give us ramyeon.
(Meanwhile...)
Give us ramyeon.
(the tear gas hangover ramyeon is ready.)
He left some.
- Is this the tear gas ramyeon? - Tear gas ramyeon?
(For the past 49 years, this ramyeon stayed in one place...)
It must be spicy.
(and comforted the hearts of many students.)
So this dish is 49 years old.
- I'll... - We should know that.
I won first place, so I'll take mine first.
(They'll eat ramyeon according to the ranking.)
I don't think Hoshi will need his own dish.
I'll take some bean sprouts.
(She enjoys her privilege as the 1st place winner...)
And she took some clams.
(as she gets bean sprouts and fermented kimchi.)
And kimchi.
Okay. Kimchi.
(Salivating)
- I like kimchi. - It looks good.
I also need some soup.
(She takes some soup out of the bowl.)
Watch your hands.
Pick this up for me.
- Into your plate? - No, into the bowl.
(She doesn't pour that much.)
I don't eat a lot. It's okay.
- Is that it? - Here.
Take this.
- What do you mean? - Eat that.
(This is what you are giving us?)
Have that. This is for me.
- Thank you for the food. - Wait.
(The remaining 4...)
Then Ji Hyo should leave some for us.
- She should share that with you. - You can share that.
(would need to share this.)
This?
That's cool. She sounds tough.
(Slurping)
Okay. So Min, I'll remember that.
Okay.
But when we eat...
(Ji Hyo takes her share too.)
I'm being generous. This is a lot.
(Shameless)
- That's a lot. - Here.
(The best ramyeon in the world...)
- So is this for us? - Yes.
(is taking a bite of someone else's ramyeon.)
- It's good, isn't it? - I should remove it from the shell.
Ji Hyo, you gave them...
Ji Hyo gave them a lot.
Don't get me wrong. It has meat. You can suck it out.
Don't get me wrong, okay? Don't get me wrong.
It has meat. You can suck it out. Don't get me wrong, okay?
(Se Chan gave the others 1 clam with a generous heart.)
- It'll come out. Trust me. - So...
(He's unbelievable.)
I'm not lying. Eat up. It'll come out.
(One bean sprout)
- That's it? - You should give him something.
You have to decide whether to eat the clam or the bean sprout.
I'm done.
(1 clam and 1 bean sprout remaining)
It's really spicy.
I'm going to eat some of the noodles.
- You'll give him the clam? - It really is spicy.
(He puts the bean sprout on top of the clam...)
I knew it. You're giving him only the bean, not the stem.
(and eats it at once.)
Good. How do you like it? Savor it.
(The rich flavor of the clam and the crunchy bean sprout!)
I could taste the soup as I chewed the bean sprout.
- It's crunchy, right? - Try this.
Taste it.
(Something's delivered to Hoshi.)
We followed the rule.
- You have something to eat here. - Can we have a look?
Hoshi, show it to them. It's yours.
(The bean sprout head)
"Share even one piece of bean."
6 of us are sharing 1 bowl of noodles.
(Eating)
- It's good. - Indeed.
Even the bean sprout was seasoned well, right?
I don't think so.
- Ji Hyo is younger than me now. - She's 20 now.
(Current age)
I'm in my 20s.
Ji Hyo is younger than me now.
I'm the youngest among us now.
- Se Chan. Gosh. - Yes, Hoshi.
(So Min, 25, Mingyu, 23, Hoshi, 22, Ji Hyo, 20, Se Chan, 20)
Se Chan, why didn't you leave more food for us?
I'm sorry.
It happened that way.
I ate only one piece of bean.
I'm sorry. But it's actually Mingyu's fault.
- You did wrong too, you brat. - I'm sorry.
You should've left more food for us.
I'll make sure you'll eat more food next time.
You brat, how dare you?
Slack off at the next game.
(Hoshi lost ramyeon and got a younger brother.)
Of course, Hoshi. I'll do as you say.
Ji Hyo, did you enjoy it?
Yes, So Min. It was delicious.
(Polite)
- Ji Hyo, did you enjoy it? - I really enjoyed it.
- Shut it. We're the same age. - Are we the same age?
You two are the same age.
Treat me as a same-age friend. Don't act like you're older than me.
- I didn't do that. - These two are...
(They're friends, but he instinctively speaks honorifics.)
It's because I'm intimidated.
- Let's get going now. - Let's go.
(Team Ji Hyo reduces their age from 159 to 110.)
- Let's go. - We're going to...
(Team Suk Jin with the total age of 198 is leaving.)
Oh, man. This is unbelievable.
This is the worst combination for a team.
We're all so old.
Why must we search for old restaurants?
If we just eat something at a convenience store,
that store would look so old.
Suk Jin, put on your seatbelt.
(The team of oldest members)
I'm putting on my seatbelt, you brat.
Good. The third oldest member should check it.
(What is Team Suk Jin's choice in reducing 198 years of age?)
- Let's go to this restaurant. - Why?
(Jae Suk picks a restaurant in Namdaemun.)
B restaurant at Namdaemun Market, Jung-gu.
It sounds like an old restaurant.
- What food do they serve? - What kind of food?
(Menu)
- Noodles. If they have bulgogi, - Oh, noodles?
(Pyongyang naengmyeon restaurant...)
- they have naengmyeon too. - They serve naengmyeon.
(with 60 years of history)
Pyongyang naengmyeon?
It says it's a 60-year-old restaurant.
Do you like naengmyeon?
(Out of nowhere)
Of course, I like naengmyeon. I'm a big fan.
(Of course.)
You can make the noodles for naengmyeon, right?
How can I make noodles?
That's what Soo Yong's jokes are like.
(Soo-DRAGON's dad jokes are groundless.)
- I know. - What else?
- Strawberry milk. - How to make strawberry milk.
(Soo-DRAGON's joke series 1, strawberry milk)
Make the cow blush.
(How to make strawberry milk: Make the cow blush.)
So that you can get strawberry milk.
(Turn its body red and milk it.)
That's how you make strawberry milk.
Even his jokes are old-fashioned.
- Right. - That's funny.
I used to make people laugh with my jokes.
(I used to make people laugh with my jokes.)
People would laugh so hard that they couldn't keep it together.
(He offers a piece of old joke...)
(calmly.)
Chang Hee is nice, right?
I haven't had a chance to get to know him.
Chang Hee is much nicer than you.
- That means he's really nice. - I thought so.
(Surprised)
He's really nice.
(Ji Suk Jin, a nice guy)
Soo Yong, you know what I mean, right?
That means he's really nice.
To survive this long without the ability to talk funny,
(All he has is his upright character.)
you must have a good personality.
(Suk Jin and Chang Hee survived with their upright character.)
- Chang Hee is nice... - Chang Hee.
(Complimenting)
and perfect in every way.
- He's also hard-working. - I see.
But he lacks the ability to talk funny.
That's okay.
Chang Hee, let me ask you a question.
- Sure. - When Cho Sae Ho became popular,
you got a little jealous of his success, right?
(Slandering as usual)
- I'll be honest with you. - Tell me honestly.
I didn't feel jealous at all.
- Really? - Yes.
- I was happy for my friend. - Of course.
(Chang Hee's an angel.)
- I never felt jealous. - There's no way he got jealous...
- Soo Yong. - because he cut ties with Sae Ho.
(He makes an old joke when they're about to forget it.)
- They don't see each other now. - Gosh, seriously.
- They still see each other. - I'm going to meet him...
(Sae Ho and Chang Hee are true friends.)
- after the shoot. - Soo Yong.
Have you ever felt jealous of Suk Jin's success?
Of course, I'm jealous.
(That's obvious.)
(Soo-DRAGON won't hide how he really feels.)
Why? You're jealous too.
Why would he be?
- Jae Suk, aren't you jealous? - Why would he?
Jae Suk, aren't you jealous?
- Why would he be? - He became more successful than me.
(Why is Jae Suk jealous?)
You know he's more successful.
- I bet he's jealous despite that. - No way.
(Even if you're successful, you still get jealous.)
What he just said was so funny.
When Kim Yong Man was popular, I didn't watch his shows.
(Reminiscent)
I know.
- Really? - Yes.
(Together, it brings back memories.)
- In the early years of my career, - Yes?
although Soo Yong and I debuted in the same year...
- You didn't watch his shows, right? - No, I didn't.
- Of course. - It because I was upset.
- It's not that I was jealous. - You wanted to be on TV too.
I was just upset and afraid I might want to be on the show too.
I understand.
- I didn't want to feel that way. - You see, Jae Suk would...
If it had not been for "Talk Box"...
If it had not been for that show,
Jae Suk would be running a business now.
It's because he was cast on the show when his career was precarious.
(They can laugh off because they're both successful.)
- It was... It's the same for me. - That's true.
- I haven't come here in a while. - Namdaemun Market.
(They're near Namdaemun Market.)
(The place full of memories from when they were rookies)
I used to come here often to buy stage outfits.
You shopped here too, right?
When we were younger, we didn't work with stylists.
(They had to get their own clothes for shows when they were rookies.)
I used to come here with other comedians...
- That's right. - to buy a suit.
I haven't been here for a long time.
(They're glad to come to Namdaemun Market because of old memories.)
These stores must have been here for almost 50 years.
- It's nice. - We could complete the mission...
(The team of oldest members goes well with Namdaemun.)
- in this area. - Absolutely.
If we visit a few restaurants here...
(The restaurant is located between old clothing stores.)
- "B" restaurant. We're here. - This is it.
- Such places are hidden like this. - Let's go.
(It's a popular Pyongyang naengmyeon restaurant at Namdaemun Market.)
I can see the history of the restaurant.
(It's known for jeon and chewy noodles.)
(The wall is covered with the traces of past years.)
(The market merchants have been quenching...)
(their hunger here for a long time.)
My, it's nice.
That bindaetteok looks so delicious.
(Crispy mung bean pancake is a bonus!)
They've been running this restaurant here for 60 years?
(Light, but savory Pyongyang naengmyeon combo)
- Sanitize your hands, everyone. - Okay.
Let's eat something.
(They're ready to accept the old restaurant.)
- You're here now. - Yes.
- But we did some research. - Yes.
Three generations have been running this restaurant...
- for 60 years, - Yes.
but they registered the business in 1984.
(They registered the business in 1984.)
So it's 37 years old.
(So it's 37 years old in the record.)
- Gosh. That's ridiculous. - You can't do that.
They've been running this place for 60 years. Then why...
(Come on.)
But we don't have any evidence to prove it.
(Running Man relies on accurate information.)
They've been running the restaurant with the same name for 60 years.
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
(They call the owner for help.)
We heard this is a 60-year-old restaurant. Is it true?
It's 60 years old, right?
In what year did you open this restaurant?
(Please tell us it's been 60 years.)
My grandmother-in-law started the business...
around the time when Korea was liberated from Japan.
(See?)
- See? It's been 60 years. - Back then...
You can prove it, right?
(Of course.)
- It's a family business. - Exactly.
- Then we... - It's as old as Namdaemun Market.
- Exactly. - That's what I'm saying.
Then to be fair, we'll meet you halfway.
- Oh, yes. - That sounds fair.
- Oh, I see. - Then 48 years...
(They agree to settle...)
(with 48 years, which is between 60 and 37 years.)
- It has a 23-year gap, so... - We'll settle for 48 years.
- 48 years. - All right.
If you look at the owner's watch...
- Her watch is from "R" brand. - Why would you say that?
- That wasn't necessary. - I'm surprised.
(History of Namdaemun shines in her wrist.)
You could've put it this way.
We can tell how successful...
(Don't say it directly.)
- this restaurant has been... - Yes.
- only by looking at the owner. - Exactly.
(The owner's wrist guarantees the taste.)
You can tell how tasty their food is to attract a lot of customers.
All your children studied overseas, right?
- What? - That's what they usually do.
(Suk Jin thinks successful restaurants...)
Why would you ask if her children studied overseas?
(send their children to study overseas.)
- Thank you, ma'am. - Thank you.
(Thanks to the owner for her cooperation.)
- We'll order food later. Thank you. - Okay.
You can deduct 48 years from your ages.
(They can reduce 48 years.)
We'll begin the game to decide the order.
(Here's the mission to decide the order of age reduction.)
It's Age Based on Physical Ability.
(Team Suk Jin's first mission)
(Age Based on Physical Ability)
You will take a three-step biological age test.
(They will take a 3-step biological age test.)
I'm not good at things like that.
I don't have a flexible body.
You'll be ranked in the order of your biological ages.
I'm not good at things like this because I'm not flexible.
(Worried)
- Same here. - My body is not flexible at all.
- I can't do things like this. - Let's begin the first step.
(The youngest 39-year-old is advantageous.)
(Put your arms together and raise them.)
- Oh, gosh. - Tell them how to do it.
If your elbows are above your eyes like this,
- you're in your 20s. - That's too hard for me.
30s up to your nose, 40s up to your lips,
and 50s if your face is invisible.
- If my face is invisible? - Take turns to try it.
(The elbows must meet. Jae Suk will start first.)
- You don't get to practice. - Jae Suk.
- Shall I go first? - Okay.
My body is not very flexible.
(The physical age of MC Yoo who takes good care of himself is...)
- Doing this alone is hard for me. - Exactly.
Gosh, I can't do it.
- Hey, that's it? - His arms are apart.
(Arms)
- Hey, that's it? - His arms are apart. Look at that.
Gosh, I can't do it.
(His arms are shaking, and his face is not visible.)
- Hey, that's it? - His arms are apart.
- I couldn't see his face. - I can't do this.
- He failed. - You're in your 50s.
(Jae Suk's physical age is in 50s.)
- You're in your 50s. - I'll aim to be in my 40s.
- You're in your 50s. - Gosh, seriously.
(I think I have a chance to win.)
Okay. I'll aim to be in my 40s.
(I'll beat Jae Suk.)
- Gosh, seriously. - I'm keeping my arms together.
(His ready position looks perfect.)
- Right? - Yes.
(What could be the biological age of the confident Suk Jin?)
(Struggling)
I think his biological age is over 70.
(He can't do any better than Jae Suk.)
(His arms went up 3cm and stopped.)
I think his biological age is over 70.
(Laughing)
(I'll get to eat naengmyeon.)
Your arms are apart.
(His biological age is over 70.)
(But he's still a teenager at heart.)
- He can't lift his arms at all. - I can't do it.
- You're in your 50s. - It's because I'm not flexible.
(Suk Jin's physical age is in 50s.)
It's a piece of cake.
(Happy)
- Easy-peasy. - Yes, indeed.
- You try it. - You can just show your chin.
(What's Soo Yong's physical age?)
- Exactly. - Try it.
Your lips are visible for now.
His lips are visible?
(He barely shows his mouth and secures 40s.)
Your nose is almost visible.
- It's hard. - I think that's the best he can do.
- The lips. - Over 40?
(Soo Yong's physical age is in 40s.)
- Yes, he's over 40. - Gosh.
- It's Chang Hee's turn. - All right.
(High expectation on the youngest 39-year-old Chang Hee)
Nam Chang Hee
- I am Nam Chang Hee - All right.
(Shaking)
What's wrong with him?
What's wrong with him? His biological age is over 60.
- Wait. Just a little higher. - Hey.
(Chang Hee's physical age is in 50s.)
You're in your 50s.
- My gosh. - Chang Hee.
I'm disappointed.
(He should be flexible at 39.)
I thought you were quite flexible.
I can move fast, but my body is not flexible.
(That's new.)
- You can move fast? - Yes, I'm fast.
- His biological age is over 50? - You're over 50, 50, 40, and 50.
(Soo Yong did better than expected.)
- It was the first step. - My gosh.
- It was the first step. - I can't do it.
(The team of oldest members complains.)
- Let's move on. - You came in first.
- Let's begin the second step. - Why are my arms shaking?
(Jump Rope With Your Arms)
- It's jump rope with your arms. - I can't do that.
- What? - I see.
With your hands locked in front of your body,
(With your hands locked in front of your body, )
you have to pass them under your legs and hips.
(you have to pass them under your legs and hips.)
Pass them under my legs?
If you fail at your feet, you're over 50, at your legs, over 40,
at your hips, over 30, and if you succeed, you're over 20.
Some of us have a chronic disease.
- I have back problems. - I was born...
- to be inflexible. - That's ridiculous.
I couldn't do things like this even when I was a teenager.
I couldn't do it when I was in the military either.
(Complaining)
- We're not flexible. - Can we do something else?
They're complaining a lot because they're quite old.
It's not like that.
(Did you say we're quite old?)
- Listen to me. - Why won't you stop complaining?
- Just do it. - Fine. Let's begin.
And then legs...
(The youngest Chang Hee goes first.)
(He passed one foot easily.)
Could he pass it under his leg?
What happens if he succeeds?
He's made it to the age group between 40 and 49.
(His feet went over his arms.)
- He stopped at his hips. - That's it.
- Can't you pass the hips? - Gosh, I can't do it.
(Chang Hee's physical age is in 30s.)
- You're in your 30s. - I'm in my 30s.
- It's your actual age. - Yes, it's my actual age.
(He's proud to be close to his actual age.)
I'm in my 30s. This is how it's done.
If you can't pass your knees...
(The next player forces himself to be energetic.)
- If you... - What is he doing?
What is he doing? Suk Jin, what's this?
(He stretches in an old style.)
- Put them up! - I'm trying to make them flexible.
- That's an old-fashioned way. - Okay.
- I'll give it a try. - I can only pass one leg.
(One foot easily goes through.)
- Okay. - A foot is out.
You seem flexible enough.
(If the other foot goes through, he'll at least be in his 40s.)
Your hands must stay clasped.
(Why can't you step over that hands that are in front of you?)
It's like watching a baby walk for the first time.
(With silly movements, )
(he falls to the floor.)
It can't be done.
Your biological age is in its 50s.
(Suk Jin's body age is in its 50s.)
- You try it. - Unbelievable.
But this...
- My two legs... - Just you wait and see.
(Getting confident after watching Suk Jin)
I may be stiff and have a sore back,
- but both legs will go through. - Gosh, this is...
Since you're on the older side...
(Putting one foot easily)
- Your foot grazed your hands. - Hold on a second.
- See? - You can't do it either.
- He can't do it. - No way.
(See?)
Jae Suk, seriously?
What...
I may be stiff and have a sore back, but both legs will go through.
(He was confident up until a minute ago.)
- He can't do it either. - I should be able to do this.
(He hops on one leg...)
- He can't do it. - No way.
Jae Suk, seriously?
- You can't... - You worked out for nothing!
My gosh.
(and ends up destroying the property.)
Your biological age is in its 40s.
(Jae Suk's body age is in its 50s.)
- This isn't accurate though. - I'm quite stiff.
- This is about being flexible. - I'm not flexible at all.
(They file a complaint again.)
But that adds to your biological age.
- One must be flexible for this. - That's true,
(Flexibility is also part of one's body age.)
- but it's not crucial. - Okay.
- All right. - Hold on.
Is Yogi Daniels in his teens then?
- Yogi Daniels. - Who's that?
(Yogi Daniels, 10 years old in physical age)
He's over 60, you know.
- This is ridiculous. - Yogi Daniels can do this.
I told you that I'm not flexible.
(His mental age is probably still in its teens.)
Do I put my leg through?
(Last up is Soo-DRAGON.)
Both legs must go through.
(He also puts one foot easily.)
- Like this? - He'll probably manage both legs.
I guess he can't.
Seriously?
- Hey. Can't you do it? - In some ways,
this isn't all that bad.
They're all just as bad.
- This is a mess. - There isn't much of a difference.
(It's a mess, and nothing works well here.)
In sports events, there's the group of death.
Meanwhile, this is paradise.
I'm in paradise.
Next, you will hold the V-sit for 10 seconds.
(Holding the V-sit for 10 seconds)
- Sit with your arms out front. - Okay.
(The body age will be measured by the angle of the legs.)
- Lift your two legs. - This I can do.
Come on.
(The result of Stage 3)
See? Look!
(50s, 50s, 20s, and 30s)
- No way. That's not it. - Let's check our sugar levels.
(Soo Yong 36.6 years, Jae Suk 43.3 years, )
Or our blood pressure.
- Blood pressure... - Must we go that far?
(Chang Hee 43.3 years, and Suk Jin in his 50s)
You'll shed years off your age starting with whoever came first.
(Soo Yong will subtract his years 1st.)
Soo Yong, you're up.
You won the game, so take at least 15 years.
(They can tolerate up to 15 years.)
You're on the older side, so you need to shed a lot of it.
(Calmly taking the years off)
Hold on. Soo Yong?
(Nothing can be heard except the sound of the Velcro tape.)
I hear a ripping sound.
- I know. - Soo Yong...
(He asked if he can take off 12 badges, )
Do I rip off at least 12?
(yet his hand moves constantly.)
6, 7, 8...
You're still only at eight?
It's all right.
What's taking you so long?
- How many are you ripping off? - 12.
(In a heap)
- 12. - Just 12?
(He subtracts 35 years.)
What took you so long though?
(Pretending ignorance after removing a lot of badges)
- It's not easy. - It seemed like more.
- Am I next? - I only discarded 12.
(Jae Suk goes second.)
- I'll tell you how much is left. - Sure.
I ripped off 12.
(Soo Yong shed 35 years off a total of 48.)
- I ripped off 12. - Are you kidding me?
- How sly of you. - Why?
(Kim Soo Yong, currently 20 years old)
I'll shed off the amount I promised.
(Jae Suk sheds 12 years off.)
- You know how much. - 12 years?
(Chang Hee sheds none, and Suk Jin subtracts 1 year.)
You've got to be kidding me.
You're 20 now.
(Ages after subtracting)
- Not even Kwang Soo would do this. - Exactly.
The food's here.
Thank you.
(Feeling rejuvenated, )
In the order you finished the game in,
(they now taste Pyongyang naengmyeon of the 60-year-old restaurant.)
you'll take as much food as you want.
Take as much as you want with your spoon.
- I mean, with your chopsticks. - Sure.
- Pass me the vinegar. - I'm dying to try some.
(Soo Yong is up first.)
I'll only take a quarter.
That's considerate of you.
(He subtracted a lot of years...)
(but takes a decent amount of naengmyeon.)
But it's not much.
- That's a quarter. - You only get one turn.
Sure.
That's kind of you.
(Kim Soo Yong, has a small appetite, a rare character in Running Man)
This isn't something you see on Running Man every day.
(Jae Suk goes next.)
(It's obvious that he's planning to take a lot.)
- Hey. - What?
Be considerate.
(A heap)
(This is what we normally see on Running Man.)
Soo Yong should've eaten more.
(Chang Hee goes 3rd.)
- Take a heap. - Can one scrape the edge?
(He uses a ladle to secure his noodles.)
- There you go. - Okay.
Get some of the broth too.
That I can give him.
(Here you go.)
Do you know why he's being generous?
He doesn't favor Pyongyang naengmyeon.
Unbelievable.
(Ji Suk Jin, the taste of a child, still not familiar with this taste)
- I thought he was being kind. - You probably did.
He's not that kind of guy.
Let's try the broth.
(Jae Suk is a well-known noodle lover.)
(Thanks to him, the naengmyeon seems delicious.)
(Meanwhile, Soo Yong is known to make food seem unappealing.)
(Just so you know, this is him enjoying the food.)
(Then there's Suk Jin who doesn't like Pyongyang naengmyeon.)
I can smell the beef broth.
This is delicious.
I'd like some bindaetteok.
(Don't.)
- Don't order him any. - Of course not.
You need to choose your next destination.
(They are somewhat unsatisfied with the meal except for Suk Jin.)
- We... - Yes?
- We had noodles. - Since we had noodles,
(They had noodles 1st.)
we should get some meat.
(Going for meat for 2nd?)
Let's eat a meat dish.
- Pork galbi takes long to cook. - That sounds good.
(I like pork galbi.)
- It takes long to cook. - What do you say?
(Quickly served)
- Hangover soups. - How about a hangover soup?
What about this C restaurant?
That's the one...
where people from the Kim Du Han era used to eat.
- Then it's been around for long. - The C restaurant...
(The oldest restaurant of all)
- opened in 1937. - See?
(It opened in 1937.)
- That's the one. - Let's go there next.
(They can deduct 84 years.)
- Since 1937. - Just so you know,
- it's nearby. - That's right.
(They call the restaurant first.)
Hello, this is Restaurant C.
Hello, it's a pleasure.
- Sure. - You see,
we're filming Running Man,
- and I'm Ji Suk Jin. - Yes, hello.
- Why would he introduce himself? - Yes, hello.
- She's not excited though. - Could we perhaps...
film there for a short while while we eat?
(Revealing his identity wasn't effective at all.)
- At this hour? - Yes.
Let me ask my boss first.
Can you leave your phone number?
My number...
(Failing to ask the proper questions...)
- My number... - Yes?
(leads him to revealing his own phone number.)
- Just a second. - Say you'll call back in 10.
(Chang Hee steps in to solve it.)
I'll call you back in five minutes.
- Sure, in five minutes. - Got it.
(The minute-long call was fruitless.)
Sure.
Are you kidding me?
Who calls a restaurant like that?
- I got to the point, didn't I? - But...
(Brazen)
- That's not... - I got to the point.
You should've asked when the restaurant opened first.
(He applied none of his experience in the last 1 minute.)
- We already know that. - Ask what dishes they sell.
Also, why...
- would you reveal your identity? - We'll have boiled pork slices.
Suk Jin identified himself,
but she wasn't that excited to hear from him.
("Yes. Hello.")
- She didn't seem pleased. - She was only being polite.
(The employee didn't respond as Suk Jin expected.)
That's what it was.
I see you don't know.
- "I'm Ji Suk Jin..." - I'm sure she danced in joy.
(As she answered...)
She danced in joy?
She must have.
She sounded calm,
(Suk Jin's secret to feeling young is his infinite optimism.)
but she was dancing with joy.
Suk Jin's hilarious.
It's seolleongtang, so how can it not taste good?
(He gives up calling them.)
(The dish)
- It's seolleongtang, right? - No, hangover soup.
- It's the same. - With intestines.
- They have it all. - Seolleongtang?
- Right. - Then we're good.
- Suk Jin can't eat those dishes. - What?
He can't eat intestine soup.
- I can't eat clotted blood. - What a picky eater.
- Suk Jin... - He...
(He requires a great deal of care as he was raised like a prince.)
- He was raised like a prince. - He's the worst.
- He never ate these things. - Did I have to be on this team?
- Suk Jin. - Clotted blood...
It's too disgusting.
Doesn't Restaurant C...
have a kid's meal?
He can have the kid's meal instead.
(Pork cutlet for kids suits Suk Jin's taste.)
Or we could order from another restaurant.
- We'll have it delivered. - He's the worst.
(Team Suk Jin still has 150 years of age.)
(They move to the next restaurant hoping for a lucky shot.)
We'll have assorted boiled pork slices.
- Sure, let's get searching. - Think about...
(Meanwhile, Team Jong Kook with the total age of 177 is...)
- what we mentioned earlier. - That's right.
We can find many old restaurants in Jongno and Myeong-dong.
(They target Jongno and Myeong-dong.)
- Myeong-dong and Jongno. - Right.
Ever since the Kim Du Han days...
(They search the nearby restaurants first.)
Type in "50 years", and you'll get a whole list.
Toegye-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul.
Guys, Restaurant M...
- has been open for 50 years. - See?
- Let's go. - Let's go there.
- It opened in 1966. - That's right.
(A 55-year-old kalguksu restaurant that opened in 1966)
The food there is delicious.
- I love this place. - Let's go.
(They depart right away to deduct 55 years.)
So right now, Namjoo is...
- I'm 26. - Right, 26.
So let's all match her age first.
Must we do it this way though?
- Match what? - You're being selfish already.
(They're already focused on deducting their own ages.)
Why should we match our ages first?
You'll only betray us later.
- Why would we betray you? - Earlier,
as soon as he heard the rules,
(Lee Kwang Soo, a tattletale)
he told Jong Kook his idea while grinning.
- That's what I hate the most. - That's not the case.
What's the main rule anyway?
- I still don't get the game. - Me neither.
- All I want to do is eat. - Guys.
Okay, then. How about this?
- We'll match ours to Kwang Soo's. - Okay, that sounds good.
(How about matching their ages to Kwang Soo's?)
Is that okay with you two?
Why do we need to level our ages though?
Because...
(I don't know either.)
- We don't know the rules. - Too much of an age gap...
The oldest two will receive the penalty.
(They want to match their ages to shorten the difference.)
- I see. - The oldest two.
I'm sorry to say this,
but we've repeated this way too many times.
- We'll explain it one last time. - Let me explain.
As you know, we...
(Professor Kim lectures them on age.)
- First... - The restaurant's 55 years old.
(55-year-old Myeong-dong restaurant, 36-year-old Kwang Soo)
Minus nine years, and I'll be Kwang Soo's age.
(45-year-old Jong Kook deducts 9 years to make 36.)
- What about you? - In my case...
- We're 6 years apart. - Yes, 6.
(42-year-old Haha deducts 6 years to make 36.)
- That's what you'll shed. - I have an idea.
Spare us 15 years from 55 first.
(He's saying he and Haha can make Kwang Soo's age...)
That'll level our age with Kwang Soo's.
(if they're given 15 years.)
Then we'll have 30 years to share among us.
(Contemplating)
- We'll share the 30 years. - Then we'll divide it evenly.
- You two will be safe. - Only in the first round.
(Their promise)
- Only at first? - We won't challenge you yet.
(Give us 15 years first to even out the ages among us.)
Let us match Kwang Soo's age first.
- Sure thing. - Are we good?
- Then 15 years each... - Yes.
No, not each. Just 15 years in total.
(Jong Kook's lecture was all for nothing.)
Let us take just 15 years in the first round.
We'll match our age only to Kwang Soo's.
As you know, I like to play fair.
(He did his best to explain, )
I play fair too when I need to be.
(but the girls don't seem to have understood.)
- He... - I play fair until I'm provoked.
- We'll match ours with Kwang Soo's. - That will come to bite you.
- Just with Kwang Soo. - You know how he is.
(But Kwang Soo doesn't want them to lower their ages.)
A weasel like him makes us all suffer a loss.
- Shedding 11 years each is fair. - We need to...
(Evenly among 5 people)
level our age with Kwang Soo's.
What do you mean by shedding 11 years?
The restaurant has been around for 55 years.
- And there are 5 of us. - 11 years, 11 years...
(She pauses every time there's a number.)
- 11 years, 11 years... - I get it now.
- 11 years, 11 years... - Hold on a second.
The girls are absolutely clueless.
I'm pretty sure that...
siding with you today won't benefit me at all.
Just don't do anything, all right?
(He tells them to stay still for not knowing the rules.)
No matter how much we explain it, we can't get through to them.
- I get it now. - You need to understand this.
- I get it now too. - Just eat whatever is served.
(Giving up)
That means we need to compete against each other.
- That's right. - 11 years, 11 years...
- I get it now. - If you can be kind enough to...
(Still trapped in the circle of 11)
Are you still calculating the years?
So 11 years each.
- What... - No, not 11 years each.
I'm sorry, but can we stop talking for a second?
I'm getting woozy.
(Complaining of motion sickness)
- I want you to trust us. - I'm curious though.
Why are we even in teams?
- What? - This isn't some competition.
- It's a single player game. - How are we competing right now?
We're trying to make sure the team wins.
(It's a strategy to win as a team.)
- This is just our strategy. - All right, then.
If we're in it to win it,
please explain the rules clearly to me one last time.
Please explain the rules clearly to me one last time.
(Another explanation?)
You've got to be kidding me.
Are you serious? She really is clueless.
(Bomi is trapped in the game's rule.)
Just eat the food that's presented to you...
and receive the penalty at the end.
This isn't complicated, but she just doesn't get it.
(The older members are frustrated.)
Why are you trying...
- to shed years off your age? - Okay, listen up.
- Why shed the years? - So our team members...
(The age)
(Dispirited)
- have a collective age of 177. - Unbelievable.
Bomi, why did you come here?
(They keep going back to the time before they heard the rules.)
- Do you know this is Running Man? - To eat.
- She's just pretending. - I'll explain to you.
- There? - Deduct 65 years...
(He explained the game rule only for Bomi for a while.)
You mean, the age badges, not my actual age?
(The endless struggle to understand the rules continues.)
That's correct.
- It's your actual age. - It's your actual age.
- But if you don't deduct... - That's what I said.
(Screaming)
(Complaining of abnormal symptoms)
I've become claustrophobic.
(He passed out.)
- I'm serious. - Bomi, seriously.
(Bomi can't seem to understand the rules forever.)
I bet Bomi is still trying to figure it out.
(What will be the fate of Team Jong Kook?)
- No. I understand the rule now. - But actually...
I haven't been here in a long time.
(Myeong-dong)
- We should put on a mask now. - Okay.
(Each of them has memories of Myeong-dong.)
I haven't come to Myeong-dong in a really long time.
- We're here. - This is it.
(Established in 1966)
- All right. - Oh, my.
(This is a popular kalguksu and dumpling restaurant.)
(Their kimchi is as famous as their kalguksu.)
(Many tourists also visit the place as it's located in Myeong-dong.)
It smells so good. I'm excited.
(It's a popular destination for both locals and tourists.)
Oh, my.
It looks so delicious.
(They smell the broth as soon as they enter the restaurant.)
- Was there a place like this here? - Hello.
It was easy to find.
Where should we sit?
- You arrived at your first place. - Yes.
(Team Jong Kook arrives at their first restaurant.)
- I'm so excited to eat here. - This restaurant is very famous.
They opened up another location in Los Angeles too.
(According to Jong Kook, it must be good if it's also in LA.)
- What's most shocking is... - Really?
(In this restaurant...)
It's also one of the good things about this restaurant.
You can eat as much rice as you want.
- It's free. - That's great.
- Am I right, sir? - I love rice.
(He asks the staff.)
- It's great. - Only when you order noodles.
- I see. We should order noodles. - Yes.
I wasn't saying that we'll only eat free rice here.
- We wouldn't do that. - We won't just ask for free rice.
(He must have watched Running Man.)
Of course, we'll order food.
- We're not that kind of people. - Why would we do that?
(It's time to check the history of the restaurant...)
(from the staff.)
Could you tell us about the history of the restaurant?
- It was established in 1966. - In 1966?
(It's a 55-year-old restaurant. It was established in 1966.)
- Suk Jin was born in that year. - Exactly.
(1996?)
- It's the same age as Suk Jin. - That's right.
(This restaurant...)
- In 1966? - Yes.
(Suk Jin can now be friends with this old restaurant.)
You don't know what month it was, right? I bet Suk Jin is older.
- He was born in February. - In the beginning of the year.
- When you finish eating here, - Yes.
(After they have a meal in this restaurant, )
(they can earn 55 years.)
you can deduct 55 years, the age of this place,
- from your ages. - Okay.
But it's so unfair. Is being old a sin?
Of course, it's not.
(Suddenly?)
Then why would you come up with a rule like this?
The idea alone can...
(The men in their 40s suddenly pick a fight.)
- make older people... - Must Suk Jin die then?
It can make older people upset.
- I mean, is being old a sin? - It's okay.
Do you think you will never be my age?
(Too immersed)
That's why we're giving you a chance to get your age deducted.
- What I'm saying is... - I know.
that the members of our team...
- reached an agreement. - Haha.
You sound so bossy right now.
- The tone of his voice... - I am talking right now!
- It's not like that. - He sounds even bossier than me.
What's with you? What has gotten into you?
(Goosebumps)
- We'll get 25 years. - Doesn't his hat look like...
(Even his hat suggests how old-fashioned he is.)
- a traditional hat called gamtu? - And we'll divide...
(He's an old-fashioned man with old values.)
the remaining 30 years.
The remaining 30 years.
- What happened to him? - I can't believe him.
(Shocked)
He's so bossy. He's much bossier than me.
(Haha was once one of the young members.)
He used to have a young mind.
- We'll let you make that decision. - Okay.
(He is now one of the old farts.)
Then I have no problem.
Wait. What was the rule? 1, 2, 3, and 4.
(Abruptly)
(Bomi abruptly starts talking...)
- No dividing by the same number. - Correct.
(and brings up the rules.)
For example, 2, 4, and 8. Or...
Bomi, I think you're explaining it because you're embarrassed.
No, that's not the reason.
All right. I'll explain...
(The first mission to the team who's trying to understand the rules.)
about the game you'll play.
You'll play the same game you played on Jeju Island...
(It's a mission from Jeju Island that embarrassed everyone.)
and gained the worst result.
It's Half Proverb Quiz.
- It was really difficult. - Proverb?
We'll tell you the latter part of the proverb.
(They must try to complete a Korean proverb...)
You have to complete the sentence in three seconds.
(by listening to the latter half of the proverb.)
- This never has a peaceful day. - That's easy.
- What... - It's easy.
My family never has a peaceful day.
- Hey. - What's the answer?
(Even the knowledgeable members couldn't do well.)
- A tree with many branches. - Oh, right. I know that proverb.
- I don't know many proverbs. - But...
It was difficult.
- I don't know many proverbs. - But I think I have a chance.
He's right. We have a chance to win.
- The smart ones are not here. - I think...
(But among these members, they suddenly become confident.)
- I can beat them. - We have a chance to win.
- I don't know many proverbs. - I'm begging you...
- Bomi and Namjoo should go first. - I don't know any proverbs.
(Cutting off)
Proverbs...
(As everyone is losing confidence...)
- Kwang Soo should go first. - Okay.
- No. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- I don't agree... - The winner gets to eat, right?
The winner gets to eat food...
- and gets the age... - Get the age deducted?
Bomi, come on. Please.
I'm done for.
(Bomi, who finally understood the rules will go first.)
Give me the question.
- Bomi, - Bomi.
- we'll begin now. - Okay.
Move to Gangnam.
- 3, 2... - I move to Gangnam.
(Confident)
One.
(It's more of a declaration than a proverb.)
- That was good. Next. - My gosh.
(Going to Gangnam along with friends.)
- Gosh. I really don't know. - That was good.
This never has a peaceful day.
- Three. - Well...
- Two. - I never have a peaceful day.
(Again?)
Her answer always starts with "I".
(The wind never sets on a tree with many branches.)
- I'm worried. I can't just laugh. - Kwang Soo, why...
Let's move on. Keep going.
But you don't know how giyeok looks.
- You look at a sickle. - Correct.
(She finally gets it correct.)
You stay up all night.
- Well... - During the exam period.
During the exam period, you stay up all night.
(She falls for Kwang Soo's bait.)
(Is this not correct?)
- Frying beans. - "Frying beans"?
- Using cooking oil. - Two.
"Frying beans"?
(Cooking oil is a must when stir-frying beans.)
- Using cooking oil. - Two.
- Beans? - One.
- You eat and fry beans? - Wrong.
(Eating rice?)
"You eat and fry beans"?
(Frustrated)
- I'm relieved that she's here. - Frying beans with lightning?
- Yes, that's correct. - Okay.
(They can't laugh out loud as Bomi is doing her best.)
It's so difficult because we hear only the half.
It's confusing.
(Everyone's arguing how hard this mission is.)
- It's hard to guess the front half. - Exactly.
But she did a good job.
(Bomi gets 1 correct.)
- It's difficult. - Is it Jong Kook's turn?
(It's now Jong Kook's turn.)
- Me? - Yes.
(Jong Kook was embarrassed as he got none correct.)
Give me some easy questions.
- Let's begin. - Okay.
And pull yourself together. Three.
- Empty your stomach? - Two.
- One. - Jong Kook.
(Oh. right. Cold water.)
Are you serious?
I mean...
(Now she can flash a big smile.)
You won't be the worst.
- 3, 2... - If you don't say anything.
- Correct. - What?
The taste of the sauce.
- 3, 2... - What? The taste of the sauce...
(He mutters as he's flustered.)
- One. - The longer you store the sauce...
- Wrong. - The jar isn't better than...
(Right. It was pot.)
You break your nose.
- 3, 2... - Even when you fall backward.
- Even when you... - There's more.
- 3, 2... - What did you say?
(There's more to it?)
- One. You failed. - Isn't that correct?
- A rock. - "If you're unlucky."
- That's the missing part. - Oh, right.
- You unlucky punk. - What?
(He uses the proverb he just learned.)
- You said the proverb, right? - Don't act like you knew it.
- That's it? - Yes.
(Jong Kook gets 2 correct. It's now Haha's turn.)
- How many did he get right? - Two.
- 2 questions. - I'm relieved that I got 2 right.
We should stop him.
Haha, you're up.
You knock on the window.
- 3, 2... - When you're desperate.
(Knocking on the window while sleeping.)
Wrong.
You can't find any.
When you need medicine as poop... When you need poop as medicine.
(You can't find medicine to be used as feces?)
(You can't find dog feces when needed for medicine.)
- What do you mean by that? - Darn it.
(Bomi who got 1 correct actually did really well.)
That's hilarious.
Let's move on.
This is impossible even for a king.
- 3, 2... - "Even for a king"?
- Running Man games... - One.
(Even the king can't end the poverty.)
(The new proverb 2020: Even the king can't do Running Man games.)
Next.
With a horseshoe.
3, 2...
The one who feels at ease.
- What's horseshoe? - I don't what horseshoe is.
(They don't know what a horseshoe is.)
- And no man is below others. - Three.
- Why are you doing this to me? - Two.
(He loses his temper at the difficulty level.)
Why are you doing this to me? You never did it before.
(Why are you doing this to me in front of Bomi and Namjoo?)
Under the sky...
- No man is above others. - Oh, right.
(Haha doesn't get any questions correct.)
And no man is below others.
- They were too difficult. - I think...
(It's very typical of old people to blame others.)
- They were difficult. - The ones in the beginning weren't.
- Those two questions were easy. - They don't suit me.
Don't mind him.
- The one with "poop" suits you. - Indeed.
(What are you talking about?)
It suits you well.
- I'll announce the result. - Okay.
(The result after Kwang Soo and Bomi)
- Kwang Soo came in first. - Yes.
- Jong Kook is in second place. - All right.
Namjoo is in 3rd place, and Bomi is in 4th place.
Haha is in bottom place.
Haha, thank you.
We'll deduct 15 years as we planned before, right?
(Let's deduct ages equally just like our plan earlier.)
About that...
We should try following the rule to figure it out.
- Just wait for now. - You're in bottom place.
(Jong Kook changes his mind after getting 2nd place.)
- Why did you change your mind? - You thought that too, right?
- It's not like that. - I love this about him.
- Am I right? - I really like this about him.
- Deducting 15 years... - We should follow the rule.
(He just wants to submit as many as he wants.)
is against the rule.
But they said we could do that.
(He's now betrayed by his own brother.)
It's against the rule.
Who are you, mister?
We're not allowed to do that.
(It'll now be chaotic with Jong Kook's change of heart.)
He said that we can do that if we all agree.
Before the food is out,
(It's time to deduct ages.)
you can take off as many badges as you want...
out of 55 years that you gained...
(They can deduct 55 years.)
and give the badges to us.
Let's do as we agreed, okay?
(Kwang Soo, ranked 1st, will deduct first.)
- Shall I step forward? - They shouldn't...
You should submit the badges without letting us know.
(Ripping)
- Hey. He took off a lot of them. - I mean...
(Already)
- He took off a lot of them. - I mean...
- I should deduct a few years. - How many did he take off?
(Kwang Soo already lost his mind.)
Just a few. I took off only four.
- How many will you take off? - Not many.
(Kwang Soo is the only person Jong Kook can't control.)
- How many? - You shouldn't have let him.
(How many ages did Kwang Soo deduct?)
How many years will you deduct from your age, Kwang Soo?
- Don't take off too many. - Okay.
- You punk! - He's taking off so many.
(He rips them off with his palms.)
How many badges is he taking off?
I think he'll take off all his badges.
Kwang Soo, don't take off too many.
(The man who doesn't know what reasonable means goes first.)
Gosh. I can't believe Kwang Soo.
(He rips off all 30.)
- Kwang Soo. - He's so mean.
(He wants to rip off more, He tries to calm Kwang Soo down.)
Hey!
(The production crew is trying to calm him down.)
- He's taking off all the badges. - Hey!
- Stop it. - Kwang Soo, my gosh.
(The crew gets involved from the first turn.)
- Gosh, seriously. - Deduct 36 years...
(We thought it'd end in vain if we don't do this.)
The staff members are trying to stop you, you punk!
Hey.
Kwang Soo, stop it. It won't be funny if you do that.
(Kwang Soo, please know what reasonable means.)
Fine. Deduct all the years you need and get out.
(Just be 0 years old and get out of the game.)
- You can't do it in the beginning. - Just leave.
I think there will be some years left at least for me.
(After a little struggle, Kwang Soo finishes his deduction.)
Jong Kook, come forward.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
You know me, right? I'm not that kind of person.
(He walks confidently by talking about his normal character.)
I'm a reasonable person.
I'll tell you how many years he deducted.
(How many years of 55 years did Kwang Soo use?)
Exactly. I need to know that.
- I'll decide based on that. - I didn't take off many.
- You'll get to deduct some years. - Really?
He submitted 30 badges.
(He used 30?)
My gosh. He's a crazy punk.
(He looks as if he wants to submit more if he can.)
He took off all the badges he had?
Hold on a second.
(Lee Kwang Soo, currently 6 years old)
You shouldn't have given him a chance to do that.
(Kwang Soo used almost half of 55 years.)
I'm shocked.
- You still have enough years. - He must've lost his mind.
(They now have 25 years left.)
Then... My gosh.
He must be out of his mind.
Then I will...
- So we have 25 years left? - Yes.
Then I'll take off 20 badges.
(Kim Jong Kook will use 20?)
(Kim Jong Kook is now changed.)
(Jong Kook gets 20 years younger and is no longer the oldest.)
Okay. Done.
(Namjoo learns there are only 5 years left.)
My gosh. I can't believe this.
I guess there's no year left.
(Shameless)
- Why? How many do you have left? - Gosh, seriously.
(Kwang Soo is used to doing this.)
How many?
(But Jong Kook looks unsettled as it's his first time betraying.)
Tell no one else but me, and I'll tell you.
Can I redeem myself?
(After some pondering, Namjoo submits her age too.)
I was considerate of you two.
(It's now Bomi and Haha's turn.)
- How many do we have left? - Really.
I shouldn't expect much.
- Your team gained 55 years. - Yes.
But the members before you deducted 54 years in total.
(There's only 1 year left?)
- What? - That's not the reason.
- You became... - Do you think it was me?
(The three used 54 years of 55 years.)
- You became a pirate. - Do you think it was me?
(Bomi submits something too.)
But you...
(The three are busy blaming each other.)
You left me no choice...
because you deducted...
One of them went too far.
(Haha, the final player)
- How many do we have left? - He's like a pirate.
You have none left.
How can we have none left?
(He can't believe what he just heard.)
I guess they took off all the badges they had.
- The last person... - The bottom place has none.
(Bomi used up the last year and is now 1 year younger.)
has a low chance of getting the age deducted.
All other members turned in different numbers of age badges.
(Haha became the oldest member.)
- Okay. - Are those leather?
- Are you wearing leather pants? - What is up with your pants?
(Changing the topic)
What about my pants?
(Old fossil Haha is sensitive.)
Look at you.
That hat looks like a traditional hat, doesn't it?
(Bomi's already the 2nd oldest.)
We might be the oldest ones.
- Are you satisfied with the result? - I am totally satisfied.
I wouldn't say I am satisfied by 100 percent, but...
All right.
You suddenly became a preschooler.
Can he even walk at his age?
(Lee Kwang Soo, 6)
You suddenly became a preschooler.
Would it be okay if I go and change my diaper?
It happened so suddenly.
(He's the youngest cast on Running Man.)
- It's not that bad. - It happened in the first round.
Shouldn't he eat baby food?
(The age changes in the team.)
We will serve food.
- Okay. - It must be delicious.
(Hot kalguksu to warm them up is served.)
- This is it. - We got one serving.
This is it.
Would it be okay if I eat this much?
(Kwang Soo starts eating first.)
- Of course. - Okay.
I will take two dumplings.
(25-year-old Jong Kook wants dumplings.)
All right. I followed my conscience.
(The rest got as much as they wanted.)
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
(How's the restaurant that's been running for 55 years?)
This restaurant has been around for 55 years.
I vouch for this restaurant.
(They exclaim as soon as they taste the food.)
You must eat this kimchi.
(The dish is perfect...)
(with the dumplings and kimchi.)
Look up restaurants with 100 years of history.
(They need to find the next restaurant.)
Jong Kook.
Pyongyangmyeonok.
It's the perfect restaurant to visit next.
(Cool Pyongyang naengmyeon after hot kalguksu?)
- It will be delicious. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - We can go to Hadongkwan next.
(Then it's beef bone soup next.)
- Yes. - Then we will be done.
Then it will be a happy ending.
- We won't need to fight. - Exactly.
(Team Jong Kook finishes eating with a plan to form an alliance.)
- Okay. - Then we will be done.
We will be done.
Let's clap the slate.
1, 2, 3.
(The shoot at the first restaurant ends.)
(Jong Kook heads somewhere.)
The staff members will move first.
(He approaches the trunk.)
(He takes something out.)
Hold on. Where do I do this?
- Where do I do this? - You need to find a spot and do it.
- Do I need to do it in secret? - Yes.
Really?
(Does he need to do something in secret?)
(He stealthily moves to the back of the car.)
(Is that a die?)
(A moment ago)
All right.
(Jong Kook checked his phone.)
How many age badges do you have left?
I can't show them.
We will find out soon.
(Running Man's hidden mission)
(Only the oldest member in the team receives this text every 2 hours.)
I wish I could show you.
(For the hidden mission, you can roll the dice...)
(and deduct your age and 1 person in another team.)
How many age badges did you remove? A lot?
I didn't remove that many.
(Did the oldest member in the team get a hidden mission?)
Me too.
(Every 2 hours, the oldest member in each team gets a hidden mission!)
(2 dice are hidden at the set at all times!)
(The white die reduces your age...)
(and the red die reduces a selected member's age in another team.)
(However, the location of the dice changes every 2 hours.)
(The oldest members were informed of the hidden mission.)
(Jong Kook was aiming for his chance to do the mission.)
(He finally got his chance to complete the hidden mission.)
I will roll it.
(He rolls the white die to reduce his age first!)
(3 years are deducted from Jong Kook's age.)
(3 years are also deducted from a member of another team.)
- What is that? - What?
- What is that? - It's nothing.
(Kwang Soo comes out of nowhere and catches him in the act.)
(He plays innocent.)
What are those?
I found them in the trunk.
(Hitting)
(Kwang Soo resorts to violence.)
What are those?
- What are those? - I found them in the trunk.
(Yelling)
(He gets cornered for his suspicious behavior.)
You suddenly found dice in the trunk...
- and threw them. - I did it without any thoughts.
- Let me try it. - What?
- Let me throw them. - It isn't something you can do.
(Kwang Soo demands the dice without knowing what it's for.)
I just...
Is this your secret space?
(Scanning)
No, it isn't.
(Stealing the dice)
Haha, that's not how you do it.
- Let me try it too. - I mean...
(They always steal it first on Running Man.)
That's not how you do it.
- What are these? - Nothing.
(What are these?)
1, 2, 3.
(He rolls the die without knowing anything.)
Six.
Let's go.
(Kwang Soo tries to figure out the situation.)
- Did you roll it? - Did I get anything?
(Did you just roll the dice?)
(He steals the dice.)
Is this a game center or what?
Why are you doing this?
(He rolls the dice.)
6. 6.
What is this? Is it a mission?
Is it a mission?
Do you know what you are doing?
- No. - Then why are you doing it?
(Of course not.)
Will you deduct seven years from my age?
- What? - Will you deduct seven years?
(He instinctively bets when he sees dice.)
- No. - Is it a mission?
Why did you roll the dice?
(You don't even know what it's for.)
I was bored, okay?
(Angry)
(He angrily throws the dice.)
(I am so annoyed.)
(This clueless gambler is annoyed.)
What is this?
Let's hit the road.
(He used his energy without any gain.)
Is it really nothing?
I think it's a mission only Haha and Jong Kook received.
I didn't receive a mission. I just copied Jong Kook.
(He really has no idea.)
Why did you roll the dice, Kwang Soo?
Dice?
- Why did you do it? - I followed him.
It seemed like a mission.
(Me too.)
Haha, why did you roll the dice?
I just followed Jong Kook.
(Haha copied Jong Kook, )
Wasn't it your mission?
- Did you do it without a clue? - Yes.
(and Kwang Soo copied Haha.)
All right. You rolled the dice.
Jong Kook, which member will you choose?
(Thanks to Jong Kook's hidden mission, )
- What? - A member from another team, right?
(1 person in another team gets 3 years deducted by default.)
Yes.
I will choose Se Chan.
(He picks Yang Se Chan.)
Okay.
- Tell us what that was about! - Why won't you tell us anything?
We feel left out.
It doesn't affect you.
(What about me?)
Like I told you earlier...
(Chuckling)
Did you receive a mission?
Haha and Kwang Soo simply played with the dice.
Why do you keep saying that?
(Annoyed)
(The dice will be hidden at a different location now.)
- Jong Kook, as for you, - Okay.
(It'll be informed to the oldest member in the team 2 hours later.)
your result will be reflected.
(Meanwhile, in Team Ji Hyo's car)
Seriously.
(He receives a text about a deduction in his age.)
I guess other teams can't eat meat...
(3 years have been deducted from Jong Kook and Se Chan's ages.)
if one team eats meat.
(He gets a benefit without knowing what's going on.)
Did you eat a lot?
I drank some soup.
(Polite)
By the way, So Min,
Is it hard?
act your age.
(Se Chan makes a comment.)
Okay? When you are in your mid-20s,
you shouldn't keep food from the younger members.
Hey, I am older than you. I am 25 years old.
I know that, but you shouldn't tell me what to do.
Listen.
Don't stretch out the last syllable. I don't like it.
(It bugs me.)
- Keep it short. - Okay.
Okay.
(He is as childish as a preschooler.)
I will keep it short!
Shall I talk like this?
Shall I talk faster?
(He annoys me so much.)
What am I going to do with him?
Call me when you come to Yongsan. I will buy you a meal.
(Out of nowhere)
Okay.
But I don't know your number.
I will give you my number.
(Her real intention)
- Tell her you will memorize it. - Just ask.
Don't be ridiculous.
Stop being jealous!
- I am not being jealous! - For goodness' sake.
(20-year-old gets jealous easily.)
It would be nice if he tells you he will memorize it.
He gets so greedy about something he won't have.
(Ridiculous)
I am not being greedy! She is ridiculous.
What time is it now? It's 12:30pm, right?
- If it's 12:30pm... - We need to move fast.
(We need to hurry up.)
We should hit the road again by 1:30pm.
- At this restaurant, - We don't have much time.
(While Team Ji Hyo is quarreling...)
we really need to move fast. Otherwise, we will lose.
(Team Suk Jin, Team Ji Hyo, Team Jong Kook)
(Team Suk Jin is close to the second restaurant)
It wasn't enough food to fill my stomach.
(Suk Jin complains because he is hungry.)
This is ridiculous.
Suk Jin has a lot of complaints.
I am still hungry.
Suk Jin's complaints are never big. They are always small.
(The Petty Gang boss' petty complaints)
I will eat more.
- I will eat more. - Fathers are like that.
But you should know...
(But that doesn't mean...)
that Suk Jin never goes against...
the production crew's wishes.
He does everything.
(He complains, but he does what he's told.)
- Do you know what I mean? - Yes.
"Why are you making me do this?"
(He complains endlessly.)
"This is ridiculous." When he gets the cue,
(Then when he gets the cue, he does it without fail.)
he does it without fail.
(He becomes a professional when the camera comes on.)
- You know people like that, right? - Yes.
(They are nearing the second restaurant.)
The thing is,
it's not easy to hold on to a position for years.
(That reminds me.)
It's not easy.
Working in the show business for 30 years...
- is hard. - It isn't easy.
- I... - There was a crisis.
I told myself,
"I will work until the age of 30."
- Really? - I didn't know...
- if it was the right path for me. - You weren't sure about that.
(The team of oldest members talks about life seriously.)
I wondered if it would be okay to pursue this career.
I told myself that I will quit if I don't succeed...
until the age of 40.
- And? - So...
when I hit the age of 40, I said,
"I will quit if I don't succeed until the age of 50."
I pushed the deadline.
(He renewed it himself.)
You did?
(He failed to become popular until the age of 40.)
I will hang in there until the age of 60 and quit.
(He renews it again.)
- You just need to stay healthy. - That's right.
We saw earlier that he is in good health.
(The old comedian's been renewing himself for 30 years now.)
- I keep pushing the deadline. - That's good.
- You don't need permission. - This is the place.
(Meanwhile, they arrived at the second old restaurant.)
- It opened in 1937. - Okay.
You can see the history.
(It really is an old restaurant.)
Look at this place.
(Cheongjinok is a haejangguk place with 84 years of history.)
It's Lee Ju Il.
(It opened in 1937 and has been running for 3 generations.)
- Nami. - It really is an old restaurant.
(President Kim Young Sam visited on September 12, 1997.)
This is a meaningful restaurant.
(Haejangguk with clotted blood, tripe, and radish green is popular.)
This is incredible.
- Seriously. - This restaurant...
(Haejangguk with clotted blood, tripe, and radish green is popular.)
This restaurant opened in 1937.
(The restaurant has 84 years of history.)
Its hangover soup was picked as Seoul's future heritage.
Suk Jin can't eat...
(However)
clotted blood.
- No, he can't. - What should we do?
Boiled pork.
Would you like to order boiled pork?
No, no. Hangover soup is their signature dish.
Why are you being so difficult when he offered to change the menu?
They could take out clotted blood.
- We need to eat clotted blood. - We love clotted blood.
We want to eat the original version.
(It's the second restaurant, but he's likely to starve again.)
- This is driving me crazy. - It's just Suk Jin.
- We need their signature dish. - That's right.
(Rubbing in his face)
I must do my best with the mission.
I bet I will only get clotted blood if I place last.
(The smell of clotted blood is strong.)
Seriously.
- That will happen if I place last. - Hold on.
You don't like the taste, right? You can still eat it, right?
- I can eat it. - That solves the problem.
(Of course.)
I can eat it.
- Let's begin the mission. - Okay.
(Proverb mission over 84-year-old Haejangguk)
Frog. 1, 2...
(A frog)
- "Demetan Croaker..." - Incorrect.
(A well with a frog)
- Hold on. - "Demetan Croaker..."
- I placed second. - My goodness.
(The result of the mission)
- This makes no sense. - Turn in the age badges.
(It's time to deduct their ages in the order.)
21 years each.
I left some age badges behind.
(They go from Chang Hee to Soo Yong.)
I didn't turn in a lot.
My goodness.
Gosh, I turned in only a few.
Are there any years left for Jae Suk?
(Jae Suk.)
- Are there any years left for... - Jae Suk, your turn.
(Lastly, it's Jae Suk.)
- How many years remain? - One.
For goodness' sake.
(That's a lot.)
(Jae Suk could only deduct 1 year.)
All right. If I place first the next time...
Just you wait.
(Deducted 38 years, deducted 42 years, deducted 3 years)
We will do this again. This isn't the end.
Seriously.
Do you know what's a relief?
Even though Suk Jin placed second,
he can't eat clotted blood.
That's right.
I am hungry.
(He hasn't eaten anything.)
- The soup. - You know...
- He might just drink the soup. - He might just drink the soup.
I will eat rice. I will eat it.
(Groaning)
The owner will give a lot of clotted blood.
Please give us a lot of meat.
There is that.
(The haejangguk with 84 years of history is served.)
Thank you.
This is...
(The dish has a generous amount of clotted blood and tripe.)
It looks delicious.
(Gulping)
Gosh, it's...
- Shall we add rice? - It looks delicious.
(The rice)
- I am sorry, but I placed first. - That's right.
- That's right. - You placed first.
(He returns the scoop.)
- That's how it is. - I see. That being said...
(Then Jae Suk got a text.)
- What's that in the bowl? - That's how it is.
- What is this? - What?
(Due to Ji Hyo's hidden mission, a year got deducted from your age.)
"Due to Ji Hyo's hidden mission, a year got deducted from your age."
- What? - Lucky you.
(Puzzled)
"Turn in an age badge to the production crew secretly."
(Turn in an age badge to the production crew secretly.)
Why did you read it out loud?
(You're supposed to turn it in secretly.)
What is this?
(Soo Yong also checks the text he received earlier.)
I didn't receive anything.
I received a chance. Is it okay if I do it?
The die chance.
(Cheerful)
- Why did you reveal it? - What?
(It's a hidden mission.)
It's a hidden mission. Why did you reveal it?
(He reveals the hidden mission without thinking.)
(Jae Suk turns in 1 year.)
Ji Hyo must have succeeded in the hidden mission.
(Meanwhile, the 3 of them are eating.)
There is a lot of clotted blood.
(He takes a ladleful without the clotted blood.)
Gosh, this seems to be a dish...
that isn't easy for me.
The smell...
- What isn't easy for you? - This dish.
He is complaining about the smell.
(He placed 2nd, but he can't eat.)
- It isn't easy for me. - There is a lot of food left.
Is that porridge?
(Suk Jin got forced into a diet.)
He is the worst. I told you.
(3rd place Soo Yong gets food.)
- Watch. - It isn't easy for me.
Soo Yong likes to eat,
(Soo Yong.)
but he eats in an unappetizing way.
Watch. He eats in an unappetizing way.
(Guys who stop you from eating)
(Jae Suk starts an eating show instead.)
It's so tasty.
By the way,
why am I eating so much when I placed last?
(Why am I eating so much when I placed last?)
(He is having his fill thanks to a picky eater.)
(He looks around without eating.)
Gosh, this is a dish with history.
(He talks about the history without any food in his mouth.)
- A dish with history. - He didn't eat much.
Watch him.
He keeps doing this with rice.
(Pushing the rice around)
Why are you mincing the rice?
(The human mortar is mincing it until it becomes porridge.)
Suk Jin, why are you mincing the rice?
This is a dish with history.
(He's not bothered.)
I can feel the Korean spirit.
Do you know what he said?
He can feel the Korean spirit.
- The ancestors' spirit. - He is ridiculous.
(He feels the ancestors' spirit without tasting the dish.)
- This is the place. - When did the restaurant open?
(Team Jong Kook arrived at the second restaurant.)
1980.
(However, )
It says, "100-year-old restaurant".
(they see a sign that says 100-year-old restaurant.)
100 years?
Is it 100 years old?
What is this place?
(They expect the restaurant to be 100 years old as they enter.)
They even received a medal.
This restaurant serves Pyongyang specialty.
(Anticipating)
It's from Pyongyang,
(100-year-old restaurant that started in Pyongyang?)
so it must be incredibly old.
- I bet it's 200 years. - Did it start in Pyongyang?
(It's his wish.)
It was passed down through three generations.
(In fact)
Three generations?
Then it must be over 100 years old.
(It must be over 100 years old with 3 generations.)
- How old is it? 100 years? - We should ask.
(How old is this restaurant?)
You have arrived at the second restaurant.
(The food was prepared before they arrived.)
They set up a table in advance.
- We will proceed once you sit down. - Shall we do that?
(They take off the masks for the show.)
- All right. - Sir.
(They call for the owner with high expectations.)
(Excited)
- Hello. - Hello.
(An employee comes in to tell them...)
Please come in.
(about the history of the restaurant.)
It's my first time to meet the owner of a 100-year-old restaurant.
(Adding pressure)
I heard that this restaurant is 100 years old.
Sir,
how old is this restaurant?
(There was a sign that read, "100-year-old restaurant".)
It says, "100-year-old restaurant".
(Is it actually 100 years old?)
Is it 100 years old?
It opened in 1984,
so it's 37 years old.
It's 37 years old.
- 37 years old. - 37 years old.
That's... That's incredible.
We don't mean this specific building.
(In a rush)
We mean...
The brand.
We mean the entire brand,
- not this specific branch. - In that case,
(They want to hear that it's 100 years old.)
the grandfather of the owner...
(He carefully explains the history of the restaurant again.)
(Please.)
- ran a restaurant in Pyongyang. - Right?
(Let it be 100 years old.)
He ran Daedongmyeonok there.
(The owner's grandfather)
If you combine that history...
- If you combine that history... - If I do that,
this restaurant would be about 100 years old.
This restaurant would be about 100 years old.
(They finally hear "100 years"!)
- I got goosebumps. - That's Dadongmyeonok.
(Don't be excited.)
- This restaurant... - How old is...
(Then how old is this restaurant?)
- Pyongyangmyeonok? - How old is it?
It must be close to 100 years old.
(He has an answer he wants to hear.)
It's 37 years old.
(Firm)
No, no.
The sign reads, "100-year-old restaurant".
(Clingy)
- It's our pride. - I see.
(They can't give up on their hope.)
When he moved to South Korea,
he didn't open the restaurant right away.
- He did something else. - He did something else.
(Disappointed)
Will you only count the history of this restaurant?
(100-year-old restaurants is a project...)
- Yes. - 37 years. Okay.
(to help restaurants over 30 years last over 100 years.)
What should we order?
- Which dish is the most popular? - Pyongyang naengmyeon.
(A bowl of Pyongyang naengmyeon...)
(in a 37-year-old Pyongyang naengmyeon restaurant.)
We should eat Pyongyang naengmyeon.
(Noodles with the aroma of buckwheat and clean broth complete the dish.)
Please give us 1 serving that feels like 5 servings.
(As much as they were excited, )
- That's too bad. - 37 years.
(they're disappointed.)
- 37 years. - I continued to send a signal.
(It's a bummer.)
We should hurry up and move on to the next restaurant.
- That's right. - Let's hurry up.
We need to go to Hadongkwan.
(I still have over 80 years left.)
We should do that.
- This restaurant is 37 years old. - Okay.
(The second restaurant is 37 years old.)
The mission is, Blow Out Candles With the Entire Body.
With a fan attached to your waist, you will generate winds.
(With a fan attached to your waist, the order will be determined...)
The time it took you to blow out five candles...
(by the time it took you to blow out 5 candles.)
will determine the order.
When we simulated the game, men had an advantage.
(When the staff stimulated the game, )
(men had an advantage.)
Thus, we will put the candles 50cm closer...
- for women. - What?
(So, the candles will be 50cm closer for women.)
- Here... - Will the candles be...
- here? - Yes.
- Is it even possible? - Yes.
(Not feeling confident)
Since women have a handicap...
If you are against it...
(Hesitating)
I am not against it.
(So cool)
If I am against it, will you reflect that?
(Narrow-minded)
To be honest, I am against it.
(He is petty.)
(He promotes gender equality.)
- It's too much. - I am against it.
(He's very sensitive before missions.)
If it's a small advantage, I would understand.
It's too much.
(Complaining)
How much of a benefit would you accept?
Move the sticker.
(As much as you want)
- What is your problem? - No, no.
(She hates it.)
- We are on the same team. - This needs to be fair.
(This is the only time he talks about equality.)
I know that we are on the same team.
Then let's play fair.
Don't give us a benefit.
(She refuses the benefit in the end.)
- No, no. You need it. - Should we play the same way?
- Come on. - We aren't that mean.
(No, we're still on the same team.)
- All right. - Move it a little bit.
Move it a little bit.
(He's considerate.)
(Two big hand spans...)
That's good.
(is a fake.)
What?
- Where? - Just don't give us a benefit.
(That's cheap.)
- We will give it. - Do two hand spans.
(They agree on two hand spans.)
Do two hand spans.
- For goodness' sake. - Do two hand spans.
(Reducing)
For goodness' sake.
(Wriggling)
Do two hand spans.
- You moved your fingers. - You are heartless.
(Amazed)
- No, I didn't. - You moved your fingers.
That's good enough.
(The strict old fossil approves.)
- That's good enough. - It's close to where it was before.
- It was generous of Kwang Soo. - Seriously.
Do we put this on our waist?
(The mission starts.)
Haha, it's your turn.
Isn't that what you wear to work out?
(Haha tries first.)
Do I keep going until I blow out all the candles?
(The order is based on the time it takes to blow all 5 candles.)
Yes. The clock will keep going until you blow out all of them.
Don't grab the belt with your hands.
(Strict)
Get ready.
Set...
(Go.)
(One candle goes out already.)
He blew out one candle.
(He swings as much as he can.)
- Are you timing it? - The wind is strong.
(The wind is strong, )
The flame is coming back.
I think the location is off.
(but the candles come back alive.)
- It worked. - They won't go out.
It went out.
(There are only two left.)
Haha is fast.
- A bit more. - I did it!
(He succeeded to blow out all the candles.)
26 seconds.
(Haha's record is 26 seconds.)
- This is difficult. - Why do my knees hurt so much?
(He traded his knees for the record.)
- His knees will get ruined. - Why do your knees hurt?
- Hey. - Why do your knees hurt?
You can do it.
(Bomi will go next.)
Bomi.
(She gets a benefit.)
We stand closer to the candles.
Can I grab the handle?
(The fan)
No, you can't.
Never.
(Don't even think about it.)
Don't ever grab it.
(He's the biggest old fossil ever.)
- Don't ever grab it. - We become so sensitive.
(He's embarrassed to say it.)
- Don't ever grab it. - Get ready.
Hey.
(Her foot slightly touches it.)
- Don't step on the line. - She stepped on the line.
- I am sorry, but if you do that... - Hey!
(Very sensitive)
- you will just be out. - Oh, no.
- It's over if you step on the line. - Just go back.
(The old farts are very critical when it comes to others.)
You will automatically be in last place.
- Okay. - Go back more.
- Don't step on the line. - That's enough.
(They finally accept it.)
I'll accept that.
- Get ready. - Okay.
(She's already tired before she begins.)
- Wait a minute. - Go.
What's happening?
- What's happening? - She put them out quickly.
(The candle lights were put out as soon as she started.)
(Everyone stands up.)
- She was too close. - This isn't right.
(He says it now.)
- Gosh. - This is reverse discrimination.
(The old fart is angry.)
- She's good. - This isn't right.
Everyone agreed.
- Everyone agreed to this. - Still...
(Speechless)
Please decide it again then.
- Let's do it from here... - This is too easy.
(The handicap is taken away.)
- because she's good. - I could do it.
- We're much older than her. - Let's try it from here.
(He is a typical old fart.)
- Let's try it first. - Gosh.
(She tries again under the same condition.)
- Let's try it first. - But this is...
- Or... - I'll try it.
Let's try it first, and if it's too hard...
- Get ready. - Let's try it.
(The table is now at the same distance as Haha's.)
Go!
(Sabotage)
(Despite of Haha's sabotage...)
- What is happening? - She's just good.
She's just good.
(The candlelights were put off within 3 seconds.)
- How many seconds did I take? - She only took three seconds.
- She's just good. - Okay.
(Sad)
Honestly, you must give us an advantage.
(Serious)
I'm serious.
Do you know how old we are?
That is reverse discrimination.
- The angle is important for this. - That's good.
(Happy)
- Good. - Watch your feet.
(Kwang Soo, now 6 years old, tries to blow out the candle.)
- Watch your feet. - Okay.
Okay.
(A cute preparation that meets his age.)
Okay, get ready.
- I'm done. - You punk!
Go!
(Start)
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
It's over.
(He tries as hard as he can.)
Oh, my. This is just...
- Oh, my. - It's over.
(No effect at all)
It's over.
Oh, my.
(He got the hang of it now.)
- He's doing a good job. - That's it.
- No. - Okay!
(Did the candles blow out?)
- It's back on. - No.
Hurry!
(Take a look again.)
(The candlelights look like they will get put out, but they won't.)
What are we going to do?
- He got it. - I'm mad.
He got it.
What are we going to do?
- Okay! - No. Put it out.
(Okay! What?)
(The flame is up again.)
(It's a supernatural phenomenon that only happens to Kwang Soo.)
Is this a prank show? Is it a prank?
(Impressed)
Is it a prank?
(Flapping)
He's going to be funny now.
(He changed his strategy to be funny from winning.)
(It's a never-ending desperate struggle with candlelights.)
- Okay. - A new...
It got put out.
(It finally got put out!)
- A new... - How could you...
- He got it. - He finally did it.
(He burned into ashes.)
Lee Kwang Soo took 42 seconds.
(Kwang Soo's record is 42 seconds.)
- This will be hard. - It's harder than I thought.
(It's a lot harder than it looks.)
- It's hard looking at him do it. - Did some of them come alive?
- It's Namjoo's turn next. - It's the fourth person.
(It's Namjoo's turn.)
Is it me?
Make sure embers are completely extinguished.
(Today's lesson)
You need to gather your hands behind your back to do a good job.
(Advice of a person with the best record)
- Yes. - Get ready.
- Okay. - Go.
(Cheerful)
- She lost her balance. - She's bad.
(Namjoo won't make it.)
- Why is she drawing an eight? - What's happening?
(She's drawing an infinite loop with the fan.)
Is she being serious or what?
(Confused)
- She's serious. - What is she doing?
(She's putting the candlelights out with screaming and laughter.)
Why are you moving up and down?
If not...
(Moving)
Why are you moving up and down?
(Why is she suddenly moving up and down?)
I mean...
(No matter how much she shakes...)
What is happening?
(the candles do not budge.)
- I mean... - Aren't you going to do it?
- She won't be able to do it. - She got it.
(She finally gets the hang of it.)
She got it. That's it.
- Make long strokes. - Yes.
- Make long strokes. - She got it.
There's the last one left.
Namjoo, you crossed the line too much.
(Very strict)
- Namjoo. - It's because...
(Kwang Soo is very strict.)
- It's okay. Make long strokes. - there's a line.
You just have to make long strokes like earlier.
(He's very strict with others.)
- Make long strokes. - This one won't get put out.
- Make long strokes. - It's really not getting put out.
(There's only one more problematic candle.)
That one won't get put out.
(It's playing hard to get.)
- I... - Oh, my.
That one has a long wick.
Blow it out for her, Haha.
(If Namjoo fans, )
(Haha will try to put it out by blowing it.)
Blow it out for her.
(Passing)
See? Do it again.
Namjoo, you need to move.
(Under the coach's instruction...)
You need to be in sync with each other.
(Tiki-taka)
- You can't do that. - Yes!
(They finally succeed.)
(A perfect combination)
You got it.
Namjoo took 1 minute 41 seconds.
(Namjoo's record is 1 minute and 41 seconds.)
- This is really hard. - This is hard.
Bomi did a really good job.
(Impressed)
- She did a ridiculously good job. - This is hard.
How did you do it?
- I just shook everything. - Bomi did a good job.
(Simple)
Is it my turn now?
He got it.
(This is the result of Jong Kook also shaking everything.)
- What happened? - He's certainly good.
- What happened? - Oh, my.
Okay.
- Oh, my. - I got it.
(He succeeded at putting the candlelights out in 9 seconds.)
- I got it. - I'm getting stressed out.
(Speaking from his heart)
I just need to be in second place.
(Satisfied)
We will start taking away age from first place.
(Their age will be deducted in accordance with the ranks.)
You can take away as much age as you want...
(They can deduct 37 years.)
from 37 years, the age of this restaurant.
- From 37 years? - Yes.
- Wait a minute. - Bomi, I beg you.
From 37 years?
(Bomi is currently 27 years old.)
How many do I have?
(It seems like she's taking away a lot of things.)
- Okay, she's done. - You look really light, Bomi.
(She returns after brazenly removing a lot of things.)
No, I'm not.
- Kim Jong Kook is in second place. - Okay.
(It's now Jong Kook's turn.)
I'll take a look.
(Jong Kook is currently 22 years old.)
I still have a lot. I'm full.
(The remaining years left after Bomi's deduction are...)
- These are the remaining years. - Yes.
There are 10 years left.
(She deducted 27 years.)
(0 and rich)
(How many years did she deduct?)
Really?
I was more considerate than you thought, right?
(He's really surprised.)
- She's... - Your face turned completely red.
No, I really didn't take away a lot.
- How serious is it? - I didn't take away a lot.
(How many?)
I think we should put her in an incubator.
Does she have to get in an incubator?
(The Curious Case of Bomi)
Right now, she's...
- I'm inside my mom's belly. - Right now, she's...
Is she inside her mom's belly?
Gosh, this is really...
(Pondering)
At that rate...
Our team has no sense of teamwork, right?
(Haha the oldest member)
- We just have to win. - Let's not do this.
We can't win if we do this.
(Jong Kook took away 6 years. He's currently 16 years old.)
There's only this much left?
He just went crazy anyway.
(Haha is now 39 years old, Kwang Soo is 5 years old.)
Can he walk or not? Just tell me that.
He can't walk in my opinion.
(Toddling)
He can't walk. He can't walk now.
(The last person is Namjoo, who is currently 22 years old.)
- Namjoo. - Yes?
- Don't go. - I'm not going to take it away.
(You'd rather not.)
Namjoo, you won't be able to take anything away.
There's nothing left.
(As you know...)
Okay.
(She accepts quickly.)
You got it, right?
There's no other...
- I already knew it. - Okay.
(She didn't expect much.)
I guess you can't help it.
- We will give you your meal now. - Okay.
(It's time to enjoy Pyongyang naengmyeon.)
- It looks good. - Oh, my.
(It's an addictive food that you can't get out.)
They gave us double portions.
Okay, I'll eat this much.
(They pour into their bowls in the order of their ranking.)
(Slurping)
(Kwang Soo, who was 4th place, takes away some naengmyeon.)
Aren't you taking away too little?
(Kwang Soo.)
- Let's eat together. - Okay.
(Only as much as he can eat.)
- You should eat a lot. - Aren't you hungry?
(Worried)
(His younger sisters are moved.)
I'll eat this.
(Not the bowl in my hand.)
So...
(Kwang Soo takes the bigger bowl and gives the other to her.)
- Do you want some more? - No.
I'm sorry, but I really like naengmyeon.
(Annoying)
- I thought you were full. - We will also go there next time.
I never thought that a baby who can't even walk properly...
could eat so much Pyongyang naengmyeon.
This is different.
(The 5-year-old Kwang Soo is addicted to naengmyeon.)
Kids usually don't like Pyongyang naengmyeon.
I didn't know you could eat that in an incubator.
(Bomi)
Aren't you supposed to be breastfed?
(Pyongyang naengmyeon feeding?)
- I'm being breastfed right now. - Gosh.
- You first started with 177 years. - Yes.
(Team Jong Kook started with 177 years.)
You currently have...
82 years left.
We have a lot left.
Let's go with 90 years.
- This is unbelievable. - Why?
There's a cafe that has 100 years of history.
(We must get going now.)
- What? - It's right next here.
- Hurry up. - Let's order quickly.
(The key is a race against time from now on.)
We don't have much time.
- Let's hurry. I'm anxious. - 63 years are on the line.
(Every team is beginning to feel anxious.)
- I must get rid of them. - Get out quickly.
(It's an old restaurant war with age on the line.)
- You must hurry. - I kept telling you we must hurry.
(Which team will be the winner?)
(And)
(November 2020, The penthouse resident presentation)
- Is this the penthouse? - Please join us.
(It's a luxurious opera performance for VIPs.)
What is this?
(4 residential candidates of the penthouse appeared.)
The ratings are...
(Kim So Yeon, Lee Ji Ah, Eugene)
(Ha Do Kwon is also here, and he is after Jong Kook.)
He's like my soul younger brother.
(Their malicious fight to join the top club began.)
She's punching her.
Do Kwon.
(Will they join the top club...)
She's enjoying Running Man more than anyone else.
(or the bottom club?)
Do you know how malicious she is?
(Their war of nerves is tough.)
Oh, no.
- We don't have time. Hurry up. - You can't do this.
(There are only a few people allowed to join the top club.)
No, stop! What kind of war is this?
(Who will join the top club and become a penthouse resident?)
Let's join the top club!
(The penthouse is currently recruiting.)