Hello.
- Hello.
- Hello, guys.
- The weather is very nice.
- You know what?
So Min is doing just fine.
- I see.
- Jae Suk.
- I went to So Min's place.
- You did?
How did it go?
- She was doing fine.
- Did you...
- take a picture?
- No, I didn't.
(He went to So Min's house
with Kwang Soo.)
So Min.
Hi, So Min.
This is embarrassing.
- Why?
- Oh no.
(She even laced up his apron
with a smile.)
Hey, this isn't "We've Got Married".
I know that.
He's just watching us silently.
You guys are acting like
as if I'm invisible.
(The host is a little too fussy.)
(Don't spill anything
on the carpet.)
(To be honest,
I think I've got an upset stomach.)
(You can see what happened
at So Min's place next week.)
She looked...
- very natural.
- Okay.
Considering the situation,
she's way too cheerful.
I hear that everything else is
still in recovery,
but her mouth has already recovered
200 percent.
- It has a motor.
- Yes.
- That's not good.
- All right.
Haha has worked on the reggae duo,
Sulreggae's debut album...
- for the past two years.
- That's right.
(Jae Suk pours out words
with his hands put together.)
- Hold on.
- Are you at it again?
You just sounded like
you were reading a news article.
- I was so surprised.
- Try to sound more natural.
I thought he was a news reporter.
- I was so surprised.
- This isn't entertainment news.
You produced another album?
It's because I couldn't find...
any reggae album
that's easy to listen to.
This album is very easy
to listen to, especially in spring.
You're not one
of the singers, right?
- I'm not.
- You're not?
That's good.
- So it's romantic reggae, right?
- That's right.
- I can't wait.
- It'll make your heart flutter.
- Exactly.
- Is that what you're saying?
(No, no)
(The romantic,
retro-style reggae duo...)
(produced by Haha, Sulreggae)
We haven't seen new singers
from Quan Entertainment...
- in a while.
- It's their new venture.
- I wish you good luck.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Everyone, isn't the weather nice?
- Yes.
It's nice from today.
Usually, in May,
many colleges have festivals.
- That's right.
- So today,
we invited celebrities
who are usually very busy...
around this time.
- Today...
- I'm sure they're very popular.
Singers are usually very busy...
- around this time.
- That's right.
- Jin Young is usually busy too.
- Right.
- But these days,
- She has a lot of time right now.
she can come on the show any time.
- I see her on TV a lot.
- Exactly.
Even if she has time, I want her
on this show only sometimes.
- Why do you say that?
- I like it.
But you do want to see her
sometimes?
It's so fun to see Jong Kook
with Jin Young.
- She's tiring.
- He becomes so cute.
I can't do my usual thing.
- It's impossible.
- Here.
(Where is Jong Kook?)
So we invited
the kings and queens...
of college festivals
from different genres.
I'm curious.
There are two hip-hip singers,
one indie singer,
and two idol singers.
So the 5 guests divided into
3 teams will perform one by one.
All right.
Each team has a money gun
loaded with 2,000 dollars,
and they will shoot it at any time
during their performances.
(A money gun?)
We're supposed to pick up the money?
The money you pick up...
from the ground
will be your mission fund.
Gosh, why would we...
(You want us to pick up
money from the ground?)
We have to pick up money
from the ground?
That'd be humiliating.
We never pick things up
from the ground.
But it suits Suk Jin best.
It suits him better
than anyone else.
That'd hurt my pride.
Suk Jin, pick anything up
from the ground,
and you're dead meat.
(Suk Jin laughs it off.)
All right.
Let's welcome the first team.
Please come out.
We don't know when they'll
shoot their money gun.
We won't be able to enjoy
their performances.
Oh, my.
(Who are the first guests?)
- Oh, my.
- Hey!
BewhY!
- It's Jessi!
- Jessi!
(Intense rapping
with flow and clarity)
(The top rapper, BewhY)
(Powerful rapping and singing
with deep emotions)
(The irreplaceable,
charismatic Jessi)
- BewhY!
It's Jessi!
(BewhY flexes his money gun
as soon as he's on stage.)
(Running)
Gosh.
Hey! There's so much here.
There's so much.
(BewhY shot all his money at once.)
(Everyone is busy
picking up the money.)
Pick it up!
(1,000 dollars is picked up
in the blink of an eye.)
(Unstoppable flow)
(BewhY's rap makes even
the muscular ballad singer dance.)
I'm a BewhY fan!
I want to see his performance!
(Says BewhY)
(Cheering)
- BewhY!
- Next up is Jessi.
Unbelievable.
I want to see their performances,
but they keep shooting money.
(It's the charismatic girl,
Jessi's turn to perform.)
Focus on my performance.
- Okay!
- I love this song.
Twerking!
(The Sechan Corgi starts twerking.)
("Who Dat B" by Jessi)
(On alert)
(Jessi shoots all her money
at once too.)
(Swarming)
(The money magically
gathers everyone.)
Let's go!
(Now that all the money has been
picked up, they can have some fun.)
(Relaxed)
(They're pretending
they understand hip-hop.)
Jessi!
(Sexy to the end)
(Team Hip-hop flexed their
money guns in a relaxed manner.)
BewhY and Jessi!
Hey!
Someone stepped on the money.
That was so low.
- Suk Jin's hands were so fast.
- It was unbelievable.
- He almost crawled.
- After saying he wouldn't do it...
Also,
we're supposed to watch
the performances.
- Exactly, but it's impossible.
- You were the most desperate.
This time, let's try to enjoy
the performances more.
Let's do that.
- Don't obsess over money.
- That's right.
Let's see who starts running first.
- All right.
- Let's see.
(Who is the next guest?)
Who is it?
- It's BOL4!
(Ahn Ji Young of BOL4)
(Her unique voice suits
the spring day perfectly.)
(The queen of the charts,
Ahn Ji Young of BOL4)
- Ahn Ji Young!
- BOL4!
Money!
(She shoots her money gun shyly.)
(Running)
(They said
they'd watch the performance.)
He rolled.
(Rolling and pinching)
- Gosh!
- Hey!
(Ji Young finishes her performance
in shock.)
Hyojung!
(Lastly, Team Idol)
(Jin Hyuk and Hyojung)
- Hyojung!
- Hello!
(Hyojung is known for
her cute and lovely charm.)
(OH MY GIRL is conquering
every music charts right now.)
("Nonstop" Becomes the No. 1 Song)
(Even his breath
heats up the stage.)
(Jin Hyuk recently debuted
as a solo singer.)
Stay here.
(Shooting)
(They run toward the money
for the 3rd time.)
(Despite the money cleaners,
Hyojung stays calm.)
(The money gun is fired.)
(The idol singer is full of energy.)
(His performance is flawless
to the end.)
- There's some left.
- Why is there so much?
I can't see it.
You beggars!
You beggars, move!
(Hyojung donates some money
to Suk Jin.)
Thanks.
(Suk Jin steps on some money.)
Don't step on the money.
All right.
Put your money in your bag
and hand it in so we can check.
I never pick things up
from the ground.
With these amazing singers here...
In front of younger people...
I wouldn't even pick up
10-dollar bills this way.
We have no money left!
- We have nothing left.
- We don't usually do this.
Please come down!
I ran so much.
We have five kings and queens
of festivals here today.
I'm a little disappointed.
- I wanted to hear them sing.
- I couldn't hear anything.
But we had a mission.
As soon as they appeared...
You said we should enjoy
their performances,
- but you started running first.
- Who?
You ran so fast.
It reminded me of my dog
running toward his food.
As soon as I throw his food
on the floor...
- It makes him go crazy.
- Yes.
Kwang Soo is even wearing
a poop-colored jacket.
Exactly.
You totally looked like a beggar.
Every penny is so sweet.
Let me introduce our guests.
First, Jin Hyuk.
- He's so good-looking.
- He's a member of UP10TION.
Idol singers have
amazing stage presence.
Do you have any tips
for having a great stage presence?
- For example...
- For example?
Normally,
when you're out of breath...
- Show us what you'd do normally.
- At the end...
This is what you'd do normally.
- He's exhausted.
But on camera...
(He stares right at the camera.)
- That looks completely different.
- He stares at the camera.
The eyes are important.
(Casually stare at the camera.)
As if to say, "Look at me."
Your chest has to move up and down.
Up and down.
(Too much, just right)
That looks so different.
- For an idol singer,
- That looks really different.
- he's pretty funny.
- He's funny.
- I haven't seen...
- He's the male version of Mi Joo.
- Mi Joo?
- Mi Joo.
OH MY GIRL's new song...
- topped the charts right away.
- Hello.
- What's the title?
- It's "Nonstop."
- "Nonstop".
This is the first time
you've topped the charts, right?
- It is.
- Let's give her a big hand.
- You must be so happy.
- Congratulations.
- All right, Hyojung.
- Yes?
Can you perform your new song...
- for us?
- Sure.
Please.
This song topped the charts?
("Nonstop" by OH MY GIRL)
(My heart slightly fluttered)
I love the song.
- It's really nice.
- It's perfect for the weather.
It's so nice.
I love this part.
My heart fluttered.
(Is she sanitizing her hands?)
(Hyojung's cute performance...)
(makes everyone's heart flutter.)
- I love that.
- It's a really nice song.
- I love the song.
- My heart fluttered.
There's something her fans...
often say.
They think sexy dance...
- doesn't really suit her.
- She's too cute.
- Her face is so cute.
But...
if she changes clothes
and parts her hair differently,
- she'll look sexy.
- Do you think so?
- Part her hair differently?
- Maybe...
if you get a little tan too...
- I should get a tan?
- Just a little.
That means she has to change
completely.
- That's right.
- The thing is,
she's in an idol group.
- If she wants to look different.
- I get it.
I'm a girl too, you know.
Jessi, show us.
- Show us.
- No!
- Just the facial expressions.
- I don't know the dance.
How do you start?
- Just dance to the music.
- Yes, a freestyle.
You're showing Hyojung
how it's done.
Let's do this!
(Can't wait.)
2, 3, 4.
(What?)
(R-rated version of "Bubble Pop")
Jessi!
- What are you doing?
- Stop.
- Stop it.
- That's not it.
- Jessi, please.
- Gosh.
What on earth are you doing?
- Jessi, hold on.
- What is this?
- That was startling.
- Hold on.
- Hey. This is...
- Jessi.
- Hey!
- This is my style.
Yes, we understand that.
We understand that,
- but it wasn't appropriate...
- Just look though.
- Everyone can keep to their style.
- Keep your own style.
- Yes, do it your own way.
- Of course.
Next up is Ahn Ji Young.
(The unique vocalist
Ahn Ji Young of BOL4)
Anyway, she released a new song.
- That's right.
- It was released on the 13th.
- Yes.
- Songs by BOL4 are always sweet.
- Exactly.
- Right?
- Could we perhaps hear it?
- Sure.
- Here's her mic.
- Let me.
She has such a unique voice.
Way to go Mr. Fashionista.
(Se Chan's fashion turns heads.)
That's how we wore our jackets
in the 90s.
I remember photos of celebrities
in that style.
(Reply 1990s)
(He even looks like someone
from the 90s too.)
The weather's too hot, that's all.
- I had no choice.
- It's cool though.
- But...
- You sure are a celebrity.
Yes, top celebrities are different.
- I was too hot in it.
- It's not easy to pull off.
- I'm not kidding.
- Ji Young, please go ahead.
("Hug" by BOL4)
(Her tone and the melody
is perfect for the spring.)
Gosh, it's nice.
I love it.
(Whoo!)
Can you believe her voice?
(BOL4 always delivers!)
- I love the "whoo" part.
- Your voice...
It gives me the tickles.
- Your voice gives us the tickles.
- Whoo!
That's what I was going for.
Can you sing that "whoo" part again?
(A pleasant breeze goes whoo!)
A pleasant breeze goes whoo!
- A pleasant breeze goes whoo!
- Whoo!
(They can't get enough
of the "whoo".)
- I just got goosebumps.
- Jessi.
Jessi, could you try that too?
- Yes, please.
- A pleasant breeze goes whoo!
- Sing that for us.
- What are the lyrics again?
"A pleasant breeze goes whoo."
- "A pleasant breeze goes whoo."
- A pleasant breeze goes whoo.
- A breeze goes...
- A pleasant breeze.
- A pleasant breeze...
- Hush.
A pleasant booze...
(She flares up by herself.)
- Hold on.
- Jessi!
(She's not used to
such sweet lyrics.)
Did she just swear?
Let me try that again.
She was like, "Darn!"
- A pleasant breeze goes whoo
- A pleasant breeze
- A pleasant breeze goes whoo!
(She has the lyrics down.)
A breeze pleasant...
(A breeze pleasant?)
(She just can't say it correctly.)
- Just don't.
- Don't bother.
- Don't do it.
- Just stop.
- Jae Suk.
- Don't do it.
- I have a genre I'm good at.
- Right.
- You specialize in a different one.
- Jessi, hey.
My gosh.
Anyway Ji Young, I hear that
many think you lived abroad.
- Because of your pronunciation?
- Yes.
Where were you born?
Yeongju, North Gyeongsang Province.
- Yeongju?
- Yes.
(While Ji Young tells us
how she's been...)
(Mumbling)
- Then...
- Jessi, stop practicing.
She's still practicing that line.
- Why?
- Why doesn't it stick?
A pleasant breeze.
- A pleasant breeze goes whoo!
- That's it.
A pleasant breeze goes whoo!
(She smiles
as she finally says it correctly.)
I feel like you should be
blowing out smoke at the end.
It's just a personal opinion.
- I'm not saying that's true.
- Stop it.
I'm not saying
you smoke or anything.
- Just stop.
- I should've kept that to myself.
- Stop it.
- Your leg is still recovering,
- so she will overpower you.
- Sorry about that.
Next up is Jessi! It's Ho Hyun Ju.
No, Kwang Soo. Don't.
- Jessi!
- I know you don't mean it.
I love Jessi.
- Then...
- I love you.
Jessi is the best!
Jessi's last appearance
on the show was five years ago.
- I was shocked to hear that.
- It seems recent though.
The last time she was here,
she understood the rules
when the race was over.
- Right.
- That's right.
(This is too difficult though.)
(He's frustrated.)
(She went home not fully
understanding the rules.)
You only understood the rules
when the game was over.
What?
- Got it.
- History might repeat itself.
- We're good.
- It might happen once again.
- Jae Suk, don't give up.
- It just seems that way.
- Well...
- Jae Suk, don't give up yet.
(They couldn't be
more frustrated with her.)
- Hold on.
- Jessi, wait.
He made it sound complicated though.
Jae Suk glared at you just now.
- I had my reasons.
- That's right.
- Hey, Jessi.
- It was difficult to understand.
(Jae Suk meets his match
after 5 years.)
It's been a while since I saw
Jae Suk glare at a guest.
- Don't give up. You can do this.
- It's fine.
I asked her the question,
so I'm good.
Anyway, that was Jessi!
(He quickly wraps up
the interview.)
Go, Jessi!
- Next up is BewhY.
- BewhY!
BewhY forever.
His real name is Lee Byeong Yoon.
- BewhY is said to resemble Se Chan.
- Yes.
He's somewhere between
me and Hong Hyun Hee.
He resembles both
That's how it goes.
- Haven't you heard that before?
- I have.
He doesn't have
that hairstyle anymore.
You two have similar noses.
- It's our teeth.
- That's not it
BewhY's teeth stick out more.
Really?
I'm just saying.
You just scraped his pride.
Exactly. This hurts my pride.
I usually have
the most protruding teeth.
I don't know why, but we suddenly...
moved on...
to talking about
his protruding teeth.
What I find the most interesting
about his rap is that I can hear...
- the lyrics even though it's fast.
- Exactly.
- I can hear all the lyrics.
- That's right.
It's been a while,
so I'd like to ask him...
to rap for us a little bit.
Could you smack our ears
with your fast-paced rap?
Let's hear this.
(He seemed flustered at first,)
(but he transforms
as soon as he grabs the mic.)
("Neo Christian Flow" by BewhY)
Isn't he amazing?
How does one rap like this?
He's not even out of breath.
Where does he stop to breathe?
(He tore up the stage.)
I got goosebumps.
- How do you remember the lyrics?
- How do you remember all that?
- Where do you breathe?
- You don't seem out of breath.
It's easy for him
because it's his song.
(She chimes in again.)
- Seriously?
- Jessi!
- But I...
- Of course, we know that!
- We know that too.
- It's not because we didn't know.
Then why ask that question?
(Jessi chimes in
when they're praising BewhY.)
You're cool too, okay?
Gosh.
Today, the members and the guests
will split into teams of four...
and form a performance group.
You will earn money
depending on how you do each round.
The three
who earned the most will win.
Before we begin the race,
you'll split into teams.
You each earned a mission fund
earlier on.
- Right.
- Let me tell you how much.
Jae Suk earned 770 dollars.
That's it?
Suk Jin earned 1,080 dollars.
Haha earned 1,270 dollars.
Kwang Soo earned 1,150 dollars.
- That's a lot.
- Haha earned the most.
Isn't it funny how Ji Hyo managed
to pick up so much?
- I did my best.
- It's uncanny.
You will write down...
how much you'd pay
to cast each guest.
- I'd love to team up with Jin Hyuk.
- Right.
Shall we?
Show us your numbers.
Let's do this.
Did I write down too much?
Sorry, but we're still
testing the waters.
Jong Kook, come on.
- Jong Kook?
- Really?
- Suk Jin?
- Seriously?
- I should've put down more.
- I didn't want to choose him,
but he offered the most money.
(The other teams
finish picking who they want.)
It's over now.
You don't get another chance.
(Team Idol: Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
Jin Hyuk, Hyojung)
(Team Hip-hop: Kwang Soo,
Jae Suk, BewhY, Jessi)
(Team Indie: Haha, Se Chan,
Ji Hyo, Ji Young)
After the race is over,
the three with the most
amount of money earned...
will win prizes
according to their ranks.
The two with the least amount
of money will receive a penalty.
- My gosh.
- After each round,
you will discuss
how you'll divide...
the money among you.
That's the amount of money
you'll individually receive.
Please go and get changed.
We'll begin the first round...
- at a different location.
- Okay.
(Let's go and make some money!)
What's this?
I bet we're supposed
to hang from those.
The first game to earn
money for your performance...
is Cutting the Rope.
Cutting the Rope?
One person from each team
will compete at a time.
The first one to be eliminated
will earn zero points...
while the other two
will earn one point each.
The winning team
will receive 3,000 dollars.
The team in second place
will receive 2,000 dollars.
The team in third place
will receive...
- 1,000 dollars.
- That's a lot.
How much is it again?
- 3,000 dollars.
- 3,000, 2,000...
SBS must be rich.
What we have so far is chump change.
Anyway, one member from each team...
will wear the harness
that is supported...
by five ropes.
You will stand on
a foothold and wait.
In the order I point at,
you will answer my question...
with the correct syllables.
(Answer the question
in the correct syllables.)
- Oh, that game.
- If you take more than...
three seconds or make no sense,
you will have to choose...
- 1 rope out of the 5.
- And it'll be cut.
Only two of them
are supporting your weight.
- Got it.
- You will lose support...
if one of those is cut,
and you'll fall when both are cut.
(The harness is operated manually.)
- Got it.
- Sounds like fun.
Please choose who'll compete first.
The first one from our team
will be...
- Kwang Soo.
- Sure.
- Se Chan is up.
- Since Kwang Soo is competing,
- we choose Jin Hyuk.
- Jin Hyuk?
- Go, Jin Hyuk.
- Because I'm tall?
- That's right. Stand in the center.
- Let's do this.
(The first players enter the arena.)
- Jin Hyuk!
- The center of Team Idol.
Your technology has improved.
- It's improved?
- Yes.
- Technology.
- It's always been this good.
I will now ask the question.
The one who's picked will give
a five-syllable answer.
And the other two
will answer in turn.
Why can't I give
a three-syllable answer?
I can't think
of any five-syllable words.
What are some five-syllable words?
Let's begin.
Focus.
What's a nickname you want
to give to your girlfriend?
Kwang Soo goes first.
(What's a nickname you want
to give to your girlfriend?)
- Pencil Eraser.
- What?
(Time's up.)
(Does he call his girlfriend
Pencil Eraser?)
What was that?
You could've said things
like "Cute Baby".
I couldn't think of anything.
Why can't you think
of words like that?
I have no idea now.
Why is it so hard?
Hey, wait.
Can you make it easier for me?
Fine. You should just say any
five-syllable word. Say anything.
I can't even understand
the question.
Pick a number from 1 to 5.
Four.
- Four?
- Yes.
(He picks number 4.)
Cut rope number four.
1, 2, 3.
(Is rope number 4 real or fake?)
(Gulping)
(He picked the real rope.)
(Number 4 was a real rope
that was holding Kwang Soo.)
Is this how it goes?
(Number 4 was a real rope
that was holding Kwang Soo.)
- Hey, wait.
- My gosh.
(They are terrified
by the technology at Running Man.)
Is this how it goes?
Gosh, I'm so surprised.
- It's going really low.
- I'm so startled.
- So this is how we play it.
- Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo, pull yourself together.
- What?
Pull yourself together.
- Hang on.
- He picked the real rope.
- I mean...
- He's so unlucky.
- Are you good at this game?
- Pull yourself together.
- Are you good at this?
- Stay focused.
Why are you so bad at this?
You could say things like
"Cute Baby".
- Now he's...
- You keep saying that.
That's the only word
you can think of.
He barely came up with the word.
- "Cute Baby".
- "Cute Baby"?
- That's the thing he can say.
- He just keeps saying...
"Cute Baby".
Can't you think
of five-syllable words?
- Okay.
- Let's continue.
What was your first impression
of Jessi? Jin Hyuk, you're up.
Totally tough girl.
(He gives a 5-syllable word.)
Good.
(Kwang Soo is supposed to give
a four-syllable word.)
Cute and sexy.
It should be a word
with four syllables.
My goodness.
It should go like 5, 4, 3, 2, and 1.
Cute and sexy has five syllables.
Please let this slide.
- He didn't know the rules.
- I'm sorry.
- We can't do that.
- He really didn't know.
- He didn't know the rules.
- Why did you not know?
Are you a fool or what?
He's dumb.
Admit that you're dumb.
I'm dumb.
Okay. I can let it slide then.
- I'll give you one more chance.
- Okay.
- This is the last time.
- All right.
- Okay.
- It's simple. 5, 4, 3, 2, and 1.
What's the first thing you look for
when you see a girl? Kwang Soo.
(What's the first thing you look for
when you see a girl?)
Body and face.
(Body and face)
Face, body.
Eyes, nose, and mouth.
Heart.
Brea...
(Brea...)
Wait. I'm sorry.
Cut it.
Hey! How could you...
- Cut it.
- I'm sorry.
I have no excuse.
You need a one-syllable word.
One syllable.
Nose or Eyes.
- My gosh.
- I know that.
I meant the heart.
I care about the heart.
That's how he feels.
What's wrong about that?
Stay quiet, Jessi.
You should've said eyes or nose.
Se Chan, you failed.
Pick a number.
- Three.
- Okay.
- That must be the real rope.
- Number three.
I hope Se Chan will
fall down right away.
1, 2, 3.
Gosh, I'm scared.
- Look at the angle.
- 1, 2, and 3.
(Sliding)
- Gosh, this is scary.
- Let's move on.
All right.
What comes to your mind
right now? Se Chan, you're up.
(What comes to your mind right now?)
Things are getting worse... Darn it.
- "I want to go home."
- Why is it so hard?
What's wrong with you?
"I want to go home."
- "I want to eat."
- "I want this to be over."
"I want this to be over."
My goodness.
That was easy.
Pick a number.
- Number 1.
1, 2, 3.
(What's rope 1 Se Chan picked?)
(No change)
There's no change.
(Relieved)
What part of your body
are you not proud of? Kwang Soo.
(What part of your body
are you not proud of?)
Face and body.
Why did you not say buttocks?
Gums, face.
- Jin Hyuk.
- Shoulder line.
(Shoulder line)
- Kwang Soo.
- Eyes.
- Se Chan.
- Everything.
(Everything)
(He suddenly makes a confession.)
- Everything.
- Good.
- Do you like it? Everything.
- What was that?
- Which part of your face?
- Okay.
What do you want to do
with someone you live? Se Chan.
I want to go on a trip.
Amusement park.
Time's up.
- You could say kiss.
- Kwang Soo.
My goodness.
(He's really bad at games.)
I thought Se Chan was going next.
He could've said "wherever".
- My gosh.
- Pick a number.
- Number 3.
(Kwang Soo picks number 3.)
(Kwang Soo already cut
1 of the 2 real ropes.)
(There's only 1 real rope
among the remaining 4.)
1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
- My gosh.
- Oh no.
He's the first one to lose the game.
He picked the real one again.
He's so unlucky.
- He's out.
- Come on out.
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
Team Indie and Team Idol
get one point each.
- We got one point!
- Yes!
Jin Hyuk did a good job.
Who's next?
- Next up is Ho Hyun Ju.
- They are so young.
- They are young, so...
- Hyun Ju.
- Am I going next?
- You should.
They are all too good.
- Just go.
- But they are young.
My gosh.
Just go ahead and do it.
Go up there.
She's so talkative.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
Wait. Let me practice.
- Just do it.
- Ask me a question.
- Any question.
What do you want to say to your mom?
I love you.
All right. That's what you do.
- Just do it. Go, Hyun Ju.
- I love you.
I love you, Mom.
Ho Hyun Ju, just come here.
Why are you yelling at me like that?
Come here.
I'm really tired.
I'm tired when I'm with her.
Hyun Ju, put this on.
She does have a unique character.
- My gosh. The ropes are...
- Just do it.
They must be good.
Please lean forward.
Good luck, Hyun Ju.
Go, Hyun Ju!
Go, Ji Young.
- Go, Ahn Ji Young.
- Good luck.
- Mapo-gu!
Hyun Ju, be confident.
Hey, shush.
(Hey, shush.)
I got this.
(Getting upset for the 3rd time)
Let's begin.
Wait. Please do it slowly.
Wait. Who's first?
- I don't know.
- He hasn't said that yet.
I don't know!
- Hey, I don't know.
- Let's just begin.
- I'm so tired.
- Please begin.
- Let's just begin.
- I don't know.
I'm sorry.
What do you look for in a guy?
Jessi. One...
- Face and...
- 2, 3...
Face, personality, body.
What?
I say.
(What? I say.)
- What?
- Bo Pil.
You should give her a yellow card.
- Hey, I said it.
- It was too late.
- Hey.
- It wasn't late.
- What?
- Earlier...
Hey, director.
- It wasn't late at all.
- Think about earlier.
Just give me a chance.
- It was too late.
- Please.
Don't get intimidated.
You're intimidated by her, right?
He's intimidated.
(Coward Bo Pil,
Director of Running Man)
Don't get cold feet. She failed.
- Time's up.
- Just give me a chance.
Just give her one more chance.
This is your last chance.
- Let's start over.
- So you don't get more chances.
- And Bo Pil, don't get cold feet.
- Okay.
She seemed pretty upset.
That's why he gave her a chance.
She seemed upset.
It's so funny.
Where did you have
your first kiss? Jessi.
- 1, 2...
- It doesn't have to be true.
On top of the closet.
Okay.
What?
Hey, it's hip-hop. Hip-hop!
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
Does that count?
Yes.
Wasn't it in the closet?
She just said it.
On top of the closet?
- It doesn't have to be true.
- You can just say a random place.
It doesn't have to be true.
- Okay.
- Just say any place.
- It doesn't matter.
- Next.
I don't know it yet.
Playground.
Bed.
It's not true. She's just saying
a random place.
- Next.
- Home.
Good.
This is more fun than I thought.
It doesn't have to be true.
I can't stop imagining
a kiss on top of the closet.
Squeezing myself into the space.
Good. What's the first thing...
you thought of when you woke up
in the morning? Hyojung.
Running Man is the best.
- That was a good one.
- Jessi.
Running Man again?
Should I go home?
What do I do?
- Oh no.
- What's wrong?
- She just sounds cute.
- "What do I do?"
- We say that.
I know what she means.
"What do I do?"
Pick a number.
Doesn't that count?
- Number 4.
It will be all right.
1, 2, 3.
(She picked the real rope.)
I like her reaction.
That was good.
- Hyojung.
- I like your reaction.
What should we do with Hyojung?
- What do I do?
- Oh no.
What gift do you want
to get Suk Jin? Jessi.
I hate everything.
(What was that?)
- Why?
- What was that?
I don't want to give him anything.
Why?
She doesn't want
to give him anything.
She just doesn't want to.
- Hang on.
- Listen.
She can't give him anything
because she doesn't want to.
She doesn't want
to give him anything.
- Put yourself in her shoes.
- That's not a gift.
"I hate everything" isn't a gift.
- She doesn't want to.
- She should name a gift.
She just doesn't want to.
- Then I...
- There's nothing she wants.
I don't want to give him anything.
Jessi was being honest.
She just hates it.
- I don't want to give him anything.
- She should name a gift.
A gift.
You failed. Pick a number.
- Number 1.
Cut number 1.
1, 2, 3.
(No change)
Good. You are safe. Okay.
My luck is very good.
I know. You're lucky.
How do you feel when you look
into a mirror? Ji Young.
This is great.
Let's laugh.
"Let's laugh". Good.
Big breasts.
(What?)
- Keep going.
- It makes sense.
- Go.
- Keep going.
- I can't think of anything else.
That was good. Keep going.
- Keep going.
- Go.
The best.
Yup!
- "Yup"?
- What was that?
- What does that mean?
- Yup!
- What's wrong with it?
Yup!
It's like an exclamation.
- Doesn't "Yup" work?
- Pick a number.
- 5.
- Pick well. 5.
1, 2, 3.
That was a great reaction.
- That was a great reaction.
- Hyojung is out.
Jessi!
(I won!)
No way! Did Jessi win?
(Did Jessi really win?)
Hey, you!
What was that man's name?
- Se Chan.
- "That man".
Jessi, go up there.
Don't look down on Korean-American.
What?
- Why? What?
- What?
- Take these off.
- "What?"
"Why? What?"
- "Your head bing bing."
Teach me some English words.
"Your head bing bing."
Se Chan.
- BewhY, let's go.
- Let's go.
I will win a point.
Let's go. What do you want to say
to your first love?
Haha.
Are you doing well?
Where did you go?
I miss you.
Hello.
Bravo!
Come on!
That was the worst.
- For goodness' sake.
- That was the worst.
- There's "Come" or "Go".
- "Come" and "Go".
He will fall in the next round.
"Come" and "Go" both works.
Doesn't he have any ad-libs?
Let's see how well you do later.
Jae Suk was
slowly getting nervous...
as his turn was approaching.
- Doesn't he have any ad-libs?
- Hyojung. Pick a number.
- Yes?
- 5.
- Suk Jin chose rope number five.
- Let's go.
1, 2, 3.
(It was a real rope.)
Okay. I like this angle.
I can't think of anything
since I am hanging like this.
Don't think too much.
Don't think of anything.
- What?
- I mean...
Why do you keep talking to me
in a casual way?
She wasn't talking to you.
- Why do you keep doing that?
- She wasn't talking to you.
Why are you attacking her
when she wasn't talking to you?
Don't hold grudges.
When did we agree
to talk to each other casually?
- Why do you keep doing that?
- I was talking to BewhY.
What did you say?
- BewhY.
- I was talking to BewhY.
Then why did you glare at me?
You are sticking out more.
Am I sticking out more?
Suk Jin.
- Focus on the game.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- I am so nervous.
Which nickname
do you want to give to your lover?
BewhY.
I...
(BewhY fails to answer in time.)
- Hey!
- For goodness' sake.
He couldn't freestyle.
Why couldn't you answer?
I tried to think of something.
There is "Cute Baby".
Is that the only thing on your mind?
Come up with something else!
- I don't need anything else.
- That's his only repertoire.
It works perfectly.
Jae Suk will play the game too,
right?
On, my goodness.
BewhY.
- Just say what comes to your mind.
- Hey.
Don't think too hard.
Experience!
No! Not experience!
He should go with the flow.
(Taken aback)
Would you let me speak?
Seriously.
Go with the flow.
- Let me speak, okay?
- Don't be like that, Jessi.
She shut me down.
I am absolutely sure
Jae Suk will get slapped today.
- I am absolutely sure.
- I won't do that.
Pick a number.
(It's BewhY's turn to pick a rope.)
Five.
1, 2, 3.
Okay.
(After all that nagging,
BewhY picked a real rope.)
What do you do first
when you go to the restroom?
BewhY.
I brush my teeth.
- Mind the syllables!
(BewhY gets eliminated
despite his team's guidance.)
(Team Idol and Team Indie
get 1 point each.)
That was incredible.
In the last round, we'll play
until a winner is determined.
Then the points
will be distributed accordingly.
- Jae Suk.
- I will show you.
Jae Suk, it'll be ridiculous...
- if you do badly.
- Here comes the king of ad-libs.
I'll show you how it's done.
To play the game
against the king of ad-libs...
Let's go!
- Okay.
- This is the last round.
- Let's go.
- The score is...
Kwang Soo, watch me win.
Jae Suk, show us what you can do.
Go up there.
- I will do my best.
- The genius of ad-libs will play.
- The emperor will play.
- Jae Suk, come on.
- Come on.
- You can do it.
- Cute Baby, let's go!
The national MC is the best!
Which nickname
do you want to give to your lover?
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook.)
Cute Baby.
(Caught by surprise)
Hold on.
Why did he steal that one?
(Why did you steal that one?)
(His only ad-lib was stolen
right before his eyes.)
Oh, my goodness!
- Cute Baby!
- Hold on.
- Cute Baby.
- There are other nicknames!
Right, there's My Baby.
- My Baby.
- Okay.
Your ad-libs are really limited.
- Why didn't you say "Pretty Baby"?
- Let's start over.
- Okay.
- For goodness' sake.
- "Pretty Baby" would have worked.
- I only thought of "Cute Baby."
("Cute Baby" couldn't help him.)
This is just a game.
Don't be nervous.
- All right.
- Okay?
- 2.
- Good luck.
- Two.
- He must be scared.
1, 2, 3.
Okay.
- Hang in there.
- Okay.
Jae Suk. Don't talk too much.
Cute Baby, let's go!
Okay!
(Ji Hyo came to lean forward
as well.)
Which past of yours
do you want to hide?
Jong Kook.
Glasses in my Turbo days.
Next.
Grasshopper...
Four syllables!
- You are driving me crazy!
- Good job.
What is your problem?
- Seriously.
- "Grasshopper..."
(He would have done better
in his rookie days.)
- How can we get him to ease up?
- What was that?
I am a fan, but...
- I am a fan too.
- This is too much.
- I want to see you do well.
- Okay, okay.
Just go down a syllable each time.
Why are you so nervous?
- I will survive.
- Make sure you do that.
- 4 and 5 remain.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- 4 and 5 remain.
(Hanging)
- His legs went weak.
- Hold on.
- For goodness' sake.
- 4 and 5.
Four.
Jae Suk chose rope number four.
1, 2, 3.
Come on down.
You looked like the biggest coward.
- You are a coward.
- The biggest coward.
For goodness' sake.
He tried to step on the floor.
Okay, okay. Okay.
- This is your last chance.
- Jae Suk, this is the last chance.
- Do as well as I did.
- I will show you.
- I will bring you victory.
- Seriously.
- Jae Suk.
- I will bring you victory.
- I...
- Go back to your seat!
I will survive.
I will win 3,000 dollars.
- The syllables go down by one.
- Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- I did it too.
What do you want to say to your ex?
Jong Kook.
Are you well?
Next.
That's right. You...
(That's right. I'm...)
Hold on.
I answered.
- Why can't you do it?
- I answered.
- For goodness' sake.
"I miss you." How's that?
- But...
- "I love you."
"That's right. You..."
It has an implicit meaning.
(Jae Suk was
all talk and no action.)
Bye.
Doesn't it work?
- Bye.
- 1, 2, 3.
"That's right. You..." doesn't work?
That's ridiculous.
I am sorry.
- He apologized.
- We won once, right?
Name your favorite Korean celebrity.
Sunwoo Yong Nyeo is the best.
2, 3.
Okay!
(Ji Hyo is the 2nd
to get eliminated.)
You won.
"What do I do?"
- "What do I do?"
- Okay.
- We are doing really well, right?
The results
of the first mission are out.
Team Idol placed 1st
and received 3,000 dollars.
(Team Idol acquires 3,000 dollars.)
Team Indie placed 2nd
and received 2,000 dollars.
Team Hip-hop placed 3rd
and received 1,000 dollars.
(Jae Suk was responsible
for the small amount of money.)
It's still a lot.
Now will come...
the process which requires
psychological warfare,
the division of the performance fee.
The four team members
will secretly choose...
whether they want to monopolize
the money...
- or share it with the team.
- 3,000 dollars is a lot of money.
Choose between the Monopoly Card
and Share Card...
and reveal it on the table.
If all members choose Share,
the money will be quartered.
If 3 members choose Share
and 1 member chooses Monopoly,
one member will take all the money.
If 1 member chooses Share
and 3 members choose Monopoly,
the one member will take
a quarter of the money.
- A quarter?
- Don't choose Monopoly.
- What if everyone chooses Monopoly?
- The money disappears.
- The money disappears?
- Yes.
- What will you choose?
- Share, of course.
- We will share.
I won't betray my team.
- Me neither.
- This is the first round.
- Let's divide the money equally.
You will have
the most amount of money.
Everyone.
Team Idol, sit down.
- Okay.
- You will share, right?
- Let's share the money.
- I think you will backstab me.
- Let's all choose Share.
- Okay.
Hyojung, I am the type to share.
What will you do
if that doesn't happen?
- I will be honest.
- I am the type to share.
- Take responsibility.
- Jong Kook will choose Share.
- I am the type to share.
- I will choose Share too.
- You will choose Monopoly.
- I don't trust your eyes.
No. I will choose Share too.
- Let's bring our hands together.
- Let's go.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
I know exactly which card to choose.
Show your card
on the count of three.
1, 2, 3.
(Team Idol promised
to share the money equally.)
(Will all the members choose Share?)
1, 2, 3.
(They reveal their cards.)
(Suk Jin chose Monopoly.)
For goodness' sake.
Suk Jin will monopolize the money.
What?
He will take 3,000 dollars.
(He changes his life
by monopolizing the money.)
You guys are so naive!
(Such is life.)
I think this team will have
2 Share Cards and 2 Monopoly Cards.
- No, no.
- Monopoly will win.
No. Let's share the money.
We made up our minds.
We have the best teamwork.
You made up your mind, right?
- Mapo-gu!
- Choose Share.
- Of course.
- Let's not be greedy.
- All right.
Show your card
on the count of three.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Share all the way!
(Monopoly, Monopoly,
Share, Monopoly)
(The three Running Man members
chose Monopoly.)
- One Share.
- For goodness' sake.
(For goodness' sake.)
- What?
- Ji Young will get some money.
- Ji Young, you got the money.
- For goodness' sake.
(Ji Young acquires 500 dollars.)
I can't believe you guys.
- You guys are so small-minded.
- You guys play so dirty.
Forget it.
Ji Young, thank you.
- For goodness' sake.
- I am glad you took the money.
- I am glad.
- How did this happen?
You said you will choose Share
no matter what.
Come on.
We will see them lose
all of the money.
Let's choose a random card.
- Let's say a few words each.
- Be quiet.
- For goodness' sake.
- Choose a random card.
Check the cards.
Let's choose Monopoly.
Monopoly?
- Do I have the right cards?
- We should choose Share.
- Let's choose Share.
- You understand, right?
- We might lose all the money.
- Let's choose Share.
(What?)
Stay still!
I already know what will happen.
- Choose a card without looking.
- He is trying to trick us.
You have two Monopoly Cards.
- See?
- You little...
Kwang Soo will betray us.
- I have two Share Cards.
- I am sorry.
(1 minute ago)
(Kwang Soo checked BewhY's cards...)
(and switched one with his.)
(Pretending to be calm)
- I am sorry.
- BewhY.
- Okay.
- Monopoly.
This is like "Tazza: One-Eyed Jack."
I simply tested BewhY.
Okay, you passed.
- What?
- I am serious.
- Both of them...
- Kwang Soo is so petty.
- We placed last.
- Share the money.
- Jessi, choose Share.
- Me?
This is not comfortable.
Comfortable?
What?
- This is not a competition.
- You mean "Competition."
- It's "Competition."
- "Competition".
What are you doing?
You are so embarrassing.
I am disappointed in you, Kwang Soo.
- How embarrassing?
- Weren't you trying to be funny?
If you are ignorant,
just don't say anything.
Did he say,
"This is not comfortable"?
Well...
That's not important, Jessi.
Okay?
Just pay attention
to what's important.
Why do you butt into every matter?
(Wow.)
I am going.
Where are you going?
You made up your mind, right?
- We will see 4 Monopoly.
- 1...
1, 2, 3.
(What will be the result?)
Monopoly... Share.
- What?
Only Jessi wins.
(Jessi chooses Share alone
and acquires 250 dollars.)
- Does that mean...
- Only you acquired the money.
(She cheers belatedly.)
(Everyone else chose Monopoly
and failed.)
Jessi is pure.
- She acquired a quarter of it.
- You liar!
She is nice.
"You liar"?
Me?
What did I do to be called a liar?
(Current Rankings)
Okay. This is good.
Jjamppong and tangsuyuk.
(They board the bus
for lunch and the next mission.)
- Where should we sit?
- I think we can take any seat.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Do we sit with the team?
- I don't want to do that.
- Sit with the team.
- No!
Okay.
I don't want to sit
next to Jae Suk.
He gives off bad energy.
Seriously.
(BewhY prepares a seat.)
Oh, no!
Will Jae Suk sit next to me?
Kwang Soo, please sit here.
- Oh, my goodness. No, no.
- What?
(She hates it.)
Please, BewhY. No, no.
- What is up with her?
- Is your butt wet?
What?
It's because he was nervous earlier.
Don't say anything.
Oh, no! Oh, my goodness. Seriously.
(They sit together
and move to the next location.)
Where are we going?
We will go and eat lunch.
BewhY, did you lose weight?
That came out of nowhere.
(What was that?)
- What do you know?
- Seriously.
- What do you know about BewhY?
- What was that?
Stay quiet
if you have nothing to say.
- I think so.
- What is wrong with you?
- You lost weight, right?
- I think so.
I am a fan of BewhY.
Which song of his do you like?
- If you are a fan, name 3 songs.
- 3 songs?
- He hasn't released three songs.
- What are you talking about?
(Brazen)
(What?)
- He has released so many songs.
- What are you talking about?
I was joking.
Jessi, what do you like to eat?
- Me? Fish.
- Yes.
- Really?
- Kimchi stew, doenjang stew...
Ji Young, what do you like to eat?
- Me?
- Yes.
There isn't anything I like.
You failed.
- Jae Suk, you failed.
- You failed.
- Make something up.
- Jae Suk.
You became flustered.
Jae Suk, you can save
this interview.
- Come on.
- This interview is going terribly.
- Ji Young.
- You can do it!
Cute Baby, let's go!
- Ji Young.
- Yes?
- This is his second attempt.
- You can do it!
What do you usually do
in your free time?
I stay home.
(The national MC gets knocked out!)
- The interview failed.
Cute Baby, let's go!
- Jae Suk, you can do it!
- Let's go!
- Ji Young is incredible.
Ji Young is incredible.
BewhY, how about you?
Ask BewhY too.
I was about to do that.
- Jessi, wait. Come on!
- Oh, my.
Come on!
- Okay.
- BewhY.
- What do I want to do?
- That's right.
What do you want to do the most
these days?
I want to give a concert.
That's right.
- My answer is the same.
- It's so true.
- You are cool.
- You are cool, BewhY.
Did you lose weight because
you didn't have any concerts?
- What?
- Stop talking about his weight!
- Stop it!
- That's completely unrelated.
- He lost weight.
- For goodness' sake.
(He keeps pestering BewhY.)
You are the worst.
Stop pestering him.
Hey, you lost weight.
Did you lose weight or not?
Hurry up and tell me.
- You lost weight, right?
- Yes, I did.
- You lost more than 3kg.
- Stop it.
We will lose viewers
because of you. Stop it.
Stop it.
He said we'll lose viewers.
I really want to perform,
- That's right.
- My body feels itchy.
- Seriously.
- You can't perform.
I do it alone at home.
Do you practice at home?
- I don't practice.
- You give a concert.
You guys can't communicate.
This has been going on
the entire day.
I really can't communicate
with Jessi.
- Stop trying.
- But...
Jessi speaks in a strange way,
but you are terrible
at understanding.
- We can't communicate.
- They don't get along.
We don't get along.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
Try another interview with Ji Young.
I want to see you succeed.
Okay.
- Ji Young.
- Yes?
What's your dream?
My dream?
(It's the national MC's
secret weapon.)
- I am not sure.
- "I am not sure."
(He gets knocked out
for the 3rd time!)
- He failed.
Cute Baby, let's go!
(Cute Baby is
in the worst condition.)
- He failed for the third time.
- Ji Young is impenetrable.
She knocked him out
three times in a row.
Maybe she doesn't have a dream.
- Everyone has a dream.
- What's yours?
- Me?
I have so many dreams.
- I didn't ask.
- What are they?
- Jee Seok asked.
- Jee Seok!
His name is Suk Jin.
Suk Jin.
(Her brain is muddled.)
- She got some of it right.
- It's okay.
- He is Ji Suk Jin.
- I understand.
- It could be a pet name.
- I am so sorry.
It could be a pet name.
- Yu Jae.
- Gosh,
- I mixed up the two names.
- Yu Jae.
- It's okay.
(Thanks to Jee Seok,
the atmosphere is friendly.)
Jessi, you should treat us today.
What do you mean?
- Pay for lunch.
- We are going to eat separately.
- Isn't that right?
- You should decide...
which member will pay
with the mission fund...
- for the meal.
- Really?
Decide on a member.
- What?
- One member?
Suk Jin, you should pay.
- How much will it be?
- He should pay,
- right?
- That's right.
You should pay.
Suk Jin should pay.
If each guest says
something nice to me,
I will pick up the tab.
Say a few words.
Suk Jin, you have a big heart.
- Okay.
I almost spoke casually
to you as soon as I met you.
Why? Did he seem easy?
No, no.
(Did he seem easy?)
- He looks young.
- Was that the reason?
- Yes. He looks young.
- Oh, yes!
- Are you sure he didn't seem easy?
- That sounds so fake.
- My compliment was sincere.
- Are you sure?
- You thought you looked stronger.
- That's right.
Wasn't that the reason?
I will pick up the tab.
- Okay.
- I am the only one who can do that.
I have 3,800 dollars.
2,000 dollars will be deducted
for the food.
(Does the food cost 2,000 dollars?)
- Nice!
- Oh, yes!
This is great.
Good job!
- Oh, yes!
- 2,000 dollars!
2,000 dollars?
- 300 dollars should be enough.
- Come on!
Suk Jin is generous.
He is flexing so much.
For goodness' sake.
- Paints.
- Look at those paints.
We will have the paint show.
There are various colors.
You will have the final race
after this mission.
The mission is
the King of Performances.
- What is that?
- The King of Performances.
Two teams will take turns...
to have three rounds
of a dodgeball match.
Dodgeball?
The 1st to 3rd places
will be decided by the points won.
Two teams will standby
at the waiting place on each side.
When the whistle sounds,
each team will carry a big banner...
and move to the attack zone.
Eliminate the opponents...
by dipping the balls in paint
and hitting their bodies with them.
We need to dip the balls in paint.
In short, it's a dodgeball
with six balls.
One member in each team
and use the banner as a shield.
One member.
You are out
if you get hit by a ball.
The game ends
when all the opponents are out.
The first match is
between Team Hip-hop and Team Indie.
- Okay.
- We will win.
- It's better to see them.
Otherwise, it will be confusing.
This is unrelated to quick wits,
so Jae Suk will be good at it.
- Really?
- I like hip-hop.
- Are you ready to tear them apart?
- Yes.
- Are you ready?
- Mapo-gu.
- Okay.
- Let's begin. Get ready.
(The 1st round starts.)
Run! Run!
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo
defend the team.)
(The others get ready
to throw the balls.)
This is cold.
(We divide the beats.)
Throw!
(Jessi launches her first attack.)
- How dare you?
- Throw!
(How dare you? Jessi.)
Jessi. I'm going after you.
(He counterattacks
with a blazing throw.)
He blocked it.
(He accidentally blocks.)
Give me the ball back.
- Behind you.
- Hey.
(He hits Jessi.)
- Jessi is out.
I'm not!
Why is Jessi out already?
- Jessi is out.
- I'm not.
- Hold on.
- Time out.
Jessi is out,
- but she's refusing to go out.
- Wait.
(She keeps on pretending
she doesn't know the rules.)
Wait, when did I get hit?
- What happened, Jessi?
- I have something to say.
- Oh, gosh.
- You're out, Jessi.
- Please step out.
- Go out before I hit you again.
- Move forward.
- We should move forward too.
Move forward.
I missed.
(Gosh, I missed...)
He can't even play dodge ball.
- Give me the ball.
- Why did you throw it on the floor?
(What game is he good at?)
What's wrong with him?
(This is our chance!)
(Kwang Soo is out.)
Over there.
Kwang Soo is out.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is out,
but why are they all laughing?)
- Why?
- Don't be mistaken.
- What's wrong?
It's not what it looks like.
(It's a good spot to be mistaken.)
He used me as a shield.
- I know.
- I was trying to go that way.
(He used Kwang Soo as a shield.)
Good job.
Kwang Soo, you were supposed to
hit the head.
Don't do that.
(How dare you hit Kwang Soo?)
(He hits the same spot.)
Hey!
Haha is out!
- Haha is out.
- Now!
- Take a ball.
- Take a ball now.
- Come on!
Go, Ji Young.
- Take a ball now.
- Come on.
(She advances with two balls.)
(What?)
(I'm very angry!)
(Flinging)
- What are you doing?
- What is she doing?
- Ji Young.
- What are you doing?
Ji Hyo,
you should attack for Ji Young.
- You should.
- Go.
You need to get both.
(She's been playing games
for 10 years as Running Man ace!)
(She played all kinds of ball games.
How will she attack?)
You need to get both.
(Tossing)
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
(Her throwing skill
regressed by 10 years.)
- Catch it.
- I mean...
She went out.
No!
(They're killed at the same time.)
(We won!)
- Good work. That was two in a row.
- Yes!
- Okay.
- Okay!
Round two is
Team Idol versus Team Indie.
That team has the advantage.
Ready...
I'm scared.
(Round 2 starts.)
(At the whistle, Team Indie...)
(secures the balls first.)
Already? You have to wet it first.
- Hey, hey.
- Take the ball.
- Good one.
(Heel-kick pass)
- Good job, Hyojung.
Take the ball.
Try hitting us!
(Try hitting us!)
- Good block.
- Seriously.
What do you think
you're doing, Se Chan?
(Se Chan the laundry machine is
working at full speed.)
- Hurry up.
- You have to dodge.
(Thump)
No!
(She keeps on blocking.)
- Good one.
- No!
(He was watching in the corner.)
- Good one.
- Hey.
- You're out.
- Ji Hyo is out.
Let go.
Haha is out.
- You're out.
(It passed Suk Jin...)
(and hit Kwang Soo.)
- You're out.
- You got him.
What's wrong? What's the matter?
- Kwang Soo, hold on.
- What's the matter?
- Hold on.
- That's all right.
- What happened?
- Move back.
- He's acting.
(Squirming)
- What's wrong with him?
- Why do you keep getting hit there?
- Hey, hey.
- In the groin.
Why do you... I mean.
Give me a ball. Quick.
- Hey, hey.
- Stop it.
- It's 3 on 2. You never know.
- Let's win.
You never know. Anything can happen.
- I'm scared!
- No, don't be afraid.
(Faking)
Go, go. Attack!
- Hey!
- Come here.
(Team Idol takes possession
and attacks.)
- Okay, you blocked it.
- I blocked it.
- Block it.
Hold on.
Go for it!
(Hyojung is an iron wall defense.)
I blocked it!
(Jong Kook and Se Chan's competition
is fueled by Hyojung's sacrifice.)
(Se Chan's blazing throw)
Okay, Jong Kook is out.
I should have done that earlier.
(Se Chan's blazing throw)
Come on!
- Come on!
- I was going to throw.
- I know.
- Come on!
- It's okay.
Hide behind me.
Hyojung.
(Rate of successful defense is
100 percent.)
Good job!
Throw it!
- Good job!
- What's with her?
Good job, Hyojung.
- Go forward.
- She blocks everything.
Good job, Hyojung.
(He gathers his energy...)
(and attacks again.)
Hey.
She got hit.
- Hyojung is out.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Hyojung.
- Hyojung.
- It went through her shield.
- Ji Young.
- Run away!
- Get him.
- Okay!
(Great job, Se Chan.)
We won.
- Goodness.
- We...
(After playing another round,
here are the results.)
1st place is Team Idol, 2nd place is
Team Hip-hop, and 3rd is Team Indie.
Are we doing that again?
We're doing this again?
First place is Team Idol,
so you can go first.
Please.
- Be honest.
- Let us raise our ranks.
- I know.
- Let's...
- do it this time.
- But look.
- Gosh.
- If I...
take 3,000 dollars...
You'll increase by a lot after this.
You're first place already,
so if you get more greedy,
you're a son of a gun.
(Why are you being so greedy?)
- You're first place right now.
- Hey.
I'm first place right now, so think
about it. Will I take all?
- I know.
- You have to promise me then.
- Let's share.
- Of course, we'll share.
Pick Share.
- Okay, I'll pick Share.
- Share.
- Did you make up your minds?
- Yes.
1, 2...
(What is Team Idol's result?)
Three.
(Monopoly again?)
- It's Monopoly.
- Suk Jin.
He's the worst.
(He fooled them again.)
(Let me get some air.)
You're incredible.
- I know.
- Suk Jin!
How could you pick Monopoly
for the second time?
I'm sorry, guys.
I picked the wrong card.
- That was my bad.
- Hey.
(He tries to make up for it, but
their team is about to dissolve.)
I can hear people cursing at him.
- Suk Jin, that was cool.
- Two times was cool.
I mean it.
- I didn't think he'd do it again.
- I'm sorry.
Suk Jin earned 3,000 dollars.
That was a mistake.
Team Hip-hop is next.
So that means...
If we pick Share,
- we can all have it.
- Same amount.
- I know.
- There's that face again.
Look at Kwang Soo's face.
He has that face.
(It looks like the face right before
he's about to cheat.)
Look at that.
- I'm serious.
- Look at him.
- Why are you laughing?
- No,
- I swore.
- I know.
- One...
- Kwang Soo is picking Monopoly.
Kwang Soo is picking Monopoly.
Two,
- three.
- Share or not?
It's gone.
(Only BewhY picked Share.)
Okay!
BewhY earns a quarter of the amount.
- Forever, BewhY.
- Yes.
- BewhY took it again.
- Only BewhY took it.
BewhY took it?
Four of us have high ranks.
- True.
- Correct.
So we should pick Share
and take 250 dollars.
I agree.
Please.
All three teams said the same thing.
250 dollars is good enough for me.
- My gosh.
- Please.
Ji Young,
will you pick Share or Monopoly?
Monopoly.
(Monopoly.)
(She makes a shy confession.)
- What?
- We should pick Share.
- She's too honest.
- We talked about this.
- I was simply asking a question,
- Ji Young.
but I got chills
hearing her response.
She's going to pick Monopoly?
(Touching)
- Nothing happened.
- Stop it.
(You didn't get chills.)
Come on.
- Nothing happened.
- My gosh.
Why are you doing this to me?
I got chills,
and she said, "Nothing happened."
Nobody told you to tell them.
What's wrong with her?
(She was laughing...)
(and spilled paint.)
- What are you doing?
- What's going on?
Don't do this. Come on!
Don't move. Their team is playing.
- But I...
- Have you made up your minds?
Wait. There's a cheater
on this team.
- What do you mean?
- Somebody took my Monopoly Card.
Who is it? Seriously, tell me.
- It's not me.
- Let me see.
- Who is it?
- It's not me.
- Hey!
- Ji Young!
(Is it Ji Young then?)
Is it you?
- What is the matter with her?
- It's not me.
- What do you mean?
- It has to be you.
- Hey.
- She's weird.
- What's this?
- I was wondering who it was.
(It was BOL4!)
(Exactly 1 minute ago...)
(She was innocently looking
at the cards.)
(Sliding)
(This is her first variety show,)
(and she already learned
a bad habit.)
Ji Young,
why are you being like this?
Show your cards.
See? Okay.
- I trust you.
- All right.
- Let's share it.
- One.
- Let's do this.
- Two.
- I hope everyone picks Monopoly.
- Let's do this.
Three.
Let's go.
- Show us your cards.
- Share?
Hey.
(Ji Hyo is the only one
who picked Monopoly.)
Ji Hyo picked Monopoly.
She picked Monopoly.
- No way.
- She picked Monopoly?
Ji Hyo wins 1,000 dollars.
- Unbelievable.
- Thank you.
- I'm shocked. She fooled us.
- You promised us.
But I...
Haha.
- You did a good job.
- Come on.
- Please don't be angry.
- I'm not.
Can't Suk Jin go home?
He looks so uncomfortable.
Do you want to go home?
- It's okay.
- I'll talk to the staff.
- This is life.
- This is life?
Next week, we'll laugh together.
What are you talking about?
Once Jong Kook gets angry...
He's not like that.
He's not like that. You cutie.
(Suk Jin gets far away
from the cutie.)
Jong Kook is not like that.
(I should try to think of
something good.)
It's okay. He's not like that.
- What was that?
- That was the worst.
He's worried Jong Kook will hit him.
He's not like that.
(With everyone happy,
Round 2 is over.)
It's time to carry out
the final mission.
You'll be given 30 minutes,
and this is your last chance
to win additional money.
It's called The Last Festival.
(The Last Festival)
This mission is important.
You never know until it's over.
Nine of you, who are not captains,
- will play Name Tag Elimination.
- Name Tag Elimination?
Once you rip off someone's name tag,
bring it to the captain's room.
There, you'll divide the money
between you and your captain.
One name tag is worth 500 dollars.
(The eliminated one
loses 100 dollars.)
You'll play the Share
and Monopoly Cards,
and the money will be divided
between you and the captain...
- according to the result.
- Yes!
When the 30 minutes is up, the 3
members with the most money win,
and the two members with
the least money will be penalized.
Please move
to your starting positions.
Okay.
(The Current Amounts)
I'll rip off all name tags.
I'm at the bottom right now.
(Jin Hyuk is
in a desperate situation.)
Since I'm on Running Man,
I want to experience it.
I want to rip off
as many name tags as I can.
These shoes are slippery.
What? What was that?
- Did your shoelaces hurt so much?
- Who is it?
(Se Chan copies Jessi.)
Then change your shoes.
- Who is it?
- Who do you think?
I'm just a guy.
- It's me.
- Gosh.
Hurry up and lace up your shoes.
What is he doing here?
This is my starting position.
As soon as the race starts,
I'll rip off your name tag.
I don't think so.
1, 2, 3.
Are we playing...
the Share and Monopoly Cards
here too?
- Suk Jin.
- Should I stick to my strategy?
If you ask me,
- you're already on the train.
- Right?
- I can't change my mind here.
- You're already on the train.
Just get punched once,
and that'll be it.
Seriously.
It'd be weird to stop here.
(Suk Jin is experiencing
an inner conflict.)
(The countdown begins.)
3, 2, 1.
The race starts.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
Come here for a second.
Jessi.
Let's make a plan.
How much do you have?
I have more than you.
Did you have to say it like that?
"I have more than you."
Why did you...
Gosh, I can't believe her.
(Hurry up!)
- Is someone there?
- No.
Let's make a plan.
I'll protect you to the end.
(You'll protect me?)
- You're lying.
- I promise.
Fine, I'm leaving.
Bye.
(Inner conflict)
Come with me, Jae Suk.
- All right.
- I won't rip off your name tag.
Do you promise?
Are the microphones
in some kind of room?
(Some members are
looking for microphones.)
Microphones.
(Why are these two
looking for microphones?)
For those who don't feel confident
about Name Tag Elimination,
we've hidden a few
Bluetooth microphones...
here and there
so you can perform alone.
If you find a microphone...
and sing for a minute
without getting caught by anyone,
you can get the name tag
of a person you choose.
Really?
(That way, you can win 500 dollars
without ripping off any name tag.)
(Where are the microphones?)
(Ji Young is looking for
a microphone too.)
(She finds one.)
My heart is pounding.
I want to hide somewhere.
(She is looking for a safe place
where no one will find her.)
(Excited)
I'll sing "Some" by BOL4.
(She starts singing
while hiding in the corner.)
(Being careful)
(The singer doesn't want
anyone to come to her concert.)
(She gets startled
in the middle of dancing.)
(While Ji Young is singing
carefully,)
(Jae Suk and Jessi appear.)
- What was her name again?
- Hyojung.
- She's scary too.
- No.
I met her in the elevator earlier.
(The concert is nearing its climax.)
- Ji Young?
- Ji Young.
(And there are two people
getting close to the singer.)
(Please don't come near me.)
In my opinion...
(The uninvited audience
is approaching.)
We can't go on like this.
(Ji Young is
just around the corner.)
(Will Ji Young manage to sing
for a minute?)
- I know.
- Can you walk in front of me?
(Jessi doesn't trust Jae Suk.)
I'm tying my hair up,
- and I can't relax.
- You can relax.
(Ji Young has sung for a minute.)
(Happy)
- We should trust each other.
- No.
You've disappointed me
so many times today.
(Startled)
I'm just...
- I'm just...
- Stop.
She's over there.
(Jessi finds Ji Young.)
She's over there. Let's go.
Who?
Ji Young?
Please. I'm scared.
(Jessi charges at Ji Young.)
Gosh, this is scary.
Hey!
- She's over there!
- Jessi!
(Just then)
(Jae Suk blocks her way.)
Jae Suk. Wait!
(Ji Young is blocked on both sides.)
- Ahn Ji Young.
- Wait!
- Just a second.
- Come here.
- Wait!
- Ahn Ji Young.
Just a second, Jae Suk!
- Listen to me.
- Ahn Ji Young.
- Please listen to me.
Jessi, listen to me.
(But...)
(Jae Suk ripped off
Jessi's name tag?)
Hey! You...
Jessi, listen to me.
(Their alliance breaks down.)
Jessi is out.
(Ji Young runs away
in the meantime.)
Wait, Jessi.
(Jessi loses 100 dollars.)
Jessi.
- Seriously?
- I'm sorry.
You betrayer.
- You betrayer.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Jessi.
- Sorry.
- I never.
(Their non-aggression pact
breaks down.)
Jessi.
(Hyojung is quietly
taking a look around.)
(BewhY appears right then!)
(It's BewhY!)
(He innocently approaches Hyojung.)
(She gets ready to attack.)
Gosh, you startled me.
(The innocent impala's eyes)
(The impala starts running
right away.)
(The baby beast, Hyojung,
hunts down her prey.)
(Haha pops out all of a sudden.)
(He attacks the baby beast.)
Who is it?
(Haha hid as soon as he heard
Hyojung's voice.)
(And then he attacked her
from behind.)
(The impala luckily survives.)
Hey!
(Her name tag is ripped off.)
It's ripped off.
(Hyojung is out.)
Hyojung, thanks.
If you sing, I won't catch you.
(Haha brings Hyojung's name tag...)
(to the captain's room.)
- Haha is here.
Am I the first one here?
- What happened?
- I ripped off a name tag.
Whose name tag?
Whose name tag did you rip off?
- Hyojung?
- Then...
it's time to divide the money.
(500 dollars will be divided
between Haha and Ji Hyo.)
We don't have to do this, Ji Hyo.
Are you in second place right now?
- Let's share it.
- You're in third place.
- If we share it, we can both go up.
- Okay.
Haha will break his promise.
I'm serious.
- Are you sure? Do you promise?
- Yes, I promise.
If you've made up your minds,
show your cards.
- 1, 2, 3.
- I'm serious.
(If one of them betrays the other,
he or she wins all 500 dollars.)
(Will both of them pick Share
as they promised?)
- I'm serious.
- Haha will pick Monopoly.
(Only Haha picks Monopoly.)
- I'm serious.
- Haha will pick Monopoly.
(I'll take it all.)
I was 100 percent sure.
I was 100 percent sure
that he'd pick Monopoly.
You still don't know him?
- I knew it.
- Ji Hyo has a long way to go.
I told Kwang Soo,
- "Haha will pick Monopoly."
- Definitely.
- That was unnecessary.
- Exactly.
- Go away.
- Totally.
(Swearing)
I knew Haha would pick Monopoly.
Haha wins 500 dollars.
Okay. Thank you.
500 dollars...
(Jong Kook brings a name tag
to the captain's room too.)
Jong Kook is here.
- Jong Kook.
- Let's do it.
You ripped off BewhY's name tag?
- You can see it?
- Hand it in.
- This is fun.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
I'll show you my big picture.
(It's time to divide
their winnings with Suk Jin.)
- Show this Share Card.
- Okay.
- I'll show Monopoly.
- Why?
"Why"?
(Laughing)
- "Why"?
- I have to show Share?
- I'll show Monopoly.
- You'll show Monopoly, and...
You'll show Share,
and I'll show Monopoly.
Okay, let me pick a card
randomly then.
What are you talking about?
- You're being ridiculous.
- This isn't working.
- I understand.
- Sir.
It's not easy.
- This is Share.
- Your right hand is Share.
- Right hand, okay.
- Leave your left hand on your knee.
- Okay, I'll lift my right hand.
I'll lift my right hand. Okay.
- Okay. 1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3.
(Monopoly)
(They both picked Monopoly?)
I picked my right hand.
Why is it Monopoly? What happened?
(He shuffled the cards.)
- My gosh. What happened?
- Was that necessary?
- Why is this in my hand?
- Suk Jin.
What happened?
You were like a gambler.
- You knew he was picking Monopoly.
- He's a gambler.
- When did he do that?
- My right hand.
- Why is this in my hand?
- How did he do that?
When did you switch them?
- You both earned zero dollars.
- What happened?
(Sighing)
I was out of my mind, Jong Kook.
I had no idea.
I switched without realizing.
(Jae Suk ripped Jessi's name tag.
He walks to the captain's room.)
Jessi?
- Jessi.
- You took your teammate's name tag?
This is one-on-one.
- Really?
- Kwang Soo.
You can rip
your teammate's name tag?
Hurry up.
- What do you want?
- We have to pick Share.
- Will you pick Share?
- Yes.
You have a lot of money,
but I don't.
You have to pick Share so that
we can earn 200 dollars each.
Okay?
- You mean it, right?
- I mean it.
- Watch. This is going to be fun.
- This is fun. I want to watch.
(They watch the spectacle
unfolding in front of them.)
- You should pick Share.
- Hurry up.
That'll be better.
Kwang Soo.
Don't even look at this.
I'm going to ditch this.
Okay.
- You have to be serious.
- Okay.
I'm serious.
(He checks the Monopoly Card
on the floor.)
I'm serious
because this doesn't make sense.
You're holding the Monopoly Card.
(You're holding the Monopoly Card.)
How did you know?
(He got caught.)
Who are you? How did you know?
(He's frightened.)
How did you know?
- I know you.
- Were you watching me?
- I got chills. How did you know?
- Goodness.
(Before the others got here,
he got for an extra Monopoly Card.)
(He hid an extra Monopoly Card
in his pocket.)
(He pretended like he was
throwing away the Monopoly Card.)
(He tried to switch the cards
while Jae Suk wasn't looking.)
How did you know?
Come here. Take the Share Card.
- I will.
- Let's get started.
Here.
- I'll pick Share.
- One...
This is Monopoly.
Fine. Take this away.
Okay.
Take this away.
(They decide to take away
the Monopoly Card.)
All right. 1, 2, 3.
(Grabbing)
- What's wrong with you?
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- I'll never earn any money then.
Hurry up! We're waiting.
Hurry up.
- Let's go.
- Pick Share.
- I will.
- I'm serious.
- Me too.
- 1...
- You'll be sharing 500 dollars.
- 1, 2, 3.
- We'll share 500 dollars.
1, 2, 3.
(They don't move.)
Why can't we do this?
- Lift your hand!
- Pick.
250 is not bad.
- This is interesting.
- Can't you do it?
This is interesting. We can't do it.
- We can't.
- It's not easy.
1, 2, 3.
- All right.
- Share.
- Jong Kook, come over here.
- Suk Jin.
(Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
each earn 250 dollars.)
My gosh. Jae Suk was unbelievable.
- What are you doing?
- No, it's not like that.
Two people on Team Idol...
(He got attacked by
Jin Hyuk and Hyojung.)
ripped my name tag.
Young people are so...
Him...
and as Jae Suk got older...
We should do a double attack.
- I think we should.
- But you swear?
- I swear.
- Okay.
Because I did this with Jae Suk,
and he ripped mine off.
- Really?
- Yes. I got betrayed three times.
I hear Jessi's voice. It's Jessi.
(Flinching)
She's complaining about me.
Right now,
everyone is betraying each other.
We have to double tag team.
(She gets closer to Jae Suk.)
Let's find Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk is right behind her.)
What are you doing here?
(Grabbing)
Hey!
(Betraying again)
He didn't get it.
- I got it.
- You didn't.
- It's not completely off.
- I got it.
I got Jessi.
- I got Jessi.
- Okay!
- I got her name tag.
- He didn't.
- I got it.
- It's not completely off.
- Let's see. It's off. You're out.
- It's off. See?
- Give it back.
- What?
- What? Hey!
- No.
- How dare you?
- I'm sorry, Jessi.
Jessi.
He's like a ghost.
- Hold on, Jessi. I'm sorry.
- This is the second time.
I'm sorry, Jessi.
What happens to that?
The one I ripped?
This doesn't count.
- You got it after I ripped hers.
- Does it start over again?
All right. Give me mine.
(Ripping)
- Not yet.
- Yes!
(Jong Kook came out of nowhere.)
(He removed Jae Suk's name tag.)
- He betrayed me twice.
- Am I out?
- Yes!
- How?
He betrayed me twice.
Well, you didn't move.
What was I supposed to do?
- You have to give it back.
- Jong Kook.
- I have to take it with me.
- Jong Kook is scary.
- He's so scary.
- In that moment.
- Come on.
- You ripped hers off too though.
I wasn't done,
and you came up from behind.
What do you mean?
You were wrapping up,
so I went up to you.
I wasn't done.
Don't make me feel disappointed.
You were done already.
Why are you disappointed?
Why would you play like that?
- Play how?
- Why?
- What do you mean? What's wrong?
- That was dirty.
Jong Kook!
Where are you going?
Jessi is following us.
Catch Jae Suk. Please.
(He runs away without looking back.)
I haven't seen Haha pick Share
in this room yet.
No, I did once.
Jae Suk.
Why do you keep ripping off
Jessi's name tag?
- She's so mad at me,
- I mean.
so she's talking trash about me
to everybody.
(My gosh...)
My gosh. Jae Suk.
I took pity on you. I liked you.
How could you do this to me?
Jae Suk is next.
Let's go.
- I'm serious.
- Not again.
All right.
(They place Monopoly Cards
away from them.)
Monopoly.
(Squirming)
(Slapping)
(He finds the hidden Monopoly Card.)
This.
My bad.
- How could you?
- My bad.
Okay. I accept.
That was a mistake. I swear.
I accept.
I deserve to be slapped. I accept.
(He's reflecting deeply.)
I swear.
(This is the last time.)
Let's get started right away.
Let's get started.
Stand up.
- Stand up.
- Pardon?
Stand up.
- Why?
- Stand up.
- Hold on.
(As soon as
he pushes Kwang Soo over,)
(he finds another Monopoly Card.)
(How could you?)
Hey.
- I don't have anymore.
- You don't, right?
- Where did he hide them?
- I had two.
- You and I both have Share Cards.
- Okay.
- 250 each.
- Let's go.
1, 2, 3.
(Share, Monopoly)
What? Where did you get this?
Where did you get this?
What?
(Where did he get
the Monopoly Card?)
(Jae Suk searched Kwang Soo.)
(He put the Monopoly Card
on his seat.)
(Hands are faster than the eyes.)
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
- I didn't see that.
- "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
- All three are here.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk.
- Okay.
(He's happy
as he leaves the captain's room.)
(There's somebody here.)
(Quiet! Did he see me?)
(He approaches carefully
from behind.)
(Peekaboo)
(He caught me.)
- Jessi. I'm sorry.
- No, no.
Jae Suk, I let you go twice
because you didn't have any money,
but you were so cheap to me.
I know.
But let me explain.
- I didn't have any money.
- How could you do that twice to me?
- We promised.
- Jessi.
I'll give you my name tag,
- so no more hard feelings.
- Let's start over again.
- Okay.
You can't go after mine again.
Let's start over again.
(As soon as
they settle on an agreement,)
(Jin Hyuk comes out of nowhere
and attacks.)
(Jae Suk helps Jessi
and attacks Jin Hyuk.)
- Loyalty.
- I helped you.
Did you rip mine off or not?
(At that moment!)
(Jong Kook keeps on
coming up behind Jae Suk.)
(He removes Jae Suk's name tag.)
Stop coming from behind.
- You should have ripped his off.
- I was going to.
(He gets 100 dollars deducted.)
(Peeking)
It's crazier here.
(She witnesses chaos
outside the elevator.)
(She pauses and hesitates.)
(She closes the door and withdraws.)
I don't want to get caught up
in that fight.
(This is that fight.)
Grab him. I got him.
- Here.
- I can't do it.
Jessi.
(Jin Hyuk is resisting a lot!)
(He endures
to the best of his ability.)
No worries.
(He can't win 2 to 1.)
(Jae Suk removes
Jin Hyuk's name tag.)
- Darn it.
- Jin Hyuk is out.
I got eliminated so many times.
Kwang Soo.
- This will be fun to watch.
- Let's do half.
I have to watch. This will be fun.
- I'm serious.
- Me too.
- There's nothing in this hand?
- No.
- I'll hold this.
- I don't think he'll do it.
Let's pick Share.
(Will they both pick
Share this time?)
For sure?
There's nothing in this hand.
(He looks for the Monopoly Card.)
Let's hold our hands.
That's a good idea.
Good one.
Last time. Here.
- Let me see.
- Let's get started.
Me too. See?
- I wonder what will happen.
- One,
two,
three.
(They don't move.)
- Why?
- Why aren't you holding it up?
- Hold it up.
- Don't you understand?
- You hold it up on three.
- Why not?
- Why aren't you holding it up?
- Okay, on three.
Let's get started. 1, 2, 3.
(Slowly)
Share.
- Share.
- How warm.
- We did it.
- Done.
The race is over.
Let's move our final location.
(The race is over.)
Like I said before,
the top three members will get
prizes according to the ranks.
(The top three members get prizes
according to their ranks.)
And the last two
will receive a penalty.
Okay.
The winner with 4,550 dollars is...
Ji Suk Jin.
- He's really...
- Thank you.
- He's really sly.
- My goodness.
He's really sly.
- I've been in first place for long.
- Jee Sly.
- Did he have that much money?
- Yes.
We didn't have to try so hard
to rip off his name tag.
It was no use.
(Jessi still doesn't
understand the rules.)
I kept explaining the rules to her
while they all celebrated him.
We ripped off his name tag a lot.
- But it didn't work?
- "Did he have that much money?"
Jae Suk, seriously...
The member in second place
with 2,130 dollars is...
Song Ji Hyo.
- What?
- Really?
Is Ji Hyo in second place?
- Me?
- She got a lot of money at first.
- I know.
- Next.
- Right?
- He's got 2,130 dollars.
It's Kim Jong Kook.
Me? Isn't it you?
- I thought it was you.
- He just ran around...
ripping off the name tags.
When you took off the name tags,
it felt like you tore my skin off.
You grabbed it like this.
- Jessi.
- What?
- Okay. Sorry.
It looks like an American sitcom.
American sitcom.
- Is it a sitcom?
- Okay.
- Is it "LA Arirang" or what?
Haha and Ji Young are
in fourth place.
Se Chan is in 6th, Kwang Soo is
in 7th, and Hyojung is in 8th place.
- Jin Hyuk is in ninth place.
- Yes.
Now I will announce
the 10th, 11th, and 12th.
This can't be.
And we have Jae Suk, BewhY,
and Jessi left.
- Two of you will receive a penalty.
- Who would that be? You two.
You?
- This worked out.
- My team is so bad at games.
- What?
- The member in 10th place...
- doesn't receive a penalty.
- Please.
The 10th is...
(Who's the member in 10th place
who won't receive a penalty?)
BewhY.
Jae Suk is in 11th,
- and Jessi is in 12th place.
- This is why I...
- I...
- They are the best couple.
- Jessi.
- The best couple.
- This is why...
- I hate Jae Suk so much.
- We should've cooperated.
- Wait.
Jae Suk and Jessi.
- We lost?
- Yes.
"We lost?"
- "We lost?"
- Oh my goodness.
Please bring in the prizes
for the top three members.
- It's Korean beef.
- Congratulations.
First place gets Korean beef,
second place gets Korean pork,
and third place gets vitamins.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Suk Jin.
I'll eat it with my family.
- Next is the penalty.
- Yes.
It's the highlight of college campus
festivals. Water balloon throws.
That's right.
It's frustrating that I ended up
in here after all the betrayals.
(They throw water balloons
at the betrayer.)
This is hard. I can't hit them.
(Kwang Soo throws balloons
at Jessi.)
Look at that.
- Gosh, Jessi. Are you all right?
- Okay.
I can't just hit him.
- Jessi. I'm so sorry.
- What are you doing?
No, I didn't mean it.
I couldn't control it.
Who was that?
- Are you okay?
- Hey, don't talk to me.
- Jessi, are you okay?
- I'm not a baseball player.
Don't talk to me.
Gosh, I'm just...
Darn it.
I'm not throwing it anymore.
- What are you doing?
- I can't do this.
- Are you okay?
- I was trying to hit the wall.
Are you all right?
I tried to hit the wall.
- Throw it again.
- Kwang Soo.
Did you hit me in the face?
No, I throw it upward.
- I couldn't control it.
- Okay.
- Oh no.
- You know what?
Just...
(Slurring)
What did you say, Jessi?
You know what? Come on.
- Jessi.
- Hey.
What's the problem?
Jessi, what was that?
I hate you.
Jessi's nose was running,
and it went back in.
- I've seen it come out,
- That's enough.
but I've never seen it go back in.
- It was like a cartoon.
- I know.
- Bye, everyone.
- Bye.
- See you later.
(The veiled people put
everyone in confusion.)
(Sim Eun Woo from "A World
of Married Couple" is here.)
(Kim Min Gue and Kim Jae Kyung)
(The real dilemma begins now.)
(A soccer game
full of slapstick comedies)
(The swamp of dilemma where
they have an X man in the team?)
(Will they be able
to the endless dilemma?)
(And...)
(They meet So Min
after a long time.)
(Something is going on
between the two of them.)
(Between the couple,)
(Kwang Soo is in a dilemma.)
(The members at the crossroads,
Too Much Dilemma)