(This episode is a skit about
a patriarchal family, the Yu's.)
(Family Tree of the Yu's)
(Father: Jae Suk,
Sons: Haha, Kwang Soo)
(Father: Jong Kook,
Sons: Suk Jin, Se Chan)
(Daughters-in-law: Ji Hyo, So Min)
(Chuseok full of happiness
like the full moon)
(To celebrate the national holiday,)
(the Yoo family is
gathered together.)
It's Chuseok.
(The first three people
to arrive are...)
Gosh.
(Chairman Yu's second son,
Jong Kook and his family.)
(Yu's second son Jong Kook)
(Jong Kook's son Suk Jin,
Suk Jin's wife, Ji Hyo)
What's this?
(Jong Kook, Suk Jin, and Ji Hyo
came to hold the ancestral rite.)
- My goodness. Grandpa...
- Come in.
Come on in.
It's quite large.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
(Suk Jin's answer ruined the mood.)
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
(Suk Jin is playing
Jong Kook's eldest son.)
(That makes it too hard for everyone
to get immersed in the situation.)
Why? What is it?
(Yoo Suk Jin, Jong Kook's eldest
son, Song Ji Hyo, Suk Jin's wife)
Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin's appearance makes it hard
for Jong Kook to act.)
Suk Jin.
You brat, take better care
of your appearance.
(He looks as if he went through
a painful ordeal.)
- Why do you look so old?
- Dad.
Look at me. You see?
I still look so young and healthy.
- Dad.
- What's with you?
You made soup with a snake for me,
but it turned out to be
a venomous one.
Remember? You said
it wasn't venomous.
- Gosh, seriously.
- It's a family tradition.
Everyone in this family ate
a venomous snake.
Seriously, what happened to you?
(Jong Kook chokes up
whenever he sees his son Suk Jin.)
- Honey.
- Why...
Strangely, you look better with Dad
than with me.
(It feels sad for some reason.)
This is so...
- It doesn't make sense.
- What is going on?
I've done a lot of role plays,
but this is too unreasonable.
This is what comedy is about, Dad.
- Right.
- But how can you...
have so many kids
without even getting married?
(How can you have so many kids
without getting married?)
(He's a child that Jong Kook had
without getting married.)
- It's weird...
- I mean...
that they all ran away
right after giving birth.
I don't know why they ran away.
Honey, what if Father doesn't
like me?
- I told him about you.
- What did you say?
I told him good things about you.
I said you are pretty.
(Jeon So Min, Se Chan's wife,
Yoo Se Chan, Jong Kook's second son)
(Oh, my. He said I am pretty.)
I told him that he'll meet
such a pretty woman.
Honey, must I carry this?
My gosh. You look so pretty today.
(He suddenly compliments her.)
- Do I look pretty?
- Yes, you dressed up prettily.
Honey, you look great as well.
We're here.
- Hi.
- Come on in.
Father, hello.
- I'm sorry we're late.
- Hi, Dad.
- Hello, Father.
- Oh, my. Hello.
- Come on in to give him a bow.
- Suk Jin, hello.
- Hello.
- Come on in.
- You didn't come empty-handed.
- Se Chan, you should carry it.
- That's so thoughtful of you.
My second son and his wife
are so attentive.
- Dad, I'll give you a bow first.
- It's not me.
- Oh, no. I'm sorry.
- My gosh.
(Dad, I'll give you a bow first.)
(I'm not your dad.)
- You brat.
- Wait. I'm sorry.
- How could you...
- I thought you were my dad.
- Don't do that.
- I already told Suk Jin...
to take better care
of his appearance.
- Right.
- So, he's my elder brother.
- Give Dad a bow now.
- Let's do that.
- Dad, I'll give you a bow.
- Hello, Father.
- Welcome.
- That's great.
I wish you good health.
Thank you.
- See? Se Chan looks his age.
- Yes.
- We should give him a bow too.
- Yes, we should.
All right.
(Hesitating)
Dad, you must be
feeling uncomfortable.
Exactly. Go ahead, you brat.
Must I give you a bow?
Of course. That's what you should do
as my son.
- We can just skip it.
- You should do it.
- I wish you a long, healthy life.
- Thank you.
(He's being playful.)
You punk!
(He didn't bow properly.)
- You always...
- How rude.
- Hey, why did you bring this?
- Why did you do that, Suk Jin?
- Why did you bring that stick?
- Come over here, you punk.
- Why did you bring it here?
- Come here.
- Yes, Dad. I just...
- You always...
- Did I raise you like that?
You always wanted me to be manly.
- I didn't raise you this way.
- But...
Cham, cham, cham.
Come here.
(My poor husband.)
- He's playing that game again.
- I didn't raise you this way.
- I understand, Dad.
- I didn't raise you like this.
Do it properly this time.
(The eldest son got a second chance
to give him a bow.)
Come on.
(He's being playful again.)
(He bowed
halfheartedly and quickly.)
That was a good push-up.
(He's too proud to bow
to Jong Kook.)
- What was that?
- It was a nice push-up.
- Wasn't it cool?
- Dad, shall I help Suk Jin?
- Yes. You help him.
- Here we go.
(Here we go.)
- That's great. You did well.
- He did properly this time, Dad.
- That's good.
- It wasn't hard.
- I wish you a long, healthy life.
- I always told you...
Why did you bring that stick?
That's mine.
- Jae Suk will be here shortly.
- Oh, he's coming.
- Gosh. He's coming.
- My goodness.
I feel like I'm home here
whenever I come.
(Jae Suk, the eldest son
of the Yoo family)
(Haha, Jae Suk's eldest son,
Kwang Soo, Jae Suk's second son)
- We haven't seen them in a while...
- Be quiet.
Don't be so loud.
Let's walk quietly.
We haven't visited them in a while.
- How nice.
- Indeed.
Someone's here.
- Is it you?
- They must be here.
They can just come in.
Why would they press the doorbell?
- Uncle Jong Kook, we're here.
- Who is it?
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Uncle Jae Suk is here.
- Hello, Uncle Jae Suk.
- Hi.
- How have you been?
- Hello.
- My big brother is here.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- Have you been well?
- Is he...
(They're facing a crisis.)
He's my eldest son.
- He didn't take care of himself.
- Is he your eldest son?
- That's why...
- It's been a while.
You should take better care
of your appearance.
Jong Kook, have you been
practicing martial arts?
No, that's not it.
You know I work out every day.
- I know.
- Why...
did you all come alone?
Why didn't you bring your wives?
- So Min, you're barefoot.
- Hold on.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you going somewhere?
I'm sorry. I should've
paid more attention.
- I forgot to wear socks.
- Are you a spa owner?
No, I'm not. I'm her husband.
- You're her husband?
- Yes.
- I see.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Why did he get eyebrow tattoos?
Don't say such a thing.
- Don't take this seriously.
- It's not like that.
- Actually...
- This is just a role play.
I got the tattoos
at the spa I work at.
- Let's sit down.
- Please sit down.
Was Uncle Jong Kook married?
- He must be married seeing that...
- Of course, I'm married.
This is my sister-in-law.
- Who?
- She's my sister-in-law.
Is she Jong Kook's wife?
- No.
- No, not him.
- She's Suk Jin's wife.
- Suk Jin is my husband.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm her husband.
- She's his daughter-in-law.
- He's my father-in-law.
- I'll explain, Uncle Jae Suk.
- I was born in 1988.
- I can't believe...
- It's a mess.
- She's my daughter-in-law.
Wasn't Ji Hyo married before?
- What are you talking about?
- Why would you bring that up?
- You know she had...
- Don't talk about her past now.
- What are you talking about?
- We met after a long time.
Hang on a second. You...
- talk as if you're older than me.
- That's not true.
- You should be careful.
- You brat, I warned you earlier.
- Dad, please don't be mad.
- You little...
You brat.
- You're younger than me.
- I'm sorry.
You brat.
- You're younger than me.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, stop.
What's our relationship?
Is he my cousin?
Don't we have seniority over him?
- It's decided on the basis of age.
- I'm really sorry.
- I didn't know that.
- Between cousins.
- Jae Suk, teach your kids well.
- I'll do that.
- I'm sorry.
- We didn't know.
Listen, you two. If you do something
wrong, your dad will get hit.
Why would I get hit?
- Understood.
- Got it?
- Oh, gosh.
- Discipline your kids properly.
(Peace came for a moment
as Jong Kook held the stick.)
How dare you act like that
when you don't even have a job?
What? I run my own business.
That's a lie. You're jobless.
My business is about to take off.
- I don't believe you.
- What have you been up to?
I sell pork cutlets.
I enjoyed your pork cutlet.
(I enjoyed your pork cutlet.)
It was so good.
- I really enjoyed it.
- What are you doing?
- They never forget to mention it.
- Right.
- It's going to become a hit.
- He's doing so well.
Let's sit down.
- Someone's here.
- Who could that be?
- Who is it?
(The doorbell is ringing.)
(Someone else is here?)
- Someone's here?
Who is it?
Could that be someone's girlfriend?
- Hello?
- What?
My goodness. He's...
What? What's going on?
- But...
- Is someone here?
Who is it? What's going on?
Isn't he the customs agent we met?
- Someone's here. Oh, my.
- Who is it?
- His name has "Gu", right?
- Hello.
- Hey, what are you doing here?
(Kwon Hyeong Gu, assistant director,
plays cameo roles)
His name is Hyeong Gu.
What's wrong with you?
He failed last time.
Did he get a second chance?
I'm a lawyer.
- You're a lawyer?
- I see.
What kind of lawyer
would be shaking like that?
- I guess he drank a lot last night.
- Why...
- is your voice so shaky?
- No, it isn't.
I've seen a lot of lawyers
like him...
You're Chairman Yu's family, right?
- Yes, we are.
- All right.
He looks a little like
Lee Hong Ryeol.
- Hyeong Gu.
- He looks like Lee Hong Ryeol.
I can't help myself when I see it.
(Slapping)
He has such a big forehead.
- He has such a big forehead.
- I know what you mean.
- I can't help myself.
- I know.
- Please understand him.
- It's like flipping a pancake.
- It's a habit.
- He likes to play jokes.
- I have this habit.
- I know.
- Yes.
- All right, Hyeong Gu.
Oh, right. Grandpa was rich.
It must be about his inheritance.
- Oh, right.
- He had a lot of money.
Unlike our appearances,
our family is rich.
Exactly. Our family owns
a lot of properties.
That's why I married you, honey.
You didn't marry me for money.
You chose me because I'm handsome.
They got immersed in their
characters too much.
- They're doing method acting.
- Above all...
- I can't even breathe.
- They're...
- like method actors.
- They're like method actors.
- It feels like it's real.
- You look so happy.
It'll be hard for them
to get out of their characters.
Chairman Yoo made
his last will and testament.
I'm here to deliver it to you.
I guess Grandpa kept up
with trends.
It looks like a mission envelope
we use.
(What could be written in his will?)
- It's quite long.
- It's long.
"Dear my children
and grandchildren."
I have decided to select the heir
in a fair and just manner...
after I leave this world.
Make three types of jeon
using eggs that I like...
and serve them
at the ancestral rite.
The family who finish preparing
the ritual table first...
will inherit a large portion
of my fortune.
The losing family
will do house chores.
"The losing family
will do house chores."
"Good luck, everyone."
My goodness.
I guess eggs are important
for today's mission.
Today is the 10th Chuseok...
after Chairman Yoo passed away.
The heirs will be chosen...
just as Chairman Yoo wrote
in his will.
We must be chosen as the heirs.
Each of you will receive 10 eggs.
You have to make 3 types of jeon
by 3 p.m...
using eggs that Chairman Yoo liked
following the given recipes.
The family that prepares the table
first will win.
- My team has only three members.
- That's right.
But you will have benefits instead.
Of course. Only then, it'll be fair.
It won't be hard
if we follow the recipes.
However, the number of eggs
you have is also important.
The person in the winning family
that has the least eggs...
will have to do house chores.
(The person with the least eggs
will do house chores.)
The rest members of the family
will inherit his fortune.
As for the losing family,
only the person with the most eggs
will inherit his fortune.
The rest of the family
will do house chores.
If a family fails to complete
the dishes by 3 p.m.,
all the members of the family
will do the chores...
- before going back home.
- Okay.
You can either hide
or protect your own eggs.
(It's within their discretion
to hide or protect their eggs.)
You can also find out
someone else's eggs...
and use them.
Meanwhile, you can get more eggs
by completing missions.
And all eggs have
only one day left on it,
so you can't resell them.
- So can we steal others' eggs?
- Yes.
(It means they can steal
someone else's eggs.)
Gosh, it will be a mess.
This is an individual game
after all.
You're right.
But it can be like a team game.
We will have to protect
our family anyway.
- Exactly.
- Right.
Please go take a look
at the ancestral rite table.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Jong Kook.
- Look.
Grandpa has a protruding mouth.
(Amazing DNA)
- Se Chan got his mouth.
- It's all mixed up.
He's got Jae Suk's teeth.
- He looks like me though.
- Right. He looks like Se Chan.
- They mixed our faces.
- Right.
I think you're right.
We should place
three kinds of jeon here.
- Okay.
- Egg jeon.
- We just need to make three jeon.
- All right. Get out of here.
I was talking about the key point.
(The recipe for three dishes will
be revealed after each mission.)
I have to protect my family first.
All right. Now you should
keep your eggs safe.
- But you can't carry them around.
- Right.
So I will give you some time
to hide the eggs...
in the neighborhood.
You can break the eggs
of your team, but...
- What?
- It can happen.
You can break
the eggs of your team members...
to make jeon quickly.
If you betray your team.
I can cook using
someone else's eggs.
Gosh, we should try
to make our team win.
- Family comes first.
- That's ridiculous.
- We can do that later.
- If you betray us...
- No, I won't do that.
- We will disown you.
- Seriously, I won't be like that.
- I won't let it slide.
I'll slap you in the face.
- Sure.
- I think our team will win easily.
Kwang Soo has been light-fingered
since he was little.
I take after my dad.
- Why do you think I'm like this?
- I know.
Gosh, this is dangerous.
- And Haha isn't so reliable.
- Gosh, no.
I know. He's just as bad.
- But we're quite clean.
- You guys are no different from us.
Uncle Kong Kook, didn't you say...
that you don't believe in
fortune-telling earlier this year?
- But you wear pink all the time.
- The best color for you...
- is pink.
- It's pink again.
I do believe it.
What are you talking about?
I shouldn't do things
that are not good for my fortune.
I'll give each family
five minutes...
to hide your eggs.
You should hide your eggs well
and look for others'.
It's disadvantageous
to hide eggs first.
Because the second team might
find some eggs while hiding theirs.
Exactly.
So the fathers will play the game
of slap-match to decide the order.
- Okay.
- Slap-match.
Dad!
- Great.
- My dad is the king of slap-match.
- Dad.
- I haven't done this for long.
We should play the game
of slap-match on Chuseok.
It's been a long time though.
We have to win this game.
Okay.
(Powerful player, Jong Kook,
King of slap-match, Jae Suk)
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
Put it down here.
Don't step on it.
- Go, Dad!
- Good luck!
Let's do this.
- Father, go get them!
- Dad!
(Jong Kook slaps first.)
Okay!
(Jong Kook fails to flip it.)
You've lost your strength.
(Rooting for their family)
It's okay.
Hang on.
- What are you doing?
- You did the same thing to mine.
Hey!
You did it too. It's okay.
There you go. That's my boy.
You're so cute.
(Jong Kook's eldest son is
a favored child in the family.)
(Ta-da.)
Move over.
You might get hit.
- Okay.
- You might get hit.
He can't do that
to Uncle Jong Kook though.
- Be quiet.
- Dad tried not to touch him.
Will you hurry? Go ahead.
(Jae Suk's turn)
1, 2, 3.
- Yes!
- Oh, no.
(Jae Suk fails to flip it.)
(It's Jong Kook's turn again.)
- Dad!
- Good luck!
(Jae Suk's ttakji)
(Jae Suk's turn)
(Jae Suk flipped
Jong Kook's ttakji.)
(Our dad won!)
(Jae Suk won
the game of slap-match.)
It's okay.
- Dad!
(They laugh and cry
playing the game of slap-match.)
We have to play the game
of slap-match on holidays.
Right.
- This is upsetting.
- Our family has become one.
Team Jong Kook lost the game.
I'll give you the eggs first.
- Okay.
- Take the eggs.
You can hide the eggs
in the entire area.
It has my name on it.
If you find their eggs
while hiding yours,
you can break them
or use them to make jeon.
All right, Team Jong Kook.
Please begin.
- You have five minutes.
- Okay.
Do we have to hide all of them?
My gosh.
Where should I hide these?
If they find our eggs,
I'm sure they will break them.
What should I do?
My gosh.
Where should I hide them?
This is serious.
I think we should go up there.
(Se Chan hides his eggs...)
(in a kitchen cupboard.)
(Ji Hyo hides her eggs...)
(in a tissue box.)
This is good.
(This is perfect.)
What if I can't find my own eggs?
This isn't open.
Where should I hide the eggs?
(Where should I hide the eggs?)
Hang on. I'm pressed for time.
(She has only 5 minutes,
so she's pressed for time.)
Oh, right. Open your bag.
Open your bag.
Don't break them.
You have three.
Make sure not to break them.
Seriously, you should
never break them.
(She found an even better place.)
Don't break this.
(Don't break this.)
Don't you dare break it.
You have one egg here.
(Meanwhile,
Jong Kook's eldest son is...)
Be careful.
(He's filming a thriller
by himself.)
I hid five eggs in here.
I should hide one more.
There are six here.
I will hide mine in this house.
Where?
- Why do you ask?
- You...
- Don't be like that.
- Why do you ask?
It's not like I'll do
something with your eggs.
Even your family might betray you.
You never know.
You can't say that we never know.
- Haha, listen to me.
- I know them.
- I can't believe them.
- Dad, don't even think about it.
I want my team to win.
(He doesn't really mean it.)
You think? Then why
are you going there?
- What?
- You said you want our team to win.
I'm just checking to see
if there's a place to hide.
I should definitely
hide some in the house.
But this is...
Where should it go?
I don't think it's a good idea
to hide them separately.
Should I hide them all together?
(Staring at Kwang Soo)
(He's like a hyena
lying in wait for his prey.)
Gosh, Haha.
(He gets caught...)
(staring at Kwang Woo.)
- Don't be like that.
- What? Why?
- What?
- Let's not do this to each other.
- What did I do?
- I could see it on your face.
What did I do?
- Don't do that.
- Gosh, no.
I didn't do anything.
Do you really want to do this
to each other?
I mean...
You two are brothers.
Why are you hiding it
while saying that?
All right.
We are family. We have to
make our team win. Okay?
(Team Jong Kook is done
hiding their eggs.)
Shall we go out now?
Please go ahead
and hide your eggs.
It's obvious
where they hid the eggs.
It's better for us to find them.
I'm sure they hid it there.
(They will look for the eggs
while hiding theirs.)
I should find eggs
in a place like this.
Do you want to leave your egg here
with me to prove our friendship?
Really?
- If it breaks, we're done.
- Right. We're done.
Then I'll break your eggs.
Haha, here.
Let's put the eggs in here.
This is about friendship.
Put it in.
(Haha puts his egg
in the liquor box.)
(Is Kwang Soo
putting in his as well?)
Wait. You didn't put in yours.
(Only good people can see
Kwang Soo's egg.)
Oh, right. I should
put mine in here.
Okay.
- Get lost.
- Haha.
- Forget it. Get lost.
- Haha, I'm serious.
- No.
- I'm not doing this.
- Give me another chance.
(Kwang Soo has the liquor box
to himself now.)
What?
My gosh.
Haha.
(He found eggs?)
(Jong Kook hid 2 eggs in the box.)
- My gosh.
- Are there eggs?
(He runs hurriedly
to Kwang Soo upon hearing the news.)
- Let me see.
- Look.
My gosh.
We have to get rid of them.
We should make jeon with these.
Let's do that.
We should use them.
This is amazing.
This is great. Well done.
(Kwang Soo is on fire.
Where is he hiding his eggs?)
- No.
- What?
Why?
(He looks anxious.)
(He smells a rat and goes
through the bag hurriedly.)
(He found So Min's eggs in the bag.)
We all have the same ideas.
I can find more eggs. I can.
What do you want, honey?
Let me pour you some juice.
Get me a cup.
I'll get you some juice.
Thank you.
Suk Jin likes water.
Don't give him juice.
- He'd want some.
- No. He doesn't drink juice.
He only drinks water.
I like juice.
- I like juice.
- No. This is for your health.
You haven't changed
since your childhood.
No, Suk Jin. Just drink water.
You just fell for a woman and...
I fell for a woman?
Honey, you should watch and learn.
What do you mean?
- I'm nice to you.
- She wants him to watch and learn.
I'm really...
Honey.
- What's going on?
- What's wrong?
What?
(They all are flustered.)
(Even the skit master is flustered
by the situation.)
(Something amazing happened
to them before they knew it.)
- This is great.
- Already?
- Good for you.
- Look at you.
- There you go.
- No.
- Look at you.
You're just back
from your honeymoon.
You're unbelievable.
- Hang on.
- Your honeymoon...
Isn't it that you have
an upset stomach?
- Don't try anything strange.
- No.
It's an upset stomach.
(They are having a productive day.)
No. While hiding her eggs,
she ate a raw egg.
They're back.
Why are you fighting already?
Uncle Jae Suk, why are you
fighting already?
Gosh, he's unbelievable.
- There you go again.
- He's really sly.
Kwang Soo, what's wrong?
- Why are you guys fighting?
- We should do this together.
- Don't do things like that.
- What?
Oh, it wasn't him.
Don't do things like that.
(He yells at Suk Jin
for no reason.)
Oh, it wasn't him.
Stop doing things like that.
- Why did you get confused?
- It's a habit.
- I see. Okay.
- Can you make some room for us?
Well... Can I call Se Chan's wife
by her name?
- You can...
- She's your niece-in-law, so...
- You can call me Sweetheart.
- Sweetheart.
- "Sweetheart"?
- Yes.
She told us great news earlier.
- She even did that too?
- Yes.
Just earlier, she did it.
(Jae Suk is taken aback.)
She meant that she can't cook today.
It means Ji Hyo should
do all the work.
- To avoid doing work?
- Yes.
She even had that calculated
in her head.
My goodness. I'm surprised.
My dear Pouty Mouth...
Pouty Mouth is the fetus' name.
- We named the fetus Pouty Mouth.
- Yes, Pouty Mouth.
- I didn't know.
- That's intense.
- What now?
- I'm dizzy.
Will our show air at 11 p.m?
(The airing schedule might
be changed.)
The 1st mission will begin
in 10 minutes.
Before that, we'll give you
the recipes.
Whether you use your own eggs
or someone else's,
you just have to make jeon...
and put the exact number of jeon
on the table.
You're not allowed to steal
food on the table and broken eggs.
- Broken eggs?
- Yes.
- You can't steal any broken eggs.
- We should steal it before cooking.
Yes, you need to steal an egg
before it's broken for cooking.
Remember you can't steal such eggs.
We'll give you the recipes now.
- The recipes?
- Yes.
- I think we should...
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- We should go in.
- Let's go in.
- Team Jae Suk will receive...
(Beef jeon)
(Beat five eggs
and add salt and pepper.)
(Make 10 pieces of beef jeon,
and it's done.)
Considering the difference
of the number of members,
Team Jae Suk will receive
three pieces of each type of jeon.
Because we have fewer members?
- So we have to make 10 pieces.
- We have to make 10 pieces.
"Add salt and pepper..."
- And then cover the meat...
- "Cover the meat with flour,"
- "and then cover it with egg."
- Then we can just fry it.
- Is that it?
- Yes, 10 pieces.
We need five eggs,
which is the most important.
- Exactly.
- We need five eggs.
We need beaten-up eggs.
It's important to get five eggs.
Hold on a second.
It gave me a lot to think about.
We should figure out
what would be the best.
- My gosh.
- Are we going to play a game?
You'll play a game
to get more eggs.
And you'll have a 10-minute break
while cooking.
You can find your eggs back
or steal someone else's eggs.
- Shall we go outside?
- We need more eggs.
Let's go outside
to bring our eggs...
- Let's find some eggs.
- Broken eggs can't be stolen.
- Let's go out to find some eggs.
- Right?
If we break an egg outside,
we can't use it, right?
Can't they steal it
if I break it now?
(Can't they steal it
if I break it now?)
- Can I break it now?
- Yes, you can.
- Whose egg is it?
- Whose egg is this?
Is it yours?
(The owner of the broken egg is...)
- It's So Min's.
- What? Where did you find it?
- I found So Min's egg.
- Where?
- Do you have more?
- Hey, step on it.
- Where did you find it?
- I found So Min's.
I can break another one, right?
- Yes.
- Really?
(I can break another one, right?)
- Whose is this?
- Whose egg is it?
I found Jong Kook's egg.
(I found Jong Kook's egg.)
- What?
- Jong Kook.
Hey, Jong Kook.
Oh, right. He's my dad now.
You broke two eggs.
- Yes, I broke 2 eggs.
- You need 3 more eggs.
Jong Kook, one of your eggs
is broken.
I won't forget what he did.
I have made up my mind.
(I have made up my mind, Kwang Soo.)
(Without knowing
Uncle Jong Kook is mad at him,)
(Kwang Soo is looking for
another egg.)
(The master of finding eggs
is searching every cupboard.)
I think they hid an egg... What?
(Did he find another egg?)
(It's the egg that Se Chan hid.)
Okay.
I'm on a roll today.
(He's like an egg detective.)
I'm on a roll.
(My gosh!)
- Go away.
- Wait.
- Why?
- No reason.
- It's not what you think it is.
- Let me see it.
- I'll just have a look.
- What? It's not yours.
Hey, don't do that. Jae Suk!
- Why?
- I said, stop it.
- Jae Suk! Stop it.
- What is it?
Stop it.
- I'm serious.
- Why?
- Hey, stop.
- Jae Suk, stop her.
- What's wrong with you?
- Get her away from me. Look at her.
My gosh. Seriously.
- Jae Suk.
- Stop. Gosh, seriously.
Why are you doing this?
- Come on.
- I have something to tell him.
- What is wrong with you?
- What are you doing?
(Kwang Soo put the egg
in his mouth.)
(Cracking)
(The egg got broken in his mouth.)
Hey, come on. My gosh.
- Okay.
- Hey.
(It's so embarrassing
to show this on Chuseok.)
(The dirty fight in the Yoo family)
Okay. I broke one egg.
Why did you put it in your mouth?
- You can't use it now.
- She tried to...
Oh, boy. You can't use it now.
She tried to break the eggs
in my bag.
I can't believe this.
Was it Se Chan's egg?
Gosh.
I should've broken it sooner.
I broke almost five eggs.
I don't have any left...
Gosh. Jae Suk!
She broke another one!
Hey, how could you... Jeon So Min.
She broke Jong Kook's egg too.
(2 of the 4 eggs Kwang Soo found
are useless now.)
Jae Suk, we had four eggs.
I shouldn't have come
into this room. Darn it.
Did they fight again?
- We found a few eggs,
- Really?
- Whose eggs?
- but So Min broke all of them.
Who did that? Was it Ji Hyo?
I just said So Min did it.
(I just said So Min did it.)
Your eldest son can't seem to
get it together.
- Honey, I'm here.
- Oh, right.
You shouldn't go near So Min.
- Why?
- He has Alzheimer's.
I found two eggs,
but she broke them both.
Whose eggs were they?
One was yours,
and the other was Jong Kook's.
How did you find mine?
I found yours
where I was going to hide mine.
- Gosh.
- We all think alike.
- But she broke them.
- Did you find mine?
Jong Kook, let's begin.
- Okay.
- So you found my egg.
Is that mine?
- Why did you do that?
- What?
- Where did you find that?
- Sit down.
- That's yours too.
- This one is yours too.
Why did you find only mine?
It's Kwang Soo's.
(The eldest daughter-in-law Ji Hyo
found two eggs of Kwang Soo.)
Let's put it in here.
(She's proud.)
- Didn't you break the other egg?
- There was another one.
I put two in the bowl.
Why did you keep one egg?
- I put it in my pocket.
- Why?
- It must've been broken.
- To exchange it with mine.
- Gosh, you.
- Gosh.
(He's unbelievable.)
- Well...
- Bring one of your eggs.
I feel like we have another member.
It's like "X-Man".
- We found three eggs.
- Why did you do that?
I planned to exchange the egg...
with mine if I saw someone
finding mine, but So Min broke it.
Good job, So Min. Good job.
- Thank you.
- Well done, Sweetheart.
- She's good at everything.
- Gosh.
- Darn it.
- It's a tie, right?
We'll begin the first mission now.
The first mission is
Nagging Hide-and-Seek.
Both teams will play
offense and defense.
The defensive team write
what you heard the most...
on national holidays
on your headband,
and hide in three minutes.
The offensive team must find them
in 10 minutes,
and when you read the phrase
on the headband, that person is out.
That sounds fun.
The team that eliminates all members
on the other team faster wins...
- and will receive three eggs.
- Great.
- Okay.
- While hiding or searching,
you can look for eggs
or hide them as well.
The three of you will wait...
- in this room.
- We can just read the phrases.
Since this team has five members,
three of you will be tied together.
Then let's have Jong Kook
and Se Chan play individually...
- and we...
- The three of us together.
Then your team wins.
So Min, write a phrase on it.
Write something they would
never be able to imagine.
- "Why won't you get married?"
- Do you know any difficult phrases?
(They're trying to think of
something difficult to read.)
- You mean, English phrases?
- Yes, English phrases.
You know... Something that sounds
like packshae... Payshave?
- "Why don't you..."
- "Don't do..."
Is there a word like "newtrorasive"?
Something long and difficult.
(He's making up weird words.)
It's so frustrating
since I'm not good at English.
- "You should..."
- Poly... Polyster...
- No.
- Or...
How about that word?
It begins with "F". Fa... Fame...
What is it that you want to say?
I just want difficult English words.
Gosh, this is so frustrating.
- "Favorite"?
- Yes.
I'm sure they'll write
something difficult.
Jae Suk, tell us
some difficult phrases.
(Jae Suk, tell us
some difficult phrases.)
They won't be able to read
Chinese characters.
None of them will.
They won't be able to read it
even if we stand in front of them.
We can just walk around
without worrying about them.
Let's write Chinese characters
and find some more eggs.
That's a great idea.
Let's just walk around.
Jae Suk, I'm so happy that I'm
on your team. My dad.
I respect him so much,
and I'm proud of him.
Me too. He's so cool.
How about this?
"Hwang Min, go and tell
his mom to come here."
Hwang Min is my cousin's name.
It'll be hard for them
to guess his name, right?
"So Min, go and..."
- What should I write?
- Go on.
"And bring Hwang Min's mom here..."
- Grandmothers often say that.
- Exactly.
- It's done.
- That's better.
"You should do awesome comedy..."
- "that everyone would like."
- That everyone would like.
(Tell Hwang Min's mom
to come to Hakgok-ri.)
You should leave now.
You have three minutes.
- Let's get going.
- We have to hide outside.
- Jong Kook, shall we go there?
- Yes?
- Where?
- The trampoline.
Shall we?
They can't read this
even if they find us.
- That's a good idea.
- Let's go up there.
- I thought the same thing.
- Suk Jin,
don't worry about us
and keep So Min safe.
- Okay. We will...
- Honey, see you later.
- We should find more eggs too.
- Let's go up.
- Let's find some eggs too.
- Sorry?
Let's do that.
There it is.
(He's excited!)
(Se Chan has nothing to fear
as he has everything he needs.)
Let's make them all fall down.
- Let's go in.
- That's a great idea.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
- If they try to come in here,
- Hey.
we can make them fall down.
- You stay there. I'll be here.
- At the corner.
- When they come in here,
- Yes.
- we can make them fall down.
- Exactly.
(They think like little boys.)
Let's go this way.
- I found Kwang Soo's egg here.
- Really?
He hid his eggs around here.
- How about we hide in a car?
- That's a good idea.
- Me too. Let's hide in a car.
(They're innocent
like little children.)
- 8, 7,
- Let's go.
- 6, 5...
- Tell them we're here.
4, 3,
- 2, 1.
- We'll let them know.
The mission starts.
We'll find them.
- Let's find them first.
- There they are.
- You read Se Chan's.
- They're here.
(Come here and try to read mine.)
We welcome everyone
who comes here.
(He's excited about playing
with his cousins.)
(Like this.)
(He's singing excitedly.)
(The nausea-inducing
jumping strategy)
"Everyone..."
(The nausea-inducing
jumping strategy)
"Everyone would..."
"Everyone would like"?
"Everyone would like". Yes.
(They're not doing
the Sargent jump.)
- Kwang Soo, take a look.
- Hey.
You can't be there.
- You can't grab him.
- Hold on.
- Just a second...
- Se Chan!
Awesome and favorite...
- And...
- And favorite...
- Favorite.
- Yes, favorite.
Awesome and...
You should do awesome comedy
that everyone would like.
Awesome and... Right?
Nice.
(Se Chan's out!)
Run, Jong Kook!
(Jong Kook manages
to escape on his own.)
It's Jong Kook. My gosh.
He looks like a servant, doesn't he?
Especially with that
around his head.
Why isn't anyone coming over here?
It's a little upsetting.
This has to be the best spot.
(They're well hidden,
but too well hidden.)
(They're bored.)
(Stomach rumbling)
I must be hungry.
- Are you?
- Did your stomach rumble?
- It's upsetting.
- I know.
They're not letting us do our jobs.
Let's work, people.
I want to work.
Can I find the eggs then?
I can, right?
(After being eliminated,
Se Chan searches for the eggs.)
Hold on a second.
Okay.
(He spots an egg.)
It's Jong Kook's.
(It's Jong Kook's.)
Darn.
(Se Chan spots an egg
that belongs to his team member.)
Darn.
(What do I do?)
(And so the inner struggle begins.)
(Up until 5 minutes ago,
they rode the trampoline together.)
(The servant is clueless
as to what's happening.)
Where's our bowl?
(What choice will Se Chan make?)
It's Jong Kook's.
(I'll add Jong Kook's egg.)
(He quickly cracks it
before anyone sees him.)
This is Jong Kook's too.
(He adds two eggs
that both belong to Jong Kook.)
(Team Jong Kook's egg count)
That's four.
(Meanwhile,
Haha's only searching for eggs.)
This is So Min's.
What else can I do though?
(They have all their five eggs.)
That's five, right?
- Where are they?
- 7, 6...
- Where's Suk Jin?
- 5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
- It's impossible to find them.
- Please gather around.
(The search ends
with only Se Chan being eliminated.)
- Why couldn't you find us?
- Where were you?
- We were all upset.
- Weren't you in a room?
An urgent situation
never occurred for us.
- Why didn't you look for us?
- It was upsetting, you know.
Did you find some eggs?
How many did you find?
- Did you find more?
- Yes.
- You? How many?
I found Haha's.
- Just one?
- Yes. Let's head upstairs.
- Do we have 4 then?
- Yes, we only need 1 more.
We only need one more.
(It's Team Jae Suk's turn to hide.)
For us, this is just a formality.
We'll be searching for eggs instead.
(Team Jae Suk's plan:
Find the eggs.)
Keep searching for the eggs
even if they find you.
- Okay, got it.
- You know what I mean, right?
- The prize is only three eggs.
- Okay.
(Instead of hiding,
they'll be searching for the eggs.)
What's a difficult
Chinese idiom to read?
Are you done?
Sasangnugak.
- Sasangnugak?
- Yes, sasangnugak.
That'll be okay.
"Always keep in mind..."
"the four-character Chinese idiom,
sasangnugak."
"Always keep in mind..."
"the four-character Chinese idiom,
sasangnugak."
(Kwang Soo searches
the definition of "sasangnugak".)
Sasangnugak means...
a house of cards.
Right. So what did you write down?
"Always keep in mind..."
"the four-character Chinese idiom,
sasangnugak."
And one should.
- A strong foundation is always key.
- That's right.
Right.
(Always keep in mind
the Chinese, idiom sasangnugak.)
(Wherever I am,
let nangjungjichu happen.)
(Haesan lies in front of me
while Songshan is behind me.)
Here we go then.
Where would they be?
I doubt there are any here.
They won't make it that easy.
This is a good hiding spot.
(Searching thoroughly)
- The search will begin.
- What should we do first?
Should we find the other team
or the eggs?
Let's see where they are.
- Are you searching for eggs?
- Of course.
We should look for the eggs.
Let's see where they're hiding.
(How are my eggs doing?)
They're doing well.
(Someone comes by.)
(Jae Suk was on
the opposite side.)
It's Jae Suk!
(He runs away
after spotting So Min's eggs.)
Kwang Soo!
(He spots the eggs and calls
Kwang Soo to run away together.)
She's on my tail. Come on.
(Without being able
to put on his shoes properly,)
(he runs with his hair
flapping in the wind.)
- Wait. Someone took my eggs.
- Here she comes.
(Kwang Soo hides in the back.)
Man... No, young lady...
(He jumps over the wall
before she can read it.)
Jae Suk!
Must you go this far?
(His cameraman is forced
to jump over the wall too.)
I can't jump the wall.
(The grasshopper within him
remembers how to be nimble.)
There's nowhere to go from there.
Must you go this far?
(Do you have a problem with this?)
I saw "man".
(So Min turned around
to go back when...)
Aren't there any eggs here?
(Is something there?)
(Gulps)
(She slowly moves toward Kwang Soo.)
Don't you have a bag?
(Her voice keeps getting closer.)
You're not carrying a bag.
Hey!
(Busted!)
Hold on. Hey!
(An unexpected profit)
Get over here.
You took my egg, didn't you?
I won't guess your sentence,
so give me back my egg.
- I couldn't find it.
- Someone took mine.
- Sangnugak...
- Kwang Soo, no.
An old bachelor.
(She has no idea
what sasangnugak is.)
- Don't be like this.
- I'll get down.
I'll get down there.
(He's relieved by
her lack of intelligence.)
What is called sasangnugak...
Wherever I am...
(She can't read any of the idioms.)
- Wherever I am...
- This will block her view.
- Wherever you are...
- Can you hold us both yourself?
- Did you find them?
- We need to read this.
- Nang...
- Here they are.
Can you read that?
Wherever I am,
let "nangjungjihu" happen.
- Wherever you are...
- The idiom.
Make sure you're always bold, Ji Ho.
It's nangjungjichu!
Wherever I am,
let nangjungjichu happen.
let nangjungjichu happen!
- Jae Suk, you're out.
- Okay.
- Sasangnugak...
- It's an idiom.
The Chinese idiom sasangnugak...
- Jae Suk, you must come out.
- Right.
I can't believe I saw it as "Ji Ho".
- The time...
- 10 seconds left!
10 seconds!
- Sasangnugak...
Always keep in mind
the Chinese idiom...
Six...
- Do you know what it means?
- Incorrect.
(Incorrect!)
- Okay, good.
- What was it?
- The idiom...
- At least one was saved.
It's "Always keep in mind."
- So that's what it was.
- That was close!
- The Chinese idiom sasangnugak...
- Always keep it in mind.
I missed that last part.
- So...
- I read most of it though.
So Min would never have guessed it
had she been alone.
So Min was completely clueless.
She didn't know what
nangjungjichu was.
If it weren't for Suk Jin,
I wouldn't have guessed it at all.
How can you not know
what nangjungjichu is?
You said "Ji Ho" at the end.
That's what I thought it was,
so I kept saying it.
We ran all over the place,
didn't we?
You ran to places
that didn't have any paths.
He ran through the bushes.
Let me tell you...
that I saw Hong Gil Dong in person.
- Hong Gil Dong is real.
- I made noises too.
- Jump, jump, and run.
- Exactly.
- Didn't you hear me?
- Was that you?
Anyway, Team Jong Kook
won this game.
- You get three eggs.
- What a relief.
- Thank you.
- You can cook with these...
or accept stickers
if that's what you decide on.
- Right.
- Let's use one.
- Can't we use one?
- Let's use one to cook.
- Just one.
- Right.
You can get stickers on them.
- Why don't you...
- We have other games to play.
Can I get one then?
I lost three of mine.
- Well...
- Hold on.
Father, that's another issue.
We didn't tell you
how much you all lost.
- Well...
- Hand them over.
Hold on a second. Suk Jin...
You didn't lose any of yours,
so why are you being greedy?
(Even Jong Kook is
too immersed in his character.)
Did you hear that?
Right, he's my father today.
Who taught you to be this greedy?
Who else? I'm just like you, Dad!
- I mean...
- How's this a functioning family?
Let me know
once you come to a decision.
- Suk Jin...
- Here's the second recipe.
Why are you being greedy
when you still have all your eggs?
More skewers?
- Jong Kook.
- He hasn't lost any of his eggs.
We need five eggs for this recipe,
- so let's use them all.
- Right.
- Okay, let's use them all.
It's now lunchtime.
You can use all the products here.
- The shelves are packed.
- Really?
Enjoy your meal and get cooking.
The next round will begin at 1 p.m.
(Team Jong Kook's egg count)
Let's crack one more here.
- Yes, of course.
- Crack one more.
What about the other eggs?
- We'll crack them in there.
- We'll need them for other games.
We should have them cracked open.
- Crack two over there.
- Right.
(The fifth egg is cracked.)
- Se Chan, we need another bowl.
- A bowl? Got it.
(They need a new bowl
for the tricolored skewers.)
(While Team Jong Kook
steps ahead...)
- Haha.
- Yes?
What should we eat?
We need to make the beef jeon.
There's a lot to do.
- Let's eat lunch first though.
- Right.
We're starving, right?
There really is a lot.
There are cup noodles.
Then let's start eating.
(Se Chan comes by to get a bowl.)
I'm hungry.
- Me too.
- We should eat.
- Hold on.
- Se Chan.
I'm going to crack yours.
Why would you do that?
Whose is that?
- Se Chan.
- Let's say it's yours.
Haha is listening. Jae Suk.
I'll betray them.
- We found a lot of yours.
- Hey.
How many did you find?
Give it to me,
and I'll let you know.
If you tell us where
Suk Jin's are...
or where Ji Hyo's are...
We'll find them and give you five.
The ones with my name on it?
How many of mine did you find?
- You don't have many left.
- Almost all of them are yours.
- How many did you find?
- We found eight of them.
Really? How?
Even if your team wins,
you'll get the penalty.
You will definitely get it.
(These 3 blackmailers
con their family.)
You won't come in first.
Okay.
What if I found Suk Jin and
Ji Hyo's eggs and cracked them?
- You could do that.
- Okay, then.
- Don't touch mine from now on.
- Okay.
You know where mine are, right?
They're inside the toilet
and behind the tissues.
- I told you where they are.
- Okay.
And behind the tissues.
I told you where they are.
- Okay.
- So I will...
get rid of the others'.
- Right.
- Suk Jin's eggs...
- and Ji Hyo's eggs.
- And Ji Hyo's.
(Se Chan gets fooled
and decides to betray his team.)
(He returns to his family's side
with evil intentions.)
Se Chan, welcome back.
What took you so long?
Come here and make
the tricolored skewers.
- Okay.
- Come and put on a pair of gloves.
- What else is there?
- It smells like the holidays.
It really does.
Pass it over after you put
flour on it.
(The beef jeon is almost finished.)
- This is incredible.
- I need some more.
- What do you need more of?
- Gosh, it's hot.
- Parchment paper.
- This one?
Gosh, it feels like we're a family
since we're doing this together.
It would be a lot of fun
if we were a family, right?
- If we were a family?
- It would be so much fun.
- It would be fun, right?
- It would be.
If we were a family...
We would gather together
like this.
It would be nice if Se Chan
became a part of my family.
Is there a possibility?
- Of course there is. My nieces.
- Can you pour in more oil?
- Oh, your nieces.
- Right.
- Guys, I have...
- Done!
- I have something to confess.
- What is it?
(I have something to confess.)
What is it?
- A deal came in from downstairs.
- What kind?
Gosh, what's wrong with you?
- It came in, but I'm telling you.
- Is that why you came back so late?
He must have felt guilty because
we were so harmonious...
- like a family.
- Right.
- For a moment,
- Aren't I right?
since it smells like the holidays
and everything, I had to tell you.
What kind of deal was it?
- When I was downstairs,
- It's done.
they said they already found
all of mine.
- If we win everything,
- Yes?
we won't get the penalty, right?
- The person in last place gets it.
- Last place in our team.
The person in last place
in our team gets it?
I'll come in last place then.
I'll come in last place...
No, that's not right.
- That's too much.
- I'll come in last place...
because I have
a penalty transfer card.
- That's too much.
- I'll come in last place...
(Jong Kook has
a penalty transfer card?)
(3 months ago, on July 12)
(During the 10th anniversary
special live broadcast)
(Jong Kook got a penalty transfer
card using his analyst skills.)
I won't use it today.
I'll just get the penalty.
(He saved
his penalty transfer card.)
(It just so happens he only has
2 weeks left to use it.)
- I have to use it soon.
- That's right.
- You have one.
- Kwang Soo was so cheeky earlier,
- That's right.
- so I've already decided on him.
Are you going to use it today?
What should I do?
- Let's just do what we need to do.
- I'll do whatever you say.
I'll even pretend to die
if you tell me to.
I can take care of the penalty,
so let's be sure to win as a team.
- Is this my apron?
- Dad.
- He's our dad.
I should feed my dad.
- Se Chan.
- We need to put some more jeon on.
Isn't it good?
(They finished 10 more beef jeons.)
(They place it on the ancestral rite
table before Team Jae Suk.)
(Unlike Team Jong Kook,
who's making progress,)
(Team Jae Suk forgot about
their grandfather,)
(and they're excited
to feed themselves.)
I should heat up some rice too.
Let's have some rice too.
I'm hungry.
(It sounds like something is frying.
Is it beef jeon?)
(Of course not. It's fried dumplings
for themselves.)
- It looks good.
- It really does.
Haha, can you prepare our meal
while we make the beef jeon?
(The rice just needs to heat up.)
(Sneaking in)
(He just steals it.)
(He blatantly steals the rice
that's ready.)
Hey!
- Gosh, that...
- What is it?
What's wrong with him? Is he crazy?
What's wrong?
He just took this.
(The Yoo family has no morals.)
(Laughing)
- Suk Jin. I brought some rice.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- They were heating it up,
- so I took it.
- Good job.
Bring the rice to the table.
(Take the rice once it's ready
before they take it again.)
(That's how Team Jae Suk's
lunch got more delayed.)
He just stole it.
(Jerry came back down
to the 1st floor.)
(Tom has no idea
and is focused on the dumplings.)
(Jerry goes after the ramyeon,)
(but Tom figured it out.)
(Tom can't hide his expression.
He is genuinely angry.)
You guys should eat too.
What are you doing?
(Jerry comes near
the ramyeon again.)
- I was just looking.
- Why...
(In the meanwhile,
Tom's dumplings are ready.)
I'll bring over the Spam
after I cook it.
Oh, my. Hey!
Hey! That...
I'll bring it over.
(Hey!)
That's not right.
You shouldn't take that.
Hey!
(Laughing)
Guys! Let's have dumplings!
- What?
- You did a good job!
I stole it from them.
That little thief.
We can't associate with you guys.
Suk Jin.
- Dad.
- What is it?
- You could've just asked.
- Why did you steal it?
- Dad.
- I made that for us.
- Dad, have it.
- This isn't right.
- We only had dumplings.
- Leave the rest for us.
- Don't do this.
(Their audacity makes it seem
like they made it.)
It's not cooked inside.
(This rotten family!)
(Team Jae Suk is hurt.)
We really shouldn't associate
with that family.
Father, you should have some.
That family is so vulgar.
Did they take a lot?
If I finish making it, they take it.
They're so uneducated.
My goodness.
They are a piece of work.
It's all because their father...
is uneducated.
- All he did was fight.
- Right.
My goodness.
How many jeons do we have to
place at the table?
- We have to make...
- A total of 10.
- We need to make seven then.
- Yes.
(Since Team Jae Suk has less
people, they were provided with 3.)
(Meanwhile,
Kwang Soo heads to the kitchen.)
(He charges at Ji Hyo.)
Okay. I'll give them to you.
Just don't crack them.
- Your eggs?
- I'll give them to you.
I'll give them to you
after I cook this.
- I promise.
- Really?
I'm going to crack them if you don't
give them to me in five seconds.
- Okay. I'll give them to you.
- Five.
- I'll give them to you.
- Four.
- Whose is it?
- No more.
Whose is it?
- Whose did you give him?
- It's mine.
He was trying to crack them,
so I just gave them to him.
(How dare you take
my sister-in-law's eggs?)
- Haha.
- Where is our mother?
(The newlywed rushes in.)
- Hey.
- Don't.
- We're going to crack it.
I stole the ones in Ji Hyo's bag.
It's better to just crack them.
It's better to crack them
than to put them in there.
- We have to put it in.
- Crack it in here.
(The Tiger Moth newlywed is ready
to end things.)
Okay. Here.
- Wait.
- Gosh.
My goodness.
(They gave them the eggs...)
(and took the ramyeon.)
(Even the daughters-in-law
have a nasty habit of stealing.)
- So Min, hurry up and go upstairs.
- Okay.
Seven.
(After much difficulty,
Team Jae Suk places the beef jeon.)
Goodness, Grandfather.
Enjoy this.
(He acts filial as he places
the precious 10 beef jeons.)
Done.
(Team Jae Suk also finishes
the first dish, beef jeon.)
Goodness.
We need about three more eggs.
- I put mine...
- Yes?
(Jong Kook says he'll give his eggs
to use as he has the transfer card.)
You know the thing above
the trampoline?
(He hid his eggs in a place
they would never find.)
- If you go there...
- That's a good hiding spot.
If you stick your hand
in the rain gutter...
and move it,
you'll feel it in there.
(They get 3 eggs thanks to
Jong Kook's sacrifice.)
He was telling the truth.
- Let's win no matter what.
- The transfer card...
The transfer card is amazing.
(They divided the labor to complete
10 tricolored skewers.)
Our family is peaceful.
(They divided the labor to complete
10 tricolored skewers.)
- Should I place them?
- Yes.
- Can I place it like this?
- They just placed it.
Gosh. They are slow.
They are like that.
Let's move on to the next mission.
Yutnori is a must.
But the board...
The master of yutnori will show you
how it's done.
Excuse me, Suk Jin.
Yes? What is it?
If you think about it,
we have seniority over you.
- Seriously.
- Seniority doesn't matter...
between cousins.
Suk Jin.
He keeps getting scolded
by Jae Suk...
and Jong Kook.
- Dad...
- Suk Jin can't lean on anyone.
- Uncle Jae Suk.
- He got criticized all day long.
Please say something to Dad.
He called me a brat.
- He has no one to lean on.
- All day long.
Suk Jin, bring me a cup of water.
- Dad.
- Suk Jin, bring me a cup of water.
Do you know what makes it sadder?
Even his wife is staying quiet.
Throw it.
(He gets an ointment
for mosquito bites.)
He went to the mountain earlier.
He channeled Hong Gil Dong.
Why did you do that?
Why did you go...
- to the mountain?
- You know,
when I jumped over the wall,
I heard the beats of the wings.
He exerted his force
even though the wall was very low.
He gave up quickly
when he got a mosquito bite.
For goodness' sake.
All right. The last mission is...
Shall We Play Nukdungbegi?
Nukdungbegi.
You will play Jeju Island's yutnori
to honor your grandfather.
- I see.
- He was from Jeju Island.
I just learned
that he was from Jeju Island.
As you can see,
the board is a bit different.
You can take the shortcut
if you get a mo.
(Shortcut)
Put the yut-sticks in the bowl...
and throw them
to the other team's area.
I see.
It doesn't count if the sticks land
outside or on the line.
(It doesn't count if the sticks land
outside or on the line.)
- This is hard. This is hard.
- This is hard.
Many throws will be invalid.
This is hard.
We miss the shortcut
unless we get a mo.
Getting a mo is the best.
Or you can get a gae after a geol
or a geol after a gae.
How dare you point your finger
at your uncle?
- You punk!
- I was pointing at the board.
Jae Suk, you are stretching it.
I am not stretching it.
He crossed the line.
Shall we make a fighting ring?
For goodness' sake.
It's natural for brothers to fight.
- Shall we make a fighting ring?
- It's perfectly natural.
Please calm down.
Be quiet, you punk.
Why is Suk Jin so mature?
Uncle Jae Suk,
you are being unreasonable.
How dare you talk back to me?
You are wearing an outfit
in the color of sweet potatoes.
Do you want your eyes to take on
the color of sweet potatoes?
I have had enough.
You haven't visited my house once!
I will take you down with taekkyeon.
(Do you want to get a taste
of taekkyeon?)
- I learned it too!
- I will take you down.
I learned it too!
- Jae Suk.
- What is it?
- Sit down.
- My goodness.
- I wanted to sit down.
- Sit down.
I wanted to sit down.
- Uncle Jae Suk.
- Don't be like that.
Ji Hyo, have you been in prison
or something?
What is up with that hair?
Leave her alone. It's her style.
Prison?
- I like that style.
- Don't talk to Ji Hyo that way.
How could you ask her
if she has been in prison?
Watch your behaviors.
The Yoo family is a big mess.
Right? The Yoo family is a big mess.
How could he be like that
on a good day?
All right. Let's play this game.
You win if all three pieces
go past the finish line.
- It won't be hard.
- okay.
Father, let your daughter-in-law
go first.
That's a good idea.
- You can go first.
- Hold on.
Since when did we have
someone so cheesy in the family?
I cringed.
She is so cheesy.
- So Min.
- Seriously.
- Sit behind the line.
- Okay, Father.
- There you go.
- Why is she so cheesy?
There you go. Good job.
Who wears socks like them?
- What an eyesore.
- Who wears socks like them?
So Min, are you feeling better?
Will you be able to play the game?
I had too much jeon earlier.
- Is that so?
- Besides, Pouty Mouth likes jeon.
- I see.
- Stop it. Stop it!
- She is ridiculous.
- She is cheesy.
(She makes everyone cringe.)
Sweetheart.
My goodness.
(She is graceful.)
- She is graceful.
- There you go.
- Good job.
- Geol.
- Geol is a good one.
- Dad, you like geol.
Geol is a good one.
Do I like geol?
- Geol.
- It's a geol, Dad.
It sounded like "You like girls."
It's a geol, Dad.
If we get a geol,
we will catch their piece.
- Let's catch it.
- Then we will get another turn.
Come on.
Gosh.
- Yut.
- There you go.
Your knees need to touch the floor.
- That's right.
- You need to sit down properly.
- Gosh, I didn't know.
- Haha.
- What are you playing at?
- Why are the rules so strict?
Why should we
talk to Suk Jin politely...
- when we have seniority?
- What are you talking about?
- Seniority doesn't exist.
- Are you challenging me?
My goodness.
(Take this taekkyeon attack.)
What is he doing?
He looks like a grandpa.
- Good job.
- You little brat.
I will take you down with taekkyeon.
- "Taekkyeon".
- Dad.
Do we need to suffer this outrage?
We outnumber them.
All right.
Haha.
Okay!
- It fell outside.
- There we go.
It was a good opportunity.
You were too greedy.
- Ji Hyo, go next.
- You look a bit tired.
I am okay.
You should go inside and rest.
- No, no.
- Ms. Prison.
- No.
- Ms. Prison!
- I am okay.
- Ms. Prison.
I can throw the sticks like this,
right?
That's right.
- Throw them lightly.
- Hey!
Okay, okay.
- This isn't easy.
- She failed.
- Good job.
- Let's go, let's go.
Hey, Beanpole.
How could you say that to your son?
Is he Japanese?
Are you a Japanese intruder or what?
What? How could you say that?
For goodness' sake.
How could you say that
during Chuseok?
- Watch your mouth.
- I am sorry.
- How could you say that?
- Are you learning kendo?
- Stop it.
Look at his posture.
Please sit cross-legged.
Look at your outfit.
How could you pick...
- that kind of an outfit?
- It's hanbok.
- No way.
- It's modernized hanbok.
He looks like
one of the Ninja Turtles.
(He clears up a misunderstanding
and throws the sticks.)
- My goodness.
- His arms are too long.
What is this?
Are his arms that long?
Perhaps the mat is too short.
His arm...
- What?
- Gae.
(He did well despite an attack
on his outfit.)
- Gae.
- Your younger brother will go.
- My younger brother.
- Se Chan...
- specializes in beating Beanpole.
- That's right.
- Hey.
- What is up with that pose?
Get a gae or...
- Get a gae. Let's catch them.
- Fail! Fail! Fail! Fail!
Fail! Fail!
- That's good. Gae.
- Okay.
- Gae!
- Dad!
Catch the piece.
(We got them.)
- Dad, I did it.
- Catch the piece.
(How did this happen?)
- Let's catch it.
- Then we get another turn.
You get another turn
if you catch a piece.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- We need a gae or geol.
- That's right.
- We can get their piece.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
(He gets another turn.)
- Okay.
- Hey!
- Get either a gae or geol.
- That's too bad.
Come on.
Let's go, let's go.
This round is important.
Out. It's on the line!
- It isn't on the line!
- This round is important.
- Out. It's on the line!
(Is it on the line?)
- It's on the line!
- It isn't on the line!
- Safe, safe.
- The stick...
- isn't on the line.
- Okay!
- Is it a yut?
- It's a yut.
- That's a bit tricky.
- It's a geol!
- Hey.
It's a yut!
- Look at it.
- It's a yut!
- A geol... Is it a yut?
My goodness.
(A geol... Is it a yut?)
"A geol... Is it a yut?"
I told you to keep quiet, you punk.
- A geol.
- It's a yut.
- Why...
Why did you have to be so vocal?
- It would be great to get a gae.
- Geol.
Let's run away. Go.
I believe in you.
Let's go.
- Here comes Kim Jang Hoon.
- Don't shake the sticks.
Isn't he Kim Jang Hoon?
I think he is Kim Jang Hoon.
(My dear)
(Stifling his laughter)
Don't mind him.
(My dear)
(He attacks Kwang Soo
by singing like Kim Jang Hoon.)
Do I really look like him?
I don't, right?
(His attention wavers.)
- I like Jang Hoon, but...
- You don't look like him.
- I don't have his hairstyle.
From here,
- you look like him.
- Listen.
- I like Jang Hoon,
- Families can joke about this.
- but I don't look like him.
- That's what holidays are about.
- Seriously.
- You don't look like him.
- Kim Jang Hoon.
- Why did you suddenly bring him up?
- I will go. I will go.
- Dad.
(Jae Suk decides to go
since his son is shaken up.)
Do! Do! Do! Do!
- Gae, geol, or yut.
- Do! Do! Do! Do!
Do! Out!
(This is driving me crazy.)
- Yes!
- "Ik"! "Ek"!
(They make fun of him
with some taekkyeon moves.)
- "Ik"!
- Good job.
You brats!
- "Ik"!
- Okay.
- This is driving me crazy.
It's out.
I am sorry. I am sorry.
- Let's go.
- Let's catch their piece.
- Fail! Fail!
(Jong Kook does well.)
- Gae! Geol! That's good.
- It's a geol.
(Team Jong Kook advances.)
Let's go, Kwang Soo.
Let's go, Kwang Soo!
- Yut, yut.
- Anything would be nice.
- Gae would be nice too.
- Han Gi Beom will aim...
- for a three-pointer.
- Why is his hand shaking?
(Another doppelganger attack)
Shouldn't you stop him
from calling me Han Gi Beom?
You do look like him.
I need to put my everything
to this throw.
- He really looks like him.
- Come on.
He is starting to resemble
Kim Yeon Koung.
That's right.
He is starting to resemble her.
How did he become so ugly?
- Is his hand shaking?
- How did he become so ugly?
- That's good.
- Gae!
- We caught their piece.
- Let's go, let's go.
- One more turn.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
(Throwing)
- Why did you throw it?
- He threw it.
- I guess it didn't stick.
- What?
- For goodness' sake.
- He threw it.
That was... Okay.
- Go.
- Getting a gae...
- would be nice.
- Then you should run away.
Go.
- It's on the line!
- No!
- It's on the line.
- Okay!
You failed.
It's out, okay?
(It's out, okay?)
- You little...
- Dad.
Shall we stop playing?
- This won't do.
- Shall we stop playing?
- Shall we?
- Go ahead!
- Don't be like that.
- Come on.
- Are you holding a weapon?
Head!
- Head!
- Look at you.
- I could beat you up.
- "Ik"!
- For goodness' sake.
- Come on.
(The martial artists' showdown
ends without a single touch.)
- Okay!
- What is it?
- Geol.
- Catch it.
- Let's go!
- Okay!
- Catch it.
(He throws the piece as revenge.)
Throw it.
- Did you throw it?
- What?
- No, no.
I just put it down.
- Okay.
- Would a gae be nice?
- Just throw the sticks.
- Gae!
My gosh. Gae.
(Please.)
- It's a gae!
- Gae!
(They reach the shortcut.)
- We are fast.
- This is good.
- Dad, show us.
- We are good at this.
- Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
(I will show you the power of Dad.)
It's out.
- He is really bad at this.
- For goodness' sake.
- He couldn't throw them right once.
- He is really bad at this.
- Why are you so nervous?
- Why can't I get them in there?
Dad, move.
- I am sorry.
- Dad.
A do or a geol would be bad.
Anything is good, right? Okay.
- What is it? Yut!
- Yut!
(It's a jackpot.)
- Ji Hyo.
- Yut.
Gosh, what is this? Gosh.
- My goodness.
- Sweetheart is dancing.
- She is good.
- This is what Chuseok is all about.
- It's a yut!
- That's good.
- She is good.
- Come on out, yut!
Sweetheart is good.
Sit down.
- Okay.
- I feel dizzy.
So Min must have brought luck
to the family.
That one hasn't gone yet.
Geol. Geol. A geol would be nice.
- Gae.
- Let's get a piece out.
- Let's do that.
- Let's get it out. Let's graduate.
- Okay.
- Let's get it out.
- Let's do that.
- Get both pieces out.
- Okay.
- We have 1 piece left.
- It can be anything.
- Okay.
- Don't throw them high.
- You can get a do.
- You can get a gae.
- He hadn't succeeded once.
- This is...
- Okay.
He is too nervous.
His heart is pounding.
- Dad.
- His heart is pounding.
- Okay!
- My goodness.
Dad!
- That was hilarious.
- My goodness.
- This is driving me crazy.
We keep missing a turn
because of him.
Why do you get so nervous
about a game?
- It's a game between the families.
- I am sorry.
- What's so hard about it?
This is driving me crazy.
- Take them down.
- I will do that.
They are...
- Father, good luck.
- Okay.
- Yut!
- Father, good luck.
What is she doing?
Isn't she the Magnet Woman?
- Magnet Woman.
How did she do that?
So Min has all sorts of talents.
- Let's go.
- Do, gae, geol, yut.
- It can be anything.
- Which piece should I catch?
- Yut would be nice.
- Okay.
- Mo!
- It's a mo!
(We did it again.)
(The passionate techno dance)
(Jae Suk grits his teeth.)
- It's a mo!
- What is it? What is it?
What is it? What is it?
- What is it?
- Can't you read the room?
Can't you read the room?
This is fun.
This is good, So Min.
- It's a mo.
- This is a crucial moment.
Here comes a mo.
Let's catch a piece with a gae!
Let's take it out with a gae.
- This is so much fun.
- Let's crush them.
- I hope they get a do.
- That would be perfect.
Okay.
(It's a yut.)
- Yut!
- Okay.
- If we get a geol...
- Then it's game over.
- Is it game over already?
Yes. It's game over
if we get a geol.
- Geol!
(Did they really get a geol?)
- It's a gae.
- Gae.
- Is it a gae?
- Shall we catch it?
- Catch their piece.
- Catch it.
Okay.
Let's get another yut.
(He becomes flippant.)
(Slapping)
(An angry slap)
(He adds a dropkick.)
He brought that upon himself.
- Dad!
I was going to suppress myself
since it's a good day.
- Come here!
- It's a fight!
- Dad!
- You little punk.
Dad, they are...
- Hey!
- We are playing yutnori.
Why would you do the techno dance?
I could hit your head
with a bamboo sword!
They are truly angry.
They are serious.
(Their anger level is at its max.)
How should we finish it?
- Just go.
- So Min, go.
- The youngest member.
- It's game over if it's a yut.
- Go outside with a yut...
or have fun with a geol.
Make it entertaining.
- She is elegant.
- Thank you.
She is like a forsythia.
- She is elegant.
- My goodness.
She is like a forsythia.
(She suddenly stretches out
her leg.)
- What is that?
- On a national holiday...
What are you doing
on a national holiday?
- What are you doing?
- It's her socks. I am sorry.
- She is in "The War of Flowers".
What are you doing?
She is in "The War of Flowers".
- I am sorry. I am sorry.
- On a national holiday...
It's her socks.
She is pulling a prank.
- It's a diversionary tactic.
- A diversionary tactic.
- That's good.
- Anything is good.
- Okay.
- It's a geol. We are almost done.
Do, gae, geol.
- Okay.
- Gosh, good job.
- Mo, mo, yut, gae.
- Okay.
Mo, mo, yut, gae.
I will begin.
(He talks big.)
I will show you
how to turn the tables.
(I will show you
how to turn the tables.)
(It's the last chance
to have his revenge.)
(The yut-stick bomb)
Do, gae, geol, yut...
You little...
Are you kidding me?
- Are you insane?
- Step on him!
Hold on.
- Are you kidding me?
- What are you doing?
- What was that?
- They are con artists!
How many sticks were there?
- Dad!
- Let's do it again.
- What are you doing?
- How many sticks were there?
For goodness' sake.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
That's good. It's a do.
- Gae.
- Gosh!
I got a gae
from mo, mo, yut, and gae.
(Team Jae Suk's worst player
talks big.)
Dad. We are almost done.
- Do we just need a do?
- We just need a do.
Hold on. Should I make it fun?
What should I do?
- Shall we fail on purpose?
- What?
- Shall I use my left hand?
- Okay. Left hand.
- Left hand.
- That's a good idea.
- Use your left hand here.
- Shall I use my left hand?
- Gosh, throw with your eyes closed.
Throw with your eyes closed.
- Throw with your eyes closed.
- Shall I do that?
- Yes.
- Okay, okay. I will do it...
- with my eyes closed.
- Like Michael Jordan.
I will do it with my eyes closed.
Okay. My eyes are closed.
He might get a do.
(Team Jong Kook will win
if they get even a do.)
(Please let him fail.)
- That's incredible.
- It's over.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- Let's go!
This is Chuseok!
It ended in a fun way.
Have a happy Chuseok!
Bring three eggs.
We are on another level.
We win no matter what we do.
We handed out three eggs.
Now comes the last recipe.
(What's the last recipe?)
Korean meatballs.
Make the dish by 3 p.m.
The team that finishes it 1st wins.
- Okay.
- 3 p.m.
- It requires 10 eggs.
- 10 eggs?
We need 10 eggs this time.
(We need 10 eggs?)
(There will be
a fierce competition for eggs.)
- Let's move on to the final race.
- Okay.
(Let's move on to the final race!)
Please gather around.
The current time is 2:22 p.m.
- The race ends at 3 p.m.
- Okay.
The team
that sets the table first wins.
Once you are done,
sound the gong
and get the table checked to win.
Even if you finish the second,
you need to complete the dish...
to avoid the all-member penalty.
Let's begin now.
- Go.
- Go, go.
(Team Jong Kook: 4 eggs short,
Team Jae Suk: 7 eggs short)
Where did Suk Jin put his eggs?
It's important to have 10 eggs.
Why don't we
gather ours around and...
How many eggs did you get stolen?
I got four eggs stolen.
I got six eggs stolen.
- Come on.
- That didn't happen.
- Yes, it did.
- Don't be like that.
I got 3 to 4 eggs stolen.
- The number suddenly changed.
- It sounds like a lie.
- 3 to 4 eggs.
- 4 eggs. Exactly 4 eggs.
- I got 4 eggs stolen too.
I will donate three eggs.
Who will cook?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
(They can't stand
seeing Kwang Soo win.)
This won't do.
- Come on.
- Right?
Go and cook.
- Dad.
- That's the way to go.
We need to go and...
Listen to your dad, punk!
Do you think I will sit there
and cook obediently?
Then what do you want to do?
- Hey.
- We need to win.
We need to make
the tricolored skewers, okay?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors...
and have the loser make
the tricolored skewers.
Okay. That will be fair.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
(Dad, please make
the tricolored skewers!)
This is driving me crazy.
(Kwang Soo runs somewhere
as soon as the race starts.)
(Why is Kwang Soo here?)
- Are these all the eggshells?
- Yes.
- Aren't there stickers?
- No.
- My stickers.
- Your stickers aren't here.
(Kwang Soo wants to put his stickers
on other eggs.)
Ji Hyo, you...
(Ji Hyo is uninterested.)
You are like Sin Saimdang.
It's like a different world here.
It's like a documentary.
(Ji Hyo cooks elegantly
in beautiful hanbok.)
(She keeps her distance
from the vile Yoo family...)
(and films a cooking vlog.)
(The most elegant woman)
There are no eggs.
- Where are Suk Jin's eggs?
- I don't see them.
(When Haha heads to the playroom,)
(So Min follows.)
Haha.
(She stays near Haha.)
- What?
- You took my eggs, right?
- My eggs.
- Of course.
- Did you take them?
Yes, I did.
(At that moment)
(So Min suddenly takes
something out.)
- What?
- They are mine! No!
(She struggles desperately.)
(Cracking)
(So Min's eggs crack.)
My eggs!
Yes!
(She tried to get the egg before
Haha found it, but...)
That one's mine.
(She couldn't protect 2 eggs.)
My goodness, Haha.
(They say a thief is frightened
even by a mouse.)
I thought you would open it.
You were planning to, right?
- No, it never crossed my mind.
- Stop lying.
Gosh, it smells nice.
(Jae Suk is making the jeon.)
(He's finally done with
the tricolored skewers.)
We have to turn the tables
no matter what.
(Determined)
(He dreams of turning the tables...)
(as he places the tricolored skewers
on the table.)
(Both families finished making
beef jeon and tricolored skewers.)
(They need 10 eggs
for Korean meatballs.)
(Team Jong Kook has 6,
Team Jae Suk family has 3.)
Where are the other three?
Bring them over.
How can I?
Stop being greedy.
You still have yours too.
Mine? Okay.
What if I get caught on my way?
I...
I should bring them. Okay, let's go.
If things continue this way,
we're going to lose.
I can't take them out. Gosh.
(He watches where Jae Suk goes.)
I think there is something in here.
- So Min.
- Yes, Haha?
- I know this.
- What?
Suk Jin said it was under a gutter.
I don't know anything besides that.
(Under a gutter?
That's quality information.)
(The moment So Min gave Haha
the information...)
I know this.
(Kwang Soo was near the audio team's
equipment.)
(He finds out the information
at an incredible timing.)
Suk Jin said it was under a gutter.
(Under the gutter?)
There's an egg over there.
(He couldn't find Suk Jin's egg
no matter where he looked.)
Suk Jin's egg is over there.
(Looking under the gutters)
Are they...
(Suk Jin spots Kwang Soo.)
My egg is over there,
and that's where he's looking.
(At that moment)
(Shouting)
(He hits his shin.)
(It's a pain that's hard to describe
with words.)
What's wrong?
- Did you get hurt?
- What's wrong?
(He's expressing his pain
with ugliness.)
No, I'm fine.
(At that moment,)
(Suk Jin sees that Kwang Soo fell.)
(He rushes toward the gutter where
he hid his egg.)
Why is Suk Jin here?
(Fighting)
Did you find something?
It must be here!
It must be above here.
(Jae Suk tries
to climb up quickly.)
Hold on.
- Hold on.
- There must be one here.
(Peeking)
There's nothing here.
(There's no egg there?)
It might've fallen.
There should be one there.
There's nothing there.
- There's nothing there.
- I'm sure there's one here.
(He peeks using his height.)
Suk Jin came here when we did.
(Kwang Soo finds something.)
(He finds 1 egg that Suk Jin hid.)
(He puts it in his bag
while everyone is looking away.)
There's nothing here.
But Suk Jin is keeping an eye
on this area.
But why is Suk Jin...
Suk Jin is keeping an eye
on this area.
Suk Jin was looking
in this direction,
so I came here and pulled the table
when he ran toward me really fast.
(He puts the table
back in its place.)
(But there's a sudden
bag inspection.)
(It's quiet for a second.)
There's an egg in there.
Let's crack it.
- Jae Suk!
- Let's crack it!
- Protect me!
(He asks Jae Suk to protect him.)
I found Suk Jin's egg.
If you keep doing that,
we're going to crack it.
You found mine?
- That one is mine?
- Who is yellow?
- Is it yours?
- This one is Suk Jin's.
Should I crack it?
Yes. It's better to just crack it.
Okay. Crack it.
Crack it.
- That's better.
- It's better to just crack it.
Give it to us.
- Crack it.
- No.
- No, we can't.
- Just crack it.
- Should we crack it?
- Stay here.
Stay here
while I look for the others.
- I haven't been able to get mine.
- Where are they?
In the back alley.
Can you hold them off in here?
I'll go and get it.
Bring three. We need to end this.
- That way, we can win.
- Should I bring all six?
- We just need three.
- Should I bring them all?
- What if they find it?
- You have six left?
Okay, then bring them all.
Hurry up then.
You get it.
Where did you put yours, Kwang Soo?
- Okay.
- Where are Kwang Soo's eggs?
(He's moving.)
(Suk Jin runs quickly to
the back alley.)
- Hey.
- He said it's in his pants.
- They're in his pocket?
- Is it still there?
Where did you put it?
(Suk Jin filmed his own spy movie
while burying 6 eggs in here.)
We just need three.
(If he can find them, they can make
Korean meatballs right away.)
(But at that moment)
- Hey!
- There's something over here.
(He's blocked right in front
of the eggs!)
Someone grab him.
(The moment Suk Jin
started moving,)
(Jae Suk sensed that
something was off.)
You don't have any yet?
Hey!
(He sees Suk Jin coming
and climbs over the window.)
(He blocks the path.)
- Hey!
- There's something over here.
- Someone grab him.
- There's something here.
- There's something over here.
- Hey!
You should've done this earlier.
You should've done this earlier!
This was foolish.
- I told you to hold on to him!
- You could've gone this way,
- so why did you go that way?
- My gosh.
There's something here!
(They finally find it.)
- Hey!
- I found it!
(He grabs his collar with one hand
and steals with the other.)
(He removes some of the dirt...)
(and finds the eggs.)
(The path is so narrow that
they can't move this way or that.)
Someone help me grab him.
What are you doing?
You should've done this sooner.
(He digs out 6 eggs.)
Move. Move out of the way.
(A short reach)
It's over.
- Hey.
- Just crack them.
That punk!
My goodness.
(If they can create an egg mixture
safely, they can turn the tables.)
Just give me one.
Give me one,
so I don't come in last place.
Let's make a deal.
Just give me one.
(Please, give me one.)
I shouldn't come in last place.
I'll get a penalty then.
Just give me one
so that I don't come in last place.
Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
- We need to get three of yours.
One.
(They use 3 of Ji Hyo's eggs.)
2, 3. That's enough, right?
Let's go.
- Let's go and make them.
- Let's go.
We just need to make them now.
Hurry up and bring them.
(They had 3, and Jae Suk and
Kwang Soo stole 7 of Suk Jin's.)
I found one too.
It belongs to Se Chan.
That's four.
- Let's hurry up and make them.
- Okay.
Let's hurry up and make them.
Turn it on.
Where is the recipe?
Hurry up. Let's look at the recipe.
Hurry.
Give me the spatula.
(Team Jae Suk begins to
make the Korean meatballs.)
Hurry.
We got this.
Just pour it in.
(Just pour in the egg mixture.)
Just pour it in. It's fine.
(Pouring in...)
(the egg mixture)
You poured too much of it in.
If you do this, the temperature
of the pan will fall.
Okay. Hold on.
- Move it over to that side.
- Okay.
- Why did you pour everything in?
- It's okay.
You can't do this.
- Jae Suk. Why did you do that?
- This is driving me crazy.
- I was in a rush.
- Why do you keep causing trouble?
You were like that during
yutnori too.
(Troublemaker)
It's because I'm in a rush.
I'm sorry.
Put it in. Hurry.
(We're in such a hurry.)
We need tongs.
Hurry up and put them on the pan.
You got all your eggs taken.
Why are you bossing us around?
We have to move quickly
or else we're going to lose.
I'll do it. Don't do it.
It'll fall apart.
This is fine.
You have seven minutes left.
Please.
(Thanks to Jae Suk's mistake,
the winner is a mystery.)
Put it in.
- Suk Jin. No.
- It's fine.
- We need to hurry.
- He's worried he'll come last.
Even if it looks like this,
I'm sure it'll taste good.
If we came sooner and made them,
we would've won.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
It's 2:54 p.m.
(Which family will make the Korean
meatballs and complete the table?)
(6 minutes before the end,
Kwang Soo appears.)
(Kwang Soo prepares
to hit the gong.)
(Jae Suk brings in
the Korean meatballs.)
Goodness, Grandfather.
- Grandfather.
(Team Jae Suk family finishes
setting the ancestral rite table.)
Grandfather!
- Grandfather.
(Grandfather is proud.)
We lost.
They said it's over.
(That's too bad. We lost.)
- Why are you so...
- Some of us can get exempt.
- Okay.
- We need to finish the jeon.
If we finish before 3 p.m,
we won't all get the penalty?
Yes. We're all done.
Let's place it.
You have five minutes left.
Grandfather, I'm sorry we're late.
Suk Jin, move over.
- We're done too.
- Both teams finished,
but Team Jae Suk came first,
so they win.
(Team Jae Suk finished first,
so they win.)
I'll give you five minutes.
We've prepared boxes for you.
Bring back your eggs,
and we'll count them.
- You can't steal them now, right?
- No, you can't.
You just need to bring them here.
This was the perfect spot.
I thought they would find this one
really fast.
(So Min hid her eggs in the dirt.)
But this was the one that was safe.
I'm so nervous about this.
(Jae Suk hid all 10 of his eggs
in 1 place.)
(He opens up the air conditioner,)
(and all 10 eggs are still there.)
Thank you.
(He's so crafty.)
Nobody would've thought
to look here.
(Kwang Soo hid his egg
in the trash can.)
(What's this?)
Someone found it?
(Who on earth found this one?)
Someone went through
the trashcan?
(Ji Hyo went through the trash
and stole Kwang Soo's egg.)
Gosh.
(It's been 10 years,
they all think alike.)
(They're done looking for
the eggs they hid.)
Team Jae Suk wins by two minutes.
- Okay.
- Yes!
Among the three winners,
the person with the least number
of eggs will get the penalty too.
This is a bit unfortunate.
Please reveal how many you have.
- I have 10.
- 10?
- I have 8.
- 8?
(How many eggs does Kwang Soo, who
put on a splendid performance have?)
- He...
- I have five.
(Kwang Soo came in last,
so he will get the penalty.)
Did anyone on my team
break any of my eggs?
- Since it's over.
- No.
Haha, did you break any of mine?
You did, didn't you?
Hold on. No, it's not like that.
(I ought to...)
I broke the one in the ice cream...
and the one in the plastic bag.
Goodness, you are...
What about this team?
That's six.
I have one.
I had two left.
- 4.
Five.
(How many eggs does Ji Hyo
have left?)
I have six left.
- I had four left.
- Then Song Ji Hyo will get a prize.
Today's prize is a Chuseok
Korean beef set.
(Today's prize is a Korean beef set
for Chuseok.)
(It's Korean beef.)
This is amazing.
You're on the same team.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- What's gotten into you?
- I'll enjoy Chuseok.
- Dad.
Let me tell you
about today's penalty.
Your grandpa wanted you
to do some chores.
You will make songpyeon
for the production crew.
Gosh, you guys must be happy.
The 5 of you will make
100 pieces of songpyeon.
- 100 pieces?
- Yes.
- It's meaningful.
- Make 100 pieces before going home.
- Are you feeling happy?
- No.
Don't smile.
Your uncle is really...
He's really upset. He's mad.
He's really annoying.
He has all his eggs.
He has 10 eggs.
Where did you hide them?
Because of you,
our team lost.
It's not because of me.
It's because of Suk Jin.
Why don't you
make songpyeon with us?
I'm not good at making songpyeon.
It's not hard.
You can learn how to make it.
But the thing is...
- What?
- I should go. My car is ready.
I'm going to give you
a penalty anyway.
He will use his penalty
transfer card to you.
(Jong Kook uses
his penalty transfer card.)
Oh, that's right.
(Jong Kook transfers
his penalty to Jae Suk.)
I'm using it on you.
(Jong Kook transfers
his penalty to Jae Suk.)
- You should stay.
- Gosh, no.
You're being really annoying today.
- Wait.
- You just gave out your gifts.
You are being really condescending.
Jong Yoon, turn off the car!
Go take a nap!
Make some songpyeon
before you go home.
If I make pretty songpyeon,
I can have a pretty daughter.
Isn't it about dumplings?
No. They also say that
about songpyeon.
Add a lot of sugar.
No, it will be too sweet.
Kwang Soo, this is ridiculous.
- No.
- Kwang Soo.
This is too much.
- It's a prize.
- It's a dud.
- It's enough for one meal.
- This is too much.
- No, it's not like that.
- What is that?
We all have our own tastes.
You just want to finish it
quickly and go home.
- No.
- It looks like a foreign dish.
There are people
who prefer big ones.
You should make it look nice.
There are about two pieces
that don't have stuffing in them.
- Let's steam them.
- Okay. Let's do that.
(Now they need to
steam the songpyeon.)
I can't stop making it.
- Keep making it then.
- Okay.
They told me to stop making it,
but I just can't stop.
I want the production crew
to eat more songpyeon.
You don't even know who they are.
(You don't even know who they are.)
You're not wrong about that.
That can be the last serving.
Okay. We just need one more.
All right. The production crew
will steam the rest.
- Okay.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
- Happy Chuseok.
- Steam the songpyeon...
and enjoy it.
- Okay.
- All right. Let's go.
Just say something before you leave.
You can't just leave like that.
He's like a robot.
- Like a talking machine.
- Good job today.
- Hang on.
- What was that?
- He's so cold-hearted.
- What's with him?
"I want the production crew
to eat more songpyeon."
When they said it's over,
he went, "Gosh, I should go."
He already took off his microphone.
- He's like a machine.
- Thank you.
(There are 4 gift boxes
in front of them.)
(The guys are excited
to have a couple race.)
(They are the guests
for today's couple race.)
(Are they Ji Hyo and So Min?)
(Two beautiful guests,
Song Ji Hyo and Jeon So Min)
(They will find
their original intention...)
(with the videos of their
first time on Running Man.)
(Jong Kook's serenade in the subway)
(It will make her heart flutter.)
(You're being ridiculous.)
(So annoying!)
You're so pretty.
(Is it an attack or a compliment?)
(Throwing up)
(Super cringing)
(It's a mission for the guys
who have changed a lot.)
(Going back to the basics)
(New students of Running Man
High School, So Min and Ji Hyo)
(To go back to the basics,)
(they should take good care
of the two sisters.)
I love it.
(Their struggle
to go back to the basics)
(How would it end up?)
(Back to the Basics Race,
Precious Sisters)