(A wedding hall
with fancy chandeliers)
- Hello.
- It's 36.1℃.
- This place is lovely.
This is pretty.
This is where we did
the card shark thing before.
Is it okay to have
a low temperature?
- I'm 34℃.
- I'm 33℃.
You're cold-blooded.
I'm 36.4℃.
It's not just body temperature.
It's the temperature of your heart.
- I see.
- He has a frozen heart.
Whatever.
- You have a low temperature, right?
- Exactly.
- No.
- You're right about that.
If that's the case,
it should be 99℃.
That's the temperature of my heart.
He's starting it again.
(He's trying to look humane.)
Things seem quite heartwarming
this morning.
- What's heartwarming?
- What do you mean?
- They always try to get on my case.
- You sound like a machine.
- You just say that mechanically.
- What's heartwarming here?
- What was that?
- You don't sound sincere at all.
I mean it.
Today, as the beginning of
the 2020 Year-End Award Ceremonies,
we will have
the first Friendship Award.
- It's an award ceremony.
- The Friendship Award?
- Friendship?
- First, let me introduce...
- your best friends.
- Okay.
Jae Suk's best friend.
Who's my best friend?
(Yoo Jae Suk's best friend)
(Jae Suk has a lot of friends
who are famous celebrities.)
(Which one of them
will join Running Man today?)
Jae Suk's best friend.
Who's my best friend?
Lee Kwang Soo.
- What?
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(What?)
- What?
He's my close friend,
but he's younger than me.
- Is Kwang Soo a guest?
- Is Kwang Soo my best friend?
- Yes.
- Who's a guest?
Is Kwang Soo a guest?
So he's our guest for today.
Why am I a guest?
You're a guest.
Today, we should
treat him like an actor.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- He's a guest.
What is going on?
- We have a guest today.
- It's Lee Kwang Soo.
Mr. Lee Kwang Soo.
You look handsome.
(Lee Kwang Soo, a comedian and
actor with 10 years of experience)
- He looks cool.
- We have Lee Kwang Soo here today?
- He's cool.
- He does the chicken foot greeting.
- Next is Haha's best friend.
- Okay.
It's Ji Suk Jin.
(Haha's best friend
is Ji Suk Jin.)
It's Ji Suk Jin.
- What? Why?
- I like that.
- I like it too.
- It's good for me.
We've been doing a lot of things
together on YouTube.
Haha and Suk Jin
aren't best friends.
They are not that close.
- No, we work together a lot.
- We get along well these days.
- They are incompatible.
- We do a lot of things together.
They're just trying
to get more subscribers.
- And Song Ji Hyo's best friend...
- They are not best friends.
- is Yang Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Best friends?
- Yang Se Chan.
(What?)
Is it because of Hyochang Park?
- It's just...
- Hyochang Park.
It's just a business relationship.
- Ji Hyo's friend?
- You must've gone crazy.
(The pairs of best friends
are not convincing at all.)
You are insane.
They don't even know
each other's number.
- We're just...
- Hyochang Park.
It's just business.
And Jong Kook's best friend.
- Is it So Min?
- Please come on out.
- What?
- Isn't it me?
(Isn't it me?)
- What do you mean?
(Who's Jong Kook's best friend
coming down the stairs?)
- What's going on?
- Jong Kook.
- It's Tae Hyun.
- What? Cha Tae Hyun.
Is it Tae Hyun?
- He's Tae Hyun.
- My gosh.
(Real reactions)
- He's his best friend.
- He's Jong Kook's real friend.
- Hey.
- He's...
- He has his real best friend.
- What is he doing here?
(Cha Tae Hyun,
an ace variety show marksman)
Director!
(Tae Hyun calls the director first.)
- Is this his first time here?
- Is it?
I'm not sure.
- What? Hey.
- Have you been doing well?
- Hello.
- He's going to Chan Hee.
Mr. Kang.
(He just walks past the members.)
(And he greets
Director Kang Chan Hee.)
- You didn't say hello to us.
- Hey.
- Mr. Kang.
- My gosh.
- You should talk to me first.
- Who do you think is...
your best friend here?
Why did you go to Chan Hee?
We met again after two years.
I saw the rest of you before.
You should look at me. But you...
We talked on the phone two days ago.
Why did you not tell me about this?
You didn't ask.
He's funny.
Why would I tell you that
when you didn't even ask?
Hey, is your new movie coming out?
I'll start a movie.
So you came here for no reason?
I'm on a variety show tour.
- It's a variety show tour.
- Is he serious?
What is he doing here?
There was an article
that said this about me.
- What?
- A variety show hitchhiker.
(A variety show hitchhiker)
A hitchhiker?
I love that nickname.
He just appears in variety shows
for no reason once in a while.
I said this about Tae Hyun before.
He suddenly texted me and asked
"When should I join your show?"
This is what he does.
- He was drunk.
- That's not true.
- No?
- I was asked to join this show.
He was asked to come.
I was asked to join Running Man.
I was like, "Running Man"?
- Out of the blue?
- I had no excuse to refuse it.
(I had no excuse to refuse it.)
(He decided to join our show
as he had no excuse to refuse it.)
Ji Hyo thinks this is
Tae Hyun's first time in our show.
- She thinks she's never met you.
- He's been here before.
Tae Hyun was in our show
a lot when we started it.
(10 years ago, he was
in the 10th episode.)
(He was once on the same team
with Ji Hyo.)
(Embarrassed)
We met many times.
That's because
when Tae Hyun was here...
Just stay quiet.
It was a very interesting story!
- Just stay quiet.
- He's right.
He's right.
- Was she sleep?
- When Tae Hyun was here,
- She slept a lot.
- Ji Hyo kept sleeping.
- Oh, right.
- She slept in the car.
So Tae Hyun asked me carefully.
"Is it okay to sleep like that?"
(So Tae Hyun asked me carefully.
Is it okay to sleep like that?)
Hey, you should tell us interesting
stories like that with confidence.
I was going to, but you stopped me.
- You should speak with confidence.
- Right.
She was shooting a drama back then.
She was sleeping
with the drama script.
So I understood her.
- I thought she'd be very tired.
- Right.
- You didn't.
- You talked behind her back a lot.
Was it on TV?
(Was it on TV?)
(He fails to talk her up
because of the witnesses.)
It wasn't.
Didn't Tae Hyun say this?
"Does she always sleep like this
shooting a TV show?"
Exactly.
(Jong Kook's best friend Tae Hyun is
back in Running Man after 9 years.)
Then So Min has no friend?
- What about me?
- Who's So Min's friend?
All right. Next is...
So Min's best friend.
- I know who it is.
- Please come on out.
Who is it?
(Who is it?)
- It's Mi Joo.
- Mi Joo.
She's Mi Joo.
(Welcome, Mi Joo.)
(Mi Joo, a variety blue chip
with cheerful charm)
Mi Joo is here.
So it's like crazy plus crazy.
(So it's like crazy plus crazy.)
Hello.
She's Mi Joo.
- She's a rising variety star.
- I know.
Sure.
- From what I heard,
- Yes?
before Mi Joo was invited,
she got a call from So Min.
Right. I suddenly
got a call from So Min.
"Hello, So Min."
"Mi Joo, I'm calling you
to get credit for something."
"Really? What is it?"
"I got you in Running Man."
- That's the worst.
- "Hey."
(I got you in Running Man.)
(She sounds like an old fossil.)
- That's the worst.
- That's horrible.
You can't be like that.
You picked up only bad things here.
It's the worst.
Gosh, I got goosebumps.
We have five teams
for The first Friendship Awards.
So we all are teamed up.
We have the sixth team here.
Please come on out.
- There's another team of friends?
- They are a team.
- Hey, he's my friend.
- Yang Dong Geun?
Yang Dong Geun and Jang Dong Min.
Dong Geun is my friend.
You got to make money somehow.
(Startled)
- Hey.
- How are you?
- Hello.
- Dong Min.
- Hey.
- Hello, Dong Min.
Dong Min and Dong Geun
are Haha's close friends.
- They are very close.
- They're my friends.
You did a TV show together.
- As friends.
- Right.
And we've known each other
for a long time.
Here's the thing.
They were thinking of
pairing me up with Haha,
but it didn't seem good,
so they paired us up together.
That's what happened.
So we should make sure...
to ruin this episode today.
Let's do that.
They will ruin our show for sure.
All our guests for today
can ruin this show.
Hang on.
Should I break a camera first?
(Hang on. Should I
break a camera first?)
Now we have one team left.
- There's more?
- There's another team.
- One more team?
- They're here.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
(Yeon Jun and Huening Kai
of TOMORROW X TOGETHER)
(TOMORROW X TOGETHER
with versatile charms)
(With their fascinating looks
and refreshing beauty,)
(Yeon Jun and Huening Kai are here.)
They're TOMORROW X TOGETHER.
- My gosh.
- Hello.
Welcome.
They are Yeon Jun...
- and Huening Kai.
- They're from BTS's agency.
- That's right.
- That's true.
They're like BTS's
younger brothers.
Let us introduce ourselves.
One Dream.
- Hello, we're TOMORROW X TOGETHER.
I haven't seen them for a long time.
Now it feels like we have guests.
Right.
We are having more guests
than I thought today.
- We have a lot.
- This is a lot.
Are we going to have 100 guests
like we did before?
Let's introduce ourselves then.
Tae Hyun, this year marks
our 10th anniversary.
And he was in our show
nine years ago.
- Nine years?
- That's unbelievable.
I didn't know you'd come.
Me neither. I had no idea.
I talked to him on the phone
for about 30 minutes.
- And?
- He could've told me about this.
- Why did you not tell him?
- He didn't ask.
I mean...
You didn't ask what I would
do on Monday.
You usually say
things like this in advance.
- What do you think?
- You didn't ask me.
You would understand me
if you were married.
I don't say anything
unless I'm asked.
(All married men
relate to what he says.)
Why would I tell you that
when you didn't even ask?
- You're right.
- Okay.
- I should learn from you.
- I get it.
You don't answer questions
that people don't ask.
I won't say anything
unless it's needed.
Right. And we have...
TOMORROW X TOGETHER here.
This is your first time here.
- Right.
- How would you describe...
your friend Yeon Jun with one word?
Well, I'd say he's my treasure.
Your treasure.
What about you, Yeon Jun?
(What does Huening Kai mean
to Yeon Jun?)
He's a cute friend.
A cute friend?
- A cute friend.
- All right then.
I should ask this question to them.
What does Jong Kook
mean to you, Tae Hyun?
- What?
- Protein.
(Protein)
- My gosh.
- Good.
That's what I mean to him.
- What about you, Jong Kook?
- That's what I mean.
- What does Tae Hyun mean to you?
- Just protein?
What does Tae Hyun mean to you?
- To me?
- Yes.
(What does Tae Hyun mean
to Jong Kook?)
Real estate.
He shares information
about real estate with me.
He gives me a lot of information.
Tae Hyun is real estate
to Jong Kook,
And tax.
and Jong Kook means protein
to Tae Hyun.
Good.
And we have Yang Dong Geun and
Jang Dong Min who are best friends.
Dong and Dong!
- Dong and Dong!
- Dong and Dong.
Do you two
get along with each other?
- I don't think they do.
- Do you even have things in common?
- They're really close.
- Are you judging our relationship?
I'm not judging.
- They don't match.
- You're right.
- That's why we get along well.
- I see.
We are very
different from each other.
- But we respect the difference.
- Is that so?
- They're very close.
- Yes.
Dong Geun, what can you
tell us about Dong Min?
He can't say anything.
You may ask me questions.
What are you talking about?
He can't say anything.
You may ask me questions.
What are you talking about?
He was going to speak.
He wanted to say something
but you stopped him.
- I'm sorry.
- He was about to say something.
I'm sorry.
He doesn't like people
asking him questions...
- or being with many people.
- Is that right?
But let us hear him say something.
This is for his own good.
- I'm protecting him.
- All right then.
It seems to me
that you two haven't been close...
for a very long time.
You're right. When I first saw him,
I was in my 20s.
- Remember how he used to look like?
- Sure I do.
(He swaggered in his walk.)
This is how he walked.
- And you didn't like it, right?
- No.
You must've hated it.
The first thing that popped
into my head as I saw him was,
"I will never
be friends with that guy."
(I will never
be friends with that guy.)
(He closed his mind
the first time he saw Dong Geun.)
- "What's up, what's up?"
- That's enough.
Then I had several chances
to film shows with him.
But the first impression
was too strong...
- that I couldn't get closer to him.
- I know what you mean.
- You hated him.
- Whenever I see him, he was like...
(Whenever I see him, he was like...)
(Swaggering slowly)
- I knew it.
- He walked like this.
- So you got closer recently.
- Yes, it seems like it.
But as I got to know him...
- I could understand him.
- So you got to know him.
They have a very special
bond with each other.
- When Dong Min films a show...
- So we were...
Hey, stop talking.
Let him talk.
Why are you stopping him?
- You can't stop him.
- Hey.
- I want to hear him.
- He talks well.
- No, he's not going to talk.
- Really?
This is like a funny skit.
It's rude to make someone
speak so suddenly.
(Thanks to his friend, he's
meditating silently from the start.)
Today, we are going to pick the best
couple with perfect chemistry.
It's the first Friendship Awards.
Each two best friends will team up.
Coins will be given, according
to the result of your mission.
At the end of the mission,
prizes will be given accordingly...
only to the top three teams
with the most coins.
And today,
a penalty will also be given.
The penalty will be
given to individuals, not to teams.
The penalty will be given to the top
three with the most penalty badges.
But in my case, teaming up...
- with Kwang Soo is bad for me.
- It doesn't matter, right?
Penalty will be
given to individuals.
Then you should've
said that earlier.
Now I'll explain
about penalty badges.
You can buy a penalty badge
with three coins.
Write down the name that you want
to give a penalty to on the coin.
Then give it to the PDs
who are wearing red caps.
You have to hand them
three coins secretly.
Then a penalty badge
will be given to that person.
- Secretly.
- So...
So I should earn coins
to get rid of someone else.
And not to get a penalty myself.
(Collect coins
for prizes and penalties)
But you need to collect
coins to receive prizes.
We won't reveal to you
how many penalty badges you have.
But we will inform you how many
penalty badges the top three got...
at the end of every mission.
But if you wish to know
how many penalty badges you got,
you should give a coin to us.
Then we'll let you know.
- It cost a coin?
- Yes.
What's more important is this.
You use three coins
to give a penalty badge...
and a coin to know your number.
So it's important
who's holding the coin bag.
- You're right.
- I'll get that.
- Come on. I'll hold it.
- Why are you making them fight?
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
- Wait.
Let's do rock, paper, scissors
to decide.
- Come on.
- Let's do it.
- No way.
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
Come on. Do rock, paper, scissors.
There's no way you're holding this.
Just stay still.
- Let's do this fair and square.
- Stay still.
- Let's count first.
- Just wait.
You can't use them as you want.
I'm telling you. You don't
have to worry about a thing.
(Each team gets 20 R coins)
Gosh, what is that?
- I think it's hopscotch.
- This feels bad.
I think it's hopscotch.
- Gosh, there are balloons.
- My goodness.
Yes, there are balloons.
- This feels really bad.
- It looks like tofu.
(Two pieces of paper barely hold
the balloons from each side.)
- What is this?
- It's that rope game.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
It looks fun.
You are allowed to
give coins to us now.
- Let me explain the rules again.
- I can give you coins now?
Write the name you want
on the coin and give it to us.
Then a penalty badge
will be given to that person.
- You have one, right?
- Yes.
I can write down a name?
Hey, you can't let
anyone see the name.
Is that so?
So we're supposed to
write the name on the coin?
Why did you write my name down?
Why did you write down my name?
- I wanted to write it on each coin.
- You do that.
You can't do that.
Tae Hyun, why are you
writing Kwang Soo's name down?
Because I want him
to get a penalty.
Then I'll write down your name too.
If you write his name down,
he could write down our names.
- You can't let him see it.
- Come to think of it,
members of TOMORROW X TOGETHER
are here with us today.
- Why don't we watch them perform?
- Yes.
- We should listen to their song.
- Right.
- Come on out.
- I can't wait.
Go for it.
TOMORROW X TOGETHER.
("Blue Hour"
by TOMORROW X TOGETHER)
(The older sister loves it.)
(My goodness!)
(TOMORROW X TOGETHER
is so cool!)
(Increasing the tension
with their brilliant performance.)
("Blue Hour"
by TOMORROW X TOGETHER)
(Flapping)
Don't do that.
They're amazing.
- That's not how they did it.
- They are so good.
We would've been sorry
if we didn't see this. Gosh.
By the way,
- Dong Geun.
- Yes?
Sing "Alleyway" for us.
(Everyone's cheering for him.)
Dong Geun.
I love "Alleyway".
- Here he goes.
- "Alleyway" and his friend.
- I love it.
- Perform with your friend.
(His mega-hit K-pop song in 2002
is a remake of Lee Jae Min’s song.)
(The song features YDG's
robot dance and addictive melody.)
(Everyone sang along at least once.
"Alleyway" with his charming tone)
(Can't wait!)
(They still remember the move!)
The robot dance.
(They were teenagers back then
so they're excited.)
You're right.
- He's a good dancer.
- None stop.
(Brings back memories of 2002!)
Come on, louder!
YDG!
1, 2, 3!
Come on, twins' dad!
Gosh, you're cool!
Here he goes!
Let's go!
(He's popping his joints
just like he did 18 years ago.)
He's good!
(A song from the early 2000s
still sounds exciting.)
Amazing.
(Folding and unfolding dance)
I haven't seen this in a long time.
(Finishing a performance
from old memories.)
(Great satisfaction)
- That's my friend!
- YDG!
Tae Hyun's "I Love You"!
Sing "I Love You".
- "I Love You"!
- Sing it for us.
- Sing "I Love You."
- "I Love You."
- Come on, sing it.
(The friends' talent show
is getting bigger and bigger.)
- I love this song.
- Me too.
Tae Hyun, we really love this song.
You must remember
the song very well.
- Yes, we love it.
- You're right.
(Mega-hit title song of
Cha Tae Hyun's...)
(first full-length album
released in 2001)
(The song features addictive
beats and his Eagle Dance.)
(Tae Hyun was 26 back then.)
(I love you!)
- I love the song.
- Wasn't it popular back then?
I recorded
the guide track for this song.
- You worked on the guide track?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
(He's genuinely surprised.)
Here he goes. Cha Tae Hyun!
- Cha Tae Hyun!
- I can't believe I'm watching this.
- I love you, Cha Tae Hyun!
- Cha Tae Hyun!
(Starting the engine
of the eagle from the 2000s.)
Here it is.
(Ecstatic)
Here he goes!
(The eagle from 19 years ago)
(Ready to fly high gorgeously)
I regret my love
- Cha Tae Hyun!
(Singing "I Love You"
just like he did in the old days)
Gosh, this is it?
(The talent show
just seems so funny to his friend.)
(This is the sophistication
of the 2000s.)
(I think it's enough.)
You did well.
(Finishing Tae Hyun's performance
from the old days.)
Great.
Gosh, I loved it.
He was so popular
when he released this song.
- You're right.
- It topped the charts.
Mi Joo is here with us
in a long time.
I'd like her to perform
one of Lovelyz's songs.
- "Hi."
- "Hi"?
- I want to listen to "Hi".
- Destiny?
She's a goddess from Okchon.
Yes, a goddess from Okchon!
- She's Ok-Mi-Goddess.
- Ok-Joo-Goddess.
- Ok-Goddess.
("Hi" by Lovelyz, 2015
Mi Joo's Solo version)
Look at her jump.
(Today, she turns into
an innocent girl group member.)
(She's good.)
- Look at her.
- She's good.
We needed this.
She sure is a goddess from Okchon.
Mi Joo, lift the spirit
up to the highlight!
(A die-hard fan requested her
to lift her spirit up!)
(Here goes the highlight.)
(Dimly)
Now say "Hi".
(Changing abruptly)
(Hi?)
(Bouncy Mi Joo is up!)
(The goddess is saying hi
using every bone in her body.)
You're amazing!
You're good!
You're amazing, goddess from Okchon.
I love you!
She's really amazing.
She's so good.
Everyone, give her a big hand!
Okay, okay!
- You're the best.
- So good.
- She's the best.
- Goddess from Okchon.
She is the best.
Mi Joo is the best.
- She really is bouncy.
- Yes, she is.
I thought she was
on the hot sand in the beach.
I thought she was jumping like that
because the sand was hot.
- She was lovely.
- She's really good.
- You were...
- Gosh.
- pretty.
- She's good.
- I was?
- Yes, you were.
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, sing "Mosquito" for us.
"Mosquito"?
- Yes, "Mosquito".
- What's "Mosquito"?
He likes it.
- They know it.
- "Mosquito."
He likes it. They know it.
- Yes, I know it.
- They love "Mosquito".
- "It was itchy."
- "It bit my foot."
- Sing it for them. They love it.
- Yes, you should.
Come on. They love it.
The kids love it, so do it.
Show them.
Why do I have to do this
standing out in front?
- Do it for us.
- Please.
Yeon Jun seems excited.
They'll enjoy it.
A giant mosquito bit my foot.
(A giant mosquito bit my foot.)
It was itchy.
(He shows off
his 10-year-old talent.)
That was awesome.
It was the best.
I've never seen this before.
Gosh, this is...
(He's excited to see it in person.)
I just did it because
they'd like it.
He just did it for you guys.
They really like it.
- It was the best.
- He did it for you guys.
They really like it.
It was really good.
This is the first mission
for the Friendship Awards.
It's called Torn Friendship.
Torn Friendship?
One member of each team
will sit under the water balloon.
And the other member will sit
in the question seat.
They will ask each other questions,
and they must give
irrelevant answers.
If you give a relevant answer,
your opponent will pour
a spoonful of water on your paper.
- On the paper.
If you keep pouring water on it,
the paper will get wet and cut off.
So the balloon will fall.
It's a tournament.
This is how it goes.
Okay.
Round One is Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
versus Jong Kook and Tae Hyun.
If we win this game,
will we get coins?
Sure. But you move on
to the next round.
- Kwang Soo, you know what to do.
- Sure. I do.
You can't say anything
about my wife.
- What? My gosh.
- What was that?
That's what this game is all about.
I'm not good at games like this,
but I'll give it a try.
Okay.
Kwang Soo, I heard you didn't
want to film "The Pirates".
Purple.
(He gets flustered
by the sudden slander...)
(and barely gives an answer.)
It's not like that.
He's flustered.
I'm working on the movie now.
(He embarrasses him by talking
about the movie he's filming.)
I heard that a lot.
- Well done.
- What are you talking about?
Don't think about it.
- It's going well.
- Don't think about it.
- When did I say that?
- Stop thinking about it.
Don't answer it.
It's stranger when you get upset.
- Shall I begin?
- He's not good. Go easy on him.
What do you think of Jong Kook?
- I'm so sleepy.
- Good.
Did he get it wrong?
- He succeeded.
- He did?
Tae Hyun is good at playing games.
I heard you don't get along with
Son Ye Jin in "The Pirates".
- I heard that.
- Hey, just say something.
- That's what I heard.
- Kimchi.
(He just listens
to the question silently.)
(Time's up.)
He didn't finish his question.
- And that's not true.
- Why did you not say anything?
Son Ye Jin doesn't even
appear in the movie.
You should talk
about something else.
- She doesn't?
- She's not even in the movie.
Then you could've just said
something else.
So you fell for that.
- You shouldn't care about it.
- Okay.
- Where should I pour it?
- On the left.
Look.
- You should do it in the middle.
- In the middle?
Sure.
(He pours water in the middle.)
I'll pour it on one spot
to make it weak.
Kwang Soo.
I don't care about the water
balloon. Don't worry.
- Just do it at ease.
- Okay.
Trust me. Okay?
- Is it my turn?
- You should ask a question.
You should ask a question.
The water...
- It's melting.
- I'll go next.
- There's a hole.
- Oh no.
It's melting.
- It's melting.
- We should hurry.
We should've poured it on one side.
- To make it long.
- It spreads faster that way.
You should hurry. It's melting.
Just do it.
How are you feeling now?
Gosh, I'm sleepy.
Oh, okay!
(Tae Hyun said something about
his condition, so it's wrong.)
- He said he's sleepy.
- This is hard.
- He's caught.
- Hey, make it long.
- Long.
- Don't spread it.
- Make it long.
- If you do it well,
- you can turn the game around.
- You should make it the same.
- What if...
- This is dangerous.
My gosh.
(He shakes it to the last drop.)
We have to hurry.
It will be ripped soon.
- Hurry.
- My turn.
Do you like Yoo Jae Suk
or Zo In Sung?
Choi Bo Pil.
(He named the main director.)
(Wrong)
(He tried to evade the question by
calling the main director's name.)
- How cowardly.
- Hey.
- Let's hurry and continue.
- What was that?
You could've said anything else.
Why did you say
Choi Bo Pil all of a sudden?
My gosh.
Good.
- That's going to rip soon.
- Hurry.
On the other side. Good.
- It will break.
- Good.
That's going to rip soon.
- All right. I'll do it now.
- Hurry.
- This is...
- You did your job.
Look at this.
- I'll do it.
- Look at this.
I can do this.
It's okay. Let me take it over.
You've done your job. Well done.
- That's not what I meant.
- Jae Suk.
- Let's continue.
- We should hurry.
- Ask a sharp question.
- Okay.
There's a bad rumor
going around our neighborhood.
- They live in the same town.
- I like Jang Hyuk.
Look at him.
(Sulky)
- Was it a sharp question?
- He's not good at asking questions.
The question was...
- He's not good at this.
- It's just one step back.
I just take 1 step back
to take 10 steps forward.
We live in the same neighborhood,
and there's a bad rumor about you.
That can't be right.
(He denies it shaking his head.)
What are you doing?
He got me.
What was that?
(The nation's beloved MC is
sensitive about his reputation.)
"That can't be right."
- "That can't be right."
- He said "That can't be right."
Oh no.
- Okay.
- He's really bad at games.
- "That can't be right."
- Don't worry.
- Don't take it seriously.
He said "That can't be right."
He wants to explain.
He has to explain.
- What was that?
- Don't worry.
(The balloon bursts.)
Okay.
(The paper was barely holding out.)
(It burst.)
(It burst above Kwang Soo's head
as soon as they switched seats.)
He said that can't be right.
Gosh, Jae Suk is so funny.
You are so weak-minded.
You're unbelievable.
Tae Hyun is really good.
How could he say that?
He's so good at playing games.
Next teams.
Suk Jin and Haha versus
Dong Geun and Dong Min.
Dong Min is really good at games.
- He's really good.
- He's the master of games.
- He's a genius.
- A genius.
- We have experience though.
- Okay.
We've done this a lot before.
(The veteran player Suk Jin is
fighting against the game master.)
Isn't Wonju far from here?
I ate two days ago.
He's different. You can't do this.
He's no match.
You invested in something
without telling your wife.
Stir-fried frog.
You invested in stir-fried frog?
- Does it make sense?
- It makes sense.
- How does it make sense?
- It does.
- Does it?
- You invested in stir-fried frog.
Who would invest in stir-fried frog?
That's not a good idea.
People in my neighborhood
are investing a lot of money in it.
In stir-fried frog?
Who didn't invest
in stir-fried frog here?
- I did.
- Me too.
I also invested in seasoned frogs.
Sure. I did it too.
Just a little.
- I see.
- I didn't put a lot of money in it.
So you invest in stir-fried frog.
- You should do it too.
- I see.
Okay.
Go easy on us
so we can play this for a long time.
- Let's play this for a long time.
- Hey.
Don't be so cheap.
It will be ripped right away.
You should hurry.
- You can't touch the paper.
- They have to hurry.
- Don't touch the paper with it.
- Let's hurry.
Hurry and ask a question.
- Hurry.
- Go ahead and ask.
Is your stock investment going well?
I'll be a member
of the national team.
It makes sense.
- Why?
- He can be in the national team...
- for stock investment.
There's no national team
for stock investment.
- I know.
- That darn...
(The promising stock investor,
Dong Min, is short-tempered.)
- You can be on the national team.
- That's true.
You'll be on the national team
for stock investment.
- It makes sense.
- It totally makes sense.
Why did you give a relevant answer?
- Okay.
- Let's continue.
He's not so good.
What did you eat this morning?
I sleep.
You slept in the morning.
- So you didn't eat?
- Yes!
Why?
- That's not it.
- You slept instead of eating.
You slept in the morning.
- You didn't eat.
- No.
That's just an assumption.
- You sleep in the morning.
- It's an assumption.
"What did you eat in the morning?"
"I didn't eat anything."
That's an answer about food.
What kind of director is he?
(He even questions
the qualification of the director.)
He's not good at Korean language.
- Continue.
- No, it makes sense.
You should hurry.
You hope the price of your land
in Wonju will go up, right?
I hope it will go down... Darn.
(While Suk Jin struggles,)
(the balloon bursts.)
It burst.
- Well done.
- You keep doing things like that.
- Keep up the good work.
- Okay.
Next up is So Min and Mi Joo
versus Ji Hyo and Se Chan.
You shouldn't think a lot
before answering.
You shouldn't ask
if she likes something.
"Where is good?"
"What do you think of this?"
It's very moist in here.
I think Ji Hyo is good at this.
- You should empty your head.
- She's always like that.
She often gives irrelevant answers.
Ji Hyo seems to have
something else on her mind.
Ji Hyo can be really good at this.
I'm scared.
Writer Jeon.
How are you feeling now?
So Min...
(Time's up.)
(Hesitant)
(What?)
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- It was too late.
- You should answer quickly.
She always answers
after two seconds.
It was too late.
I always think before I talk.
- She pours water there.
- There?
You poured it here?
Hey, that will rip right away.
- She's really mean.
- Let's make it quick.
My gosh.
(Devastated)
Let's end it quickly.
We don't have to make it long.
(However...)
(It's ripping already.)
No, wait.
Hang on.
Wait. Just a moment.
What was that?
Wait.
(The balloon threatens
Se Chan to death.)
What do we do?
- What do I do?
- Come here.
Why didn't it burst?
We didn't get to ask a question.
What was that? Hey.
- What was that?
- What's wrong?
- It wasn't even a sharp question.
- It was funny anyway.
You can't pour it there from now on.
- From now on?
- Why not?
- Se Chan.
- Kwang Soo and I were...
- Hang on.
- I'm sorry.
You can't say he's handsome.
Tell me three reasons
why you love your wife.
She's pretty, nice, and rich.
(I love you, honey.)
- This is good.
- She's a perfect wife.
Tell me three occupations
of the men you dated.
Idol artist, actor, and news anchor.
(Idol artist, actor,
and news anchor)
- Good. This is Mi Joo.
- Well done.
- Good.
- This is Mi Joo.
- Okay!
- You did a good job.
- She did a good job.
- It's a shame.
In the order of the ranking,
Jong Kook and Tae Hyun who came in
1st will receive 15 coins.
15 coins?
- Okay.
- 15 coins?
So Min and Mi Joo will receive
12 coins.
Team Dong Geun and Team Yeon Jun
will receive nine coins.
The rest teams will receive
six coins.
- That's quite a lot.
- Six coins?
(The bottom 3 teams obtained
6 coins.)
I'll announce the three people...
who got the most penalty badges
so far and how many badges they got.
- Already?
- Is there any?
- None of us has any enemies here.
- That's not possible.
(Some of us already got
penalty badges?)
That's not possible.
(Some of them went to the staff
to give others penalty badges.)
Two of you are in first place.
- Already?
- Two of us?
Each of them received
one penalty badge.
- What?
- So soon?
(Who purchased 1 penalty badge
for 3 coins already?)
(Before the mission began...)
Why would you talk to them
when you have seniority over them?
I'll sort things out by myself.
- So don't talk to them.
- Then...
- Then I'll give you a mission.
- Okay.
(After Dong Min gave him a mission,)
(Se Chan quietly came up to
a staff member in a red cap.)
I just hate her.
She was so mean in the game.
(He turned in 3 coins to give So Min
1 penalty badge.)
- One badge?
- Yes.
For one coin, we'll tell you
who they are via text message.
No one would do that
when they have only one badge.
We would want to know
when we have at least five.
Someone turned three coins in.
- 3 coins for each badge.
- Yes, to give someone 1 badge.
- You need 3 coins...
- to give 1 person 1 penalty badge.
- Each of them got 1 badge.
Who received it?
Kwang Soo, you got one badge.
(Kwang Soo, you got one badge.)
- Did you turn your coins in?
- Yes.
- Earlier...
- When did you do that?
What's wrong with him?
Why would say that to Kwang Soo?
- I wrote your name on it.
- You're not supposed to say it.
- Don't let him sway you.
- He might give you a penalty badge.
- Is what he said true?
I turned three coins in
as soon as I received the coins.
- Don't let him sway you.
- I said, don't say it to him.
- Why would he do that to me?
- Don't tell others.
- You shouldn't.
- Don't speak to Tae Hyun today.
- What he said about the movie...
- Calm down.
- Don't speak to Tae Hyun.
- It wasn't true.
- Don't talk to him today.
- I'm happy that I got the part.
Hey, listen to me.
Don't speak to Tae Hyun.
- Did he really write my name?
- Stop it.
I turned in the coins
because I didn't know.
- I won't talk about it anymore.
- They won 15 coins.
Everyone, you're hungry, aren't you?
- Yes!
- We'll have a lunch break now.
- Okay.
Come with your partner
to receive a lunchbox.
You can eat at 1 of the 3 places
we prepared.
2 teams will team up
for the 2nd mission.
- Really?
- So you should talk...
to the team you want
and get an agreement.
- Okay. I see.
- Okay.
Good. There are six seats here.
Dong Min.
You know us.
You should team up with us.
No, he should team up with us.
Dong Geun.
- But...
- Come on. Dong Min.
Team Dong-Dong,
enjoy your lunch.
- Enjoy your lunch.
- We'll always be polite.
- You too.
- We want to team up with you two.
- I'm glad you're my friend.
- Look at them.
- Look how rude they are.
- Hey.
- Don't try so hard to please him.
- Are you his minion or what?
- I feel a little uncomfortable.
- It's good to be treated nicely.
- That sounds amazing.
- Of course.
I want to drink some water
before I start eating.
- Water? Just a moment.
- Yes.
Good. Se Chan is so thoughtful.
- Hey, think about it.
- We don't do that.
Suk Jin wouldn't go
and fetch you water.
- Hey, bring it here.
- Here you go.
- I'll open it for him.
- Bring it here.
You don't have to open it for him.
Dong Min says he's thirsty!
- I can do this much for him.
- Thanks.
- You didn't have to do this.
- You don't have soup. Here you go.
- But first,
- Yes?
each team must be clear
about their goal...
in this race.
- Suk Jin, is your team's goal...
- Yes?
to win or to avoid the penalty?
What is your goal?
- To win.
- Our goal is to avoid the penalty.
- No, to avoid the penalty.
- I want to win.
- You two must come to an agreement.
- I know.
Suk Jin, why do you have
no desire to win?
- Gosh.
- It's not like that.
They don't agree with each other
when they're on the same team.
- I'm too uncomfortable to eat.
- Calm down.
We'll come to an agreement soon.
- We share the same goal.
- It won't take long.
- What is it?
- 1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3. Avoiding the penalty.
- Avoiding the penalty.
(Avoiding the penalty
is their goal.)
- Good. That's more like it.
- Absolutely.
A band of misfits like them...
- Our goal is...
- 1, 2, 3.
- Team Dong-Dong's win.
- That's our goal.
- Oh, my.
That means they'll betray you.
I mean,
saying such a thing in front of
the cameras makes me uncomfortable.
(He's acting prissy.)
Gosh, seriously.
I'll explain our first strategy.
Let's call us good teams.
- Okay.
- And the other teams are...
bad teams, for example.
Our first strategy is to make
the bad teams use a lot of coins.
- I see.
- How are we going to do that?
Each of us will have to get
one penalty badge.
- 1 penalty badge?
- 1 badge costs 3 coins, right?
So they'll have to spend 18 coins.
Got it?
Meanwhile... For example, everyone
except for Ji Hyo gets one badge,
- and Ji Hyo gets two.
- Okay.
Then we make sure the other team's
members get more than two badges,
so she can avoid coming in last.
- She can avoid coming in last.
- Exactly.
- He sure is so smart.
- You understand what I said, right?
He's saying that we all are on
the same team from this moment on.
We're eating together.
What does it mean?
- It means that we're a family now.
- Yes.
Have you ever heard
the oath of the peach garden?
Do you know what "oath" means?
- Pardon?
- What does "oath" mean?
I think it means to go back.
- "To go back"?
- Yes.
It means there's no turning back.
That's what it means.
The three of them swore they won't
go back on their promises...
and be loyal to one another
for the rest of their lives.
(While they're forming an alliance
under Dong Min's lead...)
Kwang Soo,
you won't betray us, right?
- Of course, I won't.
- Don't worry.
There's no reason
for betraying each other.
We must do well
at the next mission...
and gain as many coins as possible.
We don't have so many coins
now either.
(Setting up a camera)
(Staring)
How many coins do you two have?
Only three of us are in the frame.
Is that okay?
(The screen of the camera
that was just set up)
- There's...
- It's okay.
I'm sorry, but can you
move your soup aside?
(I'm sorry, but can you
move your soup aside?)
- Sure. I'll move it, but...
- Listen to me.
I might dump the soup on you.
(I'll move it,
but I might dump the soup on you.)
Don't worry about it.
I'm filming you right now.
What do you mean by that?
I was asked to film you secretly.
- Seriously...
- Look. There's a camera here.
- I'm filming you right now.
- I guess it's true.
By the way, why did he set up
the camera like that?
We would all in the frame
if he put it in the middle.
Exactly.
But he put it in the corner,
and Kwang Soo is out of the frame.
He even hit me with the elbow
to make me move to the side.
Don't worry about it.
That's not a problem.
You should worry about Tae Hyun.
He's trying to...
Could it be true?
Should I check if it's true?
If he really gave me a badge,
I won't let it slide.
- If he did what?
- If he gave me a badge,
I'll get back at him right away.
- By any means...
- That's your problem.
You don't have many coins,
but he has a lot.
(Before the 1st mission began...)
- No one is around us, right?
- Yes.
Here you go. I want to give a badge
to Kwang Soo.
- You're turning in 3 coins.
- Yes, for 1 penalty badge.
(Huening Kai gave a penalty badge
to Kwang Soo!)
I'm absolutely sure that Tae Hyun
gave you a badge.
I think so too.
There's no way...
(He has no idea
that Huening Kai gave him a badge.)
that we both got a badge, right?
That can't be.
(The lunch break ended when they
only became more suspicious.)
- She'll probably get the penalty.
- You shouldn't do that.
Who on earth spent
so many coins already?
- Right?
- I'd spend my coins all at once.
Who were they?
What's wrong with him?
This is not how it works, Tae Hyun.
- You shouldn't let others know.
- This isn't how it works.
- Come on, Tae Hyun.
- Hey, since I got...
more coins, I'll spend
as many as I want.
Where did all your coins go?
(Where did all your coins go?)
(Dong Min is happy that Tae Hyun is
spending coins thoughtlessly.)
- Are you serious?
- Hey.
I don't know either.
I gave him all the coins we won.
Why did you give him all of them?
- I let him do whatever he wants.
- I thought I should...
I want him to enjoy himself since he
came on the show after a long time.
Guys, don't worry about him. I'll
give him as many badges as I can.
- Okay.
My gosh.
In this mission,
two teams will pair up.
Tell me which team your team
will team up with.
- Is this your final decision?
- Yes.
- The four of us.
- All right.
- My team and Team Dong-Dong.
- Okay.
- Each team has four members.
- With Se Chan's team?
Okay. Good.
- I'm happy with it.
- Me too. I feel light-hearted.
You two look like
a team of old thieves.
Shut it. Shut your mouth.
- The two of them...
- They look like...
- look like...
- a team of old thieves.
- the thieves from "Home Alone".
- Exactly.
- Reenact a scene from the movie.
- I said, shut it.
Now, we're going to reveal
the second mission.
Huening Kai and Yeon Jun, could you
please turn that around?
- Yes.
- What could it be? I'm curious.
- Go ahead.
- They got unlucky.
Their opponent team was
too strong.
- You're right.
- Of course.
- What's that?
- It's a board game.
What is it?
Oh, my goodness.
We're playing this game?
It looks just like the famous game.
- Have you ever played this?
- They did a good job at making it.
Are you good at this game?
I'm so good at it.
For the second mission,
we changed a few things of
the world travel board game...
we all played with friends.
It's Into the World with Friends.
You will be divided into four teams.
This game has similar basic rules.
The 4 teams will take turns
rolling 2 dice,
and move your marker
according to the result.
Build a hotel or a villa
in the ownerless city...
and receive a fee from other teams
that stop there.
- Can you see the prices?
- Yes.
That's the amount you pay
for building a villa or a hotel.
You have to pay double the amount
when you stop there.
- Understood.
- It's simple, right?
- Okay.
- I think...
I told you that there are
two dice, right?
One has numbers,
and the other has go, back,
- and go double.
- Oh, I see.
- 3 and double means 6 moves?
- Exactly.
The game ends in 30 minutes.
The team
with the most game money...
- will receive the most coins.
- Right.
This is too easy.
They're the two bossiest members
on Running Man.
This is too easy.
- Let's do this!
- All right.
I've never tried this before.
- What should we get?
- "Jiseokjin World"!
- What was your channel?
- It's "Haha PD".
Oh, right. "Haha PD".
He doesn't know.
What should we do to win?
- Getting a higher number?
- Yes, that'd be great.
- Okay. Let's begin.
- You need to stop at a good city.
- Here we go.
- You get paid when you pass Go.
- Go to the deserted island.
- 2, 3.
I hope they stop
at the deserted island.
- 2 and go.
- Oh, we got 2.
- They got two. It's Beijing.
- It's Beijing.
Pay 80 dollars for a villa
or 160 dollars for a hotel.
- You should build one.
- How much do we start with?
Hey, let's just build a hotel.
- Let's build a hotel.
- That's good.
- You should buy it no matter what.
- Exactly.
We don't have much time,
so you should buy it no matter what.
Every city you can buy.
- What's "back"?
- We just have to avoid number two.
Anything else would be okay.
- Roll the dice.
- You should move backward.
Getting a back would be great now.
- We got a go.
- Nice.
- Jakarta!
- Buy it.
- It's 200 dollars.
(They're building a hotel.)
- We're in trouble.
- Director.
What happens if we get
a back from the start?
You can't move.
- Oh, we can't move at all.
- I see.
- We can't move?
- Shouldn't we move backward?
- We don't move backward?
- You have to go back.
You have to let us move backward.
That's how we can buy
the expensive land.
We should be allowed to do that.
Why are you angry, Mr. Jang?
- It should be allowed.
- This is just a game.
Why write "back" on the dice then?
- Write "stay" instead.
- It's just for the first roll.
(It only applies to the first roll.)
You know,
Bo Pil has met
his fair share of celebrities,
but none like Dong Min.
Someone who complains directly.
- He's the first since Jessi.
- Since Jessi.
Team Dong-Dong will go next.
Sure, okay.
- We need a double, Dong Min.
- A double.
Roll a six.
- 1, 2, 3.
- No way.
- That'd be really lucky.
I bet we'll roll a "back".
- Back.
- Hold on.
- Move them backward.
- You can't.
- Hold on.
- We go four steps back.
- You have to stay where you are.
- They can't move yet.
You're off to a tough start.
They're both bad
at rolling good numbers.
What you least want
is a 2 or a 6.
- Okay!
- Roll "back" instead.
- Let's go.
- Roll two.
1, 2, 3.
Don't worry.
We'll end up winning anyway.
Back?
- Two!
- All right!
Yes!
Okay.
- Pay up 320 dollars.
- What did I tell you?
We have to pay?
Pay us 320 dollars.
That was the cheaper one,
so we're fine.
Pay up if you booked a room
at our hotel.
That'll be 320 dollars.
- We need to pay them.
- What's funny though...
that constructing the hotel
is 160 dollars,
but a room is 320 dollars a night.
Okay.
- I'll roll this one.
- Sure.
- Roll a four.
- Here we go.
- Roll a 4.
- 1.
- 1, 2...
- 4, 4...
4, 4, 4...
Two and go.
(Golden Key card)
- Wait.
- The Golden Key card!
- What's our card?
- "Sell at half the price."
- "To your friends..."
- "Give them money."
- I'd like that one.
- 100 dollars each.
- "Sell at half the price."
- "Go to the deserted island."
You can show them.
(They pick a card from the stack.)
Darn.
- It's actually beneficial.
- No way!
- Gosh.
- If only someone else chose it.
- What is it?
- Darn.
"The old-age pension has been paid."
"Suk Jin, the eldest, will receive
200 dollars from the bank."
Nice.
- You're receiving a pension?
- It's so fitting.
- This...
- You're receiving a pension?
I would've received it
regardless of who picked the card.
What a waste.
- If only someone else chose it.
- Exactly.
Isn't it fitting?
- Suk Jin...
- You're being treated well.
- You are.
- Roll a 5.
- No, roll a 6.
- 6 and go.
- 6.
- Back.
- It's "back".
Okay, you still can't move yet.
We'll be at the starting line
forever at this rate.
Why can't you get going?
- Dong Min...
- It's all right.
It's fine. It's all right.
- Go ahead.
- Let's land on Seoul.
- 1, 2, 3.
- 3.
- Roll a four.
- Back.
- Back. Okay, that's good.
- Nice.
- It's not bad.
- Taipei.
- Let's buy it.
- I thought we moved forward.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Is that 100 dollars?
- Yes.
I'm better at this back home.
- Let's do this.
- And go.
We're currently the richest.
- Go.
- Five.
1, 2, 3, 4.
- Buy Athens. We have the money.
- Of course.
Buy a hotel.
- 280 dollars.
- 280.
- It's not even a lot.
- 30 minutes.
- Land on Athens and we'll see.
- Don't roll a "back".
That's 28 times...
- Can we roll one at a time?
- You can.
Six.
- Go.
- One at a time...
Can we construct another?
- Yes.
- You can construct a villa.
Then construct one.
- Okay.
- Roll a "back".
- Dong Geun, roll a "back".
- Back!
- Back.
Go!
- He rolled a "go".
- Go...
- Roll 3, 4, or 5.
- You guys...
- 3, 4, or 5.
- Roll a 2.
- 2.
- 3, 4, or 5.
- Roll a 1.
- 2.
- 3, 4, or 5.
3, 4, or 5.
- A three!
- Nice.
- Three.
- That's Manila.
Three. All right!
- Buy the darn thing.
- Get us a hotel.
- That's right.
- Get a hotel.
- A hotel.
- Buy a hotel.
Dong Geun, nice.
(They celebrate by dancing
to "Alleyway".)
Nice.
- Do this to collect money.
- Sure.
(They can annoy the others
while doing so.)
A double.
- A double is good.
- Roll a "back".
- Back.
- Then...
- A double.
- Back!
- Back.
Roll a six.
- Roll a six.
- Get ready to collect.
Roll a six.
- Roll a six.
- Get ready to collect.
- 1 and 2 are fine.
- 5 or 2.
5 or 2.
- Yes, 5 or 2.
- Roll a 3.
- 6.
- 3.
- 5 or 2.
1 or 4.
- One.
- The deserted island.
- We're on the deserted island.
The deserted island!
That's not so bad.
At least we don't
have to pay anyone.
I guess.
You have to skip a turn
while on the deserted island...
and draw on a beard
since you can't shave.
Nice!
A beard. Good.
You'll both draw on a beard.
Turn into Woong's father.
Woong's father.
- Is this a permanent marker?
- Of course not.
- What the...
- Hold on a second.
Are you kidding me?
(He looks sly.)
- It looks perfect on him.
- A beard...
Is that allowed?
- Couldn't you give me a beard...
- It's done.
that makes me look like a gentleman?
This isn't friendly in any way.
I'd like those Groucho glasses.
It suits you so well.
- No way.
- I wanted to look like a gentleman.
(Painter Yoo is satisfied
by his masterpiece.)
- It suits you.
- Let's keep going.
- Roll a four.
- Here we go.
- 1 would be great.
- Roll a 4.
Four and go.
- Roll 1.
- 4.
(Please roll a 1.)
- 1.
(They roll a 1.)
(Team Red has a villa and hotel
and will collect 600 dollars.)
(They end up staying at a place
that costs 600 dollars.)
Nice.
They're so annoying.
Can they be more annoying?
(They can't contain their joy.)
Didn't you land on it earlier?
They're raking in the cash.
They're suddenly collecting.
- How much is it?
- 600 dollars.
Answer quicker, darn it.
He's so on edge.
Answer quicker.
- This is just a game.
- Let's speed things up.
It's just supposed to be a fun game.
- Don't be like that.
- Let's speed things up!
Shove that in there.
Hold on a second.
You didn't pay the full amount.
- Wait.
- We did!
I only received 400 dollars.
- We paid up.
- 200 dollars is missing.
- We paid 600.
- We paid up.
- Hand the rest over.
- We paid it all.
The 200 dollars...
We paid!
We paid the whole amount.
- What do you mean we paid less?
- Pay the rest.
- Pay up.
- We paid 600 dollars.
We missed the transaction.
- Pay up the rest.
- We paid 600 dollars.
You didn't see the transaction?
- Hey.
- We paid up.
Pay up the rest.
Get lost!
- What...
- Who plays board games this way?
How does this make sense?
They should pay up.
This goes against international law.
We paid the whole amount too.
- Guys.
- That's right!
From now on,
you'll pay right in front of us.
"From now on"?
- "From now on"?
- Sure.
Just because he's strong...
- Why you...
- No way.
Kwang Soo, darn it.
Yeon Jun, go ahead.
Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo!
(I'll submit penalty badges.)
I'm sorry!
(He suddenly becomes polite.)
- What's wrong with you?
- I was only joking.
- Are you kidding me?
- Why are you doing this?
- Why...
- I gave you 100 dollars.
Our team paid up.
- He gave Tae Hyun money.
- Unbelievable.
Why did you give him 100 dollars?
Whatever...
(What's good is good, right?)
Give back the 100 dollars.
- Give it back.
- You can't take it back.
You can't take it back.
- Give it back.
- Are you kidding me?
Why would you bribe him?
- We barely have money ourselves.
- Tae Hyun,
write down Jae Suk's name instead.
Go and hand it in.
- Hey!
- Should I?
- You can change your target.
- Got it.
- Write his name instead.
- Unbelievable.
Here you go.
What are you doing?
That's from our team's fund.
- Fine. Tae Hyun?
- Hey.
That's enough, okay?
They're unbelievable.
This is hilarious.
Get back here.
We can roll anything but a three.
- A three.
- Right.
- Dong Min.
- Roll a three!
(Please roll a 3!)
- Double...
- Go and three.
- Roll a 3.
- Roll a 2.
- A three.
- The deserted island.
- 3.
- 3!
(Did they roll a 3
like Team Yellow wanted?)
(It rolled over to a 6
at the last second!)
It's a six!
We're on London.
- Let's buy.
- Yes, buy it.
Buy it.
But a hotel.
- This must be right up your alley.
- It is.
Roll a 2, 4, or 5.
Make sure it's a "go" first.
- A go.
- Roll a 2, 4, or 5.
- Go and 3.
- Roll a 6.
- 3.
- 6.
(6: Team Green's land,
3: Team Yellow's land)
- Roll a 2, 4, or 5.
- 6!
Darn!
(Darn!)
The deserted island
is better I guess.
We're good.
The deserted island.
We'll take a break.
(Instead, a beard
must be drawn on them.)
Nose hairs?
(Blowing)
(Nose hair flew out
after sneezing.)
Black snot.
- That's cute.
- It's not bad.
Face this way.
(Her facial muscles
are free-spirited.)
- What on earth?
- Can you stay still?
This isn't a photo shoot, you know.
- All right.
- Draw it all around her mouth.
What the...
(Pointillism)
I can't look. I have trypophobia!
I can't look!
This is the beard I wanted.
She looks like a geezer.
It's the worst beard I've ever seen.
(How do I look?)
(Startled)
(Even Team Yellow
is shocked by her beard.)
- Not like that.
- I can't see it.
At least we get to take a break.
We just need to avoid
rolling a three.
- Sure, a three.
- No one's rolled a double, right?
- Roll a one.
- Give me a double.
- Go.
- Roll a four.
- 4.
- Just avoid rolling a 4.
(Roll a 4, and they'll end up
at Team Green's London hotel.)
- Just avoid rolling a 4.
- 4.
- 1.
- Just avoid rolling a 4.
- Keep rolling.
- Four!
(It's a 4!)
A four!
(They collect 680 dollars
while dancing to "Alleyway".)
(The old thieves lose 680 dollars.)
(We're here to collect!)
- That'll be 680 dollars.
- 680?
680 dollars?
It serves you right
for being so cocky.
1, 2, 3, 4,
- 5, 6.
- Good luck never lasts.
Yes, let's collect.
This is great.
- All right.
- Nice.
Roll a "back".
You're a master at this,
so roll a go or a back.
- Go.
- That's it.
- 4.
- 6.
(They'll be in danger
if they roll above a 4.)
- 4.
- 5.
- 6.
- 4, 5, or 6.
(They'll be on Team Yellow's land
if they roll a 5.)
- 4, 5, or 6.
(The cheer captain
appears out of nowhere.)
(4, 5, and 6 bring them together.)
- Off it goes.
- Keep rolling.
- 6!
(Six!)
(Let's collect!)
(We're doomed.)
- Six.
- Bring on the money.
- That's right.
- Give us the money.
How much is it?
That'll be 320 dollars.
- Okay!
- 320 dollars.
(Why did we have to roll a 6?)
- 2, 5, or 6.
- It's our turn now.
- 1, 2...
- Let's do it.
- It belongs to Team Blue, right?
Tae Hyun, let's roll the dice.
I hope they get a go. Get a go.
- Nice.
- A back is better.
- A back is better at this point.
- You're right.
(They have to pay a fee
if they get 2, 5, or 6.)
- Get a 5.
- 4. 4.
- 5.
- 1 or 3.
- Play the music right away.
- Get a 2. Please. 2. 2.
(If they get a 5,
they'll go to Team Green's land.)
(What number could Team Blue get?)
- 2.
- 5.
- It's a five!
- Yes!
(Five!)
(Disappointed)
(They're collecting a fee
for the 3rd time in a row.)
(Give us money.)
Gosh. This is ridiculous.
What's this?
How much do we owe you?
How much is it?
It's not very expensive.
It's 320 dollars.
They've received a lot of money.
320 dollars. Okay.
Gosh. Why did we stop there?
Let's go. Where are we?
We're the yellow one, right?
We're in London.
(Next up is Team Yellow
who haven't made much progress.)
- I want to buy that city.
- Roll it.
- I want a back.
- Let's get a double go.
- They'll move forward.
- Let's keep moving.
- Let's go as far as we can.
- 4. 4.
- One? Good.
- Let's go. Let's go far away.
(They moved only 1 step.)
- Golden Key card? Okay.
- Golden Key card!
- I'll pick the card.
- I'm excited.
- It should've been a four.
- I hope it's something good for us.
I hope they have to perform
in front of us.
- Performing a funny act.
- Something good for us.
"While walking down the street,"
Darn it.
What is it? Let me see.
What is it? What does it say?
Let me see. What is it?
- Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
- It must be a bad one.
"While walking down the street,"
"you ran into Jong Kook
who is a gangster."
- "Give him 100 dollars."
- Okay!
(My gangster friend is the best.)
- Give me 100 dollars.
You call this a Golden Key card?
That's just ridiculous!
(Team Yellow got robbed
when they don't have much money.)
This is not a Golden Key card.
So there are bad ones too.
Really?
(Team Green's hotel in Manila)
- Yeon Jun, I'm counting on you.
- Yes?
- Huening Kai.
- Any number or word would be fine.
You just have to avoid
getting a go and a 2 or 5.
- Get a two.
- Get a go.
Go and number two.
(Finally, they landed on our land.)
(They keep getting involved
with Team Blue in bad ways.)
- 400 dollars?
- 400 dollars.
- We were on the deserted island.
- How much?
- 400 dollars.
- I'm so happy.
You didn't pay us 200 dollars.
- That's not true.
- Yes, exactly 200 dollars.
You didn't pay us 200 dollars.
- He looks so upset.
- What are you talking about?
You're wrong. We paid you.
- Kwang Soo...
- We paid you.
Gosh, you.
- Why...
- Come on. Give us the money.
- Why would you write my name...
- Pay us 400 dollars right now.
Come on, Jae Suk. Pay us.
You and your nose hairs...
- Pay us now.
- I'm going to pull it all out.
- Pay us 400 dollars now.
- You shouldn't be like this.
Why would you threaten me
by writing my name on the coin?
- You owe us 400 dollars.
- Look at him.
What are you trying to do?
- Give us 200 dollars more.
- Come on. Pay us now.
The bank should say something
to him.
You earned a lot of money.
Roll your dice without any pressure.
We'll win if one more team
pays us a fee.
Hold the corners. That's good.
Go and 3 or 4.
- Go and 3 or 4.
- Go.
- 3 or 4.
- That's good.
- 1, 2, or 5.
- 3 or 4.
Five!
- The deserted island?
- A beard.
- Hey, Mi Joo.
- A beard again.
- It's okay.
- Draw a beard.
- Not again.
Come on.
- Draw an eye on her forehead.
- Draw between her eyebrows.
- Draw an eye.
- Yes, on the forehead.
That's awesome.
You look so cool, Mi Joo.
That's cool, Mi Joo.
How many fingers do I have?
- That's awesome.
- How many?
- 1, 2, 3.
- Hey.
(That feels so good.)
That sly brat...
- So Min doesn't look likable.
- Look at So Min.
My gosh.
(She looks like a 3-eyed man.)
- Look at that. Gosh.
- You two have a staring contest.
You two have a staring contest.
(Neck and neck)
- It's a never-ending match.
- Yes.
- Until one of them washes her face.
- She looks so cute.
- It's a never-ending match.
- Gosh. They won't give up.
- Until one of them washes her face.
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
We have to pay if we get a six.
We must avoid it.
- Okay.
- Really?
- We must not get a six.
- Suk Jin.
You should get a six
so you can go bankrupt.
- Get a 6 and get some rest.
- We go bankrupt if we get a 6?
- It belongs to your team, right?
- 6, okay? Yes. They should get a 6.
Throw it like this. That's good.
You're nervous, aren't you?
- Go.
- That's great. Get a six.
- Let's get ready.
- Get a six.
- Six.
- They'll go bankrupt.
- Not yet.
- Six.
- They'll go bankrupt.
- Not yet.
- 6.
- 6!
(They got a 6!)
(Shocked)
(Six!)
(They have to pay 1,040 dollars.)
Bankrupt, bankrupt
(The owners are announcing
Team Yellow's bankruptcy.)
(Out of all cities, they landed
on the most expensive city.)
- 1,000 dollars, 1,000 dollars
- 1,040 dollars.
- 1,040 dollars
- We're not bankrupt yet.
Give us the money.
Here's 240 dollars.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Here's 300 dollars.
10, 11, 12, 13, 14. Here you go.
That's 1040 dollars.
We had exactly 1,040 dollars left.
- That's amazing.
- We need to get paid.
They knew they'd go to that city
and saved the exact amount.
They're house poor.
- They're house poor.
- We had the exact amount left.
1,040 dollars.
- We'll go to Athens if we get a 2.
- 2.
- That's our land.
- We can get back up again.
- I hope they get a 2.
- Get a 2, so we get back up again.
- 4 or 5.
- Don't you worry.
- I think our team will do well.
- Go.
- Great!
- Good.
- 2. 2.
- 4 or 5.
- 4 or 5. 4 or 5.
- 2. 2.
- 4 or 5.
- 3.
A Golden Key card.
- We got a Golden Key card.
- Good job.
- A Golden Key card.
Good.
- We're safe.
- I hope you run into a gangster.
Run into a gangster.
- I hope so too.
- What is it?
- That might be better.
- "You got hired for a commercial."
"Make delicious stir-fried ramyeon."
What does this mean?
We have to cook ramyeon?
You have to cook ramyeon.
You've been chosen as the models
for an indirect advertisement.
That looks so delicious.
But you know...
- You should pay us for that.
- Why won't we get paid?
- We deserve a modeling fee.
- I've never seen that before.
- I'm sorry.
- Please cook at the back.
Go and eat up.
Gosh. This isn't a Golden Key card.
Why must we cook ramyeon
while playing the game?
You should do it.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(They'll decide the chef
by playing rock-paper-scissors.)
Rock-paper-scissors
- You lost.
- Yeon Jun, cook it.
Yeon Jun, make it delicious.
It's our turn.
(The game continues.)
- It's our turn.
- If we get lucky.
Haha, what are you doing?
It's our turn.
What was that?
- They have no money.
- Is it our turn?
- It's not our turn.
- 40 dollars and...
- We're in Paris, right?
- They have no enthusiasm.
Hey, why aren't you enthusiastic?
I don't know why.
- You should get a double 2 or 4.
- I'm running out of energy.
It's okay. Hey, don't give up.
Okay. I'll go first.
They've lasted longer than expected.
- Go.
- Go and 6.
- 6.
- 1, 2, 3, 4,
- That's us.
- 5, 6.
- They'll lose money again.
- 1 R coin.
(Friendship Development Fund,
Pay 1 R coin at the information.)
Things aren't going well for them.
They lost everything.
They got the bad one
they had to avoid.
How did that happen?
- Out of everything...
- They got unlucky.
- Why did you take the coins?
- I didn't.
Who stole our coins?
Gosh, you thieves.
- What's wrong?
- Who stole our coins?
(Who stole my coins?)
- Why would anyone do that?
- What?
- Are you serious?
- So Min.
- It wasn't me. I swear.
- Gosh, seriously.
No wonder why my bag
was moved here.
But Haha, you know how things work
on Running Man.
You shouldn't have left your bag
lying around.
Why did you say you'd keep them?
You're so sloppy.
But... This is different.
I said we should never
steal what's in each other's bag.
- We all are carrying our bags.
- Exactly.
Why did you leave it
when everyone else was carrying it?
- What were you thinking?
- Who did it?
- You practically give it away.
- Fine.
- You're so bold.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Mi Joo.
- He lost his coins?
- Well...
(Why bother talking?)
Hey, give me back my phone.
(Hey, give me back my phone.)
You mean jerks!
Give me back my phone.
(They steal everything
when you let your guard down.)
How could you steal my phone?
Who did that?
Director, is this reasonable?
How could anyone steal my phone?
Haha, this is a good thing.
Call your phone now. The one
whose phone rings is the thief.
- Right? I'll call your phone.
- You're right. Let's try that.
Let's make it clear. This is theft.
This is theft. It's theft.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Everyone...
Everyone, be quiet.
My phone is here.
- Is it on vibrate mode?
- Who took it? Call his phone.
- Hello?
- That's my phone.
Hello?
- Hello? We found the thief.
- Who is this?
- Hey, the thief is right here.
- We found the thief.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Who is this?
- Haha.
- Isn't that Haha's phone?
- Oh, this wasn't my phone.
- You had it.
- Tae Hyun, I liked you so much.
I can't believe you!
You should be careful.
(Tae Hyun helped him become
more alert.)
Be careful.
You must look after your belongings.
Seriously.
(Meanwhile, Yeon Jun works hard
with product placement.)
(He pours the sauce...)
(and mixes the sauce well.)
The noodles are ready.
- Really?
- Let's go and eat them.
- Yeon Jun.
- They look delicious.
The smell is incredible.
The smell drives me crazy.
It's good to see
the whole family eating together.
Seriously.
It's really spicy.
It's really chewy.
- It's spicy in a tasty way.
- That's right.
Who took it?
(Who took it?)
(His bag disappeared.)
(Only the strap is dangling.)
You guys are too much!
(You guys are too much!)
He was wearing a seat belt.
(The seat belt couldn't protect
his bag.)
He was wearing a seat belt.
- Only the strap remained.
- That's so funny.
That's so funny.
I was wearing it like this.
(They are learning the importance
of keeping the items close.)
This show...
Someone with that technique
should go to jail!
That technique doesn't belong
to a celebrity!
- It's here.
- The R coins...
Bring my R coins.
It's here.
Look inside the bag.
He lost everything.
For goodness' sake.
(The old thieves became dirt poor.)
Hold on. My right kidney...
Come on.
(When you are on Running Man,
look after your own body.)
I feel like something is missing.
That was so funny.
Listen.
While the matter
doesn't concern my team,
the two of them lost everything.
Seriously.
To tell you the truth...
Do you know how sad it was?
I stood for five minutes...
with nothing but the strap
around my body.
I am serious.
This is too much.
(While everyone was enjoying
the noodles)
That's right.
Did you take it?
- It's tasty.
- I like it.
It's tasty.
- My goodness.
- Seriously.
It's tasty.
I know.
It's spicy,
but I can't stop eating it.
(He finished removing the bag
from the strap.)
(While committed the perfect crime,)
(he focused on Ji Hyo's bag
without a clue.)
Suk Jin.
(Then he took a sip of coffee
while feeling proud of himself.)
This is so annoying.
I am sorry, but something like this
has always happened.
- You should be more careful.
- Okay.
- You know,
- Look after your items.
it was the 1st time in 10 years
to have nothing but the strap.
(Always keep your bag on the front.)
I have never seen
this kind of technique before.
I saw him from afar...
and thought,
"Why is he wearing a seat belt?"
- That was so funny.
- It was the first time.
Let's resume. All right.
I will get back at those thieves.
- Let's go.
- It needs to be three or higher.
It needs to be three or higher.
- There you go.
- Any number is fine.
That team always gets good numbers.
- Just don't get one.
- They always get good numbers.
- There you go.
- The deserted island. That's good.
We are done.
- We are done, right?
- Let's finalize this.
All right.
(Team Green gets a mustache
on the deserted island.)
Everyone is wearing the bag
on the front.
Did you lose everything?
(Look over there.)
That's so funny.
(The owner of the bag
is preoccupied.)
(The thought of getting some R coins
makes him excited.)
Are you looking for these?
(They are here.)
I took them out just in case.
(Huening Kai took out the R coins.)
There is nothing in the bag.
(Suk Jin's heart beats fast
for no reason.)
Are you making fun of me?
It's not like that.
I left it on the floor
to find the thief.
Suk Jin, you are too much.
I should have known.
The yellow pouch caught my eyes,
but it was empty.
What he said was so funny.
- "Are you looking for these?"
(Even the 19-year-old boy knows
how scary it is at Running Man.)
We will get the results now.
Okay.
(The final rankings
of R-Blue Marble)
The results are out.
- The team in the first place...
- It must be Team Green.
- The 1st place gets 30 R coins.
- This team gets 30 R coins.
Dong Geun, Dong Min,
Se Chan, and Ji Hyo.
(Team Green places 1st
with 4,220 dollars.)
We made over 2,000 dollars.
30 R coins.
- 30 R coins?
- Yes.
We need to divide them. Come here.
In second place are
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo,
Yeon Jun, and Huening Kai.
The 3rd place gets 20 R coins.
Before we move on to
the final mission,
we will share the current status
regarding the penalty badges.
In the first place...
(1st place)
is a member
with three penalty badges.
- That's not a lot.
- Three.
- 3 penalty badges are a lot.
- That means 9 R coins got spent.
That's right. Someone bought
3 penalty badges with 9 R coins.
Three penalty badges.
Then there are 2 members
with 2 penalty badges.
They are the candidates
for the penalty.
I need proof to...
For the final mission,
we will play the Escape Room Game.
It will be fun!
You can rearrange your group
for this game.
Please decide on the team now.
Okay. Shall we play the game
with So Min and Mi Joo?
- Let's go!
- Okay.
Play with Dong Min and Haha.
All right.
(Dong Min and Dong Geun rescue
Suk Jin and Haha.)
All right.
Shall we play the game together?
Okay, okay.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo
get left behind.)
I am sorry,
but if Ji Hyo and I play
by ourselves,
we won't be able to escape
even after 10 hours.
They won't be able to escape.
We will need to use English letters.
- Let's move.
- Okay.
(They set out to play
the Escape Room Game.)
- The R coins...
- Let me check how many I have.
My goodness.
- What?
- It was so scary.
I don't have any left.
Hey.
(They didn't expect to be leading.)
Let's use our coins.
Kwang Soo,
whose name will you write?
Tae Hyun.
That's a good idea.
Okay? Nine R coins.
Se Chan.
Two for Se Chan.
(Glancing over)
(Kwang Soo has other plans.)
(He is writing down
Jae Suk's name.)
(He puts 2 penalty badges
under Jae Suk's name.)
Thank you.
(Thus, Jae Suk has 4 badges
and Kwang Soo has 3 badges.)
You can pay one coin and see
how many badges you have, right?
- Let's check.
- Okay.
Let's check.
(Tae Hyun has 5 penalty badges.)
(Look at this.)
Did you get the result? Let's see.
How many R coins did they use on me?
- I guess he has penalty badges.
- I know.
Right?
Hey.
I think it's Kwang Soo's doing.
That caught me by surprise.
(I let down my guard for a second.)
- All right.
- You need to attack.
Otherwise, you will get the penalty.
Someone will get the penalty.
(They became the 4 strong candidates
for a penalty.)
We should finish Tae Hyun off.
This won't do.
Let's finish Tae Hyun off.
The final race
of the Friendship Awards is...
Shoot for the Grand Prize.
You will play the Escape Room Game
and receive R coins...
- in the order of escape.
- Okay, okay.
If you need a hint in the room,
you can buy it with two coins.
- The R coins?
- That's nice.
You can purchase and check
the penalty badges...
until you arrive
at the final location.
Ji Hyo, do you know
what our best option is?
We won't be able to finish first
anyway.
Do you know what our best option is?
- We hang in there.
- That's right. Let's make sure...
we use as few R coins as possible.
- Okay.
- That would be our best option.
Otherwise, we will waste R coins
and fail to place first.
We might end up escaping next week.
Would that be okay?
- Next week?
- Yes.
That would be okay.
Of course.
We arrived at the location.
- Do you see the blindfold?
- Yes.
Please put it on.
- Now?
- Yes.
Put it on.
(They must wear a blindfold
for the Escape Room Game.)
(Glancing over)
(Jae Suk glances over
at blindfolded Kwang Soo.)
(Then his eyes move to the bag.)
For goodness' sake.
(The war of nerves began.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Come on.
- Let's put on the blindfold.
- Let's not do this.
How am I supposed to cover my eyes
when Kwang Soo is on the team?
- My eyes are covered.
- I am scared.
I am nervous.
We can do it, Ji Hyo.
(They are ready
for the Escape Room Game.)
(The place where they took off
their blindfolds is...)
- That startled me.
- I feel dizzy.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I am scared.
What is going on?
It's a horror theme.
- I am scared.
- You said it won't be scary.
(The atmosphere is tense
in the cramped room.)
(Nervous and anxious)
- You said it won't be scary.
- Is it a horror theme?
Please wait. I am receiving a call.
Where are you going?
It's a horror theme. Look at this.
Look at this. He will lock us in.
(Screaming)
(Closing shut)
Hey!
(Making a fuss)
For goodness' sake!
(Jae Suk, Kwang Soo,
So Min, and Mi Joo's room)
(The story takes place
at a doll maker's studio.)
(The cowards of Running Man...)
(got stranded
in a doll-making studio.)
(You will become beautiful.)
(The locked room is filled
with dolls and photos.)
(To escape,
you must open all the locks.)
- Hold on.
- What is this?
My goodness.
Do we need to escape from this room?
What do we do?
- We need to find the clues.
- Hold on.
- "You will become beautiful."
- We need to find the clues.
They said the theme isn't horror.
I can't deal with the horror.
That's it, right?
Nothing scary will happen, right?
(Rattling)
- For goodness' sake.
- That startled me.
Be quiet, okay?
- Gosh.
- Be quiet, okay?
Why did it fall?
It just fell on its own...
due to the magnet.
For goodness' sake.
We need to solve this first.
- We need to solve this first.
- Look at this.
Here it is.
"You will become beautiful."
- Hold on.
(It's the same sentence
that is written on the iron gate.)
Hold on. The missing letters are
ieung, ieung,
- Rieul...
- Ieung, and rieul.
(Do the missing letters give
a hint?)
- Ieung and i.
Giyeok.
What does this mean?
(Rieul, ieung, i, and giyeok)
Do they correspond
with the alphabet letters?
The alphabet letters?
How does that work?
- Like this.
- Eric?
- Hold on.
- Do they spell "Eric"?
Rieul.
- Ieung.
- I...
(Screaming)
I can't do this.
Stop it!
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo disappeared
with a shout.)
Kwang Soo.
- I...
- Stop collapsing to the floor!
Go on without me.
I can't do this.
I don't think I can do this.
A, ya, eo, yeo, o, yo...
- What could this mean?
- This must mean seven.
I don't know
what the other letters mean.
(Rieul, ieung, i, and giyeok)
(The answer is 2017,
the number that looks the same.)
(So Min got 7,
but she can't get the rest.)
- Come on.
- 2, 7...
- Try 2017.
- 2017. 2017.
2017.
- It worked!
- All right!
- It worked, Jae Suk.
- Is it 2017?
So Min is so funny.
Despite being over the place,
she is really bad at this.
- Seriously.
- What is she doing?
- She isn't good at this.
I gave you all the hints.
You said you love
the Escape Room Game.
I gave you all the hints.
I mean...
You didn't solve anything.
- Hold on.
- You just shouted.
But this... What do we do with this?
When will it fall?
(Meanwhile,
Ji Hyo and Se Chan's room)
(It's the museum-themed room
for beginners.)
(When you go out the first door,)
(three more rooms exist.)
(You need to go back and forth)
(and exchange fake items
with genuine items.)
I see.
(They enter the first room.)
Is it over if we escape this room?
That sounds easy.
(Of course not.)
(Dazed)
We began, Ji Hyo.
Did we begin?
We need to find the clues.
There will be things here.
We need to open the doors.
(He keeps stating the obvious.)
We need to open this lock.
Will that lead us to the door?
Once we open it,
we will find something.
I think I will be
the brain of the team.
You?
You haven't done anything.
There could be a hint here.
Look at this.
(If you look at the exit sign
above the door,)
(you can clearly see
the number 117.)
(You just need to enter the number
into the keypad.)
(Difficulty level: Very easy)
(They just need to see
the exit sign.)
This is so annoying.
(At that moment)
(117 is clearly visible.)
(He passes by it.)
Are we doing this right?
(What?)
Se Chan, this is fun.
We aren't solving anything!
This isn't fun at all.
I think this is fun.
It's so fascinating.
- Let's think.
- This is comb-pattern pottery.
This is "Principles and Practice
of Eastern Medicine".
Who wrote it?
- Heo Jun.
- Heo Jun, right?
How old is Heo Jun?
Do you know his birthday?
- His birthday?
- Yes.
I don't even know how old he is.
How would I know his birthday?
(I don't know
when Heo Jun's birthday is.)
Heo Jun... Hold on.
"Heo Jun" was an MBC drama
that aired on channel 11.
Hey.
You went too far.
(They think about everything
they know about Heo Jun.)
(After struggling with Heo Jun,)
(they purchase their 1st hint
with 2 R coins.)
"If you look at the exit sign,
you will see a number."
- 1117.
What?
- What?
- That startled me.
Are we done?
Oh, this is the beginning.
Ji Hyo, this is the beginning.
This is the beginning.
This is so much fun.
(There are many rooms
they need to escape from.)
What is this? There is a box.
This is driving me crazy.
It's from Jin Beom.
Let's open it.
(The parcel from Jin Beom
contains a hint for the next room.)
(Jin Beom)
(They have already seen
Jin Beom's phone number.)
(Jin Beom's phone number
is the password.)
(However,)
(they are opening the parcel.)
(They get a cushion
that has no meaning whatsoever.)
What is this?
Are we being fooled?
There are English words on it.
They might be a hint.
(They forget about the parcel...)
(with Jin Beom's name.)
- This is it.
- Guys.
Let's do this. Happy Cookie.
Let's go.
This must be the first hint.
Except for One Cake...
One Cake.
Except for One Cake,
everything is sold out.
One Cake.
"One Cake" must hold a key.
Then there is an arrow...
that is coming out of "One Cake".
This picture means something.
It's in English.
(The 5-letter lock
has the same cake picture.)
The poster has the same picture.
They must be connected.
This picture means something.
"Ok new cat keep"
doesn't make sense.
(Except for One Cake,
everything is sold out.)
Hey, look at this.
- Hey.
- What?
One Cake.
- Right?
- You are right.
One Cake.
If we remove the letters,
we get K, W, T, E, and P.
Try the lock.
K, W, T, E, and P.
- This is incredible.
- Try the lock.
- You are right.
- K.
- W.
- T.
- It worked.
- Did it work?
- Okay.
- My goodness.
- That was incredible.
- We did it.
We did it.
- Take it out.
- Look at this.
(They passed the 1st stage
in less than 5 minutes.)
(They make a good team.)
All right.
We will be done in no time.
Hey.
Had I been here alone,
I would have gotten stuck.
In that case,
I don't need to help.
- I will just write the names.
- Try it.
(Tae Hyun decided what to do
in 5 minutes.)
- This is R.
- You are right.
R, A.
Three...
(He writes names on the coins
with his back to the members.)
(He writes Kwang Soo endlessly.)
Hold on. Let's do this again.
This is wrong.
They are so smart.
H and U.
(Kwang Soo, So Min,
Kwang Soo, So Min)
(Tae Hyun makes the penalty badges
like a factory worker.)
We need to go out this way.
That's the next step, right?
From here...
I feel dizzy.
I am not that brave.
You are braver than us.
- I feel dizzy.
- Me too.
(Jae Suk looks
particularly brave among them.)
- Where was it?
- Hold on.
"The scent of moth balls
and bleach pierced the nose."
"The restroom seemed to be empty."
"That was when I felt
a sense of presence."
"A feeling of unease
took over my body."
Shouldn't we work on the lock?
- That could be it.
- Hold on.
The lock...
Hey!
- Open the door!
- Hey!
Open the door!
- Open the door!
- We need to look at that.
(Kwang Soo was trying
to steal from So Min.)
Hey!
Who turned off the light?
So Min, why did you turn off
the light?
You should pull it.
I am stepping out.
I will look for more clues.
- Gosh! Gosh!
- What is it?
I will look for more clues.
(She freaks out
after stepping on the cloth.)
That startled me.
(Didn't So Min say that she likes
the Escape Room Game?)
- Gosh.
- That startled me.
There is something here.
(Jae Suk and kids, 35 percent done,
Jong Kook and kids, 30 percent done)
(Ji Hyo and kids, 2 percent done,
Dong Geun and kids, 45 percent done)
We need to take a look
at everything...
inside the room.
1, 0... You see this
on the top, right?
- It's open.
- It was written backward.
(Opening)
- It's open.
I did it. I solved it.
- What? How did you do it?
- No way.
What did you do?
We are moving fast
since a genius is on our team.
What do I do?
(This team is showing the suspense
of the Escape Room Game.)
(They are still fixed
on the cushion.)
My goodness.
- What?
- I tried to get it over there.
You know,
we are thinking about
breaking things, not deducing.
(They give up and try to leave.)
Do you know what's funny?
(Beeping)
What?
(The door got locked.)
It's locked.
(They continue to play
the Locked in the Room Game.)
Please...
Please open the door for us.
Hey!
We will get angry.
(Angry)
We are sorry.
(They plead
with the production crew.)
We did everything we can.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan
looked back on their lives.)
(49 minutes have passed.)
My goodness.
(It sounds like
a team managed to escape!)
Seriously.
- We did it.
- Yes!
(Suk Jin and the kids
managed to escape.)
- Gosh.
- We finished first.
We did it.
We finished first.
We are the best.
- We are the best.
- We are so cool.
Did we finish first?
- We did it.
- That's right.
- How many?
- You get 30 R coins per team.
(30 R coins per team)
This is good.
Let's move.
Zero...
(Team Cowards
heard the other team cheer.)
(So Min, the professional escapist,
feels bad.)
(They finish 2nd.)
- My goodness.
- It was so scary.
We still finished second.
Second! Get the flag.
Two teams haven't finished yet.
- We took too much time.
- It seems that way.
- We came out too late.
- Okay. We finished third.
- We finished third.
- That's too bad.
That's too bad.
(Tae Hyun places 1st
in terms of badge production.)
We can't do anything!
We can't escape!
This is the worst game!
I would rather get...
the water bomb.
(I would rather get
the water bomb.)
I would rather get the paint bomb.
(While Se Chan is crying)
Everyone,
the last team is taking a while.
Let's move on.
When will they come?
- They won't be able to escape.
- What's going on?
- We opened the door.
- Really?
The two of them...
solved one puzzle.
Really?
They solved one puzzle.
We will show the prizes first.
Prizes.
(The prizes will be revealed first.)
The first place gets
the Friendship gold rings.
The second place gets
the Korean pork set.
The third place gets
the vitamin gift set.
We actually didn't total
Se Chan and Ji Hyo's coins yet.
But we don't think they are
in the top ranking anyway.
- They're not.
- Should we wait for them?
- We can go home, right?
- Yes.
Hey...
- Oh, my.
- Did you come?
I almost died from stress.
- Did you take it?
- We...
We only solved one question
after getting a hint from the coins.
We went to a doll and talked to it.
We talked to the doll.
We were saying that the door would
open if we pressed the doll's eyes.
We were shining the flashlight
all day like this.
Nothing happened.
Did you come?
Are you done?
Okay, this is third place.
(We will start by announcing
3rd place right away.)
- Huening Kai and Yeon Jun.
- Oh, my.
- Gosh.
- You're in third place?
- They have 73 coins.
- Didn't you only win a little?
The Korean pork set for second place
is for Jeon So Min and Mi Joo.
- What happened?
- I can't believe it.
- They have 79 coins.
I can't believe it.
The long-awaited first place has...
- a whopping number of 85 coins.
- Of course.
They are Yang Dong Geun
and Jang Dong Min.
(Yang Dong Geun
and Jang Dong Min have 85 coins.)
We did it.
(They won the Grand Award of
the 1st Friendship Award.)
- Look at Suk Jin.
- That's amazing.
Dong Min, we were on the same team.
There are three people
who will receive a penalty today.
- Yes.
- The penalty.
- I only have to avoid this.
- Please...
I don't think we'll get it.
They have a total of 53 badges.
- No way.
- 53 badges?
- That's amazing.
- That happened.
- Do they have 53 badges?
- Yes, badges.
- How many coins did they use?
- That's 180 coins.
1st place has 20 badges.
(1st place has 20 penalty badges.)
- It's Lee Kwang Soo.
- Really?
Me? Why?
(Kwang Soo who received love
equally...)
(from the youngest to the oldest
is 1st place from behind.)
60 coins? Do people have
a grudge against him?
Next.
Jeon So Min is in 2nd place
with 14 badges.
- Me?
- Oh, my.
Why me? I did my best today.
- Why Jeon So Min?
- Why me?
- I gave them to her.
- Why?
Why me?
I wrote your name
on all of the badges.
Why me? Tae Hyun...
- Third place is...
- Why me?
He wrote your name on all of them.
For 3rd place, 1 person got 8
and 1 person got 7.
The person who got seven
won't receive the penalty.
- It's either me or Tae Hyun.
- It's you or Tae Hyun.
- If so...
- It's either me or Tae Hyun.
That's right.
It's 1 between the 2 of you.
It's either me or Tae Hyun.
The 3rd place who will receive
the penalty with 8 badges is...
- It's Tae Hyun.
- It might not be me?
(Is it Tae Hyun who made
indiscriminate attacks...)
(or Jae Suk who was
even killed by his team members?)
Eight badges.
It's Cha Tae Hyun.
(Cha Tae Hyun will
receive the penalty.)
- In the end...
- It's Cha Tae Hyun.
- I thought it was me.
(It was still an amazing match.)
- This is unbelievable.
- This is really unbelievable.
- Jae Suk...
How many did you write
for Jae Suk?
- This is really unbelievable.
- That's right.
- I can't believe it.
- It was close.
- The penalty is...
- We have to eat something.
(Kwang Soo, So Min,
and Tae Hyun's penalty is...)
- the Vinegar Friendship game.
- Gosh.
The 3 of you only have
to share drinking 1L of vinegar.
- That's nice.
- Seriously.
A lot of children watch
this program, right?
I would like to make
a public apology.
(A public apology?)
Ji Suk Jin's bag...
- Was it you?
(He revealed the truth of the seat
belt incident with his own words.)
- I...
- He's a professional.
did it for entertainment.
- Yes, you must apologize for it.
- But...
- you completely fooled us.
- I must have...
lost my mind for a moment.
I will also make a public apology.
- Why?
- You shouldn't do it.
- Whose is it?
Is it Haha's?
(She bows to Haha.)
You're the worst.
- Wait, what about Ji Hyo's?
- What about mine?
- Who stole Ji Hyo's?
- Who did it?
(I'm sorry.)
It's him.
(They went round and round.)
- Everyone...
- Earlier, I saw that...
I had fun here.
I hope this never happens again
on Running Man.
- We won't do it again.
- No.
1st place and 2nd place are
meaningless.
It's a friendship game.
We should drink a moderate amount.
- The smell is...
- Is it okay?
(She unexpectedly drinks a lot to
set an example to children.)
- It will make your stomach hurt.
- Your stomach will ache.
(You shudder since the taste feels
like it will make you healthy.)
- Is it that bad?
- That's too bad.
- What did I do to deserve this?
- Okay.
Okay, let's drink
a little bit for him.
Let's drink it for him.
(Among peaceful residents,)
(there's something that will
disturb peace.)
(If you want to survive,)
(run away right now.)
(Running Man: Sweet Home)