- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hi.
(Feeling fresh for the spring)
I asked you to put on a freshman's outfit.
- Yes. - Do you feel like freshmen?
- Not that much. - Well...
- It's... - What's up with Haha?
- I... - Isn't that for a night guest?
(Looking dark)
- Isn't he a returning student? - Our outfits are so different.
I think my stylist put some effort into this.
You dressed like an IT specialist.
- At the Electronics Market... - By the way,
Seok Jin doesn't look like a freshman though.
Why not? This is how they dress.
- What? - He just put on whatever was there.
This checkered pattern is a given.
- You just look like... - Freshmen wear checkered shirts.
an old man who can't dress well.
(You just look like an old man who can't dress well.)
- Hey, you. - But you are indeed my role model.
- The role model of the year. - Look who's talking.
By the way, everyone's outfit is awful.
- So Min looks like a freshman. - The jacket from the department.
- She looks like a college student. - She looks like a freshman.
(The jacket from the department completes the freshman outfit.)
In my opinion, So Min's fashion is that of...
a clueless senior student who tagged along to the orientation.
Just that thought is suffocating.
- She thought about the old times. - Yes, she looks like a senior.
- She wanted to look young. - Right.
- She works at a company now. - The department jacket...
She came here on her weekend.
- Manager Jeon. - She took a half-day off.
- She's Manager Jeon. - She took a half-day off...
and came to the orientation.
And he became a successful thug.
(He made it in the dark world early in his age.)
(The big brother of the dark world, Kook)
- Right. - There are people like him.
- That's right. - This kind of people does exist.
There's a major for Physical Fitness.
- Physical Fitness? - I chose Physical Fitness.
He opened up a billiard club in front of college.
- Billiard club? Okay, okay. - He's a successful owner.
- He opened a billiard club. - A billiard club.
We plan to hold an orientation for the freshmen...
- to celebrate the spring. - Orientation.
- That sounds fun. - It's the orientation.
- I've never been to one. - Really?
- No, never. - We will start...
the orientation right away.
Please take a look at your schedule today.
- There's a schedule? - Please hold your orientation...
- according to the schedule. - We're starting.
That's the schedule for the orientation.
We took this schedule from a real orientation of a college.
- Really? - Yes.
- This is the recent one. - "Lunch".
- "Lunch". - I'm looking forward to it.
- "Introduction". - "Recreational activities".
We are all freshmen today.
Kwang Soo, you entered college in 2019.
- Yes. - Please introduce yourself.
Hello, guys.
(Nice to meet you.)
Don't be so casual.
(I had to take the college entrance exam again.)
Right. How old are you?
- We just started our school year. - We don't know each other.
- Some are older than us. - Everyone here had their fun.
I just said one line. "Hello, guys."
- How could you... - You should realize...
- you shouldn't call them "guys". - Okay, okay.
- Okay. - All right.
- Hello, everyone. - Okay.
I'm Lee Kwang Soo. I'm a freshman.
You sound so weak.
Let's pour some oil onto one spoonful of your passion.
(Complaining about his passion)
(Chanting a slogan)
(Hello, everyone.)
Hello, everyone.
(He came for an orientation, but he sounds like he's enlisting.)
I entered college in 2019. My name is Lee Kwang Soo.
As I'm shy, I didn't have a chance to talk in front of a group.
He said he's shy.
(Laughing)
My goal for this year is...
Face forward and scream for three seconds.
What is this place?
(Screaming)
Are we in the army or what?
Seriously. I could hear the echo.
Okay. I got it. Let's give it up for him.
I hope we get along.
- Why don't you introduce yourself? - Se Chan.
Out of my way.
Hello. I'm a freshman who entered college in 2019.
What's up with his face?
I'm Yang Se Chan.
- He's so ugly. - I'm Yang Se Chan.
- He's really a freshman? - He's really a freshman?
Actually, I've never been to an orientation. It's my first one.
Show me your special talent.
- Can you show us a special talent. - Show us your special talent.
Special talent? Okay.
I do this a lot on "Comedy Big League".
- Yes, do one for us. - I love that show.
- Okay. - What is it?
- Do you know this guy named Greg? - Yes.
- This black guy sings soulfully. - Is that so?
(This is the black soul of Greg.)
(Greg can express Korean rhythm and blues better than Koreans.)
(Because I love you)
(Skipping a beat)
(Singing the song a beat later with vibrato is the key point.)
- This black guy sings soulfully. - Is that so?
I will impersonate him and sing "I Miss You".
- I know him. I know Greg. - Do that for us. I know Greg.
- I know Greg. - He's a great singer.
He's a great singer.
(The memories of my deep love for you)
(And those days)
(The skipping-the-beat method makes him sound like Greg.)
He's good.
(I can't use my love as an excuse)
(to hold you here)
(The female students find his singing...)
(hilarious.)
Hold you here
(He's killing it at the orientation.)
- That's Greg. - Good job.
- I love this kind of acts. - This is my impersonation of him.
- Okay, great. Go back to your spot. - Okay.
- Welcome. - Thank you.
- That's totally my kind of act. - That was great.
Hey, friend.
I learned that I'm supposed to do this at orientation.
Do what?
I'll start now!
Democracy to Running Man! Entertainment on TV!
(This is an outdated method of introduction.)
- What is she doing? - I'm a future star!
20191756.
- Hold on. Wait. - I'm Jeon So Min.
- This isn't going to air. - Accept my energetic greetings!
- What are you doing? - Hey.
Show me your acceptance letter.
- What? - You didn't get accepted, right?
I did get accepted.
- Stop lying! - Do your introduction again.
Okay, then. Hello, guys.
(Sounding like a freshman)
I entered college this year. I'm Jeon So Min.
I really want to go on a lot of group dates.
- Do you have a boyfriend? - No, I don't.
She's a bit over-the-top.
- She really wants blind dates. - Where did you go to school?
She's too much.
- Why would she say that now? - Exactly.
Ever since I was in high school,
I wanted to date a student in the upper grade.
Dating someone from my school is my dream.
That means it's Seok Jin.
- What do you think about me? - No.
I don't want a returning student. I want a student in an upper grade.
- I want a senior student. - What?
- A student in a grade above mine. - I'm not a returning student.
Do you think he'd keep coming back for 20 years?
- What are you talking about? - I'm not a returning student.
This is like "Whispering Corridors".
Anyway, like your dream, I wish you'd meet someone great.
- Thank you. - Okay.
(Date someone from the school.)
- You're next. - Okay.
(The big brother of the dark world is next.)
Guys.
(Exuding a dark presence)
- I can tell he'll be the boss. - He's scary.
He'll be the boss.
This is what I can do for you guys.
If students from another school come at us,
- I can stop them. - I feel so reassured.
- Why would college students... - We're in college.
- have group fights? - We don't do that here.
Really? College students don't fight?
- We don't fight. - Listen.
- It happened in my high school. - That doesn't happen at college.
- There are no group fights... - People don't fight at college?
- at college. - Why did he kill the mood?
What? What did you say?
I wasn't talking to you, sir.
(Acting scared)
- He's in our grade. - He's in the same grade.
- Why did you talk to him like that? - Hey, he's in the same grade.
- We're the same age too? - Anyway,
I'm good-natured.
I'm cheerful too.
Let's get along well.
Anyway, let's give it up for him.
- Welcome. - Come back to your spot.
He's next. Here he is.
- All right. - Okay.
Everyone.
- You all think I'm old. - Yes.
But I was born in the early year of 1999.
(He makes a shocking statement.)
- What? - That's why...
Do you mean, 1899?
(I get it!)
Doesn't that mean he's a mummy?
(This mysterious student, Seok Jin, has been showing for 121 years.)
- 1999? - 1899.
It's 1999.
(He turns out to be a dinosaur student.)
- He looks young if it's 1899. - He does look young.
(He looks like a 54-year-old guy.)
- Goodness. It's hilarious. - It's so funny.
- Why don't you go next, Ji Hyo? - It's so funny.
Do a brief introduction.
- She's pretty. - She is indeed.
She's pretty.
Hello.
My name is Song Ji Hyo. I entered college this year.
She put on makeup.
(She catches their attention.)
I wanted to look pretty today. I even got a haircut.
Ji Hyo, you look very tired today.
Yes, I'm tired.
I think I've been standing up for too long.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Which introduction tired you out the most?
The one before mine.
(It's the one before hers. It means it's Seok Jin's.)
I was really shocked.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend now.
I thought so.
(A mean remark of a 54-year-old guy)
(My gosh...)
Seriously.
Let's give it up for her.
Thank you.
- She's pretty. - Great.
- She's pretty. - Next.
(Here comes the hipster of Running University.)
- He already looks pretentious. - My gosh.
- He already looks pretentious. - His outfit...
(Fixing his front hair to intensify his hipster sentiment)
He's acting pretentious.
(This is the comment of his impression.)
(Sighing)
(I didn't mean to say it out loud.)
- What's up with your hair? - I'm sorry.
Let's not get on each other's bad side.
(Acting like a jerk for the 2nd time)
Unbelievable.
- Should I handle him? - That little jerk.
- My gosh, that guy. - Hey.
You should take care of him. I can't stand him.
Anyway, let's not get on each other's bad side.
Let's get along well.
Why don't you rap for us?
Sure.
(Responding to it right away)
- That was good. - Is that a freestyle rap?
- Give him a theme. - He's pretty good.
- Rap for us. - Okay.
Nothing ever stops me.
- My gosh, he's good. - Okay, then.
Give me a theme.
- Orientation. - Orientation.
(The theme of the freestyle rap is the orientation.)
OT
Your face
A fly in the ointment
(Your face, a fly in the ointment)
- Is this it? - That looks so cheap.
I won.
What did he win?
- What did he win? - OT.
- Come back in. Clap for him. - Thank you.
- Your hair is great. - Welcome.
- Welcome. - He's unique.
- He's not like the others. - You're so cool.
- His hair is cool. - Welcome.
- I have a list of new freshmen. - There's more?
We have more freshmen.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
- Other students are joining us. - What is this?
- We have more freshmen. - We do?
All right.
This student.
This student used to be in a group.
(If the student used to be in a group...)
Does that mean the student is a singer?
- This student used to be a member. - Is it an idol singer?
(Who is this mysterious freshman?)
Hey!
She made her debut 13 years ago. It's Hong Jin Young.
- It's Jin Young. - Jin Young.
(Welcome back to Running Man. She's the 9th member of the show.)
(This passionate freshman comes with a thumbs-up.)
Hello, I entered college this year. I'm Jin Young. I major in trot.
- You're majoring in trot. - Nice to meet you.
She only looked at the camera, not us.
- You're majoring in trot. - Yes.
I want to be a singer...
this year,
and my first full-length album happen to come out this year.
- Your full-length album? - Yes.
This is your first full-length album.
- This is your 1st? - Yes, it's my 1st one.
- You made your debut a long ago. - Then...
Then will your 2nd full-length album come out after 10 years?
(It took 13 years for the 1st one to come out.)
I didn't know it either.
- That's impressive. - This is my first one.
- You only released singles then. - Yes.
By the way,
I saw her for the first time...
in a show called "Cider".
It's not airing anymore. It was a KBS program.
- That's right. - She acted on the show.
- She acted on the show. - For the skits?
I remember thinking that she was really good at acting then.
- You did a great job with it. - Thank you.
I was Anna in "Anna's Mistake".
- "Anna's Mistake" . - Yes.
- "Anna's Mistake"? - You were Anna?
- Really? - She was Anna.
- I know the show. - You do? You know me?
- "Anna's Mistake". - You were Anna?
- Jin Young was Anna. - Really?
My face did change slightly compared to before.
- Right? - Yes.
- No, no. - I am that Anna.
- I know that show. - That's right.
Since we talked a lot about this,
they'll definitely air the footage.
They'll air the footage.
By the way, Anna...
(We will summon...)
(Anna we liked back in the days.)
- Anna, what are you doing? - I'm curious.
Mr. Heat.
I'm "kimming" up.
(Anna with off-the-wall charms was Jin Young from her early days.)
- I found out that it was Jin Young. - Right.
All right. Jin Young is joining us today.
Okay. She's majoring in trot.
I'll bring in the next student.
I'll tell you after I bring the student in.
All right. Come on out.
(This mysterious freshman is joining them late.)
(Who is this student?)
(The rookie of the film industry, Keum Sae Rok)
- Keum Sae Rok. - Keum Sae Rok.
Can I introduce myself a bit more?
You don't need to...
(Rapping)
(This pretty actress has an unusual and unexpected swag.)
(She was in "Believer" and "The Fiery Priest".)
(She's a rising star the film industry is keeping its eyes on.)
Hello.
I'm a fresh newbie of Running Man. I'm Keum Sae Rok.
(I'm a fresh newbie of Running Man. I'm Keum Sae Rok.)
- A fresh newbie. - A fresh newbie.
She's so fresh.
She's like a real freshman.
- She's a real freshman. - I can feel that vibe from her.
- She's elegant too. - This is her first time here.
- In that sense, she's a freshman. - That's right.
(Freshman of Running Man, Sae Rok.)
I'll have fun today.
- No, you must entertain us. - Okay.
(He corrects her mindset.)
- You're so cold-hearted. - My goodness.
- The leader is honest. - That was too mean.
- Our leader is honest. - What's wrong with you?
It's important that you have fun today, but you must...
- entertain the viewers too. - That's right.
- That's our request. - Okay.
Is there a variety show you like?
- Running Man. - Except for our program.
- Haha and I... - Okay.
live in the same neighborhood.
- I'm also the guardian... - Do you live in Mapo-gu.
- of Mapo-gu. - I'm the sheriff of Mapo-gu.
- Are you the guardian? - Bang, bang, bang.
- Bang. - I'm also the sheriff.
- You're the sheriff too. - Yes.
- She lives in Mapo-gu too. - I live in Mapo-gu too.
She's the guardian of Mapo-gu.
(Sae Rok is the guardian of Mapo-gu.)
- He's the sheriff of Mapo-gu. - I'm the sheriff.
What about you?
- She just lives there. - I live in Mapo-gu.
- I see. - She's a civilian.
I just live in Mapo-gu.
- Ji Hyo lives in Mapo-gu. - She is the resident there.
She's a resident.
- Great. - I didn't know.
I will bring in the last freshman after Sae Rok.
Let me tell you about this student.
We're very familiar with this student,
but I bet you've never heard of the name.
- Who is it? - All right.
- This student... - We might not recognize the name?
- We've never heard of the name? - Just like the name...
(Who is this mysterious freshman that puzzles the members?)
(The first queen of Drama Department)
My goodness, my goodness.
Hello.
(She's a pretty and tall actress that never fails the viewers.)
(It turns out she's a dancing queen.)
(The queen of excitement)
- My goodness. - Hello.
My goodness.
(The actress who knows how to have fun is back.)
- Hello. - My gosh.
- My gosh. - We'll have so much fun today!
- It will be fun today. - And...
(They are excited.)
- Right. - I'm not sure if you know this.
She changed her name to Han Da Gam.
- Really? - She changed her name.
(She changed her name to Han Da Gam.)
She changed her name.
- It's Han Da Gam. - I saw that trending up online.
- I wanted to... - Okay.
approach the public in a more friendly and affectionate manner.
I'm trying my best.
(She maximizes her friendliness.)
She's scarier now. She's scarier.
- She's a new person. She's scary. - She's weird.
She's gotten weird.
Excuse me. We can feel...
that you're trying hard, so it makes us uncomfortable.
Hello, guys.
(Stubbornly acting friendly)
- What's up with her hand gesture? - Don't force it.
- I haven't seen this for a while. - You're making us uncomfortable.
- It was so hard to change my name. - Pardon?
- It was hard to change it. - Then why did you...
- Try to embrace my new name. - But why did you choose...
- Da Gam? - Why did you choose Da Gam?
- There are other names too. - There has to be a meaning.
Bok Soon is a friendly name too. That name could've comforted us.
- What did you say? - Bok Soon.
There are names like that.
My aunt's name is Bok Soon.
(My aunt's name is Bok Soon.)
Is that so?
- You're scaring me. - Your aunt...
- Really? - Your aunt...
- Da Gam is a great name. - Yes.
- I like the name. - It's a great name.
- The name has a nice ring to it. - People will criticize you a lot.
Kwang Soo, Do you want to have a stage name?
Well...
If I were to, is there a name that suits me?
What do you think, Da Gam?
I used to hate this name when I was young.
- Bo Gae. - How about...
- Lee Bo Gae. - Lee Bo Gae.
- That's... - Bo Gae.
- I wanted a name. - Bo Gae.
(Lee Bo Gae)
(This has to be the friendliest name ever.)
- I wanted a name. - Hey, that's great.
- What a great name. - Lee Bo Gae.
- Lee Bo Gae. - That's great.
- Lee Bo Gae. - Lee Bo Gae.
- I like Lee Bo Gae. - Lee Bo Gae.
- Unbelievable. - Bo Gae.
- Lee Bo Gae. - It's a friendly name for everyone.
- Lee Bo Gae. - When you call his name,
you must put your hands behind your back.
- Lee Bo Gae. - Lee Bo Gae.
- You should gather your hands. - Lee Bo Gae.
- Lee Bo Gae. - "Yes."
- This suits him. - Bo Gae is a nice name.
- That name suits you. - Give So Min 50 dollars.
- You really named him. - Right.
- Lee Bo Gae is a great name. - Lee Bo Gae.
Since they're joining us today,
just like I mentioned earlier,
- we'll look at their talents. - Yes.
- We showed our talents too. - Right.
What's your special talent?
I can change every song into a trot song.
- That's my special talent. - She's majoring in trot.
- My major is trot. - Is that so?
- Should I sing "Listen"? - "Listen"?
- "Listen". - "Listen".
I love this song by Beyonce.
Listen
(Beyonce's "Listen"...)
(requires the singer to move people and hit the high notes.)
(It's the song with the highest difficulty level.)
(She'll pull off this song after turning it into a trot song?)
(Listen)
That sounds so mellow.
(Mellow)
(Mellow sounds of "Listen" play all over Gapyeong.)
(Can complete)
(She demonstrates her voice vibration.)
(Impressive)
(Her magical singing of turning rhythm and blues to trot music.)
I like this version better.
- It's great. - I know.
- I like it. - This is very sentimental.
The highlight is important.
(Climax is important.)
(Here comes the part where the singing explodes.)
(Listen)
(Jin Young sings in 6 different tones.)
- It's great. - She sings so well.
(Singing hard)
(She puts pressure on her voice.)
(Vibration is the finishing stroke.)
You pushed up your shoulders so much.
She cringed a moment ago.
When you sing high notes,
you use your shoulders.
- I do? - You pushed up your shoulders.
(Is the secret to singing high notes her shoulders?)
I thought she might disappear.
(Her shoulders go up every time her voice vibrates.)
(Squeezing her shoulders is the secret to her singing.)
That's it.
The trot music version is good too.
- It was great. - It's because she's a good singer.
Sae Rok, what's your talent?
In a drama called "Marry Me Now",
- I danced to "Ring Ring". - Did you?
I danced at a congratulatory ceremony.
- Can we take a look? - I have to do it with Jin Young.
- Really? - Yes.
Let's see.
(What will her dance to "Ring Ring" look like?)
They're doing it together. They prepared it.
- This is good. - You're doing well.
- Awesome. - Good.
- Here it comes. - Let's go.
Ring Ring
1, 2, to the right.
(Let's go straight to the right.)
To the right?
(I'll be in charge of keeping this performance exciting.)
(The new sheriff shoots cute bullets.)
(She shoots again.)
(The performance is getting more exciting.)
(They dance in sync.)
("Ring Ring" sisters)
She's good.
(She's quite good.)
Start with the right.
Left.
(She imitates her twist step perfectly.)
(She's new but experienced in dancing.)
- She's a good dancer. - Gosh.
- She's good. - Here it comes.
Let's go.
(The climax of "Ring Ring" is coming.)
- Let's go. - "Ring Ring".
(Are you ready for excitement?)
(Ring Ring)
(One more time)
(I'll take care of this round, everyone.)
- She's got the groove. - Dance together, everyone.
She's a good dancer.
(Ring, ring, I'm your older sister)
(I'm the professional on stage today.)
She knows the entire dance.
(The older sister)
(We're Ring Ring sisters.)
They're good.
- She was well prepared. - She knows how to dance.
- It's obvious that she can dance. - It was good.
Da Gam, do you have any talent?
(What's Da Gam's talent?)
Everyone, I'm good at making acrostic poems.
Really?
- Making acrostic poem? - Yes.
Acrostic poems?
- How about Kim Jong Kook? - I'll try Kim Jong Kook.
- Kim Jong Kook? - Yes.
(She makes an acrostic poem with "Kim Jong Kook".)
All right, please start.
"Kim".
Does he eat salty food like kimchi?
That's good.
"Does he eat salty food like kimchi?"
- All right. - "Jong".
He exercises all day long and only eats chicken breast.
"Kook".
When will you get married?
(When will you get married?)
She made it with care.
(Her acrostic poem is complete with her concern for him.)
(Han Da Gam knows how to complete acrostic poems.)
- The last one was good. - It was surprising.
Let's give a round of applause to these three freshmen.
Welcome.
Today is Spring Orientation Special.
It's Mysterious Returning Student Race.
- What? - "Mysterious"?
Among 11 freshmen invited to the orientation,
there's someone who pretended to be a freshman.
(He bursts out laughing.)
(A returning student pretending to be a freshman?)
There's one tactless returning student.
I told you.
- Lee Bo Gae. - I told you.
Isn't it too easy?
- Isn't it too easy? - You know that it's not me.
You know that it isn't me.
You'll play a total of three rounds of orientation games.
If you catch the returning student, freshmen win.
- We must catch the student. - You'll receive prizes.
During every round,
the returning student will carry out a hidden mission.
Freshmen will listen to the hints...
and select a student whom they suspect.
If the selected student is the returning student,
your prizes will be accumulated.
If it's not, you'll be punished.
The first game will start.
Okay.
- Let's start. - Okay.
Let's do it.
(What will be the first game?)
(2019 Freshmen Orientation Schedule)
(Orientation Game 1)
We're at an orientation.
Our fellow students...
(He uses an old-fashioned word.)
- By the way... - "Fellow"?
- "Fellow"? - That's so old-fashioned.
All of us are returning students.
Our student leader is too old.
We're here together.
People play a lot of games at orientation.
It's called Insider Game these days.
That sounds good.
Insider Game? Let's play a round of I Am Ground.
- Introduce yourself? - I am ground, introduce yourself
It's been a long time.
Cave expedition.
Hotteok.
What's this? Is this cave expedition?
- Do you know it, Sae Rok? - Yes.
What is it?
Dig poop.
(Dig what? It's shocking.)
- Right. - That's right. I remember that.
That's right.
Only those who know will play. I don't know this.
- You don't know? - Give it a try.
- I am ground, introduce yourself - Start with Ji Hyo.
King Kong shower.
- Dig poop. - It's fun.
Fool.
Cave expedition.
Hotteok.
- Ground, it starts now - Start
Cave expedition. Hotteok.
(So Min calls for hotteok.)
Hotteok. Dig poop.
Dig poop. King Kong shower.
(Ji Hyo is King Kong shower.)
King Kong shower. Dig poop.
(She calls for dig poop but makes a gesture for hotteok.)
- That was hotteok. - She got it wrong.
- She got it wrong. - This isn't easy.
- Does this game still exist? - Does it?
- This is an Insider Game? - This is such an old game.
(It's a game played on "X-man" where insiders gathered 13 years ago.)
(It's one of the games enjoyed by ancient insiders.)
- When is I Am Ground from? - It's an old game.
- It's not an Insider Game, right? - It's an old game.
It's an old game.
We prepared a game called Water Seat Game.
Water Seat Game?
"Water Seat"?
(If you get penalized the least, you gain penalty exemption card.)
- We'll give you calamansi extract. - It's sour.
Those who lose drink a cup as a penalty.
- Calamansi? - Gosh.
It's an actual extract.
It's really yellow.
- The color is so bright. - Goodness.
- It's the color of mustard. - It really is.
Excuse me.
Are there substitutes?
- There should be black knights. - Yes.
I'll drink it for you.
- Black knights? - They're allowed.
You drink two cups if you get rejected.
- Jin Young, I'll do it for you. - Will you drink it?
(I'll give you a cup.)
- You have to grant him a wish. - Right.
Sae Rok, I'll drink it for you.
(He sounds so cheesy.)
Everyone. We have...
Running Man's Insider Game Collection.
Is that so?
(2019 Running Man's Insider Game Collection)
(Orange Game)
It's Orange Game.
The first player makes an imaginary small orange with hand movements.
He throws it to the next player.
- Orange, orange - Let's play Orange Game.
- It should be small at first. - It should be small.
Start. Let's start with you.
- Orange, orange, orange - Orange, orange, orange. You.
Here you go.
(He must make an orange bigger than the previous player.)
You.
(Kwang Soo points to Haha.)
(He makes an orange as big as a fist.)
(Haha points to Ji Hyo.)
(Is it bigger than a fist?)
It got bigger.
(It's getting bigger.)
It's dangerous.
(Ji Hyo points to So Min.)
(Moving about)
It became much bigger all of a sudden.
Orange, You.
- Make it bigger. - Orange
(The orange is as big as a ball of snow.)
(Da Gam points to Jae Seok.)
(He jumps to lift the orange.)
Goodness.
(Jae Seok points to Seok Jin.)
(Orange, orange)
(It's an orange that Class of 1919 would have.)
(Seok Jin's pronunciation and movement seem old-fashioned.)
Orange. You.
Just do it slowly.
Make it bigger.
(Will Jong Kook make a bigger orange?)
Roll it.
(Shall I make one?)
(It's a genetically modified giant orange.)
That's right.
Orange, orange. You.
It's like the show "Family Game".
(He needs to make an orange bigger than Jong Kook's.)
Hurry up.
(Otherwise, he gets penalized.)
(Grunting)
(He makes an orange planet.)
Orange, orange, orange
(We approve of it.)
- That's good. - You.
(He makes an orange as big as the Earth.)
(He points to Sae Rok.)
It's Sae Rok.
(She's fully ready.)
(What happened to her voice?)
Orange.
Orange, orange
(What's wrong with her voice?)
Who is she?
This is good.
(She makes a giant orange.)
Orange. You.
- Me? - Da Gam.
Next is Da Gam.
(She's burning with determination.)
- Orange. - What's going on?
(She rolls on the floor.)
- Orange, orange - Da Gam.
Stop it, Da Gam.
(What is this?)
(Orange Game is stopped.)
This won't work. This game won't work.
- We can't find the right game. - We can't find it.
- She should be penalized. - It's my first cup.
(She drinks calamansi that's good for the skin and losing weight.)
Do other fellow students know of another game?
I know one.
Orange fart
- Whose orange fart is it? - There's Orange Fart.
You farted. Then you say, "Farting".
- Those next to you say, "It smells" - It smells
- This is cute. - Who gets penalized?
The one who laughs.
- Okay, it sounds good. - It'll be fun.
(They try Orange Fart.)
- This is it. - Keep your face expressionless.
- Keep your face expressionless. - Okay.
- You can make others laugh. - This is it.
Anyone who laughs...
- Anyone who shows their teeth. - will be penalized.
- Okay, start. - Start with Kwang Soo.
- Whose orange fart is it? - Whose orange fart is it?
You farted
Farting
- It smells - It smells
- Whose orange fart is it? - Whose orange fart is it?
You farted
Farting
(Laughing)
(She fails as she laughs.)
It smells
- I couldn't hold back. - That's a failure.
It's embarrassing in case I really fart.
(She's ready for calamansi.)
So Min is out.
(It must be so sour.)
Is it very sour?
(It's a shot of sour and sweet calamansi.)
I could have drunk it for you.
- Start. - Start with So Min.
- Whose orange fart is it? - Whose orange fart is it?
You farted
I fart
("I fart"?)
Wait.
(It's a warning for laughter.)
(Sae Rok got it wrong.)
She was wrong. You can talk, Da Gam.
(Sae Rok failed, so she must drink.)
- Sae Rok. - "Farting".
- Field by the village entrance - Orchard one shot
- Do it again. - Yes, yes, yes
- 21 shot - 21 shot
- Did she drink it? - Goodness.
(Sae Rok takes it in one shot.)
- It must be bitter. - Start.
- Whose orange fart is it? - Whose orange fart is it?
You farted
(What's wrong with her voice again?)
Farting
- It smells - It smells
- Whose orange fart is it? - Whose orange fart is it?
You farted
Farting
(She's extremely bubbly.)
(She farts very close to his face.)
- It smells - It smells
- Whose orange fart is it? - Whose orange fart is it?
(It's Da Gam's turn to point.)
(She hums.)
(You can talk.)
(You can't laugh, but you can talk.)
- What is she doing? - Come on.
- You are... - She's...
Nothing changed other than her name.
(You're right.)
- Da Gam. - She's terrible.
(She drinks her second cup of calamansi.)
It must be sour.
Let's play the K-pop Star Game.
(2019 Running Man's Insider Game Collection)
(K-pop Star Game)
(Sing a song that contains the given word in order.)
Is there any starting phrase?
K-pop songs
(It sounds mellow.)
- K-pop songs - Wait.
- Goodness. - The melody itself is terrible.
(It's not like an Insider Game.)
The melody isn't like an insider.
Let's just do this.
Start by saying "K-pop".
(It feels so old-fashioned.)
- Are you startled? - Let's do that.
Come on, it's still an Insider Game.
"K-pop" sounds silly.
K-pop is good music
(It's the returning student's perfect singing method.)
(It's an old-fashioned phrase that an old man would sing.)
He sounds like an old man.
- K-pop - What kind of Insider Game goes...
- K-pop is good music? - K-pop is good music
K-pop
That's good. I start.
Start.
- K-pop is good music, K-pop - K-pop is good music, K-pop
- The keyword is "Our". - "Our"?
(Our meeting is)
Goodness, this is insane.
(I was going to sing this song.)
("Meeting" by Noh Sa Yeon released in 1982 is an old song.)
(Everyone panics.)
I was going to sing this song.
K-pop
(Our river and mountain are good)
(Suddenly it turns into a public service advertisement.)
- You're out. - Come on.
(Haha sings a song for a public service advertisement and fails.)
I was going to sing his song.
I'm serious.
- Drink. - Drink, drink
Drink, drink
Drink today and tomorrow.
Ask your Mapo-gu sibling.
- She would drink it. - Ask your Mapo-gu sibling.
- Ask her. - She'll do it for you.
Mapo-gu.
(Furtive)
(Ask Sae Rok instead.)
Sae Rok.
Be my substitute.
(Will you be my substitute?)
I'll protect Mapo-gu. I refuse.
(I'll protect Mapo-gu. I refuse.)
(The protector of Mapo-gu is firm.)
- Okay. - Okay, two cups.
- Drink 2 cups. - Drink 2.
- Okay. - Drink two, Haha.
Okay, Mapo-gu.
(He tries again to the resident of Mapo-gu.)
I got confused for a moment.
- I beg you. - Okay, Mapo-gu.
(He asks his long-time Mapo-gu sibling to drink 2 cups)
- I refuse. - Okay.
(She rejects after thinking.)
- 4 cups. - 4 cups.
Drink four.
Try it again.
Stop it and drink them yourself.
You wait and see.
(Sae Rok and Ji Hyo, wait and see.)
(He drinks them with his eyes closed.)
It makes my mouth water.
- He should have drunk one. - Okay, okay.
(We're sorry, Haha.)
- All right. - Start with Haha.
- Yes, let's start with Haha. - It starts now.
- Here it comes. - "Her".
- Okay, start. - "Her"?
- K-pop is good music - K-pop is good music
- K-pop - K-pop
(It goes counterclockwise starting Haha. )
(To her)
(Which song has such an antique melody?)
("Please Tell Her" by Firetruck was released in 1987.)
(Go, Jong Kook.)
K-pop
(I know her better than anyone)
(The lyrics include "her", but which song is it?)
- It's my song. - K-pop
(Jong Kook is an amazing singer.)
He sings so well.
(It was his own song.)
It's nice.
(It's Seok Jin's turn.)
(She was very pretty)
("She Was Pretty" by Park Jin Young)
You don't know...
(It's the song that everyone was thinking about.)
You don't know the rest of the lyrics.
- What? - What are the lyrics?
(She was very pretty)
(As if)
(She might rise to the sky)
(Does she suddenly rise to the sky?)
What? What did he say?
- Wait a minute. - What do you mean?
Are you telling her to go to the underworld?
Is she a fairy?
"She was very pretty". How far do I have to sing?
- Is it two verses? - No,
- I got it. - but you should sing more.
- Let's go around once. - Seriously.
- Seriously. - We stop at the third player.
Let's do this.
- Fellow students. - Yes?
- Let's work harder. - Okay.
Let's go, Class of 2019.
(We're freshmen.)
- Let's go. - Here's the keyword.
- Okay. - Let's go.
"Man"?
- Start, K-pop is good music - K-pop is good music
- K-pop - K-pop
- There's a man - It was mine.
(Seok Jin steals a song.)
Wait, your tone isn't going up
Listen to the original song.
- How can I go any higher? - You shouldn't sing if you can't.
(The original singer sings it correctly.)
- Start. - K-pop
(He pronounces clearly.)
It went up.
(There's a man who loved you very much)
(His blood pressure is at its top.)
(He hits his limit.)
(He's out of tune.)
What's this?
- K-pop - K-pop
(They approve of his singing.)
(You don't understand men)
(The melody sounds strange.)
What?
Wait, I'm serious.
(Does Kwang Soo not know the melody?)
That's enough. Wait.
(This is the original tune.)
Is it Buzz?
("You Don't Know Men" by Buzz)
(You don't know men)
(He tries again.)
What are you doing?
(It's worse than before.)
That's wrong, Kwang Soo.
(A singer demonstrates. This is it.)
- Isn't it the same? - No.
- You don't know - You don't know
(He tries again.)
(Just drink it.)
(Is this it?)
(Kwang Soo doesn't know the tune.)
Don't do it if you don't know the song.
Let's start on the other side.
- You should start this time. - Me?
They keep getting wrong. Start.
- K-pop is good music - K-pop is good music
- K-pop - K-pop
(Fill me up with love)
(Hong Jin Young's "Love Battery" finally comes up.)
(She succeeds thanks to Jin Young.)
- K-pop - K-pop
(Because I love you)
That's good.
("Because I Love You" by Yoo Jae Ha)
- K-pop - K-pop
(It's Jin Young's turn.)
(It sounds very sweet.)
It's good.
("Love That Guy" by Bobby Kim)
She sang it so well.
- K-pop - K-pop
I'm going to love
(Isn't this the most popular "love" song?)
- I was going to do it. - I'm going to love
- K-pop - K-pop
Who talked about love?
(She sings a song back in the 70s and 80s.)
- I was going to do that. - Me too.
Oh, no.
- K-pop - K-pop
I love you
("Rain and Your Story" repeats "love" more than 20 times.)
- K-pop - K-pop
(Next is Haha.)
This is Lee Hyun Do's version.
- I love you - Right. I know.
(He mimics the dance as well.)
- 2, 3. K-pop - K-pop
I love you from your head to your toes
I forgot about that.
- K-pop - K-pop
(Next is Seok Jin.)
This is Yim Jae Beom.
Because of love
(His tune is unstable once again.)
(What is this song?)
(Because of love)
Don't you know?
(It's "Love" from the drama "City Hunter)
- Because of love - I know this song.
(Next is Kwang Soo.)
- Right? K-pop - K-pop
- I love you - Oh, right.
- I'm happy - He loves that song.
- K-pop - K-pop
I love you
I will follow my heart
Why do you sing so disgustingly?
(Jae Seok mocks him.)
- Hold on. - Why?
- Were you talking about me? - Goodness.
You did. You were singing disgustingly.
- What do you mean? - He looked really weird.
I love you
(He sang the ugly version of "Asparagus" by Kim Kyung Ho.)
It was too high.
Goodness. All right, then.
- K-pop - K-pop
(Next is Ji Hyo.)
I love you
(It's Jin Young's song.)
(They continue to get more songs right.)
- She sang English lyrics. - That's Position.
(With her outstanding singing skills,)
(Jin Young also gets it right.)
(So Min also gets it right with her perfect dance moves.)
(Da Gam sings an old song and gets it right.)
Goodness.
(It's his turn soon, but he's stuck.)
- K-pop - K-pop
This is Brown Eyed Girls.
- You need to sing it. - Sing it.
- I can't remember. - You must.
- 5. - 4.
- Three. - He's wrong.
He's wrong!
(He fails to sing the song.)
Goodness, I almost got it.
- All that you said was L, O, V, E. - No.
Your voice is tingling me
Do you hear me? I need you, I love you
Right.
- It's Brown Eyed Girls. - This is hard.
(He drinks the juice.)
We started off by playing insider's games,
but now, we're beginning to look like the "Family Game".
One bottle of soju, please.
(He's suffocated.)
- Can we play a game we know? - One bottle of soju, please.
Make sure you order an appetizer.
This could be the hidden mission. "Lose in the game."
(The returning student could be given this mission.)
- "Lose in the game." - The whole time?
Maybe they need to interrupt the game.
(The game failed because of a few of them.)
(Da Gam didn't bother to make an orange and rolled around.)
(During the Orange Game, she failed by talking mute.)
(Kwang Soo also failed by not getting the tune right.)
(Seok Jin kept failing due to incorrect lyrics.)
Who's the returning student?
(There are many suspicious candidates.)
You are the most suspicious one.
- Who is it? - There's something going on.
(What was the hidden mission? And who did it?)
(Amongst the suspicion, Water Seat Game begins.)
(They fail and drink.)
(They fail again...)
(and drink.)
(The game ends with none of them becoming insiders.)
(All that they've succeeded to do is drink the juice.)
- The winner is Se Chan. - Okay.
- What? - I didn't drink the juice at all.
- You're exempted. - Okay.
(Se Chan receives the penalty exemption card.)
Now, it's the first Apprehension Time.
(It's time to catch the returning student.)
I have no idea.
(Who is the returning student?)
What did that student do?
- Everyone. - I really have no idea.
Each of you will get a chance to guess who it is.
If that person turns out to be the returning student,
your prizes will be accumulated.
If you guessed wrong, your penalties will be accumulated.
On top of that, the returning student...
has failed the first mission.
They failed?
(The returning student has failed the first round.)
- They failed. - The student failed.
Because of that, you will all be given a crucial hint.
The student mentioned often about age and rank.
(The student talked often about age and rank.)
Age and rank?
(Who was it?)
Seok Jin told Da Geum...
What was that?
(Ji Hyo gets Da Gam's name wrong.)
(She gets their guest's name wrong.)
Apologize.
Ji Hyo.
- I'm so sorry. - Goodness.
How could you get her name wrong?
Be at ease.
Seok Jin...
talked to Sae Rok about age.
To Da Geum, he...
(She gets it wrong once again.)
"Da Geum"?
("Da Geum" will be the most-searched keyword.)
Come on.
Why do you keep getting her name wrong?
That was hilarious.
Da Gam...
- You can relax. - Da Gam...
He talked to Da Gam about something.
He talked about how they used...
to be on TV together in the past.
I did. I wanted to ask her for a favor.
That's why.
Da Gam was on TV with me often...
- back in the day. - Okay.
Do you remember? Do you?
It was on KBS, Da Gam.
(He emphasized being her senior. Is he the one?)
You should all know that I'm not the returning student.
- I mean... - We need...
to remember who it was that sang many old songs.
I think...
- it's Da Gam. - Me, too.
- Right? - I think...
(The returning student mentioned things about age.)
(Da Gam sang many 80s songs, emphasizing her age.)
(Did she do that on purpose? Is she the returning student?)
But Haha also pretended to be our senior...
and said he could do this and that for us.
He said that.
(He suddenly offered to drink the juice.)
(Is he the returning student?)
- What? - It was weird for him to offer...
to drink for her.
What's so weird about that?
(She suspects Haha.)
Now, please pick...
one person each.
Jin Young, whose name was mentioned the most?
We picked Seok Jin and Haha.
(They picked Seok Jin and Haha the most.)
For us, it was Da Gam.
- So it boiled down to three. - All right.
- Let's vote. - Okay.
Wait. Who's the most talkative here?
It's you.
(You're the culprit.)
(If the most talkative one is the returning student,)
(it's definitely Seok Jin.)
- Don't make us suspect you. - Gosh.
- Oh, it's me. - Don't do that.
Usually, the most talkative one is the culprit.
Let's start with Haha.
1, 2, 3.
(The 1st candidate is Haha.)
- No one? - No.
Next is Seok Jin.
1, 2, 3.
(The 2nd candidate is Seok Jin.)
(He gets 3 votes.)
- 3 people. - 3.
Next is Da Gam.
Next is Da Gam. 1, 2, 3.
- She was obvious. - Da Gam.
Next is Da Gam.
(The 3rd candidate, Da Gam, receives 7 votes.)
- Da Gam. - Hey, how could you?
- Goodness. - All right.
(Sae Rok votes for her as well.)
- How could you? - Da Gam was...
quite suspicious today.
It's easy to see after hearing the hint.
We have chosen our returning student.
1, 2, 3.
- Han Da Gam! - Han Da Gam!
(The freshmen pick Da Gam.)
If that person turns out to be the returning student,
- your prizes will be accumulated. - Yes.
If you're wrong, your penalties...
- will be accumulated. - Okay.
(Will their prizes or penalties be accumulated?)
That's interesting.
- Is this foot volleyball? - How interesting.
- Are there three teams? - It'll be fun.
This time, we will play with a ball.
If you win this mission,
you'll be able to have lunch.
(Their lunch is at stake.)
- I'm hungry. - That'll be good.
- We need to do well. - We definitely should.
- We need to be serious. - I have to do well.
- I'm starving. - I'm hungry!
This is Three Team Gym Ball Foot Volleyball.
Gym ball?
- Gym ball? - What is that?
- Gym ball? - I'm done for.
- It's that big ball. - Gym ball.
They have them at the gyms.
- Gym ball? - Gym ball.
- Is it possible to play with that? - I'm done for.
(It won't be easy.)
You'll be divided 4, 4, and 3.
There will be three teams.
You'll all play simultaneously.
Every time you lose, you'll be deducted one point.
The team with 10 deduction points will lose.
- We can scheme against a team. - You're right.
That's possible.
The winning team...
(What will they get?)
will get pork belly.
Seriously?
(It'll be a party.)
(They'll have pork belly.)
No way. I'm craving pork belly.
- I want that fat. - It suits this occasion.
- It definitely does. - Yes, here in Chuncheon.
If we do grill them, it'll truly be an orientation.
The second team to win...
will have instant noodles.
That's still good.
I'd be happy with second place.
- He loves it. - I like that better.
- And last place? - The losing team...
- will have rice and lavers. - Okay.
- Rice and lavers. - Second place will be fine.
I'm fine with coming second.
Jong Kook prefers second or last.
- I want pork belly. - All right.
Even for this round, the returning student will be...
- doing their hidden mission. - Okay.
- Really? - Watch closely.
(What is the returning student's mission?)
It's the person who messes up.
(He guesses that the student will mess up on purpose.)
Okay, the returning student's hidden mission for this round...
- is not getting first place. - Seriously?
- Who is it? - Who is it?
(The student will prevent their team from getting 1st place.)
(The person who repeatedly makes mistakes...)
(is most likely the returning student.)
- We need to watch closely. - We do.
We need to be alert.
- Maybe it's Da Gam. - It could be Kwang Soo.
(Is one of them truly the returning student?)
(Team Sae Rok, Team Jin Young, Team Da Gam)
- Let's go now. - All right.
I'm nervous.
Who will serve?
- Over there. - Let's focus.
We'll do it. I'll serve.
(The match begins.)
Okay.
(Kwang Soo serves first.)
Okay. It's mine.
(He hits the ball towards Team Sae Rok.)
(Will they get the first point easily?)
- Okay. - Okay.
(It hits the net.)
What was that?
(Team Da Gam gets 1 point deducted.)
- Wait. - What was that?
- Okay! Good work. - Yes!
- I'm not used to that ball. - Come on.
Did we get a deduction?
We did.
Really?
(Se Chan serves.)
It's mine.
(Hitting)
(It hits his stomach.)
He's out.
That was very suspicious.
- That's not right. - Come on.
Wasn't that weird?
(He makes two mistakes in a row.)
- Hold on. - He's the returning student.
- Look, Bo Gae. - Is it really you?
- Isn't it him? - What?
- What's wrong with you? - The ball is hard to control.
- Are you serious? - It's hard.
It's hard to control it.
- It's because of the ball. - This isn't right.
It's too hard to predict.
This makes no sense.
- This is... - We'll have to keep an eye on him.
- Wait. - Let's focus.
Do you want to try, Jin Young?
(Team Da Gam has two deduction points.)
- Do you want to try? - No, you can.
What are you two doing?
You're getting along well.
Hold on. This is that American couple.
- American couple? - That team's a bit weird.
The ladies are related to him.
- Oh, shush! - Let's go.
(They should keep it down.)
Focus.
(I'm on Ji Hyo's side.)
- Focus. - Focus.
- Focus. - Okay.
(Jong Kook kicks the ball to Kwang Soo.)
Do a heading.
(If he fails once again, he'll be suspected for sure.)
- Focus. - Focus.
- Focus. - Okay.
(Jong Kook kicks the ball to Kwang Soo.)
Do a heading.
(Will he be able to counterattack this time?)
(It hits his head.)
- Hey! - Okay!
(The ball goes out.)
Do a heading. Hey!
(The other team would've lost had he not touched it.)
It touched his head.
- It's out. - It was out.
You should've been at the back.
- What were you doing? - I swear, the sun was blinding me.
- Seriously. - I swear.
- It was the sun. - Whatever.
- Okay. - Here we go.
Okay!
Good.
(Haha serves to Jin Young.)
- Good. - Get it.
(Jin Young unstably receives it.)
Kick it over. Good!
(Jong Kook had quick reflexes.)
Do a heading.
(The ball flies towards Kwang Soo.)
(Heading)
(It hits his face.)
Heading. Good.
(He defends with his face.)
- Get it. - It went out!
(It hits Jong Kook's foot and goes out.)
- It went out! - Okay!
(Even Jong Kook couldn't counterattack Kwang Soo's shot.)
- Okay. - They are doing nothing.
I know.
I thought it was out. It's longer than I thought.
The field is quite big.
I saw the infamous heading face of Kwang Soo's.
(His heading face...)
(is patented.)
(It's the face of a sad angel.)
All right.
(Team Da Gam: minus 3, Team Jin Young: minus 1)
(Haha serves.)
- It's mine. - It's mine.
(The ball flies towards the team with the least points.)
- Okay. Nice! - Good.
Good.
(Flustered, Haha kicks it towards Team Jin Young.)
It's okay. Darn it.
(The ball lands at an ambiguous spot.)
Sorry. I should've kicked it harder.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Good. - Hold on.
Why couldn't he kick it?
(She catches onto something.)
What?
Have you ever seen him fail to kick a ball?
- I know. - That's weird.
This wasn't that long of a distance.
Normally, he would've kicked it over.
- He couldn't do it? - It's not me.
- It's not me. It was a mistake. - He couldn't...
- kick it over? - It was my mistake.
Let's win this game.
(We'll see if it was a mistake or not.)
- I'll serve it. - He's odd.
(Was it truly a mistake?)
All right.
- Okay. - It'll come this way.
Get ready.
(Team Da Gam: minus 3, Team Jin Young: minus 2)
Good.
It's in. Good.
(The ball flies towards Jong Kook who just made a mistake.)
(He fails to kick it over.)
He's weird.
It's in. Good.
Hold on. Isn't he suspicious?
(He made two mistakes in a row.)
- That's a bit odd. - Why are you so bad?
That seemed intentional.
- It doesn't make any sense. - That was suspicious.
- Come on. - That's really weird.
You're suspicious.
Hear me out. I thought it was out.
- No, come here. - I thought it was out.
- No. - But it turned out I was wrong.
- You're making an excuse. - I thought it was out.
- He's suspicious. - If he thought it was out,
- he wouldn't have received it. - You're right.
I'm serious. It's not me.
It isn't me.
Bo Gae in this team and Jong Kook in that team.
Bo Gae is suspicious.
You're right. He's weird too.
All right. You can serve it.
- He's weird. - Let's go.
It's here.
(Haha's serve goes to suspicious Jong Kook.)
- Kick it. - Okay.
- Good. Nice. - Okay.
- Good. Go, Sae Rok. - Nice.
(Sae Rok counterattacks with a heading.)
Good job, Sae Rok.
(Jong Kook successfully kicks over the ball.)
- Nice, Jong Kook. - Head it!
(The ball flies.)
- Okay! - Okay!
(She flinches and moves away from the ball.)
- It didn't reach my head. - Wait.
Is it Da Gam? Why isn't she doing anything?
- She hasn't been doing anything. - She moved away from the ball.
- The ball didn't come to me. - She dodged the ball.
- I saw it. - Hey.
- Are you performing the mission? - No, the ball wasn't coming to me.
(She pretended to move towards the ball...)
(but didn't even reach out and rather avoided it.)
She moved away.
- I think it's her. - She dodged the ball.
One of us is currently performing their mission.
You're right. We need to keep an eye out.
- We need to toss it to everyone. - You're right.
- We need to observe all of them. - Da Gam is suspicious.
- Which way should I kick it? - Over there.
- Over there? - Yes.
(Jae Seok serves.)
Get it!
(The ball flies to Da Gam.)
- Get it! - Go!
Okay.
(She keeps making mistakes.)
Are you being intentional?
- You're acting so strange. - It's her.
- What was that? - It's not me.
- Were you being intentional? - You're acting weird.
It's not me.
- Then you should serve. - Try it.
Gosh.
We'll know for sure this time.
- Something's fishy. - I think...
Doesn't she seem like the returning student?
(Another mistake, and everyone will suspect her even more.)
- Okay! - Good work.
(She lightly kicks it.)
It's out.
- Out. - It's out.
(The ball is out.)
Da Gam is very suspicious.
(She fails at serving the ball.)
- She's so weird. - Don't you think it's her?
(Thanks to her, they lose a total of 3 points.)
Let's beat them.
It's mine.
(4 more losses in points, and Team Da Gam will lose.)
Good, good.
(They need to be encouraged.)
(Da Gam compliments her teammates.)
Get it over the net.
- So Min! - Good.
Get it.
(The ball descends towards Da Gam's head.)
(Did she just catch it with her hand?)
(This time, she fails by playing with her hand.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E442 Running Man
"Spring Orientation Special"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Hey, they have...
two returning students.
That side is full of returning students.
It's chaotic.
- It's a mess. - I'm so upset.
- Hey! - I'm certain!
- Da Gam, are you the one? - Yes?
- I was just scared of the ball. - Is that so?
- Yes. - Don't lie.
(Everyone has been suspecting her since the previous games.)
I'm scared of the ball.
(Are these two making mistakes intentionally?)
We need to find the returning student.
- Kick it. - Okay.
- It's out. - It's out.
- It's out. - Hey!
Let's go.
- Yes. - Get it!
- Get it! - Darn it.
(This time, it's Da Gam's turn to fail.)
- What did she just do? - Gosh, Da Gam.
She received it with her bottom.
Get it. Okay.
- Seok Jin! - I'll do it!
Okay!
(Thanks to the candidates, they lose.)
It's over.
- Okay. - Okay.
I'm so frustrated.
(Are these two returning students?)
Their team doesn't exist anymore, right?
- It's against the two teams. - We don't exist anymore.
We'll at least get instant noodles.
(For the finals, the winner needs to get 3 points.)
Serve it.
We should kick it towards those who are suspicious...
so we can observe their actions.
We need to observe them.
Okay.
(Jin Young serves.)
- Good. That was good. - Nice.
- I'm sorry! - Nice!
I'm sorry!
That makes no sense.
That's suspicious.
- I'm serious. I swear. - That was good.
I really swear.
(Team Jin Young: 0, Team Sae Rok: minus 1)
- That's right. - It's working.
Ji Hyo, hold on. Hurry.
Nice one.
(The ball that ace player Ji Hyo kicked...)
(goes to Haha once again.)
- Hold on. - It's out.
(His kicking skills fail.)
Okay. Nice one.
That's weird.
Haha, it's the second time in a row.
- It is weird. - That's quite strange.
No, it's really not. I'm sorry.
It's weird. I think it's a mission.
- This is driving me crazy. - You're usually good at acting.
He adapts to it well like that.
- We only have a point left. - We're in trouble.
We can do it. We can win this.
- Then you should do well. - Okay.
Okay, let's do this.
Nice one.
We should send it over to the candidate...
and see if that person is acting suspiciously.
We need to see if they're acting weird.
(The ball goes to Haha for the third time.)
(Will he receive it well this time?)
Oh, no.
(Bounces off)
Out. It's done.
(It goes out straight away.)
- Gosh. - Hey, you're the returning student.
- The returning student. - I'm really not.
- Why would I lose? - I can see that he is one now.
I'm telling you the truth.
- He's being weird. - Trust me.
No, listen to us.
He seemed suspicious, so we passed the ball to him a number of times.
He failed to receive them all.
It's hard to fail while heading.
Haha is being weird.
- No, it's because I closed my eyes. - He gave up.
We passed it to him a couple of times but...
- It seems like... - I honestly tried my best.
I tried my best.
- But this is... - They are even weirder than me.
In this group, Jong Kook is weird.
- Here, it's Da Gam. - It's Da Gam over here.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo and Da Gam.
This place is filled with returning students.
This really feels like an orientation.
- That looks delicious. - The sausage looks delicious.
They're cooking well. Look at the sausage.
Look at this.
I can smell it from here.
- It's here. - That looks delicious.
The sausage is ready.
(Cooling it before eating it.)
Yes, it's ready.
(2nd place will have an instant noodles party.)
(We could've eaten it if we didn't make a mistake.)
I can't hold it in anymore.
It's so good, right?
My team, let's not be like this.
- We look like losers. - This is all Da Gam's fault.
Why is it my fault?
Da Gam is the returning student. That's why we lost.
That's true.
(While Da Gam is being suspected for being the returning student.)
Let's find the returning student quickly.
Please turn yourselves in.
- No. - It's Da Gam.
It's been decided who the returning student is.
- Who is it? - We roughly know now.
It's Da Gam and Haha.
- Haha? - I'm really not.
- Jong Kook. - I really did my best.
- These are the suspicious members. - I really worked hard...
- for my team. - Haha did seem suspicious.
It's weird. He seems weird too.
In the second round,
the returning student's mission was...
(The returning student's mission in the last foot volleyball game.)
(To not place 1st in the game.)
(Who will it be?)
Wait. You need to tell us if they succeeded or not.
Yes, we need to hear that first.
The returning student...
(If they placed 1st, they failed. If they didn't, they succeeded.)
- did succeed. - That's right.
(The returning student's mission was successful.)
- Who placed first? - Did you really suspect me?
- Did you really suspect me? - Good job.
Jong Kook, Se Chan, Jin Young, and Ji Hyo...
- aren't the returning student. - It's Da Gam, Haha,
- and Lee Kwang Soo. - It's not me. I worked hard.
I think Kwang Soo is the most...
Yes, Kwang Soo was acting strange too.
- Kwang Soo? - He was being unblievable.
- Kwang Soo was weird. - It's not me.
- We were on the same team. - Kwang Soo...
- Are you all suspecting me again? - He was weird.
- Is it you, Kwang Soo? - It's really not me.
Everyone, to check off this round's returning student,
you need to avoid one member who is being suspected...
as the returning student and get into pairs.
(The rest of the members need to form a pair.)
- You can't pair up with them. - That's right.
- The four of us are safe. - We are safe.
You'll be doing the last round together...
- as a pair you choose to be. - Really?
The pair assignment is very important.
Honestly, Da Gam was the weirdest.
(Da Gam was the weirdest.)
- Honestly, Da Gam was the weirdest. - Da Gam really was.
- Da Gam was very strange. - She wasn't taking part.
- Ji Hyo... - Ji Hyo and Jin Young...
- are both safe. - We need to pair with them.
- I need to avoid Da Gam. - Ji Hyo and Jin Young.
- Se Chan, you can go first. - Am I first?
I guess I'll have to choose...
You need to choose someone who isn't the returning student.
He's a safe one.
I will choose...
Jin Young.
(Se Chan and Jin Young)
Sure.
(Confirmed)
(Se Chan and Jin Young form a pair.)
For me,
if you get rejected, you have to go last.
That's dangerous.
You should see that Jae Seok is also pretending to be...
- the class leader. - He's being weird too.
- He's being too passive. - Everyone.
Ji Hyo is certainly safe.
- You're right. - Yes, I'm certain.
- Ji Hyo. - Pass.
(Suspicious Jae Seok reaches out but is rejected by Ji Hyo.)
(You're rejected.)
You're last now.
- Hey, I'm... - Go to the back of the line.
- Hey. - Go back.
This is so unfair.
- Who's third? - Me.
- He's going to Ji Hyo. - Will they meet again?
(Jong Kook is obviously...)
(going to her.)
Honey.
(Honey, Jong Kook who's safe is here.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo)
- Honey, let's go. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo accepts Jong Kook jauntily.)
I'm speechless.
- What? - You guys look good together.
- I'm speechless. - It's because...
- it's certain that he's safe. - It's certain. You can't do much.
- He's certainly safe. - My turn.
I'll choose you, So Min.
(Haha who's suspicious goes next.)
Haha is too suspicious though.
- Gosh. - She's...
- So Min is weird too. - Yes, I find So Min weird too.
- So Min is weird. - Sae Rok, trust me.
(I only have you, Sae Rok.)
Yes?
(Haha and Sae Rok)
- Sure. - Yes.
(Suspicious Haha and less suspicious Sae Rok form a pair.)
- But he's weird. - I knew it.
- At this rate, Da Gam will be left. - Gosh.
They're both weird.
If I avoid Da Gam, So Min is left.
If I avoid So Min, Da Gam is left.
So Min is a better choice though.
They're feeling the same way.
They might be feeling the same way.
Why?
(Who will Seok Jin choose as his pair?)
- Da Gam. - What?
Wait for the next person.
I'm sorry.
- Goodbye. - Okay.
(His worry was meaningless.)
- I'm sorry. - She said sorry.
She said sorry.
She apologized to Seok Jin.
(Rejected Seok Jin goes to the back.)
- I'm going to let it pass. - I'm sorry.
- It's not my first time. - I'm sorry.
- Kwang Soo has a chance now. - Kwang Soo.
- Wait. - Kwang Soo.
- He's suspicious. - Returning students should pair up.
It's really not me.
Okay.
Jeon So Min.
(Will Kwang Soo choose So Min?)
- Sure. - Okay. It's really not me.
- Nice to have you. - He's the most suspicious one.
- It's not me. - I suspected Haha...
and Jong Kook.
The important thing to do now is to leave out the returning student.
(Da Gam, Jae Seok, and Seok Jin are left.)
(It's Jae Seok's turn again.)
- I choose... - Wait.
How is she not the returning student when she has hands in the pocket?
(She seems suspicious to anyone.)
She's the returning student.
(It's the old school trend.)
She had her hands in her pockets like this.
Is Da Gam really the returning student?
She only had her thumbs in.
This is so unfair to me.
I saw with my own eyes. During the foot volleyball,
She had her hands in her pockets and said, "Look who's the boss."
I heard it.
(An old school slang used in middle and high school by rebels.)
- I heard it for sure. - She said it naturally.
- Really? - "Look who's the boss."
- Really? - "You were the boss."
As I said before,
instead of wanting to be a pair, we need to...
- avoid the returning student. - We need to do that.
- Leave the returning student. - The returning student.
So, I'll choose Jee Seok Jin.
(So, I'll choose Jee Seok Jin.)
(Jae Seok chooses Seok Jin instead of Da Gam)
- Wait. - It's really not me.
- You're the one. - You're going to regret this.
- We have to find the one. - Gosh.
We have to find the returning student.
This is the first time that a guest member is left out.
- It's the first time. - It is.
The last member left is Han Da Gam.
She's been suspected twice in a row.
- It's been twice in a row. - That's right.
She didn't try to fit in.
If all of you are correct,
the prizes will be accumulated twice.
If she's not the returning student,
the penalties will be accumulated twice.
This is the last mission to confirm who the returning student is.
The last mission is...
a tournament in men and women's division.
After tying the sleeves of your hoodie together,
you will have to stick two words on your back.
You need to find out the words of your opposing player,
and explain what it is to...
your partner who has their eyes covered.
The first pair to get it right wins.
(The pair who gets both words first wins.)
A word on the top and the other on the bottom.
This seems difficult.
(The list of matches)
Okay.
Yu Jae Seok.
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Yu Jae Seok.
Lee Bo Gae.
I want to just see the word.
I want to see them too but I can't.
We're starting. Ready.
- Let's go. - Set.
At first,
this is the war of nerves.
Look at their eyes.
Jae Seok, you're at a disadvantage if you stand still.
(Jae Seok starts lowering his height.)
Your head...
- They're like wild animals. - You need to turn your head.
The colors of a giraffe and a grasshopper.
- The colors suit them well. - They're starting.
(What are they doing?)
(They are in their own intense league)
Look at them.
I saw this on "Animal Kingdom".
The giraffe meets the grasshopper.
(Giraffe as known as Lee Kwang Soo. The eight-footer.)
(Look, it's a grasshopper.)
The grasshopper is smelling it.
(Smelly guy)
The female giraffe is heading toward the male grasshopper.
(The mysterious sight of a giraffe and grasshopper's exploration.)
They're starting.
The grasshopper is looking at its back.
Finally, it's the war of nerves.
They're using their strength now.
- They're both standing. - They stood up.
That's right. Quickly.
That's right. 1,2,3.
- It's like a mirror. - Move swiftly.
There you go.
- Go closer to his face. - There you go.
- Closer. - That's it.
(Jae Seok defenses with his flexibility.)
Good.
I wish I don't have to go up against those two.
Haven't you seen it yet, Jae Seok?
- Kwang Soo, you need more time? - He has a long way to go yet.
The giraffe...
versus...
(Look at these silly guys.)
(A dirty play between the giraffe and the grasshopper)
- I've seen this in a movie. - "Secret Garden".
(How much longer)
(Do I have to look only at you?)
- How much longer - Giraffe and the grasshopper.
(How much longer do they have to do this?)
- Do I - Do I
(Kwang Soo,)
(since when did you have such looks?)
(What an amazing face you have.)
(From "Animal Kingdom" to "Secret Garden",)
(there's no other game like this one.)
He lifted his back. Now flip him!
(Kwang Soo attacks Jae Seok's important part.)
Hey!
(Scanning the words)
He got it.
(So Min, catch this.)
(The answer is cuteness.)
Cuteness?
(She gets it right.)
Why did you have to meet me?
Revenge.
- Why... - "Temptation of Wife"?
(It's similar.)
(What on earth is that?)
So Min.
(The answer is temptation.)
- What? - Well...
- Temptation. - Okay!
That's right.
(Kwang Soo wins the match against Jae Seok.)
What happened?
- That was impressive. - Goodness.
- Good game. - Good game.
- You're good. - Thanks.
It was a fair play.
I should have done it.
(Kwang Soo advances to the next round.)
(Next round is Haha and Sae Rok versus Se Chan and Jin Young.)
I saw it.
- Okay, Jin Young. It's something... - I'm listening.
- that you do to someone you like. - Pretending?
(Se Chan easily dominates Haha and gets the first word right.)
(This time, he coils around Haha like a cobra.)
(With his merciless attack,)
(he catches the second word.)
(Jin Young quickly gets the word right.)
- This team wins. - Okay.
(Se Chan advances to the next round.)
Call me the little Kim Jong Kook.
(He's confident.)
Let's do this.
Show me you aren't a returning student.
- I'm not. - Then win this match.
I can't wait to watch this match.
This will be exciting.
This is going to be fun.
Is it the match between the tiger and the giraffe this time?
- Goodness. - The tiger and the giraffe.
(Will Kwang Soo, the tallest member, win this match?)
All right, get ready.
(The words for each team)
Get ready.
Set.
(The semi-final match starts.)
Okay, good.
(Jong Kook presses Kwang Soo with his strength.)
Jong Kook is enjoying it.
That's a nice move.
(The muscular tiger versus the tall giraffe)
Nice.
The penalty exemption card is on the line.
(Kwang Soo trips after jumping alone.)
My goodness.
- Hang on. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is mad.
There you go.
Jong Kook is going to lift him.
(Kicking)
All right, let's do this.
Let's do it.
(Kwang Soo jumps on him right at that moment.)
(Jong Kook is below him.)
What's going on?
Kwang Soo is making his counterattack.
(It's the beginning of his counterattack.)
The giraffe is dominating the tiger!
Their positions are shifted.
The giraffe mercilessly attacks the lion.
(The giraffe ruthlessly kicks the savage animal.)
(Do you want a beating?)
(But Jong Kook keeps a smile on his face.)
There's still a smile on his face.
You know, tigers play around with their quarry...
before killing it.
It must be Jong Kook's new toy.
He seems curious about his new toy.
(He doesn't want to play with Jong Kook.)
- Who's the returning student? - It's not me.
- Come out now. - Just say it's you, Da Gam.
- Let's end it here. - Kwang Soo.
Han Da Gam, come out.
- Han Da Gam. - Goodness.
"Han Da Gam, come out."
(It's time they suspect her, Han Da Gam.)
I didn't do anything.
(Jong Kook starts using force...)
(as no one comes forward to confess.)
(Just take a look at it.)
(He scans the words.)
- Stay still. - He's letting Jong Kook see it.
- He showed it all. - Jong Kook saw the words.
(The answer is single since birth.)
Those guys who were single since they were born.
- Single since birth. - Single since birth.
Single since birth.
(Kwang Soo wants Ji Hyo to get it right already,)
(so he reveals the answer faster than anyone else.)
He said it himself.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo get the first word right.)
What is going on?
Are they running?
His teammate better throw a white towel.
Goodness.
Kwang Soo, just show him.
That's enough!
Letter of apology!
(Jae Seok reveals the answer to stop the game.)
The answer is letter of apology!
Letter of apology, punk!
That's the answer.
Look at him.
He's turned to a wreck.
You write this when you did something wrong.
Letter of apology.
Not you. Say the answer, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo, get the answer right already.)
Letter of apology.
When you did something wrong.
It's over.
- It's over. - What happened?
- Goodness. - I couldn't see.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo advance to the finals as expected.)
- My goodness. - I couldn't see.
Get ready right away, Se Chan.
You're up next.
Next is Se Chan.
I couldn't see the words.
Se Chan, you look so...
- Se Chan. - You look...
- so dark. - Goodness.
I was feeling cold a while ago, but I'm not anymore. It's nice.
You think it's nice?
(How to compete with the warmed-up tiger)
- Jong Kook. - How relaxed.
Jong Kook, just look at it.
- Do it now! - No.
(Take a peek and get it done already!)
- Proposal. - Okay.
- Hulk. - Okay.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo get the answers right in a second.)
- The winner is... - Okay.
Kim Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook wins the game as expected.)
(And the winner's partner is...)
- Ji Hyo is no joke. - Ji Hyo is strong.
- Say things out loud, Jin Young. - Okay.
Ready, set.
The first word.
(She catches the word as soon as the match starts.)
Jong Kook.
- It's what we do often. - Wait.
- Spy. - That's right.
(They easily get the first word right.)
(This ace member even controls Jin Young in a leisurely manner.)
- The first time you kiss someone. - First kiss.
- First kiss. - It's over.
(Ji Hyo advances to the finals too.)
It's crazy.
(At that time)
Ready, set.
(The new challenger appears.)
Sae Rok, what's wrong with you?
(The real tough cookie has appeared.)
What's wrong with you?
- Nice. - She's strong.
(So Min lies down to fight against this unexpectedly strong opponent.)
She's lying down on purpose.
(I've waited for this.)
(The frightening shadow of Sae Rok jumps on her.)
(I'll be easy on you, So Min.)
So Min might lose.
(Sae Rok attacks So Min on her.)
Sorry, So Min.
So Min!
Goodness.
Haha.
Jae Seok's nickname.
- Grasshopper. - Grasshopper!
(They immediately get the words right.)
Good job.
(The strong girl, Sae Rok, and the original ace, Ji Hyo...)
(will be competing in the finals.)
It's the finals for the female members.
- Bring them the stickers. - Okay.
Get lost, Team Green!
(The members are upset about Team Green.)
Sae Rok, go for it.
- Let's do it. - You can do it.
- I can do it. - Go for it, Sae Rok.
- Beat Ji Hyo. - Goodness.
We can't let Ji Hyo become the winner too.
- Sae Rok, you have to win. - All right.
Ready, set.
(Who will be the winner of this big match?)
Ji Hyo isn't an easy opponent.
Sae Rok is really strong.
Really?
- But she's exhausted. - She's strong.
Look at Ji Hyo. She's strong too.
She's rolling the sleeves like Jong Kook did.
Goodness.
- Sae Rok is putting all her might. - Did you see it?
Not yet, sir.
(She's so polite.)
What...
She talks like she's really in college.
- "No, sir." - It's how freshmen talk.
"No, sir."
Go ahead and see it then.
(Do it, freshman.)
Yes, sir.
(She suddenly uses her Herculean strength.)
Sae Rok is no joke.
(She spots the word first.)
Haha.
- It's two words. - Okay.
Red light, yellow light.
Red light, yellow light? Traffic lights!
- That's right! - Gosh.
(Sae Rok gets one word right before Ji Hyo.)
- This is unpredictable. - Sae Rok is amazing.
- She's no joke. - She's good.
- Seriously? - Ji Hyo is...
(Ji Hyo starts her counterattack at that time.)
Take a look at the other word already.
(Sae Rok will win if they get one more word right.)
(But then Ji Hyo starts spinning her like a windmill.)
(How does it feel to spin around and around?)
(Sae Rok refuses to get spun anymore.)
Goodness.
(It's such a fierce match.)
My gosh.
(They don't give each other a slack.)
- They're good. - What is that?
- It's showing there. - What's that?
(Ji Hyo doesn't miss the slight second of her slack.)
- Goodness. - She saw it.
Jong Kook, what's other than jjamppong?
Jjajangmyeon.
(That's correct.)
They have one word left each.
Ji Hyo is different from So Min, isn't she?
- She's so different. - She's very different.
She's strong like a man.
She's trying to hide the other side.
- Really? - Gosh.
She gave up on one word to hide the other.
(Sae Rok is trying to defend the remaining word.)
Gosh.
(She's so smart.)
- How are you going to look though? - I know.
(It's a nice strategy,)
(but she can't look at the other's word this way.)
It's like a cape.
(Sae Rok somehow ended up in a defensive position.)
- Sae Rok is defending now. - I know.
Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo is going aggressive.
(Ji Hyo spins her like a windmill again.)
- Goodness. - Sae Rok.
- This is enough. - Sae Rok.
- Stop it now. - Goodness, Sae Rok.
- Sae Rok. - Oh, no.
(She can't move.)
- Stop it now. - Please.
Give in now, Sae Rok.
- This is enough. - Sae Rok.
- Give in, Sae Rok. - Sae Rok.
(Ji Hyo scans the remaining word at that time.)
Jong Kook. It's your nickname.
- Tiger? - Not that one.
- What? - A thug.
Your nickname.
Other than Ace.
- Man of Power. - There you go.
(The answer is Man of Power.)
(They get the other answer right.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo both become the winner of the final mission.)
Good work, Sae Rok.
- She held up so long. - I know.
Good work.
- We need to check the hint first. - Right.
It's time for the final judgment.
In the final round,
- the returning student... - What did the returning student do?
used an old buzzword.
(The returning student used an old buzzword.)
(An old buzzword?)
- An old buzzword? - Hold on.
Earlier... What was it?
- What was it? - "Look who's the boss."
- "Look who's the boss." - Haha said it.
Jong Kook.
(Before the final round started...)
(She had her hands in her pockets and said,)
("Look who's the boss.")
- I heard it for sure. - "Look who's the boss"?
- Really? - "Look who's the boss."
(Haha claimed he heard Da Gam say, "Look who's the boss.")
- I meant... - Haha is suspicious.
I meant she said something along the line.
- Is Haha the returning student? - "Look who's the boss."
("Look who's the boss" came out of nowhere.)
If it were a mission,
he wouldn't have done it so openly.
I thought Da Gam was the returning student.
Maybe she isn't it.
She isn't nervous at all.
- She is enjoying the show with us. - She is relaxed.
Think about it.
- She didn't do anything. - I think it's Sae Rok.
- Earlier, - Watch her carefully.
when we played games...
(Why did she suddenly bring up Sae Rok?)
She is so scary.
She said to me...
- I am sure everyone heard her. - I think it's Da Gam.
"I think it's Sae Rok."
(Do you think it's me?)
"Watch her carefully."
- Look at her eyes. - It's Da Gam.
I personally think it's Da Gam.
It's Da Gam.
So Min, what do you think?
I also think it's Da Gam.
- Everyone thinks it's Da Gam. - Da Gam?
You will regret this!
It's Sae Rok!
(Is Da Gam the returning student?)
If Da Gam is the returning student,
you will divide three prizes among yourselves.
If Da Gam isn't the returning student,
you will divide three water bombs among yourselves.
Do we need to divide them among ourselves?
- Now, - Da Gam.
we will remove Da Gam's name tag and check her identity.
When did they prepare this?
- Please turn around. - I am really curious.
Da Gam, we will check your identity.
In 1, 2.
(She has to be the returning student.)
(Da Gam was suspected from the beginning.)
She acted strangely from the start.
(What could be Da Gam's identity?)
What?
(She isn't the returning student.)
- Are we wrong? - She isn't the returning student.
(She was an innocent student who entered the university in 2019.)
You should have denied it harder.
I told you I am not it!
Why didn't you listen to me?
- Da Gam. - Why didn't you listen to me?
The returning student is...
(Who could be the returning student...)
(who hid his or her identity until the end?)
- Haha. - My goodness.
(The returning student is Haha.)
- It's Haha. - I told you!
It's Haha.
- It's Haha. - How could you do this?
For goodness' sake.
- How could you? - I told you I am not it.
Look who's the boss.
(I did it!)
(Before the start of the shoot)
Gosh, this is...
Haha, you are the returning student...
who wants to hang out with the new students.
In Round One, use a style of speech of the returning students.
"I'll do so-and-so for you."
(A style of speech of the returning students)
Say that to all female members once.
Excuse me. Are there substitutes?
- I'll drink it for you. - Black Knights?
They're allowed.
- Jin Young, I'll do it for you. - Will you drink it?
(He succeeded to say it to Jin Young.)
Sae Rok, I'll drink it for you.
(He succeeded to say it to Sae Rok.)
(He failed to say it to Da Gam and Ji Hyo.)
(Haha failed the first hidden mission.)
In Round Two,
you must keep your team from placing the first.
(Keep your team from placing first in the foot volleyball match.)
(He kicked the wrong way.)
(He made a home run.)
(He headed the ball out of the field.)
- The returning student. - I'm really not.
- Why would I lose? - I can see that he is one now.
(He succeeded in the hidden mission.)
Your hidden mission for the final round...
is to use an old buzzword,
"Look who's the boss."
- "Look who's the boss?" - "Look who's the boss."
(He didn't know what to do.)
She had her hands in her pockets and said, "Look who's the boss."
I heard it for sure.
"Look who's the boss." I heard it for sure.
- Really? - "Look who's the boss."
(He said "Look who's the boss" and succeeded in the last mission.)
I can't believe you!
He behaved strangely during the foot volleyball match.
I can't believe you.
You are so shameless.
Since you failed to catch the returning student,
you will get three water bombs.
- They are for 3 people. - Let's pick 3 people.
That will be neat.
- That will be neat. - Race of Wits?
Shall we play the Race of Wits?
Okay. Let's sit down.
- Shall we stand up? - Yes.
Okay.
Get ready.
Sit down.
- Start. - One.
- 2. - 3.
- Did you stand up? - All right.
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok stand up at 3 simultaneously.)
The two of them...
The two of them are out.
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok are out.)
Why did you stand up?
For goodness' sake. Why did you stand up?
One place remains.
Get ready. Start.
- 1. - 1.
(They stood up as soon as the race began.)
- They are out. - They are out.
(Kwang Soo and Da Gam stood up simultaneously.)
One of them will be chosen.
I struggled all day today!
Then we will have a vote.
- That came out of nowhere. - The two of us.
- What? - That came out of nowhere.
Listen.
You know,
having this experience on Running Man...
- will be a good memory. - Seok Jin.
(Da Gam hasn't experienced the water bomb.)
We need to think about the unfairness...
of having the same person take the water bomb.
(Kwang Soo always takes the water bomb.)
Seriously.
- It's the three of us again. - You are right.
- This is the same picture. - Yes.
(Everyone is tired of this picture.)
You know, having this experience on Running Man...
(Will they opt...)
(for a new picture with a new person?)
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Lee Kwang Soo.
(Let's make changes later.)
The penalty will be given to...
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Lee Kwang Soo.
(He is familiar with the penalty.)
Seok Jin, Jae Seok, and Kwang Soo, come to the water bombs.
It will help you have a fresh start in the New Year.
(It's a familiar sight.)
One.
- Two. - Let's go.
(Splashing)
(They get hit...)
(by a water bomb again.)
- My goodness. - My goodness.
Thank you for your hard work.
(We thank Da Gam, Jin Young, and Sae Rok.)
(50 mysterious boxes are piled up in a room.)
(Inside the boxes...)
(is a big secret.)
(The moment they open the boxes, their journey begins.)
(It's a parade of rare items that have never been seen.)
(From an heirloom that could be a national treasure...)
(to a vinyl that is hard to find)
(The items are priced.)
(We could witness something spectacular.)
(A dollar?)
(Zero dollars?)
(There are more twists.)
(1,000,000 dollars?)
(What is the secret behind these boxes?)
(Unboxing, the Secret of the Boxes)