(So Min's raw voice resonates at the vintage cafe.)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - My goodness.
- Did you release a new song? - Hello.
- Hello. - I...
- I had to film a show that day. - Okay.
But So Min and Ko Young Bae decided to have a meeting...
and already finished the lyrics.
She went to see him in private.
- Exactly. - Right.
I'm all for having meetings,
but why did you meet when I wasn't free and write the lyrics?
- Why did you do that? - Hey.
But your team doesn't have a group chatroom...
since you don't have that app.
- Go on. - But...
The songwriter, Gummy, and Jong Kook have their own group chatroom.
(But I have the application too.)
- Really? - By the way,
- you guys are awful. - Is that true?
Just hearing about it is upsetting.
- Really? - I didn't know he wasn't in it.
You guys are terrible.
- We were talking, - That was too mean.
but he was so silent. I thought that he didn't even try to help us.
- Really? - But he wasn't in the chatroom.
- Come on, Jong Kook. - Hey.
- That's too sad. - That was so mean.
He wasn't in it. I wondered why he wasn't.
Kwang Soo, we don't have a group chatroom, right?
We don't have their numbers.
(We don't have Apink members' phone number.)
I saw them when we filmed together. I don't know what they're up to now.
- That's the worst. - Right. We don't have a chatroom.
We don't have their numbers.
What about your team, Seok Jin?
Apink sent us a song first.
Let me tell you about the first song.
Kwang Soo's part lasted 3 seconds, and mine lasted 6 seconds.
So our parts lasted nine seconds in total.
- I said we couldn't do that. - I thought you were bad singers.
They treated you like bad singers.
When I got the guide track, a woman was singing the song.
And a guy sang next. "Blah blah." That was it.
- "What?" - Oh, no.
- And we'll dance... - Nine seconds are too short.
for 3 minutes and 20 seconds next to them.
(We'll dance for the rest of the song.)
- Are you a dancer or what? - We'll keep dancing.
I'm so sick of dancing!
- I said we couldn't do that. - Dancing...
Hey, things are better with me.
- They gave me a longer part. - That's great.
By the way, Haha's third child was born recently.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
You have a big responsibility.
You'll be crazy about your daughter.
- He's the perfect dad. - He desperately wanted a daughter.
- Yes, I did. - Right.
You're having babies for the sake of Jong Kook too.
- Right. - My gosh.
Thank you.
That's why Jong Kook uploaded a post on his social media account.
- What did he say? - That's right.
He wrote that she should show her boyfriend to him first.
- Right. He did write that. - Once she gets a boyfriend,
I wrote that she should show him to me first.
- I wonder how old he'll be by then. - Right.
He can still probably beat the guy.
Anyway,
I don't know which jerk will be my daughter's boyfriend.
- Why? - He's already hostile.
- He's done for. - He's already hostile.
- She's a baby yet. - We should scare him first.
- And we'll get started. - We can crush him.
Right. He's dead meat.
Now that summer is in full swing,
we've prepared a couples race you'll do with guests today.
- Couples race. - That's nice.
For your information, today will be all of the guests'...
first time to be on our show.
- Really? - That doesn't happen often.
- Right. - Compared to their amazing careers,
- they are not as well-known. - I see.
- So... - Their popularity is low.
There's an actor who was in a movie that sold 16 million tickets.
- Really? - But why wouldn't we know?
- We would know that actor. - And there's a guest who filmed...
- over 60 commercials. - Over 60 commercials?
- That person is a celebrity. - That person must be so famous.
If that person filmed 60, is he or she old?
- What? - Will there be an old celebrity?
If that person filmed a commercial every year...
There's a genius guest who debuted at the age of 11.
- A genius? - At the age of 11?
And there's a guest who was the most searched person online.
- But... - I'd know. I watch TV a lot.
If they are distinguished, we would know them.
- I'm on a lot of social media. - Right.
- I'll bring them in now. - Shall we?
- Please come on in. - All right.
- Who are they? - They'll come out at once.
- Here they are. - Here they come.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(These 4 ladies are on Running Man for the 1st time.)
(Jang Jin Hee, Actress in a popular movie)
(Song Ji In, 60 Commercials)
(Seung Hee, Debutant at the age of 11)
(Rothy, Most searched person online)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
- We recognize some of them. - Right.
I know Seung Hee.
- We know Seung Hee. - We know Seung Hee.
I am so sorry, but I don't know them.
Hey. Just don't say that out loud.
Haha, stop it.
Why don't you introduce yourself first?
Hello, I'm an actress. My name is Song Ji In.
All right!
(Looking innocent and bubbly)
(She already filmed countless ads. Advertisers love this actress.)
(An actress who can pull off a wide array of roles)
- I see. - Right.
- I'm such a fan. - I remember her now.
- I recognize her now. - I'm such a huge fan.
- Others... - You don't know her.
- You don't know her. - I'm a huge fan.
All right. Just like I said earlier, Ji In debuted in 2008...
through Davichi's music video for "Love and War".
- What? - Hey, it's me.
- "Love and War". - I featured in the song.
You don't recognize me?
(He quietly walks out of the frame.)
I featured in the song.
(She hits him hard with a heavy punch.)
Darn it. I don't recognize her at all.
"You don't recognize me?"
You were in a historical drama very recently, right?
- Yes, I was in "Haechi". - Really?
- "Haechi". - Stop pretending to know her.
- "Haechi"? - I told you that.
I told you that.
- I told you that. - Wait.
Isn't Ji In in your agency?
- Yes, she is. - We're in the same agency.
Now, I can put the pieces together.
- I can put the pieces together now. - Hey.
All right. We'll go inside now.
- You got her this gig. - My gosh.
Now, So Min can get people jobs.
- No, no. - This is unbelievable.
- So Min can bring in people? - You are in the same agency?
- That's not true. - I get it.
- Go, So Min! - My goodness.
- Seriously. - Goodness.
- You've crossed paths before. - What?
What? I filmed a commercial with you?
That's why we shouldn't just criticize Haha.
- My gosh. - Gosh.
- You filmed a commercial with her. - He can't remember her.
- You filmed it with her. - When did I...
- When was that? - It was with Lee Young Ae.
(Jae Seok and Ji In in a commercial together)
I see. There she is.
- Lee Young Ae... - I know that commercial.
When we filmed the commercial, "Infinite Challenge" came to film.
- Right. We went to film a show too. - They came too.
You were there too.
(Haha, you were there too.)
Right.
- Hello. - Right.
- It's been a while. - Sure.
- She has a fun story about it. - What was it?
That's when I had just started my career.
I didn't have an agent then.
I went to the set to film the commercial alone.
Go on.
You were sitting down there and eating gimbap.
- I think I remember that. - Go on.
When I said that I came in to check the outfit,
you thought that I was from the advertiser.
You got up right away when you were eating gimbap.
"My gosh."
Did Jae Seok behave like that too?
- Jae Seok. - Did he do that too?
- He gets up quickly too. - You were insecure too.
- He did that? - You used to be insecure too.
- You were insecure. - "How is this outfit?"
- "Is this okay?" - "Shall we go with this?"
"My goodness."
- "I'll do my best." - "Do you not like it?"
Jong Kook wasn't like that before. But he's teasing me a lot lately.
- "Is this okay for you?" - Jae Seok.
- "I'll do my best!" - My goodness.
- I did that? - Yes, you were just like that.
- My goodness. - That's funny.
All right. Let me introduce the next guest to you.
First off, give a round of applause to Jang Jin Hee.
(Looking shy)
(She made a glorious debut as a model at the age of 16.)
(Jang Jin Hee, an actress with the perfect body proportion)
(She was beloved for her role as Ha Kyun's favorite killer...)
(in "Extreme Job" which sold 16 million tickets in theaters.)
("How far should I cut?", Jin Hee's famous line)
You were the killer in "Extreme Job".
- Right. Sun Hee. - By the way,
- Jin Hee. - she'll be a match to Jong Kook.
I can see that.
(Scowling)
She's tall.
- She's the best fighter. - Seriously.
She can do jujitsu and walk like a model.
She debuted at a young age of 16 as a model.
Can you show us your walk?
- My gosh. - Can you walk down from over there?
She's really tall.
- Play the music. - She's cool.
Total girl crush.
(How will the former model walk?)
(Looking chic)
Her posture is different to begin with.
- How could she do that? - Look at her.
She changed completely.
She's so cool.
(Looking confident)
(She turns the spot she's standing on into a runway.)
- Her eyes changed completely. - She's so good.
She was a model indeed.
She's so cool.
Jin Hee, please dance after your walk.
(Smiling)
- She's different. - She has to turn around.
- Her pose is different. - Yes, indeed. She's done it before.
(I'm Jang Jin Hee.)
(Doing a traditional dance)
(Dancing away)
(She comes back to her shy self.)
- She made it fun. - By the way,
- That was impressive. - her walk was different indeed.
- She looked like a foreign model. - Right.
- She did the facial expression too. - How did you change it so quickly?
- She's impressive. - She's cool.
Next.
- She's next to Seung Hee. - My gosh.
I know her.
- You know her? What does she do? - Really?
- She is Shin Seung Hun's... - Yes.
Seung Hun is helping her become a singer.
(She's known as his muse and a hotshot singer.)
This is Rothy.
Hello.
(Rothy is a new singer Shin Seung Hun discovered.)
(Last week, on a TV competition show, )
(her outstanding singing made her go viral online.)
- She must be a great singer... - I guess so.
- Seung Hun... - if he gives her private lessons.
He has high standards.
Could you tell us a few things that your teacher, Seung Hun,
taught you?
As for variety shows...
- He taught you about variety shows? - He taught you...
- about variety shows? - But he's not entertaining.
So he didn't tell me a lot since he's not on variety shows.
- When I'm on music shows, - Okay.
he told me about the jawline of a ballad singer.
He told me to make my jawline stand out.
- His jawline isn't sharp anymore. - Come on, that's enough.
(His jawline isn't sharp anymore.)
- Don't say that. - I saw him recently.
I agree with you on that.
Goodness.
All right. Next.
"We found them, OH MY GIRL."
This is Seung Hee from OH MY GIRL.
(The last guest is Seung Hee from OH MY GIRL.)
(She's the main vocalist in a girl group, full of fairies.)
(Actually, her talent and singing skills...)
(have been confirmed on various TV show at the age of 11.)
(The prodigy singer is joining Running Man today!)
She's the best.
Hello, I'm from OH MY GIRL.
As you all know, she debuted...
- on "National Singing Contest". - Right.
- She was young too. - At the age of 11.
- She was the prodigy singer. - Right. She was.
She used to sing folk songs, so she can turn...
- pop songs into folk songs. - She's good.
Or she can turn children's songs into folk songs.
Can you sing some folk songs?
Which song should I turn into a folk song?
I can change any song.
- Try it with "One Man". - You can change it?
("One Man" is a masterpiece ballad song. How will it sound?)
(There's a man)
Oh, goodness.
(He loves you dearly)
- That sounded to sorrowful. - "Loves you dearly".
Did you hear her lilting voice?
- That sounded so colorful. - She'd be great with trot songs.
She loves animals to the point that her hobby is watching animal videos.
Are there any animals that resemble us?
Kwang Soo stands out the most since he's the tallest.
- There's a monkey named sifaka. - What?
(That's Kwang Soo's lookalike.)
- What? - She scared me for a second.
- I was so shocked just now. - That was the name.
- What? - It was a weird name.
- What did she say? - It suits him so well.
- Does that really exist? - How does that monkey look?
- A sifaka monkey. - It's a white monkey.
I know which one she's talking about.
(Unable to talk)
- What about me? - Nutria.
You? You resemble your mother.
(You? You resemble your mother.)
- You're the spitting image of her. - When you asked that question...
When you asked that question,
you were trying to look handsome. That was so annoying.
- That was so annoying. - Seriously. He's...
- He's unbelievable. - He tried to look handsome.
You wanted to look handsome.
- He looks just like nutria. - I totally agree.
However, I always say this.
I really believe that there must be...
- a lot of opportunities... - Yes, there must be.
- for these talented individuals. - Right.
They don't have a lot of chances to show their talent these days.
Today, a prize and a penalty are at stake on this couples race.
Before we start the race, you will pair up first.
To decide your partners, you'll cast the Talent Dice.
The female members will receive a dice with photos...
of the male members on each side.
Everyone will challenge to win the talent the female members...
submitted beforehand.
If the female member wins her own talent match,
she can choose a male member that she wants.
But if she loses, the winner can switch two of the photos...
on the dice.
We can switch the photo stickers.
- Ladies, please take your dice. - Okay.
Go ahead and take it.
My gosh, there are no male guests.
(She talks to herself very loudly.)
We're here. You have us.
Since there are no male guests today,
Ji Hyo and So Min seem...
- I don't feel motivated. - look exhausted all of a sudden.
Come on, cheer us up.
But I do feel sorry.
What do you mean?
Their side dishes aren't that attractive.
Side dishes? Don't call us that.
All right. To play this game,
- you wrote down your talent. - Yes.
We're going to reveal one at a time.
- Yes. - Who wants to draw first?
- So Min, do you want to go first? - Me?
- So Min's talent must be in there. - Exactly.
(If she wins the talent match, she can switch the photos herself.)
I'm curious about her talent.
I read what she wrote down.
- It was hilarious. - So Min...
- So Min has a lot of talents. - What?
- What is it? - I picked this one.
What is it? What are you good at?
I chose my own.
"Happy Virus"?
(So Min's Talent: Happy Virus)
- What do you mean by that? - Well, I can make you laugh...
in five seconds.
(That's my talent.)
- How? - You can make us laugh?
- I won't laugh. I don't laugh. - Isn't this too hard?
This is hard.
It's hard to make us laugh after saying that you will.
If you're going to give this a try,
you can challenge So Min at this talent match.
But So Min has to choose one person...
and make that person laugh in five seconds.
Jae Seok.
(I choose Jae Seok.)
I think he's going to laugh more easily.
- Right. He does laugh easily. - He can't hold it back.
- I can hold out if I wanted. - He's already laughing.
You can do it if you put your mind to it.
- Give it a try. - He's already laughing.
- It's funny that she'd try this. - Is that so?
(Why would an actress try to make us laugh?)
- I mean... Hold on. - How can she be so gutsy?
Why would she?
Even comedians don't do this a lot.
(Even comedians don't do this a lot.)
Even the professionals don't do stuff like this. They don't.
Why would professionals set this up?
(No professionals would declare to be funny.)
It's ridiculous how she called herself Happy Virus.
Are you sure you can pull it off?
Yes, I am sure.
Don't be disappointed when I don't laugh.
- I'm serious. - I can do this.
Jae Seok, come closer. No, come closer.
- I'll lower the card and start. - Okay.
- Look at my face closely. - Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Flaring her nostrils)
(Well, this is...)
- Come on. - What was that?
(He was looking at So Min's face up close.)
(Her nostrils knock him down.)
- What was that? - What?
- How did that work? - Why did you laugh at that?
- She just flared her nostrils. - Hey.
She was right in front of me. She did this right in front of me.
(Did you see that?)
- Look at that. She's... - Is that funny?
It's your fault for laughing at that.
- Seok Jin, you should try it. - Try it on me.
- Do it on me. - Go ahead.
- Look. - Okay.
She was...
- Goodness. What's wrong with her? - Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3. - She's so weird.
(Can So Min make Seok Jin laugh?)
What if he falls in love with her?
(What if he falls in love with her?)
- Seok Jin, why did you turn red? - Hey!
Why did your face turn red?
- Why did you get red? - "Pounding, pounding".
- Seok Jin lifted his heels. - Stop that.
- What's wrong with you? - Nothing is wrong with me.
Why do you... Why do you keep turning red?
- I didn't laugh. What is it? - Seok Jin.
- You guys are the weird ones. - Seriously.
All of a sudden, you close your eyes.
(He keeps cornering Seok Jin.)
(The new love interest is important, not verifying the talent.)
Happy Virus.
- All right. - It should've been Laughter Virus.
So Min succeeded for now.
- I did it. - So Min succeeded.
- I'll try it. - You'll try it?
(Which member will Rothy pick?)
I can choose? I'll choose you.
- Me? - Yes.
(You'll try to make me laugh?)
Comedians don't laugh if they set their mind to it.
- Can you step back and do it? - I can just do anything.
(Se Chan tries to keep a safe distance.)
- I can just do anything. - Wait.
- Come here. - I know for sure.
He'll laugh if she says she loves him.
He'll laugh if she says that. Look. He's already laughing.
- He laughed when I said it. - Stop it.
- He laughed when I said it. - Please stop it.
- I'm going to hide my gums. - Tell him you love him.
Rothy. First, face the back and turn around like this.
Like this?
- Use your hair. - Hit him with your hair.
Show me.
(Show me your gums.)
(Will she be able to make Se Chan, the man who never laughs, laugh?)
(Laughing)
(At Rothy's tactic with her hair, )
(he shows her his gums.)
(That's it. Well done.)
- Hey. - I can't help it.
- I'm so disappointed. - I can't help it.
- I'm happy. What can I do? - Hey.
You should have flared your nostrils like So Min.
(She tries her cute moves on Se Chan.)
She didn't do anything.
I laughed at her because it was ridiculous.
(Rothy beats So Min and wins with the help of Haha.)
Does anyone want to give it a go?
Perhaps, I shouldn't have. Kwang Soo.
(Jin Hee will try to make Kwang Soo laugh.)
Okay.
Kwang Soo is good at holding back.
- I'm good at that. - He's good at that.
(Can she make Kwang Soo laugh?)
- I'll be really objective. - Why are you so far away?
- But you know, he's... - Yes?
I'll give you a tip.
- He laughs when he's in pain. - What?
(Whispering)
- He laughs when he's hurt. - In that case,
can I make him cry in five seconds?
(She sounds so innocent.)
- You'll make him cry? - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo looks nervous.
- Are you going to hit him? - You'll make him cry?
- She'll make me shed tears? - She'll hurt you.
Jin Hee, can you tell me what you're planning to do?
I'll do a low kick.
Where are you pointing at?
(Kwang Soo is sensitive.)
(Flinching)
- Where will your low kick land on? - Jin Hee.
- Within five seconds... - Shouldn't she make him laugh?
Aren't you supposed to make him laugh within five seconds?
- He said he laughs when he's hurt. - I see.
Well, I've gotten a lot of kicks before.
(She's ready to launch her low kick.)
I'll try it now.
Kwang Soo is good at enduring the pain.
I've gotten a lot of kicks before.
(Can Jin Hee make Kwang Soo laugh with her low kick?)
Here I go.
(Kicking hard)
(Screaming and laughing)
He laughed. Kwang Soo laughed.
That must've hurt.
Jin Hee wins.
I could feel his pain.
Are you sure he laughed?
It surely must be a virus. He's still smiling.
Doesn't the person who smiles the longest win?
You're right.
It's fun.
He keeps smiling.
Jin Hee won.
She won.
You can remove two stickers from So Min's die...
and switch them with others' faces.
She'll remove the people she wants to partner up with, right?
That's right.
- This... - She's looking at you.
(She removes Kwang Soo's face.)
- I need to remove 2, right? - Yes, 1 more.
(She removes Jong Kook's face.)
She took the good ones.
Whose faces would you like?
- Mister Seok Jin and... - Why?
(She picks Seok Jin.)
She called you mister.
- And? - Seok Jin and...
- Oh, 2 of his? - You want 2 of his?
- Yes. - What?
Is that possible?
- I'll end up with him. - Hey.
Their relationship is hilarious.
This is something new.
There are so many pictures of Seok Jin on my die. Look.
Ji In, please pick.
(She will pick the second talent.)
- "Thigh Wrestling". - Who wrote this?
- Who was it? - Who was it?
Me.
- You? - Yes.
She's really good at squeezing.
How good is she?
(Her squeezes are suffocating.)
(They force you to kneel down.)
- Yes, she is strong. - This is...
I think Jin Hee will beat her.
Let's try Ji Hyo's talent, "Thigh Wrestling".
If it's another female member, they can have a match.
If a male member wants to compete,
they must carry her on their back while she squeezes their sides.
- My gosh. - You'll win...
- That's impossible. - if you can withstand five seconds.
Ji Hyo and Jin Hee can have a match.
This is going to be a big match.
But you see, Ji Hyo is really strong.
I'm curious.
(Ji Hyo the Destroyer is a champion.)
(No one could withstand her squeezes.)
(Everyone kneeled before her.)
I bet she'll be no match for Jin Hee.
- Me too. - I think so.
(She's full of muscles and experience.)
(Who else needs to laugh?)
Perhaps, it's because she's wearing black,
but she looks much stronger...
- than usual. - Right.
Get ready.
(Ji Hyo will attack first.)
(Will she still be the champion or will Jin Hee take her spot?)
Set, go.
(The match begins.)
(Squeezing)
- Ji Hyo, go. - Please use your strength.
- Ji Hyo. - Is she doing it?
- Ji Hyo. - Focus.
- I don't think... - Ji Hyo.
Don't joke around.
- Ji Hyo. - This is your game.
- Don't joke around. - You came up with this game.
If you were going to lose, why did you choose it?
Done.
Let's switch positions.
- You can counterattack. - Show us.
- You can withstand it. - You can.
- You can. - If you do, it'll be a draw.
Ji Hyo, you need to withstand it.
Get ready.
Ji Hyo, squeeze.
(Will she be able to save face?)
Squeeze. Set, go.
(Ji Hyo will be defending now.)
(Her legs spread immediately.)
(They're shocked.)
She's so strong.
She's a beast!
She's shocked.
She's insane!
That's it. Jin Hee wins.
(Jin Hee wins both rounds.)
Hey.
She had no idea someone so strong would come out.
Jin Hee must be extremely strong.
She'll remove all the stickers.
Did she win the entire game?
- She's too strong. - I know.
- She's like a bullfrog. - A bullfrog?
She's upgraded her level.
She's at the highest level.
She's too strong.
Then how about the men compete?
- Show us. - Show us, Ji Hyo.
If we can withstand it, can we switch their partners?
- Yes. - Right.
(If they win, they can switch the stickers on her die.)
Like this.
(Squeezing)
(He falls immediately.)
I heard something break.
- He's smiling again. - Are you okay?
It's the virus again!
- It is! - It's scary!
It's happening again.
Where did that sound come from?
He's laughing so often today.
Then...
Kwang Soo is a bit...
- Should I do it? - Will it hurt?
- Does it really hurt? - Okay.
This is okay.
- If I can... - Withstand?
- withstand it, - Here.
I can switch the stickers, right?
- Yes, you can switch Ji Hyo's. - Got it.
You should be able to carry her first.
Can you even carry me?
(She provokes him.)
- Can you even carry me? - Of course.
Come on.
He has his pride, you know?
- He's strong. - He's still a man.
You almost hurt my feelings.
What if he falls ill tomorrow?
My gosh.
Did you hear him grunt?
(Staggering)
Smile. Smile.
- My gosh. - Put your legs around him.
Get ready.
- Get ready. - Have we not begun yet?
Ready, set, go.
(Squeezing)
No, no!
(She just squeezed a little bit.)
(Screaming)
(Rolling)
Oh, no! Smile!
- Happy virus! - He's smiling!
- That's good! It's the virus! - Hey.
Everyone is smiling today.
My gosh!
- I almost died! - Don't die!
- She must be so strong. - I'm curious.
- I almost died! - I know how you feel.
Is it that bad?
How bad is this?
- He said, "No, no!" - Se Chan.
- This is... - It's crazy.
Your ribs might shatter.
It's like 100 anacondas are squeezing you.
Try it.
I was shocked.
- Oh, hold on. - Wait.
(As soon as he carries her, it feels ominous.)
- My gosh. - I was shocked here as well.
(He can sympathize with him.)
- Right? - Once you carry her,
you get shocked.
- You think the game has started. - Really?
My gosh.
- Try your best. - It hasn't started yet.
- My gosh. - He's quite resilient.
You're right.
Get ready, set, go.
(Squeezing)
- What was that? - He collapsed.
Get ready, set, go.
(He couldn't withstand 0.1 seconds and collapse.)
He's smiling.
- It's really painful. - It's the happy virus.
- How bad is it? - My gosh.
Your ribs might break.
- Jae Seok. - Why are you getting up there?
- Why? - Why do you keep climbing?
(She climbs on top of the stool as if nothing happened.)
(Why do you keep climbing?)
You can barely breathe.
- Come on. - Try it, then.
- Try it. - You can barely breathe.
I almost swore.
(Seok Jin disappears from the monitor.)
(He fails to pass the 1st obstacle.)
(He gets on all fours like a sinner.)
- Go home. - It's over.
That's the end.
- I'm done. - It's over.
Some may think we're overreacting.
- Tell the producer to try it. - Seriously.
- Come here, Bo Pil. - Hurry.
- Come here. - Since we're entertainers,
some might think that we're overreacting.
- Try it and see for yourself. - Try it.
Express only what you feel.
Don't pretend.
- He's known to be honest. - You're right.
You should bend your knees a bit.
My gosh.
He's not the type to show a lot of reactions.
- Get ready. - Get ready.
Get ready, set, go.
(Screaming)
(He lets out a single cry and collapses.)
(Thanks to his genuine response, the happy virus spreads even more.)
That didn't last long.
He collapsed.
Take the day off and go home.
He just got married.
That was a genuine reaction.
- His cry was so sincere. - You're right.
Jin Hee wins this round as well.
She won again.
You can remove the faces on Ji Hyo's die.
- Ji Hyo's. - She's incredible.
- She removed Se Chan's face. - Se Chan.
Kwang Soo.
She picked Kwang Soo every time.
Whose face would you like to add to her die?
Jae Seok's.
Mine?
Two of my faces will be attached to Ji Hyo's die.
Shall we move on?
Jin Hee has been winning every time.
- You're on the lead. - She's amazing.
Seriously.
- Jin Hee. - No one can beat her.
(The third talent is...)
- "Unusual Children's Song"? - "Unusual Children's Song"?
Whose is this?
- It's mine. - It's yours?
(This is Seung Hee's talent.)
- What is this? - It's fascinating.
Literally, it's about a children's song.
It's a North Korean song called "Peekaboo".
- Peekaboo? - Yes.
- That sounds cute. - Shall we see the video first?
Shall we?
(It sure does look unusual.)
- It's the one with kids. - What does it mean?
- What does it mean? - I know this.
She's so cute.
(I come home cheerfully)
(The cute movements are key.)
This is hilarious.
(Says peekaboo to me)
She's so cute.
- How cute. - How cute.
(The girl is so cute.)
That was so adorable.
- How cute. - My goodness.
- My gosh! - How cute.
- She's so pretty. - How do we do this?
How cute.
- Do we need to mimic her? - She is adorable.
- Are we mimicking her? - It suits her.
- Yes. - Right?
- Here we go. - OH MY GIRL.
(Seung Hee goes first.)
(Singing)
(I carry a rabbit backpack)
(She's exactly like the girl.)
She's so adorable.
(He smiles at her like a dad would.)
(Says peekaboo to me)
She was so cute.
This is the highlight.
(It doesn't look cute when he does it.)
- That was so adorable. - How do we beat her?
How... Gosh, she's brave.
I bet So Min's ready.
- You're right. - Can you do it?
- Can you? - I think I can.
She's good at such things.
- How did it go again? - She's good at such things.
(Wriggling)
Why does she look so unctuous?
(It's definitely different.)
Do it in your own style.
[VIU Ver] SBS E461 Running Man
"The Couple Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
She doesn't want to lose.
(She takes a firm stand until the end.)
She has to dance too.
(Says peekaboo to me)
(I'd like to unsee that.)
(Shaking his head)
- Did it work? No? - How about Ji Hyo?
- I look forward to this one. - Ji Hyo.
- Go for it. - Ji Hyo.
- You have to act cute. - You need to focus.
Think back to first grade.
I'm an elementary student.
- An elementary student. - That's right.
You're five years old.
(Brainwashing herself to become an elementary student.)
That's right.
(She is possessed into an elementary student.)
Wearing my rabbit
Gosh, I can't watch this.
I skip
What's wrong with her?
Anyway, she has to finish the song.
- Seriously, what's wrong? - Guys, it's all right.
Says peekaboo to me
(Says peekaboo to me)
(A mix of cuteness and awfulness)
But you made it.
- Hey. - You're almost 40 years old.
Seriously.
You shouldn't do that. Your age ends with a nine.
When you were doing this...
You're right.
I thought you were asking for a cigarette.
- Everyone. - I was asking for two.
- Let's vote on this one. - Okay.
- I vote Seung Hee. - I vote Seung Hee.
- Seung Hee. - I vote Seung Hee.
Seung Hee wins this round.
(Seung Hee is the winner for this talent.)
That was an obvious one.
You can't beat that.
Who would you like to swap, Seung Hee?
I choose Se Chan and...
- Jong Kook. - She chose Jong Kook.
She chose Se Chan and Jong Kook.
Thank you.
Now, it's Rothy's turn who's also known as Kang Joo Hee.
- It's my turn. - Rothy.
Joo Hee.
- Mimicking a singer. - Mimicking a singer.
(The next talent that Rothy picked is to mimic singers.)
Who's talent is this?
It's her own.
It's Rothy's.
(Rothy's talent is to mimic singers.)
- Are you good at that too? - Sounds fun.
- Her talent. - I see.
Who are you going to mimic?
First, I'll mimic IU.
(She mimics IU first.)
When she first made her debut,
she had that fresh voice of a rookie...
- and had a sweet voice too. - You're right.
The main point you have to grasp is to tell yourself...
- that you're the cutest. - Sounds good.
- I'll give it a go. - Go for it.
In 1,2,3...
Marshmallow
- Marshmallow - She sounds very similar.
It's so sweet
(She sounds just like IU.)
(The freshness of IU as a rookie and an enthusiastic voice...)
(is the main point of "Marshmallow")
Marshmallow
(She mimics IU perfectly.)
(Synchronised 200 percent)
They sound similar.
You sound exactly like her.
- Who else can you mimic? - Show us more.
- Show us, Joo Hee. - There's no end to it.
- Who? - Soyou.
Soyou.
The half air and half sound technique.
Soyou tends to give a twist with her falsetto.
They call it the falsetto of afterlife.
- Afterlife? - Falsetto of afterlife.
(What is the falsetto of afterlife?)
These days it feels like you're mine
It seems like
You're mine but not
(That's the falsetto of another world.)
I get what you mean.
You can barely hear it.
When you're just about to enter another world.
(The high-pitched voice...)
(aims for another world.)
(A skilled song mimicker is born.)
Goodness.
- I didn't expect that. - I get it.
- You got this. - Good job.
That was good.
- She's good. - Well done.
- She's good. - She's something.
Do you have more, Joo Hee?
With Hwasa, you need a sexy voice.
- Yes. - I like your explanations.
- You need to be briefed first. - You have to...
throw your voice downwards.
- As if you're messing around. - That's right.
(Mimicking Hwasa's singing)
(I'm looking forward to this.)
She's doing it.
(Stupid)
(She sounds more like Hwasa than Hwasa.)
She won again.
- Hey. - Wait.
- She's so good. - You're good.
- You're good. - Stupid
- She's good. - Stupid
- She's good. - I loved it.
- I loved it. - That was fun.
(So Min can't miss out on this.)
So Min, why don't you give it a try?
- You choose to mimic IU. - Like how you were taught.
Try to sound the same.
(Rothy shows an example first.)
Give it a go.
She's doing it.
(Stupid)
You really looked stupid.
- You looked stupid. - I thought that was Joo Hyun.
"You fool!"
(Stupid! You fool!)
That was it.
Would someone like to compete against her?
- This is... - It's impossible to beat.
You can't go against this.
It's unbeatable.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Joo Hee. - Joo Hee.
My goodness.
- What a relief. - Rothy.
- Well, that was... - Can I just take it off?
- "Stupid". - You won with that one word.
- Stupid - A lot of talented people.
- I'm jealous. - She took off Jong Kook.
She chose Jong Kook.
Last time when Seung Hun asked me this favor,
I gladly promoted your new song. Didn't you know?
- She stuck it back on. - That was sudden.
What are you doing so suddenly?
- You can't do that. - You can take it off.
- Why did you do that? - You can take it off.
- What's wrong with you? - I'm just messing with you.
- He won't lay a finger on you. - "Didn't you know?"
- Rothy... - This is difficult.
It's difficult, but you chose me straightaway.
(It's difficult, but you chose me straightaway.)
- Hey. - That was so abrupt.
Choose another one.
- It's mine. - She chose Jae Seok.
- Okay. - I choose Kwang Soo and Se Chan.
Se Chan is popular.
Kwang Soo and Se Chan.
- Thank you. - We have two more left to go.
We have two left.
Whose talent is "before and after"?
It's mine.
(Ji In's talent, Before and After)
It's the theatre of situations.
(Talent from shooting over 60 adverts)
This is before.
(Before using fabric deodorizer)
And after?
(The perfect act of the after situation.)
(The expressions that we saw from adverts.)
Are you trying to extend your advert contract?
(Haha catches why Ji In decided to do it as her talent.)
(Her goal is to extend her contract.)
She's trying to look good for the advertiser.
- I remember it. - She wants a call from them.
She did a good job.
Ji In did a good job with this.
Let's come to the conclusion and let Ji In be the winner.
- This is the last one. - Yes.
- What's "arm talent"? - Arm talent.
(Jin Hee can cross back her arms and let her fingers touch.)
That is no joke.
Try it, So Min. I think you'll be able to do it.
- Hold it up here. - You're quite close.
Hold it there.
Doesn't this look risque?
Why is your hand down here?
(PG19 hand movement)
(Why is your hand down here?)
Goodness.
Can you push it down?
Seok Jin can do it.
- Can he? - Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin can do it?)
I'm doing it.
Stay still.
(A successful illusion)
Seok Jin.
You're a true comedian.
- I was taken aback. - They're alive.
- So now... - What happens to Jin Hee?
Jin Hee is the winner again.
(Jin Hee is a true conman, winning 3 games out of 6.)
We will start throwing the dice which will decide your partners.
- Rothy. - Rothy can go first.
- Rothy. - In 1, 2, 3.
(A male member who will become Rothy's partner is...)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
Lee Kwang Soo is out now.
Seok Jin is all over this dice.
- So Min, just come here. - Seok Jin.
- Jee Seok Jin. - Yang Se Chan.
Yang Se Chan.
(With 50 percent chance, nothing has changed.)
(Seok Jin is chosen.)
- Hey. - Well...
- You had no choice. - I'm satisfied.
I'll accept it quickly.
Get together as teams and we'll start introducing the games.
All I know is that our team will win all the games.
You have no rival in the world.
Winners will get a prize but losers will receive a big penalty.
It's a couple race where you stay together to survive,
but get apart if you want to do better alone.
I want to do better alone.
You have to get apart from each other?
There will be a total 4 rounds with 6 couples.
Every round, the winning couple will select a prize badge...
while the losers will select a penalty badge.
When the whole game finishes,
you will minus the number of penalty badge from the prize badge.
The winning team will receive a Korean beef set...
and be exempted from the penalty.
- Exempted from the penalty. - Korean beef set.
- Let's have some Korean beef. - I'm excited about this.
On the other hand, the losing team...
will choose another team...
to go through the penalty together.
You have to be nice to each other.
I'm worried that people will want to choose you.
- You're the problem. - They will choose you.
We will reveal the video that shows the penalty.
- Why are you doing this? - There's a video?
What is it that they even prepared a video clip for this?
Come on.
- What? - My goodness.
- What? - What is it?
(The penalty of the losing couple and the chosen couple.)
Where are you going up until?
- That's so high. - That's too high.
Don't you do that to practice your skydive?
Gosh.
Really?
(Indoor skydiving)
(The high-tech penalty that is perfect for cowardly members.)
(Which two couples will have to go through this?)
Were they screaming?
Is it safe for your bones?
But...
How are we supposed to do that?
You'll be able to experience what skydiving is like.
Losers will have to complete the indoor skydive.
Indoor skydiving?
Don't you bump into walls?
We will move to our first location.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(Today's first mission with prizes and penalties.)
What is this?
- What is this? - What's going on today?
This is the first mission that will give you the chance to obtain...
a prize badge. "Endure the weight if you want the prize."
Yes, endure the weight.
You will team up with two other couples.
A male member from each team will lie down on the benches.
The female member will have to bring as many objects...
within two minutes and place it on top of the male member.
We will only measure the total weight...
of the objects that are placed on top of the body.
- Objects that are on the body? - That's correct.
We have to endure that weight.
However, a couple from each team can distract the male members...
and tickle their feet.
Objects that have fallen off the body will be excluded.
I'm sure Jae Seok won't be able to win this game.
Let's first divide you into two groups.
(Jae-Ha-Kwang versus Seok-Jong-Se)
Will one couple from each team please step forward?
It hurts.
- It really hurts. - Get ready.
I know where to poke.
Don't lift your leg up.
- We didn't poke you yet. - It hurts.
We didn't do anything yet.
Okay.
How can I grab them?
Like this.
I can't stack anything if he's here.
- You can't be there. - Hey.
You can't be here.
(Move! Jong Kook kicks Kwang Soo's butt as a punishment.)
Like I said, you can't be here.
- Oh, dear. - Move.
(Why does he let himself get targeted like that?)
Are you sure about this?
It's still possible, right?
Be my guest then.
(His butt gets punished again.)
Be my guest.
- Go ahead. - Okay. I'll try another way.
- I won't do that. - No?
I trust you, Kwang Soo.
You'll only play a single game.
Get ready...
(Ji In and Ji Hyo will go head to head.)
(They only have 2 minutes.)
Go, Ji In!
(Tightly grabbing)
(Ji Hyo starts off by stopping her opponent.)
(What?)
(Things are getting wilder.)
(Is this how it's supposed to be?)
Be careful, guys.
What's going on? Guys?
Guys, what are you doing?
Make sure you win!
(Song Ji In versus Song Ji Hyo)
What's gotten into you two?
What is this?
(Everyone forgets about the game and watch them.)
What are you doing?
Somebody please stop them.
(It's a new interpretation of the game.)
- What... - Be careful.
What are you two doing?
Just go and get the items!
(After fighting for the better spot, they go over to the items.)
(Ji Hyo, hurry!)
That's it.
Wait, why are you grabbing that?
- My gosh. - Stack them up.
- Come on. - What a mess.
(Ji In isn't good at playing games though.)
Hold on. At least let my face show!
(The first item covers Haha's face.)
It hurts!
(Just then)
(Ji Hyo brings in a mattress.)
Stack it on you.
Still... Okay, you're good.
(We should make it harder for him!)
- It hurts! - What now?
Kwang Soo's in the way.
Hold on.
Fine, I won't do it!
Rothy, don't. Hey, we've stopped.
We won't do it anymore.
(Why? Just do what you want.)
(Haha screams and makes a big fuss.)
It hurts.
How can this hurt? Stop lying.
It's only a feather.
It's a feather!
How can a feather hurt?
What do you think you're doing? Where did she go?
Hey, it's a ballpoint pen.
It's really a pen.
(They thought it was rubber.)
That's why I said it hurts!
I said it hurts!
It was a pen all along.
(So he wasn't faking it.)
(Both teams only have 5 seconds left.)
Don't help the items stay on there.
(Ji Hyo even stacked an iron pot.)
- One! - Time's up.
(Both ladies did their best during the 2 minutes.)
Time's up.
Time's up. Stop.
- There we go. - You have to stop now.
I'm not holding onto them.
- Look. - My gosh.
I see a similar amount.
Do we just weigh these?
Help her with the other end.
(He breathes fresh air for the first time in 2 minutes.)
Are you sure this is how the game is played?
(The sole of his foot is a mess.)
Unbelievable.
A few holes have been drilled.
It was good for blood circulation though.
It's good for your health.
Do you know...
what we should focus on though?
At the beginning, Ji Hyo and Ji In...
- really went for it. - I know.
- It was for real. - Yes, it was.
- They meant it. - It was truly on.
It began here, but the game continued over there.
They weren't kidding.
I haven't seen girls fight like this since middle school.
I don't know which schools they're from,
but the two best fighters went head to head.
(I'm the best in this neighborhood.)
Jin Hee just laughed though with her arms crossed.
(When the two of them went for it, Jin Hee laughed.)
(They seem adorable.)
(The real winner is yet to be revealed.)
Here's the last one.
You didn't stack much.
We managed 81kg.
(Jae-Ha-Kwang managed 81kg.)
(Ji Hyo must've stacked more items to win.)
(What's the result?)
65.5kg.
(Seok-Jong-Se managed 65.5kg.)
(81kg versus 65.5kg)
(Jae-Ha-Kwang wins!)
(We lost.)
(We lost, but it was a good game.)
Good job.
What time is it?
Rothy!
It doesn't end here.
The winning three teams...
will choose the prize OX card.
The losing three teams...
will choose the penalty OX card.
(What do these cards mean?)
What are these OX cards?
Let me give you an example.
Every time you win, you will choose a prize OX card.
If all three teams choose O card,
then you'll all receive a prize badge.
If you all choose an X card,
you will receive nothing.
If one couple choose a different card,
no matter what that card is,
that couple will receive two prize badges...
while the others receive nothing.
- We might not receive anything. - Exactly.
- Meanwhile... - Kwang Soo, gosh.
The losing three couples will also choose a card.
If all three couples chooses X card,
then you'll all receive a penalty badge.
If you all choose O card,
you'll receive nothing.
That will never happen though.
However, if one team chooses a different card,
that couple will receive a prize badge instead.
You can win a prize badge even if you lose.
The other two couples will receive two penalty badges.
The options are very tempting today.
It's all about not being greedy.
(Being the odd one out will be rewarding.)
(O or X Card Choice Scenario)
Does everyone remember the rules?
- X, X, and O. - The team with a different card...
will receive two prize badges.
I'm sure that team will lose.
Just look at Kwang Soo.
This is what we should choose.
I'll hold onto this one.
(Kwang Soo emits a feeling of betrayal.)
We should choose O card for now.
Doesn't it look like Jin Hee's warming up?
(Kwang Soo, take a look.)
She's a human weapon.
(The human weapon awaits to punish the traitor.)
What will you do if I choose O card?
- Jin Hee? - That should be your only choice.
- Can you kick up high? - A high kick?
- Show him. - Okay.
That'll really hurt.
- Even I'm scared. - She only needs to kick once.
Let us discuss again.
Let's just each win a badge.
You know what that kick will do to you.
(Screeching)
- What's that? - The sound you'll make.
- That's how I'll sound? - Yes.
I heard a wailing sound.
Kwang Soo, don't give in so easily.
You shouldn't get scared on TV like this.
(Kwang Soo, I know you're a decent man.)
(Kwang Soo's biggest dilemma)
All right then. In 1...
(Receiving two badges alone can save them from receiving a penalty.)
(Will Kwang Soo choose to be loyal instead?)
- In 1... - In 1, 2, 3!
Show it to the camera.
(Haha and Ji In, Jae Seok and Jin Hee)
(Kwang Soo and Rothy)
- They chose X card. - Who?
(Kwang Soo and Rothy betrayed the others.)
So you chose X card.
I knew it.
- He chose X card. - It's an X card.
He chose the X card.
I knew it. He's in the lead now.
- He's in the lead now. - You're right.
He's in the lead.
I tagged him on social media with this phrase,
but he earned his money by betraying people.
(He's earning money by betraying others yet again.)
This is his job, so we should understand.
You three should choose your cards too.
We've already made our choice.
No one's hitting anyone on our side.
No one will receive a penalty badge if we all choose O card.
Let's keep the peace.
Are you ready? One...
Be kind and generous. Only O card is the right choice.
- Let's be a team. - In 1, 2,
and 3, show the camera.
(Only Seok Jin and So Min chose X card.)
- See? - What happened?
(The other two teams receive 2 penalty badges.)
What did I tell you?
Congratulations!
(Betrayal is everywhere just like a normal day in Running Man.)
I should've changed it at the last minute.
The couple in the last place will choose...
another couple to receive the penalty too.
- They'll choose another couple? - Right.
- They'll choose? - I see.
So one can be a target.
- Let's head to our next location. - Let's go!
(What other mission awaits them this time?)
Let's go!
- Are we off to eat? - Let's go, everybody.
Okay, everybody.
- Okay, Okay. - Okay, everybody.
Seung Hee, your mouth is getting similar to Se Chan's.
Right?
Seriously?
Is that how far my mouth sticks out?
She apologized.
Se Chan's popular among the ladies.
- What? - The ladies...
I was popular among women at that age as well.
- So Min. - Yes?
You're one of them.
- Me? You think I like Se Chan? - Yes.
(She likes him!)
- So Min likes him. - As if.
You like him.
Do I?
- What do you like about him? - Guys, stop it.
You're making Seok Jin jealous.
She's supposed to be having a love line with Seok Jin.
I'm not sure if it will work out, though.
Our country isn't that...
It's not that open.
I've been doing variety shows for a long time,
- but I've never done one like this. - It's a first.
- It's a first. - I've never seen it on TV.
So Min actually...
- does have feelings for Se Chan. - She likes him.
I personally think they look cute together.
- No. - No.
They don't look cute together.
Are you getting jealous?
I'm not even saying anything.
(I'm not even saying anything.)
And So Min can't make Se Chan fall for her.
- Me? - Yes.
Me? I'm just not trying.
Really? Can you seduce him?
Will he fall for you if you try?
I can seduce him in a day.
(I can seduce him in a day.)
Just one day.
Haha,
- I can say for sure... - Hey.
that it will only take me half a day.
Come over to my place later on.
(Come over to my place later on!)
(They will open up a seducing class after the shoot.)
I'll show you.
- How exciting. - I'm dumbfounded.
So Min's family really likes Se Chan.
- Her mother really likes him. - Yes.
My mom thinks of all single men...
as a candidate for my spouse.
- What about Jong Kook? - She really likes...
- She likes him. - Jong Kook.
What about Kwang Soo?
(So Min's mother's favorite is Jong Kook.)
- She likes him. - What about Kwang Soo?
Wook Min really likes him.
- Her little brother. - I think men...
- like him in particular. - I know why Wook Min likes him.
- Why? - It's nice to know a naive guy.
(It's nice to know a naive guy.)
It is.
I'm not naive!
Wook Min would feel pressured around me.
Yes, he's a bit difficult.
He could even talk him into buying him a new gym.
(They move on to the new mission with the naive Kwang Soo.)
It's nice to know a guy like him.
A pushover.
(The next mission and lunch await them at the restaurant.)
We will have lunch at an all-you-can-eat barbecue place.
Wow, I used to love pork ribs when I was young.
It smells so good.
(All-you-can-eat pork ribs with its amazing partner naengmyeon.)
- Isn't this crazy? - Naengmyeon with grilled meat.
This is amazing!
Don't cut the noodles.
- Is it pork ribs? - Yes.
(Yummy)
(At the same time...)
(The three teams have to watch them eat.)
This is driving me crazy.
The next mission...
is called "Telepathic Four-Letter Words".
"Four-Letter Words"?
- Say... - Hello.
(They will take turns to say a 4-letter word with the initials.)
Crazy!
(They have great chemistry.)
- Pacific ocean... - It is.
- Kitchen... - Towel.
- Butterfly... - Effect.
(Correct)
- Battle of... - Yeonpyeong.
She knows that?
Jong Kook, Haha, and Se Chan's teams...
can begin eating all they want.
Okay!
(That is how they were able to have a great meal.)
I'm so happy!
The smell is driving me crazy.
Pork ribs taste best on top of rice.
Dipped in doenjang jjigae.
That's good.
(A piece of grilled meat with seasoned green onions)
- Ji Hyo, did you know that... - Hey!
(Hey! Stop that!)
I was flipping it for you.
I was flipping it so you could enjoy it.
- I'm going to flip you over. - I wouldn't eat...
(I'm going to flip you over.)
(Startled)
- You're being so mean. - Don't even think about it.
- Leave it. - You're being so mean.
I was always like this.
Now, a plate full of meat...
and this.
Do what you wanted to do.
(A plate of pork ribs and naengmyeon)
Get kicked by Jin Hee, and you can take this.
- Okay. - "Get kicked"?
I'll get kicked.
Go ahead, Jin Hee.
But you're on the same team.
She'll go easy on you.
I've been kicked by Bo Mi and many others,
but she's worse than you can ever imagine.
(She's worse than you can ever imagine.)
Fine, Jin Hee.
- It's going to hurt. - He's really going to get kicked.
- I'm ready to kick. - Okay, kick.
I'll kick.
He's trembling.
(How hard will Jin Hee's kick be?)
(Smack)
Gosh...
- Gosh... - I was so surprised!
I think she kicked his bone.
Help me.
Jae Seok.
(This looks like...)
- Gosh, gosh. - "Gosh".
(His thoughts on Jin Hee's kick, "Gosh".)
- Gosh. - I approve. I really do.
Gosh...
- "Gosh"? - I approve.
(They leave behind the memory and arrive at the third mission.)
Why is it so grand?
- What is this? - What is this?
(The place is filled with second-hand cars.)
What is this?
(What kind of mission will they have to accomplish?)
We will begin the actual game, which is a battle.
You will take turns for each round.
The mission is called "Fly on Our Car".
The offense team will sit in front with their eyes covered,
and hit the other team...
with a fly swatter while they get through.
The defense team has to dodge the fly swatters...
and get through the back seat within 60 seconds.
Once you take a turn swatting,
you can take another turn after singing...
"says peekaboo to me".
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
Then we will proceed.
(Since they know the rules, the games will begin!)
- Are you ready? - Yes!
Go!
I'll make sure you don't get through.
We have to sing it after one swat, right?
We can't do it at the same time.
- We will begin! - One minute is plenty of time.
(They have to go through without getting swatted.)
Slowly. Take your time.
Let's go!
- We will begin! - Let's go!
One minute! Ready, get set...
(Time limit of 60 seconds...)
(Start!)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
- He's so fast. - Says peekaboo to me
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo...
- Says peekaboo to me - We have to get through that?
- Says peekaboo to me - What is that?
(It won't be easy...)
- You have to do the gestures. - I'm scared.
Says peekaboo to me
(Rothy, who was looking for the right time, goes for it!)
(She has to dodge the fly swatter and gets through the back seat.)
(Will she be able to succeed?)
(Swat)
My goodness.
Says peekaboo to me
(A fly swatter slap)
(No...)
(This soon?)
- Says peekaboo to me - Did she get hit?
- Is it over? - Says peekaboo to me
Fail.
(Rothy fails at her first try at variety shows.)
Says peekaboo to me
(They're fully ready to attack Kwang Soo.)
(Stretch)
You have to together.
(He jumps!)
(He goes for the short gap in between swings and jumps.)
(Long)
Says peekaboo to me
(He passed easily.)
(Look at his length!)
Says peekaboo to me
(It is the end of Seok Jin and So Min's offense.)
Did they succeed?
- Kwang Soo succeeded alone. - Okay!
What? Seriously?
I hit someone, didn't I?
So Min slapped Rothy with the fly swatter.
Did I?
(Was that her cheek? I'm sorry.)
Is this how you do it?
Only one of them succeeded, so do we win if we both succeed?
(The offense and defense change places.)
Let's both get through.
Where do we have to go through?
- Gosh! - That's going to hurt!
What is that?
(The tallest member Kwang Soo's terrifying attacking range.)
Ready...
(The game starts.)
Says peekaboo to me
- Do the gestures too. - Says peekaboo to me
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(Seok Jin goes in during the short gap.)
(He is swift despite his model year.)
(Will he be able to get through?)
(My gosh...)
(Swat)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(He couldn't dodge Kwang Soo's super reach and got a fatal blow.)
(Oh, my goodness.)
(He tries to get out, but...)
(Swat)
(It is full of fly swatters.)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(It is So Min's turn.)
(She leaps up as soon as it begins!)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(She dodged it!)
(Swat)
- She got hit. - Says peekaboo to me
(So Min is out.)
(Seok Jin and So Min failed to get through.)
Both failed. Kwang Soo's team won!
Okay!
(Kwang Soo and Rothy win.)
Kwang Soo hits so hard.
Seriously...
Were you trying to kill a fly or a human?
It's because I couldn't see.
- I couldn't see. - Next up,
- Jong Kook... - Yes!
and Ji Hyo.
- Yes. - And...
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo versus Haha and Ji In)
This game is hard.
I really want to do well.
- Do I go like this? - I want to be a hero.
(Swish)
- This is going to hurt. - This is going to hurt so bad.
- He could slit open the flesh. - Says peekaboo to me
(You're going to go that far?)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
- He's fast! - Says peekaboo to me
- Says peekaboo to me - He's too fast.
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
- The seats are about to burst open! - Says peekaboo to me
- Gosh! - Says peekaboo to me
Have we started?
How are they supposed to get through that?
Ready...
Says peekaboo to me
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
Why did he push the car?
To pretend that he got on.
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(The terrifying speed)
Says peekaboo to me
- It's too fast! - Says peekaboo to me
It's so scary!
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(Even though the swatting was fast, he jumps.)
(He flies up with all his might...)
(and dodged it.)
(And dodged it again.)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(He passed through.)
(Haha succeeded.)
He didn't get hit?
(He dodged the fly swatter like Neo dodging bullets.)
He didn't get hit.
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
- You have 15 seconds left. - I hit someone.
Says peekaboo to me
(Jump, swat)
(Ji In failed.)
- She got hit. - Ji Hyo got her.
- That's a shame. - Haha got through.
Really?
It was like a scene from a movie.
It was "Mission: Impossible".
Says peekaboo to me right?
Says peekaboo to me.
While I'm blocking...
Do we have to go one by one?
It doesn't matter. You can do whatever within 60 seconds.
But...
Jong Kook says scary things sometimes.
His way of thinking is unique.
Is he going to throw Ji Hyo?
Those guys...
Ready.
And...
(The game starts.)
Says peekaboo to me...
(Ji Hyo is waiting for the right moment.)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(Fast)
(Both the timing and speed were fabulous.)
(This is who Ji Hyo is.)
- 20 seconds has passed. - Says peekaboo to me
I'll wait.
(The car moves.)
(Right after their attack, )
(Jong Kook jumps up.)
(Will Jong Kook's jump pay off?)
(Jong Kook passes through.)
What happened? Did something happen?
Says peekaboo to me...
(He passes very quickly.)
(By jumping, )
(he escapes right away.)
(Shocked)
Both of them succeeded.
Incredible.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo win.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo win.)
What's with these two?
It's impossible.
- What's with them? - Let's not compete against them.
- It's our turn. - It's our turn.
Do you want to attack or defend?
- We'll attack. - Okay.
- Should we try to pass first? - Yes.
She has long arms.
Ready.
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(Jae Seok and Jin Hee take turns.)
Says peekaboo to me
(Dodging)
(Dodging again)
(Like a flying squirrel, )
(she escaped so easily.)
(Amazed)
Oh, my.
(Seung Hee is a versatile flying squirrel.)
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
(Hesitating)
(Hit)
(Screaming)
(Perfect strike)
- What happened? - Hey.
- What's wrong? - The timing...
(My goodness.)
What happened? What's wrong?
- I mean... - Gosh.
I looked, and Jin Hee wasn't doing anything.
Only Seung Hee passed.
- Did Seung Hee pass? - She passed right away.
- Okay. - Good job.
She was like a flying squirrel.
I caught a huge fly.
(It's Se Chan and Seung Hee's turn to attack.)
(Says peekaboo to me)
(He waits for a moment before attacking.)
We haven't started yet, Se Chan.
(The producer holds back his laughter.)
He's weird.
Ready, and...
(The game starts.)
Says peekaboo to me
(As they're the youngest, they're especially fast.)
(Slow)
Says peekaboo to me
(What is he doing?)
- Says peekaboo to me - Says peekaboo to me
Says peekaboo to me
(Se Chan's strategy is to wait for a moment before attacking.)
(Meanwhile, the sloth stands on his both feet.)
(What is he going to do?)
(He is standing right in the middle.)
Says peekaboo to me
(Here, neither fly swatter reaches Jae Seok.)
(He sure is smart.)
(What the heck is going on?)
(Jae Seok waits for the right moment.)
Says peekaboo to me
(Jumping)
(Jae Seok passes by waiting in the middle.)
- He passed. - Next.
Says peekaboo to me
- Now, 10 seconds left. - Says peekaboo to me
(If she passes within 10 seconds, Jae Seok and Jin Hee win.)
- Says peekaboo to me - In 6, 5, 4...
(To tell you about Jin Hee...)
(She even defeated the ace easily.)
(She also made a man kneel down.)
(There has been no stronger guest than she is.)
(Will she prove her ability again?)
- Four... - Says peekaboo to me
(Hit)
(Hit again)
Gosh. What happened?
(Screaming)
What happened?
(She is knocked out by two consecutive hits.)
I took too long, Jin Hee.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
I thought you weren't doing anything.
I was hit on the leg.
One member of each team passed,
but Seung Hee was a lot faster, taking only 10 seconds.
(Se Chan and Seung Hee win.)
The winning teams are, Jong Kook and Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo and Rothy,
and Se Chan and Seung Hee.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo and Rothy, and Se Chan and Seung Hee)
We lost again.
The winning teams will receive cards.
- The winning teams... - Okay!
Three.
- What? - It's all O cards.
- Three O cards. - Did I do a good job?
You did a great job.
- Three. - Here we go.
(Only Seok Jin and So Min picked O card.)
Did we pick it?
Kwang Soo and Rothy are in the lead now.
(Kwang Soo and Rothy are in the lead.)
Congratulations.
(They arrive at a pool in Suwon for the last mission.)
- Oh, my. - Oh, no.
We're in trouble. They're flying chairs.
It's this again.
We'll be flying off the chairs. Gosh.
This is not okay.
Even the weather is perfect for flying though.
You're right, but still...
The last mission where you get to turn the tables is Flying Quiz.
(Flying Quiz)
- Okay. - It's a quiz.
We've never won except for the first round.
Let's win this time, Jin Hee.
For this mission, men, and women will play separate rounds.
The quiz is about situations that couples can face.
You're to give an answer appropriate for the situation.
If more than half of the judges show an O card,
it counts as a correct answer.
If more than half show an X card,
the answer is wrong, and the partner will be penalized.
After all rounds are finished,
the couples with more correct answers will win.
The top three teams will get a chance to win a prize badge,
and the bottom three teams a penalty badge.
The judges have to agree with our answers.
- That's right. - Okay.
Is there no one correct answer?
- You have to steal their hearts. - There's no right or wrong.
- This is hard. - Gosh.
The judges have to agree.
Ji Hyo doesn't use a messenger.
(Ji Hyo doesn't use a messenger and is bad at couple situations.)
I bet Seok Jin will be the worst at this game.
You have to make the judges sympathize with you.
I understand women well.
- You understand women well? - Of course.
But your wife is always unhappy.
Male members will play first.
- Let the female judges enter. - Okay.
(The final mission starts.)
Female judges, please come in.
- Who are they? - Hyung Seon?
- What? - Hyung Seon?
Ha Neul?
- Wait. - Our staff members?
- Is that Hyung Seon? - Ha Neul too?
(Female staff members become the judges.)
Hyung Seon. Ha Neul.
As far as I know, Hyung Seon is not normal.
(I'm not normal?)
- When it comes to relationships... - Wait.
You look a bit like Guan Yu today.
(Like Guan Yu, she looks aggressive.)
You look like a really good fighter.
- Hyung Seon. - The guard has appeared before.
- That's right. - That's right.
- She's very strict. - She's appeared before.
Ha Neul...
I don't recognize the one at the end. Who are you?
- Who? - The one on the far right.
She's the one who puts microphones on you every week.
It's Hae In.
(She's the one who puts microphones on you every week.)
- It's Hae In. - It's been more than five years.
I wasn't serious.
- Please sit down. - Okay.
Hae In must feel so hurt.
- Please don't feel offended. - She must be dumbfounded.
I can read women's minds.
(What is he saying?)
Say "start" before you answer.
- Okay. - Start!
Here's the first couple's chat.
(Honey, drive safe. Tell me when you arrive.)
(I'm sorry. I tried to be careful, but I scratched your car.)
(I know how much you care about your car. I must have been crazy.)
"Honey, drive safe. Tell me when you arrive."
"I'm sorry. I tried to be careful, but I scratched your car."
"I know how much you care about your car. I must have been crazy."
"I'm so sorry."
Start!
- Isn't it too early? - No.
Okay.
Honey, don't worry about my car.
Scratching it once is not enough. Go scratch it a few more times.
It's okay.
(Scratching it once is not enough. Go scratch it a few more times.)
- That's so lovely. - That sounds...
- a bit sarcastic. - I'm trying to be humorous.
- I'm just being humorous. - In 1, 2, 3.
- That's sarcastic. - Oh, my.
(What do the female judges think of his humorous reply?)
(All X cards)
- It was the worst. - It was the worst.
- Oh, my. - Wasn't it nice?
- It was so sarcastic. - I'm making her feel better.
Here we go.
- Don't worry. - In 1, 2, 3.
Don't worry.
(Flying)
(She spreads her arms out like wings.)
(I'm flying today too.)
My goodness.
- I know. - Hae In, why...
Why did you show an X card?
It sounded like he was mocking me.
It hurt my feelings.
- It hurt her feelings. - Wait.
What about you?
He was telling me to have an accident.
That's not what I meant.
He asked for an accident.
- Okay. Start! - Start!
- Start! - Let me answer!
- Jae Seok. - Let me answer.
Please call me.
(Why does he want a call?)
- It's a messenger. - It's a messenger.
(Were we talking about a messenger?)
Use a messenger.
He doesn't use a messenger.
- I'm sorry. - He doesn't use a messenger.
You must have been surprised. Are you okay?
You must have been very surprised.
Try to calm down.
Don't worry too much about the scratches.
Maybe you should just call.
This is not...
(Is this not how you message?)
You should just call.
How can you write...
How long are you going to write?
You must have been surprised.
Is he sending this long message?
To read that, you'd have to click on "See All".
- I hate it. - It's too long.
You have to write short.
My answer is, "You must have been surprised."
But...
"Calm down."
"You must have been surprised. Try to calm down."
In 1, 2, 3.
(2 O cards and 3 X cards)
(Jae Seok failed to win a majority.)
- 2 O cards. - His partner has to fly.
(His partner, Jin Hee, has to fly off her chair.)
I'm sorry.
(Flying)
(It looks somehow stable.)
She didn't fly so far.
She didn't fly very far.
(Relaxed)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Start.
(Haha gets the chance.)
- Give me just one chance. - Sit down. I figured it out.
- Just one chance. - This actually happened to me.
I have the perfect answer.
She sent those messages...
because some of it is dealt with.
So I replied,
"My car!"
- What? - With crying emojis.
My car!
(What?)
You said that first?
"But are you okay?"
- What? - It's, "My car!"
- It's not even worth to find out. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Will Haha's answer be right?)
- You only got two. - See?
That wasn't the answer.
I needed just one more person.
Shall we move on to the next question?
The females can go this time.
- I definitely had the answer. - Good luck.
I got this.
Good luck, Jin Hee.
- I'm confident I can do this. - I think you'll be good at this.
I'm confident.
It's the same for you guys.
The females have to answer the questions...
which the males would be able to identify with.
Here we go.
I'm sure she can do.
(Baby, where are you?)
(Do you know what time it is? Where are you?)
(We were supposed to meet at 2 o'clock, it's 3 o'clock.)
(You're not even answering my phone call. What are you doing?)
(I'm so sorry, baby.)
(I lost track of time playing games.)
(I'll finish up and leave right after.)
This makes me annoyed.
(Her boyfriend is late as he was playing games.)
- This will make you annoyed. - Let me answer.
Take it slow!
(Let me answer!)
(Why are you so impatient?)
Let me answer.
(It's a difficult situation.)
"You can come when you're finished."
"Or should I go to the PC cafe you're at?"
You would say that? Stop lying!
You would never say that!
(She's being criticized for her fake response.)
(He's still rooting for her as he's on the same team with her.)
That's very kind.
The last, "Should I go to the PC cafe you're at?"...
could be the giveaway for them.
It sounded a bit scary.
Because she's only going so she can check who he's with.
- Wait a minute. - That was her answer.
In 1, 2, 3.
(What will the panels say about her answer?)
(She got 4 X cards and 1 O card.)
- She has more X cards. - Why?
(She failed to get the majority vote.)
I want to play games with my boyfriend.
It's because they haven't met a girlfriend like her!
That means she's coming to see you.
I wanted to play together.
It sounded threatening.
It was a bit threatening.
- You sounded upset. - I told you not to go first.
In 1, 2, 3.
(He's flying in the air.)
(With a stabilized pose and a calm expression, )
(that was a perfect example of Flying Chairs.)
That was really amazing.
You guys don't love her enough.
It's too threatening for her to come.
- It's frightening. - Yes.
- Let me answer! - What are you doing?
You don't know beans about men!
(You don't know beans about men!)
I do know men.
Let me answer.
"I only have one last game left. Can I come when it's over?"
I say, "All right, Baby."
"You said it's one last game,"
"so promise you'll play just one more."
("Promise you'll play just one more.")
- I swear if she got those texts, - She would never say that.
she would have replied, "You little punk."
Hey!
("You little punk.")
- I would never say that. - I can imagine.
(He's framing her for her fake response.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(What will the panels say about Ji Hyo's unusual answer?)
(She got 3 O cards and 2 X cards.)
(Ji Hyo succeeds with the majority vote.)
Okay!
This is unbelievable.
- I did good, right? - Ji Hyo actually got it.
I did well.
- Ji Hyo actually got it. - Let me answer!
(Now everyone wants to say their answers.)
Stop it!
Let me answer.
Don't be too cheesy.
"I see, Baby. I was worried since you weren't calling back."
That's a fake respond.
(That's a fake respond.)
(Booing)
That's a fake respond.
(They're all booing for her disingenuous reply.)
- "Call me when you're finished." - That's good.
That's good. It's not uncomfortable at all.
(What will the panels say about Ji In's reply?)
- In 1, 2, 3. - Her reply was so innocent.
(She got 3 O cards and 2 X cards.)
- Yes! - She got it.
(She succeeds with the majority vote.)
Wait a second.
Don't think about it like she's your actual girlfriend.
It has to be from someone you actually dated...
or the one you're currently seeing.
That was a good answer.
Start. Let me answer.
Let me answer.
(He cannot hide his anxiety.)
Do well.
Imagine that we've been a couple for a few years.
She can't go up to them, can she?
- It's cool out here, isn't it? - It is.
"Okay. Come when you're done."
She's so cute!
(Giggling)
- She's so cute! - What I just did was an emoji.
She's just trying to make it the right answer.
That was great.
Our lighting director laughed.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(She got all X cards.)
(So Min failed because of too much cuteness.)
- Why! - Stop doing that.
- That's enough. - Why is it okay for them to do it?
Why is it okay for them to do it?
Why won't you give me an O card?
Go look into the mirror.
Just stay put!
So Min, stop doing that.
(So Min, stop doing that.)
I'm sorry.
(He flies in the air skillfully one more time.)
(This is the class of a Flying Chair veteran.)
- Let's switch males and females. - Yes.
(They switch seats for the males to do the quiz.)
- Ji Hyo. - Good job.
Here's the next question.
(Will the male group succeed this time?)
You have just found out...
that the lottery you bought your girlfriend won the grand prize.
"This is awesome. I won the lottery."
"I can't believe this. What should I do?"
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
This is quite difficult.
"It's dangerous for you to be alone right now."
"Trust me."
You sound like a fraud.
- You sound like a fraud. - Hey.
Is this a thriller film?
(Who would trust you?)
It sounds like you're going to kidnap her.
I'm sorry, Seung Hee.
(His partner, Seung Hee flies into the air.)
(Goodbye, Seung Hee.)
Let me answer.
I won't be too cheesy.
This is my not-so-cheesy reply.
(She's anxious.)
"Congratulations, Baby."
"Just give me 300 dollars."
("Congratulations, Baby. Just give me 300 dollars.")
- Did he say, "300 dollars"? - That wasn't cheesy at all.
- That was cute. - That wasn't cheesy.
In 1, 2, 3.
(What will the panels say about Jae Seok's reply?)
(He got 4 O cards and 1 X card.)
(Jae Seok succeeds with the majority vote.)
That actually worked?
- How did that work? - Let me answer.
Can we listen to their thought? Shouldn't we?
I would be willing to give 300 dollars.
See?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
I said it first.
I'll be calming the minds of the panels.
"Wow. Amazing. What? Good luck."
"That's amazing."
And lastly, "We're splitting it in half, right?"
("We're splitting it in half, right?")
(It made her sigh.)
What did he just say?
"We're splitting it in half, right?"
- In 1, 2, 3. - It sounds relaxing, isn't it?
(What will the panels say about his reply?)
(He got all X cards.)
You can't ask for money.
You can't ask them for money.
It's all theirs.
They won't give us a penny!
(They won't give us a penny!)
They're greedy people!
They know nothing but money!
- The panels are mean. - I bought you that lottery!
(So Min flies into the air.)
Haha and Ji In are in the first place.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are in the second place.
That's a relief.
Seok Jin and So Min are in third place.
- All right. - We were not that terrible.
It's time to draw the last card.
It's the last one?
Haha, Ji In,
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Seok Jin, and So Min...
will draw the cards first.
Are you going first?
- Come here. - Like this?
How many do you have?
- I have... - We have...
- We don't have that many. - How many do you have?
- We have a bad one. - You have one disadvantage?
- We should all go with O cards. - Yes, please.
(They can all win a prize badge each when they all submit O cards.)
- Yes. - Let's do it.
- Yes. - Let's win one.
Then we're back to zero.
So Min, if you deceive me,
I'm serious about this.
I won't be mad at you,
- but I'll remember it forever. - Why would you say that?
Okay, in 1, 2, 3.
(The final winner wins an exclusive Korean beef gift set.)
(The last place team has to do an indoor skydiving.)
Three!
(What will the top 3 teams choose?)
We all chose O cards!
(They all chose O cards.)
- We all chose O cards. - See?
- See? - I was going to choose an X card.
The three teams in the first place are...
Seok Jin and So Min, Kwang Soo and Rothy,
and Haha and Ji In each with one prize badge.
- What if... - The teams in the last place...
If we choose a different one from them,
- then we're the sole number one. - Yes.
If either Se Chan or Jae Seok's team choose...
the minority card, you will be tied in the first place.
(If they choose a different card, they won't be in the last place.)
- In one... - Just choose any card you like.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Which team will win the prize badge by choosing a different one?)
(Kwang Soo and Rothy: O card)
(Jae Seok and Jin Hee: X card)
(The result is up to the choice of Se Chan and Seung Hee.)
It's an X card!
(Se Chan: O card, Kwang Soo: O card, Jae Seok: X card)
(Jae Seok and Jin Hee win 1 prize badge.)
(Jae Seok and Jin Hee are no longer in the last place.)
That's awesome.
He's in the last place now.
Se Chan and Seung Hee are the only ones in the last place right now.
That's the worst.
Now, Seok Jin and So Min, and Haha and Ji In...
will play a game to be number one.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Seok Jin and So Min: X card)
(Haha and Ji In: O card)
It's an O card!
She's the queen of O cards.
(Haha and Ji In wins the grand prize by drawing an O card.)
(I thought we could finally win this time.)
This team will be given Korean beef gift sets and penalty exemption.
Gosh, it's Korean beef.
(Thank you for the beef.)
It's time for the last penalty.
- Se Chan and Seung Hee... - Yes.
may choose a couple to take with you guys.
They were so happy.
It was difficult to watch.
Can you choose the teams that are ruled out first?
- Please do. - The teams that are excluded.
So that we can be at peace.
First off, since we've been working together...
with Ji Hyo and Jong Kook, they're safe from the penalty.
- Thank you so much. - Yes.
- Thank you. - I guess...
you get back what you give.
We worked hard for it.
The team that picks an X card will receive the penalty with us.
Seok Jin, pick one.
I'll pick one.
Seok Jin.
I wish you pick the cross straightaway.
- Please. - Seriously.
- Please. - Make it hilarious for us.
Seok Jin, I beg you.
I really don't want the penalty today.
I even reached the finals for So Min.
Show it to us.
(Seok Jin and So Min choose their card.)
- Let's do this. - I'm anxious.
- I feel uneasy. - Show it to us.
In 1, 2...
(Desperate for him to choose the X card.)
(Which card did Seok Jin and So Min pick?)
(Seok Jin and So Min chose the O card.)
(We're doomed.)
- No. - We're safe.
Ji Hyo.
Didn't I do well?
The person who loses picks first.
Rock-paper-scissors.
You pick first.
Just pick any of them.
All right, the other team now.
Show them to us at the same time.
- I'm curious about this. - I'm so nervous.
Two...
Three.
(Which team will be left back when others can head back home?)
We're done.
(Kwang Soo and Rothy choose the penalty X card.)
- We're safe. - We're done.
We're safe.
We didn't plan this.
- We didn't. - We didn't plan this at all.
(Kwang Soo and Rothy receive the final penalty.)
(After the shoot, when everyone left...)
- Don't tell me this is a dream. - My goodness.
Is this it?
(Indoor skydiving with a top speed of 360km per hour)
(The first runner is Se Chan.)
He's going.
You can do it!
(He gets uglier because of the pressure for being first.)
(He enters the range with assistance from the coach.)
(But...)
He looks so ugly.
(Kwang Soo is shocked by his appearance.)
- He looks so funny. - Just look at him.
(His nose starts running as soon as he enters.)
You have a runny nose!
Please close your mouth.
His snot is reaching his lips.
(Screaming)
How does his mouth look like that?
He's going up.
(He shoots up vertically straightaway.)
(Like getting sucked into a black hole, )
(he shoots up to 20m high.)
(The higher he goes, the wider his mouth opens.)
He's spinning. Where's he going?
(Jaw dropping)
Look at his face.
- He's smiling. - He made eye contact with me.
That was frightening.
(After Se Chan's skydive that might appear in your nightmare, )
(Seung Hee and Rothy try their best to maintain their looks.)
Off she goes.
(Seung Hee shows...)
(an example of a perfect skydive.)
She's good.
How is that possible?
Why doesn't her mouth open?
What's this?
It looks easy right? Just wait for your turn.
(It's finally alien Kwang Soo's turn.)
He's starting.
- He looks pale. - That's what happens to your lips.
- You're right. - That's what happens.
- His mouth is opening. - He has his mouth opened.
He's too tall.
What's happening?
(He hasn't even entered yet but his expression changes first.)
What's wrong with his face?
My goodness.
What's wrong with his face? Did I look the same?
- Yes. - Did I?
You were worse.
I think you looked similar to him.
(He tries to rely on the wind.)
(An alien of 2m falls down.)
That's hilarious. Look at his lips.
He's about to go up.
Doesn't he have to get ready first?
This is shocking.
His face is shocking.
(Why am I sinking?)
(Look at his face. Did we look as bad as him?)
- Was I that bad? - Well...
- You were worse. - He's drooling.
He's drooling.
I feel bad for the coach.
He's about to go up.
He's going up.
Off he goes.
(He shoots up.)
Weren't you scared up there?
(Screaming)
(His face tells us how scary it is.)
(Thankfully, the 2m-tall alien seems to be doing fine.)
Did my mouth look like that too?
What's wrong with his mouth.
(The alien makes an emergency landing.)
(It's a complete gift set from the ugly man.)
Goodness.
He keeps doing that.
Why am I not done yet?
(The coach will give up soon.)
The coach is going to give up on him.
(Why am I not done yet?)
Look at him.
(Why are you laughing at me?)
He seems more relaxed now.
(Kwang Soo just managed to complete his flight.)
(Gosh)
You have to watch this episode to see your face.
- You have to. - You just escaped your aquarium.
What do you mean by that?
- That was scary. - Now...
You have completed today's penalty.
(We would like to thank Song Ji In, Jang Jin Hee, Seung Hee, and Rothy.)
(We would like to invite our viewers to the Running Man Fan-Meet.)
(More details on our official website.)