(Last week)
(It was a battle of singles with Hee Jin, Bona, and Jae Young.)
(2 of them are a secret couple, and 1 of them is a relationship virgin.)
(Find the secret couple! Thus began the war of suspicion.)
(Ji Hyo and Jae Young became likely candidates for the secret couple.)
(And Hee Jin was another strong candidate.)
(She didn't share the hint she received with the others.)
(Which 2 members are the secret couple?)
(And another hint was at stake on Three-Way Tug-of-War.)
(Team Hello Honey,)
(Team Comedians,)
(and Team Youth finished scouting college members.)
Come on, this isn't fair.
What is that? Hold on.
Jong Kook is unbelievable.
- They walk differently. Look. - Is he serious?
Why does everyone on his team walk like Jong Kook does?
(They are Jong Kook's lookalikes. They walk confidently.)
Isn't that too much?
Will this even be fair for us?
Are you here to fight us or what?
(We'll tell you about this team.)
(He stood out as soon as I walked in.)
(At his first glance, he picked a model and a big guy.)
(After the soda mission, he finishes scouting the guy.)
(How tall are you?)
(My height is 191cm.)
(He even finished scouting...)
(this handsome, tall guy with a flexible back.)
He's so tall.
- We got the military science major. - Are you serious?
We chose the modeling major.
- We had the modeling major. - Listen.
(Jong Kook is commanding the elite, Big Build 11.)
We lost. We lost.
But your team looks too strong.
Right now, someone from the military science major...
ripped his pants.
- What? - His pants got ripped now.
- Why is that? - What?
- Why did he rip his pants? - We were playing a game.
I see.
(He twisted his feet with sharp moves.)
(Wait, time-out. His pants...)
(As he was exploding with energy, his pants exploded too.)
(They did their best with the gags on.)
(The team finished scouting the Playful Gag Trio too.)
(She feels reassured about her team.)
His pants got ripped all the way here.
(They look strict, but clumsy.)
(They are the real clumsy men.)
My gosh, our team is clustered together.
Our team looks so adorable.
It's like we're herbivores.
(This herbivore-looking team is...)
We're so cute.
We're cute.
(In this vast campus like the meadow of Africa,)
(they finished scouting Freddie Dog, an unexpected fighter.)
(And...)
(They also scouted the giraffe and llama who do everything to win.)
(People are getting along in Campus Africa today as always.)
(We're like herbivores.)
(The Animal Kingdom of the Herbivores)
Kwang Soo, you're one person short. Is that number seven?
- Yes. - He's not here yet.
- I don't know what that is though. - He went back for the attendance.
- It was for the attendance. - It was for the attendance.
- He got the place wrong too. - Three.
- There's nothing we can do. - Really?
- 2. - 2.
(Sounding firm)
- Why do you sound so cold? - Come on.
(It's because this doesn't concern you.)
(Seok Jin is a cold fighter when it comes to games.)
You sounded too cold.
Someone has a blind date at 6pm today.
Where is she? Who is it?
- She has the blind date. - Right.
- It's at 6pm. - She dressed up nicely too.
She has to look nice for that.
She skipped her class to be here.
- We don't have much time. - I'm so nervous.
We must hurry, so she makes it in time.
If you have a blind date, you can go early.
- No, no. - It's a group blind date.
Everyone, the rules are simple.
Each team will start tugging the rope at the sound of a whistle.
The team that rings the bell...
at the end of the rope wins the game.
Everyone, stand and hold your rope.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- I'll be at the end. - No.
- Should we line up here? - Do what you want to do.
- Jae Seok. - This way?
- Strong people must be in front. - Strong people go to the front.
- Or other teams can easily pull us. - In the front...
When he blows the whistle, lean back and start tugging.
We have to go that way. Alternate from the sides.
- Should we pull at short intervals? - Should we?
- Yo-heave-ho, Yo-heave-ho. - Short intervals? Yo-heave-ho.
(They aim to win with the chant.)
Do you have a slogan?
- We can do, "1, 2. 1, 2." - 1, 2. 1, 2.
- I won first place in the army. - Really?
The gaps were consistent.
We used our arms to measure the gap.
- That's great. Show us how. - That's so interesting.
- Extend your arm. - A shoulder apart.
We have to alternate the sides first.
We won first place with this method.
- Okay. - Okay.
- You should stand over there. - Here?
We'll do the chant, "Yo-heave-ho, Yo-heave-ho".
When we start the game, you'll end up rushing it anyway.
Stronger ones will be in the front.
It's better for the smaller ones to be in the back.
We can mix it up. Four of you should come here.
How are we supposed to defeat them?
- Those guys... - Jong Kook is instructing them too.
(This is so scary.)
Hey, that number seven from the modeling major.
I bet he's famous at this school.
I think he was a swimmer too.
All right. Are you ready?
- Yes! - Do a good job.
- We can do this! - Yes!
- Let's go! - Let's do this!
- We can do this! - We can do this!
Let's go for it!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
My throat hurts.
(Kwang Soo with long arms and legs is the tail for Team Youth.)
(The tail of Team Hello Honey is...)
(Jae Young, another tall guy.)
- Let's do this! - We'll start now.
Get ready!
Set.
(The Three-Way Tug-of-War starts.)
(Team Comedians is in perfect order with their chant.)
(Team Youth is evenly spreading out the strength.)
(Team Hello Honey believes in Jong Kook's command.)
(It's a close game.)
- Yo-heave-ho, Yo-heave-ho. - Yo-heave-ho, Yo-heave-ho.
(However, at that moment...)
(Chanting)
Pull! Pull!
(Exerting superhuman power)
- Yo-heave-ho. - Yo-heave-ho.
(It's moving to Jong Kook's team.)
- No! - Yo-heave-ho.
(Jae Young is approaching the bell too.)
(Team Hello Honey is getting closer to the bell.)
(Will they win as soon as it starts?)
- Everyone, do it together. - Start.
(Will Jong Kook's elite group win just as expected?)
- Hang in there! - Yo-heave-ho.
Yo-heave-ho.
(We can't lose like this!)
(Kwang Soo has a lonely fight with the bell.)
- Yo-heave-ho. - Just a little more! A little more!
(I want to create a miracle of the bell with my fingertips.)
(Please help me create the miracle with my unlucky hands.)
(Do not give up until the end.)
(He focuses on the rope instead of the bell for now.)
(Exerting force)
(With Kwang Soo's scream,)
(the rope is heading toward him.)
(He pulled it!)
- To the back! - A little more!
No!
Pull! My gosh!
My gosh. Hey, hey.
(It's a miracle of herbivores, up against Jong Kook's elite group.)
(The giraffe, the captain of herbivores, sets out.)
(Go! Show people how strong we, herbivores, can be!)
(A story of the giraffe who defeated the tiger will be remembered.)
A little more! A little more!
Please!
(He's only a few inches away from the bell.)
(He's literally right in front of it!)
- No! - Yo-heave-ho!
(Jong Kook's elite legion is being dragged against their will.)
(They are so close that they can almost taste their victory.)
(No!)
No! Pull!
(This is it! Pull it now!)
(I just need to extend my arm...)
(to reach the bell!)
(Missing the rope)
- No! - Just a little more!
(He missed the rope that was right in front of him.)
Please! Please!
(That was a great opportunity. Gosh, what a shame.)
Kwang Soo... Pull!
Pull!
(My warriors,)
(get up.)
(As Jong Kook leads them,)
(the soldiers of his elite legion start moving in perfect teamwork.)
- No! Please! - Let's go!
- Please! - We can do it!
(Wavering)
- Hang in there. - Come on.
(We'll lose if we don't do anything.)
Come on! Pull!
(We won't go easy on you now. We'll make sure we win this game.)
(And at this moment,)
(Jae Young extends his arm to the bell.)
- Pull! - No way!
(They are so close to winning the game.)
(No!)
(The moment he rings the bell, they'll win, and the game is over.)
Hang in there!
(What's the result?)
(Ringing)
(Team Hello Honey wins.)
- You did great. - Good job.
- Hey. - Great job.
No, no, no.
- That was so hard. - It was so hard.
- We didn't have enough people. - We weren't even close.
(The bitterness of losing to Jong Kook feels familiar.)
Good work.
(Whistling)
(Flinging)
It's always annoying.
I'm serious.
We never win a single match!
We went all the way to the bell in the beginning.
- We were so close, weren't we? - Yes, it was so close.
That was no joke.
- Congratulations. The victory... - Thank you.
goes to Jong Kook's team.
Yes!
- Thank you for your help! - Well done.
Our team worked so hard for us.
By the way, if we hadn't had these five guys with us,
- it would've been over right away. - Right, right.
- These five guys were great. - They were so good.
- They helped us stay... - We pulled to their chant.
- They worked so hard. - Their chanting...
Their chant was so great.
They got more energy...
out of our chant.
(With the military science major's loud chant,)
(Jong Kook's elite legion received more energy.)
But their teamwork was great. They are indeed soldiers.
We'll bid farewell to the students...
- who worked so hard for us. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you so much.
- Thank you for your help. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you, everyone.
- Your pants were ripped. I'm sorry. - It's okay.
- Thank you for your help. - Thank you.
(We will root for your bright youth.)
This isn't what's important now.
We have to figure out who the secret couple is.
- He's right. - I completely forgot about it.
This isn't the main game.
- I totally forgot. - We have to figure out who it is.
- Everyone. - Yes.
I said the secret couple must do a hidden mission for every round.
- Yes. - Did they succeed?
I informed you, if they failed, I will share a hint with everyone.
- Yes. - They must have failed.
They failed.
(The secret couple failed the hidden mission.)
(They acquire a hint about the secret couple.)
- This is amazing. - Move back.
(What on earth was the mission?)
- Which member failed? - Why did you fail?
I told you it's not me.
(Their suspicion is directed at Ji Hyo, the prime suspect.)
- Or could it be... - It's not that!
Was their mission losing the game?
- So Ji Hyo had no choice. - She had to lose, but won.
- No. - Really?
(Was the hidden mission losing the Three-Way Tug-of-War?)
- You'll know once you get the hint. - Okay.
(Is Ji Hyo a secret couple?)
(Right before the tug-of-war...)
- Jae Young, you must do it. - Yes.
(She and Jae Young had a mysterious conversation.)
(Did she not look happy after winning it because of the mission?)
(Are they truly the secret couple?)
- Okay. - Wait.
- When she was playing it... - Is that so?
I felt this earlier.
Kwang Soo couldn't reach the bell when he could have.
(Kwang Soo is a strong candidate too.)
Something is definitely off.
(It's suspicious how he lost it when it was so close.)
Something is definitely happening.
When I was pulling, I saw Kwang Soo.
- He could have reached it. - Did you not ring it on purpose?
- No, I really couldn't reach. - He was so close.
I tried with my arms and feet.
(He was literally right in front of it.)
(It's very suspicious how he just missed it.)
(Is Kwang Soo really the secret couple?)
- No, no. It doesn't make sense. - You're it.
Did you not ring it on purpose?
- Really? You didn't on purpose? - I tried with my arms and feet.
I have a hunch. He could've rung it. Something is up.
- Who could it be? - Okay.
- Give us the hint. - The secret couple must've won.
Give us the hint first.
- The guy... - Okay.
(The hint about the secret couple is revealed.)
- The guy of the secret couple... - The guy.
uses his real name in the entertainment industry.
Lee Kwang Soo.
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Wait.
Everyone uses their real name!
- Me. - Who else?
It's everyone except for Haha.
We know for sure that Haha isn't.
- Jae Young uses his real name. - Se Chan uses his real name.
- Everyone uses their real name. - It's everyone except for Haha.
- It's everyone except for Haha. - We know it's not Haha.
It's not me. I told you it wasn't me.
If you're a relationship virgin, come to me.
- That's right. Haha is the safest. - Come talk to me in secret.
- That's right. - Yes.
He's right.
1 of the 3 winning members must receive the hint.
Why don't you share the hint when you get it?
Please share it with us.
Yes, you must share it with us.
- We must catch the couple. - Everyone.
- Shouldn't I get the hint? - I'll get the hint.
- I agree with you. - I agree.
- Me too. - That's fair.
- See? I should. - I'm really not the couple.
Just to be safe, I'll take a look.
I can share it with you.
There's no need for you to get it.
- You'll really share it with me? - Of course.
Then just share it with the three of us.
No, I'll share it with everyone.
- It's really not me. - I'll take a look to be safe.
- Jong Kook... - I'll share the hint.
- I can share it with you all. - Talk to him.
- Jae Young, talk to him. - Jae Young.
(It's okay.)
- I can share it with you. - You should get the hint.
(Acting scared)
- I will share it too. - I'll take a look.
- Jae Young is smart. - He knows how to read the room.
- Hurry. - All right. Here's the order.
I'll read it first. The three of us will read it.
- Then we'll decide to share or not. - Okay.
- We'll do that. - Okay.
- That's good, right? - Wait.
- Before that... - Jong Kook said he'll share.
(He can pick a hint about the couple or the relationship virgin.)
(Which hint did Jong Kook choose?)
Let me take a look first.
My gosh.
What is it?
- Let's share. - Why don't we share it?
(He said, "My gosh" as soon as he read it.)
It said, "The guy is taller than 175cm."
(The guy of the secret couple is taller than 175cm.)
You guys raised the number.
(Again, it only excludes Haha as he's shorter than 175cm.)
Hey, how tall is Haha?
- 175cm? - Se Chan isn't it either.
- You're shorter than 175cm? - You're not it.
Hold this. This is insulting.
- Hey, you're shorter than that. - This is insulting.
- He's so short. - You're not that tall?
- Stand up straight. - You're shorter than that?
I thought you were taller than that.
- This is insulting. - Isn't that you?
This is really insulting.
- Se Chan isn't it either. - That's true.
Did you set it to 175cm for Se Chan?
(Even in the Shorty Club, there's a gap too.)
We know for sure that these two aren't the couple.
We've excluded two members now.
(2 of the candidates for the secret couple are excluded.)
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
I think Haha's height was 170-something.
Now, you only have the final mission.
- This is the final mission? - As for the final mission,
- we'll do it indoors. - Okay.
- Yes! - Let's do that.
Relationship virgin, come to me.
(Will the singles be able to catch the secret couple?)
All right. You're no longer with your teams.
- We don't have teams now, right? - Is that so?
The last mission to catch the secret couple is...
Shining Singles' Trial.
(The last mission, Shining Singles' Trial)
- A trial? - Singles' Trial.
It's like the song.
(How will we do the trial?)
Hints about the secret couple and the relationship virgin...
are hidden all over the building.
There are hints here.
Find the hints. Every 30 minutes, 2 trials will be held.
During those trials, you will decide on which members to eliminate.
My gosh, two trials. That's nice.
If the selected members are indeed the secret couple,
the relationship virgin and the singles will win.
However, if the relationship virgin is eliminated,
or if you fail to catch...
the secret couple even after two trials,
the secret couple will win.
The prize will go to the secret couple.
No, no.
- Let's stop them. - We must.
We should catch them.
We must protect...
- the relationship virgin. - That's right.
If you're the relationship virgin, go to Haha or Se Chan.
- We'll protect you! - Let's protect that person.
Relationship virgin, go to them now.
That's right. We'll protect you.
(Can the singles protect the relationship virgin...)
(and catch the secret couple?)
This is hard.
I don't think Se Chan,
Jae Seok, and Seok Jin...
are not the secret couple including myself, of course.
So far, we haven't won any hints...
that tell us which members are the secret couple.
But I don't know what hint Hee Jin received.
(Last week, at the restaurant,)
(Hee Jin won a hint.)
(Because she didn't share the hint, she was easily suspected...)
(as one of the secret couple.)
It's either Kwang Soo and Hee Jin or Ji Hyo and Jae Young.
This morning,
I caught Hee Jin and Kwang Soo exchanging looks...
when we were receiving our clothes.
I even remember the clothes they were handing out.
(He's been suspecting them.)
Secret couple...
Jang Hee Jin.
(So Min also suspects Hee Jin.)
It's either Hee Jin and Kwang Soo or...
I think it's Jae Young...
(Hee Jin and Kwang Soo, or Jae Young and Ji Hyo)
and Ji Hyo.
(These 4 are the most-suspected candidates.)
(Is the secret couple among them?)
The race starts now.
Let's go.
We just need to find the couple to finish our mission for today.
(They need to eliminate the secret couple.)
Once we catch them, the single members win.
(At that moment...)
Look at them.
(So Min and Jae Young...)
(come out from the same room.)
You guys were together.
No, we weren't.
- What? - He came out from there.
How many floors is this building?
(Jae Young followed So Min out.)
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
- What is it? - Okay.
All right.
You're really suspicious-looking at the moment.
People are suspecting you for whispering...
- to Hee Jin. - Whispering?
You're the most-suspected, okay?
(At that moment,)
(they find a hint hidden inside the vending machine.)
(That hint is mine!)
(So Min acquires it first.)
No.
What are you doing?
Stop it. What are you doing?
Stop it!
- Hey! - What are they doing?
What are you doing?
- It's Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo! - It's mine!
- He found one already? - Don't do that.
It's mine.
(After stealing the hint, the culprit runs away.)
(Catch that suspicious-looking man!)
(What is he up to this time?)
- He's so mean. - What happened?
It was mine. He's so suspicious.
He wanted my hint so badly.
We could share it.
(After stealing it, he runs away.)
(He gets cornered and is forced to share the hint.)
What is it?
- Come here. - Let's share.
"The female of the secret couple is in her 30s."
(The female of the secret couple is in her 30s.)
(Song Ji Hyo, Jang Hee Jin, Jeon So Min)
(Bona, who is in her 20s, is ruled out.)
Bona is out of the picture.
(Then the remaining women are...)
- It's not Bona. - Haha.
(Hee Jin, Ji Hyo, and So Min.)
- Kwang Soo... - What's wrong with you?
- did a good job. - Why?
- I got a huge hint. - Let me see.
- It was mine. - I ripped it.
- Let me see. - Why did you do that...
when I found it?
- You were in it. - It's her.
- I was in it? - What was the hint?
I'll let you know in private.
If I'm part of it, let me know.
- It says your name. - Fine, don't tell me, then.
Are you sulking?
(Sulky)
- I'll let you know. - Forget it.
(He's flustered.)
- I'll tell you. - Forget it.
- No, I'll tell you. - Let me go.
Why would you get sulky...
- I'll tell you. - while shooting?
- Come on. - The culprit is...
a beauty.
(The culprit is a beauty.)
It's me.
(I'm the beauty.)
That's why I couldn't tell you.
- It's me. - I can't tell you.
- You look happy now. - I'm the culprit.
I'm the beauty the hint mentioned.
- Really? - Gosh, I pity you.
- How could you say that? - Your name was written on it.
- It was? All right. - Yes.
(Bona is looking for the hints alone.)
(Where could they be?)
(She finds one.)
Is this it?
(What will this hint say?)
(The relationship virgin uses their real name.)
(Excluded: Haha, Song Ji Hyo, Bona)
(Those three individuals are exempted.)
- My goodness. - You startled me.
(Hee Jin, a strong candidate, appears.)
What is it? I guess you found a hint.
(What is it? I guess you found a hint.)
Did you find anything?
Should we exchange information?
What is it?
Let's be friends.
We're both single members, so let's exchange information.
Bona.
(Suddenly)
- Bona. - My goodness.
(Another strong candidate appears.)
- Kwang Soo. - Did you find anything?
- Kwang Soo, listen. - Bona, you're off the leash.
- How? - How about me?
- Let me go first. - How did you know?
I'm sorry to say this, but I've found a hint.
- What is it? - What did it say?
Let's share. I have a hint too.
- Me too. - You do?
Yes, we all have one.
- Let's exchange hints. - Yes.
(They all agree to share their hints.)
- I memorized mine. - What?
So did I.
"The female suspect..."
"has dyed her hair."
But I dyed my hair.
I dyed my hair too.
What's yours?
- You're lying, aren't you? - I bet he is.
- Then... - You don't have a hint, do you?
- I didn't write it. - You don't have one, right?
- No, I do. I'll show you. - Be honest.
Actually, I have more than one.
I got one in the beginning, and I found one here too.
- Right, you got one at the start. - Yes.
- That's a good one. - I'll show you mine.
- Here. - Let me see.
"The female of the secret couple is in her 30s."
- So Bona's not a suspect. - No way!
- No way. - Hold on.
- Come here. Did you find a hint? - Aren't I right?
Did you?
Let's share, now that I know you're not one.
(Haha and Bona are confirmed single members.)
Bona, let's share.
- Wait a minute. - Come here.
- Step away. - Haha.
(They're naturally divided up.)
It's not me.
- Don't come. - I shared with you!
- Go lie down over there! - Fine!
- Sit down over there. - You shouldn't trust Kwang Soo,
- all right? - What do you mean?
You're one of the suspects.
Yes, Hee Jin's a suspect too, so come here.
Bona, it's not me.
- Let's go first. - That's a good idea.
You're just going to leave after hearing my hint?
(You can't just leave like this.)
- What? - Are you just leaving?
Be on alert at all times.
Hold on. Let me explain.
- Wait. - Hee Jin, who is it?
- What? - Who's your partner?
(He tries to corner her.)
- Who's your partner? - It's not me.
- It's not me. - Tell us.
- Kwang Soo. - Who's the guy?
- Hear me out. - Bona, let's run.
Come here.
Haha, it's not me!
- Wait! - Look at you!
(While pleading his innocence, Kwang Soo runs towards Haha.)
- Hey, hey! What did you do? - Wait.
- Did you just look at my name tag? - It's not me!
He wanted my name tag!
No! It's not me!
- It could be Hee Jin. - You were looking at it!
It's not me. I didn't look at your name tag.
Bona, scream.
(That means "Don't come near me.)
Good. Good job.
- What are you doing? - Now, run away.
I'll keep them here.
- It's really not me. - This way?
I'm really not the secret couple, but Kwang Soo is!
Come on, Bona!
This is driving me crazy.
She keeps doing suspicious things.
Kwang Soo...
Don't come near me.
- You're making them suspect me! - It's you!
- Don't put the blame on me! - Come here.
No, come here.
Kwang Soo, I know that it's you.
(Could the secret couple be one of them?)
I really have no clue.
(Jae Young, another candidate, is looking for hints alone.)
Hey, I got one.
(At that moment,)
(he finds a hint.)
(What does this hint say?)
(The male of the secret couple is an actor.)
(Lee Kwang Soo, Kim Jae Young)
(There are only two actors.)
(After reading it, he hurriedly hides it.)
(Looking around)
That was close. Goodness.
I should get rid of them.
(What does that mean?)
Today's race will be called...
Secret Couple Amid the Battle of Singles.
And you two are the secret couple,
hidden among the single members.
(Jae Young was the male.)
Okay. Thank you.
There's a way for you guys to eliminate the others...
during the race.
If you suspect someone of being a relationship virgin, you can...
(They need to do something.)
Only then, you'll be able to remove their name tag.
If that individual is not a relationship virgin,
a crucial hint about you two will be revealed to the others.
(Secret couple)
(Kim Jae Young was the male of the secret couple.)
No one is showing me their hints.
- It's not you, right? - No, it's not.
It's not me either. Then it's Hee Jin.
But I have no way to find out since I have no hints.
And they won't show theirs either. They just won't show me.
Let's look for hints and exchange them.
I'm really desperate to know anything,
whether it be about the relationship virgin or the secret couple.
I just want to know.
(While So Min is busy with her soliloquy,)
(Ji Hyo finds a hint.)
You got one! Awesome!
Ji Hyo, let's share it.
(She has found one!)
Ji Hyo.
Please don't do this to me.
(Ignoring)
(What does her hint say?)
(The relationship virgin is a male in his 40s.)
(Excluded: Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, Se Chan, Jae Young)
(Judging by the previous hints, it's either Jong Kook or Jae Seok.)
I'm an outcast.
I'm certain.
She pretty much sealed the deal just now.
(Seok Jin approaches Ji Hyo, a strong candidate.)
Are you going down?
You're very suspicious.
- What? I didn't do anything. - Why would you grab his hand?
- It's a mission, right? - You can't just listen...
to Jong Kook's side of the story.
Why would you grab his hand?
Jong Kook said to me,
"If you're a couple, you probably have a mission."
So I just played along, said yes, and grabbed Jae Young's hand.
- All right. - It was really nothing.
I'm serious.
Jong Kook seems to be accusing you quite a lot today.
- I know. You know how... - Right? Isn't he weird?
Jong Kook tends to corner...
- those around them... - Right.
- when he receives a mission? - Everyone's suspicious.
Wouldn't the hints be hidden...
in places like this?
(Jong Kook accused Ji Hyo and Jae Young all day.)
(He claims that the two were being suspicious.)
(He suspected them for the smallest things.)
(He's been acting like a detective all day long.)
(Could he be the relationship virgin?)
I'll be susceptible to attacks if I'm in remote places.
Let me see. There's someone over there.
(Someone has been following him.)
(It's Ji Hyo.)
(It's me.)
Wait.
You're strange.
I should be here.
- It's dangerous. - I was joking around.
No. Aren't you dying to eliminate me since I've been accusing you?
That's our show's pattern.
(The one who suspects the most will be eliminated the earliest.)
(Jong Kook continues searching for hints.)
(And Ji Hyo tails him.)
Look at her face. How strange.
Walk past me.
Go. Pass.
Whom did you call?
(Did you call someone over?)
(At that moment,)
(Jae Young, one of the secret couple, appears.)
Could it be here?
What was that?
(He hears Jong Kook's voice.)
(Ji Hyo being in this remote library feels suspicious for him.)
No way.
Where is he?
(He carefully approaches Jong Kook.)
Hello.
- Hey, did you find any hints? - Yes.
You're not a part of the secret couple.
Let me see.
(He distracts Jong Kook with his hint.)
(Jong Kook takes the bait.)
Even dates?
Right, I was born on the 25th.
(This is his chance.)
I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
(In a blink of an eye, Kim Jong Kook is out.)
(If he's the relationship virgin, this race is over.)
- Yes, it's me. - How dare you?
(He's not the relationship virgin.)
Come here.
- I knew it. - I'm sorry.
(If Jong Kook is not the relationship virgin,)
Hey.
(Jae Seok is the only remaining candidate.)
If I get eliminated, the race is over.
(Listen carefully.)
- By whom? - It's true.
- By the secret couple. - Why are you telling me now?
- You're the relationship virgin? - I must watch out.
(What is his identity?)
(This morning, before the opening scene)
Jae Seok, you're the ace among the single members.
You're the relationship virgin.
(He was indeed the relationship virgin.)
(They chose the relationship virgin based on his appearance.)
Let me emphasize this.
If I'm out, this race is over.
- What? - Haha,
- this is our guess. - Be quiet.
If I get eliminated, this is all over.
- Got it? - You should...
- What's your mission? - be careful.
This is bad.
(He realizes that he ripped the wrong name tag.)
Kim Jong Kook,
a single member, is out.
He's out?
Kim Jong Kook, a single member, is out.
What?
(It's a bolt out of the blue.)
How was he eliminated?
- How was he out? - Not knowing that is scary.
- Because... - I will now give you...
a crucial hint regarding the secret couple.
- For free. - Jong Kook is out?
(Their 1st trial will start in 5 minutes. What is the hint?)
The male of the secret couple...
(The male of the secret couple is...)
debuted as a model.
- Then... - That's why I suspected Jae Young.
(There are only two candidates.)
- It's either Jae Young... - Or Kwang Soo.
It's 1 of those 2.
Seok Jin can never be a model.
He debuted as a model.
(Kwang Soo hears the hint as well.)
To be frank, I didn't debut as a model.
(I'm just a tall comedian.)
I can't say that I was a model.
Who wrote this hint? Never mind. Fine.
My goodness. I wonder who came up with this hint.
I'm not sure.
It's Jae Young.
(He finally realizes.)
Then it's So Min and Jae Young.
No, wait. Is it Hee Jin?
(He doesn't know who the female is.)
So it's Jae Young?
It could be you.
What do you mean?
What kind of nonsense are you spewing?
- What are you talking about? - There are only two models.
Right, but I'm not the one.
(You guys picked Jae Young.)
Darn it.
(No one is on his side.)
I'm flabbergasted.
(He needs to prove to the others that he's innocent.)
Wait a minute.
(He finds the single members.)
(He runs towards them to plead his innocence.)
Be careful.
- Seok Jin, we need to run. - It's Kwang Soo.
- It's him. - Let's run away.
It's not me! It isn't!
(Where are you all going?)
It's not me!
(They block him.)
Hey! Where are you?
(I'm an innocent single member just like you!)
- Hey. - Seok Jin.
Darn it.
- It's not me. - It is you.
- I promise. - I know it's you.
- I can't prove it, though. - I heard the hint.
The male member debuted as a model.
I'm innocent.
- Hey! - I'm really innocent.
It's not me.
It really isn't me.
- His face looks suspicious. - I know.
His facial expressions look so suspicious.
- I'm serious. - I couldn't sleep much yesterday.
It's because my eyes look sunken, but I'm not the one.
(At that moment,)
(the two models finally meet.)
- Hey, it's not me. - How did you eliminate Jong Kook?
(Hear me out.)
(You're impressive, Kwang Soo.)
You.
It's really not me.
What is this?
- It's Jae Young. - It's Kwang Soo.
- It's Jae Young. - Why do you think so?
- If it's not me, it's him. - Right.
I swear that it's not me. You'll know.
- It's not me, either. - This doesn't make sense.
- I don't know. - Why wouldn't this make sense?
You spent the day with me. Shouldn't you know?
(Jae Young is happy with Kwang Soo's irrational explanation.)
It was you.
(What will become of their fates?)
It's time for our first trial.
Let's head towards the court.
Jong Kook was out.
He's been getting eliminated first these past weeks.
This is the first trial.
For this trial,
you will only choose one individual...
who seems the most suspicious.
(Only one of them will be judged.)
Just one?
It should be male.
Either Jae Young or Kwang Soo.
Yes. He's right.
Should we pick Kwang Soo or Jae Young?
I'm truly innocent.
This is bad.
(If they can't catch him, the second half will be difficult.)
- Is it you? - No, it's not.
It's Kwang Soo.
It's one of them for sure.
Yes, you're right.
We're so close to catching him.
- Listen. - Let's do it.
- What? - It's not me.
I'll say one thing.
- I wasn't going to say this. - You better not lie.
But I found a crucial hint.
(He seems to know something.)
What is it?
(There was a hint that Kwang Soo didn't reveal.)
(What is this crucial hint?)
(20 minutes ago)
(He found a hint.)
(After reading it, he was at a loss for words.)
(He saved it for this moment.)
(Nervous)
You fabricated it, right?
(Jae Seok can't trust Kwang Soo.)
- My goodness. - I'm 100-percent sure you did.
(He's been known to fabricate hints.)
- I'm sure you did. - No, you'll see.
- Let me see. - He fabricated it.
- Let me see. - I can't show you...
because it's a hint about the relationship virgin.
(It's too dangerous to reveal the relationship virgin's identity.)
- Then you shouldn't reveal it. - Right.
Did any of you hear me talk about this hint?
- Let me see. - Wait.
- If I show it... - The relationship virgin...
We need to check and see if he fabricated it or not.
Wait. He can show it to me.
- I can. - I'm a single member.
- Me too. - I can.
That's why I didn't show this to anyone.
- Show it to Haha and me. - Me too.
I'll show it to all three of you.
This will prove my innocence.
- Okay, okay. - I will be...
- We got it. - Let me plead my innocence!
- Don't cry out. - We got it.
(It looks like they just want to see the hint.)
- I need to convince them. - All right.
(Let me talk.)
- Show it to us. - It's been a while...
- since I found this hint. - We'll help you.
- But I didn't show it to anyone. - Let us see.
(This hint will prove of his innocence.)
(If his innocence is proven, Jae Young will be judged.)
(What is this hint?)
(Darn it.)
Are you serious?
(He's flustered.)
What is it?
It's fake, isn't it?
Why? What is it?
("The relationship virgin is male.")
- He must be in his dreams. - My goodness.
I can't believe you. Just sit down!
Whom are you trying to deceive?
Why? This is a very important hint.
We all know that.
- We knew it. - Hey.
How were you going to turn the tables with that?
(They can't believe him.)
(He thought no one else knew.)
I thought only I knew.
(Jae Young is relieved.)
Jae Young, it's your turn to plead your innocence.
I also shared my hint with you.
If it were me,
there would be no one else...
- you'd suspect alongside me. - What?
- What? - My partner.
(He argues that there's no female partner they suspect.)
No, we have one.
- Actually, there are a few. - The one sitting next to you.
Where were you when Jong Kook was eliminated?
That's when I found this hint.
(He's so proud.)
(You can't help but suspect this scanty alibi.)
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - I swear.
- I really... Seriously. - Kwang Soo.
- Who were you with? - I don't know.
- I was alone. - Do you have a witness?
Fashion design major... I was with the cameraman.
We can't trust the cameraman.
Where were you then, Jae Young?
I came down from upstairs.
- Who were you with? - I was alone.
(They can't prove the validity of the alibi.)
Let's do it this way.
Let's think about who is easier for us to deal with,
and give him a second chance.
(Let's do this way.)
(We should let the person who is easier for us to deal with survive.)
- That's a good idea. - Yes, if Kwang Soo survives,
- we'll be in trouble. - Things will get messy.
- If Kwang Soo survives... - Wait.
Ji Hyo.
We need to be 100 hundred percent sure about this.
- Wait. - It's Kim Jae Young.
(Unlike Ji Hyo, Seok Jin suspects Jae Young.)
No, it's Kwang Soo.
Even if it's not Kwang Soo,
we can defend ourselves from Jae Young.
- We can't do that with Kwang Soo. - Please make a wise judgement.
- But Ji Hyo. - Yes.
(Hearing the explanation sparks curiosity.)
- Why are you defending Jae Young? - Right?
- Right? - That's what I'm talking about.
(Ji Hyo has been getting worked up to defend Jae Young.)
- Right? - Right? It's weird.
Since this morning...
It was weird that they were holding hands in the car too.
I swear that it's not what you think.
I swear that it's not what you think too.
I really swear that it's not what you think.
Me too.
(The battle of pledging)
- Because... - Who can't pledge?
(Kwang Soo has pledged over 300 times.)
(With no concrete proof)
I'm so confused.
You have to think about this carefully.
I'll tell you about this.
(Suddenly, he wants to talk about it.)
- This isn't a threat. - Yes.
If I go up now,
I will tell you the important hint...
- about the relationship virgin. - Everyone knows already.
(I'll share everything I know.)
- Everyone knows already. - Among us...
We know it already. We shared the hint.
- Do you? - We do.
Why would you threaten the relationship virgin...
when you're single?
- I just want to spoil everything. - Why?
(I have nothing to lose.)
(Kwang Soo just wants to wreak havoc.)
I'll be out of this. What does it matter?
Why? How could you do that?
- I hope everything fails. - We're a team.
I'll share this with the secret couple.
(Browbeating)
Get rid of me then. It's not me anyway.
I'm innocent.
I'll just sacrifice then.
(I'll just sacrifice then.)
- He's so cool. - Then...
If he wants to go, let's just send him.
(No hesitation)
- It's what he wants. - No.
- What? - Jae Young is so cool.
- He is. - Because...
- Kwang Soo. - you can choose him afterwards.
I'm even more confused now.
Let's start voting.
(First trial's voting starts along with Jae Young's smooth acting.)
Please tell us the results.
The voting results were very close.
- Right? - Were they close?
- Were they close? - Is it six to four, isn't it?
It's six to four.
- Really? - You were very lucky, Kwang Soo.
(You were very lucky, Kwang Soo.)
(Was Kwang Soo lucky?)
The person who is going to be judged is...
(Kwang Soo tried to create a mess with a useless hint.)
(Jae Young tried to gain trust with a bold strategy.)
(What will the results be?)
It's Lee Kwang Soo.
What do you mean that I'm lucky?
(You're lucky that you were picked by just one vote.)
You were lucky.
(Trying to control his facial expression.)
1,2,
- 3. - Is he the one?
- No. - Look at that.
(Kwang Soo was just a single.)
(The back of a victimized man)
- Is it not? - I told you it Kim Jae Young.
- Is it Jae Young? - I told you that it was Jae Young.
(What should I do?)
I'm sorry.
(It is confirmed that Kim Jae Young is one of the secret couples.)
(What will be the fate of the secret couple?)
(The second half of the game starts.)
This isn't easy.
(Jae Young's strategy for the second half)
I'll hide near the emergency exit...
and wait for an opportunity.
(I'll hide near the emergency exit and look for an opportunity.)
We don't have much time.
How are we supposed to get him out?
(We need to find him first.)
- Hey. - Come here.
- Are you the relationship virgin? - I am.
Yes, I am.
I have to ride on their back or give them a piggyback.
(Jae Seok's way to eliminate the secret couple)
(One of the secret couple is out if the relationship virgin ride...)
(on the back of one of the secret couple or give them a piggyback)
- We will tell you something useful? - What is it?
If you give a piggyback to a member...
who is thought to be the secret couple,
or if you manage to ride on one of the secret couple's back,
the member will be out of the game immediately.
Do I need to ride on his or her back?
This is too difficult.
But if you get a member...
who's not a secret couple out of the game,
we will reveal the information...
- about you to everyone. - You will?
I see.
(Only the relationship virgin can get rid of the secret couples.)
- We have to find Jae Young. - Jae Young?
We aren't sure about Ji Hyo yet.
Let's get rid of Jae Young first.
We're going to be quite busy.
Se Chan, you go with Jae Seok.
I'll go with Seok Jin.
Let's go find him.
Jae Young might also have a way...
- to get rid of us. - You're right.
I don't think...
he has to remove our name tags to do that either.
I don't think so too.
- I think he has another way. - I'm sure he does.
He must have another way.
(On the other hand, Jae Young hides in the emergency exit.)
(When he's cornered, he can contact his partner only.)
(One of the three members is also going after...)
(the relationship virgin's name tag together with Jae Young.)
(First suspect, Jang Hee Jin)
I need to find the relationship virgin first.
Whatever happens, I need to find the relationship virgin.
(Hee Jin is obsessed to the hint about the relationship virgin.)
(Or...)
(Glimpsing)
(She looks at her phone secretly.)
(Ji Hyo keeps checking her phone when no one is around.)
(And one last person who is being suspicious.)
- She's acting suspiciously, right? - Yes, she is strange.
She keeps looking for us.
Se Chan.
(So Min keeps following these two around.)
Shall we run?
Why are you ignoring me?
I didn't do anything wrong. What's wrong?
- She is being weird. - Yes, she is.
- She's following us around. - I know.
(She keeps following Jae Seok who's known as the relationship virgin.)
She's always behind us.
It's weird.
Why would she do that? It's strange.
Why are you running away from me?
You know how much I trust you, right?
Let's just hide.
(They ditched So Min and continue to look for Jae Young.)
He hid himself really well.
I know, and it's a big place.
(Gosh)
It's a hint.
(While looking for Jae Young, they find this.)
(They discover a hint.)
(He finds a clue at the right timing.)
(What does it say?)
(The female partner of the secret couple...)
(a regular member of the show.)
(Hee Jin is excluded.)
(Ji Hyo or So Min is one of the secret couple.)
- It's not Hee Jin then. - It's So Min.
Wait, is it Ji Hyo?
- I'm so confused. - This is driving me mad.
Jae Seok.
We need to find Hee Jin.
- Hee Jin is not the secret couple. - Wait.
It's either Ji Hyo or So Min.
(The hint brings them back to the beginning.)
(They're worked out.)
Wait.
Is it So Min? Why did she keep following us?
(Suspect 1, So Min who kept following around Jae Seok)
The person who tried to protect Jae Young was one of those two.
- Ji Hyo? - Those two protected Jae Young.
(Ji Hyo tried too hard to protect Jae Young earlier.)
(20 minutes ago, during the trial)
(No, it's Kwang Soo.)
(Suspect 2, Ji Hyo who tried to protect Jae Young)
It's either one of them.
So Min...
- I'll try riding on Ji Hyo... - It's one of the two.
or So Min's back,
- but what if I'm wrong? - If you're wrong?
Then we're done for.
We can only get rid of one person by the voting.
Since we already know it's Jae Young, we need to vote him out.
But I might be out of this game if things go wrong.
The problem is that we don't know how they'll get rid of me.
(What should we do about this?)
(Hee Jin who's proven to be a single appears.)
I think the person who's the nearest...
to Jae Young is the culprit.
(She discovers Jae Young.)
(Her footsteps quieten.)
(Carefully)
I think if I follow Jae young around,
someone will appear.
It's him.
(Hee Jin's strategy is to trail the secret couple's meetup.)
Is he running away?
Isn't he running away?
(Jae Young is escaping with quick footsteps...)
(but he suddenly stops.)
I'm here early.
(He waits for someone.)
Why isn't she here?
(Did he see someone?)
(In the direction of where he was looking at,)
(Ji Hyo appears.)
(She carefully approaches Jae Young while looking around.)
(Jae Young...)
(also approaches Ji Hyo.)
Who is that?
That's right. It's Song Ji Hyo.
(That's right. It's Song Ji Hyo.)
I knew it.
(Then, these two people run off in different directions.)
What?
Why are they running away?
(Ji Hyo runs away with no reason...)
(and Hee Jin finds this suspicious.)
Why are they running away?
(She catches her at a dead end.)
- Do you want my name tag? - Why are you running away?
I saw you having a lovely time with your partner.
- What? A couple should... - Ji Hyo.
You're caught.
I was trailing Jae Young around.
- What are you on about? - But...
you appeared.
(Are you the secret couple?)
- Hee Jin. - And you told him...
"don't come closer."
I swear it's not me.
It's really not me.
Wait. Isn't that Jae Young?
- Where? - It's Jae Young.
- Where? - Over there.
He went over there.
He went over there. To that side.
This way.
He's there. Catch him.
(One of the secret couple, Kim Jae Young is found.)
(There are two of them.)
- Hey. - Hurry up.
- Come this way. - Where?
- Hee Jin. Wait. - Hurry.
- Wait. - Corner him.
Be careful.
Seok Jin.
The eighth floor.
(Jae Young couldn't attack Jae Seok and escapes to a hideout.)
It's Jae Young.
(Right then, the oldest solo was walking around the upper floor.)
- Come this way. - It's Jae Young.
- Gosh. - Jae Young is over there.
- Catch him. - No.
(The solo army unites as one.)
Gosh, he's...
- Catch him. - Let's go this way.
Wait. What's the point of catching me?
(Jae Young gets caught.)
There's nothing you can do after catching me.
- Hey. - Hold him tight.
We just need to eliminate him.
- How did you guys know? - It's not me.
Jae Seok, get him!
(The relationship virgin rides on his back.)
(His attempt to attack Jae Young is a success!)
Good.
Get him!
The male of the secret couple, Kim Jae Young is eliminated.
- We got him now. - We got him.
- Good. - We got him.
So that was his skill.
Could it be So Min?
I think it's So Min.
So Min tried to protect him.
- Me? You guys are mean. - So Min, I thought we were friends!
This is driving me crazy.
- Or is it Ji Hyo again? - I feel tight.
Ji Hyo, are you the secret couple?
I swear, it's not me.
- I'm telling you, it isn't me! - Is it So Min?
Can we have another hint?
- This is really upsetting. - Seriously, it's not me.
- I swear. - This is confusing.
- Who is it? - It's really not me.
(One of them is acting.)
(That's the end of the race!)
- The second trial will begin now. - Let's go.
We'll talk at the trial.
(It's their last chance to eliminate the secret couple.)
Today's race was...
the toughest of all time.
It's still confusing to the last minute.
We narrowed it down earlier,
but I still can't figure it out.
(The 2 suspects create a big-time confusion.)
I didn't even do anything today.
Seriously.
No, you did a good job.
- But guys, - Right.
let's think about it.
I don't want to suspect So Min,
since she's clearly upset about it.
- You always suspect me! - This will be the last time.
- Haha... - Last time.
- always suspect me. - We have no choice.
- Are you serious? - I don't know what your mission is,
but you went to Jae Young for a bite of the meal.
As if you really liked him.
I didn't ask for it.
- You did. - Jae Young gave it to me.
- Jae Young gave it to me. - You went to Jae Young,
and Kwang Soo stole that food.
When all that was happening and we were distracted,
it was Jae Young...
who gave you all that food.
- Jae Young gave her the food? - Yes, he did.
- Jae Young gave her the food? - No, it was Se Chan at first!
- I did give her at first. - It was Se Chan at first.
- Yes, he did. - He did give her the food.
As of today, I am officially dropping...
the title of the playgirl.
(She wants a new character.)
- Why? - Just like that?
I'd rather lose the title...
than be accused of something I'm not.
You wanted to be the playgirl.
- No one told you to be it. - Right.
It's already up to you to drop or take the title.
That's hilarious.
I have a question for So Min.
Why did I get the feeling that you were chasing...
me and Se Chan?
(Were you chasing me and Se Chan?)
(So Min did keep on following...)
(Jae Seok, the relationship virgin, and Se Chan who's obviously single.)
I was following Se Chan.
- I was chasing you. - Why were you chasing me?
- To get some hints! - Were you single?
Because I had no hint!
And no one...
See, at the beginning of the race,
Kwang Soo took my hint, so I couldn't see what it was.
We saw that.
Right, if there's the Relationship Virgin in here, hear me out.
I went to So Min,
and I talked to her, "I know you're upset."
"Are you really not the couple?" And she...
(I said, "I know you're upset.")
She cursed me out.
(That shows how upset she was.)
Hold on a minute, Ji Hyo did that too.
She cursed me out.
(Hold on a minute! Ji Hyo also cursed me out!)
And it was inappropriate for television.
I read her lips and it was clearly inappropriate for television.
- This is so confusing. - But you guys have to remember,
at our first trial,
Ji Hyo was the only one who was protecting Jae Young.
Let me just say this.
I'm really not the couple,
so if I were to step up there...
and I got eliminated, that would be fine with me.
That was a typical last resort.
- Jae Young said the same thing! - I'll talk.
- I'm pretty sure I heard it. - I'm serious.
- I'm innocent. - What did you hear?
Jae Young was far from me,
he didn't know I was there, and he said this.
- Jae Young said... - What did he say?
(Jae Young said something, not knowing Seok Jin was near.)
He said, "Where's Ji Hyo?"
It's exactly what he said.
(He was talking to himself during the race out of pressure.)
(Where's Ji Hyo?)
(Seok Jin was close enough to listen to Jae Young's...)
(suspicious monologue.)
Hear me out.
He could have said that to meet with me,
or he could have said it trying to eliminate me!
That's not right. Why would he say your name?
- This is so confusing. - It's okay.
The relationship virgin...
Wait a second!
(It's time to choose between So Min and Ji Hyo.)
This is...
- really confusing. - What if...
- So Min wasn't... - I can't choose.
- I don't know anymore. - Go with your first one in mind.
Isn't it weird that Jong Kook's team narrowly won the tug-of-war?
Okay, then I'll also...
If it's So Min, I'm going to freak out.
If Jo Hyo is the secret couple, it'll be really shocking.
We have the results.
- Really? - What's the score?
Once again, it was very close.
- Again? - It was 5 to 3.
So what? Someone's got to go anyway.
The last person to be judged is...
[VIU Ver] SBS E446 Running Man
"Find the Secret Couple"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
The last person to be judged is...
Song Ji Hyo.
(It's Song Ji Hyo with 5 votes.)
(It really isn't me.)
It's not...
It's not me.
(Those who voted for So Min think it's not Ji Hyo.)
Should I be worried that she's confidently walking out there?
- For real? - It's not me!
- No, it's not me! - Are you sure?
- It isn't me. - It's not Ji Hyo, you guys!
- It is Ji Hyo. - No, it's So Min.
(If Ji Hyo is the secret couple, the singles take the final victory.)
- 1, 2. - 1, 2.
(Only one vote has changed her fate.)
- 3. - 3.
(Is Ji Hyo the secret couple?)
(Ji Hyo was not the secret couple!)
It's not Ji Hyo.
- I told you! - It wasn't Ji Hyo?
(I told you it wasn't Ji Hyo!)
- No! - I told you it wasn't me.
I told you it wasn't her.
(The female of the secret couple was Jeon So Min.)
(How did you guys like my acting?)
I told you guys!
She looked sincerely upset!
(In the morning of the shooting)
(The secret couple, Jae Young and So Min met for the first time.)
Good. Thank you.
Should we go on dates starting right now?
(Should we go on dates starting right now?)
Don't we have something like...
- Missions? - Since we're a secret couple,
we'll need some sweet missions in public.
I'm sure So Min
will like these sweet missions.
(We've prepared some hidden sweet missions for So Min!)
- Are you okay with that? - Yes, I like them.
At every round, the secret couple needs to...
accomplish missions without being noticed by the single members.
Round 1, "Feed your partner."
- Just one person to another? - Just one?
- Either way, right? - Right.
(Round 1, choose your team.)
(So Min did not want Hee Jin to be on her team...)
(so that she can do the mission with Jae Young on the same team.)
(It's easier if we're on the same team!)
(Don't worry, So Min!)
(Jae Young pretends he's giving it to Ji Hyo,)
(and So Min pretends she's fooling around and steal it.)
(That was smooth.)
(They showed some teamwork to complete the 1st mission.)
If one person of the secret couple...
locks arm in arm with the relationship virgin,
the other partner will be able to...
eliminate the relationship virgin.
(The other partner of the couple may eliminate the relationship virgin.)
(Their strategy was to take out the most threatening enemy.)
(She approached Jong Kook naturally and locked arm in arm with him.)
You can now eliminate Jong Kook.
(I locked his arm. You can eliminate him.)
I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
(Jae Young succeeded in tearing out his name tag.)
(A beautiful couple's play takes out Jong Kook.)
(Yes!)
(And she finishes with perfect acting.)
The winners of today's race are...
So Min and Jae Young.
- They did a fine job. - Thank you.
- You guys made it so confusing. - Here,
- take these. - It was such chaos.
- Wow, what is it? - Wow.
Thank you.
- It looks pretty. - It's pretty.
Thank you very much.
Lying makes me exhausted.
This was the most confusing of all time.
It sure was. It sure was.
I'm not talking to So Min for a while now.
- What do you want me to do? - I'm not going to talk to you.
They're going to say something if I don't try hard!
(It's really not my fault.)
(Just for So Min,)
(we've prepared her birthday special.)
Hello.
Wait.
I just got here.
What is all this?
This place looks beautiful.
Will you tell me why I'm here alone?
Today is a special episode for your birthday.
(Today is a special episode for your birthday.)
- It's my birthday! - It is.
(Today is So Min's birthday.)
The title of the special is...
a thrilling real variety,
"Sulliver's Love Race".
Sulliver's race?
We've picked...
some of your partners from TV series.
To check how you would match them in real life,
you will be going on dates.
All of them are coming?
Who are you expecting?
(Who would be her matching counterpart?)
There's too many of them.
Kim Ji Suk.
Also, I worked with Oh Chang Seok and Ha Seok Jin before.
And long before them, there's Song Won Geun.
Who else... There's too many.
I'm fine with anyone as long as it's not Sang Yeob.
(As long as it's not Sang Yeob.)
(Why do you not like me, So Min?)
And if by chance,
Sang Yeob walks through that door,
I'm going home straight away.
He's been on this show too many times.
(Just 3 weeks ago,)
(they made it very clear, the two were too close like family.)
We referred to your romance dreams...
- to plan your date for today. - Yes.
All expenses will be paid...
by whoever you choose among the members of Running Man.
(Any member she wants)
It will be charged to that member.
(The chosen member has to pay for everything.)
(This is such awesome production crew and a show.)
I love it.
What's more important is...
whether I'd be able to enjoy the date without the guys.
Since you brought it up,
the members will be hunting you...
to stop you from charging them.
(The chase to stop the charge begins now.)
If you get caught, you will have to pay for everything...
that you have used that day.
(I knew you would do that.)
- Okay, got it. - If you get caught,
there will also be punishments.
And your date will be terminated.
(If she gets caught, her date is terminated.)
It's over when I get caught?
I go home after they catch me?
Okay.
That sounds like a tough one. I shouldn't get caught.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello! - Hello.
- It's still cold in Paju. - It is.
- It is cold. - Kwang Soo got a haircut!
(Kwang Soo got a haircut!)
I did get a haircut.
Why did you do it? You look bad.
- Why did you... - You shouldn't have cut it.
Why don't we show the viewers some consistency, Kwang Soo?
- There's nothing back there. - I can't even grab his hair.
You just look naked.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Go and get hair extensions.
Why would I do that?
- It's over, I already cut it. - The viewers are going to be...
uncomfortable looking at you.
- You look young, though. - He does.
Maybe 41 years old.
41 years old?
He said 41.
- That really upsets me. - He's in his mid-30s.
Where is So Min?
- Where did she go? - Where is she?
- I don't see her. - She's on something, again.
What we record here today will be aired on...
- April 7th. - That's her birthday!
- I see. - Oh, really?
- Okay. - So what?
For So Min's birthday...
Wait. It's her birthday special?
Yes, it's So Min's birthday special.
Are we buying her presents for her birthday?
- Please, she gets too picky. - She does.
- She really can. - Right.
She can get real picky.
So Min's birthday special for today is...
get thrilled or throw away,
Sulliver's Love Race.
Sulliver?
Isn't it Gulliver?
- Get thrilled or throw away? - Sulliver.
It's been 15 years since I last felt thrilled.
- You're lying. - You're lying.
- I don't ever get thrilled. - Stop lying.
You were thrilled when Yang Jung A showed up here.
(You were thrilled when Yang Jung A showed up here.)
- You did! - Be quiet.
- Why are you... - Shut it!
- keep lying? - Shut it!
- I said I don't get thrilled... - Why are you...
under any circumstances.
- Stop lying! - I don't get thrilled.
I won't just share what I know.
At this moment,
So Min is already on a date...
as she wishes.
- She's on a date? - Right now?
(Right now?)
- She's on a date? - This is madness.
- That sounds like So Min for sure. - Are we setting up...
So Min with other guys?
So Min's back of the ear will be bleeding by tomorrow.
She's going to get hurt.
It's going to leave a mark.
She does this too much in front of guys she likes.
- She's going to get an infection. - Right.
- I think she's already hurt. - She does it too much.
Why don't you two get ready?
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo)
- Get ready for what? - Get ready for the dating race.
(He's flustered!)
- Get ready for what? - Well, she's ready.
- Stop it. - She wants to do it.
She's drawing her hair back.
- Ji Hyo, get ready. - Stop it.
- Get ready for your love race. - Get ready.
He's going to Los Angeles.
But the thing is,
everything she does on her date...
will be charged to the person that...
So Min chose among you guys.
What? Why?
(The member chosen by So Min will be paying for everything.)
- My goodness. - That's not fair!
Why do we have to pay for it? She's the one on a date!
- Right. - What did we do wrong?
Before her date is over,
you have to find her and take out her name tag.
(That way, they don't have to pay.)
- Then it will be charged to her. - Yes!
- Okay, okay. - We need to take out her name tag.
Hold on, if we don't take out her name tag,
we pay for it and get punished?
She must be using tons of money.
We can't have that.
Clues about her dating course and location...
will be given when you complete certain missions.
- Okay. - We need clues.
Your first hint...
- is waiting inside the building. - Let's go.
Let's get her, guys.
Okay, good.
(7 of them enters the building.)
I mean, she's the one on a date,
- and we have to pay for it? - It's our money.
That's what I mean.
(They're entering the building.)
- What is this? - What is it?
- Are they the clues? - I think they are.
- Wait... - This is the escape room.
Another room escape? Sounds great!
- It's escaping the room? - Right, that's it!
What are these?
What's this?
(There are suspicious objects all around the room.)
(What is this place?)
What is it?
It says we can track her down when we escape from this room.
(You may track down So Min only when you escape from this room.)
(The main gate is locked. Where is So Min?)
Your first destination is...
a course meal restaurant.
That sounds great. In a fancy restaurant...
eating delicious course meal together with candles on.
That's why here are these candles.
(She's drawing her hair back.)
(She's waiting for the one to enjoy this date with.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E446 Running Man
"Sulliver's Love Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(He's here!)
Ji Suk!
(Ji Suk!)
(She greets him while clapping.)
(It's Kim Ji Suk, the top actor in the heart of a girl in an island)
(She picked him as someone who she was interested in.)
(They looked very good together in the TV series.)
So Min!
(It's been so long, Ji Suk.)
- How have you been? - So good to see you!
(They're hugging it out.)
How have you been?
(They meet after three months.)
We've finally met again!
Thank you.
(Thank you for inviting Ji Suk.)
Thank you very much. Ji Suk.
- Happy birthday. - Thank you, did you get up early?
- I did. - Was it far to get here?
You look more beautiful than the last time I saw you.
(You look more beautiful than the last time I saw you.)
(Her heart flutters.)
- Really? Today... - I mean...
- Do I look... - What?
Loot at me.
What?
(She's showing off her fancy outfit.)
- You look pretty. - Do I look pretty?
- And... - Did you dye your hair?
Yes, a little bit. It's weird seeing you...
in a place like this.
Is this awkward meeting me here?
I'm not...
(She looks shy.)
Do you feel awkward with me?
It's not that, I heard that...
I have a date tonight,
- I am here on a date. - and I'm embarrassed a bit.
(Her heart flutters again.)
- You're embarrassed? - Yes. Well...
I kept asking them that I wanted to be here.
- You did? - Yes. And it seems like...
you're saying random stuff about us.
I did not.
(Ji Suk wanted to ask So Min.)
(She panics out.)
I did not.
Why am I number 2?
When did I say that? I never said that.
You said Gong Myoung was number 1 and me, number 2.
(Gong Myoung is your number 1 and I'm your number 2?)
(She chose Gong Myoung last time without hesitating.)
- I'm just so embarrassed. - Do you like him?
Do you think he's good-looking?
That's not it, I was being polite to a guest of our show.
Well, I'm here. So change it.
Look at the camera.
(Look at the camera and say it.)
What do you want me to say? My ideal type is...
Is it Gong Myoung or Kim Ji Suk?
(Gong Myoung or Kim Ji Suk?)
It was actually Ji Suk.
(I'm sorry, Gong Myoung.)
(He seems satisfied.)
(I'll change it back when you come here.)
Why is it so awkward now?
I couldn't sleep well because I was too excited.
About all this dating stuff.
Stuff like this...
Can you look at me when you talk to me?
(Ji Suk is sad.)
No, I mean...
Here's the thing.
Ever since I joined Running Man,
I've never had such a sweet moment before.
(She went under a lot of physical activities and punishments.)
(She can't even look at him in the eyes.)
So, how about you?
We were filming at that island for six months.
Right.
So when I was coming here, I felt a little weird.
It felt different.
What kind of feeling?
It was different from meeting a character on a set.
Different in what way?
I got a little bit nervous...
when I heard that it was going to be a date.
I'm excited, are you not excited?
Well, I saw everything you did...
on television.
- That's not... - And on the news.
(I wanted romance with Ji Suk, but that didn't happen.)
- That's not true. - Why did you...
- say all that? - I was just...
embarrassed to call you.
Was I that focused on acting?
No, you weren't! Why don't we talk about it now?
- Yes, go ahead. - Have you ever...
had feelings for me while shooting?
(Now So Min asks Ji Suk.)
(They spent 6 months as a loving couple.)
(Has he ever had feelings for her?)
My heart did flutter.
(Ji Suk's heart fluttered.)
(So Min's heart flutters for the third time.)
Several times.
- Several times? - Yes.
Things you did without thinking...
made my heart flutter.
However, you went away as if nothing happened.
Was I the first one who acted like that on a set?
Yes, you were.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
We're having a meal while being on a date.
- This is a great place. - Isn't it amazing?
(It's warm and soft soup to calm them down.)
(How are the other members doing...)
(while they're on a dream date?)
(They start to search for hints to escape from the room.)
(They must escape to chase after So Min.)
- Hey, what's this? - What's this?
- What is it? - It's a drawing machine.
(They find a small drawing machine.)
A drawing machine?
(There are a lot of things inside.)
(Mysterious pieces of paper are inside clear capsules.)
If we escape...
from this place early, we can catch her right away.
- This is it. - It's a safe.
We must catch So Min.
- We need to open the safe. - We do.
(There's an alphabet password on the safe.)
- We need to open the safe. - Do we?
So Min is on a date while we're here...
Is there something inside?
Why are we in here?
Jong Kook.
- These cars... - There must be a hint here.
What about the TV? Why is there a TV?
Where's the remote control?
I should find the remote control.
(So Min and Ji Suk are on TV.)
Is this the remote control?
- What's this? - What?
(So Min is on TV.)
- It's So Min. - She's on a date.
Who is it? It's Ji Suk.
- It's Ji Suk. - It's Ji Suk indeed.
Look at So Min.
Are they on a date right now?
This is unbelievable.
- Wait, Jae Seok. - What?
Are they eating in there?
Right now?
They're eating upstairs.
- I smell food. - They're in this building.
Do you smell food?
- I do. - Yes.
- It smells like food. - It smells like garlic bread.
- It smells like food. - They're eating here.
- I smell bread. - Find them now no matter what.
We must get out of here.
(So Min and Ji Suk are having a date on the second floor.)
They're in here.
They're nearby.
(Once they leave this room, the upstairs is very close.)
(Once you escape from this room, you can catch So Min.)
There must be a hint.
(While they realize the truth on the first floor,)
(So Min has no idea on the second floor.)
What have you been doing?
- Me? - Yes.
I gained some weight and worked out.
Did you work out a lot?
Yes, I worked out so much...
while shooting that drama.
At that time,
I didn't know what was going on.
When there was no running water at your lodging,
- it was our first shoot. - Wait.
(So Min had no choice but go to Ji Suk's lodging.)
I was taking a shower early in the morning.
You told me to come out with clothes on.
I was afraid that you'd come out undressed.
I thought you were my stylist.
When I came out, you were standing in front of me.
(You were standing in front of me after I took a quick shower.)
You were wearing pajamas and holding a towel.
I was startled then.
Then this is what you said.
"When you leave, be careful."
"If anyone sees you, we'll be misunderstood."
That's right.
(That's what happened.)
You have something on you.
- Where? - I have nothing to wipe with.
There are no napkins.
(Here's some napkin.)
(She sticks out her face.)
(Can you wipe it off for me?)
(What did you say? What's wrong with her?)
(So Min has a secret that she can't tell.)
While being on a date,
all I do is make the other members pay for the date and run away.
However...
during the course meal,
you must make your date say and do...
five specific things.
Then you can move on to the next.
(I knew it.)
This isn't an easy date.
What are the five things?
He must say the word "pretty"...
and that his heart fluttered.
He must also say that he's jealous.
He has to cut the steak for you...
and wipe off the food from your mouth.
(How do I make him do that?)
Isn't that too harsh?
Unless he's an extremely sweet man...
(An extremely sweet man has appeared in front of So Min.)
(You now look prettier than before.)
(She gains 1 as soon as he arrives.)
(She tries to lead him on...)
(to make him express his feelings.)
(She clears the 2nd mission when he says that his heart fluttered.)
(She clears 2 missions quickly.)
(She has to make him wipe off her mouth.)
(She's fidgety.)
Wide it off for me.
(Do you want me to wipe it off for you?)
(She gets up.)
I'll come to you.
(If you really want it, I'll come to you.)
You have a lot on you.
Thank you.
(She clears the mission of having him wipe off her mouth.)
- Thank you. - Let's make it look pretty.
Let's make it look pretty.
- Pretty? - Let's do it again.
If you want to make it pretty,
we have to do it like in "Secret Garden".
When I eat,
you have to wipe it off with your mouth.
You have to wipe it off with your mouth.
I'll use my hand instead.
- Are you pretending not to hear me? - You don't realize it yourself.
Do you get it?
Okay, start.
(So Min doesn't realize that she has soup on her, and he finds it.)
(She opens her mouth wide and eats some soup.)
(It's delicious.)
(He looks at So Min lovingly as she has soup on her face.)
- So Min. - Yes?
- Right here. - What?
Where?
Gosh, you're clumsy.
(He looks at her gently.)
(Let's make it pretty like in a drama.)
(You have to wipe it off with your mouth.)
(He wipes it off with his hand instead of his lips.)
I'll do it.
Let me wipe it off again.
Thank you, Ji Suk.
He's such a detailed person.
By the way,
I had the most kissing scenes with you.
Every time I get closer to you,
(He had the most kissing scenes with So Min.)
it feels different.
(It feels different to see you here.)
- It's because of this set. - Right.
- Don't you think so? - You're right.
That's right.
Why do you keep repeating it?
What's so right?
It feels so awkward.
Let's change it then.
How? Shall we play a game?
How?
How about this?
We haven't seen each other in a while.
- Let's see if there's telepathy. - That sounds good.
How about this?
After a count of three...
(A test to see if their answers are the same)
Sea or mountain? 1, 2, 3.
- Sea. - Sea.
A drink that you enjoy having when you're tired.
- 1, 2, 3. - 2, 3.
- Coke. - Coke.
(I know well, don't I?)
I'll get everything right.
During the shoot,
what was your favorite food?
What? There are so many.
We recognized it...
as soon as we took the smell of it.
Do you remember?
1, 2, 3.
- Pork cutlet. - Pork cutlet.
(Their answers are the same 3 consecutive times.)
Let's do another one.
Who did we talk...
about the most behind their back?
(Who did we talk about the most behind their back?)
(The person we talked about the most behind their back?)
Can we say it?
- It's because you had affection. - It was out of affection.
- You wanted his love. - Right.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- Director. - Director.
(Our beloved director)
(Yes, that's right.)
He only liked Sang Yeob.
That's true.
He felt bad for Sang Yeob.
That's why...
he was most affectionate to him.
Sang Yeob wasn't well.
He was having a hard time.
That's why the director wanted to take care of him.
He thought that Sang Yeob was lonely.
You don't stop talking about Sang Yeob.
That's strange.
So what happened?
How did you feel?
Were you ever jealous of Sang Yeob?
(It's a direct question.)
(Please say that you were jealous.)
- I thought Sang Yeob... - I thought you liked Sang Yeob.
(I thought you liked Sang Yeob.)
That's a misunderstanding.
I don't have feelings for Sang Yeob.
You were so sweet to him.
- No. - To Sang Yeob.
I'm envious of Sang Yeob.
You're envious?
- Are you jealous? - Yes.
Did you do it on purpose?
- No. - Did someone order you?
- That's not it. - Why?
Were you ever jealous of Sang Yeob?
I was many times...
since our first meeting.
When I came back from the restroom,
the two of you were...
sitting so close.
When I returned, you stayed back.
- That was... - I didn't know you well.
I get jealous easily.
So?
Were you jealous?
I'll be honest.
I was a little...
(Please say that you were jealous.)
Speaking of Sang Yeob...
(Please hurry.)
(She must clear all the missions to go on her next date.)
(Will he say it?)
I should be...
more confident about myself.
(He changes his subject to being confident.)
(Confidence instead of jealousy?)
I shouldn't keep complaining.
Even if you mention Sang Yeob,
I'll accept it.
(This isn't what I wanted.)
I'm so curious.
(She doesn't give up.)
What are you curious about?
I'm wondering...
if you were jealous of Sang Yeob or someone else.
I answered. Why do you keep bringing up Sang Yeob?
(He's getting farther away from saying that he was jealous.)
I miss Sang Yeob all of a sudden.
(She makes a big impact.)
I understand what's going on.
(Did Ji Suk understand something?)
Listen.
(Did he realize it already?)
This is what I heard about when a man and a woman are on a date.
Women don't like men who make them...
- feel awkward and uncomfortable. - No.
(Misunderstanding is getting worse.)
Right?
That's why you miss Sang Yeob whom you feel comfortable with.
I suddenly wished that he were here.
So you're saying that...
- I'm not enough. - That's not it.
- If Sang Yeob is with us, - I understand now.
it'd be less awkward.
- I know. - We'd have a lot to talk about.
It's too boring for you...
to be with me only, right?
(It must be too boring to be with me only.)
That's not true.
(That's not what I mean, Ji Suk.)
That hurts both me and Sang Yeob.
That's not what I mean.
- I'm leaving. - No.
(She's close to ruining the date.)
Please don't go. Don't go.
You have to play with me today. That's why you came here.
(How will their conversation about Sang Yeob end?)
How do we get out of here?
(7 members are busy looking for hints.)
Is this live?
How do we open the safe?
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
I think we should put this in here.
- What? - Don't we insert this car...
(Should we insert this toy car in the socket over there?)
- Don't you think? - I think so.
Right? It seems like it.
"Power off"?
(Underneath the safe, there's a small hole...)
(and suspicious words that say "power off".)
(That must be it.)
This is it.
- Do we plug it? - Kwang Soo.
- Yes? - Use your long arm.
Your arm is long.
You may reach with your arm.
- It's done. - No, Seok Jin.
That's not it.
- I took a look. - This is it.
- This is it. - This?
I was wondering why it was here.
- It should be plugged in. - Plug it in.
Wait a minute.
I think this car should be turned on.
(However, there are no batteries.)
It doesn't work.
Are there any batteries?
(The car doesn't work without batteries.)
Batteries.
(While the toy car is not plugged into the safe...)
We have to insert money.
(Another group is working with the drawing machine.)
(Shall we take a look?)
- I can see it. - Here it is.
(Buzzing)
- We got it. - So Min is on a date while we...
Is there anything inside, Seok Jin?
(A transparent capsule is in the drawing machine.)
(He moves it carefully.)
(He smiles. That's right.)
(Clicking)
It came out.
(They draw one out and open it.)
- Is there anything? - No.
(It's just an empty piece of paper.)
(He's quite upset.)
(What's wrong with this now?)
(When it's frustrating,)
It's annoying.
(Let's just put this upside down.)
(She pours it out.)
It's upsetting.
- What are you doing? - We don't have time.
(Tapping)
Just do it.
(This isn't how to play it.)
It works. There's a T.
Hey!
- There's a hint. - We found something.
(They find a useful hint.)
It says "T".
- It's English. - There are hints.
- Did you draw one? - No, we drew several.
Open that one.
- Did you draw any? - There are more.
- Yes. - Did you draw any?
There are hints inside.
What is it?
There are hints inside the drawing machine.
- Is that so? - What is it?
- Why isn't it working? - Hints are in this machine.
(Do it like Ji Hyo.)
Just pour them out.
- Goodness. - There's a C.
My goodness.
- It works this way. - What are you doing?
Put them up here.
Put them up and take a look.
- T, O. - Do it like this.
- There's also a C. - It's English.
- Let's see. - There's an H.
Yes, H.
Goodness.
What is it?
It's English.
Can we make a word with these letters?
- W, H, O. - T, O.
Is there another T?
- T, O, T. - Are they based on colors?
- Isn't it "WOO"? - That's amazing.
- "WOO"? - Is it "WOO"?
That startled me.
- What is it? - That startled me.
(Kwang Soo collapses.)
(There's something under the table.)
- Who is it? - Is there someone?
Someone grabbed my legs.
He's a cameraman.
(Kwang Soo's cameraman went after Kwang Soo's legs.)
(Kwang Soo, it's me.)
(The cameraman and Kwang Soo become distant by 120 points.)
- Is it the camera? - Is it English?
It's English.
C, H.
- "Catch". - "Cha"?
How about "car"?
Isn't it "catch"?
C, A, T, C, H. It's not it.
- It is "catch". - No.
- "Catch". - There's a U.
- What is it? - W, A.
W, A, T, C, H.
- "Wow"? - It's "watch".
- "Watch". - W.
- It's "Watch". - "Watch".
- W. - There's an O.
Wait, let's do it slowly.
- Wait. - I have no idea.
O, U, T.
- Doesn't it mean out? - It's "out".
- O, U, T. - O, U, T.
Will someone be out?
"Watch out"?
It's "watch out".
- "Watch out". - To be careful?
- "Watch". It's "Watch out". - "Watch out"?
What does it mean?
- Be careful. - It means to be careful.
Does "watch out" mean to be careful?
- Yes. - Watch out.
Is one of us helping So Min?
Does she have a helper?
Does "watch out" mean to be careful?
It's him.
(At a time like this, it's always him.)
Come here. You looked suspicious after getting a haircut.
(Kwang Soo is suspicious because of his haircut.)
- What about me? - It's him.
What's wrong with you?
- Yes. - Wait.
- It must be Kwang Soo. - This one is right.
- Isn't it you, Ji Hyo? - It's not me.
I'm doing my best here.
- Isn't it you? - It's not me, Jae Seok.
It's really not me.
- Be careful, Ji Hyo. - It's not me.
(When they don't believe each other...)
There's a clock right here.
- Isn't this... - Kwang Soo.
(Hey, Kwang Soo!)
Before we understand the hint,
- don't get ahead of yourself. - What happened?
What do you know?
(There he goes again.)
He becomes serious only when we're stuck.
I understand that Jae Seok enjoys it.
- Stay still. - Is this how it's done?
It's "watch out".
It's "watch out". It means to be careful.
(Does "watch" indicate the clock?)
There's a clock.
(They search the clock that doesn't work.)
(Unlocking)
What?
"Even I will disappear."
(They find a hint.)
- What is it? - "Even I will disappear."
There's a hint in the clock.
"Even I will disappear."
(There's a phrase in the clock.)
- "Even I will disappear"? - "Even I will disappear."
- What? - "Even I will disappear."
(What does it say?)
There must be a spy among us.
Do we make...
a word with the hints in this room?
- Wait, Jae Seok. - What?
There's another clock, Jae Seok.
- What? - There's another clock.
Look at the time.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Can you bring down the clock?
Yes, bring it down.
Bring down the clock.
- Look. - It's in a strange place.
The clock looks crooked.
It looks strange.
(They look into the second clock.)
Someone just randomly put it up there.
Right, it's strange that a clock is here.
- There's something. - There is.
- Is there? - Yes.
(There's something.)
- There is. - "If standing up straight".
See?
"If standing up straight".
(It says, "If standing up straight".)
("If standing up straight"?)
- What does it mean? - "Straight".
Put them all together.
- They're over there. - Hey.
Does "watch out" mean...
to take the clocks outside?
Is there a way to escape if we find the clocks?
(Does "watch out" mean that they can escape if they find the clocks?)
"Standing straight" indicates something...
- different from what we know. - This must be it.
Really?
(What will be the result?)
(Their real escape starts now.)
(It gets scarier in the mysterious secret room.)
(They finally find a significant hint.)
(In the room with a blackout,)
(where's a beam of light coming from?)
(Their dreamlike date starts now.)
(Or so they thought.)
(So Min has another date other than Ji Suk.)
(Fight over me.)
(Will So Min be able to enjoy the soap opera...)
(that she has dreamed of?)
(And)
(Members chase after So Min who is in love.)
(So Min's race to keep her wallet safe starts.)
(How will their race end?)
(One Fine Spring Day)