- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Hello, Jong Kook. - Hi.
- Hello. - Look at you, Jong Kook.
- You're wearing a white shirt. - Look at his outfit.
- You're wearing a white outfit. - What?
- It has a picture too. - Goodness, Jong Kook.
- That's so cute. - What a fancy shirt.
- There's a picture? - What a cute outfit.
When people get old, they like fancy outfits.
(He can totally relate to it.)
(What?)
There's something Jae Seok...
- has to apologize to So Min for? - Listen. I should apologize to her.
I wasn't trying to set her up with a guy.
(Did he set up a date for her?)
I saw that. I saw the show.
- Me too. I saw it too. - I heard Sae Ho was in the area.
I was talking to Sae Ho.
He said he was lonely, so I told him about So Min.
But I didn't ask So Min if she wanted the date.
You didn't ask her first.
(What's the whole story behind the blind date incident?)
(Jae Seok asked Sae Ho about how he thought about So Min.)
(Trailing)
(He suddenly recommends Nam Chang Hee.)
(He feels bad to So Min for bringing her up.)
- I was so flustered. - Really?
I'm so sorry, So Min.
- Did you watch that? - I did. Sae Ho...
I mean when you're on a show, you try to be polite about it.
- You should if you can. - That would be nice.
But he looked he was totally offended.
(He straightened his face.)
- He did that? - Yes.
- He looked offended? - So Min.
- That's an exaggeration. - That was...
So Min publicly announced that she's available and lonely.
- Right. I'm on the market now. - That's why I asked.
- I... - No one is making a move.
- I thought about Jong Min. - No one made a move.
Jong Min seemed to like the idea.
- He liked it. - Really?
- He said he liked her. - But I bet she doesn't like him.
- But So Min doesn't like him. - Look at her.
(Shaking her head)
- No, he's great. - She knows her types too well.
- Why do we keep setting her up... - He's not dumb.
- with guys on variety shows? - He's not dumb.
- Won't she... - Stop it.
- Won't she be a comedienne soon? - No, listen.
- She's switching like Kwang Soo. - But still.
- Isn't she a comedienne? - Of course.
So Min will have to pay the membership fee pretty soon.
Right. She's almost a comedienne now.
And Kwang Soo is behind his fees.
I'm behind my fees?
- You're behind your fees. - My goodness.
You're unbelievable.
Would you choose Sae Ho over Jong Min though?
- Choose 1 between the 2. - All right.
- Jong Min versus Sae Ho. - It's too hard.
- Jong Min versus Sae Ho. - Jong Min versus Sae Ho.
- One... You must choose right away. - Jong Min's a good guy.
1, 2, 3.
Nam Chang Hee.
(She makes an unexpected decision.)
- Nam Chang Hee? - He's nice too.
- Nam Chang Hee. - He's a great singer.
- I like guys who can sing. - Chang Hee is?
- Is that so? - Jong Min is super good.
- He can sing and dance. - Hey, Jong Min is...
- a singer. - That's right. That's true.
- My goodness. - He's such a great singer.
Besides, Jong Min isn't stupid.
- He's totally fine. - Hey, hey.
It's Kwang Soo who's not stupid.
- "You're not stupid!" - "You're not stupid."
- "You're not stupid!" - I'm really not stupid.
Isn't that obvious?
- Both of them aren't stupid. - That's so obvious.
You're not attracted...
to Se Chan at all.
- So Min? - Me?
- There's no potential either. - I'm not interested in her.
Seok Jin, we're done with that topic.
When did that end?
(Cutting him off)
(Getting angry)
- When did that end? - It's because the writer...
flipped over the page.
- We just started this topic. - We're on another topic now.
- It was a bridge to another topic. - It ended with her answer.
- It was over when she answered. - When she answered,
- the conversation was over. - Right. It was over.
By the way, how do you know Pogba?
- You took a photo with him. - It was on your social media.
I saw the photo on your social media.
I've never seen him looking so small with someone else.
I've never seen someone put his hand around his shoulder...
- like he's a baby. - I know. That's the photo.
Jong Kook looked like this.
(Baby Jong Kook)
By the way, I was really surprised.
Pogba is as tall as Kwang Soo,
but his body proportion is totally different.
- Is that so? - What's wrong with my body?
It's always different with Kwang Soo.
This is the height I'm used to.
But he didn't look the same.
- Pogba has a muscular body. - It wasn't just his body.
And his face was as small as this.
(It wasn't just his body. And his face was as small as this.)
I mean...
- His body proportion must be great. - It's no joke.
But Pogba isn't considered handsome.
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - He's a world-class athlete.
- No, he's handsome. - Right.
He's not considered handsome, but if you're going to be tall,
you should have his physical traits.
- You're Bogba. - Not your physical traits.
- You're Bogba. - Bogba.
- Bogba. - What?
- How do you know him? - I heard that he was...
coming to Korea.
Did he contact you?
No, I got a call from someone who knows him.
- From his agency? - I got a call from them.
- Okay. - We filmed together.
And we played soccer together.
I went easy on him just in case he got injured.
(I went easy on him just in case he got injured.)
(This is a totally subjective opinion.)
- Hey, you went easy on him? - I'm telling the truth.
- He's unbelievable. - Jong Kook, I don't believe you.
- Really? - I'm being serious.
- You know what? - He's unbelievable.
I fell during the match.
I think that part probably will air.
- He fell once. - Let me be perfectly clear.
If you look closely,
I kicked Pogba's foot by accident.
I was so surprised, pulled back my foot, and fell.
I'm telling the truth. You should watch it.
I kicked Pogba's foot by accident.
I was so surprised, pulled back my foot, and fell.
(He did his best to go easy on a 200-million-dollar soccer player.)
My goodness.
All right. Today,
we'll have a break from the Fan-meet Project.
We've prepared this race for you who are preparing for the fan-meet.
It's called Invigorating Food of Alley Restaurants Race.
- Really? - Will Baek Jong Won join us today?
- It's a reward. This is so nice. - Will Mr. Baek join us?
- We ought to eat. - Yes, let's eat some food.
- I ate the triangular gimbap. - Me too. I shouldn't have eaten it.
To improve your health,
two guests recommended restaurants in Mapo-gu and Seodaemun-gu.
- Haha knows a lot of restaurants. - Right. He's from Mapo-gu.
- There are many great restaurants. - He lives in Mapo.
Two guests recommended restaurants in Mapo-gu...
- and Seodaemun-gu. - Really?
- They made the recommendations? - Is that so?
Let me introduce you to two guests who will join you on the race.
- Please come on out. - Who are they?
- Who are they? - Where are they coming from?
(Who are these guests...)
(that will join the race with the members?)
Who are they?
Welcome Chungha and Seol In Ah.
(Midnight Fairy, Chungha)
(Master of Breakdance Freeze, Seol In Ah)
(She showed groundbreaking freezes whenever she starred on the show.)
(What will she show us today? "Freeze" your channel!)
(When it hits midnight, everyone thinks of this singer.)
(Chungha, this amazing dancer, changes when she starts dancing.)
Why don't you introduce yourselves? In Ah. Chungha.
Hello, my name is Seol In Ah.
- I'm taking a break... - She's taking a break.
after "Special Labor Inspector Jo Jang-Poong".
- My goodness. - This is nice.
- "Jo Jang-Poong". - She's taking a break.
- Right. - You're on a break after the drama.
I heard that this episode will air...
- on June 23. - That's right.
- My album will be out on June 24. - That's right.
- My name is Chungha. - She must've come for a reason.
- "She must've come for a reason." - I'm glad too.
- You said she must have a reason. - Okay.
With Chungha, we'll be exchanging favors.
- That's right. - I hope you get what you came for.
- What did you say? - I hope your song wins first place.
- It will win first place. - Her songs always do well.
- Her songs sweep the charts. - Right.
- It's hard to be in the top 100. - Right.
- Don't you agree? - That's right.
What do you know about music?
Kwang Soo is a comedian.
Why are you two talking about music charts?
- They have nothing to do with it. - Right.
- Why are they talking about it? - I scolded him.
What do you know about music? Didn't I tell you?
Then should I have said it's easy then?
Be quiet.
Stay out of this.
Chungha, let's talk about your new song.
What's the title?
- It's called "Snapping". - "Snacking"?
"Snapping".
- Can you show us a snippet? - Really?
I bet this is going to be another great song.
- I can't wait to see her dance. - Chungha...
My gosh, it's nice.
(What kind of performance will she put on for this song?)
Didn't it start?
- It hasn't started yet. - It didn't, right?
- Not yet. You'll know. - It didn't start yet.
(Her posture suddenly changes.)
Did you see that just now?
(No way! That was so cool!)
This song sounds great.
(She changes completely as she starts dancing.)
- This is fantastic. - You didn't see it, did you?
- How can she move like that? - This is so hard.
(The girl with a small build exudes crazy energy.)
- Haha, did you see the beginning? - I saw it.
Hey, did you see her facial expression at first?
She looked all shy in the beginning.
- She went like this. - I got goosebumps.
- I was so surprised. - Seriously.
- Her facial expression... - It totally changed.
You know what? I bet it will only take 10 minutes for Chungha...
- to learn our group dance. - What? 10 minutes?
- Right. - It will take her five minutes.
- Hey. - That's so true.
- She'd master it. - She's so good.
- Her facial expression changed. - That was so nice.
That was crazy.
I bet it's a nice song.
I heard that In Ah and Chungha went to the same dance school...
- in high school. - Really?
- Really? - That's right.
Is this your first time meeting after the dance school?
- No. - No.
We hung out whenever we could while working.
Are you two in the same age group?
- Yes. We're the same age. - We're the same age.
- You're the same age? - You're the same age?
(I see. You're the same age.)
Why are you surprised?
- Why? - They're the same age?
- We weren't surprised. - Why?
- Don't look so surprised. - I was thinking of something else.
- That was a habit. It's my habit. - Listen.
I'm sorry. I react like that out of habit.
- She just looks mature. - That's right.
- In Ah looks like her age. - That's not important.
- Chungha looks so young. - Let's give it up for her.
(Let's give it up for In Ah who looks mature.)
- This is pity applause. - No, no.
- We're rooting for you. - Let's see when you turn 40.
- Don't worry. It'll stop there. - Because... Right.
- What you said made this weirder. - If you're serious, it's weirder.
- Stop it. - I looked like this in Turbo.
- Stop it. - I'm being serious.
- That's not helping. - Why not?
I'll be honest. We're just taking care of you.
Soo Mi had the grandma role when she was young.
(It's the nail in the coffin.)
Come on. Don't say stuff like that.
- How far will you go with this? - You bet.
- How far will this go? - "Country Diaries".
- That's right. - Your spectrum will widen.
Listen. These two used to...
- go to the same dance school. - Yes.
They prepared a performance for "Gotta Go".
- Let's give them a big hand. - All right.
I can't wait.
[VIU Ver] SBS E457 Running Man
"Zero Balance Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(In Ah is good too!)
(Her dancing skill is as good as Chungha's.)
(In Ah is great.)
- My gosh. - You guys are great.
- She's a great dancer. - Great.
(He's smiling broadly. "Both of them are great.")
(The original singer is doing her best.)
- That'll be enough. - She's like a machine.
- The song is good any time. - You were great.
- You are a great dancer. - No, no.
- By the way, - This move was great.
- they look different when dancing. - This was great.
By the way, I was a bit disappointed by Chungha.
- In Ah is a great dancer, you know. - Yes.
- She danced harder to show off. - No.
(She danced harder to show off.)
She won't go easy on In Ah.
- That made me root for In Ah more. - You did that, Chungha.
- Chungha danced harder. - Right.
Including these two guests,
you will participate in the race as individuals.
- It's an individual match? - It's an individual match?
As long as you spend a lot of money, you can win the race.
It's Zero Balance Race.
- We have to spend money? - Zero Balance?
We'll give out the cellphones for your mission.
You can spend 30 dollars with your cellphones.
The way you can spend the mission money is very simple.
You will visit restaurants the guests recommended...
and eat at the restaurants for your missions.
After each round, you can pay as much as you want...
for the bill the staff has set for you.
And you will pay in secret.
If the final amount isn't enough for the bill after everyone's turn,
the last member to pay and the member who paid the least...
- will split the remaining amount. - My gosh.
We have to be smart about this.
- We can't pay too little. - I have to be in the middle.
By the way, this will be hard.
- We have to be in the middle. - We can't be too petty.
If the final amount is more than the bill,
the member who paid the most...
will take the leftover money.
The member who paid the most?
This is another rule.
Doesn't it mean whoever pays the most has the advantage?
- This is confusing. - It's confusing.
After the race, the member with the most amount of money left...
in R Pay will win.
The winner will receive a penalty exemption ticket.
The member with the least amount of money in R Pay...
will choose a member to carry out a penalty.
They will face the water bomb.
- The water bomb. - No matter how well you play,
some people will face the penalty.
- Iron Min. If you do this, - Exactly.
Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, and I will...
- probably get the penalty. - Kwang Soo.
If you win the race, you will be exempted from this.
That's the hard thing to do.
- It's usually Jong Kook. - Goodness.
Even if I'm not in last place, when these members lose,
they always choose me.
There's this strange attraction.
(Jae Seok, potential member to face the penalty)
- Goodness. - However, during the race,
members who spend all of their money...
will face the penalty by default.
And they cannot pick another member for the penalty.
(On top of that, they can't pick a member.)
I'm getting a headache.
- Headache? - Gosh, I need some acetaminophen.
What?
(He suddenly mentions acetaminophen.)
- What is that? - Acetaminophen.
- Is that a headache medicine? - It's one of the components.
- You memorize that? - Acetaminophen...
- You memorize that? - Why?
- Why would you? - This isn't a health-related show.
- Why would you? - It's not something complicated.
You guys don't know what it is.
I doubt many people know what it is.
I seriously doubt that.
Isn't acetone enough?
- Nail polish remover? - Right.
That's all that we need to know in life.
- Nail polish remover. - Acetaminophen is unnecessary.
I will reveal three tasty restaurants...
that will serve you invigorating dishes.
Here they are.
We will go to all three of them.
(Invigorating Food of Alley Restaurants)
Goodness.
- What is that? - It means "clams and ribs".
I choose that one.
- Clams and ribs? - Yes.
Lobster, clams, and ribs.
(It's a collaboration between ocean meat and land meat.)
What is "beef steamed in hinoki cypress box"?
- Beef is in a hinoki cypress box. - It's in a hinoki cypress box.
- They put it inside. - You've tried it.
- It must be fragrant. - It's nice.
- All right. - I choose that one.
There's also boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms.
That one looks tasty.
Neungi mushrooms.
In Ah, which one do you like the most?
I eat boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms often.
- I see. - Actually, I had that...
- with my grandparents yesterday. - Really?
Seriously? You brought your grandparents?
She's a great daughter.
They loved it.
- I bet Seok Jin will too. - Right.
(I bet Seok Jin will like it just like my grandparents did.)
Why are you mentioning me?
That's right.
I'm not a grandpa.
He'll love it.
I don't like stuff like that.
- I like dishes like pasta. - Stop.
- I like risottos too. - You get indigestion.
I like Italian cuisine such as risotto and pasta.
- Nurungji risotto. - You should eat that.
- It's better for your digestion. - Right.
Come on, Jee Stream.
- His theme song has changed. - Really?
It's no longer Park Jin Young's song.
- It's a new song. - He went through the most changes.
- He has many charms. - You're unique.
Jee Stream is really something else.
Jee Stream is a cute nickname.
But when you made...
that trickling sound, that was a bit too much.
- Gosh. - The trickling sound.
The trickling sound.
- Am I an IV drop? - No.
He's an IV drop. He's a dropping pipette.
Jee Drop.
Jee Drop?
He has so many characters.
Give me one, will you?
Bed-Wetting Jee, Jee Stream, Jee Drop.
He has so many nicknames related to peeing.
- Shall we take our bags? - Okay.
We'll gather again after you change.
The weather is great.
Let's go eat.
Goodness.
If we surpass the price,
the first place will take the remainder?
- Just listen to your conscience. - Right.
- Paying enough is crucial. - Right.
While we're busy fighting about it,
- Jong Kook might win. - You're right.
- That's right. - I'm going to pay enough.
I bet he will.
Jong Kook has changed these days.
I'll pay what's due.
He's a bit crafty now.
(He's a bit crafty now.)
- What do you mean? - He's a bit crafty now.
- Me? - Yes.
Not at all. It doesn't suit me.
There's something I need to correct.
"Drop" is not the correct.
- It should be "IV drop". - "IV drop"?
So he will be Jee IV Drop.
(His nickname is changed.)
- It's much better. - It's changed.
- Jee IV Drop is... - It sounds weird.
- But we need to be exact. - Okay.
Call me Jee the IV Drop.
- It's like that LA Dodgers player. - Jee IV Drop.
Doesn't it?
Isn't his name Cody Bellinger?
- Yes. - Cody IV Drop.
- That's nice. - It's perfect.
- Cody IV Drop. - It sounds so wrong.
(We hope you become healthy once again.)
Chungha, what's your real name?
- What? - What's your real name?
- It's Chan Mi. - Chan Mi?
- Yes. - That's a pretty name.
It's pretty.
In Ah isn't your real name either.
Yes, I have a nice name. It's Bang Ye Rin.
You're a Bang?
Yes, I am.
- The surnames are different. - Her English name...
is more popular.
What is it?
- It sounds like Seol In Ah. - Right.
- It's Serena. - It's Serena.
- It's Serena. - Oh, Serena.
- Serena. - Serena.
- Serena. - How about you?
- It's Annie. - Annie.
- Annie. - Annie Kim.
- I haven't heard that in a while. - I'm Alex.
(Hi, Annie. My name is Alex.)
- Hi, Alex. - Yes, I'm Alex.
- Don't be silly. - I'm Alex.
You already have an English name.
- Cody. - You're Cody IV Drop.
- It's Alex. - You're Cody IV Drop.
- I'm Alex when I go abroad. - That's ridiculous.
Cody IV Drop.
- My gosh. - You already have a name.
I'm Alex.
- It's a nice name. - It sounds sophisticated.
Not at all.
Do you have an English name?
- Yes, I do. - Even Lia Kim has one.
- Perry. - They all had one.
- Right. - "Perry"?
- The sparkling water? - No, just Perry.
- He has an English name. - You do?
- Yes. - Tell me.
- Perry. - Why?
- Why is it Perry? - Dung Perry?
- Dung Perry? - Dung Perry?
(How dare he call the Prince of Asia Dung Perry?)
- Dung Perry. - Jong Kook knows.
- It's true, right? - Yes, it is.
But Jae Seok called me Dung Perry!
My gosh.
- He says I'm Dung Perry. - "Dung Perry".
- I'm seriously Perry. - You're Dung Perry.
Come on.
You pretended to look cool in front of me.
Cody IV Drop and Dung Perry.
Haha loves it.
- It's perfect. - Cody IV Drop and Dung Perry.
Dung Perry.
Cody IV Drop.
Dung Perry was a shock.
What about you?
I have one already. It's Sebastian.
- It suits you! - I'm Sebastian.
I'm Sebastian.
- Your name is in it. - Your name is a part of it.
My gosh.
- It's the perfect name for me. - You're right.
Sebastian.
- Dung Perry was nice. - That was hilarious.
I'm jealous.
(They arrive at a restaurant in Mapo-gu.)
This place looks delicious.
- What? - What?
(They spot something.)
Is there food on the table? What is that?
- What is that? - It's amazing.
(Lobster, clams, and braised short ribs)
- Look at that lobster. - It looks jaw-dropping.
There are many abalones.
- It looks good. - This is what we're eating?
- There's octopus too. - I want this so badly.
- Let's sit down. - This is amazing.
Annie and Serena, sit down.
Annie and Serena.
- Dung Perry. - Dung Perry.
Dung Perry.
- Sophie. - Sophie.
It's actually "pee" not "phie".
"Sopee".
If you win, you'll get the food and the order of paying.
It's called Water and Fire Quiz.
(Water and Fire Quiz)
You'll be split into teams of 2 and playing simultaneously.
They'll be multiple-choice questions.
The team that knows the answer must say, "answer".
Afterwards, they'll come up front and make their choice.
In five seconds, they must use a water gun...
to fill their teammate's mouth.
His or her teammates must extinguish...
as many candles as the number of the multiple choice answer.
(If the answer is number 5, they need to extinguish 5 candles.)
(They need to collect the water in their mouths...)
(and extinguish the candles.)
What kind of game is this?
- With the water in our mouths? - How?
For example, if the answer is number three...
My gosh.
This is so hard.
- I have a big mouth. - He does.
You should collect the water.
Having a lot of water in your mouth isn't necessarily good.
Why is he picking on me today?
- Why? - Dung Perry,
it's not necessarily good, okay?
You'll be partnering up.
If you get it right, you'll both receive a dollar each.
Really?
If you get it wrong or fail to extinguish the candles,
a dollar will be deducted from both of you.
We'll lose money.
- We get deducted. - Yes.
- There are three questions. - Okay.
Only those who get it right may eat.
I bet Jae Seok will win.
One member of the team...
that has the least amount of money...
- will be the last one to pay. - Only one person?
- I told you that the one... - One person?
who paid the least and the last...
- would split the bill, right? - Yes.
I hope I don't partner up with Se Chan.
If you become my partner, we're going to lose.
(Here)
What? Hey.
(Just take this spoon.)
What are you doing?
You just handed him a spoon.
You don't know how this works.
He just handed it to him.
The yellow looks good on you.
My gosh.
You don't know who your partner is.
Mix them up. Make it interesting.
I should be anticipating.
I want to feel anxious.
Okay.
(After mixing the spoons, he hands him one.)
How did you do it?
- It must be the same one. - Let's do it again.
- It's the same one. - How?
- Hey. - He's good.
He has quick fingers.
- Hey, mix them up. - Fine.
- Someone else can pick first. - All right.
(They pick out their spoons fair and square.)
I got white.
- Okay. - Okay! Great.
All right.
If you know the answer, tell us.
- Okay. - Then you can extinguish the fire.
Here is the first question.
Which of these choices is not mentioned by Jeong Yakyong...
- In Namyangju... - as a way to spend the summer...
according to his book "Eight Tips on How to Spend the Summer"?
- This is hard. - It is.
Number one, shooting arrows in a pine tree forest.
Number two, swinging under a zelkova tree.
Number three, playing pitch-pot alone at an empty gazebo.
Number four, eating hot food.
Number five, listening to the sounds of cicadas in a forest in the east.
Number six, playing baduk on a bamboo mat.
- Answer. - We said it first.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo get a chance to answer.)
- Do this. - Okay.
- What's your answer? - We choose...
- Number 2! - Number 2?
- I think that's right. - Which is?
- What? - What is it?
(They don't know.)
- Number one. - Come out.
- Which is? - Number one.
- Pitching under a pine tree. - Under the pine tree...
Come out.
They don't remember it.
A dollar has been deducted.
- Answer! - Okay.
- Which one is it? - Number three.
Should I do it?
- And what is it? - Which is?
Playing pitch-pot alone at an empty gazebo.
Okay.
- What should I do? - Do it slowly.
From this far away?
Isn't this too far?
Get ready. You're given five seconds.
Ready, set, go.
(She shoots the gun.)
(In Ah is drenched from the start.)
- Serena! - She has a big mouth.
- 1, 2, 3. - My gosh.
Why do you have such a big mouth?
- Three candles. - She has a lot of water.
(She needs to extinguish 3 candles.)
(Will she be able to do it?)
She has a lot of water.
(She spits it out.)
(However, she doesn't extinguish any of them.)
- That was close. - Answer.
- Answer. - Answer.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
It's not easy.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo try again.)
Number three.
Pitching in an empty gazebo.
(She's confident.)
- Pitching? - Pitching?
What are you doing?
Come on!
(He explodes.)
(She's embarrassed.)
- We got it wrong last time. - This is hilarious.
Are you talking about a helmet?
What are you doing?
Can we please play the game?
You said that before.
I was in a hurry.
- That's the wrong answer. - Okay.
- I was in a hurry. - Come on.
How could you say that we were wrong right away?
- The answer is number 3. - Number 3.
Playing pitch-pot alone at an empty gazebo.
(He's focused.)
I'll start from... I'm sorry.
- Hey. - I'm sorry!
(He accidentally shoots...)
(at Jong Kook's pants.)
I'm sorry!
(He makes a mistake.)
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean it. - That was intentional.
- That was, right? - I miscalculated.
Hey, don't do that.
Hold on.
It's embarrassing to watch. Can you lower your shirt more?
(It's embarrassing to watch. Can you lower your shirt more?)
Hey!
- You jerk! - I mean...
- What have you done? - I didn't know.
I didn't know that would happen.
- Just wet all around it. - Wet all around it.
- Do that. - Okay, mind your own business.
- Jong Kook. - Mind your own business.
- Use this to dry it. - Hey!
(Use this fire.)
- Use this. - It'll burn it!
- It'll burn it! - My gosh, So Min.
What if my pants burn?
Don't do that!
They shouldn't burn.
It'll burn the pants, not dry them.
Ready,
- set, go. - Goodness.
(Spraying)
Oh, no!
They're stable.
They're good.
(Now, he needs to extinguish 3 candles.)
You shot his nose intentionally, right?
Extinguish them one by one.
(Suddenly,)
- Two of them got extinguished. - Hold on.
(2 of the candles are extinguished.)
- They're extinguished. - What?
Nice!
I did that.
- You just need to extinguish one. - That's right.
Aim.
(If he extinguishes more than one, they'll fail.)
- Aim. - Aim.
(What?)
Aim.
- A bit more. - What is that?
- My gosh. - What is that?
- What is that? - He did it!
(He's a human water gun.)
(What is that?)
(He extinguishes 3 candles.)
My gosh, Jong Kook!
(He makes anything possible.)
(What is going on?)
(Why does he have a water gun in his mouth?)
How is this possible?
- All right. - All right.
You chose number three.
Gosh, we're wrong.
(It wasn't number 3.)
What he did was so cool.
It was amazing.
I used to do that back in middle school.
He used to be a gangster.
- Answer! - Eating hot food.
Number four.
- Okay. You may start. - Serena and Annie.
- Go. - Here I go.
- Goodness. - Here I go.
(Staggering)
- It's really strong. - Hey.
(She moisturizes her skin for her comeback.)
Do you really have to do this to her when she's making a comeback?
- She collected a lot of water. - She did.
- Extinguish 4 candles. - 4 candles.
- Four candles. - I don't know if she can do it.
(Murmuring)
(What? Did she get four of them?)
(The candles catch fire again.)
(She lacks power.)
- Answer! - Answer!
Answer! Number four!
Answer! Number five!
- Which is? - Eating hot food.
(She claims number 5 is "eating hot food".)
("Eating hot food" is number 4.)
Answer!
She just did that one!
What's her deal?
- What's wrong with you? - You said number five.
- Come on. - You said it was number five.
- It's number five. - Ji Hyo, you're hilarious.
Kwang Soo's team hasn't had the chance to do it.
I want to get wet too!
- Hey. - Come on.
You're so dry.
We haven't had the chance.
(I want to play with the water gun too.)
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo attempt again.)
- Answer! - Answer!
- Number four! - Yes, Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo?
- Which one? - You should answer.
- Number 4. - Number 4.
- Eating... - Eating... Hold on. I'm sorry.
(He stops her from talking.)
Eating hot food.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Finally. - It's his first try.
I know.
Finally.
(This is what he's been waiting for.)
(I'll aim well.)
Go.
(She begins shooting.)
(What's going on?)
Oh, no.
(I'll help you.)
(Is this how it works?)
- Collect the water! - Oh, no!
(The water pressure is remarkable.)
- Look at him. - Don't swallow!
- Look at him. - Don't swallow it!
He swallowed it.
Don't throw up.
- He drank a lot. - He's Groot.
- Go, Groot. - Do what Jong Kook did.
(Is this the only way they can win?)
(Wriggling)
- He can't aim. - It's working.
- He can't aim. - He can't.
(The water goes everywhere.)
(The candles are burning strong.)
- Where is it coming from? - It's not working.
- Why does it come out like this? - Answer!
- How is that possible? - Answer!
(The water avoids the candles.)
Ji Hyo should do it.
- Answer. - Answer.
- Go first. - Eating...
- Number 4. - Number 4.
- Eating hot food. - Eating hot food.
I don't even know if this is the right answer.
- It could be wrong. - It could be.
- Right. - I think...
(Jong Kook is the shooter this time.)
Look at that skill.
You look like a catfish.
(Se Chan's mouth is just the right fit for this game.)
- Done? - He's a fresh water catfish.
- Good. - I've seen a fish like that before.
(He's going to aim for the last 2.)
Left first? Good.
Then the right? All right. I understood everything.
(Spitting)
(Did he get all 4?)
(They reignite.)
It's okay. Stay calm.
- You're aiming too low. - Let's do it.
Okay!
(He extinguishes 2 of them.)
(I still have more water.)
Okay. Just repeat what you did.
Do the same thing.
(This is his 3rd attempt.)
- There's more. - There is?
- How much more does he have? - Good.
Does your body produce water?
- Good. Go stronger. - Does your body produce water?
(What?)
You did it!
(He extinguishes 4 candles.)
- I still have more left. - Let's see if this is right.
- Let's find out. - You chose number four.
Is it right?
(They get it right.)
Jong Kook!
(It was the right answer.)
(Their cooperation has become a success.)
- Jong Kook. - We did it.
Good job.
- Okay. That was good. - Okay.
Since it seems like this is too hard...
- It is. - How about getting three of them?
- Wouldn't that be easier? - Yes.
- We'll do that. - Okay.
The number you choose doesn't matter.
As long as you get at least three candles, you can answer.
- Okay. - We'll start.
We must succeed.
Next question.
Yang Guifei was the beautiful consort of China.
I've heard about her.
She rolled this in her mouth to cool herself down.
- What? - What was it?
Number one, a Korean cherry.
Number two, a pearl.
Number three, a jade marble.
Number four, a gold ring.
Number five, a steel marble.
Number six, a silver spoon.
- Answer! - Answer!
- Answer! - Seok Jin.
- Go. - Number four, a gold ring.
- Go on. - Let's do it.
It's number one, a Korean cherry.
Go on.
It must be gold. It's harmless to consume too.
If it's pure gold, wouldn't it bend inside your mouth?
- What? - Wouldn't it bend?
It's a gold ring.
So what if it bends? It's okay.
Seok Jin, you need to hurry! Open your mouth!
(Panicking)
(He extinguishes 5 candles.)
Okay!
- I hope it's right. - It needs to be.
You chose number four, a gold ring.
- Is it right? - Please.
- Answer! - Answer!
Ji Hyo.
- Go. - It's...
- Which one is it? - It's number one.
- Number one? - A Korean cherry.
- A Korean cherry. - It's a cherry.
It's a cherry.
- A cherry? - Yes, it is.
Let her be.
- Let her answer. - What is it?
You heard it, right? I didn't.
- What's your answer? - It's a cherry, Ji Hyo.
- It's a cherry. - It's a cherry.
- Number one. - Okay.
- What is it? - A cherry.
I thought you knew.
You said it was number one for sure.
Number one?
(Ji Hyo doesn't want to be ridiculed anymore.)
A cherry?
Answer! Answer!
(She's fallen in their trap.)
Answer!
A Korean cherry.
(He steals her answer.)
- Which number? - Number one, a Korean cherry.
- Number one, a Korean cherry. - It's a Korean cherry. I was right.
I was right.
- You're duped again. - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, that's enough. - You're so gullible.
I thought it'd be either a Korean cherry or a jade marble.
It must be correct.
(The two steal Ji Hyo's answer and finally get a chance.)
Okay!
He extinguished them all.
Everyone is getting the hang of it.
- Answer! - What?
- We're wrong? - Answer!
- Answer! - Answer!
- Answer! - In Ah was quicker.
In Ah.
Should I say it?
- Number five. - Which is?
- Steel marble. - Okay, go on.
- Let me do it. - She put that in her mouth?
- It's not good for you. - It's not.
(They choose the least popular answer.)
This is really difficult.
- Serena! - She did it.
- She passed. - Okay.
- What is the answer? - A steel marble.
Number five, a steel marble.
(I'm next.)
(They get it right.)
(Does that even make sense?)
How does that even make sense?
It's dangerous if you swallow.
What if it rusts?
(They acquire the meal card and a dollar each.)
A steel marble?
Every time someone said a number, Ji Hyo would whisper,
"This is the answer."
When another person answered, she'd say, "It's this one."
(Ji Hyo kept telling him the wrong answer.)
Why did you do that?
They all seemed right.
Here's the last question.
- Okay. - We need to get it.
We should!
- Number 4, Hongcheon. - Number 4, Hongcheon.
(Jae Seok and Haha say the correct answer...)
(after an amazing water show.)
(All questions have been answered.)
The members who can have lunch are...
Jae Seok, Haha,
Chungha, Seol In Ah,
Jong Kook, and Se Chan.
You can have lunch.
- Let's eat first. - Let's do that.
The members at the bottom are...
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are at the bottom.)
(Us?)
(We didn't end up at the bottom.)
- We're not at the bottom. - One of them...
- will pay for lunch. - They lost a dollar every time.
But they didn't try...
more than a couple of times.
I mean...
I wanted to try, but...
If you don't have enough money,
the one who paid the least will pay the rest.
You two...
This is important.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Or...
we fill one water gun with water...
- and leave the other empty. - Okay.
- You choose one of them. - All right.
We shoot each other in the face.
Choose one of...
the water guns we're holding.
The one who chooses the water gun filled with water...
- loses, right? - Yes.
It's definitely Jae Seok's water gun that's filled.
I choose Se Chan.
Why do you choose first?
- She has a point. - That's right.
Play rock-paper-scissors to decide who should choose first.
(They play rock-paper-scissors to decide who should choose first.)
(Ji Hyo will choose first.)
Jae Seok.
- No. I choose Se Chan. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo thinks Se Chan's water gun is empty.)
- Water... - What's going on?
(Water)
What's going on? What's wrong?
It suddenly released water.
Why...
- Water came out. - It suddenly...
(Wait, let me think.)
I choose Jae Seok.
(Then I have to choose Se Chan?)
- All right. 1, 2... - 1, 2...
Three.
It was Jae Seok's.
Okay!
(Although it released water,)
(Se Chan's water gun turns out to be empty.)
Ji Hyo, why did you choose mine?
It suddenly released water on its own.
Why did I change my mind?
Why did you choose mine?
Ji Hyo died while trying to live.
Right. I died while trying to live.
(They have lunch after Ji Hyo is confirmed to be at the bottom.)
(It's time to restore energy.)
(All kinds of fresh seafood are prepared.)
- 1 for 2 people? - Oh, my.
- It looks so tasty. - Oh, my gosh.
It's steaming.
This happens every time I'm with Kwang Soo.
- Hey, stay away from me. - You'll be penalized today.
For this round, you have to pay 25 dollars.
(The amount decided by the staff is 25 dollars.)
(If divided equally, it's 2 dollars and 50 cents per person.)
- That's not bad. - Then...
The person at the bottom should think a lot.
- And the person who paid the least. - Right.
If we pay more than 25 dollars, the person who paid the most...
- gets the extra money, right? - Right.
Do you think we'll pay more than 25 dollars?
Even if does, the extra money won't be much.
The food is already cooked. You can go ahead and start.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Lobster, clams, and braised short ribs)
(It tastes amazing.)
- It looks so tasty. - It's very savory.
(They put the plump lobster in their mouths.)
It tastes so good.
This...
That and a piece of lobster for a dollar.
I'll eat this.
(Don't be absurd.)
(What should I do with him?)
A piece of galbi for a dollar.
- I'll eat it. - A dollar.
- I'll eat it. - I'll give you a dollar.
- Two dollars. - I'll give you.
- I'll give you two dollars. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
You lose if you don't show anything.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Hold on.
- Give it to Seok Jin. - Okay.
- How much? - Two dollars.
- Go away. - All right.
- Two dollars. - Go away.
- I'm giving Haha 2 dollars. - 2 dollars to Haha.
Hey, go away.
- Abalone looks tasty. - Go away.
I might drop it.
Stop it. I might drop it.
Squid in gochujang... Gosh.
(Ji Hyo takes it.)
Hey!
(While Seok Jin was distracted by Kwang Soo,)
(Ji Hyo takes the lobster.)
- Give it to me. - Gosh.
(Kwang Soo steals the galbi and fishcake.)
- He must be so annoyed. - You said you'd share it with me.
You said you'd share it with me.
You... How could you...
- It tastes so good. - The fishcake tastes amazing.
I want the small octopus.
Small octopus for a dollar.
I didn't know you'd sell food.
- It sells so well. - Right.
It tastes amazing.
(A guest arrives.)
- Don't give her anything. - You're so good.
(The owner next door...)
(gives her a lobster shell.)
Hold on.
- Isn't it this? - Stop.
Isn't it this?
(It's the piece on Yondu's head.)
- Yondu. - Yondu.
- That's it. - Yondu.
- I thought it looked familiar. - It's Yondu.
Yondu.
I'm discouraged because you brought up Yondu.
I'm embarrassed.
Yondu even became the most searched word.
(Embarrassed)
The last.
5 seconds. 5...
Seok Jin, we'll play rock-paper-scissors...
- and the loser pays for the winner. - Okay.
- A dollar. - A dollar.
- Small octopus. - We'll buy small octopus.
I want it too.
- This too. - Okay. A dollar.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Okay!
(I can't let you eat.)
(Fighting)
Be careful! It's sharp.
(Stealing)
(While the two fight,)
(Ji Hyo steals the small octopus.)
(Ji Hyo is a habitual thief.)
Unbelievable.
This area is so rough.
Lunch time is over.
(The fierce lunch time is over.)
I can't guess what they'll do.
They have to pay even though they didn't eat anything.
(Thinking)
- That doesn't make sense. - Right?
- Their psychology... - They wouldn't want to pay.
They wouldn't pay a lot when they didn't eat much.
Still,
if we pay more than the bill,
the one who pays the most can get the extra money.
They might take a risk.
The most concerned ones...
- are the person at the bottom... - Right.
- and the person who pays the least. - Think about this.
If many people pay a small amount, it becomes equal.
- Right. - If 3 people pay a dollar...
It becomes equal.
I've sent each of you how much money you have.
Really?
I got it.
(They're informed of the amount of money they have.)
Seok Jin has the least amount of money right now.
What?
- Me? - It's because...
- you bought a lot of food for us. - You bought food for us.
Thank you. It was tasty.
My goodness.
- You're amazing. - I'm full, to be honest.
Everyone except Ji Hyo...
will pay one by one, in whatever order you want.
In whatever order we want?
- Say how much you want to pay. - I didn't even eat much.
I don't want to pay.
- Let me go first. - Okay.
- Let me pay a little. - How much will you pay?
- You're generous. - Pay a lot.
Pay about eight dollars.
- To make it easier for you, - 10 dollars?
- I'll pay about 10 dollars. - What?
Seriously?
Jae Seok, how much would you like to pay?
(Thinking)
(He accesses the payment page by scanning the QR code.)
All right. Should I enter the amount here?
(It's time to enter the amount on his phone.)
Jae Seok, pay a lot.
(Lobster, clams, and braised short ribs cost 25 dollars.)
To make it easier for you, I'll pay about 10 dollars.
(How much will the first person pay?)
(2 dollars)
(Jae Seok paid only 2 dollars.)
To pay two dollars and pay the least,
- the others have to pay 3 dollars. - 3 dollars.
But no one would want to take such a risk.
Two dollars would be safe.
Should I go next?
Pay just the right amount.
Jong Kook will definitely pay two dollars.
Two dollars.
(As expected, he pays 2 dollars.)
(Trusting the other members, he sticks to 2 dollars.)
Done.
- Annie. - Chungha.
- Show us some waacking. - Waacking.
- Show us some waacking. - Waack.
Two dollars.
(Chungha pays 2 dollars as expected.)
(Is everyone playing safe?)
(The members pay secretly one by one.)
- This is a gamble. - How much would you like to pay?
Five dollars.
(In Ah pays 5 dollars.)
(In Ah pays more than most of the other members.)
No one would pay 3 or 4 dollars, right?
Unless someone pays a lot...
to take the extra money...
If we pay more than the bill, someone can take the extra money.
- This is hard. - Let me know one person's amount.
(Ji Hyo pays last.)
Just go for it. Do it.
(If the total amount they pay is not enough for the bill,)
(Ji Hyo has to pay the rest.)
Regardless of whether I pay the least or not,
- I'll have to pay, right? - You'll have to pay.
If you guys pay more than 25 dollars,
there'll be no problem.
It's better to pay a lot. You'll pay anyway.
But you get only the extra, so think carefully.
It's better to pay less. Think about it.
Ji Hyo, no one can...
- No one can predict the result. - No one can predict the result.
You can't help it.
(Thinking)
I...
(Will she pay a lot to take the extra money...)
(or pay little and watch how it goes?)
(What is her choice?)
I have to pay anyway,
so I won't pay anything now.
(I won't pay anything now.)
(Ji Hyo does not pay anything.)
All of you have paid now.
Tell us if we paid more than the bill.
- Please. - I don't think we paid more.
- The total amount paid is... - How much is it?
(Did they pay more...)
(than 25 dollars or not?)
(How much did the 10 members pay in total?)
29 dollars.
- Oh, my. - It's over 25 dollars.
- 29 dollars. - Oh, my.
(It's 4 more dollars.)
How did it exceed 25 dollars?
I guess they paid a lot.
Did someone pay four dollars?
The extra four dollars go...
to the person who paid the most,
- So Min. - How much did you pay?
The person who paid the most, Jeon So Min.
How much did you pay?
(How much did So Min pay?)
- So Min would take a risk. - She would.
She'd take a risk.
10 dollars.
(10 dollars.)
(She paid as much as 10 dollars.)
I still lost money.
- What? - I lost money.
How much did you pay?
Did you pay a lot in order to win, didn't you?
Did you pay 10 dollars?
I don't know. How much did I pay?
In any case, four dollars which exceeded the total cost...
will go to So Min,
That's incredible.
Those who paid little...
also benefited from this round.
- That's right. - Who?
Who paid little?
I bet Ji Hyo paid a lot.
You didn't pay, did you?
- You didn't pay, did you? - Did anyone not pay?
- You didn't pay, did you? - I paid.
Everyone paid.
That's too ballsy.
You could end up paying the remaining amount.
Let's move on to the next location.
(It's time to eat the next invigorating food.)
Come on!
(The members' current amount of money)
Gosh, it already smells good.
I smell hinoki cypress.
- It smells good. - I know.
It smells good.
Can we open the lid?
- Let's go. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Beef steamed in hinoki cypress box)
It's bound to be tasty.
Is that beef brisket?
- It's beef brisket. - Gosh, it smells good.
This will reset our palate.
Gosh, the aroma is insane. I must eat it.
- I must eat it. - You can dip this...
- in a sauce. - I must eat it.
Beef steamed in hinoki cypress box...
and the order of payments are on the second mission,
Race of Witty Answers.
- Race of Witty Answers. - Race of Witty Answers.
It sounds like...
- my kind of a game. - It's about wits.
He loves games of wits.
You will play independently.
You will answer...
- in the methods of Race of Wits. - Okay.
When the production crew gives you a theme,
stand up and give an answer with the number of Korean letters...
that is in accordance with the order.
Use your wits to decide when to stand up.
(Members who stand up simultaneously will be eliminated.)
The faster you go, the easier it is.
The last person will have to give a 10-letter answer.
Only four people will get...
- to eat the beef. - Four people.
(Only four people will get to eat.)
- Let's do this. - I must eat this.
- Let's go. - I will go first.
- Okay. - Those who wait will win.
Let's begin.
Where do you want to go right now?
Guam.
(Where do you want to go right now?)
- Tokyo. - Ladies' room.
Israel.
(They are good.)
Budapest.
("Budapest" has 5 letters in Korean.)
(Hesitant)
(It's time to give a six-letter answer.)
Addis Ababa.
(Standing up)
(They stand up at the same time.)
They stood up at the same time, right?
- But... - Jong Kook.
- Hold on. - Thank goodness.
- Thank goodness. - Why?
Jong Kook didn't give an answer.
You stood up at the same time.
Is standing up together enough to get you eliminated?
- Listen. - I didn't know.
- You didn't know, right? - That's right.
I didn't know.
I didn't know. You didn't know, right?
(They shake hands.)
This is Race of Wits!
- Listen. - I didn't know.
I thought I had to give an answer. I didn't know.
- I didn't know. - We will accept if the rest agrees.
- Accept it. - Hold on.
- Accept it. - I didn't know.
- In Ah and Chungha, do you agree? - Yes.
(When Jae Seok asked them if they agree,)
(Chungha answered, "Yes".)
- She agrees. - Why did you say that?
She agrees.
Do you know what you agreed with?
- Chungha had no idea. - Chungha...
Chungha agreed without knowing what I asked.
- All right. - Let's play again.
- In Ah. - Let me be clear with the rules.
Standing up at the same time will get you eliminated.
How about shouting out an answer?
If you sit down and do it, I won't count it.
- Okay. - I will go first.
I will go third.
- All right. - Let's begin.
You will win if you wait.
What do you want to be in your next life?
- Hero. - Chicken.
(Ji Hyo and Haha are out.)
- I said I will go first. - Okay.
I almost shouted out, "Poop".
It was begging Jae Seok to answer.
The fourth question must be answered...
with a gesture.
- A gesture? - Okay. That's good.
Get ready. Set, go.
What do you say to seduce someone?
- Kiss. - Okay.
What's up?
I love you.
Be mine.
(It's an energetic way of seducing someone.)
(Is that how he seduces someone?)
It's scary.
You have my heart.
Have my child.
(A middle-aged man's way of seducing someone)
- It has six letters in Korean! - What was that?
It has six letters! I gave the right answer.
It does have 6 letters. The next one is a 7-letter answer.
A seven-letter answer.
I love you forever and ever.
(I love you forever and ever.)
It has eight words in Korean.
I can't believe him.
He is really bad at games.
- He is really bad at playing games. - I can't seduce, so I stayed quiet.
- Listen. - What do you have to say?
- I love you forever. - "I love you forever"?
- Just go. - Come here.
- You said "Forever and ever". - This is driving me crazy.
He can't even insist without Jong Kook.
(He can't even insist without Jong Kook.)
You were given a chance.
Please sit down.
- All right. - Please scoot to the middle.
Please scoot to the middle.
My goodness.
Let's resume.
Which nickname would you give to the person to your right?
Poop.
Beggar.
Cutie.
(Chungha is the best.)
Pot belly.
Marilyn Monroe.
("Marilyn Monroe" has five letters in Korean.)
(Seok Jin and In Ah remain.)
Eternal Sunshine.
(It's the title of a movie.)
- What did she say? - "Eternal Sunshine".
- Isn't that the title of a movie? - "Eternal Sunshine"?
- It makes sense, but... - It's not a nickname.
Can't it be a nickname?
- No. - She is right.
- Seok Jin, come here. - No!
(In Ah is right.)
(Seok Jin, come here.)
- It's not a nickname. - Come here.
- All right. - Come on.
It would be a shame to get eliminated right now.
(With Seok Jin out, 6 members remain.)
Let's go.
Get ready.
What do you say to break up?
- Go. - Get lost.
Stop it.
(Standing up)
(So Min and In Ah are out.)
- We are still in. - We have hope.
- In Ah and So Min, come here. - All right.
Get ready. Let's go.
What do you want to do before you die?
(Kwang Soo stands up by himself.)
You stood up.
- Come here. - You have 5 seconds. 5,
4, 3, 2.
- He is out. - Okay.
(He gets eliminated for staying quiet.)
- Why didn't you answer? - You stood up.
You should have given an answer.
- How strange! - For goodness' sake.
We are almost there.
There are only three people left, so we will go speedily.
Get ready. Set, go.
What do you want to be in your next life?
King.
(Startled)
That was a good one.
(Se Chan can neither stand up nor sit down.)
Bat.
(My goodness.)
(He became startled after standing up a little.)
(I don't know what to do.)
What was that just now?
What are you, a zombie?
I stopped halfway.
(I am not a zombie.)
- I thought I had a cramp. - That startled me.
- That startled me. - It was like "Ju-On".
That startled me.
(Chungha and Jong Kook win the right to eat.)
Chungha and Jong Kook won the right to eat.
Okay.
This time,
the first place will also choose the last person to pay.
(The right to eat and choose the last person to pay)
The winners of the previous round will get a dollar if they win again.
Let's begin. Get ready. Set, go.
Which movie did you enjoy?
"Mulberry".
What?
Does it exist?
Yes, it does.
- Don't you know "Mulberry"? - Oh, "Mulberry"?
"Friend".
"Aladdin".
(Haha succeeded to buy some time.)
("Aladdin".)
- "The Predator". - "The Predator".
What?
What was that?
Did you watch it together?
("The Predator" reveals their love.)
(Flustered)
- Did you watch it together? - Did you watch it together?
I got goosebumps.
- What was that? - I guess they watched it together.
Jong Kook has problems.
The two of them are out.
(Jong Kook and In Ah are out.)
- Let's go. - I should have chosen "Titanic".
- Get ready. - Do you want to get eliminated?
I think he will get eliminated right away.
- Seriously. - I will stand up in 0.1 seconds.
Get ready.
Set, go.
How do you feel right now?
Best.
So good.
I am happy.
(I am happy.)
- I am quite upset. - Pretty good.
I am happy.
(I am happy.)
- I am quite upset. - Pretty good.
Very nice.
- Okay! - What?
("Very nice" has 5 letters in Korean.)
- It has five letters. - Okay.
- "Very nice" has five letters. - Very very nice.
- No. - Seok Jin.
- No. - Very very nice.
- Go. - Very very nice.
Go.
Seok Jin, you are really bad at this game.
You are bad at it, too.
It will be funny if they compete against each other.
What were you going to say after "Okay"?
I simply said it because Seok Jin got eliminated.
- It wasn't an answer. - No.
Get ready.
Set, go. What do you say to seduce someone?
(What do you say to seduce someone?)
- Muah. - Come on.
I love you.
Okay!
- Hold on. - What was that?
- "Okay" makes no sense. - What was that?
- Listen. - You are out.
- You are out. It makes no sense. - Stop it.
No one says that to seduce another person.
You are the worst man.
- It works, right? - What?
- "Okay" works, right? - It works.
- It works. - I would use it.
When you propose,
- will you say, "Okay"? - Okay.
It works.
- No way. - Listen.
- That's not the right example. - It works.
"Honey, would you buy me this?"
- "Okay." - Okay.
- "Would you buy me this?" - It works.
(No matter what she wants, he will say, "Okay.")
- "Honey." - It works in some situations.
- "I love you. Okay." - It does work.
- Jong Kook. - I told you it works.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's say she looks amazing. - It worked...
- back in our days. - "Okay."
It works.
- I told you it works. - Raise your hand...
if you don't think "Okay" works.
There is no one.
- When you think about it... - There is no one.
Jae Seok is out.
Chungha, how could you raise two hands?
(I am sorry, but I love you.)
"Okay" works.
We said that a lot back in the days.
"Okay" works at all times.
"Shall we go and eat meat?" "Okay."
Let's move on to the next question.
I can't believe they think "Okay" is incorrect.
Let's go. What do you say when your ex calls?
Why?
Get lost.
(What do you say when your ex calls?)
(Haha stands up.)
(For goodness' sake.)
They stood up at the same time.
(They stood up at the same time again.)
- Haha. - I twitched.
"Okay" works for this question, too.
How does it work?
Why doesn't it work?
Let's say your ex called. "Okay."
- My goodness. - "Okay."
- "Okay." - It works.
Let's say you were waiting for your ex to call.
"Okay."
- "Honey?" "Okay." - "Okay."
Then the ex will be happy.
I am telling you it works.
Let's go. Get ready. Set, go.
What do you want to choose as the family motto?
Best.
- Let's live. - "Okay."
Happy.
Chungha is out.
- Okay. - Shouldn't it be "Let's be happy"?
- "Happy". - Happiness.
- It's strange. - Happiness. Happiness.
So Min, you are out.
Okay, So Min.
You're back.
- Okay. - Okay, So Min.
I got eliminated in the end.
I will go first.
Look at those fools on Chungha's sides.
(Look at those fools on Chungha's sides.)
(They look like fools next to Chungha.)
- What are you saying? - Seriously.
Don't be mean.
The fools on Princess Chungha's sides.
Gosh, I am annoyed.
Chungha, you won the previous round.
That's right. You should let us win.
Get ready. Set, go.
Name a famous person you admire.
(Name a famous person you admire.)
One letter.
(A famous person?)
Is there a one-letter name?
(Name a famous person you admire.)
(Is there a one-letter name?)
Who invented the telephone?
- Bell! - Bell!
(They answer at the same time.)
(I am sick and tired of you.)
- I am sick and tired of you. - For goodness' sake.
- Bell. - It came to your mind, right?
- You are such a cheat. - For goodness' sake.
I can't believe you.
For goodness' sake. I am sick and tired of you.
All right. Mr. Gums and Mr. Fool are out.
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo are out.)
How did Bell come to mind as soon as I heard the hint?
Now, Chungha will choose one person...
to eat with. Then we will have the last round.
- Okay. - Four people will eat.
Chungha will choose one person to eat with.
We struggled until the end.
I choose "Okay."
Okay!
I contributed to that answer.
(She chooses Jae Seok without hesitation.)
(Sighing)
Okay. Thank you, Chungha.
- Chungha, he ate. - For goodness' sake.
You deserted your friend.
I feel bad about raising both hands earlier.
- I see. - People who will eat...
are Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and Chungha.
We will have another round to choose the last person.
- Okay. - Let's go.
Let's begin. Go.
What do you want to buy your love on an anniversary?
Tangerine.
- "Tangerine"? - Ring.
Necklace.
("Necklace" has 3 letters in Korean.)
Jae Seok, why aren't you saying "Okay"?
Okay.
Keychain.
Polaroid.
(What do you want to buy your love on an anniversary?)
(It's a witty answer.)
SUV.
(It's time to give a six-letter answer.)
- What? - SUV?
Doesn't it have five letters?
- Okay. - SUV.
- Okay. - SUV is an English word,
- so it has three letters. - A vehicle.
SUV has three letters.
It has three letters.
It has more letters in Korean.
Sit on the floor.
- Sit on the floor, Se Chan. - I am an utter fool.
(He kicks himself.)
I am so annoyed.
- SUV. - It happens every time.
Even if you write it in Korean, it has five letters.
Get ready
How do you turn down the advances of someone you don't like?
- Sorry. - No.
- Okay. - My goodness.
What do you say when you want to go to the restroom?
- I want to poop. - Hey, hold on.
Hold on.
What did you say?
Which part of your body do you like the best?
- Ears. - Nostrils.
(Standing up)
- You stood up at the same time. - Haha didn't stand up.
- You are out. - No way.
You are out. Okay.
- Okay. - This is good.
Okay. I got this.
Since there are two people left,
you will alternate by adding a letter each time.
- Okay. - It's a death match.
Play rock-paper-scissors to decide who will go first.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- They won't go beyond five letters. - It's "Dumb and Dumber".
It's "Dumb and Dumber". They are Fool 1 and Fool 2.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo will go first.)
Let's go.
What couldn't you say to the person next to you?
Hey.
Fool.
I will end you.
(I will end you.)
Their answers are becoming emotional.
(What couldn't you say to the person next to you?)
Orangutan.
Three.
Super ugly.
("Super ugly" has five letters in Korean.)
(Super ugly)
(He attacks Jae Seok's looks.)
(Flustered)
He doesn't know what to do.
Ugly.
- What? - You need six letters.
- What did he whisper? - Okay.
It's time for seven letters.
Hold on.
(How could you count that as an answer?)
How could you count that?
What did he say?
- What? - He used a swear word.
(Kwang Soo is annoyed.)
I will count that as an answer.
Seven letters.
Uglier than me.
(What couldn't you say to the person next to you?)
- He did it. - Eight letters.
Much uglier than Se Chan.
(Much uglier than Se Chan.)
Yes!
(It doesn't have the right number of letters.)
You should have said, "Uglier than Se Chan".
"Uglier than Se Chan".
- Not "Much uglier". - Uglier...
than Se Chan.
Thus, people who will eat...
- are Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, Chungha, - Chungha.
and Jae Seok.
You were picked.
Chungha, choose the person who will pay last...
in this round.
Jong Kook has been exempt.
I forgot about that.
(Let's see.)
(They avoid her gaze.)
(Whom should I choose?)
I choose Se Can.
(I bet he has a lot of money.)
(She chooses Se Chan as the last person to pay.)
- Why? - There you go.
Good job.
- I avoided her gaze. - Se Chan will pay last...
in this round.
Beef steamed in hinoki cypress box will be served.
All right.
- It was freshly-made. - Okay.
(Steamed beef with the aroma of hinoki cypress)
Let's go.
This dish must be healthy.
We have to do something.
How is the soup?
It's like boiled meat.
(The 4 winners' tasty meal ends.)
- Is it good? - It's really good.
How much is the total?
I bet it's expensive. I bet it's about 20 dollars.
You finished the meal, right?
- Yes. - Thank you for the meal.
The total you must pay in this round...
is 19 dollars.
(The total is 19 dollars.)
(10 people must divide the total of 19 dollars.)
This is tricky.
If each person pays 2 dollars, the total will be 20 dollars.
Who will pay a dollar?
Someone won't pay.
You will be at risk if you only pay a dollar.
Keep that in mind.
There is no way someone will forgo a payment.
Who wants to go first?
- Haha. - Okay.
(The first person to pay is Haha.)
- I don't know. - Paying a dollar is risky.
(Haha, pay a lot.)
I think it will go over the bill.
Then it doesn't matter who paid the least, right?
(The final amount could go over the bill.)
Your heart will be at ease if you pay three dollars.
Paying a dollar is risky.
Forgoing a payment can go either way.
I will forgo a payment.
(I will forgo a payment.)
(Thinking that the final amount will go over the bill,)
I think it will go over.
(Haha forgoes a payment.)
All right.
I will forgo a payment.
(I will forgo a payment.)
(Kwang Soo also forgoes a payment.)
It's best to put your heart at ease.
- It's your turn. - Okay.
His action will be the opposite of his words.
I think...
You could either split the remaining amount...
as the last member to pay or...
Even if I take the leftover money as the member who paid the most,
the money I lose will be about the same.
I could take the leftover money as the member who paid the most.
- That's right. - Or I could make the member...
who paid the least split the remaining amount with me.
- Why are you pointing at me? - I am sorry.
(Why are you pointing at me?)
I am sorry. I am sorry.
- Me? - It's nothing.
- The target has been decided. - Yes.
- You want to make him pay, right? - Whoever paid the least...
How much should I pay?
(Their war of nerves becomes fiercer since the bill is small.)
(Everyone makes some calculations and pays.)
My bet was off the last time.
I will raise the money by two times...
and pay 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars. - Yes.
I will bet more daringly. I regretted my earlier decision.
(In Ah aims to be the member who paid the most.)
I am cool with this.
Thank you.
The amount of money I lose will be about the same.
(Paying the most amount of money versus paying enough)
(What will be Se Chan's choice?)
- All right. Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's move on.
(Payment has been made.)
- All right. - What's the result?
I told you that the amount you have to pay is...
19 dollars.
The total amount that you paid is...
(If it's not enough,)
(the last and the one who paid the least pay the rest.)
(How much did 10 people pay?)
It's 29 dollars.
(29 dollars)
(It's 10 dollars more than what they owe.)
- Who is it? - 29 dollars?
- Who paid that much? - Why?
Someone paid a lot to win.
- Someone wanted to take it all. - It's a competition.
The winner takes 10 dollars.
- The ones who paid the most are... - Who is it?
- In Ah... - What?
and Ji Hyo.
(In Ah and Ji Hyo paid the highest amount.)
You may take five dollars each.
- It's a loss. - It's both of them.
It's a loss for them.
(They pay 10 dollars and lose 5 dollars.)
It's a loss.
(It's time for Ji Hyo to pay.)
It's either the winner or the loser.
(She paid nothing in Round 1.)
I'll pay 10 dollars.
(The least in Round 1 and the most in Round 2)
(Ji Hyo pays extreme amounts.)
- Did you think that only you won? - Yes.
(In Ah also makes a loss.)
The one who paid the least must be excited.
It's a gain for those who didn't pay.
Let's go.
(Is he admitting that he paid nothing?)
They didn't pay.
- They didn't pay. - They didn't.
- Let's go to the next place. - Okay.
(Payment has been made.)
(They go to eat their last invigorating food.)
(The members' current amount of money)
By the way,
did In Ah and Ji Hyo pay 10 dollars each?
- Yes. - You risked it to win.
- There must be two who didn't pay. - I know.
- They're so bold. - "Bold"?
- Unless you're very bold... - It must be Bold Kwang.
- It must be Bold Kwang. - It must be Bold Kwang.
"Bold Kwang".
- It's not me. - It's Bold Kwang.
(The victims of Bold Kwang)
I'm in trouble.
I want to eat neungi mushrooms no matter what.
Seok Jin, if you unclear the mission and don't get to eat again,
- you'll be in trouble. - I'll win.
If Seok Jin doesn't eat again,
he's on a sporadic diet.
(Seok Jin is on a sporadic diet.)
I'm famished.
I'll win no matter what.
Will you really win?
"Sporadic diet".
We'll be arriving soon.
The restaurant is small.
Only two of you will get out and bring takeout.
- Who will the two be? - How about...
we play a game?
Those who are in love should go.
"Those who are in love"?
Seok Jin and So Min.
(All of a sudden?)
Isn't it him and Ji Hyo?
(Fantastic water gun romance)
- Were you startled? - Seok Jin and So Min?
- It was out of the blue. - Why did you undo your seatbelt?
Why did you undo your seatbelt?
(He's trying to get off.)
- Seok Jin and So Min. - That's nonsense.
They look good together.
Goodness.
So Min hopes for romance.
- My goodness. - Anyway...
- Let's go. - Here it is. It looks delicious.
There it is.
- There it is. - It's the payment.
It's here too. Hello.
Hello.
May we order a takeout?
May we come in?
Is it already packed?
- Yes. - Thank you.
It looks delicious.
It's neungi mushrooms.
(Boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms)
This is amazing.
I'll pay with zero pay.
It worked.
- It worked. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Did the payment go through?
It's made with herbal medicine.
You'll feel a lot of strength after eating this.
Eat this and get strength.
- Okay. - Thank you.
Please stay strong, Sir.
- Stay strong. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- Thank you for the food. - We'll be back.
- Stay strong, Sir. - Goodbye.
(They obtain boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms.)
This is incredible. What's this?
What?
What's this?
Did this place exist before?
(It's a grand and circular stadium.)
- It's great here. - What's that?
It's soccer, Jong Kook.
I think we have to kick it and attach it.
"Dye hair with color spray, squeaky hammer".
What's this?
This is the final mission for boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms...
and the order of payment.
It's called Soccer King Shutdolyi.
(Soccer King Shutdolyi)
- "Soccer King Shutdolyi". - Shutdolyi.
It's an individual game.
A person will kick the ball towards the target.
You succeed if you attach the ball to the center.
The one who succeeds first...
gets the right to choose the loser...
and two people to eat with.
I really want some boiled chicken this time.
If the ball is attached to the penalty area,
you get a penalty from the person who went before you.
"Dye hair with color spray" is the worst.
You can't wash it off immediately.
It doesn't wash off easily.
Please start.
- Who's next? - It's So Min.
(So Min is up next.)
She's fast.
She's definitely fast.
You're so fast that I can't see you.
Let's go, So Min.
I hope it's attached in one try.
Kick.
(Will her warming up be effective?)
(It's attached right away.)
- "Put on a funny hat". - "Put on a funny hat".
That's a relief.
- That's a relief. - That isn't bad.
It's a relief.
This is great.
How about this?
- How about a swimming cap? - How about this?
Se Chan is an expert in this.
(The work of a master of makeup)
Wait.
Look at the back of So Min's head. Is she really okay?
Look at the back of her head.
Is she really okay?
How can the back of your head be so flat?
(Is this look real?)
It looks like a thumb in a thimble.
(How does it look?)
- I can't see. - Next is In Ah.
(We're glad that you can't see.)
I hope I don't get "put on a funny hat".
Next is In Ah. She's good.
- She's athletic. - Looks good.
(What will be the result for In Ah?)
(It heads towards the center.)
"Put on a funny hat".
("Put on a funny hat")
(I'm doomed.)
- It's the thing she didn't want. - Put it on.
Is it me?
How about a matching hat with mine?
Is this the same hat?
It looks good on In Ah.
Let's see.
(Does it look good on me?)
Look at her hair.
What happened to her hair?
What did you do to her hair?
So Min gets high-handed whenever we have actresses.
Is this necessary?
(They both look like Hulk.)
That's great.
You look good.
You look good together.
Do we have to target the center?
(No one could avoid penalties.)
(Will anyone succeed?)
(Next player is Jae Seok.)
(What's the result?)
(Attached)
- "Put on a funny hat". - "Put on a funny hat".
What funny hats are there?
- This is the only one. - The yellow swimming cap?
This is it.
- This is it. - That's right.
What? You startled me.
- What? - What's this?
(What did Kwang Soo see?)
(He makes everyone burst into laughter.)
(He's coming.)
(The front of his face is compressed.)
What? You startled me.
- What? - What's this?
Is he human?
It's a monster.
It's an alien.
- Is he? - Can you see?
In Ah screamed.
(The makeup turns him into something of a different race.)
Shouldn't I be able to see?
This is what this hat looks like.
This is funny.
- Shouldn't you look like me? - I didn't know.
Can you see, Jae Seok?
- Hey. - His eyes.
- His eyes look charismatic. - Jae Seok.
You look like a good fighter.
He looks similar to Myung Soo.
- It's Park Myung Soo. - "Don't touch me."
He looks like him.
(He's possessed by Myung Soo.)
- "Don't touch me!" - He looks just like him.
- It's Park Myung Soo. - "Shut it."
- "Shut it." - He looks so similar.
- Here I go. - You look like him.
(Next up is Haha.)
It's "put on a funny hat".
Why do we get that so many times?
(It's the funny hat penalty again.)
We should put them on as a group.
Okay.
(People keep putting hats on.)
You look like Myung Soo too.
"What are you looking at?"
(Possessed by Myung Soo)
- "What are you looking at?" - How many Myung Soos are there?
- "Hey." - "This looks fun."
"Watch what you say."
(It's hard to look at them.)
- "Close your mouth." - Okay.
How many Myung Soos are there?
- They look so scary. - "Hurry up and play."
(What on earth?)
"Doodle for three seconds".
(People keep getting a penalty.)
- Ji Hyo is angry. - She's angry.
- Ji Hyo. - What's wrong?
(They get a penalty every time they kick.)
- "Doodle on the face". - "For three seconds".
She looks like Woong's father.
(Woong's father appears.)
The concept of your new performance is sensational.
She almost had it.
If only it went to the side...
- Congratulations, Chungha. - You look pretty.
You look like The Statue of Liberty.
(She keeps her pretty looks.)
Here I go.
(People keep getting makeup as they play.)
Color spray.
Please stop spraying on my hair.
(Is it possible to succeed?)
He looks like a grass doll.
- He has become a hipster. - That looks good.
- Do I look like a hipster? - Seriously.
- You look good. - Do I?
- You look amazing. - You look like a celebrity.
- Look at him. - Now I look like a celebrity.
They look good on you.
I only put on a pair of sunglasses.
- All right. - This is great.
Please attach it to the center.
(Something makes him look pathetic.)
Can you see?
- Isn't there a similar emoji? - Yes.
- He looks so funny. - This is it.
- His face looks familiar. - Isn't there the same thing?
There's an emoticon with glasses on.
- Get out of my way. - He looks the same.
You can do it.
(He kicks the ball without expecting much.)
(Attached)
(It's attached in the center.)
(Is this possible?)
- He did it. - Success.
(The soccer ball is attached to the center like a magnet.)
(Jae Seok succeeds.)
(He made it with the power of compressed face.)
- Goodness. - What's this?
What?
He knows how to hit the target.
(The final winner is Jae Seok.)
As the winner, Jae Seok will pick two...
to share boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms.
- Two? - Jae Seok, So Min and I haven't...
- eaten today. - You haven't?
- Neither has Seok Jin. - Me neither.
- Who hasn't eaten yet? - Me.
- Me. - There are three.
So Min, Seok Jin, and Ji Hyo.
I'll eat it with Ji Hyo and So Min.
Hey.
(He picks Ji Hyo and So Min.)
(Why did you even ask me?)
- Hey. - Seok Jin can't eat again?
I can't eat again?
When you pay, pick a member who will pay last.
- The one who'll pay last? - Yes.
(Slowly walking away)
You haven't eaten, Seok Jin, have you?
(Let's talk for a minute.)
It's okay. Don't worry about me.
You don't have to care about me.
Why do you care?
- I'll pick Seok Jin. - Goodness.
(Seok Jin will pay.)
Why?
(Without eating boiled chicken, Seok Jin pays.)
After the meal, we'll have the last payment time.
- Then we'll wrap up. - Okay.
Let's move.
I can't believe that I hit it.
I can smell food.
It looks so delicious.
I wanted to eat it.
(It's a table full of healthy food.)
It's invigorating food.
- Look at that. - It's made with neungi mushrooms.
It looks amazing.
The broth is great.
(The taste of healthy food is impressive.)
The broth is delicious.
I want to try some broth.
That's invigorating food.
We should eat it on a hot day.
Didn't you say that you'll show us?
(Didn't you say that you'll show us?)
- What? - What?
You said that you'll show us waacking.
- Right. - Show it to us properly.
- Show us properly. - That's right.
If you show us waacking, I'll give you some.
Chungha and In Ah.
- If they dance, is it for free? - Yes.
Come out.
(Let's dance and eat boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms.)
I'm sorry, but I don't know waacking.
Just dance.
I wonder what music will play.
What's the basic move?
Just turn the arms.
Isn't this...
(However)
(The beat is familiar.)
- I know this dance. - This is the song for our dance.
(It's the song for their group dance at their fan-meet.)
What is it?
(What kind of dance will they show?)
(Chungha starts.)
(Explosive with power)
I can't do that.
(She breaks the beat for boiled chicken.)
Is this waacking?
She's a good dancer.
(So this is waacking.)
I can't do that.
What's with her?
Unbelievable.
She dances well.
It's incredible.
(Her arms and legs move on their own.)
She's dancing without thinking, but she looks better than us.
(She's dancing without thinking, but she looks better than us.)
She's dancing without thinking, but she looks much better.
(Chungha's fantastic solo dance)
Good job.
- That was amazing. - Okay.
(Speechless)
We practiced for several days,
but we can't dance like her.
Did you give her the song in advance?
What? How do you dance so well?
I danced however I wanted.
It was freestyle, and you danced so well.
She danced however she wanted.
Why aren't you dancing, In Ah?
I don't know anything about waacking.
(She doesn't seem confident.)
(What kind of dance will In Ah show?)
Let's go, In Ah.
(Her facial expression changes completely.)
She dances well.
(She moves exactly to the beat.)
(She does a cartwheel.)
(People get excited when they see an advanced move.)
(She deserves more than a whole boiled chicken.)
Look at her.
Show us breakdancing.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(It's a perfect finish.)
(Everyone gapes.)
(You deserve the whole boiled chicken, In Ah.)
She's a good dancer.
Hey, let's show them.
Show them what?
That was amazing.
- We'll use the same song. - You look like celebrities.
Seok Jin, go up and join them.
(Shall I warm up?)
- Should I dance too? - Seok Jin is "Train to Busan".
(Zombie dance on "Train to Busan")
We'll be serious. Take a look at us, Chungha.
Okay.
(What will they show me?)
(Excited)
(We'll show you properly.)
(He starts alone.)
That's not it.
(He makes a mistake from the start.)
(Their facial expressions are like dancers.)
(They dance together better than expected.)
(Their practice is paying off.)
(They dance well.)
How does it go?
(He starts to malfunction.)
There you go.
Good.
(It's a group dance, but they're out of sync.)
(Each person creates his own dance.)
(This is the original dance.)
- It's chaos. - I'm dizzy.
What was that?
I can't remember at all.
I like the song.
Seok Jin, we practiced a lot.
- He can't remember. - I can't remember at all.
I couldn't help being nervous.
- I can't remember. - I'm nervous.
What do we do?
I can't remember at all.
We practiced for over 10 hours.
It's over.
- Everyone. - Yes?
(It's time to pay.)
I'll announce...
the amount you'll pay in this round.
- I think this will be expensive. - Will people pay?
The amount you will pay...
is 27 dollars.
(Boiled chicken with neungi mushrooms costs 27 dollars.)
It's expensive.
It's expensive. Is it the most expensive?
If we go for one chance...
(10 people should pay a total of 27 dollars.)
Right? That will be the last chance.
Go for one chance and take the rest.
(If they pay more, the one who pays the most wins the extra money.)
Let's start.
(Se Chan is the first to pay.)
How much will you pay?
Shall I take a risk?
(How much does Se Chan pay?)
Three dollars.
(3 dollars)
(If each person pays 3 dollars, they'll pay more than 27 dollars.)
Your payment was received.
(Se Chan makes a safe investment.)
This is difficult.
(How much will In Ah pay?)
I'll pay seven dollars.
(She pays 7 dollars.)
(As expected, In Ah pays a big amount.)
Kwang Soo.
(Next is Kwang Soo.)
Isn't it better to pay the most?
It's meaningless to be in the middle.
You either win or lose.
(He thinks hard because it's the last chance to pay.)
(During today's race)
(The one with the highest balance gets a penalty exemption ticket.)
(The one with the lowest balance is the loser.)
(The loser picks another member...)
(to get a water bomb together.)
(Except the winner, everyone else is at the risk of being penalized.)
(It's meaningless unless you win.)
I'll pay 21 dollars.
(21 dollars)
(What's the current total including Kwang Soo's payment?)
(3 dollars)
(3 dollars plus 7 dollars)
(3 plus 7 plus 21 dollars are 31 dollars.)
(The total is 27 dollars.)
(They've paid 4 dollars more than what they need to pay.)
(If 21 dollars is the highest, Kwang Soo gets the rest.)
(Will Kwang Soo be able to succeed?)
If I had a lot of money,
I would use everything. Then it's over.
(Someone will definitely put all his money in.)
(That's me, Jae Seok.)
(People are more careful since it's the last time.)
(Payment has been made.)
The amount that you should have paid...
- is 27 dollars. - Right.
- I bet it exceeded. - Definitely.
The total amount that you paid was...
It'll be shocking if it's 40 to 50 dollars.
- I think it'll be that much. - If it's 40 to 50 dollars...
It'll be creepy if it's over 50 dollars.
The total amount that you paid was...
(What's the total amount that they paid?)
It's 60 dollars.
(60 dollars)
How many are we?
(That's amazing.)
Everyone put everything in.
The winner will take it all.
It'll be the winner.
- It's someone who put everything. - It'll be one of them.
Who put everything in? I didn't have enough money.
One of you will the additional 33 dollars.
That's right.
The winner paid over 20 dollars.
- It must be you. - It's him.
- It's Chungha. - No.
- It's Chungha. - It's not me.
- Waacking... - It's not me.
It's Kwang Soo.
- How many did you pay, Kwang Soo? - That startled me.
Is it you?
Should I say it?
I have one last announcement to make.
I paid...
over 20 dollars.
(I paid over 20 dollars.)
Congratulations, the one who paid the most...
(Congratulations, the one who paid the most is...)
is Jae Seok, and he will get the extra money.
(Jae Seok will get the extra money.)
(Jae Seok is the final winner.)
He knew about it.
- He knew. - Jae Seok.
Did you have that much money?
I had 22 dollars.
- 22 dollars? - That's all?
I paid 21 dollars.
(He's about to lose it.)
(Jae Seok wins by just one dollar.)
I'll put everything in.
I'll take a risk.
(Jae Seok puts everything in like Kwang Soo.)
Here we go.
(He pays 22 dollars.)
(Jae Seok wins the race by just one dollar.)
Both of you paid most of it.
If Se Chan hadn't eaten and paid me a dollar,
I would have had 21 dollars.
- Because of the money from me? - Yes.
(Jae Seok would've had 21 dollars.)
As a result,
Jae Seok wins 33 dollars. He's the winner.
Kwang Soo has 0 dollars.
Oh, no.
Kwang Soo is in trouble.
In Ah, don't be so excited.
Excluding Kwang Soo,
you've placed last. You'll be penalized.
Pardon?
- In Ah. - Why is he excluded?
He went bankrupt, so he's excluded.
- I went bankrupt. - In Ah has placed last.
The one that In Ah picks will get a water bomb with her.
Jae Seok is exempt from the penalty.
(Jae Seok is exempt from the penalty.)
I got lucky today.
I was surprised in the end.
People who have gone bankrupt are exempt.
- So Min wanted to get a water bomb. - Right.
(Seok Jin tells on her.)
- Didn't So Min say... - No.
that she's hot?
She wanted to play in water.
- Who? - So Min.
(Avoiding eye contact)
And...
someone stole my fishcake.
(Feeling guilty)
(Why did you steal In Ah's fishcake earlier?)
The fishcake.
How dare you steal her fishcake?
Wait, I just changed my mind.
(Wait, I just changed my mind.)
I'll choose Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo has to get it anyway. - I have to get it anyway.
(He's set to face the penalty. Having no money is sad enough.)
(How could you choose me?)
I'll be facing the penalty with you anyway.
I don't have any money left.
(Are you making fun of me?)
(He's very sensitive.)
- Who will it be? - Have you decided?
- Yes. - 1, 2, 3.
Why are you doing this to me? Why?
(The penalty partner In Ah chooses is...)
(Seok Jin, the fishcake thief.)
- Why are you doing this to me? - This is neat.
Good job, today.
(Seok Jin, In Ah, and Kwang Soo will face the penalty.)
All right. The two of you dyed your hair nicely today.
- Yes. Both of them dyed their hair. - That's right.
Jae Seok is really annoying today.
Hey, you're next.
You guys look like a newer version of KOYOTE.
(It's 2019 version of KOYOTE.)
- Please. - Bbaekga.
No.
Seok Jin looks like Jong Min.
- He's Jong Min. - He resembles Jong Min.
- 1, 2, 3. - 2, 3.
(The water bomb is launched to get rid of the heat wave.)
(Splashing)
(Totally soaked)
Yellow water is dripping.
(Thank you for joining us for the break week.)
Good job today.
- Good job. - Good work.
(Thank you for joining us for the break week.)
(Unidentified people are singing trot songs behind the doors?)
(Singer)
(Keyboard)
(Lawn... Could it be...?)
(It's time to meet the artists for their joint performances.)
(They start preparing for the joint performances with other artists.)
(Finally!)
(If you're a group, how many of you are single?)
(They may be distracted.)
(What do you think about Kwang Soo?)
Hold on.
(They may be rejected.)
(However, they don't want to lose these artists.)
(The best lineup you can't give up on)
(The legion of the artists will be revealed soon.)
(5th Episode of 9 Years of Running Man)
(On Our Way to Escort You)