(One day in March in fickle weather...)
What is this?
Hello.
(Everyone starts at different locations.)
We're going to put a sticker on you.
What sticker?
(They start with stickers on.)
(Why is there a sticker all of a sudden?)
What is this?
Is that 11? What is it?
(The staff is attaching math signs and numbers.)
What is this?
Why are you putting them on all of a sudden?
(Everyone all gets their stickers.)
What is this? Why do I have 11 on my back?
It's not number 1? It's a minus sign?
What is this?
"When all eight members gather, you can enter the place of the opening."
"Come to 276-8, Seongsu-dong 2-ga, Seongdong-gu,"
"Seoul." What does this sentence mean?
"When all eight members gather"?
Does it mean we can't enter if even one member doesn't come?
I'm sure everyone will show up.
- You can set out now. - Let's go then.
I'm sure everyone will come. Why wouldn't they?
(Everyone individually sets out to the place of their mission.)
(Gosh, I'm really curious what this is about.)
I'm really curious what this is about.
I don't get it. I have the number 254? 254?
Is it about the alphabet?
A, B, C, D...
(He confused the equal symbol for number 11.)
I'm K. In English, I'm K.
(When everyone is trying to figure it out, Kwang Soo is...)
- Hello? - Hey.
Kwang Soo, what is this about?
They put something on my back.
You're on your way, right? What's on your back?
I couldn't see it. They didn't let me see it.
They said I wasn't allowed to.
Look at the sticker now.
- I'm not lying. - Don't lie. Look and tell me.
- What? - Stop lying. Look and tell me.
Oh, I saw it. I saw it. I could see it.
This is my number.
It's 57. It's 57.
Hey, I'm hanging up.
I'm serious.
(He's not falling for it.)
Hello, Haha.
- Hello. - Hello, Haha.
- They want us to gather. - Right.
I don't know what they put on my back.
What's yours? What's on your back?
I have a heart symbol.
(That's the biggest fake ever.)
I have a diamond symbol.
What?
(My gosh, unbelievable.)
Haha, stop it.
- What do you mean? - Just be honest for once.
- Why do you say that? - Haha.
Please just once. Please be honest just for once.
Okay. I have a minus sign.
(I have the minus sign.)
Don't kid with me.
I'm being serious.
What's yours?
I have a plus sign.
(I have the plus sign.)
Wait, is this what I think it is?
You don't have the minus sign, right?
No, I don't. I have the plus sign.
I have the minus sign.
- You have the minus sign? - Yes.
Then why did you say you had the plus sign?
Because you said you had the minus sign.
I actually have the minus sign.
I actually have the plus sign. Let's just hang up now.
Haha.
You're draining my energy from the start.
- This is funny. - I'm already exhausted.
I will recognize your scamming skills.
- Okay. I'll see you there. - See you there.
Okay.
(What was their power struggle for?)
(He only gets exhausted and more questions.)
I should rest up.
I'm so tired.
I'll know once we all get together.
(All 8 of them are assembling to find the meaning of the sticker.)
We're here.
This is the place.
Is someone already here?
(The giraffe who is exhausted is the first one to arrive.)
(Looking around)
Hey!
(What's this?)
There's a passcode.
(A three-digit combination lock)
(Why is this locked?)
I need a three-digit number.
(How am I supposed to figure this out?)
(What is he doing there?)
Hello, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok is the second one to arrive.)
Kwang Soo. What are you doing?
I'm trying to unlock this.
(I think we need to unlock and go inside.)
There's a lock on the doors. This must be where we'll do our opening.
Do you have a number?
What do you have?
Mine is a number, but...
(Keeping distance for no reason)
(Ji Hyo arrives in the midst of their mind game.)
- Hey, Ji Hyo. - What is it?
Hello.
We're supposed to use the numbers to solve this.
- Let me see. What do you have? - What?
- 139? - 139?
- What do you have? - A minus sign.
You...
- You should go. - Why would I go?
- You're to be subtracted. - Why would I go?
Why do I have the subtraction sign?
You have a subtraction sign. We should remove him, right?
- This isn't number 11. - Hello.
Wait, this wasn't number 11?
- This isn't number 11. - You're here.
Hello.
He... It makes sense now.
- Hey. - What do you have?
- Let me see. - I have subtraction.
- That's not number 11. - Hey.
- I thought I had 11. - That's an equal sign.
- You're unbelievable. - What are we supposed to make?
- We're to calculate numbers. - What are we supposed to make?
- Hey, there's a lock here. - What is this?
- It's not number 11. - There's a 3-digit combo lock.
- What is this? - What do you have?
- Hello. What do you have? - Hi.
- What is it? - What's the number on your back?
- We have to calculate numbers. - He has 254.
- I have 254. - What? 254?
I have 88.
What? What's going on?
(Seok Jin has the biggest number.)
(What happens when they put together the numbers and the signs?)
(Is the answer of the calculation the passcode?)
- Let's put this on. Take this off. - Take this off me.
Ji Hyo, take this off.
- What is this now? - Let me see.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin's number is too big.
What's this now?
It's like the number represents his age.
He's 254 years old.
- First... - We have to put them together.
- In what order should we put them? - Give me that.
- I have 88. - What are we doing?
- 88. - Give me 88.
We're supposed to use the answer for the lock.
Jae Seok, I have the minus sign.
- Give me your minus sign. - How should we use the sign?
(Since they gathered all 8 of the stickers, they must calculate.)
- How should we do this? - The order...
We have to put them in the right order.
(Since they gathered all 8 of the stickers, they must calculate.)
(In what order should we calculate the numbers?)
What's the number?
Do you think the order is based on our age?
(Is it possible that it's in accordance with our age?)
- Put mine and yours. - Is that it?
- Yours is next. - Plus.
- Plus. See? It works out. - Next?
- What about Jong Kook? - What does he have?
- I have 88. - 88.
- Yes, this is correct. This is it. - This is it.
- What about Haha? - Haha.
- I have a plus sign. - Plus sign.
This is the correct order.
- We'll subtract them. - Subtract them.
- Ji Hyo. - This is right.
- So Min. - Se Chan is next.
- What does it come out to? - What's the answer?
254 plus...
(The result of the calculation is 444.)
It's 444.
- It's 444? - 444.
- I... - Why is this 444?
- 444... - Do they want us to die?
I guess someone will be eliminated.
It's 444. I guess someone is going to be removed.
- Hey! - It's open, right?
It was 444?
(The passcode was 444.)
(The passcode entered was 444.)
Hey, we're doing well today.
- We solved this really quickly. - Hey.
- It was based on our age. - It was our age.
- It was right. - It was our age.
- My gosh, Seok Jin. - Goodness.
- I did it. - That was great.
- You have my respect. - Let me unlock this.
- This is amazing. - Gosh.
How did you figure out it was based on our age?
254 was the biggest number.
- Something feels weird today. - Open it up.
- Hey, let Seok Jin go in first. - It's pitch-dark inside.
(Hold on. What is this?)
(Why is it going smoothly today?)
- Hey, let Seok Jin go in first. - It's pitch-dark inside.
(An ominous feeling is never wrong.)
- It's pitch-dark inside. - Hey, hey.
He's dead.
(Someone is dead.)
(The truth behind the mysterious room is...)
- Is this an escape room? - What is this?
- It's an escape room. - It's an escape room!
It must be an escape room.
(Assistant Director A has faced a mysterious death.)
(What is going on here?)
- Is this an escape room? - What is this?
(They are horrified.)
- It must be an escape room. - What is this?
(The assistant director faced a mysterious death in the room.)
(And mysterious decors are placed in the room.)
(What on earth is this room?)
It's been a while. Look, someone is dead.
- Wait, hold on, everyone. - That...
Who is that?
- This is a detective game. - What is this?
(The door is closed down.)
- That startled me. - No!
- Please! Open up! - What?
- Please! Please! - No!
- Hey! - No way.
Try the combination 444 again.
- It doesn't work. - We must find the passcode to exit.
- Hey, today's special... Goodness. - This is about our reasoning skill.
- I love this kind of games. - What is this?
(What is this?)
(In the hands of dead Assistant Director A,)
(there are a piece of paper...)
(and a cassette player.)
- Is it locked? - It's Jigsaw.
- Who killed the assistant director? - Isn't this "Jigsaw"?
- Hold on. - The microphone.
Hey, don't touch it.
- Don't touch it. - Don't touch it? Okay.
Don't touch it. Don't.
- Come on. - Don't touch.
- Hey... - Everyone, freeze!
(They start the detective game.)
The culprit might be among us.
We shouldn't touch the scene.
- Everything is evidence. - I knew he wouldn't last long.
I think we are supposed to do something with this.
We should think about this one at a time.
This is weird.
(Mysterious objects are placed all over the room.)
(What are they for?)
What is this?
Jae Seok!
Just like in the movie, "Jigsaw",
- we should play this. - Right.
- You're right. Yes. - Let's play this for now.
- Yes, it happens in "Jigsaw" too. - Exactly.
(They carefully start the cassette player first.)
I am bound to be eliminated.
- What? - Eliminated?
I really wanted to stop the culprit,
but I couldn't in the end.
- The culprit? - The culprit?
Dear people who discovered my body.
Please find the culprit...
that eliminated me before the sunset.
(The culprit eliminated the assistant director?)
- There's a culprit. - The culprit is among us.
The culprit is among us.
It's one of us.
(Does that mean it's one of us?)
(The culprit who came up with everything...)
(might be among us.)
- There's a culprit. - You can find out how to stop...
the culprit when you go to 319-39, Haengdang-dong, Seongdong-gu.
Haengdang-dong, Seongdong-gu?
- 319-9. - 319-9.
(Hold on.)
(The assistant director was clenching the calendar for March.)
- Hey, this. - The culprit is So Min!
What is this calendar for?
Something is here. It's a calendar.
(It doesn't look different from a regular calendar.)
What's today's date?
- Today is the 12th. - March...
But there is no Monday here.
We film our show on Mondays.
There is a movie called "What Happened to Monday?"
(He gets a hunch.)
- "What Happened to Monday?" - "What Happened to Monday?" Right.
Seok Jin is on a roll today.
Seok Jin, you're doing so well today.
Seok Jin, we have to figure out the secret.
(Will they be able to escape in no time at this rate?)
- I'm sorry. - We have to figure out the secret.
(He was amazed at his own reasoning skill.)
(Stepping)
(Wriggling)
- He's smiling. He's alive. - Hey.
- Why did you step on him? - I don't know. I'm sorry.
It must've hurt.
You're not supposed to step on a corpse!
- He might be sleeping. - Seok Jin.
- He's smiling. - Why did you step on him?
- He's smiling though. - He's alive right now.
You shouldn't step on him.
But we can't go to Haengdang-dong from here.
(How can we get to our next mission?)
Hey, I think we're supposed to figure out the passcode.
My gosh. This...
If we open this up...
- Hey, that's Arabic. - What's this?
- Isn't that Arabic? - No, this is Thai.
Is that Thai?
(An indecipherable Thai sentence is hung next to the exit.)
Hey, if we crack this...
Shouldn't we pop it open?
- Hey. - That's from the field day.
- Shouldn't we open that? - Hey.
(A mysterious yellow gourd looks like it may have something inside.)
(And there are beanbags too.)
Hey, there's something over here too!
I found something here!
(There are a transparent cuboid and a small box at a corner.)
It opens up too.
(A small box is inside a mysterious and transparent box.)
Hey, let's solve them one at a time!
- Do one at a time. - Yes.
- Let's pop this 1st. - Do 1 at a time.
Pop that.
Throw it.
- Take that! - Gosh.
(It opens.)
- It opened! - It popped!
(Something came out of the gourd.)
- They're keys. - What?
- They're two keys. - What are they?
- We need to open something. - Where is it?
- What can we open? - Where is it?
Where is it?
- Maybe that one? - What do we have?
(He goes towards the cabinets.)
Open it slowly.
It's here.
- Do it slowly. 1 at a time. - 1 at a time.
One at a time.
- One at a time. - That startled me.
What? It opened?
- There's nothing. - Try one at a time.
Do they all open?
This opened.
- What? - Is something inside?
- Was there anything inside? - So Min.
Only the camera was here.
I think it's one of those.
Hold on.
So Min, check the cabinets.
- What is it? - Be calm.
Be calm.
The killer is among us!
(He blurts out all of a sudden.)
Goodness.
(Are they filming a movie?)
What's with you?
There's English written on this.
(Check this out.)
- What? - "Adam".
Bring them here.
- "Nam Jung Seon". - "Rafael".
- What? - "Gabriel".
(What are these English names?)
(Seok Jin attempts to open another cabinet.)
- What? - It opened.
(He opens another cabinet.)
It opened. Hey, look.
There's a basketball.
(They find a basketball inside.)
- Why is there a basketball? - What can we do with it?
Why is this in here?
(What's the use of this basketball?)
Who's the killer? How many of them are in there?
Five basketballs.
(Jae Seok looks around.)
I think we need to take that out.
(There's a box.)
We need to put these balls in there.
(We need to put these balls in there.)
(There's an opening in this transparent object.)
- In here? - You're right.
- What do we do? - We should drop it in.
I think we need to break it.
- We need to drop it in. - Right.
- And then grab it. - RIght.
- With our hands. - You're right.
- Like that? - Aim well.
I get it now.
(Something breaks.)
- Aim well. - I get it now.
(On his first attempt,)
(he breaks it.)
(The middle lid opens, and a box falls out.)
- Goodness, Jae Seok! - We did it.
- You did it on your first try. - You're amazing.
- I was surprised too. - He sucks at basketball, though.
- It's a phone. - It's a phone.
(They find a phone.)
- This is easier than we thought. - We're doing well.
- We're too quick. - You're right.
- Let's see. - Wait.
It's a translator.
(If it's a translator...)
What is it, Jae Seok?
I think we're supposed to translate this.
Look inside the phone.
(Thai is written next to the exit.)
We have a translator.
(They might be able to translate it.)
What language is this?
- It's Thai. - It's Arabic.
- Is it Thai? - Don't you see that flag?
- The flag is right there. - Sorry.
(They attempt to scan the phrase.)
- What is it? - Go a bit back.
That's enough.
- What kind of... - Hey.
- I got it! - What is it?
- Ji Hyo, you're the killer. - Why?
(Why is Ji Hyo being suspected?)
- It's not me. - Why?
"There's a password written on Ji Hyo's shoes."
("There's a password written on Ji Hyo's shoes.")
(Is there a password on her shoes?)
- Take her shoes off! - Take them off!
Take them off!
- Hurry! - Hold her.
- It's really not me. - You're the killer.
- It's not me. - She just has a hint on her shoes.
- It's not me. - What is it?
- It's not me. - You're involved in this case.
(They find a password.)
- It's here! - I found it!
(The password is found on the sole of her shoe.)
- "301500". - This must be it.
- It was her! - No, it's not me.
(Kwang Soo suspects her.)
- No, it's not me. - Come here.
- I swear. It's not me. - It was you.
- Then what was this? - I have no idea.
Believe me.
- I know that you choose your shoes. - It's really not me.
(It opens.)
- What happened? - It opened!
- It opened! - It opened!
(They successfully escape the crime scene.)
- We did it. - It opened.
- Let's go to that address. - It opened.
- Let's go. It's that bus. - There's the bus.
- You... - It's not me.
Just come with us.
- It's odd that she had the numbers. - Come on.
Who knew it'd be her?
I won't trust any one of you.
- It was odd. - It doesn't make sense.
- My stylist told me to wear them. - What is this?
- Today... - I can't trust anyone.
Ji Hyo.
- You are... - I swear.
Then why were those numbers on your shoe?
- I... - We need to interrogate you.
- It was all fabricated. - Let's find out who the killer is.
For the assistant director.
(They promise to avenge for him.)
Jae Seok, if the killer knew...
that we'd be able to escape,
wouldn't it be weird to put the password in their own shoes?
- That's exactly what I mean. - So why were the numbers...
on your shoe?
- My stylist just gave them to me. - You probably met...
- the killer. - I suspect someone else more.
- It's Seok Jin. - Why?
(Is he the killer?)
- Because he was so quick? - He knew immediately to go...
- by the order of ages. - Right?
- You're right. - The order of ages?
- Right. - That was weird.
Let me explain.
(A while back,)
(everyone was confused on how to list the numbers.)
(Do you think the order is based on our age?)
(Looking at the formula, he guessed that it was by age.)
I guessed so because I noticed that my number was the biggest.
And I saw a minus too,
so I thought we'd start with my number first.
That's how I got the age part.
If you're not the killer, you have psychic powers.
(If you're not the killer, you have psychic powers.)
- Seok Jin. - Oh, come on.
You're one of the prime suspects.
Look at this.
- The assistant director was killed. - Right.
Why do you think so?
One of us must've been unhappy about the editing.
(Editing is an assistant director's main task.)
(Which one of them is the most unhappy?)
It's one of us.
- Doesn't it make sense? - It does.
- It does, right? - Then...
- It makes sense. - Come to think of it,
- One of us was very unhappy... - you're right.
- about the way he edited things. - Then...
- isn't it Seok Jin? - Exactly.
That's why I'm suspecting him.
- That makes sense. - Yes.
That's why...
I think he is the prime suspect.
I wish it were me.
(While everyone has their eyes on Seok Jin...)
I truly wish it were me.
- Someone was very unhappy. - I wish I was the killer.
(Is he really the killer?)
Hold on.
Hey, did you take off your hoodie?
- What? - Everyone's has it.
Kwang Soo isn't.
- What? - Why aren't you wearing one?
(Why isn't he wearing a hoodie?)
- He's not? - Look.
- Why don't you have one? - What is going on?
- I just tucked it inside. - You're trying to show off.
- I tucked it in for no reason. - Why?
- I can take it out. - Wait.
Let us see.
Are you wearing something different?
- Let me see. - There's nothing inside.
- What? - I'm so frustrated.
Remove his name tag.
- Why would you? - Remove it.
- You can't. - Should I?
He says no.
(Kwang Soo suddenly panics.)
- We can't? - He says no.
- No? - Why not?
(It's not even a race, so why not?)
Removing it means I'm out.
- No. - No.
- We're not having a race. - Something smells fishy in here.
He's hiding something.
- I know. - No.
- He didn't let us remove it. - He tucked his clothes in.
I used to be Sherlock, you see.
- What do you mean? - Jae Seok isn't the killer today.
- I used to be Sherlock. - He reads many detective novels.
(He did once play the role of Sherlock.)
The aged detective, Nose!
(It's a new character.)
- Nose. - Nose.
I am Detective Nose.
He's Detective Nose!
Detective Nose.
He sniffs around the crime scenes.
- He doesn't talk at all. - He just sniffs around.
He only smells. He charges 35 dollars per 30 minutes.
- That's a unique character. - He charges 35 dollars...
per 30 minutes. He's only there to sniff.
- Detective Nose. - That's adorable.
- Where's the calendar? - Did you bring the calander?
- "Calander"? - "Calander"?
Seok Jin must've brought it.
Really?
- How suspicious. - Let's look at it right now.
Goodness. There is no Monday.
I really enjoyed that movie.
March?
(What's the meaning behind this calendar?)
If you add the dates on Mondays, it sounds like "older brother".
Why?
The sum is 58. It sounds like "older brother".
- Maybe the killer was born in 1958. - Let's see.
- Who was born in 1958? - It's 58.
Seok Jin was born in 1966.
- Jong Kook was born in 1977. - 1977.
- No, 1976. - 1976.
- I was born in 1985. - Okay.
(Seok Jin: 1966, Jong Kook: 1976, Kwang Soo: 1985)
Wait. 85 backwards is 58.
(58 is the sum of the dates on Mondays.)
Exactly. That's why he's suspicious.
- That's enough. - Hey.
(He's enraged.)
(Everyone suspects him.)
- It's you, isn't it? - No.
- It's you again. - You're suspecting me...
- It's you, right? - just because of the year?
- 58 backward is 85. - It's not me.
- I promise that... - You're my older brother.
- This doesn't... What? - You're my older brother.
- You are. - What in the world are you saying?
(Is the calendar really pointing at him?)
Judging by everything that we talked about,
Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, and Ji Hyo...
- Not me. - are highly suspicious.
Just because I tucked in...
Be quiet.
He wants him to shut it.
He is suspicious.
- He's linked to 58. - He is.
We're headed to a restaurant.
- I guess we're having lunch. - Really?
- That sounds wonderful. - Seriously?
Hey. Look!
We're having pollack.
(They'll be going to a pollack restaurant.)
- It sounds like "nose". - It's Seok Jin.
And it's the Wangsimni branch!
- Big Nose! - Big Nose!
- Big Nose! - Seriously?
- Hey! - This is certain!
How could you?
Why did you have to come to Wangsimni?
- It's definitely him. - It's you, right?
- A pollack restaurant in Wangsimni? - It's not me.
- It's Seok Jin. - It's not me.
- It's Seok Jin. - Wow, it really...
- does make sense. - Big Nose!
- This isn't right. - Big Nose!
What kind of hint is that?
- It's you. - We caught the killer!
This is a pollack restaurant in Wangsimni.
(Is this really a hint?)
- It's seriously not me. - If you eat pollack today,
- it'll definitely be you. - We're not having pollack.
I'm quite keen, you know?
You know, right?
(Everyone enters the restaurant while being certain that it's him.)
Is there a hint here?
- It's here. - I think it is.
If we order pollack, you're definitely the killer.
- We need to keep an eye on him. - It's not me.
(They can't find any hints.)
- There must be a hint here. - We need to have our eyes peeled.
- Hey. - That's good.
What is this?
The food is already served.
- Food is served? - Really? Let me see.
Hey, look.
(There's food on the table.)
- I see three baby octopuses. - What?
- It's a long-legged octopus. - There's duck.
(There's no pollack but duck meat and long-legged octopus.)
It's 100g of duck meat and 70g of long-legged octopus.
(Their weight and calories are written.)
- What is this? - It's long-legged octopus.
- Maybe it's about the calories. - Wait.
It's long-legged octopus?
- Hey. - Where are their legs?
This is long-legged octopus?
- But where are their legs? - They don't have any legs.
They're missing their legs.
- It's... - Goodness.
Do you know why they're called long-legged octopus?
- Why? - They have thin legs.
(The octopus has thin legs.)
- It's you. - What?
- It's nonsensical. - Hold on.
- Right? - Yes.
- Look at his legs. - Come on.
- Look. - Wait.
- Look at his legs. - It's not me.
- Put him down. - Hold on.
(There must be a hint somewhere around his legs.)
Gosh!
Look at this.
He's not wearing socks. They look like stockings.
- Hey, how far will you go? - Look at his legs.
- Is there anything there? - How far are you rolling them?
- No. - No?
- There's nothing there. - I see.
- Really? - There's nothing.
We should look into the octopus.
- There are three of them. - What is that?
They're missing their legs.
The answer is in here.
We need to figure this out.
(It read, "Enjoy", alongside their weight and calories.)
Shouldn't we eat them first?
- Yes, maybe it's inside. - Yes.
Maybe.
Do I need to eat this duck meat?
There are no dips or sauces.
Don't eat it.
He ate it.
- Aren't we supposed to? - Is it good?
Is it raw?
- It's raw. - First,
let's eat it.
(It says to enjoy it.)
Try them.
(Nervous and curious, they decide to eat it.)
It's good.
(Detective Nose sniffs around.)
Try some.
- I already had it. - Have one more.
It's good.
(There's nothing strange about it.)
100g and 70g.
(What do their weight and calories mean?)
169.
(Surrounded by nervousness, they finish eating.)
Shouldn't we leave now?
Where should we go?
There's nowhere to go since we don't have any leads.
Maybe we should link this with that calendar.
Let me check this box.
(All that they see are the food and the menu.)
- Let's go outside for now. - Really?
There's nothing else in here.
We did enjoy the food.
Hold on. The rooms are all covered.
She's right. They're all covered.
(At a glance, they looked like ordinary rooms.)
They have marks on them.
(Each room has the Running Man mark.)
That's right. Let's go there.
- Let's go. - Hold on.
(Jae Seok walks towards the main entrance.)
What is this?
- What? - What is it?
- What is it, Jae Seok? - What is it?
(What stopped him in his tracks?)
- What is it? - He found something.
What do 169 calories mean?
(A calorie calculator is in front of the door.)
(And it read 169kcal.)
(The entrance is locked.)
(What do 169 calories mean?)
- Hey. - I think we need to subtract...
- how much we ate. - I see.
(They read "enjoy" and decided to eat the food.)
(The door will only open once the calculator reads 0.)
- We ate 169 calories of food. - Right.
We need to burn the calories.
- Darn it. - What is it?
I think every room has something we can use for it.
- Should we not have eaten them? - Maybe there are workout machines.
(Do the rooms offer ways to burn calories?)
The doors are closed.
We're allowed to go inside.
What is this?
(He spots something inside.)
- Is someone in there? - There's something inside.
(They find a mysterious, white box.)
- There's something in every room. - There's something in here.
We need to do something.
(What is that box?)
(He opens it.)
(There are objects inside.)
Look.
Are those watches?
If you place it on the phone, it charges the watch.
(There are 8 watches, and 1 of them is being charged.)
"Wear the watches, and you'll be able to read how much you burn."
We need to wear them and do something.
(Their first mission is to wear the watches.)
I think we just need to burn 169 calories.
It shows up like this.
- Do we have to go next door? - Hey.
- We need to burn calories. - Let's go.
Shall we go next door?
(They go to R2. What's in there?)
40 to 42?
What does 40 to 42 mean?
(Jae Seok spots something.)
This will help us burn calories.
- Is it food? - "Follow me."
"If you successfully mimic the video,"
"you'll burn 60 calories."
- I know what this is. - There are...
various songs here.
There's also Sean Lee.
(They should pick the easiest one.)
Let's burn 60 calories with "Bboom Bboom".
"Bboom Bboom".
(They need to follow the dance moves.)
"Complete".
It's working.
(The video turns on.)
Hey, we need to dance.
- We need to mimic them? - Yes.
- Goodness. - Let's do it.
- So Min, come out. - Let's do it.
- Let's do it. - Go, So Min.
(The choreography is hard.)
This is hard.
(So Min and Ji Hyo are doing well.)
(Everyone successfully mimics the "bboom bboom" part.)
- They're really good. - They are.
- They're good. - It's too quick.
(Meanwhile, they're struggling.)
(They cannot control their limbs.)
(These two are the best.)
(Thanks to them, they've burned 15 calories so far.)
- Let's go. - Get ready.
- Burn those calories! - Let's do it!
Make sure to do this.
(Everyone does the "finger bragging" dance move.)
(Jae Seok mimics very well.)
(They're burning many calories.)
(You're doing well.)
(They're burning the calories they ingested while eating.)
(They try their best to burn the calories.)
(They regret eating.)
This is tiring.
Seok Jin, are you a dinosaur?
(His dance moves remind them of a dinosaur.)
Let's go!
(They need to do well until the end to succeed.)
(They've given their all to the choreography.)
(Exhausted, they finish dancing.)
60 calories.
Let's find out.
Did we burn it?
- This is tiring. - Let's go to the next room.
(So Min goes to check how much they've burned.)
109 calories?
Wait, hold on. Guys!
It reads 109 calories now. It changed.
- It went down. - It read 109 calories now.
- Okay. - That's how much we have left.
- Shall we go next door? - Let's do that.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Why do we have to do this? - What's going on?
Who's responsible for torturing us like this?
- I shouldn't have eaten. - What?
You're right.
Let's leave this.
(What awaits them in R3?)
- This is interesting. - I'm so hot.
There are balloons.
(Startled)
- I guess we need to pop them. - Look.
We need to jump.
- We'll burn 50 calories. - Hey.
We need to jump and pop them.
Kwang Soo can do it. Kwang Soo, you need to do something.
- I do? - Yes.
- Come here, beanpole. - Hurry up.
- Hey. - Gosh.
- We need your help. - What is this?
It's worth 50 calories.
- It's worth 50 calories. - Pop them all.
I'm so glad we have a beanpole.
- It's all up to you. - You'll burn 50 calories.
- Let's go, beanpole. - We'll burn 50 calories.
That one has flour in it.
(He starts popping them.)
- Be careful of the flour. - Don't pop the flour.
(You're doing well, Kwang Soo.)
Goodness. He's good.
(He's having a party.)
(He was born to do this.)
- You're doing so well. - Way to go.
- Good job. - Am I doing this alone?
(He's getting exhausted.)
- You're doing well. - It's just you.
- Good. - Switch after popping 10.
Okay. Good, Kwang Soo. You can stop.
Go, So Min.
- Me? Can I reach that high? - Go.
What's important is that you burn calories.
- Jong Kook. - Okay.
(Jong Kook happily agrees to help.)
- Let's do this. - I won't be able to reach them.
Use him to jump.
Yes, do that.
Go. No, not like that.
- No, let me. - Jong Kook.
Come here. Do it.
(He's a gentleman.)
- I'm heavy. - Get ready. One...
1, 2, 3.
(I'll pick you up.)
(Popping)
(Flying)
Watch out.
(It looks romantic in slow motion.)
(You're the best, Jong Kook.)
Are you all right?
- I flew. - Are you okay?
Love is in the air.
I flew.
(Thanks to him, she pops 1.)
- Hold on. - Which one's the lowest?
- This will take ages. - That one's low.
How long will this take?
(They need to pop all of them. They've burned 13 calories so far.)
Where is it?
Can I just do it?
(He's frustrated.)
- I'll just pop them all. - All right.
Okay.
Just keep jumping around.
Let's burn all 109 calories.
It's best for him to do it since he's the tallest.
(He keeps his eye on the target.)
(He pops two at once.)
(He's on a roll.)
He popped two at once.
He's so tall.
(They're impressed by him.)
Try two at once again. That was cool.
(He's proud of himself.)
(Let me pop some more.)
- That's good. - You're doing well.
- Good. - Good job.
- He's the best. - Good job.
Hurry up. We have no time.
Okay, I'll help you. 1, 2, 3.
- Okay. - Good.
1... 1, 2, 3.
(Everyone helps him out.)
1, 2, 3.
- He's exhausted. - 1, 2, 3.
Okay.
- Jump again. - Goodness.
- 1, 2, 3. - Good job.
- 1, 2, 3. - Nice.
- Hey, just use a stick. - Let's go Kwang Soo.
(Just use a stick.)
- You look like a stick. - Use a stick.
You're a stick. You're.
Kwang Soo, do it.
- You should do it. - You're a stick.
- Kwang Soo, 1, 2, 3. - You're a stick.
Put him right under. 1, 2, 3.
(A human stick? I will accept it.)
(The human stick hits the target for 100 percent.)
- Stand at the back. - 1, 2, 3.
Keep your head raised. We'll do it for you.
There you go.
(Kwang Soo acquired a character unprecedented in history.)
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- No, there. - Here.
(They consumed 40 calories.)
There's a cluster. Let's pop 3 of them at 1 go.
- How about hitting 3 at 1 go? - I'm not going to lower my head.
We have only about a dozen left.
Kwang Soo, you're really awesome.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(He hit the ceiling.)
(He hit the ceiling again.)
- Keep holding him. - Wait a minute.
I'm hitting my head on the ceiling.
(Please be careful.)
Okay. Okay.
- We can do it. - Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(The human stick resumes working.)
(He hits the target without a mistake.)
He got the hang of it.
Good. Good. Okay. Good job.
He's certainly improving. He improved.
He doesn't miss.
You got the hang of it.
(The human stick got the hang of it.)
- Good job. - Great work.
(We only have 2 left now.)
(The last 2 balloons pop out.)
(He took care of all the balloons.)
You got the hang of it.
- Good job. - Kwang Soo put a lot of effort.
It was great.
Jae Seok. It's 59 calories.
Do we still have calories left?
Shall we go to the next room?
- It's hard to lift him up. - It's hard.
- Kwang Soo and... - We'll go out.
(The human stick is deserted after the balloons are popped.)
I can't do this. I can't.
What's left now?
- We need to burn more calories. - Where do we go?
(They have 59 calories left.)
(Only R4 is left.)
- There's another room. - There's one more.
- It's here. - There's one more.
- There it is. - It's here.
It's here.
- What's this? - What's this?
It's water.
We did more than 100 calories, and we have 59 calories left.
Jae Seok, do we need to hold out for 50 seconds?
Yes, 50 seconds. No, 60 seconds.
You need to lie face down and hold the ball.
We'll play Race of Wits, and the last one... You know.
- Okay. - Let's...
- The last might not have to do it. - Right.
Let's start.
(The Race of Wits begins.)
(Se Chan and Jo Hyo lose.)
Okay. Two of you play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Se Chan wins.)
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo challenges holding out on the gym ball for 10 seconds.)
If you hold out for 60 seconds, we're done.
- You can hold out for 60 seconds. - If Ji Hyo makes it, we're done.
If she holds out for 60 seconds, we're done.
- Ji Hyo can do it. - Go up on the ball.
- Hold out! - Hold out!
- Ji Hyo. - Please.
- It won't be easy to hold out here. - It won't be easy.
We have 59 calories left now.
- You shouldn't hold there. - I shouldn't?
Get balance.
You can say "Start".
It will be better to keep your legs up.
- Here you go. - Let's...
You need to hold the ball like this.
I'll hold your hands and let go when you start.
(Everyone is extremely focused in the last room.)
- Let's... - Get balance.
I'm ready.
- I'll let go when you tell me. - I'm ready.
- Ready. Go. - It's good.
(Ji Hyo challenges for holding out for 10 seconds.)
(They consume calories as much as they hold out on the gym ball.)
Just a little more!
Good.
It's a lot of exercises, I guess.
She's doing great.
(She narrowly keeps balance.)
She can do it.
(She's suddenly dancing.)
(Ji Hyo escapes the crisis with dance.)
(She's the best player.)
Seven... She's good.
(She succeeds if she holds out for 5 more seconds.)
- She's doing good. - Right...
(She puts her hands on the pool.)
(Ji Hyo succeeds in holding out for 10 seconds.)
- 10 seconds. - She's good.
- 10 seconds. - 10 calories.
- Okay. - We consumed a lot.
It was hectic.
- We have 49 calories left. - Nice.
Se Chan.
Start. It's cold.
Se Chan, focus.
You can do it.
Se Chan, you're athletic.
Ready. Go.
(Se Chan begins holding out for 10 seconds.)
He can do it.
- He can do it. - There you go.
- Good. Good. - He can do it well.
What's that?
(What?)
(Dancing)
Is he performing a circus?
(He's dancing cheerfully all of a sudden.)
(Falling in the water)
(He succeeds holding out for 11 seconds with a traditional dance.)
- It's cold! - It's all right.
How many seconds?
(They have 39 calories left.)
Is it hard?
- Go ahead, Haha. - Try it.
It's because it has too much air inside.
I'll let go of your hands after I balance.
(I'll show you the dignity of my experience of 10 years.)
- Good. Good. - He can make it.
Nice.
(You can do it this way if you want to make it funny.)
(He seemed to balance.)
- This looks the stablest. - He can make it.
(He's bowing down.)
(Haha fails in holding out for 10 seconds.)
- This is hard. - It's hard.
- Can't you do it? - Please be seated.
(The calory meter doesn't move.)
Look at me. We can't do this sitting on it.
Yes, the frog. There you go.
- Okay. - I should have got on it like that.
- It would work. - Look.
- That's it. - Take off your hands.
Good. Now you can just balance.
We just need to keep our limbs apart from the ball, right?
(We just need to keep our limbs apart from the ball, right?)
- I'll do it. I will. - Why?
We just need to keep our limbs apart from the ball, right?
- Do you know what limbs are? - I do.
- It means arms and legs. - Right.
Look at me. Then... Look.
(Haha makes a pose with confidence.)
Haha.
- Here I go. - Haha.
(Is he suddenly washing his hair?)
Here I go.
- Ready. Go. - Go.
(The moment he wets his hair,)
(he falls into the water.)
Go. One...
(He tried a new pose.)
(But he failed in 2 seconds.)
- My goodness. - That doesn't work.
Wouldn't it work if I do it with my face down?
Someone can try it with face down.
- Put your head down. - What are you doing?
Try putting your head down.
- Here goes So Min. - You can put your head down?
It's a frog. It's exactly a pose of a frog.
Goodness, you're putting your head into the water.
Why are you doing it? Why?
(I'll wash my hair too.)
Wait a minute. I'll give it a try.
- She can do it. - She can make it.
It's because she's light in weight. Just take your arms off the ball.
Ready. Go.
- She can do it. - 1, 2, 3.
She just fell down.
- She will get all wet. - So Min.
(So Min fails in holding out for 10 seconds.)
I'm sorry.
(I washed my hair.)
I'll start right away. I got it.
- Put your head into the water. - Go ahead.
(Kwang Soo gets ready to hold out washing his hair.)
(He looks somewhat stable.)
- He can make it. - Kwang Soo can do it.
(They still have 49 calories left due to continuing failure.)
- He's going to make it. - Ready.
go. Okay. One...
2, 3...
(He shows different stability.)
We made it. Seven...
(He looks most comfortable as if he's an aquatic creature.)
- We made it. - 1, 2...
(He's truly amazing.)
(Go for it, Kwang Soo.)
- 12, 13... - He made it.
(He succeeds in consuming 10 calories.)
- All right. - You made it.
(He deeply cleanses his scalp too.)
- Kwang Soo, you made it. - You did it.
- You did it. - You made it.
(Kwang Soo, you made it.)
- Good. - He made it, right?
- He made it. - He did it.
How many seconds?
- We have 29 calories left. - We have just a little left.
- Jae Seok, it's 29 calories left. - We need to do it 3 times more.
We need to succeed three more times.
I'll try it sideways.
- A human body is twisted. - Exactly.
Right.
Ready. Go.
- 1, 2, 3... - He can make it.
4, 5...
6, 7...
Are you all right?
Are you all right, Jae Seok?
(He's amazing.)
(He already became one with the ball.)
- This is nice. - Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok also succeeds in consuming 10 calories.)
What's going on?
How did he do it?
- How did you do it? - What was that?
- How could he do it? - I made it.
I sat sideways.
Sideways.
Everyone has own balance.
I could do it with my own balance.
(Haha without any success tries.)
Move your body a little bit like this.
- Jae Seok made it perfectly. - I did it perfectly.
He was perfect.
Here I go.
(Haha challenges with a sitting sideway strategy.)
3, 4...
(If Haha makes a success,)
(they only have 9 calories left.)
Just a little bit more.
(If he focuses a little more,)
(he can make a success.)
(Haha who followed Jae Seok's way of sitting sideways...)
(succeeds in consuming 10 calories.)
Great.
- We only have 9 calories left. - 9 calories.
You need to sit sideways. Sideways.
- Seok Jin, go see it. - Okay.
What does the meter say?
9, 9. It says 9 calories.
- Everyone has own pose to succeed. - Okay.
- Se Chan. - I think that will work.
Trust yourself.
You need to balance moving a little bit.
1, 2...
(Se Chan starts, keeping the momentum.)
(If Se Chan succeeds, they can escape right away.)
7, 8...
(They only have 9 calories left.)
(They need to succeed just one more time.)
(Can he make a success?)
- 9, 10. - Okay.
I think I can do it some more.
(He holds out for 10 seconds and makes a success.)
- I think I can do it some more. - Okay. Okay.
- Okay. - I got the hang of it.
- Okay. - That was nice.
- It was perfect. - It was good, Se Chan.
- Okay. - We made it.
(The calory meter points to 0.)
- Let's go! - Let's go.
We're done, right? We can escape.
- Let's get out. - Let's go.
- Are we locked again? - It's opening.
- It's zero calories now. - What's going on today?
What's going on today?
- It wasn't pollack. - It wasn't.
Anyway, who's the killer today?
After all, did we just consume the calories for this mission?
- By the way... - I got something.
- Jae Seok, I got something. - What's that?
- I got something. - Only you got a message?
Move to the next location for your mission.
33 Seongsu-dong 2-ga, Seongdong-gu.
It's near the former location.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
I think someone is playing with us.
There's someone.
We haven't solved the mystery about the calendar.
If we go, in the room again...
Here. It's here.
What's this? Goodness.
Goodness. I have no idea.
Jae Seok, I guess there's something more.
It seems there's something more.
What's this? Look at this.
Why? What is it?
(There are hidden clues to find out the killer in this place?)
I think there's something here.
What's this? Look at this.
Why? What is it?
(It's right in the center.)
(There's a Pirate Roulette Game.)
This is a Pirate Roulette Game.
The address of the next location is attached under the Pirate's feet.
Find the daggers and put it into the game.
(Put in the daggers to find the address under the Pirate's feet.)
- Daggers. - Daggers are...
hidden here?
I guess there are daggers here.
We need to find the daggers quickly.
We need to pop it out to get the address under its feet.
Where are the daggers?
(They need to find daggers and put them into the game.)
Find them. Find the daggers first.
Does the mirror here mean something?
The address is under its feet.
We can't take it out once we put it into the game.
(They need to find as many daggers as possible as they can't reuse it.)
We can't take it out.
Do we need to find them?
- Right. - The daggers.
We can't take it out once we put it into the game.
I guess there are only a few daggers.
Do we need to find the daggers in here?
This is... Goodness.
(It's so hard to find the hidden daggers.)
(This is...)
(She finds a dagger on the cutting board.)
(By the way, this is the dagger, right?)
Jae Seok, look at this.
- What's that? Is it a dagger? - I found a dagger.
- She found a dagger. - Where?
(She supposedly found a dagger.)
(Hearing So Min found a dagger, the members gather.)
- Is it right? - Is this a dagger?
- I've played it before. - Does this go into the game?
- Wait a minute. - Does this go into the game?
(Can this go into the game?)
(It can't go into the game.)
- This is not the dagger. - This is not it.
- But it has the R mark. - This is it. Here it is.
This is not the dagger.
(They thought it's not what they're looking for.)
(After taking off the cover,)
(they found the hidden dagger.)
- This is it. - We found it.
You know, this is...
We're done if we put it and the pirate comes out.
That's it. We're done.
- Jae Seok. - Right. Jae Seok. It's you.
Jae Seok, you're the only one.
I don't think I can do it.
(Speaking of him...)
(about the Pirate Roulette Game,)
(he can point out the hole for someone else.)
(He can point out the hole for any size of the game and any player.)
(He can pop the pirate out with his hand.)
Jae Seok, you're the only one.
(Can he pop it out with the first dagger?)
(They can escape the room if the pirate comes out on the first try.)
(Could Jae Seok's magic continue?)
Jae Seok, you're the only one.
(Can he pop it out with the first dagger?)
(They can escape the room if the pirate comes out on the first try.)
Please, please.
(Could Jae Seok's magic continue?)
(The pirate doesn't move.)
(He fails in taking out the pirate.)
(He's just unlucky today.)
It doesn't work.
"Springtime in Hometown"? What is it? Let me see.
- There's a song. - Let me see.
- This is it. - "Springtime in Hometown"? What?
(Kwang Soo finds...)
(two pieces of scores on the desk.)
The bicycle is coming
Why is it here?
Where?
Where's the calendar? It was on the calendar too.
The calendar had to red border too, didn't it?
(Both the score and the calendar have a red border.)
I guess it had.
Why is the "Springtime in Hometown" here?
What does this mean?
It drives me crazy when I see this. I'm so curious.
You're so curious, aren't you?
Ting-a-ling
What?
Why?
The score misses some musical notes.
(It misses some musical notes.)
It misses some musical notes. Look.
There are no musical notes for "Ting".
- What? - There are not, right?
- Here too. - Wait a minute. What's this?
- This here is... - "Ting"...
It's sol.
- No, it's here. - Is it fa?
Do, re... This is sol.
Mi, this is fa.
- Fa. Fa. - Sol, sol...
- Fa. - Fa.
- Fa. - Fa, fa.
It misses a part. Jae Seok, come here.
- What are you saying? - Here, for "Ting-a-ling",
there's a musical note missing.
It's not here too.
Sol, la, si, do, re, mi.
Mi. It's mi.
- What's this? - It's the high mi.
- This is fa. - Jae Seok, Monday was missing.
Isn't it Wolmido Island?
(Monday was missing in the calendar. Isn't it Wolmido Island?)
- What's this? - Mi and do.
Wolmido Island.
I guess it's Wolmido Island. Wol, mi, do.
Is it Wolmido Island?
- Monday was missing. - You're right.
Is it really Wolmido Island?
Isn't this fa?
First, let's find the address.
(Let's see if it really is Wolmido Island.)
It's mi.
What's this?
(Ji Hyo searches for daggers.)
(She finds stairs.)
It has upstairs.
I guess it's wrong.
(Where do the stairs take her?)
What's this?
(She arrives on the 2nd floor.)
(The daggers are hidden in places on the 2nd floor.)
- It had 2nd floor here. - 2nd floor?
(What's the mysterious thing on one side?)
- It's large here. - What's this?
(She searches for daggers right away.)
(She finds something.)
(It's an ice jar with a dagger in it.)
- What is it? Is it a dagger? - It's a dagger.
- Is it in that? - It's a dagger.
(Ji Hyo gets the 1st dagger hidden on the 2nd floor.)
- Yes? - Wait a minute.
- What's this? - It looks like a maze.
- There's a dagger in it. - Where?
- In there. - Where?
(Wooden sticks are in the object.)
(A dagger is in the object.)
(It's hard to get the dagger out.)
It's tough.
So Min, be careful.
Be careful.
How many daggers do we need to find?
I guess there are big ones and small ones.
I'll take this away.
(It's tough, right?)
(I already took it.)
She found it. She did it.
(They get an additional dagger thanks to So Min.)
Ji Hyo, find the dagger. Let's go downstairs.
(Let's go downstairs.)
- Find it. So Min. - Yes?
- Let's go downstairs. - Let's go.
(They were about to finish their search for daggers.)
(Ji Hyo finds something.)
Ji Hyo, you're amazing.
It's amazing. She found one more.
You're the best.
(The dagger was attached to the picture of Napoleon.)
(Ji Hyo's sharp eyes got one more dagger.)
- I found one more. - You're good.
You keep finding them.
- Let's go now. - I think it's enough.
Where are the daggers?
(The guys downstairs don't make any progress.)
Where can we find the daggers?
Wolmido Island?
- We need to find hints. - Right.
This has R attached on it.
(They need more daggers to check the next location.)
(He finally finds a dagger.)
- It's here. - There are a lot of them.
(In the freezer in the kitchen,)
(they find popsicles frozen on the dagger.)
(It's here.)
It's here.
- There are a lot of them. - I saw R on it.
It's frozen.
- We can eat them. - We need to eat these.
- They look delicious. - We can eat them.
(They need to eat the popsicles to get the daggers.)
Come here. Have some popsicles.
- Give it to me. I'll eat it. - I can't eat this.
Kwang Soo, eat some popsicles.
(What's this?)
It's sophora root tea.
- It's sophora root tea. - Is it sophora root tea?
It's calamansi. Calamansi.
- It's sophora root tea. - It's unbelievable.
(He tasted it later.)
It's a popsicle made of sophora root tea.
- It tastes really sour. - It's so sour.
It's totally the undiluted solution.
(It immediately improves your complexion and dilates your pupils.)
- Is this the dagger? - It tastes too strong.
This is the dagger.
- This is not the dagger. - It's not the dagger.
We need to eat this. Gosh.
This tastes really terrible.
I can't eat this.
- Pick one after a game. - What is it? Sophora root tea?
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Play rock-paper-scissors, and the loser should take a bite.
Jong Kook eats it well. Let Jong Kook eat it.
(They respect his taste.)
Sophora root tea is good for health, Jong Kook.
You can eat it, Jong Kook.
- The loser should eat it. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and So Min win.)
- Okay. - Paper, out.
All right.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo win.)
Yes.
Ji Hyo is out.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(The unlucky people match.)
(Haha loses.)
- Gosh, really. - Yes.
It's too sour.
(Haha has to eat the calamansi popsicle.)
- Eat just one bite. - Eat this.
- This is too much. - Eat this and then eat that one.
This is calamansi, right?
(His mind is detoxified as well as his body.)
Let's play it right away.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - I can't eat this.
(Rock-paper-scissors for the second popsicle)
(Ji Hyo and Jae Seok lose.)
- Okay. - I won.
(The unlucky person versus the lucky)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(For a match, someone is unlucky...)
(forever.)
Jae Seok, you...
(He loses as always.)
Why doesn't she lose at all?
(Why does he lose every time?)
- This tastes crazy. - It really tastes awful.
- This is really, Jae Seok... - It might knock you out.
- It might knock you out. - It might really knock you out.
Well done.
(Starting the ecstatic state from the sophora tea.)
(Fatally bitter taste hits him later.)
This is no joke.
- This is no joke. - It will knock you out.
(He's shuddering because of the bitterness.)
- This... - What is this?
- It'll knock you out. - I can't do this.
- This is no joke. - It's good for you.
This is no joke.
- It's so bitter. - Look at this.
(After eating the bitter popsicles, they obtain 2 daggers.)
Hey, hey.
I think the sophora tea is the worst.
- It can't be that bad. - Try it yourself.
Please come up.
(Kwang Soo has a high chance of getting the penalty.)
Go on.
(Will he succeed in making the pirate come up?)
(Fails)
- This is driving me mad. - You should do it instead.
(He fails to make the pirate appear.)
You should do it instead, Jae Seok.
It won't work for people who are unlucky.
(The true unluck one reappears.)
(He aims to regain his reputation.)
(Fails)
(Why am I not unlucky today?)
Do we have to look for them again?
Do we have to eat another popsicle?
- Should we try going up? - We poked in so many daggers.
I feel like there are more upstairs.
(The miners are moving to the gold mine on the 2nd floor.)
This is no joke. It was undiluted.
(Where could it be?)
(I haven't seen this box before. What could it be?)
(He takes it out.)
What is this?
(Searching)
- What on earth is this? - What is it?
What on earth is this?
(There is something inside the box.)
- It's quite wet. - What is it?
Put your hand in it again.
(Kwang Soo puts in his hand again.)
(What was that? He's focused.)
There it is. There's a dagger.
- Come on. - My gosh.
(There's something else other than the dagger.)
- Take it out. - There it is. There's a dagger.
(The mysterious creature grabs his hand and doesn't let go.)
(What's happening to Kwang Soo?)
Why?
- What? - What's wrong?
(What's happening to Kwang Soo?)
- What's wrong? - Why?
(What's the wet and mysterious creature inside the box?)
- What's in it? - Goodness.
- An abalone. - It's an abalone.
(Screaming)
(They obtain a dagger together with an abalone.)
- It's an abalone. - An abalone.
How's an abalone this big?
(The mysterious creature was...)
(an abalone with a dagger.)
It was inside an abalone.
Was it in there?
- It was with an abalone. - What?
There's one more here.
- What? - There's one more here.
- Here. - Put your hand in it.
(What's inside this box?)
Should I...
- Is there one more? - Gosh.
- Why? - There's...
- What is it? - There is someone's hair in it.
- Someone's hair. - Just put it in.
- It's really someone's hair. - Stop lying.
- It's someone's hair. - This is nothing.
You should be able to do this.
(What's in the box?)
(Goodness)
You can do it. You're amazing.
(I feel uneasy with him as well.)
You're looking great.
You can feel it, right?
- My goodness. - What is it?
(What's the thing that Seok Jin was making a fuss about?)
- What was that? - Goodness.
- Take a look inside. - There's nothing.
- I wish we could find one more. - There's nothing.
- Try going in further. - There it is.
I found it.
Great. We're doing well.
Let's go downstairs since we found them.
- Let's go down. - Gosh.
- Did you find it? - You better make it work this time.
- If it doesn't work this time... - Seriously.
(Will they be able to succeed this time?)
I feel like there's one here.
(It popped up.)
(The pirate is out.)
- Gosh. - It worked.
(His bad luck is back.)
- It came out. - It did.
- It came out. - It's out.
- It's out. - Seoul...
(But something isn't right.)
- It's out. - It's the same address from before.
(It's the same place from before.)
(The address that was written on the pirate is...)
- Where our first mission was. - Yes.
It's the first place we were at. The crime scene.
(the location where the assistant director was killed.)
- Do we have to go there again? - Where the assistant director was.
Is it that place?
- There's something more there. - Then let's go.
I think we need to head there first to be sure about things.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(What kind of secrets are hidden in that place?)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They head to the address that they obtained with complications.)
- Do we not have a car? - Why are there two cars?
(Why are there two cars?)
- Why are there two cars? - We should split.
This one says "Jee Seok Jin, four people".
(Why are there two cars?)
What does "Jee Seok Jin, four people" mean?
(The other car...)
- What? - "Song Ji Hyo, four people".
(The other car says "Song Ji Hyo, 4 people".)
This is strange.
- It's one of these two. - No.
(Song Ji Hyo and Jee Seok jin. One of them is the culprit.)
(This is too strange to be true.)
- Oh, my gosh. - Goodness.
- No, I'm not. - It can't be.
But we did suspect these two all day long.
(Why are their names written on the car?)
Are you hiding something?
I have nothing to hide. It's not me.
There is a reason behind why it was in her shoes.
I don't know anything.
These two were related to this.
I'm not related to this.
- Then why would... - I don't know anything.
Which car do we get on?
We have to separate ourselves strategically.
Why is my name written here?
It's making me feel uneasy.
This is driving me mad.
What do we do? Do we have to get separated?
- Get on. - I'm going with Ji Hyo then.
This will decide our fate.
- It will. - You're right.
- I don't know anything. - Why is it Seok Jin and Ji Hyo?
I don't know anything. I'm being used.
- It's not you, right? - No, I'm not. I'm being serious.
- How about your shoes? - Really.
I put on my shoes without thinking.
I'm not lying. It's not me.
I wouldn't be saying this if it was me.
But what's the difference between this and that car?
But we're heading to the same address.
- The place we're heading. - We're heading to the same place.
Are we divided into two teams now?
- Why are we divided into two teams? - Exactly.
What? Jee Seok Jin's room?
- What? - Are there different rooms?
- There are different rooms. - What?
It's an escape room.
What is Jee Seok Jin's room?
I don't know what this is.
- We have to escape it again. - What is going on?
Even the rooms are separated?
- Separate rooms? - Gosh.
(What does the suspicious Jee Seok Jin's room look like?)
- It's a crime scene. - It's a crime scene again.
- Goodness. - What is this place?
What is this?
(It's like a real crime scene...)
What is this place?
(with strange scribbles and mysterious objects.)
What is this?
What is this? What are we supposed to do here?
There is a lever here too.
What happens if we pull it?
- Look, a safe. - There's a safe.
- We need to get its password. - That's right.
- As soon as we... - We need to get its password.
Yes, we do.
I guess they put something in it.
Is this a team competition?
I guess so.
(Team Seok Jin came back here to find the culprit.)
Is the door locked?
(And they are...)
The door is locked again.
(locked in again.)
We need to open it before them.
(What will their fate be?)
There is Song Ji Hyo's room?
Where? Gosh.
- What's this? - I don't know.
There is Song Ji Hyo's room.
Hey.
(It's filled with mysterious objects like the other room.)
What is this skull sign?
Why is there a mess?
- Hey. - What?
Come here quickly. Hold on.
It's 4 against 4.
(Separated rooms that look similar.)
- This is how we escape. - This is a team competition.
Let's do this steadily.
Gosh.
- What? - Hey.
- They're all locked. - Look around first.
Let's find all the clues. Open up everything.
(What will they have to do to escape the rooms?)
We need to find some clues first.
(Team Seok Jin starts searching the room.)
(Is there a clue in this?)
(There must be a clue somewhere.)
There is a door.
(There must be a clue in here.)
- Why? - What is this necktie?
What?
What is this necktie?
- What's in there? - There are more clues.
Are there more clues?
(There are more clues in here.)
Let's listen to this.
(They discover a cassette player.)
(When they first arrived in the morning...)
(the assistant director was holding this cassette player.)
(A crucial hint was recorded.)
Let's listen to this.
If you have reached this far,
you have almost succeeded.
I left clues up until here...
and tried to chase the culprit,
but I was eliminated at last.
- It's this place. - If you find the culprit...
in this room and enter his name,
you'll find the way to survive.
- Find the culprit... - But...
if you find who the culprit is later than the other team,
you'll be eliminated straightaway.
(You'll be eliminated straightaway.)
Be careful.
- It's a competition. - Hurry.
- My gosh. - It's a competition.
- They don't know it yet. - Right. They don't know.
What do they want us to enter?
- The culprit... - What do they want us to enter?
- Do they want us to enter it here? - How do we do that?
(They don't know what and how to enter.)
How do we do this? Why is there a necktie?
This is crazy.
- Hurry. Open it. - Open it.
I don't think the other team knows that they have to hurry.
(A battle of who's going to be eliminated.)
Let's look around and find clues.
Open up everything.
(Team Ji Hyo doesn't know anything yet.)
This is driving me mad.
(They search everywhere for clues.)
I don't know what's going on.
(How do the clues look like?)
Look, there it is.
(I found something.)
What is it?
(They discover the cassette player.)
- Let's listen to it. - What is it?
If you find the culprit in this room and enter his name,
you'll find the way to survive.
But if you find who the culprit is later than the other team,
you'll be eliminated straightaway. Be careful.
- We have to hurry. - We need to hurry.
We need to find clues quickly.
(They need to find who the culprit is faster to not get eliminated.)
Where is it?
- Se Chan! - What?
(So Min found something.)
What do you think this is?
(She found a picture frame with red edges.)
- What is it? - That's my childhood photo.
- Isn't that Ji Hyo? - This is Ji Hyo, and there's me.
That's me when I was little.
Who's this?
- Jong Kook. - There's Seok Jin.
- And Jae Seok. - Jae Seok.
And Kwang Soo.
- Ji Hyo, you had short hair? - Jae Seok looks like an alien.
There are eight photos in it.
That's me when I was in elementary school.
- 8 of us? - There's 8 of them?
Let's just look around.
We need to find more clues.
That has red edges around it too.
This is another clue.
It says "middle". It's a Chinese character for middle.
- I think those two are related. - Middle.
- Middle? - Come here, let's see.
Let's round them up and see. What do they mean?
Help me with this.
(Let's combine all the clues.)
Middle, Ji Hyo.
3 octopus legs?
Third grade in middle school.
Third grade in middle school?
(She combined all of them and it's hard to figure it out.)
I just got blanked out.
This is a disaster.
Hurry up, now.
We need to hurry!
(Team Seok Jin only found a cassette player.)
We need to find more clues.
- Why? What is it? - It's a CD.
(They found a CD with red tapes.)
- We need a CD player. - There it is.
Let's play it.
Let's play the CD.
- It's already plugged in. - It is. It is plugged in.
It's playing.
It's the "Magic Castle".
- "Magic Castle"? - It's "Magic Castle".
(The CD had the Classic's song, "Magic Castle"!)
Is there something missing? Like a letter in the song, maybe?
- "Magic Castle". - "Magic Castle"?
Maybe something is missing in the song.
(They're singing along in the hope of figuring it out.)
(The world that will spread out before us)
(Is too precious when we're together)
- It's not missing a letter. - All the lyrics are in there.
All the lyrics are in there.
Why did we even listen to it?
The "Magic Castle"?
- What's with "Magic Castle"? - What could it mean?
What does it mean?
What could it mean?
He's up in the air, so what?
Freely
We need more clues.
(They need another clue to find the culprit.)
- Seok Jin! - What.
I found a CD.
(He found the second CD in a box.)
- It's a CD! - CD.
(They hope it's better evidence.)
- There's another CD. - It's another CD.
- It's a CD. - CD.
What is going on?
- It's a CD. - Play it.
(What song will this one have?)
Here we go.
(Second clue)
(Seok Jin's song, "I Know")
It's my song.
- "I Know". - "I Know".
- What is this? - Should you know something?
I think there's something on him.
- Come here. - I think he's supposed to know it.
- "Magic Castle". - It's not in here.
(Nothing is on his name tag.)
- It's your song. - It's called "I Know".
"I Know"...
I know?
They're saying you do.
- I do? - Hold on.
What are the lyrics?
I know that I love you.
I feel your warm breath, but you're not...
[VIU Ver] SBS E444 Running Man
"Room Escape"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
with me. I forgot the lyrics.
(If he's supposed to know, they're stuck in here forever.)
You said "I Know".
"I Know"?
I know? I'm supposed to know?
What do I know?
- It's saying you know. - I really don't.
- I know? - It's a password.
It's saying you do.
(Seok Jin carefully approaches the safe.)
(He starts entering numbers.)
(Opening)
(The safe is open!)
- What's he doing? - Oh, I opened it!
How did you open it?
Did you know?
- I just put in my date of birth. - I told you.
- My date of birth. - I told you you knew.
This is...
(What's in the safe?)
(There's a laptop.)
I told you you knew.
Well, I didn't.
- I told you. - You knew.
(Team Seok Jin gets the laptop thanks to Seok Jin.)
- Come on. - Hurry up.
I can't believe this.
How could I have known?
(What's in this laptop?)
(The laptop is...)
(locked!)
We need a password.
(They need the password to log in.)
Now what?
- Could it be my... - Your date of birth?
(Is the password his date of birth?)
(He enters his date of birth again.)
- That's not it. - It doesn't work.
(It was the wrong password.)
We found this, but it isn't over.
This is unbelievable.
(Team Seok Jin is still wrapped in mystery.)
- We need to figure this out too. - What's the password?
What could it be?
What do they mean?
Where's that picture?
Here it is!
Here's the picture.
Ji Hyo, is this when you were in middle school?
Yes, middle school.
Middle. Middle school.
(Ji Hyo found something.)
(She found the third clue!)
- What is it? - There another one.
It's Ji Hyo's picture! That's you, isn't it?
It is me, but...
- What is going on with you? - When was this picture taken?
Look at her middle finger.
(Her middle finger is highlighted.)
Ji Hyo.
(Why is the middle finger highlighted?)
Monday, Mi, middle,
and Ji Hyo.
(The clues are Monday, Mi, middle, and Ji Hyo.)
We need to open this safe.
Should we combine some numbers we found?
We don't know how many we need.
- How many... - We need 6 digits.
(The safe opens with a 6-digit password.)
Wait, let me get my head straight.
Where did we find the key?
(Let's see, 6 digits...)
Ji Hyo, I need the first six digits of your social security numbers.
(Ji Hyo, what's your date of birth?)
The first 6 digits.
(Is it her date of birth just like in Seok Jin's room?)
- 81... - You put them in.
(Opening)
(The safe is open.)
- It's open. - What is it?
(Team Ji Hyo gets the laptop thanks to So Min.)
- It's open. - It was my date of birth.
What was the password?
- My date of birth. - It was your date of birth?
She put in her date of birth, and it opened.
- How'd they know my ID numbers? - Hold on, let's see.
All the clues we found, let's round them up.
The first one was...
- Monday was missing. - Right.
And then the long-legged octopus.
- So 4 Mondays were missing. - Yes, 4.
- 3 long-legged octopuses. - So, 3.
- We have 4, 3, - And this one. 4, 3, 7?
- 7 and 15? - But I don't know the order.
- 4, 3, 7, and 15. - Yes, 7 and 15.
It could be 43715.
- Put them in, 43715. - That's 5 digits.
- 43715. - 437...
- 15. - 15.
- Or 43157. - Right.
- Now put in 43... - 157.
- 43... - 157.
43157?
- Wrong password. - Do we have...
Do we have more clues? This is too hard!
(What would be the laptop's password?)
- I'm totally blank. - Me too.
- "Magic Castle". - When we freely
- Fly through the air - Fly through the air
("Magic Castle" and "I Know"...)
(should have something to do with the password.)
Where is it?
(Jae Seok is still trying to find clues.)
"Magic Castle".
- What? - What?
(There was...)
There's one more CD?
(another CD between chairs.)
(Jae Seok's discovery.)
It's the third one.
Right, the third one.
I still can't figure out the "Magic Castle".
(What song is in the third clue?)
It's "Gee".
"Gee"?
How many are the Girls' Generation?
Nine members.
("Magic Castle", "I Know", and now "Gee".)
Girls' Generation, "Magic Castle",
- "Gee". - "Gee"?
(Where's the correlation between those three?)
"Magic Castle" and "Gee".
(They have three clues, but still don't have a clue.)
How many "Gee"s are there?
- Five "Gee"s. - Gee, gee, gee, gee, gee
(Gee, I wish I knew.)
What does "Gee" mean?
I think "Gee" was just for Jee Seok Jin.
(I think "Gee" was just for Jee Seok Jin.)
- Right? - Makes sense.
- Oh, was it? - And the "Magic Castle" was...
- What about "Magic Castle"? - to tell us his surname.
- His surname! - Jee.
- Was it? - Yes, I think so.
- It meant the surname? - Your surname, Jee.
Maybe it is.
(First clue)
("Magic Castle" was about Seok Jin's surname, Jee.)
(Third clue)
("Gee" referred to Jee.)
- So we need to combine the hints. - That's right.
Right? I think so. We were missing Mi in the score.
(All the clues should lead to the password.)
Monday, Mi...
There's got to be something.
We haven't found anything related to these clues.
- That's true. - So this is missing the Mondays?
- Right. - Missing Mondays.
Could it be...
I don't think it's Monday,
I think it's the letters "Mon".
- Right? - "Mon".
(I think it's not Monday but the letters "Mon".)
- "Mon"? - I think that's the clue.
- Right? - "Mon".
- Since it's not in Korean. - I did think of that before.
"Mon". This is so frustrating.
"Mon".
Wait!
(Did he figure it out?)
- Why? - What is it?
- What is it? - What?
Fine dust.
Put it in. Enter "Fine Dust".
- Three from the octopus? - Right, the octopus.
(Will it be the right password?)
Come on, hurry up. Hurry up.
It's open!
("Fine Dust" was the right password!)
(Ji Hyo's room members are instantly eliminated.)
- What's happening? - What is it?
(They were also trying to figure out the password.)
- They figured it out? - They did?
- They figured it out? - Team Seok Jin...
has entered the name of the culprit.
Team Ji Hyo will be eliminated as a whole.
(Team Ji Hyo will be eliminated as a whole.)
(Fine dust was the password and the culprit.)
All of us?
We got it!
(Instructions on how to survive are on the screen.)
This is it.
"If one person finds the lever and pulls it..."
(The door will open.)
"Only three people can get out."
My goodness.
(Jong Kook fails to read the directions.)
The lever.
"Only three people can get out."
(The person who pulls the lever without thinking...)
(is Jong Kook.)
- Pull it. - Pull it.
- Jung Kook. - Keep your hands on it.
Keep your hands on it.
- Keep your hands on it, - Let's escape.
- Keep your hands on it, - Keep your hands on it,
- Keep your hands on it, - What?
(They leave Jong Kook behind.)
What?
(The confetti bombs go off inside the room.)
What is going on?
Okay.
- What? - What?
(The 3 escapees get water bombs.)
- What? - What's going on?
What?
What is going on?
(They have no idea what is going on.)
- What is going on? - What is going on?
- What happened? - I mean...
- The winner is Kim Jong Kook. - Why?
(For some reason, the winner is Kim Jong Kook.)
- What? - How did this happen?
- Is Jong Kook the winner? - How did this happen?
Why is Jong Kook the winner?
Didn't he get locked up?
My goodness.
(How did this happen?)
Thus,
the final winner of the race is Kim Jong Kook.
(The final winner of the race, Kim Jong Kook)
I didn't do much today.
I think I get it.
- The hint was fine dust. - That was the culprit.
People who went outside got eliminated due to fine dust.
- That's right. - They got killed off.
(Did people who went outside got eliminated due to fine dust?)
I will explain.
Today, you had Running Man's 444th Episode Special.
- 444. - Case Number 444,
Mysterious Cause of Death Race.
- Mysterious Cause of Death Race. - The assistant director was out...
because of the hottest issue, fine dust.
I relate to the storyline.
Let's go over the hints you found.
The calendar was missing Monday.
"Monday" was missing.
- It was like a drama. - I know.
(The assistant director had a calendar.)
("Monday" was missing.)
(Mon)
- We focused on Monday. - It didn't help us.
Then Seok Jin suddenly went...
- I realized it's "Mon". - "Isn't it 'Mon'?"
- Then Jong Kook said, "Mon". - "Mon".
- Then Jae Seok said... - "Dust".
("Mon" and other hints make up "Fine dust" in Korean.)
We thought of it as Monday all day long.
In the restaurant of the second mission,
you had long-legged octopus,
which uses the same character...
as the one in "fine dust".
I see.
- "Se" in Korean. - "Se".
The same character.
Where you found the swords of the Pirate Roulette Game...
Mi. It's mi.
(They found music sheets without mi.)
"Mi" is missing.
- The missing note was... - "Mi".
The last hint was the last name of Seok Jin, Jee...
or the middle letter of Ji Hyo's name, Ji.
(There was a hint that was related to Ji Hyo.)
(This is another clue.)
(Look at the red frame.)
(Only Ji Hyo's picture was from her middle school days.)
I laughed so much at these pictures.
Jong Kook is handsome.
Seriously.
Haha looks exactly like his mother.
Kwang Soo resembles Yoon Sang, his cameraman.
- That's right. - Yes.
Only Se Chan and I...
are opening our mouths.
- You have protruding teeth. - People with protruding teeth...
can't close their mouths.
Kim Young Chul is the same.
- I need to close my mouth. - Seriously.
(The culprit was...)
(fine dust.)
(The meaning of the hidden hints)
The password at the first location, 301500 represents...
air quality index from 301 to 500, which is the most dangerous.
(Duck meat was with long-legged octopus)
Duck meat is food that is good for discharging fine dust...
in your body.
The place where you found the swords...
was filled with plants...
that purifies the air.
Thus, the final winner of the race is...
Kim Jong Kook.
You know,
the process was good, but the finale...
The finale was tainted with betrayal.
- It wasn't betrayal. - It wasn't betrayal.
Don't call it a betrayal.
We simply acted fast.
We were wise.
- We were wise. - Listen.
I had a sly thought,
but Kwang Soo was the absolute worst.
That's not true. That's not true.
- Jong Kook went to the lever. - I pulled it.
Since nothing changed,
I was like, "What is going on?"
Kwang Soo jumped forward.
"Keep your hands on the lever."
- He said that. - That's right.
Who are you to call him sly?
As a prize, Jong Kook will receive...
- What will he receive? - Is there a prize?
The assistant director who has resurrected...
- My goodness. - He came back to life.
- Is it really a prize? - My goodness.
Is it really a prize?
I hope it will make you healthier.
All right.
(Be healthier.)
An air purifier.
- I am jealous. - Jong Kook gets everything!
We always get water bombs!
We always suffer.
You could get married.
(Do a better job.)
These days, we feel down...
- because of fine dust. - That's right.
- It's bad for our health. - Yes.
That's right. I miss the blue sky.
We hope the blue sky...
and clear air come back soon.
- Seriously. - We will be back next week.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We hope to see the blue sky from now on.)
(The 11 single members assemble.)
(Today, the members of Running Man will be...)
(the dazzling singles.)
(Avoid spring, the season of couples...)
(and bring single people together.)
(Single people become stronger when they are together.)
(You can shake off your loneliness.)
(However,)
(there is a couple who infiltrated the group.)
(Among the single members,)
(find the secret couple.)
(Who could be the secret couple?)
- I got it! - I got it!
(Hug)
(Passionate kiss)
(Explicit words)
(Will this air on TV?)
(The Counterattack of Singles)