- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
- This place is beautiful. - Hello.
- This is such a beautiful place. - Okay!
Good morning.
Kwang Soo, you shouldn't wear your pajama pants to the filming.
No. They aren't pajama pants.
I get that you feel comfortable, but you shouldn't wear those.
- They aren't pajama pants. - Hey, what is that?
- Right here... - What's crawling on your pants?
Jong Kook wouldn't have allowed this if this happened back in the days.
- That's right, I wouldn't have. - You know?
These aren't pajama pants. We weren't even in our spots yet!
- They aren't pajama pants. - You just rolled out of bed.
- No, no. - Why did you wear that?
By the way, why are you wearing sunglasses now?
Your eyes are pretty, you know.
(Take off your sunglasses.)
Seok Jin. What was that?
(It was a compliment.)
Here's what really happened. After talking about her sunglasses,
- Ji Hyo didn't look happy. - he saw she wasn't happy about it.
- He saw that she wasn't happy. - Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - He catches on really fast.
Your eyes are awful, you know.
He threw the carrot as soon as he gave her stick.
- He's not good at improvising. - Exactly.
He can think on his feet now.
I'm really good at improvising.
I bet he can do this because of his wife.
- My gosh. - Right.
"What are you doing, honey? Honey, this is beautiful."
He says these lines to survive.
Let me tell you a story about my wife.
Yesterday, she gave me some food. It was fried tofu rice balls.
I asked if we had... I saw the fried tofu a long time ago.
I asked if it was old fried tofu.
She said, "Just eat it. You're the oldest thing in our house."
(Just eat it. You're the oldest thing in our house.)
(He's the oldest person and thing.)
(His wife's line struck hard at the picky eater.)
- My gosh, his wife... - Goodness.
- She's the best. - Her improvisation is much better.
- It was awesome. - The family of improvisation.
I was so wounded inside. I couldn't say anything.
(That's true.)
I couldn't say anything.
- She has a similar sense of humor. - That was amazing.
That was great.
- Are you curious about the race? - Yes.
Before I tell you about your mission today,
- you'll welcome guests today. - I see.
- They will come through the door. - It's been a while.
It's been a while.
Please come on out.
- Who is it? - This is...
(Today's guests came all the way here in this heatwave.)
- It's a concert hall. - It's been a long time.
(Cho Jung Seok, the ideal handsome guy)
(Yoon A, perfect idol singer and actress)
(These two familiar guests are visiting Running Man today.)
- Jung Seok. - It's Yoon A.
- My goodness. - Jung Seok.
- Jung Seok. - Jung Seok. My brother-in-law.
- What do we call him? - What's going on?
- Call him brother. - Brother.
- Brother. My goodness. - Gosh.
- Brother. - Hello.
- Have you been well? - Yoon A.
- Have you been well? - Hello.
- Hi. - Hello, Yoon A.
- Hey, it's been a while. - Yes, it's been so long.
- Hello. - I'm happy to see Jung Seok,
- but now that we filmed with her, - Right. We filmed...
- with Gummy. - I'm happy to see you even more.
- I heard the news. - We wanted to invite you out.
A while ago, Gummy was on Running Man.
- She filmed an episode with us. - Yes.
Did she say anything about her experience?
Well, she... Can I be honest?
- Yes, be honest. - Okay.
I was driving and brought up the show.
I told her that she had the dream team.
I said that if Jong Kook and she could sing...
and Haha could rap, it would be awesome.
This is what she said.
(This is Gummy's answer to that.)
(Shaking her head)
Haha wants to sing.
(Haha wants to sing.)
(Haha's unyielding persistence wasn't what she expected.)
That punk. Goodness, he should know his place.
- My gosh. - You don't know your place.
- There was a talk about that. - She looked different.
You don't know your place.
Sorry to say this but after she said that,
our conversation ended there.
She didn't say anything.
- Haha, you should leave the team. - She didn't say anything.
- Go to another team. - No.
You only mentioned Haha, and things got bad in the car.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
- I'll sing more passionately then. - She sighed.
By the way, you two...
filmed a movie together, right?
- A movie? - I see.
- Really? - What's the movie about?
- It's called "Exit". - "Exit".
- "Exit". - It's about escaping a disaster.
Movies about disasters are entertaining.
Isn't this your first time working together on a project?
- Yes. - Yes.
How was working with one another?
- I... - It was great.
Come on.
(She didn't even breathe before answering.)
- You didn't sound sincere at all. - No.
- Don't say what you memorized. - Come on.
- You're unbelievable. - Stop teasing me!
- You didn't sound sincere. - Yoon A has gotten weird.
- What was that? - Come on.
Besides, what was this just now? She screamed like this.
(She still answers like an idol singer.)
Anyway, Yoon A and Jung Seok will be joining us...
for today's episode.
- Let's give them a hand. - Yes!
Today, it'll be an individual match. It's ECN for short.
Escape with Cards,
- Then It'll Be Nice. - We have to escape.
Today, you'll be locked inside the building.
(An unexpected warning)
(They will get locked up from the start?)
(The moment they enter the building,)
(all the exits will be closed.)
Let me tell you how you can escape.
The race will begin with three cards.
You'll draw those cards shortly.
Throughout the building,
there are five exits where you can escape the building from.
There are only five.
Each exit has a different condition...
- you must meet to escape. - Is that so?
If you think you meet the condition of the exit,
you can escape at any time.
- Together? - Is that it then?
If a member escapes through the exit, the exit will be closed.
That means only five of us can make it out.
That's correct. The condition for 1 of the 4 exits is...
the member with the biggest sum of the three cards.
It's the member with the biggest sum of the three cards.
(The member with the biggest sum of the cards)
And the member with three consecutive numbers.
(The member with three consecutive numbers)
And the member with 3 multiples of 5.
(The member with 3 multiples of 5)
And the member with 4 of the same number from the 3 cards.
For example, if someone has 1, 11, and 21,
that means that person has 4 1s.
These members can escape through these four exits.
The members who successfully escape from the building...
will enter Good Place.
"Good Place".
It's quite self-explanatory.
You can enjoy all the privileges on the menu as much as you want.
(Various services and meals are unlimited.)
(When they escape, they can enjoy the luxury of the place.)
My gosh, I want the massage.
You can get your eyes massaged.
Gosh, there's tiramisu too. There's a lot on the menu.
The scalp treatment is 100 dollars.
- I have to get that. - Okay. I'm in.
The members who failed to escape and members who get eliminated...
will have to pay the tab at Good Place together.
- My gosh. - We have to pay.
We have to pay for it.
The losing members will have to split the tab and pay.
(That will be a lot of money.)
However,
I told you that there are only five exits you can escape from.
I've explained to you about only four exits.
Let me tell you about the last exit.
- The last exit is... - What is it?
the Hunter's door.
(The 5th exit is the Hunter's door.)
(The Hunter's door is somewhere in the basement.)
- There must be a Hunter. - Among 10 of you,
two of you are Hunters.
(The two Hunters, who already got the mission, are among them.)
- Come on. Kwang Soo. - Who are they?
I knew that it was you by the pajama pants.
- You still must be sleepy. - These aren't pajama pants.
- I'm totally awake. - One of them is the Hunter.
- One of them has to be the Hunter. - It's either Yoon A or Jung Seok.
- One of them is the Hunter. - This is crazy.
- One of them must be the Hunter. - Definitely.
You will find three lights in front of the Hunter's door.
When the Hunters complete the secret missions during the race,
the lights will come on one at a time.
And when all three lights are turned on,
the Hunters can escape through the Door.
(They must complete 3 secret missions.)
The moment Hunters escape, the race will end.
And the members who failed to escape will face the penalty.
Hunters? I see. We need to stop them from getting out.
However,
the Hunters can only complete hidden missions when they obtain...
specific numbers the staff selected randomly.
The Hunters have already chosen 3 missions out of the10.
I will give you this list.
Remember these missions when you observe other members later.
You'll let us know what the missions are in advance?
- What is that? - Out of these missions,
- You'll show us the missions? - there are three.
- Secret missions. - "Order and eat jjajangmyeon."
- "Take someone's drink and burp." - "10-second eye contact".
- "Get furiously mad." - They chose 3 of these 10 missions.
- They did? - They were randomly chosen.
- They were random. - "Steal someone's..."
"Do the signature dance of the song, 'Gee'." That's too much.
"Put your hand on someone's shoulder for over five seconds."
- Did you start, Seok Jin? - No, no.
- Wait, but you just did. - No, no.
- He just started the mission. - I was just trying it out.
- Hold on. He started. - He did.
I was just trying it out.
- He just did the mission. - I didn't!
- "Get furiously mad." - "Get furiously mad."
He just did that.
(It's obvious that he's furiously mad.)
- No. - What was that?
- He just did the mission. - You want to finish them now?
Wait, "Change into different pants."
- Didn't Kwang Soo already do that? - No, I didn't.
I didn't change.
Anyway, the missions were chosen randomly.
- Two Hunters chose them randomly. - They were randomly chosen.
- What's that? - What?
I see. The cards are here.
I see. We have to draw the cards here.
We can't show the cards, right?
Right.
I'm sure there will be hints for us...
to figure out what kind of cards other people have, right?
But where are Jae Seok and Yoon A?
Are they the Hunters?
- Isn't that too obvious? - It must be those two.
- Are they getting the missions now? - It could be Yoon A.
- They are late. - I bet they'll come together.
There's a reason for being late.
- Did you get the missions or what? - Did you get the missions?
- Okay. - He's acting.
- Okay. - We'll play along.
It's about time you do a special episode.
Oh, boy.
(Oh, boy.)
"Oh, boy"? Okay.
It's been so long I heard someone say that.
That usually comes up in books, you know?
- Oh, boy. - "Oh, dear."
- Oh, dear. Oh, boy. - Oh, dear.
- Yoon A. - Yoon A.
Did you understand the missions?
- You're not confused anymore. - What?
- Okay. - It's better with explanations.
(Do they really have secret missions?)
Draw one card, show it to them, and put it on your back.
(Jong Kook's back number is 5.)
(His back number is 5. And his numbers are 21 and 32.)
(All 10 of them drew 3 cards.)
All right, everyone.
We'll choose the number for the Hunters now.
The Hunters can complete their missions...
only when they have this number.
(The Hunters can start the mission when they have the number.)
We will randomly draw this number.
If the Hunters have this number, they can start.
If they don't have the number, they must do their best to get it...
for their mission,
- so you must win the games. - Look for who wants to get this.
I'll draw the number now.
(However, only the Hunters will know this number via text message.)
All right. This is the number.
(The number in the tens place won't be revealed.)
(If the Hunters have this number, they can start right away.)
(They have number cards which have 3 in the tens place.)
I will send the Hunters this number through text messages.
If the Hunters have this number, they can start right away.
- But if they don't have it... - I see. The number he just drew...
If they try to do the missions, it means they already have it.
For example, something like this.
- Did you start? - No, no.
- I was giving you an example. - Did you just start?
Hey.
You've never put your hand on my shoulder.
My gosh, he put his hand on my shoulder.
(Getting close)
What are you looking at?
What happened?
(Jae Seok stares at him without trying to hide it.)
(Have eye contact with a member for longer than 10 seconds.)
(What do you take me for?)
Why are you staring at me?
- Jae Seok surprised me. - How dare you stare at me?
(I can stare at whomever I want.)
- How dare you stare at me? - He wants to do it for 10 seconds.
- He wants to do it for 10 seconds. - 1, 2...
(I want to do that too. Counting...)
- Stop it! - 5, 6, 7...
- I didn't look at him. - I think it's him.
Why is your face so red?
I didn't stare at him. I didn't.
All right. As for your first mission,
you will divide into 2 teams of 5.
The first place member of each team will get to switch cards.
(It means selection of the teams is very important.)
I have to get the Exchange Card.
Since the members of your team will play an important role,
the winner of a preliminary mission...
will have a chance to choose his or her team.
Everyone is beatable except for Jong Kook.
They are about the same.
The preliminary mission is an upgraded version of Race of Wits.
It's Upgraded Race of Witty Answers.
- What's that? - Race of Witty Answers?
You will listen to the question provided by the staff.
And whoever gets up first will answer...
the question in two syllables.
If you can ask a question in five seconds, it means you've passed.
The next person will answer in three syllables and ask a question.
And the next person will answer in four syllables.
- It's got upgraded again. - And you can ask a question then.
- We have to ask questions? - You must answer and ask.
(If two people answer at the same time,)
(or if they fail to ask a question in 5 seconds, they lose.)
Even this short game is hard.
(Since it's their first time, it might be hard.)
- Okay. - All right. Here we go.
You'll learn as you play Upgraded Race of Witty Answers.
- This is hard. - Here we go.
Go.
What term of endearment do you call your significant other with?
Honey.
(Two syllables)
You must ask a question right away.
What's your mother's name?
- Jung Ran. - My gosh.
Okay. You're out.
What's your mother's name?
(Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Haha get up at the same time.)
(3 of them are eliminated with just 1 question.)
You're out.
- Darn it. - Okay, you're out.
I said my mom's name.
- I said my mom's name. - Darn it.
I guess fools are somehow connected.
Why didn't you get up? Seriously.
- Why didn't you get up? - Why didn't you get up?
No. I'm not a fool.
Ready, set, go.
What's the title of your favorite song? Two syllables.
- "Soaring". - Ask them a question.
What's the tastiest fruit?
- Banana. - Darn it.
- Gosh, this is hard. - Name one memorable film.
"Titanic".
(Even Jung Seok is good.)
What's your favorite English song?
Four syllables.
(The members don't know much about British and American culture.)
My gosh, good job.
"Yesterday".
"Yesterday". It works.
(Gosh, I approve.)
I did it.
(Feeling proud)
- Do I ask a question now? - 5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
- Your time is up. - Go.
(He's out as 5 seconds are up.)
- What was that? - I got it.
- What was that? - You have to ask a question.
- What was that? - Wait.
Go.
You were supposed to ask a question.
It's hard to think of a question.
My goodness. Come on.
- Gosh. - Ready,
set, go.
What's your charm?
Eyebrows.
Come on. That's a lie. That's not true.
What's your favorite food?
- Favorite food. - Tangsuyuk.
What was the most entertaining book you read?
(A four-syllable title?)
No one can get up. Ji Hyo can't get up.
She can't ever get up.
(Gosh, books...)
- "Madam Gurie". - "Madam Gurie"?
I meant, "Madam Curie".
"Madam Gurie".
(What? "Madam Gurie"? Not, Madam Curie"?)
(The Nobel Prize recipient becomes oats which are good for dieting.)
- Isn't that "Madam Curie"? - What kind of book is that?
- What kind of book is that? - Why Madam Gurie?
Ji Hyo.
- Gurie sounds like oats, the food. - What are you saying?
What do you mean by Madam Gurie?
- I was thinking, Madam Curie. - Hey.
You're unbelievable.
Did she only grow oats all her life?
I was in a rush.
(Was her common knowledge that shallow?)
I'm sorry. Sir.
Was there a video that goes by, "Madam Gurie"?
No.
- There's none? - Come on. Ji Hyo.
That was funny. "Madam Gurie".
All right. This is how you play this game.
- Okay. - Okay. Great.
Here we go. Get ready.
I'm going to get up no matter what. Consider yourselves informed.
All right. Go.
What's the most upsetting thing you've heard in your life?
Idiot.
Who is your favorite actor?
- Yu Jae Seok. - Jeon So Min.
(Three syllables)
(They answer at the same time.)
Okay, okay.
Come on. Why do we keep ending up together?
- This is driving me crazy. - It's always you and me.
- Why does this happen? - I have no idea.
Ready,
set, go.
What do you want to be in your next life?
(What do you want to be in your next life?)
Dino.
(She dreams of becoming a dinosaur.)
You want to be a dinosaur?
A dinosaur?
That's two syllables.
Why didn't you say "gino" instead?
(Why didn't you say "gino" instead?)
Whom do you want to see the most right now?
My mother.
What do you want to say to your loved one?
(What do you want to say to your loved one?)
I love you.
- What? - I love you.
What's a foreign destination you want to go right now?
Croatia.
What?
(Five syllables)
(What did you say?)
- Croatia. - Croatia.
- Hurry up. - Ask your question.
How do you address your lover?
Time's over.
(His 5 seconds are up.)
- What? - It took too long.
Yoon A...
- You failed. - She asked once again!
- You failed. - I pronounced it clearly.
(His answer was audible.)
- Hey. - What was wrong...
- with my pronunciation? - You can't waste any time.
- You failed. - You failed.
- You failed. - What was wrong?
You failed.
- Nightingale! - Night...
(Jong Kook and Jung Seok talk simultaneously.)
What are you afraid of?
(They stand up together.)
They failed.
What did you do?
I was just about to say, "ghost."
But she stood up.
All right.
Let's go!
- This is doable! - Let's do it!
- This is doable! - Let's go!
I'm going to win.
- Okay. - I know for sure.
If two people fail this round, the last one is the winner, right?
- Right. - Okay, let's go.
All right.
Ready,
set, go.
What do you say to seduce the opposite gender?
Okay!
(So Min and Jae Seok fail so easily.)
I didn't say anything.
(They were doing so well.)
(The final winner arises.)
Gosh, Seok Jin.
Okay!
I won.
The winner of this game is Seok Jin.
(He has the right to choose the teams.)
Now, you can pick 2 teams of 5...
- however you want. - Okay.
He won't pick me.
Here's your mission.
Your first mission which will give you hints about your numbers
and grant you an Exchange Card...
is Drink to Live.
(Drink to Live)
There will be one less drink on the round table...
than the members participating.
Go around the table and dance to the music.
You win if you can down a drink each...
to the sound of the whistle.
However,
one of the drinks is salted sikhye.
Oh, no.
If you can't down it and smile,
you will lose.
There's also a special stage.
You can take turns dancing there.
If you down...
the sikhye, you will pass.
The better you dance, the more advantage you'll gain.
We need to form a competent team, right?
Okay.
Who can drink well?
I'm good at that.
- It's me. - Kwang Soo.
Okay!
(I'm good at drinking.)
- So Min is good at dancing. - Okay!
I'm good at dancing!
Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - Okay.
I'm good at drinking.
I am.
This is a team?
No, they will be competing against you.
- They're your rivals. - We're going against each other.
(Shocked)
Hold on. We're not a team?
I told you.
- They're your rivals. - He didn't understand properly!
(They're happy.)
(He ended up forming the most formidable team.)
I didn't get why you looked so happy.
What are you saying?
You told me to choose my team.
I told you to choose the members you'll go against.
Members I'll go against?
You, you, you, you didn't get it again!
Wait, we're going against each other?
What have I done?
This is irritating.
Pick your last member.
- Ji Hyo. - Okay.
(He picks Ji Hyo.)
You're a team.
(Team members)
My gosh.
I picked all the wrong ones.
Hold on. Why are there only three cups?
- There's 1 over there. - There are 4 in total.
The one who doesn't drink fails.
If you drink the salted sikhye...
- We just hold it in, right? - If you don't smile...
or finish it, you fail.
Seeing how big the cup is,
they must've added a lot of salt.
- Yes, it looks very salty. - My gosh.
Here we go.
- Let's go! - Do we walk around?
It's techno music.
(Dancing)
I bet Seok Jin will fail.
(He dances like a loser.)
So Min, go to the center.
(She goes to the front...)
(and shows off her patented dance.)
(Shaking)
(He can't bear to watch her.)
(Next up is the giraffe.)
(Swinging)
I'm sick of that dance.
Try a new move.
(Get out of my way.)
(It's Gurie time.)
- Hey. - You have a certain vibe.
It's Madam Gurie!
You have a certain vibe.
(Gurie shake)
It's Madam Gurie!
(She can't lose to her.)
What is that?
Gosh, So Min.
(She's mimicking something.)
(She shakes her legs.)
Look.
It's that dance, right?
It's the crab dance.
(Is she a Hunter doing her mission?)
That's not true. Oh, no.
(Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, and Ji Hyo get to drink.)
Oh, no.
I'll drink this.
(She drinks the sweet sikhye.)
Were we allowed to drink that?
Seok Jin, you're out.
What?
Who got the salted one?
(Which one of them drank the salted sikhye?)
You need to smile.
One of them drank the salted one, right?
It's not me.
(It's 1 of these 2.)
I bet it's Gurie.
Ji Hyo has a strange face.
(Jong Kook downs it and smiles.)
- What? - Who was it?
(They both finish their drinks and smile.)
Everyone except Seok Jin succeeds.
- Who drank it? - It was you, right?
No, it wasn't me.
- It wasn't you? - It wasn't me either.
It's you! You smell of salt!
It was you!
(He's caught because of the salty smell.)
Gosh, that stinks!
Was this the salted one?
- It was. - Right.
He smells like salted dry fish.
(The taste disgusts him.)
- He endured that? - It's completely salt.
It's okay. We need sodium during the summer.
(He's laidback.)
My gosh.
(Terrified)
You guys all lost.
He's amazing.
Does this mean Seok Jin won the previous game for nothing?
For nothing?
Is it over?
He formed a team and left the team himself.
- He did. - How great.
I can't believe him.
He's like Bruce Willis in "Armageddon".
Let's move onto round two.
Please play the music.
(4 of them remain.)
(It's "Gee".)
Let's go!
(She anticipates their dances.)
(Squirming)
(All focus is on So Min.)
I can't bear to watch her.
I hate it when she does that!
(She approaches the stage.)
(After approaching the stage...)
I hate those things!
(If you can't prevent it, enjoy it.)
(Take this.)
(She acts cute.)
- Does she think she's an idol? - She's good.
I thought those were the original dance moves.
[VIU Ver] SBS E460 Running Man
"Escaping Disaster"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(She does the crab dance.)
Hold on.
(Wait a minute.)
It's a mission.
(Did she just do her mission?)
No, it's not me.
This is the dance.
Wasn't that your mission?
Am I right?
(The whistle is blown.)
So Min succeeds again.
So Min was so passionate at dancing.
(So Min drinks the sweet sikhye.)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo drink the remaining two.)
(Trembling)
- It's Kwang Soo. - It is.
- It's him. - It's him.
It's Kwang Soo.
It's so obvious.
I don't think the salt melted properly.
Don't spit it out.
(He hates it.)
(He fails to finish it.)
It looks so salty.
It must be really salty.
Kwang Soo, you're not a professional.
What?
(What did you say?)
If I were you, I would've downed it.
Let's find out in five minutes.
It's impossible.
- How bad is it? - Is it that horrible?
- I drank it. - It's impossible.
- How bad is it? - Here's the last round.
- Is it that salty? - Hey!
- Stealing water. - Stealing water.
(Jong Kook suddenly steals Kwang Soo's water.)
The mission was to steal someone else's water.
He drank a lot of water already.
- He drank twice. - I just drank it. I swear.
Wasn't it stealing someone's soda?
I remember it being "soda".
Why are you drinking again?
(Everyone is suspicious of him.)
(Gulping)
- What's wrong with you? - Why are you drinking it?
You're drinking it because you stole it from Jong Kook.
- What? - What?
(He steals the water back from Jong Kook.)
(He chokes.)
You're right.
- Right? - Yes.
(I was sharp, wasn't I?)
Try drinking salted sikhye then.
(Kwang Soo is upset.)
Try it,
and let's see if you drink water afterward or not.
We keep craving water.
We can't help but drink it.
That was a sharp observation.
Let's find out.
Let's move onto the next round. If it's okay with you,
if the person who drank the salted sikhye can endure it,
the one who didn't drink it will fail.
- Okay. - That's good.
(Endure the saltiness and you win.)
It must be that strong.
- It really must be. - I like that.
Here we go.
Please play the music.
Let's go.
(This song this time is "Mr. Chu".)
It's "Mr. Chu" by Apink.
(Madam Gurie steps up first.)
(This is Gurie's chu.)
(They sing along.)
(It's as if Apink is here.)
(Dancing)
Her dance moves are accurate, but she's dancing halfheartedly.
That's how our mothers dance.
This is Madam Gurie's style.
All her moves were correct.
- That's right. - It's Madam Gurie's style.
- But it looks halfhearted. - Come on.
At least, I'm still dancing.
(The fake idol member steals the stage.)
I hate it when she does that.
My gosh.
She's just too much.
(Madam Gurie and fake idol member)
My gosh.
(Who will be the final winner?)
- We don't know who will win. - They just need to endure it.
We don't know who will win yet.
(If you endure the saltiness, you can win.)
- It must be So Min. - I have no clue.
You guys are incredible.
Who got the salted sikhye?
- It's So Min. - I think it's Ji Hyo.
- It's So Min. - You need to smile.
It's So Min. She can't finish it.
She's done.
It the salted sikhye if you need to pat it.
This is incredible.
She's crying.
(I sometimes cry.)
(Smiling?)
This isn't that type of a game.
Why is she doing that?
She's sad.
This is true sadness.
So Min wins.
I agree.
Let's get prepared for the next round.
This team...
is made of people who Seok Jin didn't pick.
- That's right. - What have I done?
We'll get started now.
You need to pick that cup.
That's the one to drink.
(Who will win this round?)
(It's "Genie" by Girls' Generation and the famous kicking dance.)
Jung Seok, you seem determined for this round.
(Taking one step at a time)
(Getting started)
Jung Seok...
is ready to win.
(Fancy move)
(Even Yoon A agrees that his dance is good.)
(Jae Seok tries to take over the mat.)
Don't be greedy.
(Kicks him out)
(Get out of my way, grandpa!)
(Kicking)
(Get out of my way.)
(Now it just seems like everyone is kicking each other.)
That's pretty funny.
(Exhausted from getting kicked)
There she goes.
She's the real one.
(Seductive)
She's so cool.
When are you going to stop dancing?
The original is different.
She's so good.
(This is not good.)
(Barges onto the stage)
(A disaster)
(Kicking each other in the butt again)
(Kicking is the trend.)
- They're hilarious. - It's funny.
(Their team is a disaster too.)
My butt hurts.
It hurts so much!
(Blow the whistle already!)
(I'm not just going to let others take my spotlight.)
(The sikhye is mine.)
Come on.
No!
It's spilling over.
(The winner of the sweet sikhye...)
(is Yoon A the dancing queen.)
(Jung Seok, Jae Seok, and Se Chan took the leftover cups.)
(Which one took the salty sikhye?)
What a merciless team.
Who is it?
It's Jae Seok!
It's him.
(Chocking)
(Panicking)
- Just give up. - Just give up.
- Two. - It's Jae Seok.
- One. - Jae Seok?
(Spits out the drink)
(He wasn't professional enough to drink the salty sikhye. He's out.)
- I can't win with my dancing. - You have to dance full-out.
The next round begins now.
(It's a song by TWICE.)
I'm not good at dancing to cute songs like this.
(Then get out of my way.)
Wait.
(She's the expert of cute dances.)
(Yoon A takes over the stage again.)
It's my turn!
- Why are you dancing? - How can we dance?
I can't dance with her taking over the stage.
(Yoon A's never-ending solo)
How can I dance when Yoon A is always taking over the stage?
(Hey!)
(It's my turn, Yoon A.)
(Let me have my turn too.)
(What are they doing?)
- Se Chan, get out of the way. - Get out.
(He's not getting off the stage anytime soon.)
(Copy me if you can.)
Come on.
(Challenge accepted.)
Jung Seok, what a funny guy.
(The whistle blows)
Yoon A.
(There are two cups left on the other table.)
- You still have a chance. - There's one behind you.
Yours might be the sweet one.
I don't have a good feeling about this.
There are three left.
(Which one will be the unfortunate loser?)
(Spits out the drink)
(Screaming in agony)
You were the first one to grab the drink too.
There's no way you can drink that.
(I survived.)
Yours wasn't salty?
(Unlucky Se Chan fails.)
It's way too salty.
Those two are so good.
They're the last two standing.
- They're survivors. - It's their first time playing.
They're really good.
They're also both great dancers.
There's no way of interrupting them.
The last round is the same.
If you can finish the salty sikhye, you survive.
I don't think I can.
- Me neither. - I don't think so.
(This round, the song is "Gotta Go" by Chungha.)
It's Chungha's song.
(Dancing with so much energy)
She's so good.
Impressive.
She's really good.
(There's no way I can win.)
What's he doing?
(What is Jung Seok doing on the floor?)
(Taking something out)
What?
(Here you go.)
(Here comes Heart Jung Seok.)
(Gummy, are you watching?)
(Heart Jung Seok is stealing Yoon A's spotlight with his heart.)
That was good.
- So good. - You're doing great.
You're doing great.
Do it together.
(Nobody can predict who will be the final winner at this point.)
(Whistle blows)
At this point, whoever can stand the salty sikhye wins.
The final round.
(One of them are drinking salty sikhye.)
(Drink the salty one and you win.)
One of them has salty sikhye.
Which one of you is it?
Is this real?
- That's impressive. - Which one is it?
(Who's drinking the salty sikhye?)
(I can't drink it anymore.)
(Flinches)
(He surrenders to the salty sikhye.)
(It was Jung Seok.)
It's impossible to drink.
So,
the winners of each round...
are So Min and Yoon A.
(The winners of the first mission are So Min and Yoon A.)
- Great. - You're really a great dancer.
I have a chance now.
So Min and Yoon A...
can switch cards with a member of your choice.
Choose a member that you want to switch cards with...
and choose one of their cards to switch after looking at them.
That gives so much leverage.
(They get to see before they choose.)
(Who will So Min choose?)
I pick Dong Hoon.
(So Min is choosing to switch with Haha.)
(So Min currently has 22, 30 and 8.)
(So Min can either choose to switch a card with Haha or leave as is.)
It was worth the salty sikhye.
- I made the right choice. - Please show So Min your cards.
(Let's see.)
My cards are amazing.
My numbers are amazing. I can exit right now.
(Haha has 2 cards in the 30s.)
(The Hunter's ball was also in the 30s.)
(What if all the weird things he did were for the Hunter's missions?)
(If Haha is a Hunter, he could lose a card in the 30s.)
Choose one to take and another to give.
- Don't do it. - Of course, I will.
- Of course, I will. - Don't do it.
- Do I switch the cards now? - Yes, you can switch now.
- Don't do it. - Give me 38.
(Give me 38.)
(So Min chose to switch cards with Haha.)
- Show the card you're giving me. - This one.
- And here you go. - Darn it.
(So Min gave her 22 for Haha's 38.)
How good is the card?
I'm going to win today for sure.
(So Min took Haha's biggest card, which was 38.)
(So Min already had a card in the 30s,)
(but during the mission, So Min also did weird stuff like the leg dance.)
(She's willing to cry to win.)
(If the Hunter's number is 30, could So Min be a Hunter?)
(Could she be a Hunter?)
They've switched now.
Yoon A is up next.
Okay.
Aren't my cards amazing?
I...
choose Jae Seok.
(I choose Jae Seok.)
(Yoon A currently has 35, 36 and 3.)
Jae Seok.
Yoon A is choosing to look at your cards.
Why are you doing this to me?
(Yoon A can choose to either switch cards or not.)
You're so mean.
(Let me see your cards.)
Seriously?
- Then I'm... - Will you switch or will you pass?
going to switch.
- You're switching? - Yes.
(Yoon A already has 2 cards in the 30s.)
(She came late today, which is why everyone thinks she's a Hunter.)
(Was it really because she was getting the Hunter's mission?)
(Yoon A chooses...)
- with the number on my back. - On your back?
Seriously?
Okay.
(Yoon A now has 35, 36 and 25.)
(If we add up all the 3 cards that Yoon A has,)
(she's the most likely one to be able to take the first exit.)
- The first round is now over. - Okay.
I'd be really shocked...
if the Hunters succeeded.
- I have no idea who it is. - Same.
(Did the Hunters succeed with their secret missions?)
What are these? People and situations?
Everyone, the second round will begin shortly.
Before that, I have an announcement.
There's a red light on the Hunter's door.
- The Hunters succeeded. - Did they?
(One of the Hunters succeeded in doing their secret mission.)
(Could it have been 1 of these 3?)
But the Hunters wouldn't have been able to do all the things we did.
Everyone drank water and put their hands on others' shoulders.
- I think... - Here's what happened.
A Hunter...
(The light only comes on when a Hunter clears a secret mission.)
(Which mission did the Hunter execute?)
One of the Hunters succeeded in secretly stealing...
something from a member.
- Steal? - They stole someone's belonging?
Did anyone lose anything?
(Before filming, during the Hunters meeting)
(Hunters chose...)
(three secret missions.)
(Change into a different pair of pants.)
(Steal one of the members' belongings.)
(These missions are all so difficult.)
(A Hunter stole someone's belongings.)
- Who is it? - I didn't lose anything.
Me neither.
- I didn't lose anything. - We don't have a lot of items.
What did you steal?
(What did you steal?)
What are you talking about?
What did he steal?
The second mission for card switching is...
- Action School. - What is that?
What's Action School?
It's a game played in pairs.
One person chooses a situation and a person without looking.
The other person acts out the words.
You're given three minutes to say the correct answer.
If the player gives the wrong answer,
shoot the player with your water gun without hesitation.
(Give the wrong answer, and you'll be shot with a water gun.)
Two teams with the most correct answers will be rewarded.
Second place is good too.
Now it's time to decide teams.
Your partner is important.
I'm good at guessing.
Draw one.
(Team Results)
Ready, and...
(Jong Kook picks two cards.)
All right.
(What?)
Is it even possible to act out those words?
(Jong Kook picked...)
("Talking back" and "Principal".)
(The player has to act out the words almost without talking.)
This is impossible. No way.
What?
(Panicking)
(He starts acting.)
(Testing the microphone)
That's clever.
(He is mimicking a principal making a speech.)
A microphone.
(I'm describing a person.)
A principal.
(Correct)
(Thanks to Se Chan's clever mime, Jong Kook gets the person right.)
(Se Chan has to mime "talking back" now.)
(Hilarious)
(Miming)
A complaining principal?
(You're getting close.)
- Gosh. - A principal picking a fight?
A frustrated principal?
(Se Chan is using his whole body.)
(I hate this. What? Do you have a problem?)
(It's something like this.)
Something like this.
Giving an excuse? What should I say?
I'm not allowed?
(Se Chan catches a chance.)
(He is literally talking back.)
- A rebelling principal? - Do you think I'm rebelling?
(He keeps talking back.)
- A principal acting up? - Am I acting up?
- That's brilliant. - I'm not acting up.
You say this to me all the time!
A lecturing principal?
I wasn't lecturing!
(He talks back again.)
This is the answer!
(It really is the answer.)
Well...
(Time's up.)
Jong Kook, "Talking back".
(Jong Kook and Se Chan fail.)
Hold on.
In this case...
- He's scolding Se Chan. - Look.
All right. "Talking".
You should have done this.
Then I would have known.
Otherwise, it's too hard.
It was difficult.
It's not easy.
It's too hard.
Why don't we say this was just practice?
- Good. - All right.
It's hard.
- All right. - Okay.
This is how you play.
You can return them.
- Okay, let's do this. - Jae Seok.
You act out the words.
I'm going to get them soaking wet.
I'm going to kill them.
- I'll take revenge. - Definitely.
Someone kept shooting me even after the game was over.
- And I saw who it was. - Kwang Soo.
(I saw who it was.)
(Surprised)
Seriously...
I'll...
I'll soak him completely.
(Indoor heavy rain warning)
This is...
(Jong Kook warns Kwang Soo that he'll take revenge.)
Please pick good cards.
I'll just go with my gut.
(What are the words for Jae Seok and Jung Seok?)
("Running into your first love on the street", "Shaman")
That's good. It's easy.
- Ready, and... - Start with this one.
Start with the person.
(He starts with exorcism.)
A psychic?
Three syllables.
(Let me splash some water on you.)
A shaman.
(Now it's time to get the situation right.)
A shaman...
(He is walking on the street.)
- Wait. - You ran into someone you know.
- Did we go to the same high school? - A shaman...
A shaman ran into his high school friend.
"Did we go to the same school?"
"Are you my high school first love?"
("High school first love" and "shaman")
(He just needs to combine the words right.)
(That's right.)
- He might get it right. - He'll get it right.
(Will Jae Seok get it right?)
"Did we go to high school together?"
(Jae Seok is too focused on high school.)
(He ends up acting instead of answering.)
I mean... Look.
Where am I right now?
You ran into your high school first love on the street.
A shaman's first love who he ran into on the street.
Say the person and the situation.
- A shaman's... - No.
A shaman is the person.
A shaman you ran into on the street who is your first love.
(Let me try.)
(Your first love has become a shaman.)
- What is that? - What are you talking about?
Gosh, this is frustrating.
- Why did you do that? - Is it really wrong?
It was almost correct.
You ran into your first love, and she became a shaman.
My first love became a shaman.
(Team Jae Seok fails because of Jae Seok's imagination.)
- Shall we give it a go? - Okay.
All right.
It's not easy.
- It's hard. - One correct answer is enough.
Ready, and...
- Knock, knock. - Knock, knock.
- Hello. - Greeting.
Keep watching. Hello.
Let me start.
(Auditioning)
- Auditioning. - Don't look for me
- An occupation. - An occupation?
An idol.
- An idol auditioning... - I mean...
I'm sorry. I'll do better next time.
- Bye. - An idol who failed an audition.
An idol failed an audition?
(Is that right?)
(Seok Jin says the wrong answer while making sure it's right.)
Next.
(Trumpeting)
No!
(She relies on...)
(onomatopoeia.)
(A performing elephant...)
(disciplined by the circus leader)
An elephant...
who failed an audition.
No. Try again.
(So Min succeeded in describing an elephant.)
A zookeeper who failed an audition.
No. Look.
(So Min switches to acrobatics.)
Someone failed an audition.
Uncle Tong.
(Uncle Tong appears in So Min's circus.)
- Uncle Tong. - No.
So Min, what happened to your hair?
(Her wet hair makes her look like...)
She looks like The Undertaker.
The Undertaker.
- Is this right? - Yes.
Gosh.
(Time's up.)
This one was right.
(Seok Jin and So Min got nothing right.)
- Just one... - That was close.
You just have to get one right.
- Who's next? - Kwang Soo.
(It's Kwang Soo and Yoon A's turn.)
I should fill up my water gun again.
- Fill it up, please. - Fill it up, please.
No.
Can I get another water gun?
- We almost got it right. - Give me one more water gun.
Unbelievable.
Jong Kook has two water guns.
It's Kwang Soo's turn.
(Because I love him so much.)
I got two water guns for him.
Aim at his shoes.
Get just one right, and you'll win.
Let's do this!
- Let's get just one right. - Let's do this.
You won't be able to see anything. There's no way you'll get it right.
(Try your best.)
(With Jong Kook's warning, Kwang Soo and Yoon A start.)
Ready,
and...
(What are the words for Kwang Soo and Yoon A?)
That's too easy.
Unbelievable.
This is the easiest so far.
(It's easier because it's only one word each.)
Food.
Rice.
Side dishes. Soup.
You should eat a balanced diet.
Say something.
- Side dishes. Soup. - Say something.
This food is good for you.
- Eat this too. - A chef?
(He finally says the wrong answer.)
(The shooting starts.)
(As warned, Jong Kook pours water on Kwang Soo so that he can't see.)
- Baek Jong Won! - It's...
A cook.
(He's getting close.)
(Regional heavy rain warning)
No one is shooting Yoon A though.
(No one is shooting Yoon A though.)
- I can't... - Wait.
Keep going.
I'm eating this, this, and this.
But I don't want to eat this.
- She's talking too much. - You can't talk.
- You talked too much. - Did I?
(We failed?)
(You're allowed to say only the necessary things.)
Try again.
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
"Try again"?
(They pick a new pair of cards and try again.)
Yoon A is so funny.
Ready.
(They switch places.)
(What are the new words?)
- That's hard. - That's hard.
(Eating rice with ramyeon, A mother-in-law)
(Wedding march)
- Marriage. - "Marriage". Okay.
(Screaming)
(The water guns make her scream.)
Yoon A, look at me!
Come over here!
- You come here! - Look at me!
- Come here! - You have to look at me!
- No! - Yoon A!
Be careful.
- A microphone. - No.
Ramyeon.
- Ramyeon. - Well...
- Can I see the cards again? - Sorry.
(Can I see the cards again?)
(Yoon A hasn't recovered from the water guns.)
It's hot?
(It's time to describe rice.)
- Cooking starts - What?
(He sings the song from the rice cooker commercial.)
A fool!
(Yoon A says what she sees.)
A fool eating alone.
(Yoon A hurts Kwang Soo without meaning to.)
Have another bite.
- This... - Ramyeon.
- Gosh. - It's ramyeon.
I'm not full yet.
What should I do?
(I'm not full yet. It means he wants rice.)
My ramyeon is finished.
(It means it's time for rice.)
(If you've ever eaten ramyeon, you understand what he means.)
What? Rice in ramyeon?
(Time's up.)
It was too hard.
(Kwang Soo and Yoon A didn't get any right.)
It's hard to describe a mother-in-law.
All right.
I'll take off my shoes.
- He's smart. - He's well prepared.
I'm sure I'll get soaked.
- Ready. - Okay!
And...
(Panicking over a clogged toilet, Good-for-nothing)
That's easy.
(Se Chan starts describing a clogged toilet.)
(Gushing)
(Shocked)
This.
Jong Kook isn't saying anything to avoid getting sprayed.
- He isn't saying anything. - He isn't saying anything.
(You!)
(Me!)
(Se Chan means Jong Kook is a good-for-nothing.)
(He gets his point across.)
Kim Jong Kook with an overflowing toilet?
(They stand up and shoot with their water guns.)
Stop it. Stop it.
What about the toilet?
Stop it.
(What is he doing?)
(Those are the shoes Jong Kook took off.)
He is shooting at Jong Kook's shoes.
(He changed the target.)
(I will make sure they are soggy even after the game.)
Look at me! Look at me!
- Surprised? - It's something like that.
(It's hard to describe "Panicking".)
A clogged toilet.
(They shoot without stopping.)
Is this a water bomb festival?
Seriously.
So the toilet is clogged. Explain the rest!
Look at me.
What about the clogged toilet, you jerk?
(He gets annoyed since he isn't close to the answer.)
This is it.
What is this?
Panicking.
Kim Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook who is panicking over a clogged toilet)
A good-for-nothing.
(A good-for-nothing who is panicking over a clogged toilet)
- Correct. - Is that correct?
Seeing Se Chan point at him,
he understood "good-for-nothing".
(He agrees he's a "good-for-nothing" of Running Man.)
He did a good job.
We need two minutes.
The microphones aren't working properly.
(They get their microphones fixed.)
Did someone shoot water in my shoes?
(This is strange.)
(Startled)
(Kwang Soo acts like he doesn't know anything.)
(You did this.)
Okay. I got it.
(What? Me?)
My shoes are very wet.
(It's all thanks to Kwang Soo.)
(I did my best.)
Seriously. Okay.
(At that moment)
(Looking around)
(He looks around before he leaves the studio.)
You prepared two pairs of jeans, right?
(Jung Seok suddenly looks for a pair of jeans.)
(One of the secret missions the Hunters need to carry out is...)
("Change into different pants.")
That's one of the secret missions.
My goodness.
- All right. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Jung Seok returns to his seat.)
- Jung Seok. - My goodness.
The microphone.
(On his pants,)
(the wet spots have changed.)
- Get ready. - Let's go.
Set, go.
- Okay. - Jung Seok,
you are a Hunter of this race.
(The first Hunter, Cho Jung Seok)
This is my third visit to the show.
If I do something I haven't done before,
they will know.
We are almost there.
(This Hunter completed a hidden mission with ease.)
(During the game,)
(he shoots the water at his own pants.)
(He is daring and meticulous beyond expectations.)
I have an announcement to make.
At this point...
- What? - Did someone complete a mission?
Did someone complete a mission?
If a Hunter has the Hunter's number,
they will be attempting their secret missions.
- That's right. - Really?
If a Hunter doesn't have the Hunter's number,
completing a mission is meaningless.
(The mission is pointless.)
(The secret mission doesn't count without the number.)
(Thus, "Change into different pants" didn't count.)
What does that mean? It's a message to the Hunters.
- Right? - I guess a Hunter did a mission...
- without the Hunter's number. - It seems that way.
Who is it? It must be one of the fools.
You are right. This Hunter is a fool.
A foolish Hunter.
All right. Which team will go next?
Since you don't have...
the Hunter's number yet, doing the missions is meaningless.
Why do you keep saying I'm a Hunter? For goodness' sake.
Let's go.
Kwang Soo thinks I am a Hunter.
(He wishes he wasn't a Hunter.)
Get ready.
(Haha and Ji Hyo are up for the last game.)
(Awake and late for school, Middle school girl)
I want to go to high school.
When will I attend high school?
A middle school student.
A middle school student. A girl?
Combine.
(Combine the two!)
A middle school girl.
She woke up but is late.
She is late.
A middle school girl who up and is late.
Haha.
(They fail because they didn't get the "For school" part.)
Okay.
She is late for school.
Thus, the first place goes...
- to Team Jong Kook and Se Chan. - Okay.
Okay.
The second place goes to Team Haha and Ji Hyo.
(Haha and Ji Hyo came close to the answer.)
(It's time to switch cards.)
One at a time.
Either Jong Kook or Se Chan should come forward first.
It's meaningless unless you come in first.
You can't escape.
I will exchange my card with Yoon A's card.
- Yoon A? - Yes.
Se Chan chose Yoon A.
- What? - All right.
You must need the number on Yoon A's back.
What?
Does he need the number on Yoon A's back?
- Is this what you want? - You need to give that to him.
- This one? - Yes.
Is this the right number?
(Se Chan took 35 from Yoon A.)
(If Yoon A is a Hunter, did she lose the Hunter's number?)
I am done.
You can go back to your seat.
I just need one card...
to exit.
I choose So Min.
(Jong Kook choose So Min.)
So Min, please come forward.
(A lot of people think So Min is a Hunter.)
It's not like that. I didn't know I could exit during all this.
- I should have exited. - I didn't know either.
Hold on.
- She didn't know? - So Min.
You aren't at a resort.
- Do you think... - You look like...
you are on a vacation at Haeundae.
So Min, what are you doing?
I am so upset.
I will exchange the number on my back...
- with this. - Then he will know everything.
I will exchange the number on my back with this.
Then he will know everything.
- Hurry up. - This is a disaster.
I won't be able to leave!
(Did So Min get the Hunter's number taken away?)
- This is incredible. - Okay.
I think I can exit right now with these numbers.
He must have 40.
(Jong Kook has 38, 21, and 32. Does anyone have a higher total?)
I wonder if anyone has a higher total.
I will take this one.
Okay.
(Ji Hyo exchanges her 4 with Jung Seok's 28.)
- Give it to her. - Okay.
This is driving me crazy.
- You can go back to your seats. - Let's go.
They are done.
Currently, there are five exits left.
The member with the biggest sum of the three cards.
The member with three consecutive numbers.
The member with 3 multiples of 5.
The member with 4 of the same number from the 3 cards.
The last exit is...
the Hunter's door.
(The members and Hunters must meet the conditions and escape.)
- Okay. - The Hunters must be anxious.
We can leave during the third round, right?
You can leave anytime.
Okay. I understood.
- Let's go. - Let me get changed first.
- Let's go. - No one is leaving, right?
I need to use the restroom.
(Everyone goes to get changed.)
I need to get changed.
(At that moment!)
(Exit 2, The member with 3 consecutive numbers)
All right.
(At Exit 2 is Yang Se Chan.)
(The numbers Se Chan has are...)
I have 33, 34...
(33, 34,)
(and 35.)
(He got 35 from Yoon A and made 3 consecutive numbers.)
I will go and enjoy the day.
(He goes out through Exit 2...)
(and becomes the first person to escape.)
(He enters Good Place.)
(Good Place)
(It's a luxurious place only the escapees can enjoy.)
My goodness.
(Food for the hungry stomach and services for the tired body)
Then... I can enjoy anything, right?
I can enjoy everything?
Really?
(The members who escaped don't need to pay.)
I will show you how much money I can spend.
I have an announcement to make before we start the race.
Se Chan...
Did he escape?
He used the exit that requires three consecutive numbers.
(The news of Se Chan's escape...)
(shocks everyone.)
- Did he escape? - Three consecutive numbers.
No way.
I thought he was going for 3 multiples of 5.
- Me too. - That exit is closed, right?
That's right. If you were going for three consecutive numbers,
you should find a different way.
(Exit 2 is closed.)
- I got goosebumps. - I can't believe it.
(He just needed to get 28.)
Se Chan is lucky these days.
For your information, the amount of money...
Se Chan purchased in this short period of time...
Why did he get this done? He got a basic manicure.
(Did he get a manicure?)
- What? - Why?
Did he get a manicure?
He got a facial massage and ordered the Korean beef special.
He also ordered a tiramisu. He used 156 dollars so far.
He is crazy.
(He used 156 dollars in 15 minutes.)
- I need to hurry up and escape. - He is crazy.
- What? 156 dollars? - He's spoiling himself.
Also,
Currently, two of the Hunter's lights have come on.
(Two of Hunter's lights came on.)
- When did they do the missions? - Seriously.
That Hunter...
changed his or her pants.
It was necessary.
- Hold on. - Everyone's pants were wet.
Everyone's pants were wet.
- Everyone changed except for you. - I didn't get changed.
That means I am not a Hunter. I am not a Hunter.
Jong Kook isn't a Hunter.
(Who is the other Hunter besides Jung Seok?)
Since a Hunter completed a mission, we will pick the number again.
If they succeed again, the Hunters will escape.
That's right. Then it will be the end.
I don't care about the Hunters. I am going to escape.
We will pick the ball again.
(The Hunter's number is 24.)
I will send the number via text message to the Hunters.
If you have the number, you can attempt the mission right away.
If you don't have the number, you need to work for it.
It all depends on how much you work for it.
The final mission that will help you to get cards and escape...
is the Card Escape Show.
Currently, four exits remain.
(Exit 2 has been closed.)
There are 1 to 4 number cards hidden...
throughout the building.
If you get the card you want,
you can exchange it with one of your cards.
(Exchange it with one of your cards.)
If you remove the name tag of a member,
you can check his or her cards and exchange one with yours.
If you don't like the choices, you can keep your cards.
- Okay. - My goodness.
Removing the name tag doesn't eliminate the member.
Said member can put it back on after the exchange.
If you think someone is a Hunter,
you can remove his or her name tag...
and check using the judging stand by the Hunter Door.
Who could be the Hunters?
If that person is a Hunter, he or she is out,
and the member who removed the name tag can escape.
If not, the member who removed the name tag is out...
and an additional light will come on at the Hunter's door.
(An additional light will come on at the Hunter's door.)
If one of the Hunters succeeds to escape...
or both Hunters are out, the race ends.
- Move to the location of the race. - Let's go.
Let's do this. Where do we need to go?
I think I have the biggest sum.
If I see the numbers on their backs, Haha's 17 is the highest.
(Haha's number is the highest at 17.)
Unless the rest of the numbers he has...
are above 30...
Yoon A has 22 on her back. I will remove her name tag...
and get 4 digits of 2.
Then I will go...
to the exit that requires four of the same number.
(He plans to escape with 4 of the same number.)
I wish I had a clue on the Hunters' identities.
(The members who can't meet the conditions for the exits...)
(aim to escape by removing a Hunter's name tag.)
I have no idea who the Hunters are.
Jeon So Min. So Min.
Where is So Min? She has to be a Hunter.
(Is So Min a Hunter?)
Who are the Hunters? I am suspicious of Yoon A.
(Did Yoon A come late because she received missions?)
Aren't the Hunters Yoon A and Jung Seok?
(Meanwhile, Hunter Jung Seok...)
Hold on.
(He needs to get 24 and complete the jjajangmyeon mission.)
Number 24.
(The Hunter's number is 24.)
The Hunter's number is 24,
but I don't know who has it.
I will have to remove everyone's name tag.
(Will the Hunters be able to get Jae Seok's 24?)
Let's begin the race.
(The members who are out or fail to escape...)
(must pay for the expenses at Good Place.)
(They must catch a Hunter or escape in order to avoid paying.)
(The race starts.)
Hold on.
(The Hunters gather as soon as the race starts.)
(How about we do this?)
(Let's call the manager and order jjajangmyeon.)
(How many jjajangmyeon should we order?)
(Just in case, let's order 5.)
(That's a good idea. If you get 24,)
(I will eat jjajangmyeon at the gate.)
(This Hunter will eat jjajangmyeon. What is this plan?)
I will give this a try.
I need to hurry up.
(He runs to the exit for the biggest sum.)
(He arrives at Exit 1.)
Please check my numbers. I will give this a try.
I have 38, 32, and 21.
Jong Kook, the sum of your numbers...
(Will Jong Kook be able to escape with the biggest sum?)
isn't the biggest.
(His 91 isn't the biggest sum.)
(I don't have the biggest sum?)
I am so annoyed.
You will be taken to the Bad Place right away.
Are you sure I don't have the biggest sum?
(Who has the biggest sum?)
(When Jong Kook was headed to the exit,)
Are you serious?
(Just a moment ago, Seok Jin ran into So Min.)
(Ripping)
(Seok Jin removed So Min's name tag.)
I got it.
(Seok Jin could check her numbers and make an exchange.)
Let's see your numbers.
I am sorry, So Min. I have a plan.
This one.
All right.
Now, the sum of my numbers is 101.
(The sum of Seok Jin's numbers is 101.)
Let's escape. I have the biggest sum.
Where is the exit? What is this?
(He was looking for the exit...)
(when he finds it right in front of him.)
(He is about to escape.)
Where are you going?
(Jae Seok comes out of nowhere.)
What? Why?
(He gets caught by Jae Seok in front of the exit.)
- Where are you going? - Why?
Are you going to escape?
No.
Don't be like that. I don't have anything you need.
I think you do.
I need a number.
Hold on. I need to escape with the biggest sum.
Hold on. I just need to exit...
through that door!
- Okay. - You leave me with no choice.
(Ripping)
(Jae Seok removed Seok Jin's name tag.)
You jerk!
(You jerk!)
All right. Show me your cards.
Give me this one.
Why would you take 40?
(Seok Jin is frustrated.)
(I am trying to keep you from escaping.)
You little...
Why would you take 40?
Why would you do that? For goodness' sake.
I will need to remove someone's name tag.
He took 40. For goodness' sake. I knew this would happen.
My goodness.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Where do I go? Here?
Yes. You have arrived at the Bad Place.
(There is a clear divider between them.)
What am I supposed to do here? Is this paradise and the underworld?
You can watch Se Chan enjoy Good Place.
For goodness' sake.
Why did you do that?
(Jong Kook, why did you do that?)
I told you not to do that.
(Se Chan feels bad for Jong Kook during the visit.)
You shouldn't have been so obsessed with the numbers.
I will give you some coffee. Come over here.
You should suck on some coffee.
Do you think I am in prison?
(Do you think I am in prison?)
Is there a smaller straw?
- What? - Is there a narrower straw?
(This is like "Prison Playbook".)
Are you seriously doing this?
Drink.
(He enjoys a sweet sip of coffee.)
Are you getting it?
(It's really tasty.)
- Is it good? - It's tasty.
It's tasty, right?
(He soothes his heart with the sweet coffee.)
I will be out soon.
(I will be out soon.)
- Make sure you come out. - I will be out soon.
- It's paradise over here. - Okay.
Don't hit anyone in there.
(Then you will get a heavier sentence.)
Hello.
Call a Chinese restaurant...
and order five jjajangmyeon.
(He asks his manager to order jjajangmyeon as planned.)
(He finishes ordering jjajangmyeon.)
(He just needs to find 24, the Hunter's number.)
Let's go.
(Kwang Soo is in search of Yoon A since she has 22.)
I need to find Yoon A. Yoon A.
Yoon A.
(What is that sound? I don't see Yoon A.)
It's the sound from the audio team.
Gosh, that startled me.
You can hear everything from here.
- I mean... - Why do you...
- It's not like that. - Come here.
- No. - Come here.
I don't hear Yoon A's voice.
Can you turn up the volume for Yoon A's voice?
Yoon A's voice. I didn't know about this.
Numbers 20, 21... Any numbers in the 20s will do.
"Any numbers in the 20s will do."
I need to get two numbers in the 20s.
(Kwang Soo gets an idea of Yoon A's numbers.)
She doesn't have any numbers with 2 besides 22.
What does Haha have?
"What does Haha have?"
She must have met Haha.
Thank you.
(Hey!)
(Yoon A appears before his eyes.)
- My goodness. - You are scary.
- Yoon A! - What?
I got goosebumps.
You were there just now. When did you...
- What? - Yoon A.
- Yoon A. - What is going on?
- Yoon A, I am sorry. - You are a Hunter, right?
- You are a Hunter, right? - What? I am not a Hunter.
- I heard that... - Okay.
you need 2 numbers with 2.
- Really? - Yes.
That must be the case with you.
So...
(Ji Hyo suddenly appears.)
What are you doing?
I am watching.
Ji Hyo,
two lions could lose a deer by fighting over it.
What are you saying?
You have somewhere else to be, right?
- I... - This is my last chance.
(This lion is desperate.)
If I don't get this number, I need to pay.
Both of you want to remove my name tag!
Go ahead.
(The desperate lion attacks the deer.)
(Will the deer become the lion's prey?)
I got it!
(Kwang Soo succeeded in removing Yoon A's name tag.)
So you removed my name tag. What do you want?
Give me the number on your back.
- The number on my back? - Yes.
What will you give me?
I will give you the number on my back.
(I will give you the number on my back.)
- The number on your back? - Yes.
For goodness' sake.
I don't know what it is, but I will give it to you.
- You are too much! - Give me your number.
What is it?
(Kwang Soo exchanges 1 with 22.)
Thank you. I will leave now.
I hope you escape safely.
There is something I am aiming for too.
(What is Yoon A aiming for?)
- Yoon A. - Yes?
Let me see your back.
- Gosh. - Let me see your back.
(They show each other the numbers on their backs.)
We don't want each other's number.
(Ji Hyo watches them.)
(They are the strong Hunter candidates.)
Jung Seok, who are you looking for?
(Screaming)
Who are you looking for?
(He looks towards Ji Hyo then suddenly attacks Yoon A.)
(He attacks suddenly as soon as he sees Ji Hyo.)
- There's one more. - Stop it.
(Tearing)
Okay.
(Hunter Jung Seok tears off Yoon A's name tag.)
All right.
Let me see your cards.
- You want to see my cards? - Yes.
(Is their goal exchanging cards?)
(Or are they acting because they're hunters?)
(Kwang Soo tried to get four of the same number.)
(As people take off each other's name tags, he fails to escape.)
(Jae Seok has 11, 23, 40, and Kwang Soo has 22, 24, and 37.)
I will exchange this...
with the one I have on my back.
- That one? - Yes.
(How many times has he exchanged?)
Take it.
(Number that will be on Jae Seok's back)
Do I have to put one of mine in there?
(Hunter's number 24)
(No one knows about it except the Hunters.)
I'm still chasing after number 24.
(Hunter Jung Seok is still chasing after number 24.)
(The Hunter number appeared.)
I'll get going.
(Will the Hunters be able to steal Jae Seok's number 24?)
The Hunter's number is 24.
(Number 24 is on Jae Seok's back.)
(The Hunters realized where the Hunter's number is.)
(Jae Seok becomes the Hunters' target.)
Where is Jae Seok?
(If he clears the jjajangmyeon mission,)
(he can escape.)
Have you seen Jae Seok?
(Hunter candidates become busy.)
Where's Jae Seok?
Where am I right now?
(Yoon A also looks for Jae Seok all of a sudden.)
(What?)
Jae Seok. Jae Seok.
(Is Yoon A calling me?)
Is that Jae Seok?
(She checks that the one faraway is Jae Seok.)
It's Jae Seok. Jae Seok.
(She takes big steps towards Jae Seok.)
(Then she starts to run towards him.)
(Hunter Jung Seok who is chasing after Jae Seok)
Where should I go?
- Jae Seok. - Wait.
(Jae Seok senses danger and runs away.)
Jae Seok.
(Hunter Jung Seok chases right after Jae Seok.)
(He goes back inside the stadium where there's nowhere to hide.)
(He gives all his might to run away.)
(However, he remains in the hands of Jung Seok.)
There's no way to go down.
(He's flustered.)
What do I do?
(At the moment he's looking for a way out,)
Don't worry.
(he's caught by Haha.)
(At that time)
(Tearing)
He tore it.
(Kwang Soo tears off Haha's name tag.)
(Name tags keep getting torn off.)
Two of you can fight.
What is it?
What about these two?
(Haha gets 11, and Kwang Soo gets 29.)
I could have defended this way.
You got all of them.
(Kwang Soo collects 4 of the same number.)
Have a seat.
Wait.
- Wait. - Actually...
(He looks for a chance to tear of Jae Seok's name tag.)
Do you know what numbers you have on your back?
- What? - Can you tell me?
(Yoon A shows interest in Jae Seok's numbers.)
Listen.
- You're irrelevant. - I know.
About the name tags...
Wait.
(At that moment)
(Tearing)
(Jung Seok tears off Jae Seok's name tag.)
My goodness.
Change my number with the number on his back.
Goodness.
(Hunter Jung Seok has only one goal.)
(He finally obtains the Hunter's number.)
You should get out.
(With the Hunter's number, he can clear the hidden mission.)
Tell me the location.
(He finds out where jjajangmyeon is located.)
I got it.
(He succeeds if he eats jjajangmyeon secretly.)
The main gate.
Let's go.
(Let's go eat jjajangmyeon.)
(Will he clear the last hidden mission and escape successfully?)
We need to catch him.
(Kwang Soo obtains 4 of the same number.)
"The one with four of the same number".
(Among hidden numbers)
It's 37.
(He obtains number 37.)
It's 37. Let's get out.
What's this?
(He has the highest sum of the numbers.)
Okay, I got out.
(Only 2 doors remain to escape.)
(Multiple of 5 Door and Hunter's door)
Those who can't escape, let's catch the Hunters.
I have no way to escape.
- Aren't you a Hunter? - Pardon?
- Aren't you? - No.
Aren't you a Hunter?
I swear that I'm not.
- Aren't you a Hunter? - It's definitely not me.
- I always thought it was you. - It's definitely not me.
I swear that I'm not.
Okay, I'll let you pass.
- You know that I'm not, right? - Okay.
What's this? Can we eat it?
(Why is there jjajangmyeon?)
- Is it for a Hunter? - Jjajangmyeon.
This is a mission for the Hunters.
"Eat jjajangmyeon".
(Why is it here?)
There it is.
(Jung Seok goes to look for jjajangmyeon.)
(He discovers jjajangmyeon.)
(Jjajangmyeon was placed in various places.)
(He leaves jjajangmyeon as bait and obtains it elsewhere.)
I should take it away.
- Are you a Hunter? - I'm not.
Let's just eat it. Come here.
(Just eat it?)
I'm not it.
(During the Hunters' strategy meeting a moment ago...)
(I'll eat it in front of the door.)
(Another Hunter intends to eat jjajangmyeon openly.)
(Was the strategy to draw attention?)
(Does that mean So Min is the other Hunter?)
It's so delicious.
(So Min's behavior is suspicious in many ways.)
(So Min's action draws attention.)
Haha.
- Haha. - Yes.
So Min is a Hunter.
She's eating jjajangmyeon.
(Was it So Min and Jung Seok's plan?)
She's a Hunter.
(Is So Min the other Hunter?)
- She's a Hunter. - Isn't she?
So Min.
Why are you eating jjajangmyeon?
I didn't eat any.
- It was to get rid of the evidence. - Only she ate it.
- What? - If I eat jjajangmyeon...
Why are you eating jjajangmyeon?
If I eat it, the light goes on, and the Hunter will leave.
(Their interrogation makes her choke.)
Why are you eating it?
To get rid of the evidence.
- It's to eliminate evidence. - She was eating jjajangmyeon.
She was eating it.
- This is unfair. - Tear off her name tag.
(At that moment)
Wait, I'm really not it.
- I'm not a Hunter. - Why did you eat jjajangmyeon?
- Hunter... - She ate it.
Listen, Haha.
(So Min is suspicious indeed.)
(She can be identified if her name tag is placed on the judging stand.)
- Seriously. - Currently,
- the Hunter's light didn't turn on. - See?
(The Hunter's light didn't come on.)
The light didn't turn on?
(Jung Seok is still eating the jjajangmyeon.)
See? This is evidence.
If the light turned because I ate this then I'm a Hunter.
I ate it.
- I believe you. - Okay.
I just ate it. I have evidence.
Then I'll eat some too.
Look if the light turns on or not.
(It's no use if the Hunter doesn't have his number.)
Wait, did you eat some?
I ate some.
(The light doesn't turn on since Jung Seok has the Hunter's number.)
Did the light turn on or not?
- Take a look. - I want some too.
- Really? - Neither of us are Hunters.
I ate some.
(The rest of them gather to eat jjajangmyeon.)
What's wrong?
Only two of the Hunter's lights are on.
See?
(4 members eat jjajangmyeon to avoid suspicion.)
- I'll eat some. - Wait.
I'm not it.
(Someone is acting in order to help Jung Seok.)
How can we find out?
(Which one of the 4 is a Hunter?)
As 3 of his cards are multiples of 5,
Jae Seok has escaped successfully.
- Jae Seok? - Did Jae Seok escape?
- Is it Jae Seok? - In the midst of all this?
(Thud)
(What's that sound?)
(He's struggling to eat jjajangmyeon without being noticed.)
(It's not easy being a Hunter.)
(It's the Hunter's last hidden mission.)
(He finishes eating jjajangmyeon in secret.)
(All of Hunter's lights are turned on.)
Hunters may escape through Hunter's door.
See? Someone cleared the mission.
The mission is cleared.
Where's the door? It's over once the Hunter goes out.
It's over once the Hunter goes out.
- I have no idea. - Hey.
Everyone, hold hands.
No one can leave.
(Hold hands all of a sudden?)
Hold hands. Hold hands.
Hold each other's hands.
Let's go over there.
A Hunter may be going over there.
(They move to the Hunter's door to block the other Hunter.)
Is it Jung Seok?
It is.
(They find out about one Hunter.)
Jung Seok will leave now.
(Jung Seok moves towards the Hunter's door.)
One of us is also a Hunter.
I know, but it could be you.
It could be you too.
How can you?
- How can you act? - How can you?
- Yoon A. - You're so good at acting.
Who is it?
- Seriously. - I don't know who it is,
- but the Hunter is good at acting. - I know.
- Haha. - It's the Hunter's door.
(They arrive in front of the Hunter's door.)
(Will they be able to stop the Hunters from escaping?)
(Jung Seok gets to the front of the Hunter's door.)
(He sees the members and hides himself.)
Isn't it you, Haha?
You're about to drive me crazy.
Are you cornering me again?
(How can I get out?)
Ji Hyo, we must decide. Let's put up someone's name tag.
All three lights are on.
- We can put someone up. - Lights are on anyway.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The loser will go.
- Then... - Seriously.
you two are suspicious, so play rock-paper-scissors.
Listen to her.
Why does she keep cornering me?
Listen to her. Why does she keep cornering me?
- She keeps accusing others. - Right?
Seriously.
(Is it really unfair?)
(Or is she acting?)
Please believe me. I'm not a Hunter.
You can post the photo of me as Yondu on social media.
My mom wears a cotton flannel dress.
(My mom wears a cotton flannel dress.)
(A battle of Yondu and cotton flannel?)
You can post my Yondu photo.
I look like a blue egg.
I have one of hers.
I'm really not a Hunter. If I am, you can post that photo.
- I swear that I'm not it. - You scare me so much.
I swear that I'm not a hunter.
I swear that I'm not.
I'm not it.
If I were strong...
Only if I were strong... I'll exercise starting today.
Current price is 600 dollars.
That's ridiculous.
(The tab at Good Place keeps going up.)
Do it now. Someone should go.
Someone should start even if you're eliminated.
It increased to 640 dollars.
- Hurry. - Stop it.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
I'm really not it.
- Why am I doing this? - That's right.
Why don't we do this?
Jung Seok is definitely it, so let's catch him first.
Are you stalling for time?
No way!
(What did he say?)
You're crazy.
Look at him. I guess he isn't it.
- He's really not it. - You're annoying.
(At that time)
(So Min tries to take off Yoon A's name tag.)
You startled me.
Isn't Yoon A?
I won't take off your name tag. I worried about your hair.
Is it her?
- Listen. - She's being strange.
- What's wrong with you? - Someone should do it.
(Tearing)
I'm really not it, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, will you put it up for verdict or not?
I will.
(She decides to put up So Min's name tag for a verdict.)
If she's a Hunter, the light will turn green.
If not, the light will remain red.
(If So Min is a Hunter, the light will turn green.)
(If she's not a Hunter, Ji Hyo will be eliminated.)
So Min.
I'm not it.
(So Min's name tag goes on the judging stand.)
(So Min tried hard to win even by drinking salted sikhye.)
(Why is she doing that?)
(She was also the first to eat jjajangmyeon.)
(So Min was suspicious throughout the day.)
(Who is So Min?)
I'm not it.
(It turned red?)
(So Min isn't a Hunter.)
So Min is not a Hunter.
- Ji Hyo is eliminated. - See?
(So Min and Ji Hyo are not Hunters.)
(Yoon A and Haha remain.)
I'm not it.
I can't figure out who it is.
(In the first game, Yoon A exchanged numbers with Jae Seok.)
- You want to exchange? - Yes.
- With the number on my back. - On your back?
Seriously?
(The sum of Yoon A's numbers was the highest.)
(Instead of escaping, she chose Round 2.)
(Yoon A kept looking for Jae Seok. Is she a Hunter?)
(Haha acted suspiciously all day.)
(Those who can't escape, let's catch the Hunters.)
(Haha gave up on his numbers.)
(Haha gave up too early.)
(Did he stay in order to help the other Hunter?)
(Is Haha the other Hunter?)
I'm really not it.
I swear that I'm not.
(Jung Seok waits for his chance.)
I swear to you.
- I'm really not it. - I can't figure out who it is.
It's really not me.
(At that time)
(Yoon A goes after Haha's name tag.)
It's really not me.
(Haha runs away.)
- It's really not me. - It must be him.
- It's not me. - Why are you running away?
It's because it's not me.
It's definitely not me.
I swear to you. I'm not it.
(Tearing)
(Haha)
(She tore of Haha's name tag.)
I said that I'm not it.
Haha.
- I'm not a Hunter. - You'll regret it.
(It's unclear who the Hunter is.)
(She goes towards the Hunter's door.)
Trust my feelings.
- Are you really not it? - You aren't?
- I'm not it. - Hurry!
(At that moment)
(He takes his chance.)
- I'm not it. - Hurry!
Hurry.
(They spot Jung Seok who comes running.)
(They run after Jung Seok.)
(Jung Seok already arrives at the door.)
(Hunter Jung Seok escapes.)
Put it on.
I'm not it.
(The game is already over.)
A Hunter went out of Hunter's door.
The Hunters have cleared their mission.
(Team Hunters clears the mission, and the race is over.)
How many times do I have to tell you that I'm not it?
"How many times"?
How can I believe you?
You always say that you're not it.
Goodness.
- Are you a Hunter? - I'm not it.
- Then who is it? - I'm not it.
- Is it Ji Hyo? - Goodness.
(Then who's the other Hunter?)
- Good job, everyone. - Please come out.
Let's find out...
if Haha is a Hunter or not.
- I'll be surprised if he is. - Try it.
I'm really not it.
I won't ever believe you again.
- Are you a Hunter? - I'm not.
(Neither of them say that they're a Hunter.)
One.
(If the light turns green, Haha is a Hunter.)
- Two. - It's definitely not me.
Three.
(If the light turns red, Yoon A is a Hunter.)
(Which one of them is a real Hunter?)
Goodness.
(The light is green.)
(The other Hunter is Haha.)
(She feels betrayed again today.)
(We were fooled.)
Good job.
- Hurray to Hunters. - Hurray to Hunters.
Hurray.
- Hello. - Goodness.
Gosh.
(Haha and Jung Seok are assigned as Hunters.)
Number 24 is...
on the back of Jae Seok.
I'll be eating it openly by the front gate.
(Haha drew attention.)
I'm not it.
(He spots Jung Seok.)
(He leads other members so that Jung Seok can escape.)
(With Haha's help, Jung Seok could escape safely.)
(Hurray for Hunters.)
In summary,
the first mission was stealing people's belongings.
Who stole it?
- What did you take? - Se Chan helped me.
Se Chan helped me.
Me? How?
- Me? How? - Where's your name tag...
on your bag, Kwang Soo?
(Where is...)
(my name tag?)
- Your name tag is missing. - His name tag was missing.
(Who took his name tag?)
Haha, did you take it...
from the sole of my foot?
We'll pick a number.
(The Hunter's number is picked.)
(The Hunter's number is 37.)
Everyone is flustered.
(Haha had number 37.)
(Steal a member's belonging.)
(He was waiting for his chance to clear the mission.)
- I know that it's not you. - I should stand there.
(What?)
I know that it's not you.
(Kwang Soo's name tag gets stuck on Se Chan's shirt.)
(The name tag falls on the floor, and he keeps playing the game.)
- We're next. Okay. - Let's go.
(Kwang Soo's name tag is on the sole of Se Chan's shoe.)
(The game is quite physical,)
(but the name tag stays on his foot.)
(Haha sees the name tag.)
(Haha obtains the name tag naturally.)
(I can't believe this.)
Look, here it is.
(He hands Kwang Soo's name tag and clears his first mission.)
I did it while smiling.
That's amazing.
I got goosebumps again.
If you look carefully,
- there are people who help them. - Right.
(They're 3 assistants.)
- Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and So Min. - No.
Me?
Why you...
Goodness.
Also the cost of Good Place was...
646 dollars.
(646 dollars)
Really?
So Min and Yoon A who failed to escape...
and eliminated Ji Hyo and Jong Kook will...
share the cost.
Yoon A is here as a guest.
- She should pay what she owes. - Right.
Just pay 15.
I hope that we will see...
- Yoon A again. - Right.
- I don't know when it'll be. - Their movie seems fun.
They worked on a movie together called "Exit".
- Be sure to watch it. - Thank you.
"Exit"!