Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
Good morning.
Hello. Hi, Mi Yeon.
Jong Kook had a solo concert after nine years.
- That's right. - Amazing!
- His life is getting better. - Congratulations.
I had a concert after a nine-year hiatus.
- Right. - That's right.
- Kwang Soo came. - Don't mention it.
- And So Min came too. - My gosh.
- Se Chan did a performance. - Right.
- He performed on stage. - I see.
And you came too, Jae Seok.
- Of course. It was your concert. - Thank you.
- It was on your social media. - I...
- He came to my concert. - You were on social media.
He came three hours before the concert.
(I'm grateful that you came, but you came 3 hours before.)
- He came early. - Why did you make it uncomfortable?
- It wasn't. It was really nice. - Really?
I went to the concert and talked to Jong Kook.
I asked him if I could make a guest appearance.
- You asked him that. - Jong Kook quietly said,
"No".
I told him he didn't have to, but he kept forcing it.
- So was he in the concert? - I told him I could be the guest.
- He wasn't supposed to be in it. - I see.
But in the end,
he was dancing by himself, and people found out.
He laughed while singing because of me.
(When Jong Kook was singing the high notes on stage...)
(What?)
(I'm the Mr. Yu the Excitement.)
- He was jumping around. - I couldn't stop myself.
It was Jong Kook's song.
I heard that So Min brought her mother.
- She brought her parents. - My parents came too.
- Her parents came too. - My gosh.
- My parents are his fans. - Did your mom see him?
Her mother was very beautiful. I was really surprised.
- After her mother saw him perform, - Thank you.
she subtly mentioned that he could be her son-in-law.
She said that, but the age gap is too big.
(The age got in the way.)
- I'm older than her. - Right.
But I still left an impression on So Min's mother...
- Exactly. - for now.
By the way, Jong Kook is...
leaving a lot of comments on So Min's social media nowadays.
I'm really happy that they are writing...
- comments on my posts. - I couldn't just help myself.
- You couldn't skip them. - Right. All of her writing...
Jong Kook especially doesn't like that kind of posts.
Jong Kook can't stand posts like hers.
It calls for my comments.
- So Min writes that kind of posts. - That's true.
It's a space for my creativity.
What did you write? What was that?
"When I'm someone's world, spring comes."
- Did you write that? - Isn't that cool? Yes, I did.
(It's indecipherable. What does this mean?)
- What does it mean? She means you. - Here's the author's intention.
- Who's the author? Is that you? - Me. My intention was...
- When someone finds you special... - Real spring doesn't come...
because seasons change.
When I'm in love, and I become someone's world,
that's the truest form of spring. That's what I meant.
(The world becomes spring.)
- Isn't this cool? - On this post,
- kjk76 wrote, - Okay.
"What does this mean?"
(Kjk76: What does this mean?)
Jong Kook. Jong Kook!
"What does this mean?"
I don't know who this is. I don't know who wrote this.
- He must've been born in 1976. - Kjk76...
wrote, "What does this mean?"
"What does this mean?"
And So Min said, "You came into my frame."
Kjk76 wrote,
"My gosh..."
(He ruins it for the 2nd time.)
- Did he use that tone? - Yes.
- Yes. - That's how he wrote?
- You can pick up on it right away. - It's written there.
Writing a comment must have been a hassle.
- That's what happened. - "My gosh..."
Seriously. He must have hated that.
Those sentimental writings.
By the way, kjk76...
- and So Min... - They have good chemistry.
have great chemistry on social media.
- They started it not long ago. - Right.
- It hasn't been long. - It's pretty new.
- Exactly. It's only been a month. - That's true.
You guys became good friends quickly.
(The atmosphere feels friendly.)
Everyone seems to be getting along very well,
but there are two guests...
- Really? - who came to visit you today.
- We have guests today? - Let me bring them in.
Come on out.
(We'll introduce these two guests.)
- Who is that? - My gosh!
(The guests are visiting Running Man.)
(Who are these two guests?)
(The pair that will bring a mega-hit to the theaters)
- My gosh, hello. - Goodness.
My gosh.
Let me introduce you to Kim Kyung Nam and Esom.
(She used to be a unique top model and made a debut as an actress.)
(Esom, a popular actress who's always getting offers)
(From a scene-stealer who used to be on people's mind,)
(Kyung Nam became an amazing and popular actor now.)
- Hello. Esom. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
- That's right. - He was in that prison drama.
- Really? - It's Kyung Nam.
Move back!
- Come to the center. - Hello.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- All right. - Welcome.
- Stop lying. - Seriously.
Could you introduce yourselves to the viewers?
- Okay. - Introduction.
All right. I am...
- He sounded really cold, right? - What do you mean?
He said he was happy to see them, but he said, "Introduction".
(Introduction)
- He's unbelievable. - I just blurted it out.
I told him to introduce himself.
(He pretended to be happy to see him like a gentleman.)
(He suddenly changes.)
He has multiple personalities. He has a few personalities.
- No, that's not true. - He has multiple personalities.
- No, I'm a warmhearted person. - Go ahead.
- No way. - He's acting territorial.
Could you introduce yourselves?
Okay, I'm Esom.
She's pretty.
- Wasn't she a model? - She was a model.
- She looks like a model, right? - Yes. She does have that vibe.
- Right. - This comedian used to be a model.
- Kwang Soo... - Right.
Comedian who used to be a model?
- Listen. - I can't believe this.
Did he film a movie with you?
- Yes. - The three of us filmed it.
- The three of you? - I see.
- With Shin Ha Kyun? - Yes.
Yes, that movie. It looked fun.
What kind of guy is Kwang Soo?
You filmed the movie with him.
Kwang Soo? He's...
- very serious at the shoot. - I knew it.
- People are talking about you. - What do they say?
Word on the street is that you're different from Running Man.
I can't act all crazy over there.
(I'm at a movie shoot.)
You should though.
I would be arrested then.
Come on, Kwang Soo.
You, you. You've become an entitled leading actor.
(He finishes his diagnosis.)
- That's not true. - No.
- That's not it. - You're full of yourself!
What are you saying? That's not true.
Is that true? Is that true, Kwang Soo?
(Please look forward to Kwang Soo's secrets from Esom.)
That was new.
- Kwang Soo is different. - Seriously.
We've heard from Esom. Now, we'll hear from Kyung Nam.
- He's tanned. - Okay.
- Hello, I'm actor Kim Kyung Nam. - Great.
- Kyung Nam. - I'm a huge fan.
- Really? - I liked you in the prison drama.
- He looks like a model. - Okay.
Wait. Do you freeze around famous people?
- Yes... I do. - Is that so?
Then, you must feel a bit awkward today.
Right.
(Suddenly interrupting)
(You must feel shy around this famous guy, Seok Jin.)
- Why would you say that? - He's unbelievably territorial.
- Are you feeling shy now? - This is driving me crazy.
- Seriously. He's not that famous. - Today...
He's too much.
- It's okay. You'll get used to me. - Okay.
- He's not that famous? - His popularity is very low.
He acts all arrogant.
All right. How was Kwang Soo's first impression?
(This is the first official question.)
(If you ask me a question like that out of the blue,)
(how could I answer that...)
(in front of all these famous people?)
(Having butterflies)
(His mental sanity has gone to the Andromeda Galaxy.)
Who said I was annoying?
(Here comes his savior.)
Annoying?
I think I heard someone saying "annoying".
Did I hear it wrong?
I don't know how it is, but it's accurate.
- Annoying. - Okay.
All right. I will ask you the next question.
- You haven't answered anything. - Okay.
(Getting ready to blurt out mean comments)
- He didn't answer anything. - You must answer.
- 0. You have 0 points. - Right.
- We'll ask and answer. - He didn't answer.
All right. Pay attention.
- Pay attention. - He hasn't answered anything.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
- You can do it. - You're doing great!
I heard that you're well-versed in acrostic poems.
- Acrostic poems. This will work. - Right.
- The best part of variety shows. - Let's do this!
You must do this one.
All right. Let's go with "Running Man".
- You can do it! - Could you do one?
- You can do it. - That's a hard one.
- Go for it. - You can do it.
You can do this. You got this!
Let's do this one!
First syllable.
I was on a treadmill.
- That was great. - Good, good.
Second syllable.
I got an IV.
Third syllable.
(Will he be able to finish it smoothly?)
On my bare skin.
(Kyung Nam is so eloquent!)
- That was entertaining. - Great, great.
- You get it on your bare skin. - That was fun.
- That was original. - Right.
Great, great. That was great.
Can you do one with Kwang Soo's name?
(Let's try this too since we're at it.)
- Lee Kwang Soo. - You can do it!
- Okay. - You can do this.
(Let's finish it off with the momentum.)
First syllable.
As you can see...
- "As you can see". - Second syllable.
We're in this crazy atmosphere.
(He's finally got the hang of it.)
It's going great.
Third syllable.
(If he comes up with the last one, it will be a big hit.)
(Will he be able to adjust to the show with the acrostic poem?)
(His mental sanity goes to the Andromeda Galaxy again.)
- You can do it! - You can do it!
- You're almost there! - You can do it!
(Wait. It's a time-out on a variety show.)
(We must get him adjusted to the variety show now.)
Pay attention.
We'll break for a commercial now.
Look forward to it.
- You can do the last one. - You can do it.
- You can do it! - Continue.
Third syllable.
(It's the last syllable in Kwang Soo's name.)
You can do it!
(Will he be able to succeed?)
(What's the result of his training?)
Why don't we have a drink?
(Why don't we have a drink?)
(He successfully saves his acrostic poem.)
- That was a basic move. - Basic move?
Get rid of your shyness!
You're almost there! Go for it!
(Good luck until you overcome your shyness.)
Shouldn't you make a pledge in case...
- you sell five million tickets? - Make a pledge.
- They must do it for 5 million. - 5 million tickets.
Why don't you make a pledge?
- 5 million tickets deserve it. - 5 million tickets.
Why don't you come back to the show with Ha Kyun if that happens?
- Yes. I'd like that. - Is that okay?
(Count me in!)
- That's good, right? Great. - Of course.
(Sell 5 million tickets and see you on Running Man, Ha Kyun.)
Great. When you sell five million tickets...
Hey, we answered everything today.
They didn't answer anything.
- You made the pledge for them. - We had our answers in mind.
We ask questions and answer them too.
We had our answers in mind.
- We asked and answered. - We had our answers in mind.
Everyone.
We asked you to come here...
- early in the morning for a reason. - What is it?
- We have invitations for you. - Invitations?
(We have invitations for you.)
- Invitations? - Invitations?
(These mysterious invitations were sent to the members.)
- My gosh. - Do we just choose one?
- Yes. - I guess we'll randomly draw one.
- Are these randomly chosen? - We can share them together, right?
Let's look.
"I welcome you to the world where you can earn millions."
"Host S".
Who is Host S?
(And a mysterious host sent them the invitations.)
You'll go to a place where Host S invited you to go.
- Let's go. - And you'll start the race there.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(What is the secret that awaits the members?)
- Can we go in now? - Shall we go in?
(The members arrive at the place Host S invited them to.)
- Gosh, it's big. Why is it so big? - We're starting.
(How will the world where they can make millions at look?)
- We're starting. - What is this?
- There are boxes. - It's huge.
- There's a lot here. - Those are box containers.
(The world of making millions is full of...)
(10 box containers.)
You said we'd get a fortune. What is this?
This place is huge.
There are boxes.
(Something seems off. What is this place?)
- Why is there 100,000 dollars? - Is that 100,000 dollars?
- What? - The cash prize is 100,000 dollars?
- What? - Yes, it is.
(The box containers unfold before their eyes.)
- It's 100,000 dollars. - It really is.
My gosh. They'll give us 100,000 dollars?
- We'll get 100,000 dollars? - 100,000 dollars?
Really?
This is amazing.
I'll tell you the rules now.
Today's cash prize is 100,000 dollars.
For nine hours, depending on how much money you save,
you can divide the leftover money with the members.
It's called Inseparable Money Race.
(Inseparable Money Race)
- Depending on how much we save? - We'll split it among us?
In other words, if you don't use a penny for nine hours,
everyone will get 10,000 dollars at the end.
(If they don't spend any money, everyone will get 10,000 dollars.)
- 10,000 dollars per person? - We're diving the money.
For the duration of the race, you cannot use...
- any of your personal belongings. - Nothing?
Not even our phone?
You must buy whatever you need.
- This is terrible. - To buy them,
you must use the intercom inside the box containers.
And the value of the money here will be different from our world.
- Of course. I knew it. - Come on.
- I see. - That's right.
- I bet everything is expensive. - That's right.
What if...
you charge us 20,000 dollars for 1 bowl of cup noodles?
- Exactly. Or 5,000 dollars. - A long time ago,
- how much was a pair of chopsticks? - Right.
- 5,000 dollars. - It was like 500 dollars.
You can only stay in this place for nine hours.
- We can't do anything? - We can't get out?
After spending an hour in the solitary container,
the door will stay open for 30 minutes, and you can come out.
Is that our recess?
- Recess? - We're totally in prison.
- It's like "Prison Playbook". - We're in prison.
And the amount of your expenses...
- will not be disclosed. - My gosh.
(The amounts of individual expenses will not be disclosed.)
- Hey. - It will be confidential.
Hey, hey.
My gosh, this is a special episode for Kwang Soo.
- Unbelievable. - Everyone.
- Kwang Soo. So Min. - We're doomed.
- Gosh, no. - No, no.
They'll go crazy with this.
I can hold out for nine hours.
All right. Please empty your pockets...
- and give them to us. - I'll collect them.
- Kwang Soo. - Okay.
I can keep my lip balm, right?
No, no. You have to buy that too.
- I can't even keep that? - Of course, not.
You can't have anything including the lip balm.
- Nothing is allowed. - Give it to me.
Esom.
- What? - What is that?
- What is this, Esom? - She has a comb.
- Why do you use that kind of combs? - This is cute.
(The popular actress has a comb.)
- Let me comb my hair one last time. - Okay.
(Rushing)
That's for her hair.
(Her smooth hair completes her beauty.)
She and I have a similar hairstyle.
- I want to go, but... - This is it.
In the back,
- there are containers from 1 to 10. - Okay.
You can choose whichever container you want...
and enter the containers one at a time.
- Kwang Soo. You're on the far end. - Okay.
Okay.
I'll go with the fifth one.
- You can't choose that one. - Why not?
It's reserved.
(It's already reserved for someone else.)
It's a reservation basis?
(He's flustered.)
- It's already booked. - What?
- It's already booked. - I thought I could pick anything.
- Room Five is reserved. - Okay.
Then, I'll go with the container on the far right, Room One.
That one? It's already booked too.
Then which ones are available?
The remaining one is Room Four.
(You'll go to Room 4.)
- Four means death. - It means death.
- Use another room then. - Room Four?
- Sure, I'll go with that one. - Great.
- Great. - Room Four.
Next up is Seok Jin.
I'll go with Room Five.
It's reserved. I booked it.
- Sure. Take Room Five. - Okay.
(Seok Jin goes into Room 5.)
(All 10 of them have gone into their rooms.)
I'm going in.
(The Inseparable Money Race starts.)
What is this? There's nothing inside?
(In the rooms that the members went into,)
(there is nothing inside.)
(The intercom system is the only thing in the room.)
This is the intercom system we can order stuff from.
(They can buy whatever they need,)
(but the prices will be different from the real world.)
Nothing is inside.
There's nothing here.
This really is like a prison cell.
(They must survive in this room for 9 hours with the bare minimum.)
Let me put on the uniform.
(They'll divide the leftover money equally among themselves.)
(Meanwhile, Kyung Nam enters too.)
(Am I really alone here?)
(Peeking)
(Since there's nobody here, he won't feel shy.)
(But being on a variety show is hard.)
(And here's another newbie on variety shows.)
(She freezes.)
(What should I do? She's as lost as Kyung Nam.)
I can last for nine hours.
(Hold out for 9 hours, and get 10,000 dollars.)
If I hold out for nine hours,
I will get 10,000 dollars. Of course, I can do this.
How much would the hourly rate be?
It's almost 1,000 dollars per hour.
Because we can take 10,000 dollars. Right?
It's 1,000 dollars per hour.
(This is totally doable.)
Should I sleep?
I can't even see anything from here.
(Listening to sounds from outside)
Hey!
(Whom are you talking to?)
(The solitary room is completely cut off from the outside world.)
My gosh, I have nothing to do here.
I'm going crazy without my phone.
(At that moment,)
(Ji Hyo finds a small stone.)
(Picking up the stone)
(Why is there a stone here?)
(Good. I was getting bored.)
Hello? How did you end up here?
In the movie, "Cast Away", there's...
a volleyball.
(He befriended the volleyball.)
The ball became his friends.
Can you be my friend too?
(The inmate in Cell 9 shows signs of a mental disorder.)
I should name you.
You're S.
(It's the 2nd Wilson.)
I mean, this is...
(Seok Jin can't stand being in the room alone.)
I have no one to talk to. This is driving me crazy.
I have to talk to someone.
(Seok Jin can't stand being in the room alone.)
(Yes, I've decided.)
Hello?
(He starts talking to the intercom system.)
Is everything possible?
Can you bring me water too?
How much do a pen...
and a piece of computer paper cost?
A pen and a piece of paper cost 1,100 dollars.
(A pen and a piece of paper cost 1,100 dollars.)
A pen and a piece of paper cost 1,100 dollars?
How much is a set of blankets?
A blanket and a pillow cost 3,000 dollars.
(As he snorts away, he refuses to talk.)
(I knew it. It's so expensive.)
I won't buy it. I won't buy it if it's 3,000 dollars.
We have to stay here without spending money, right?
(At that time, the inmate in Cell 10 talks on the intercom system.)
- Hello? - Yes, go ahead.
Can you cook me cup noodles?
Yes, I can.
How much is that?
Cup noodles cost 1,500 dollars.
- What about a meal box? - With the meal box,
- it costs 4,000 dollars. - 4,000 dollars?
(Cup noodles and the meal box cost 4,000 dollars?)
Okay. I'll pay 4,000 dollars for them.
(He only thinks about it for 1.5 seconds.)
(Jae Seok in Room 10 spends money 1st with gusto.)
This is all right. How can I just loiter around for an hour by myself?
I should eat or do something.
They'll be mad when they find out.
Oh, it's here!
(He sets his worries aside.)
Thank you. Thank you.
(He needs to focus on the food.)
(I can't believe it's really here!)
My gosh.
(He secretly receives his food.)
I ordered this.
(He blows on the noodles first.)
(Slurping)
(It's scrumptious.)
It's so good.
(Suddenly)
(Knocking)
(Who's knocking on the door?)
(I'm not expecting any visitors.)
(The staff brings in something else.)
(It's pickled radish.)
(Relieved)
You startled me.
Thank you.
You scared me for a minute.
Thank you. Make sure the others don't spot you.
(He receives the pickled radish.)
(He's relieved.)
I was so startled.
They gave me pickled radish.
(He eats the pickled radish.)
(Slurping)
(The pickled radish makes it even tastier.)
This is great.
I didn't order pickled radish, but they gave me some.
(While he's busy eating,)
(what is happening in Room 2?)
There's one thing good about this.
No matter what I say, no one can come in.
Even if I curse at someone,
I won't be punished.
Kim Jong Kook!
(Her target is Jong Kook.)
Hey, Jong Kook!
Catch me if you can!
(My ears are itching.)
(Whoever it is, I'll kill you.)
(She's afraid for no reason.)
Hello?
(Kyung Nam is lost.)
(Screaming)
(She starts to act strange.)
I'm neglected.
What kind of show is this?
I'd rather you pour water on us.
Or slap us.
What am I doing in here?
What is this?
(First open house.)
It's been an hour.
We can go out.
What?
(He can't clean the room,)
(so he decides to clean his teeth.)
Did you guys order anything?
No, right?
Did you guys eat anything?
- What? - Hey.
- What is that? - Someone used the money.
(They look at the display board.)
- Hey, who used the money? - What?
Let's not do this.
They spent 12,000 dollars.
Someone used over 10,000 dollars!
(11,500 dollars are deducted.)
The number of digits changed.
It wasn't me. I swear.
- It was you. - No, it wasn't.
- You ate, didn't you? - Seok Jin.
- It wasn't me. - Esom.
- What? - Did you use the money?
- No. - You did, right?
- I didn't. - You did, right?
No, I didn't.
Everyone.
For the next 30 minutes,
you have to stay out here.
(They have to be with each other.)
Gosh.
- That's horrible. - Why do I smell cup noodles on you?
What do you mean?
(Why do I smell noodles on you?)
- He's reeking of it. - Right?
- No? - You're just being suspicious.
I'm sure he spent it.
- No. - Come on.
- His clothes smell of it. - I smell it.
(They gather around him.)
(You did eat!)
You ate it!
- Darn it! - You did eat.
- How could you? - I smell?
- Right? - Wait.
- I smell it. - Hold on.
- It's not me. - I smell it.
- I smell it too. - No, it's not me.
Don't lie!
- Jae Seok. - I smell it!
- Hey. - Did you bathe in the broth?
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hold on. - We need to eat naked.
- Hold on. - We do.
- Wait a minute. - So this is what we're doing?
Fine! I had noodles!
- Hey! - But...
- I didn't spend it all. - No?
- You know, right? - I do.
- I'll tell you one thing. - Okay.
- He ate it. - I didn't...
I didn't order pickled radish, but I got some.
(I didn't order pickled radish, but I got some.)
You should take it back.
(Who ordered it?)
It wasn't me. I swear!
I swear!
Gosh!
- Tell them! - How dare you?
- Explain it to them! - Wait a minute.
It was you.
(The culprit was someone else.)
The smell is too strong.
(It was Jong Kook.)
(To prevent the smell from seeping into his clothes,)
(he threw his clothes in the corner of the room.)
It's over if I get the broth on my clothes.
(He carefully opened the jjamppong.)
(He then began eating.)
(Savoring)
(It tastes better in secret.)
(He didn't get the pickled radish, but he finished his food.)
This is really good.
Hold on.
- What? - The smell of the noodles...
- is reeking. - It is.
That's because we didn't eat anything.
(But I did.)
It's not me!
(He's falsely blamed.)
- I... Fine. - I don't smell...
- anything on him. - We're secluded in there.
If you're going to accuse me,
then I'll show you how to spend 80,000 dollars in an hour.
- Look at him. - I'll get hit by Jong Kook.
Hey, hey.
Kyung Nam keeps acting innocent,
- but... - What?
- He's suspicious. - Did you eat anything?
- I didn't. - I bet he ordered something.
- You have something on you! - Look at his lips.
(They suspect him.)
- Look. - Come here. Come here.
What is this?
(They find something on his lip.)
- You had bread, didn't you? - Gosh.
(What's on my lip?)
- What is this? - He ate something.
- What is it? - Hey.
You ate something, didn't you?
- What is this? - You had something.
- It's just dead skin. - He said it's dead skin.
(He explains.)
- He said it's dead skin. - You ate something, right?
- It's just dead skin. - So Min.
- It's dead skin. - It's dead skin.
(A simple dead skin has made him look suspicious.)
I had to hand in my lip balm.
(Their first open house ends with them suspecting each other.)
How about the others?
- How about the others? - Right?
- All right. - You guys better not spend any.
We have seven hours left.
(They go back into their rooms.)
I didn't know you'd reek.
When...
When I was next to Jae Seok, I could smell it so easily.
It must be a clear zone out there.
It must be.
(In Room 3)
I should continue eating.
(What?)
(Why is there cup noodles in Room 3?)
I'm sure they could smell this.
(Let's see what happened.)
(She was the first one to reach for the intercom.)
I'm a bit hungry.
Can I have some noodles?
Cup noodles, please.
(She was also a culprit.)
It was so difficult to pretend that I didn't order anything.
(It really tastes the best when you eat it in secret.)
(I might as well go all out.)
Could you...
bring my comb?
How much is it?
500 dollars.
Will you purchase it?
(500 dollars to retrieve my own comb?)
Okay, I'll buy it.
(At least, the comb won't reek of any smells.)
I can use this as a mirror.
(She uses the silverware as a mirror.)
(She finds her situation hilarious.)
(So far, 10,000 dollars have been used.)
If they suspect me even if I didn't order anything,
then I might as well order something.
I can't do this with them anymore.
(He reaches for the intercom.)
Can I call for a chef?
We only serve delivery food.
Then I'd like some cup noodles,
a bowl of rice, chopsticks,
a blanket, a pillow,
two hot packs,
a chair,
and a fabric deodorizer.
(It's a total of 8,000 dollars.)
Let me ask about the price first.
How much is a cushion?
A cushion costs 500 dollars.
It's too expensive.
How about fried chicken?
I'd like a bowl of jjajangmyeon...
and fried dumplings.
And a bottle of water in case I have an upset stomach.
(The inmates in Cell 6 and 7 are starving as well.)
Cup noodles,
chopsticks,
water,
and pickled radish.
Thank you.
I have no choice.
I need to eat to live.
Let's be in good spirits.
Let's forget about it.
(Like so, everyone spends money during their second confinement.)
(Meanwhile, in Room 1...)
(He's in a dilemma.)
I'll try to hold it in.
I need to go to the bathroom.
I need to go.
(I'll need to spend money to go to the bathroom.)
I have to stay here for seven hours.
(He's restless.)
(Can I hold it in?)
The best thing...
is to sleep.
(I wonder what everyone else is doing in this silence.)
Everyone's so quiet.
(What are we doing?)
(We're spending money.)
(He's showing the quintessence of living alone.)
(A cozy blanket and hot packs)
(A fabric deodorizer and mouthwash, the must-haves for a perfect crime)
(Welcome to Kwang Soo's lovely Room 4.)
It's so warm already.
I should just stay true to who I am.
(Now that he's all settled in, he decides to eat.)
(He has cup noodles,)
(a chair,)
(and a camera.)
(He positions his food near the camera.)
(I'm all ready.)
Hello, everyone. This is Lee Kwang Soo.
Today, I will have your favorite, cup noodles.
(Today's mukbang is cup noodles.)
I will eat cup noodles today.
Personally, I like my noodles a bit salty.
So I poured in a bit less water.
Do you see the steam?
(Hurry up and eat. I'm dying.)
Is it working?
(He checks to see if the angle is right.)
(Let me turn this.)
(This will be enough.)
(He spills the noodles.)
(He makes a big mistake.)
(That's 1,500 dollars on the floor.)
That's so hot.
(My noodles...)
(He makes an irreversible mistake.)
I'll see you all next time.
(He fails to shoot a mukbang.)
Darn it.
[VIU Ver] SBS E449 Running Man
"Inseparable Money Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
How much is it for a fabric deodorizer?
1,000 dollars.
I'll take it. Please bring it.
I need it if I want to go out. It smells so much in here.
That's so expensive, though. I just need to use it once.
(Spraying)
(He showers himself with the fabric deodorizer.)
(He and So Min are thinking about the same thing.)
(This is a nice trick.)
Okay. Okay, this is good.
(Meanwhile)
(I don't need to go. I don't.)
(He tries to keep it in.)
We've used over 10,000 dollars already. It'll be all right.
How much is it?
How much is it to go to the bathroom?
It costs 2,000 dollars.
Okay. All right.
(Hopeless)
My goodness.
(That's a bit too expensive.)
I wonder if they've bought anything.
(He's curious.)
(Se Chan is almost done...)
(with his jjajangmyeon and fried dumplings.)
I'll dip it in the jjajangmyeon sauce.
(Ringing)
(The siren is sounded.)
(He's in a haste.)
(He wipes his mouth first...)
(and then prepares to rinse his mouth.)
(I have no time.)
(He takes one big gulp.)
(He accidentally spits some out.)
(Relax)
(Meanwhile...)
Wait a minute.
(Kwang Soo is panicking the most.)
(How should I clean this up?)
(He also purchased wet tissues to clean up the mess.)
Darn it.
(He puts on a spurt to get rid of the smell.)
(I'm not sure if this will work, but I'll have to try.)
(He gargles his mouth.)
(He's doing the best he can to hide his crimes.)
(He goes out without his shoes on.)
(We hope you come back alive.)
(Second open house)
(How much did they spend this time around?)
How much do we have left?
How much?
(How much did they spend this time around?)
What? No way!
- How could that be possible? - Have you guys gone insane?
(How much is left?)
My gosh.
That's... That's too harsh.
- You scumbags. - You...
You just spent mindlessly.
- Seriously. - Are they insane?
That's all that we have left?
Kwang Soo.
- I got a glimpse of you. - What?
Let me smell you. Come here.
- I didn't purchase anything. - I smell fabric deodorizer on him.
- I didn't get anything. - Hey.
He bought a fabric deodorizer.
No, no. I really didn't.
My gosh.
You ate something too.
What did you eat?
- Is it that hard not to eat? - Kim Kyung Nam.
- I didn't eat. - You did.
- No, I didn't. - Don't lie.
- Next door... - You all spent 40,000 dollars.
- You all spent money. - Goodness.
Did you buy a fabric deodorizer? You smell so nice.
- You do. - Hold on.
You spent money.
Move back.
Do you want some water?
- Can you give me some? - Sure.
(Esom tries to get rid of evidence by offering some.)
- Kyung Nam. Hey. - Do you want some?
- Can I? - Yes.
Hey, look at him.
He must've been in a hurry doing something to have...
- forgotten his shoes. - It's not like that.
No, I took them off on purpose.
- You didn't wear any shoes? - This is...
(They're sure he was eating something.)
I had them off to begin with.
I had my reasons.
What is this in your pocket?
(Se Chan spots something.)
- What? Why? - Oh, come on.
(I didn't hide anything.)
(A fried dumpling is found.)
- What is this? - Why?
(No one's surprised by it.)
- What is it? - What is this?
It's not me. What is this?
- Come on. - This isn't mine!
- Why was there a fried dumpling? - Goodness.
- My goodness. - A fried dumpling?
- What is that? - How is that possible?
- He had it in his pocket. - It's not mine!
- What did you order in there? - How dare you lie to us?
- It was in his pocket. - What are you talking about?
- A fried dumpling? - No.
- It doesn't make any sense. - How could he?
And you sprayed fabric deodorizer on yourself.
- Hey. - No, I didn't.
(The scent is mixed in with the food's scent.)
- Hey. - I had my reasons.
- It's not me. - I can't believe you.
Seriously.
Did we use over 40,000 dollars?
- 41,900 dollars. - Yes.
You fools! We could've split the money.
I'm telling you in advance. I'm going to spend 20,000 dollars.
- I'm curious about Jae Seok's room. - Me too.
- Me too. - Me too.
- Me too. - There's nothing in my room.
I'm so curious.
(He's in danger.)
Let's play a Race of Wits.
- Race of Wits? - One.
- 2. - 2.
(So Min and Esom are chosen.)
- Oh, no. - It's them two.
- This is good. Let's pick So Min. - Yes.
- Right. - I'm curious.
Let's look at your room.
I have nothing to hide.
- Then let's see it. - Let's go to Room Two.
- Let's go. - I bet it's like...
a luxury room in there.
Let's go inside.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
I feel so wrongly blamed.
I didn't spend much compared to them.
I hope you all know that.
- Seriously. - I'm so upset.
Let's see.
(How does her room look?)
- She has a cushion. - Let's see.
- Goodness. - There are cup noodles.
(There's quite a bit in here.)
Look at that.
- There's green tea. - She drank green tea?
- She had a party in here. - She had cup noodles.
- How much was the green tea? - Goodness.
- My gosh. - All right. Let's leave.
- Please leave. - I can't believe her.
Jae Seok is surprised to see that...
I have fewer things that he does.
- We need to check his room. - Hey.
- There's nothing in my room. - We need...
- to see his room. - It wasn't that bad.
Kwang Soo's room is the worst.
- I bet he has a book in there. - So Min's wasn't too bad.
I bet Kwang Soo has a game controller or a TV.
Did you buy a fabric deodorizer?
- What? - Did you buy it?
To be honest, I almost got teary-eyed in there.
- She didn't spend much. - Look at him.
- I mean, she was... - Let's check Kwang Soo's room.
- Let's do that. - All right.
- There's nothing in there. - Look at how...
- he even forgot his shoes. - Let's vote.
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Who wants to see his room?
- Me. - Me.
Is this allowed?
(Do you want to see his room?)
(Let's go to Room 4!)
Why aren't you stopping them?
Wait! Why are you doing this?
(Running Man supports democracy.)
- Wait. Why? - Why are you so surprised?
- You could've spent all the money. - You can't just barge in!
This makes no sense!
(The door to his room opens.)
- Look at you. - He's insane.
- Look at this. - What is this?
- Hey. - What is this?
- Gosh. - Have you gone insane?
- What is this? - There are wet tissues.
- What is this? - He didn't even eat it.
- What is this? - He didn't even bother to eat.
I spilled cup noodles!
(You have no idea!)
- Come out. - I spilled it.
- Come out. - I wanted to do a mukbang,
- but I spilled it. - My goodness.
He's not a decent human being.
I think he spent about 20,000 dollars.
- I can smell it. - You spent 20,000 dollars, right?
- I think so. - I can't believe him.
My goodness.
Hold on. Time out. That means that fried dumpling was Se Chan's.
(She has an epiphany.)
- No, it's not. - It's yours.
- Se Chan, come here. - No, it's not me.
I didn't order any fried dumplings!
- Hey. - You had jjamppong.
- No, I only had the dumplings. - He ordered it.
- He had Chinese food. - I only spent 2,000 dollars.
- You ordered Chinese food. - It was 2,000 dollars.
- You have to stay for nine hours. - I know.
It has been three hours so far.
(They need to protect the remaining money.)
Let's not spend anymore.
- Let's keep the 40,000 dollars. - I know.
- Let's keep it. - Let's try for at least one hour.
I'm sure we're all full now, so don't order anymore.
- I smell something sweet. - What?
(She smells something sweet from Jae Seok's mouth.)
- I smell it. What did you have? - Do you know why?
He had something salty, so he needed some sugar.
Sweet and salty are the best combo.
(We caught you.)
- My goodness. - It smells like caramel, right?
It smells sweet.
(He's saved by the bell.)
We need to go.
(He runs towards his room.)
- He wants to spend more money. - I'm so mad.
Let's not spend anymore. We've spent enough.
(They return to their rooms.)
I was such a fool.
My room was the humblest.
Kwang Soo's room was paradise.
He had everything. He even had wet tissues.
I wanted to buy furniture but I didn't since it was too expensive.
They spent 40,000 dollars.
They all spent so much.
Kwang Soo is unbelievable.
(Here is the unbelievable Kwang Soo.)
I just bought rice from you.
Can you microwave this again?
(I just bought rice from you. Can you microwave this again?)
No.
(The man on the other end is curt.)
Look. I didn't even touch it.
It cooled down and hardened.
Can you microwave it for two minutes?
You need to order again.
How much is it?
You have to pay its original price.
(They're practically thieves.)
(In the end, he's left with...)
(the cold rice and soggy laver.)
(Chomp)
(It's not bad.)
(At the same time, Se Chan, who was eating the cold fried dumplings,)
(suddenly gets up.)
- Hello? - Yes?
Do you have ice cream?
A set of blankets...
One bag of chips...
A piece of fried chicken.
- One that's crispy on the outside, - Do you have jelly?
moist on the inside...
and hopefully warm drumstick.
And a glass of coke.
What's this?
(While everyone is busy spending money, Room 10...)
What's this? Why did Esom give this to me?
What does it say?
(Jae Seok received something from Esom, a mystery note!)
(During the prior open house.)
How do I give this to him?
Move back.
(Esom asked Jae Seok if he would like to drink some water.)
- Do you want some water? - Can you give me some?
- Sure. - Just a little bit.
(She secretly hands him the note with the water bottle.)
Would you like some juice?
(After spotting the mysterious note,)
(he just hid it in his pocket.)
The water...
What's this? Why did Esom give this to me?
What does it say?
(Why did Esom give it to him? What is it about?)
What? "You are Yuims Bond"?
"There is a spy who is after you."
("You are Yuims Bond. There is a spy who is after you.")
(I'm Yuims Bond?)
(And there's a spy after me?)
Yuims Bond must have read the note by now.
"You must find and eliminate the spy."
"I..."
I must make him trust me.
Please...
"I am..."
"the Bond Girl."
("I am the Bond Girl.")
- I'm Yuims Bond? - I need to protect him.
(Esom says she's the Bond Girl. There's a secret to this calm race.)
Hello, I'm Esom.
(This morning, before the Inseparable Money Race,)
Hello.
(Esom secretly arrives before the other members.)
Today, we are playing the Inseparable Money Race.
However, you will be given a special duty...
- along with the race. - Yes.
You are Yuims Bond's assistant,
the Bond Girl.
(Esom's special duty is Yuims Bond's assistant, the Bond Girl.)
- Me? - Yes?
Will I be all right?
As the Bond Girl,
you have to carry out hidden missions with Jae Seok,
who is Yuims Bond.
However,
Yuims Bond hasn't done any undercover work in four years,
so he doesn't know his identity yet.
You have to pass this on to him without the spy finding out,
find the spy, and eliminate them before Jae Seok gets tagged out...
(Pass the news and tag the spy out before Jae Seok gets tagged out!)
in order to win.
I understand.
(I will bring back Yuims Bond!)
Hello?
(First, buy a pen and paper while everyone else buys food.)
Do you have a pen and paper?
(Second, write on chopsticks wrapper to keep the note confidential.)
I bought juice and water to approach Yuims Bond.
I need to gain his trust.
(The Bond Girl carries out an elaborate strategy...)
(in order to inform Yuims Bond of his comeback.)
"There is a spy who is after you."
"You must find and eliminate the spy."
"I am the Bond Girl."
Yuims Bond?
(I'm Yuims Bond?)
(Though his weapon may be weak, his power stands strong.)
(The ruler of water guns, Yuims Bond.)
(One shot and one kill with his water gun,)
(he has finally returned.)
It has been a long time.
(It is all of the sudden though.)
(Let me hear what you've got for me.)
("Babam!" Someone might hear me.)
(Shall I head out for some water gun shooting?)
Bang!
I see the time has come. It's me, Yuims Bond.
What do you mean there's a spy after me?
This is the store. What are you talking about?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(They won't give me my water gun and there's nowhere else to ask...)
I don't know what's going on,
but I got a note and it said I'm Yuims Bond.
What am I supposed to do without a water gun?
Please purchase whatever you need.
Then send me the gadgets I'll need for my espionage.
A water gun, of course, and a car.
Car keys, a suit,
and everything else. Please have them sent to me.
- How much is it? - 5,000 dollars for the water gun.
- Yes. - The car...
is 500 billion dollars,
and the suit is 10 billion dollars.
I'm sorry, but are you out of your mind?
(The prices are unbelievable.)
Send me the water gun, then.
(The clueless Yuims Bond reaches an agreement...)
(and buys just the 5,000 dollar water gun.)
It's going to show through this.
The water gun's going to show.
First of all, I was so scared...
that they might come see my room.
Since I have this pen.
(They mustn't see my pen...)
(Just then,)
Thank you.
(Yuims Bond water gun arrives.)
(Seeing it in a long time, it's bigger than he thought.)
(Let me try it out...)
(It's empty!)
The water...
Hello?
It's empty!
The special solution is 5,000 dollars.
Gosh.
Please send it quickly.
(Although he feels ripped-off, he buys the solution.)
How much was it?
(The 5,000 dollar special solution arrives.)
(But it's bigger than he expected.)
All right.
(He has a water gun and a huge bottle of solution.)
I'm going to get caught for sure, if I have that bottle in here.
(He must hide it carefully in order to hide from the spy.)
It says "water gun" here...
(It says "water gun" here...)
I'll erase it.
(While Yuims Bond and the Bond Girl focus on hiding their identity,)
(the siren goes off.)
Oh no.
(It's the third open house, so she hides it under the food tray.)
(Their identities will get caught if their rooms are open to the others.)
(What will happen to the Bond Girl and Yuims Bond?)
(3rd open house)
I hope no one ordered anything.
Please!
Come on!
This is...
(How much will they have left this time?)
Someone spent money again?
(They promised not to use it.)
How much does it read?
Is there even anything left to buy?
Why can't you save it?
There really wasn't anything left to buy.
- I even took a nap. - Really?
You all ate already!
I didn't have anything to do, either.
(Congratulations on your comeback.)
- I was too full to eat anything. - What...
(Someone else must have bought something for their room, too.)
- Who used the 80,000 dollars? - Who was it?
Then let's decide with a game.
- Since we have the line drawn. - Yes.
First place gets to choose which room to see.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Just first place? - Good.
Whoever throws their shoe closest to the inner line.
- If it goes over, you're out. - If it goes over, you're out?
- If it goes over? - You're out if it goes over.
You're out if it goes past the line.
- All right. - Yes.
(She slides next to Yuims Bond.)
- First place chooses a room. - Of course.
Shoot!
(Seok Jin's try.)
(It's quite close to the line!)
- That was good. - Next!
(Seok Jin is quite good!)
I'm going to win.
(The next player, Kwang Soo, is currently winning.)
It's a tie.
(Kyung Nam tries after Ji Hyo.)
- It went past! - Wow.
He's winning.
(They're all good.)
Next is Esom.
(While everyone shows off their unexpected talent,)
(the Bond Girl Esom tries next.)
(If either Esom or Jae Seok doesn't win,)
(their rooms may be revealed!)
- It's out. - Out!
(A clear out.)
- It's a home run! - I'll go next.
- Out. - It's the first out.
That's so disappointing.
Next, Se Chan.
(Next is Se Chan.)
(It landed in the line, but the shoelace is sticking out!)
- What happened? - Isn't this okay?
- Why? - It's okay.
- The shoelace. - Out!
- You won't accept this? - Out!
- It's out. - The shoelace is sticking out.
It's my turn!
Move over!
(With the Bond Girl out, Yuims Bond is facing a crisis!)
(Jae Seok has to win,)
(in order to protect the room with the water gun!)
(Please...)
(It flew and landed on the line!)
What?
(A perfect winner)
This is...
This is unbelievable.
That is amazing.
(Yuims Bond got the hang of it and they'll reveal the room he chooses!)
- I choose Kyung Nam's room. - Go ahead and see.
(Let's go see Kyung Nam's room!)
- It's Room One. - This way.
- There's nothing in there. - I doubt there will be anything.
Let's see your room, Kyung Nam.
(There really isn't anything in his room.)
Nothing. My room is spotless.
- I'm... - It's empty.
really...
- What? - It's true!
- You didn't buy anything? - You didn't eat anything?
I never used the intercom. Look.
The intercom fell on the floor.
He really didn't buy anything.
I didn't even eat anything.
It doesn't smell.
Then where did all the money go?
- Who did it? - Who spent the 80,000 dollars?
Kyung Nam really didn't do anything.
I told you...
Are you sure you didn't eat the wrappers as well?
- The wrappers? - Just in case.
- Kyung Nam is very honest. - He's prudent.
I've concluded that...
you don't suit variety shows.
(You don't suit variety shows.)
(Yuims Bond makes a harsh comment.)
- You don't... - Why are you talking like that?
- He doesn't fit in. - It's his first time here.
You don't fit here.
- It's his first time here. - You don't fit here.
(The harsh comment makes him look back on today...)
(where he didn't even use the toilet in order to follow the rules.)
Okay.
- Come on. - Okay.
- Let's go back in. - Please hold it in.
We need the money.
There's nothing to do.
(Everyone has entered their cells.)
Seeing that Jae Seok kept...
insisting on seeing...
Kyung Nam's room,
(Seeing that Yuims Bond insisted on seeing Kyun Nam's room...)
I think he's suspecting Kyung Nam.
(I think he's suspecting Kyung Nam as the spy.)
I don't think the money is the main part of this game.
Jae Seok is quiet, too.
(The silent Yuims Bond is getting his water gun ready.)
(He cannot hide the huge bottle, so he gives it to Kwon Ryeol.)
Kwon Ryeol.
(He hides the big bottle by giving it to Kwon Ryeol.)
(4th open house)
What's happening?
Who was it?
Someone used it again.
It's really weird timing.
Where's Kyung Nam?
I bet he ate that cup noodles.
Kyung Nam, come on out!
- I think he ate it. - He ate it 100 percent.
- He couldn't wait. - I don't want it anymore.
- Kyung Nam! - What were you doing?
- You're late. - I fell asleep.
I fell asleep.
Did you eat the cup noodles?
- No, I fell asleep. - I think he did sleep.
There's something on his hair.
He did fall asleep.
- He slept? - Yes.
How do you fall asleep? Was there even a blanket?
You have about three hours left.
There's really nothing to do...
- in there. - Right.
- Totally. - You're right.
- I had no one to talk to. - Right.
I couldn't talk to anyone.
(Yuims Bond and the Bond Girl have a more important mission.)
Who could be the spy?
We're just taking a break!
We're letting you pass this time.
(It could seem like everyone is trying to save the money.)
I'm coming to get you!
What are you eating this time?
(It could seem like everyone is trying to save the money.)
I can't figure out who the spy is.
This is how people go crazy...
after being locked up in here.
How are we supposed to find the spy?
Are we allowed to take the prize or what?
(Someone is definitely a spy among these 8 people.)
Would it be unfavorable...
to someone who spends too much?
I have a job to do!
I have no clue.
What is this?
Good.
- It didn't change. - It didn't change.
- No one spent it. - No one spent it.
Good, good.
It has passed nine hours, everyone.
(9 hours of solitary confinement is finished.)
Somehow there's still some left.
Very good.
Now, 19,300 dollars will be divided...
into each and every one of you.
- That's 1,930 dollars each. - Okay.
Let's go shopping.
The final mission for you to achieve the individual prize...
is "Money Race".
Money Race?
Hidden inside this building are 10 individual vaults...
with your prize, 1,930 dollars, inside them.
(10 vaults hold 1,930 dollars in each one.)
And there's also the vault of Host S...
with the total prize, 19,300 dollars inside it.
It has the total prize in it.
After you earn your individual prize...
by opening a vault with your name tag on it,
if you find the vault of Host S,
you will be given the total prize.
- That's a lot of money. - And that's it?
It's over when I find mine, then the host's?
- Correct. - That's amazing.
Head to your own starting points,
- and start the race. - Come on!
- Okay! - Let's go win 19,300 dollars.
You know you're not going to win.
- I'm going to win. - How can you do that?
- I'm going to win. - Let's go...
find my vault!
(Money Race has begun.)
I need to find the vault.
(You need to find your vault first!)
I'm motivated today.
(Where's my vault?)
I'm in a rush.
(While everyone is looking for their vaults,)
Where's...
(Yuims Bond and the Bond Girl...)
(try to secretly meet.)
- Why did you give me the note? - What?
Why did you give me the note?
- You didn't read it? - I read it.
(Will they able to catch the spy and accomplish the mission?)
What?
Why did you give me the note?
- You didn't read it? - I read it.
(Jae Seok & Esom finally have a proper conversation.)
(He checked the note.)
- I know I'm Yuims Bond. - Yes.
(I know I'm Yuims Bond.)
So, who's the spy?
We're supposed to figure that out.
- You don't know who it is? - No.
So what are we supposed to do with the water gun?
Do we fire it on the back to eliminate them?
Here is your mission.
When the members find each vault with the individual prize in it,
they're infected by money poison.
"Money Poison"?
When they're infected by it,
they must be shot with Yuims Bond's water gun vaccine.
Otherwise, they will be eliminated.
So we're here to save our members?
(Yuims Bond's job is to save them, not eliminate them.)
When one member is eliminated due to the infection,
or Yuims Bond is eliminated by the spy,
the race is over.
But we don't know who it is.
When a member finds his or her vault, it will be announced.
Also, the vaccinated member will be...
taken by the guards to be isolated in the infirmary...
- until the race is finished. - Okay.
But the spy is immune to the money poison,
therefore they will not be isolated.
And?
Yuims Bond must fire the water gun...
at the spy's face when you find out who it is.
And the Bond Girl's job...
is to help Yuims Bond save the members...
without being suspected,
and to find and eliminate the spy.
You have a critical role.
(Mission comprehended.)
It sounds difficult. It's complicated.
(Money Poison will be coming soon.)
What does that vault look like?
(The members are only focused on finding the vault.)
I found something!
(Did he find a vault?)
- Right? - Wait!
Whose is it?
- It was nothing. - What?
(What Haha found was...)
It's garbage!
It was nothing.
(That's garbage, Haha.)
Come on.
I'm sorry.
This is embarrassing.
I thought...
I found it.
Let's find out where it is.
(There's something!)
I found it.
(He found a vault under the desk.)
It's mine.
(The vault belongs to...)
(Se Chan!)
(The password of each vault is their dates of birth.)
It worked.
(10 minutes remaining for him to be vaccinated.)
Yang Se Chan...
has found his vault.
(Now he needs to find the vault of Host S!)
(Yuims Bond heard the announcement.)
- This is terrible. - Where are you going?
- What's terrible? - I have to go.
What's terrible? Where are you going?
(He must find Se Chan in 10 minutes to fire a shot on his name tag.)
- Where are you going? - This is bad.
Se Chan found it?
I have to find him.
This is terrible.
I have to vaccinate him.
Where is he?
(If Se Chan is not vaccinated in 10 minutes, the race is over.)
It's so hot.
(And at that moment,)
(she found Se Chan!)
Did you find it?
Not yet.
But they announced it!
(We just announced that he found the vault.)
You heard that?
- I did. - Yes, I found it.
(After the 9-hour lockup, no one trusts anyone.)
(I have to tell Yuims Bond where he is.)
(Yuims Bond is also looking for Se Chan.)
There he is.
(Jae Seok has finally found Se Chan.)
(Se Chan is coming right towards Yuims Bond.)
(His water gun vaccine is locked and loaded.)
How did you find it?
In an out-of-the-way place.
That's amazing.
You're amazing.
(When Se Chan walks into a dead end,)
I have to find mine too.
(Jae Seok cautiously follows Se Chan.)
(He's being cautious since he doesn't know the spy.)
Hey.
How many are there?
I don't think he's here.
(Kyung Nam and the Bond Girl walk up together.)
- He's not here. - Let's see.
He's not here.
- Where have you looked? - I was...
on the fifth floor.
(I hope he succeeds.)
I looked around the fifth floor.
(He's left alone with Se Chan thanks to the Bond Girl.)
How many are there?
- There's only one? - Yes.
(It's time...)
(to vaccinate infected Se Chan.)
(The water gun vaccine is locked and loaded.)
(When Se Chan looks away,)
(he fires the vaccine!)
- You go first. - Thanks.
You go first.
(He successfully fires it at his name tag.)
(Se Chan doesn't even know he was vaccinated.)
Thank you.
You're going to thank me later.
I saved your life.
What?
What's going on?
I'm eliminated?
How? Why?
What's happening? I'm eliminated?
(He's going to the infirmary, not the prison.)
What did I do wrong?
Was my name tag ripped?
- This is the infirmary. - What?
You have been infected by Money Poison,
and now you will be given treatment here.
(What treatment?)
I'm infected by Money Poison?
(While Se Chan's Money Poison is being treated...)
Where could...
the vault be?
(Where is my vault?)
(He found a vault!)
(The vault he found belongs to...)
(Gosh, that surprised me!)
(The vault belongs to...)
(Lee Kwang Soo.)
(He punches in the password.)
Lee Kwang Soo has opened his vault.
- Kwang Soo. - What was that?
- Was it Kwang Soo? - He found his vault.
- Did you find your vault? - Yes.
I am going to do this.
You...
(Kwang Soo, here comes Yuims Bond!)
I am going to do this today.
Kwang Soo, did you find the vault?
Yes.
(Yuims Bond chases after the excited Kwang Soo.)
My vault was here, so...
(He readies the vaccine.)
(At that moment,)
(he sees the water gun.)
That's incredible.
(Jae Seok fails.)
(He takes a different route so that he doesn't get caught.)
- Did you really find your vault? - Yes.
I found it right away.
(Yuims Bond lost an opportunity to administer the vaccine.)
Kwang Soo saw me.
(Did Kwang Soo figure out Yuims Bond's identity?)
(Yuims Bond and the Bond Girl meet again.)
- Do you know who the spy is? - What?
I have no clue.
Be careful. We have a lot of eyes on us.
I saved Se Chan. I need to save Kwang Soo now.
Please distract Kwang Soo.
(The Bong Girl gets to work.)
- Kwang Soo! - Yes?
(While the Bond Girl catches Kwang Soo's attention,)
It's not like I can tell you anything.
(Yuims Bond moves behind his back.)
Who is that?
(He diverts Kwang Soo's attention.)
- Who is that? - Did you find something?
(Kwang Soo's head is turned,)
(so this is a chance.)
(When Kwang Soo has his back on Jae Seok,)
I saved your life, Kwang Soo.
(he tries to shoot the water gun again.)
(Spraying)
(Since the first shot landed on the hat,)
(he shoots the name tag again.)
I saved two people.
What? Why am I being dragged away?
Where am I going? Where am I going?
- What is this? - What happened to you?
(They meet at the infirmary.)
I don't know why I am here.
What is that?
What is that on your back?
- What? - There is something green on it.
Is there something on my back?
- Yes, there is! - What?
What?
- Who did it? When? - Let me take a look.
- It's green. - It's on your back, too.
(By whom and when did this happen?)
Could it be Jae Seok?
- It's green. - Right?
- Jae Seok was Yuims Bond. - That's right.
(They are 100 percent sure it's Jae Seok.)
When did Jae Seok shoot me?
Then S could be Jae Seok's S.
It could also be Esom's S.
It could be Se Chan.
It could be you, Kwang Soo.
(Is Kwang Soo the Host S?)
Let's stop.
(They don't know who Host S is.)
This is driving me crazy.
Maybe it's outside. Where is it?
(He is diligently searching for the vault to win the prize.)
(What is that?)
(I hope it's not trash.)
I can't believe it.
Haha has found his vault.
(The fact he found his vault gets announced to everyone.)
(Haha has 10 minutes until he gets vaccinated.)
(Haha gets infected by Money Poison.)
I need to find Host S' vault.
(He needs to get vaccinated in 10 minutes.)
(Yuims Bond and the Bond Girl found out about Haha's infection.)
Who was that?
Haha.
(If Haha found the vault...)
I saw Haha's vault on the second floor.
- The second floor. - Where the radish is.
Where the radish is? I should go there.
Hold on.
- I will look for him. - Don't let anyone approach him.
(They spread out on the 2nd floor and look for Haha.)
(Find Haha and vaccinate him.)
Where is mine?
(Did she find a vault?)
(She found...)
It's Ji Hyo's.
What should I do? I will tell her when I see her.
Okay. Ji Hyo's vault is here.
- Ji Hyo! Your vault is here. - Really?
(Ji Hyo succeeds to find her vault.)
Ji Hyo, have you seen my vault?
I swear this is the first time I am seeing a vault.
Thank you, So Min.
(This is the first time she is seeing a vault.)
For goodness' sake.
(Thanks to So Min, she found her vault.)
Song Ji Hyo has found her vault.
(Yuims Bond hears the announcement while he is looking for Haha.)
So Min, did you find yours?
- I found Ji Hyo's vault. - For goodness' sake.
This is a disaster.
I need to hurry up and get them. What should I do?
(Ji Hyo is infected by Money Poison.)
I found it.
Ji Hyo, I am jealous.
- I found it. - My goodness.
So it was here.
(He approaches her fast.)
Is there money inside?
No, there is the prize coupon.
- Let me see it. - Here.
The prize coupon.
(Spraying)
(My goodness!)
(What is he doing?)
I saved your life.
Don't say a word. I saved your life.
You will find out later. Don't tell anyone.
(He succeeds to vaccinate Song Ji Hyo.)
(While Ji Hyo gets vaccinated,)
Here it is! Okay, I found it.
(Seok Jin gets infected by Money Poison.)
Okay.
I need to find Haha.
Seok Jin has found his vault.
Where is he? Where is Seok Jin?
Seok Jin!
- I found it. - Where was it?
- I found it. - That's incredible. Seok Jin.
- Did you find yours? - I need to find Host S' vault.
- Let's find it. - All right.
(Spraying)
(He succeeds to vaccinate Seok Jin.)
- I need to find Host S' vault. - Okay.
Let's do this today.
Okay.
(Seok Jin, have fun at the infirmary.)
I did it. I sent him off in a good mood.
I sent him off in a good mood.
(I am the happiest.)
I have a good feeling about this.
(It doesn't last long.)
Okay! What?
What is going on?
(You need to be isolated now.)
(Time passed quickly while Jae Seok kept himself busy.)
Ji Hyo.
(About 4 minutes remain until Haha's treatment.)
Did you find your vault? What is going on?
(At that moment!)
(Haha sees Ji Hyo get dragged away to the infirmary.)
What is going on?
(Haha, bye.)
(What is this situation?)
I saw it.
(Why did she get dragged away?)
(Not only that,)
What is going on?
(Seok Jin is getting dragged away as well.)
Those who found their vaults get eliminated.
(Yuims Bond is searching for Haha.)
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
You can get eliminated.
You can get eliminated?
Those who found their vaults got eliminated.
Really? Then you must be a target.
- You found your vault. - That's right.
Then you will get eliminated.
Bye, Haha.
I am so annoyed.
This isn't a prison.
Will we be released after we get treated?
They say that, but this is nothing more than a prison.
There is hope. I am not out. I am getting treated.
- You are out. - We are out.
You are out.
You aren't out. I can assure you...
that isn't the case. This isn't a prison,
but an infirmary.
- Hey, come here. - Come here.
(I have no patience for your nonsense.)
He is making fun of us.
You need to stop spouting nonsense.
- Seriously. - Come here.
This is a prison. We are out.
(The infirmary is full of despair and fury.)
I need to find Haha. Haha.
(About 1 minute remains.)
(At that moment!)
Haha.
Jae Seok, what is going on?
- What do you mean? - Those who found their vaults...
got eliminated.
You were by Seok Jin's side...
before he got eliminated. I saw you.
(What is that in his hand?)
Hold on. I think...
(Haha finally figures out what is going on.)
- You have been hiding it. - I am saving your life.
I am saving your life. Listen to me.
- Listen to me. - Hold on.
You will die otherwise.
What are you talking about?
Let go of me.
(Time passes while Haha resists.)
(Jae Seok uses a takedown.)
- My goodness. - I got him.
(Using his hunting skills,)
I am sorry.
(he succeeds to vaccinate Haha.)
Haha, I saved your life.
I can't believe it.
(The Bond Girl thinks about who the spy might be.)
Where is the spy? Who is the spy?
This spy isn't doing anything.
People I haven't seen are...
Kyung Nam...
- Kyung Nam. - Yes?
What did you do all day today?
(With a strange laugh, he approaches Yuims Bond.)
Hold on.
Have you found your vault?
No, I haven't.
- Have you? - No. I am still searching.
- Really? - Where have you been?
- What? - Where have you been?
I was searching for my vault.
- Were you here all along? - Yes.
I was on my way out since my vault isn't here.
Don't you have anything?
(Scary)
No, I don't.
- Really? - I have nothing.
I heard that you are carrying something.
- I am? - Yes.
Something.
- Who said that? - What?
Who said that?
I heard that you are carrying something.
I am not carrying anything.
Really?
- You are acting strange. - No, no.
Everyone said you are acting strange.
- Me? - Yes.
I am simply searching.
- Really? - Yes.
- You are simply searching. - Yes.
You keep questioning me.
It's just that I heard something.
- Really? - Yes.
In any case, I will go and look for my vault.
(Yuims Bond leaves cautiously.)
(At that moment!)
(Kyung Nam chases after Yuims Bond.)
(Why is he following me?)
- Why do you keep... - No, no.
(Jae Seok doesn't have a clue about the spy.)
I just wanted to see your back.
My back?
I am not trying to do anything.
(Jae Seok's suspicion grows as Kyung Nam closes in.)
It looks like you are trying to do something.
No.
(Approaching slowly)
(Kyung Nam is right in front of Jae Seok.)
(Yuims Bond starts to run.)
(Kyung Nam goes back instead of chasing after him.)
Kyung Nam is being strange.
(Why is he going back?)
(At the peaceful infirmary)
I'm going to the restroom.
Don't get caught by...
- members who aren't eliminated. - Okay.
(He must be in a hurry.)
(While Kwang Soo goes to the restroom...)
Goodness.
What's this?
What now?
- What's wrong? - There's a quail egg.
(She has a quail egg in her hood.)
Did you put it in?
No.
Why is there a quail egg in my hood?
- I have one too. - What?
- There's a quail egg. - What's this?
I don't have one.
(Only Ji Hyo and Se Chan have a quail egg.)
Someone must put a quail egg in it.
Where's Kwang Soo?
(At that time, Kwang Soo disappeared.)
(After saying he's going to the restroom, he headed to...)
(a meeting room.)
(Why did Kwang Soo come here?)
Two letters.
(He says out of the blue.)
(What does he mean by "two letters"?)
(Kwang Soo receives a mysterious mission card.)
Kwang Soo is my special friend.
I'm here to ask you to make a race where Kwang Soo can win.
(Host S, Shin Ha Kyun)
Four years ago, he was selected as Yuims Bond's successor.
Then he was eliminated.
After what happened, Kwang Soo betrayed a lot.
He got spoiled.
(Kwang Soo wasn't like this before.)
I'm curious if you gave him second chance.
It's a pity.
I believe that Kwang Soo can pull off many things.
I have no doubt.
Please give him an opportunity...
to take revenge on Jae Seok.
(Revenge on Yuims Bond)
(Thanks to the special friend's request,)
(the mission is passed to Kwang Soo.)
Keep your identity a secret until the final race.
You'll succeed if you eliminate Jae Seok.
Do I get all the prize?
- You'll win 100,000 dollars. - 100,000 dollars?
- Do I take it all? - Yes.
If you fail, you will be penalized alone.
However,
you must find out...
how to eliminate Jae Seok on your own.
During the race that starts soon,
purchase nine quail eggs.
Quail eggs that I know?
Yes.
10 quail eggs, please.
(He orders quail eggs.)
(What do I have to do with quail eggs?)
(He finds a mission card in his vault.)
"The method to eliminate Jae Seok consists of nine letters."
"Each time you put a quail egg in other members' clothes."
"you'll be given one letter."
- This jacket looks strange. - Really?
(To eliminate Yuims Bond,)
(he put quail eggs in others' clothes.)
How many chairs are there?
(Kwang Soo was successful with Se Chan and Ji Hyo.)
If I figure out what it is...
and clear the mission,
is it over? Okay.
"Ki".
(The first letter is "Ki".)
"Ae"?
(The second letter is "Ae".)
("Ki" and "Ae")
To something something, do something something.
It's something like that.
(What's the method to eliminate Yuims Bond?)
I don't have time.
I think Jae Seok is almost finished.
(Before people find out who the spy is,)
(he must figure out how to eliminate Jae Seok.)
- Jong Kook. - He's still here.
You aren't eliminated yet.
I am eliminated, but I came back.
- How? - I don't know.
(He checks his 3 targets.)
No way. Are you eliminated?
- But you found the vault. - Yes.
- Why? - It's strange that you came out.
(Members start to suspect.)
It wasn't a prison. It was an infirmary.
- An infirmary. - Were you treated?
- Did you really leave? - Yes.
- Were you treated? - Yes.
Your face doesn't tell that you've been treated.
My face?
(His face is poisoned with money.)
How can you tell based on my face?
- I don't think he was treated. - I was.
What should we do?
What do we do? A lot was revealed, including Jae Seok's identity.
We can't pretend that we don't know.
- What do we do? - Shall we look for the vault?
I couldn't find my vault. I looked everywhere.
I can't find mine either.
There's no Host S' vault either.
- Are you sure you couldn't find it? - No.
I only saw Seok Jin's.
I think you should find your vault.
I came back from the infirmary.
I bet you found your vault, and Jae Seok gave you the water gun.
(Are Jae Seok and Kwang Soo on the same team?)
That's why...
Search him if he has a water gun.
Search him now.
(A sudden inspection starts.)
- There's no way. - Isn't he suspicious?
(Quail eggs are hidden in Kwang Soo's pocket.)
(They might find out who he is.)
There's no way.
His vault was easier to find than I thought.
(Just then,)
(Kwang Soo hides his quail eggs with his hand.)
His vault was easier to find than I thought.
- Stand up. - Why are you searching everywhere?
(Will he avert the crisis?)
Is there anything in your pockets?
No.
We have to undress him.
- He hides things in strange places. - He does.
(It's necessary to strip him down.)
Would I put a water gun there?
- Here's why. - Would I put a water gun there?
He must be searched as thoroughly...
as they do in prison.
(Speechless)
Don't say that in front of Kyung Nam.
- It's in that movie. - Right.
- "Get on all fours." - Come on.
"Get on all fours and cough."
Why would you cough?
Didn't you see those movies?
Does a water gun come out if you get on all fours and cough?
- It's nonsense. - They do.
Never.
Haven't you tried it?
- I know. I saw it in a movie. - Didn't you see it?
It's upsetting.
Did he put quail eggs in your clothes?
No.
He didn't have time for that. I was watching you.
Are there quail eggs?
Why is it quail eggs?
Does "quail" mean...
"infer the grasshopper"?
(Infer the grasshopper?)
- That isn't bad. - I agree.
Why is it quail?
Chaser of a grasshopper, Lee Kwang Soo.
(He makes up phrases.)
That's not bad.
Right? Chaser of a grasshopper, Lee Kwang Soo.
That's not bad, Seok Jin.
Do you think...
two of them are plotting all this?
(They have no idea what's going on.)
Have you seen Jae Seok?
- What? - Have you seen Jae Seok?
No.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Who are you?
I don't know. I'm just looking for S.
(He's questioning like a detective.)
- What? - Who are you?
(He's flustered by pressure from Jong Kook.)
What do you mean?
Who are you?
Tell me who you are.
If you want to say something, say it.
(Detective Jong Kook leads him on.)
(If I want to say something, say it?)
Can you close your eyes and stay still for 10 seconds?
(Can you close your eyes and stay still for 10 seconds?)
(Let me put a quail egg in your clothes.)
(The most simple and suspicious in all the 10 years.)
Stay like this for 10 seconds.
(Since it already turned out this way...)
Don't do anything.
10 seconds?
That's too strange.
Is there any other way?
Why did you ask me to tell you?
- Why? - You should think of other ways.
We can't play Roses of Sharon.
- Let's play that game. - The two of us?
I mean...
(He's getting more suspicious.)
- It's hard. - I don't understand exactly.
I don't understand.
What's certain is that we must find it.
Find what?
The box.
The secret key.
(He sounds so awkward.)
Kwang Soo.
The roses of Sharon have blossomed.
Don't peek!
(Help me properly, Jong Kook.)
(There must be something.)
Wait.
Are you saying that I should find my vault?
(He's getting exhausted.)
I'll do it.
- Kwang Soo, either way, - Yes?
(Dropping)
(He successfully puts in a quail egg.)
(He manages to put it in.)
We have to hurry and catch Jae Seok.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
(He receives another letter.)
You're behind.
Jae Seok... What is it?
Esom, did you find it?
(Esom passes by randomly.)
What? The vault?
- I couldn't find it. - Did you find the vault?
You couldn't?
(Everyone goes their ways to find the vault.)
(Wait!)
(Is Kwang Soo walking around when he got shot by a water gun?)
(What happened?)
(Esom saw Kwang Soo getting shot by a water gun.)
(The spy doesn't get treated in isolation.)
I'll go this way and look for it.
- Where? - I'll go this way.
(Kwang Soo is the spy.)
(She must tell Yuims Bond that Kwang Soo is the spy.)
(Kwang Soo obtains "Jae".)
"Jae".
What are you doing?
(He tries his mission on So Min as well.)
- Why are you doing this? - Wait.
(He puts in a quail egg.)
(He also obtains "Li".)
(While Kwang Soo is doing well...)
Kyung Nam is very strange.
(Yuims Bond suspects Kyung Nam.)
I'm sure that Kyung Nam is the spy.
He keeps looking for me.
(Kyung Nam is sacrificed for Kwang Soo's mission.)
(Kwang Soo obtains "Gyal".)
("Gyal")
"Gyal" definitely refers to eggs.
("Gyal" definitely refers to eggs.)
("Ki", "Ae", "Li", "Jae", and "Gyal")
It's something related to eggs.
(Eggs)
Put an egg in Jae Seok's something.
Put an egg in Jae Seok's body?
(Put an egg in Jae Seok's body?)
(As he finds out the way to eliminate Jae Seok,)
(Esom has come to Yuims Bond.)
Jae Seok.
I saw Kwang Soo, he got out from the infirmary.
He was with Jong Kook.
Didn't you shoot him with a water gun?
Kwang Soo got out?
He did.
He's coming.
Kwang Soo is the spy.
(Kwang Soo is the spy.)
(Yuims Bond has figured out who the spy is.)
(And the spy shows up.)
(Kwang Soo also spots Jae Seok.)
- What are you doing over there? - What are you doing?
What are you doing over there?
What are you doing?
(Why is Esom with him?)
Jae Seok.
(Yuims Bond wins if he shoots his water gun at his face.)
(He doesn't know exactly how to eliminate Jae Seok.)
Go to him.
It's Kwang Soo.
Catch Kwang Soo.
(Their chase starts.)
(He hides himself in the infirmary.)
What?
(What's going on?)
It's Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
(He's completely surrounded.)
Kwang Soo, what are you doing?
What?
Lee Kwang Soo.
(They're standing with a door in between.)
(Yuims Bond wins if he shoots water at Kwang Soo's face.)
(At that time)
Kim Kyung Nam has found the vault.
(He found the vault?)
Wait.
(Kyung Nam finds the vault hidden in the meeting room.)
(Kyung Nam is infected by Money Poison.)
(Unless he's vaccinated in 10 minutes, the race is over.)
Eliminate Kyung Nam.
I'll go in with Kyung Nam and eliminate Kwang Soo.
(Yuims Bond goes to find Kyung Nam.)
What's going on?
He isn't eliminated.
- Wait. - What's with the quail egg?
(It's his last chance to turn the tables.)
Aren't these quail eggs?
(He attempts to clear his mission on Seok Jin.)
- Stop it. - What is it?
What is it?
Stop it.
(And)
It went in.
(He puts a quail egg in his mouth.)
It went in his mouth.
(He successfully puts in a quail egg.)
- Hey. - It went into his body.
- What is it? - What is it?
What is it?
- Seriously. - What is it?
(He obtains "Kkae".)
"Kkae"?
("Kkae")
Against Jae Seok's something,
break an egg.
("Li" remains.)
"Li"?
It's his head.
"Break an egg on Jae Seok's head."
("Break an egg on Jae Seok's head.")
- He's not eliminated. - That is correct.
Okay, okay.
(If he breaks an egg on Jae Seok's head, he wins.)
It's over once I break it.
All right. Let's go.
I'm in trouble.
I have to eliminate him.
(He goes to catch Yuims Bond.)
Where are you going, Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo!
(It's Esom's voice.)
(Kwang Soo came out.)
Where are you going?
Don't follow me.
Don't.
(She goes after Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo wins once he breaks an egg on Jae Seok's head.)
(Jae Seok wins once he shoots water on Kwang Soo's face.)
(At that time)
(Yuims Bond spots Kwang Soo first.)
(He sees Jae Seok approaching.)
Why are you out here?
Jae Seok.
Why are you...
Why did you shoot water at me?
You should be eliminated.
- Why are you out here? - I mean...
(Yuims Bond versus Spy)
(4 years ago, Kwang Soo took...)
(a test to become Yuims Bond's successor.)
I trust your judgment.
(During the last successor test, he was eliminated as he betrayed.)
I knew it.
I knew you'd betray me.
(After 4 years,)
(they face each other again.)
- What? - How is this saving me?
It's to save you.
(It's the last battle to end their ill-fated relationship.)
Why are you out here?
(Will he shoot water at Kwang Soo's face?)
How is this saving me?
(Will he break an egg on Jae Seok's head?)
- It's to save you. - Look behind you.
(He shoots.)
(When Kwang Soo moves, Jae Seok sprays water.)
(Water hits Kwang Soo right on his face.)
(Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
You punk.
(I can't end like this.)
(Breaking)
(I waited 4 years.)
(I won't let you leave in peace.)
(He throws raw eggs with resentment.)
(It's a ceremony where they pat each other on the head.)
- Hey. - What?
- Let go. - This isn't the end.
(Yuims Bond is the final winner.)
I broke the egg.
(The final race ends.)
Everyone.
He invited you here.
All of you are curious about him.
- Here is Host S. - What?
What?
- Please come out. - Who is it?
Is S coming out now?
It must be a video.
- Is it a video? - Is it?
He's really here.
Goodness.
(Spy Kwang Soo's guardian)
- Hello. - Ha Kyun.
Ha Kyun.
(Host S is Shin Ha Kyun.)
- What? - What's with Ha Kyun?
Isn't it too late for him to come out?
Ha Kyun.
Why did you come out earlier?
Ha Kyun will give...
Yuims Bond and the Bond Girl, Esom,
an honorable gold card.
Thank you.
"Honorable"?
- It's real. - "Honorable".
(It's an honorable golden color.)
- It's real gold. - It really is.
Let's hear from him.
Seriously.
I didn't expect Ha Kyun to come out at the end.
It's his first time on a variety show, so it's sad.
(You're right.)
It's his first time on a variety show,
but he hasn't yet said a word.
I feel so awkward.
During the show opening,
the three of you who appeared on the same movie made a pledge.
If you reach five million in the audience,
you'll join us...
on the show.
If five million is okay,
can you join us?
Come with Kyung Nam and Esom.
- They promised. - All of us?
That's right.
(What will be Ha Kyun's response?)
Okay.
Ha Kyun promised.
As he responded,
he didn't seem to feel good about it.
- It's five million. - Right.
If it reaches five million, he'll be happy and come out.
- Of course. - Come on, it's five million.
Lastly,
Kwang Soo failed his mission today.
We prepared to hit him today.
As he disappointed his special friend,
his special friend gets to spank him.
I see.
Please take your position.
I don't know about Ha Kyun.
- I wonder how he will hit him. - How will he?
- Ha Kyun plays golf these days. - Does he?
He has a high batting average.
(He's in the best condition to hit.)
Take a comfortable position.
- How hard will you hit? - Don't get nervous.
(Nervous)
Do well, Kwang Soo.
(He changes completely.)
Okay.
(Thud)
That was hard.
Good shot.
That must hurt.
- That was intense. - Ha Kyun controlled it.
Let's clap for him.
Today's winners are Yuims Bond and the Bond Girl.
(The race is over with the victory of Yuims Bond and the Bond Girl.)
(One day, everyone's name disappeared.)
(Nine new name tags)
(Another man searches his name.)
(This Person, That Person, That Person Afar)
(We cannot be called...)
(with names that we knew.)
(Recover your real name.)
(Where is my real name that I had all my life?)
(Unique and strange names come together.)
(Will the shoot be over if you give up and change your name?)
(Does someone else have my name?)
(It's a dangerous journey to retrieve their names again.)
(Who will stop being nameless?)
You guys are...
terrible.
("Your Name")