- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Hi. - Hi.
Is it nice to meet us?
(Is it nice to meet us?)
- "Is it nice to meet us?" - Hold on.
- Be quiet. - "Is it nice to meet us?"
They didn't hear me. Be quiet.
Let's go inside and take a seat.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
(He spots something.)
- What? - Your pants...
- It's fashionable. - It's like you downsized the jeans.
You just put a button over here.
- No. - You just pulled it hard.
Your jeans look unique.
I see. That's how it's designed.
- Yes, that's right. - That's how it was designed?
- It looks like something is off. - It was designed this way.
They don't look weird.
By the way, you don't feel nervous, do you?
- What do you mean? - The fan-meet is over.
No, I've been nervous continuously.
How should I put it?
He's a professional. He really is.
- You ought to be on your toes. - Right.
- Of course. - That's just me.
- I don't mean that. - We ought to be on our best game.
A part of my chest felt nervous for some reason.
That's not where your chest is. Isn't that where your pancreas is?
(That's not where your chest is. Isn't that where your pancreas is?)
- Or ribs. - Do you have a bad pancreas?
That's terrible.
- Which organ is that? - They are driving me crazy.
- This is where my chest is. - I see.
This is where my heart is, so my chest should be here.
It's because you pointed out that your heart is at the bottom.
- Why are you joining in? - What?
(Why are you joining in?)
- When he's talking, be quiet. - What do you mean?
You were pointing to some weird part, that's why.
I just went like this.
(Taking turns teasing Seok Jin.)
Actually,
we recorded the fan-meet quite a long time ago,
- but the final one aired yesterday. - That's right.
- I like that song. SORAN's song. - Which one?
(Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok feel proud.)
I see.
- The lyrics were really good. - I told you.
- I told you it was the best song. - Right. Their song was great.
The lyrics were completely based on So Min's experience.
By the way, you wrote such great lyrics.
The lyrics were great.
The lyrics were trendy.
You should write the lyrics for Jong Kook's new album.
- What? - For Jong Kook's new album.
- No, no. - Jong Kook...
- Jong Kook. - That'd be great.
He talks like that when he really hates something.
Her lyrics are great, but they don't match me.
- She can make it work. - They don't suit my song.
Why don't you like them?
- No, they are great. - I really liked them.
I asked her to write lyrics for my song.
- For your song? - He wanted them for a reggae song.
I asked her to write lyrics for a reggae song.
Haha, there's one about fried chicken.
- Fried chicken? - Is that for a ballad song?
Yes, it's for a ballad song or a song with a medium tempo.
- "Medium tempo"? - "Medium tempo"?
- "Medium tempo"? - She's a lyricist now.
I'm glad So Min wrote the lyrics with her past relationships.
Ji Hyo has a lot to talk about too,
- but she doesn't talk about them. - Right.
Ji Hyo, your lyrics were great too.
I listened to your lyrics once. They sounded like they were rated R.
"Rated R"?
They are rated R?
Yes, mine is lethal.
- It's lethal? That's great. - right.
(It's lethal)
(The "Don't Give It to Me" pair returns.)
What's he doing? My gosh.
- I thought it was another song. - That killed the mood.
It didn't sound like a recent song.
He killed the mood with just one line.
We were having fun. Things were going great, but you killed it.
- You ruined the mood. - That was...
- That clip... - Okay.
Everyone went crazy, talking about how pretty she looked.
No one talked about you at all.
- Seriously. - You should look for a comment.
- No one talked about you. - You know what?
- People said I was a great rapper. - "Ji Hyo is pretty."
- No. - Did you know that?
- Goodness. - Even our fans knew...
- that he tried hard. - People said he tried hard.
- Seriously. - Goodness.
Everyone, try to remember the choreography.
Let's perform again on Seok Jin's 80th birthday.
- I'm serious. - Can you guys do it?
- You'll be in your 60s and 70s. - We can pull this off...
We can pull this off even on his 80th birthday.
- That's right. - Let's start on his 60th birthday.
- We can do the turns on the table. - Exactly.
- Let's start on his 60th birthday. - Yes.
He will turn 60 pretty soon.
- There are only 6 years left? - 6 years.
- Yes. - Seven years.
- 6 years. - Until your 60th birthday.
- 7 years. - 6 years.
- It's 6 years. You're 54. - By the way...
- There are 7 years left. - You're 54 years old.
- International age-wise... - Don't count international age.
- Don't count international age. - You're supposed to count that!
Besides, you were born in February.
- Chan Hee, am I wrong or what? - Lately...
Chan Hee. Don't we count international age for that?
- He's 54. - Why did you bring him into this?
- 61 years old. - I have 8 years to go.
That's unbelievable.
In autumn, the sky is high, and the horses grow fat.
You laugh at the rolling leaves. And the fleeting breeze...
I don't think Kwang Soo knows what that means.
- No, I know what it means. - "High sky and plump horses".
- "High sky and plump horses". - It doesn't mean literally.
- "High sky and plump horses". - I really know what this means.
Isn't it when horses' ears get fat or something?
- It's not the ears. - Not the ears...
(Isn't it when horses' ears get fat or something?)
- You're the worst. - No way.
- Are you serious? You don't know? - Kwang Soo. You don't know?
- You two shouldn't mock me. - Hey.
- No, we know what this means. - You two shouldn't tease me.
- It's the trio of dummies. - You really don't know?
This is such basic knowledge. I can't write them, but I know them.
- I see. - Do you know what that means?
- What does that mean? - It means the weather is great now.
That's right.
(I survived.)
Since the weather is great in autumn,
you laugh at the rolling leaves.
And the fleeting breeze inspires you to write poems.
- What? - Poems?
It's the season of men.
Before we start the race, to satisfy your flooding inspirations,
- we'll have a poetry contest. - Poetry contest?
Gosh, I'm terrible at these.
- This is perfect for So Min. - So Min.
- No. - This special is for you.
- So Min is great at writing poems. - That's right.
Please write a poem about the member sitting next to you.
I have the best member sitting next to me today.
I have Seok Jin.
Then I write about Jae Seok, right?
- That's right. - I'll write about Haha.
- I'll write about Kwang Soo, right? - That's right.
Do I have to write the poem, following the rules of poetry?
- You can write however you want. - That was...
Are we at a school right now? Some school in Cheonghak-dong?
"Although I do this..."
With the evaluation, three of you will end up with only eat rice...
- and dried lavers. - No!
The five of you will have chicken kalguksu.
- It's already a meal mission? - Who will be the judge?
(The opening segment starts with a meal mission?)
All right.
- Can I play music while I write? - Music?
(Streaming his song)
- Why are you suddenly playing that? - I need to get inspired.
Why are you suddenly promoting the song?
- I mean... - That will confuse us.
- I'm not trying to promote it. - It's going to confuse us.
- Is this how you'll promote it? - Hey.
- Seok Jin. - What's this?
(Seok Jin, let's promote our song.)
(Pink Nose Light gets up.)
(He streams the song by singing.)
(Are you watching this, Apink?)
Gosh, seriously. That's so terrible.
That's nasty.
(Promoting Brothers for "Party")
(Please stream "Party" a lot.)
All right. Get your papers.
You usually write poems at night.
- That's when you feel emotional. - "Song Ji Hyo".
(Everyone focuses on writing their poem.)
- The title... - "Kwang Soo."
Do I have to write a title?
Hold on.
This is awesome. You have to thank me later.
Can I write a long one?
Gosh, an acrostic poem...
"You, punk. Kwang Soo, you punk. You're like a sorghum straw."
Is that it?
This is it.
This is a poem. Don't make it complicated, Kwang Soo.
(That's a poem?)
(Zealously writing his poem)
Hey, that was terrible.
"I saw your eyes spinning after you drank." What's that?
- Come on. - It's just a poem.
(That's a poem about So Min?)
- Let me explain. I'm practicing. - When did that happen?
- "Your eyes spinning after..." - It's because...
You...
When we drink together, I sometimes see only the whites of her eyes.
It's when you get mad.
(They finish writing the poems while expressing their affection.)
Shall I go first?
- Jae Seok will go first. - Okay.
If you think it's complicated, you can't write poems.
Right, right.
Title, "Lee Kwang Soo".
(Title: "Lee Kwang Soo")
"What do you do?"
"Are you an actor?"
"Are you a model?"
"Are you a comedian?"
"What do you do?"
"I get it."
- "You're just Sun Bin's boyfriend." - What was that?
(You're just Sun Bin's boyfriend.)
That's not a poem.
- No, it is. - That can't be a poem.
This is trendy nowadays.
There has to be a punch line at the end.
You had a twist at the end. It was a poem with a twist.
Jae Seok, that was nice. It was good.
This is the trend nowadays.
There must be a punch line at the end.
You set it up in the beginning and had a twist at the end.
- That's right. - That's the trend.
- Here's my next poem. - He wrote a letter.
- You wrote a lot of short poems. - Yes.
- "Lee Kwang Soo". - "Lee Kwang Soo".
"I can tell you now."
"You are..."
"Actually, you..."
"look better with your mustache."
That's a poem?
(I can only tell you now.)
That was so well-written.
It started off nicely, but I love your twist at the end.
Yes, there's a twist.
This is how people write poems. I included images people have...
- Kids would write better than you. - of Kwang Soo in the poems.
This is a trendy poem.
He can write poems so quickly.
This is it.
Jae Seok's poems make me wait for the twist.
Title, "So Min".
(Title: "So Min")
"I saw..."
"your eyes spinning after you drank."
(Come on.)
"I saw..."
"your words getting rough after you drank."
- When did I... - "I saw..."
"your hands throwing the table after you drank."
- Really? - I saw that too.
"You have spinning eyes, a rough mouth, and violent hands,"
"so you're crazy."
(In the end, she's just crazy.)
There's no twist here. His poem doesn't have a twist.
I thought he'd put in a twist.
- I made the ending cute. - I thought he'd put in a twist.
That was nice.
Kwang Soo, I can totally relate to that.
By the way, this story is really sad for me.
So you guys don't even call me now?
(You're not calling me since I'm married?)
- You're 40 now. - Hey.
- You're with us now. - You're 40 now.
- Hey. - Hey, you should roll with us now.
- I probably won't join anyway... - Don't join them.
I probably won't join, but now you won't even call?
(Feeling upset)
- Hey, that's better. - "That's better"?
I got a video call around 1 a.m...
- from Kwang Soo. He missed me. - Why?
He asked me if I wanted to come out, and I said I would.
I told him to send me the address and I would head out then.
After that, he didn't answer my call.
(After that, he didn't answer my call.)
(When he said he would come out, he couldn't reach Kwang Soo.)
I kept calling him,
and I got mad.
- I'm sorry. - Why do you do that?
- I'm sorry. - Why are you so mean?
- "Did he play me or what?" - He does that when he gets drunk.
- Hey, are you making fun of him? - I'm sorry.
- No, no. It's not that. - Is that it?
I'm sorry.
He wouldn't answer my call after he said he missed me.
You just wanted to say you missed him, but Seok Jin was going to join.
- I didn't know he'd come out. - So he was uncomfortable.
(They resume presenting the poems.)
So Min.
Actually...
- She's our official poet. - No, no.
Crazy Poet.
"A flower has blossomed."
"No one knows when the flower blossomed."
"But a small flower has blossomed."
"Matured in time,"
"it withers away and blossoms. And it repeats."
(She's indeed a poet.)
"When fallen flowers cover it up like dots,"
- "the flowers..." - Hey.
Hold on. Are you trying to...
bid farewell to Seok Jin?
By "dots", do you mean the end?
- Isn't this like a eulogy? - I mean...
- Let me finish. - You're suddenly sending him off.
- What was that? - Okay.
"Traces of life, Jee Seok Jin".
- "Traces of life"? - "Jee Seok Jin".
What is it?
"Tread on it lightly and go on your path."
- I know what she's doing. - What is it?
In "Along with the Gods", when your name is called thrice,
- you go to the underworld. - Really?
(If the Grim Reaper calls your name thrice, you leave this world.)
- "Jee Seok Jin". - This?
- Jee Seok Jin. - Really?
Have you gone mad?
Why are you sending me away?
The title is "Flower in the Underworld".
(She's definitely sending him off.)
(So Min's poem gave him a chance to look back on his life.)
- This is making me cry. - I actually cried.
Our show definitely moves people's hearts.
I wrote a short one.
Actually,
a lot of people want to know about Ji Hyo.
They want to know what she's like.
She's so mysterious.
I don't think anyone is listening to him.
- You're listening, right? - Ji Hyo.
- This is about you. - Okay.
- Jae Seok, you're listening, right? - Yes.
Listen up. Listen to my poem.
I was listening. I just got inspired.
"Song Ji Hyo".
(He begins whether they listen or not.)
"You're a quiet child."
"However, when you yell out of anger,"
"you become Freddie Mercury."
"You're considerate."
"However, I'm the only one you didn't send the dried herring."
(He's asking her about the dried herring years ago.)
He's so petty.
That was ages ago.
"You're beautiful."
"I can't deny your beauty."
"The most beautiful lady on Running Man, Song Ji Hyo."
This is it.
- I don't know how to respond to it. - That's it?
- That was... - This is all.
- He likes... - What?
eating rice with dried laver.
You're almost addicted to dried laver.
(Seok Jin aimed for last place.)
("Song Ji Hyo")
All right.
"Autumn is known for its good weather."
"The sky is high, and the man of autumn, Jong Kook,"
"is raising his standards. And his muscles are getting fatter."
"He just needs to meet the one who will warm his cold winter..."
"and starts a new life while fluttering the wedding veil..."
Is your last line, "That's me"?
Jae Seok.
- What's happening? - No.
- I didn't write that. - Right?
"That's me."
That's a twist.
"When the autumn comes back again,"
"I wish that you would spend the rest of your life..."
"in warmth with a muscular child that resembles you."
"And I'm right next to you."
- "And I'm right next to you." - "And I'm right next to you."
Read the last line.
- "That's me." - Read it.
- Read it. - Read it.
(That's me.)
("Kim Jong Kook")
- All right. - Should I go next?
- All right. - She wrote a letter.
I should get married.
I should get married and be on "Same Life, Unlike Dreams".
I don't think you can.
(He sounds firm.)
- Why not? - It will be hard.
(Jae Seok's diagnosis after watching him on "Mom's Dairy")
I should be doing this while I look at him.
The title is "Se Cha Ni".
It's "Se Cha Ni".
- "Se Cha Ni". - I'll read it now.
- That sounds cute. - I bet there's a punch line.
That sounds friendly.
"Although his mouth is protruding,"
"he tries not to stand out."
"Although his knowledge is short,"
"his thoughts are deep."
That's a compliment.
"My kind friend, Se Cha Ni".
"Se Cha Ni".
"As it's getting chilly,"
"just like this strong wind, I want Se Cha Ni..."
"to push forward zealously."
- What was that? - Jong Kook.
- That was such a word of blessing. - My gosh.
- I mean... - What was that?
Imagine if Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and I were sitting next to him.
He wouldn't write something like that for us.
- He's two-faced. - This is so infuriating.
- I should expose you to the world. - Seriously.
- You're unbelievable. - This is so upsetting.
You made us look terrible with your poem.
- That was so moving. - No, listen.
Personally, I really cherish him.
- My heart is pounding. - He's my guy, you know.
I can write one like that.
"Ji Hyo, you have short legs,"
"but your thoughts aren't short-sighted."
It's easy.
Why would you say that I have short legs?
- That's not how it goes. - What?
"You have short-sighted thoughts, but you have a long waist."
(She gets mad at their mention of her short legs and long waist.)
Come on.
("Se Cha Ni")
After hearing Jong Kook's poem,
- my poem sounds... - Hurry up.
- Just go ahead. It's all right. - It's about Haha.
Title,
"Haha".
"Grow big, grow big,"
"I want everything to grow big."
- That's like a magic spell. - "Shave it, shave it,"
"I want you to shave that dirty mustache of yours."
(Shave it, shave it.)
(I want you to shave that dirty mustache of yours.)
(What was that?)
(Everyone cracks up.)
- It's dirty. - That's funny.
"Stop it, stop it, stop acting young."
(Feeling upset)
"Yes, you are. Yes, you are."
"You're also 40."
- That was nice. - That was my poem.
Great, great.
- You wrote a nice one. - I went after Jong Kook.
No, it was great.
- It's my turn now. - I enjoyed that.
The poem had advice Haha should listen to.
- I'm looking forward to it. - I can't wait.
- I can't wait. - Title,
"Yu Jae Seok".
"Hey, look."
"Where are you going in a hurry?"
What did he say? What's he talking about now?
"Wherever I look,"
"you pop up ubiquitously."
(He's on every TV station.)
"It's as if you will be leaving tomorrow."
"What's the rush in taking on everything?"
"At this rate, you might have your own news segment."
- "Hey, look." - News does suit him though.
"I will chat with you,"
"so you won't be lonely on your way out."
"Hire me."
(Hire me.)
(Are they promising to be partners?)
- The ending was the twist. - That was great.
- My gosh. - That was funny.
You're the best.
That was the best.
And he read the poem well too.
- His voice was nice. He did well. - Right.
- Now, we have eight of your poems. - Okay.
Today will be a special episode to celebrate Hangeul Day.
We have checked your spelling and spacing.
- Really? - I almost thought about doing them.
(Spelling and spacing are the criteria?)
"Spelling"?
We graded each poem based on spelling and spacing.
Members in 1st place to 5th place will eat delicious chicken kalguksu.
And the rest three members will only eat rice and dried lavers.
But spelling and spacing are really hard.
- The spacing is really hard. - It's really hard.
And we asked you to write it by hand today for a reason.
To celebrate Hangeul Day,
you'll be creating a handwriting font.
"A handwriting font"?
Based on the handwriting from your poems,
we plan to make a font out of it.
And the winner of the race...
will have the chance to create a font named after them.
And we plan to distribute the font online, so anyone can download it.
- Our own handwriting? - The name of the font...
will have the member's name in it when distributed.
I'm doomed. I didn't put any spacings in my lines.
I don't usually put in spacings to begin with.
It's not because you don't know how?
I just don't add them.
- You don't? - Why not?
- So we have the result. - What is it?
Jae Seok got 1 spelling wrong and missed 5 spacings.
- Really? - That's a lot.
Why did I get so many errors?
That's the total number of errors from the poems you submitted.
Seok Jin, you missed five spacings.
- He got all the spellings right. - Which ones did I get wrong?
Jong Kook might find this unfair,
- you wrote, "Se Cha Ni". - Why? I see.
You misspelled 2 words and missed 1 spacing.
- You have a total of three errors. - That's not a lot.
- You didn't get anything wrong. - That's not a lot.
Haha, you misspelled 1 word and missed 2 spacings.
You have a total of three errors.
- Hold on. - Haha wrote a long poem too.
And Ji Hyo, you misspelled two words...
and missed seven spacings.
Spelling?
- Which words did she misspell? - What did I get wrong?
(Feeling embarrassed)
She got the spelling wrong?
- What did I get wrong? - That's a bit embarrassing.
- You should know how to spell. - It's funny to see her flustered.
She's flustered.
Kwang Soo, you misspelled 1 word and missed 4 spacings.
You have a total of five errors.
So Min, you misspelled 2 words and missed 1 spacing.
You have a total of three errors.
- Really? - She did?
Se Chan...
(Laughing)
- What is it? - He misspelled only one word.
But he missed 12 spacings.
- You're the worst. - You should learn to write again.
- Hey, I lost my affection. - Are you serious?
- Let's learn again. - This is crazy.
- You should study it every day. - I really should.
- 12? - So...
The members who will only eat rice and dried lavers are...
Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, and Se Chan. You'll get rice and dried lavers.
- The rest of you will eat kalguksu. - Oh, my.
- Yes! - It's kalguksu.
- That sounds good. - Goodness.
(This is a mouthwatering portion.)
It's baby ginseng.
The ginseng smells so good.
- Look at the dumplings. - What should I do?
This is amazing.
This is good just with kimchi.
(Thank you for the food.)
This is so good.
Potatoes?
(He forgets about the camera and inhales the food.)
This is good just with kimchi.
Oh, dear.
This kimchi is really good.
- What's wrong? - Kimchi.
- Well... - Kimchi.
- Dumplings... - Is it good?
- The dumplings are so good. - Be quiet. Just eat.
(Why are you picking on me?)
Why?
Be quiet.
Let's start the race.
(Today's race is about producing a font. The race starts.)
Look at the rice maturing. It must really be fall.
The persimmons too.
As I told you earlier,
this is a Hangeul Day Special at Cheongdo, known for persimmons.
The race is called Those with Persimmons.
There's an older member here with no good sense.
An older member?
- There's only one. - I'm the only older member.
- Why? - There's only one.
- Why is there only one? - I'm full of good senses.
I consider Jong Kook an older member sometimes.
- Whatever. - I'm serious.
There are four guests today.
There will be four teams today for the race.
- The guests are waiting. - Is that right?
- Let's invite them first. - Let's have them join us.
Guests, please come on out.
They are inside the hanok.
- Are they coming out at once? - Who is it?
- Who is it? - Who is it?
Yu Na! Mina!
- Tiffany! - It's Tiffany.
- It's been such a long time. - Chi Yeul.
(Singer and Actress Kang Mina, Actress Park Yu Na,)
(Singer and Musical Actress Tiffany, Singer Hwang Chi Yeul)
- Hello. - My gosh.
- Chi Yeul. - Hello.
- It's been a while, Chi Yeul. - We meet again.
- It's been such a long time. - He lost so much weight.
- He's back. - You look even more handsome now.
- Stand in the middle. - You lost so much weight.
You lost weight.
How long has it been?
It's been such a long time, Mina.
- Yes. - Right.
In January 2018,
- she joined us on Jeju Island. - Right.
That's right.
She was in a drama that finished recently.
Yu Na was in it as well.
- It was "Hotel Del Luna". - Yes, right.
This drama got the whole country excited.
(Kwang Soo proves himself to be a devoted fan.)
- I didn't watch it. - Did you watch it?
Isn't it your backside that has the whole country excited?
- Jong Kook. - Don't mention that.
We decided not to talk about it.
- Don't mention that. - Goodness.
Dooly's grandpa.
I agree.
- What's that? - Dooly's grandpa.
You're scrawny.
- That totally suits him. - Scrawny man.
I told you not to take your shirt off.
What?
Hold on. Mina, excuse me,
but aren't you of legal age now?
Yes, I turned 21 this year.
- She turned 21. - Oh, dear.
- 21. - She's 21 already.
You can drink beer now with your colleagues.
(That's right.)
- 21. - Goodness.
That sounded like a morning talk show.
(He got goosebumps.)
What's the best thing about being an adult?
- Why are you having a conversation? - Let's talk about the top three.
It's nice.
It's great when you first become an adult.
Is it that funny?
(He gets mad all of a sudden.)
- It's not that funny. - Why are you saying that to him?
- Chi Yeul. - It totally suits you.
- "Jee Seok Jin at the Fortress". - It's been a while.
I like that title.
Next is Yu Na.
(This is Yu Na's first time on Running Man.)
- This is her first time. - Right.
(She was a fake Harvard student on "Sky Castle".)
(She's widening her spectrum as an actress with diverse roles.)
You were Fake Harvard.
You used to be an idol trainee, right?
Yes.
Yu Na, can we ask you for a dance?
Yu Na.
Se Ri.
This is hip-hop.
(She enjoyed clubbing on "Sky Castle" as well.)
- Bruno Mars. - She looks cool.
[VIU Ver] SBS E471 Running Man
"Those with Persimmons Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(She starts with sophisticated movements.)
She's good. I knew it.
She's playing with the beat.
- She's good. - Her eyes changed.
(Her father will approve of her dance skills.)
- She looks relaxed. - I know.
These are simple dance moves, but she makes it look good.
She's good.
(She has a great vibe.)
You look arrogant.
- You look more arrogant. - Se Ri!
- Isn't she really good? - Se Ri.
- Se Ri. - Se Ri.
(She's shy as soon as the music stops.)
- That was awesome. - That was really good.
- That was awesome. - Good job.
- You were good. - That was amazing.
- Goodness. - Amazing.
She's good.
All right. Next is Tiffany. It's been a while.
- Tiffany. - So nice to see you again.
She has good news.
You bought a house in America.
(She bought a house in America.)
- Yes. - Buying a house in America is...
He said it was good news.
I thought he was going to mention my new song.
That too, but there's no better news than having your own house.
That's true.
- LA? - Yes, in LA.
Haven't you seen Jong Kook in LA? He goes there often.
We have a mutual friend.
I know where you stay.
- Where does he stay? - Is it somewhere weird?
- No, it's not. - Don't talk about his daughter.
(Be quiet.)
(They're suspicious about his hidden daughter.)
- His daughter? - We covered it up.
- I don't have a daughter. - He doesn't.
People think I really have one because of you.
They're his close friends. He has many friends in the area.
You bought a house in LA,
and like we mentioned earlier...
- On October 11. - You have a new song?
- Yes. - "Run for You".
- I didn't know. - I am touring 18 cities in America.
- She performs in the US. - Global star.
- 18? - Before I went on a bus tour,
I wanted to say hi.
What's a bus tour?
You see it in the movies. For 4 to 6 weeks,
- you travel by bus... - You complete the tour on a bus.
to 18 cities.
That's awesome.
Can you sleep in it as well?
Yes, during 4 to 6 weeks...
Did you think it was like a bus we ride on?
Like those seats.
You can turn the seats around.
- It's not like a bus we ride on. - "Let's get off."
"Ring".
It's not like that.
Do the seats turn around to face other seats?
- Next is Chi Yeul. - Chi Yeul.
He's like family now.
- Windmill brother. - It hasn't been that long.
Chi Yeul is part of the Running Man family.
Right.
- So Min and I won last time. - Right.
- You did the windmill too. - I took a gift set.
- What was the gift? - It was an assorted gift set.
(He doesn't remember.)
- It was assorted. - Was it red ginseng?
- It was nice. - It's the best.
- It was nice. - Assorted gift sets are not bad.
- Those are the best. - It's nice.
Are you releasing a new song as well?
I had a concert in Vancouver, Canada.
You guys are all awesome.
- That's so awesome. - You're awesome, Chi Yeul.
Was the concert sold out in Vancouver?
No, it wasn't sold out.
(No, it wasn't sold out.)
(I see.)
I'm a solo singer, so my fans...
- That's right. - He changed a lot.
In the past, he would have said it was sold out.
- You're very honest. - Yes.
Each team will have 3 people plus a guest. There will be 4 teams.
There will be three rounds to obtain persimmon badges.
At the end of the race, the team with the most badges win.
A new font will be named after a Running Man member...
with the most number of badges.
If a guest has the most badges, they'll win the R ring.
The team with the least number of badges...
has to take off the tops of 100 persimmons and peel them.
- Peel them? - There's a machine for them.
We have to peel them?
What if you don't know how to do it?
We'll give you tools to work.
- Better not come in last. - Let's make the teams.
We'll play a very simple game.
A guest will shout out initial consonants of a word,
and if a Running Man member wants to be on that team,
you can say the word and act it out.
If the guest likes that member, they can approve.
If they don't like the member, they can disapprove...
and reject you.
- Let's start with Chi Yeul. - Me?
I'll go with an easy one.
Bieup, giyok.
- What? - Bieup, giyok.
- Bieup, giyok? - Bieup, giyok.
What is there?
Fart.
(He got one!)
(On his first try?)
- You're a team. - Did he recruit me?
He got recruited?
If he plays the bell once...
(Kwang Soo and Chi Yeul are a couple.)
- Is this over? - No,
I didn't want to be on his team. I just remembered a word.
- It's been decided. - Go ahead.
If that's not a word you're thinking of, play the bell once.
You got chosen.
You're on Chi Yeul's team.
Did you shout out a word without thinking?
(There are three female guests.)
It's not about any random word. This is not how it goes!
- Good. - Kwang Soo.
We got rid of Kwang Soo. Go ahead.
Chi Yeul, don't even think about winning today.
It's okay.
I like him.
Tiffany is next.
Fany, Tiffany.
Bieup, siot.
- Bieup, siot? - What's that?
Goodness, you should do this one.
- You do it. You're good at this. - Goodness.
- What is it? - You're good.
I don't know.
That's the only word I can think of.
Me too.
(It's a strong word they can't help but think of.)
Goodness.
I'm not thinking what you're thinking.
There are many words. What are you thinking of?
Clapping.
There's "clapping".
(Did she get it in one try?)
She got it? Is it an easy pass every time?
Clapping?
They're not rejecting anybody.
I'm happy, Ji Hyo.
Tiffany.
Let's win today.
- It's Mina. - Mina.
(It's Mina's turn.)
Mieum, chieut.
Mieum, chieut?
- Mieum, chieut? - Mieum and chieut.
Macho!
(I got it!)
(The first rejection)
She says you're wrong.
(I thought everyone got an easy pass.)
But macho makes sense.
Hold on.
(The judges raise their standards for Seok Jin.)
I got it. The pit of the stomach.
(He pulls up his shirt.)
The pit of the stomach.
Are you kidding me?
What? That made sense!
- Why pull up your shirt? - Gosh.
The pit of the stomach.
(It's as if they've been struck in the pit of the stomach.)
I got it.
Anchovy!
(Anchovy!)
(So Min sells an anchovy and joins Team Mina.)
You're accepting "anchovy"?
Anchovy.
"The pit of the stomach" is better.
Yu Na's next.
(Lastly, it's Yu Na.)
Giyok, jieut.
- Giyok, jieut? - Giyok, jieut.
I got it. Stiff.
(Stiff)
(That was clever.)
That was witty of him.
You have to accept that.
Okay!
Why can't I think of anything?
I didn't say anything on purpose.
- It's our turn to choose. - The tables have turned.
Please give them the xylophones.
Hand them over.
Only those picky are left.
Nice.
You're right about them all being difficult.
I'm already suffocating.
They all do as they please.
The stubborn ones.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- Giyok, nieun. - Sorry?
Giyok, nieun.
(Jae Seok's consonants: Giyok, nieun)
(Me!)
Agony.
(Incorrect)
(He's strict.)
Giyok, nieun?
(Before Kwang Soo even does anything)
What? Hold on.
Why? He didn't even do anything.
- Jae Seok! - What?
Go. He doesn't want you on his team.
(I don't want to be on that team.)
What?
- Get back in line. - What was it?
Well...
- Everyone gets one chance. - Okay.
Giyok, rieul.
(Seok Jin's consonants: Giyok, rieul)
Will no one come forward?
- You have five seconds. - It's a difficult combination.
- Giyok, rieul. - Three...
The combination is a tricky one.
- What... - I can't think of anything.
- What can it be? - Please remember me, guys.
- I don't know. - Let's move on.
Jong Kook's next.
- I'm sure you can think of one. - Jong Kook?
- I'll get back to you guys. - Joon Kook, you're next.
Guys, it's time to put your brains to work.
- What? - Ieung,
- giyok. - Ieung, giyok.
(Jong Kook's consonants: Ieung, giyok)
(Crying like a baby)
- A baby. - A baby.
(He hates it when people act cute.)
A baby.
- Yu Na's got it. - Yu Na's up.
Poop.
(Very simple)
- What? - It's a good one.
- Just like that? - Okay.
(That was good enough?)
Wasn't "baby" a good answer?
How is that a good one?
- It was good. - No, I liked Yu Na's.
- Jong Kook's on our team. - Do I join them?
Bieup, giyok.
(Haha's consonants: Bieup, giyok)
Bieup...
Wait, I know.
(Guns blaring)
More intensely!
- What is this? - Yes, exactly.
(Are they in a battle?)
Mina, shoot me.
- What? - What is this?
"Battlegrounds."
(An online shooting game, "Battlegrounds")
"Battlegrounds"?
"Battlegrounds"...
No can do. I don't even have an account.
He doesn't play that game.
Why won't you accept it?
Haha, come on.
He's 40 and old, so he doesn't know that game.
He doesn't know "Battlegrounds".
- Okay, I accept. - He accepts it.
(Haha accepts "Battlegrounds" and joins Team Mina)
- All right. - You're running out of chances.
There are only two teams left...
and one should take me.
- Right. - All right.
If not, you'll end up with me.
- Giyok, giyok. - Giyok, giyok.
- Giyok, giyok? - Giyok, giyok?
(Coughing)
- What are you doing? - What's that?
Is this for real or not?
A cold.
(A cold.)
(It's not bad...)
You fooled all of us.
- Meat! - We fell for it.
- A cold. - Are you kidding me?
- I'm not sure. - Tell me about it.
- They're both a little weak. - I know.
(Yelling)
Madness.
(Madness)
Nice!
- Okay. - Give Seok Jin a chance too.
- It's all right. - I just ended it.
It's fine.
You'll get changed and begin the race then.
- Please get changed. - Okay.
(The teams)
(Their first mission takes place at Cheongdo Fortress.)
Check out the view.
Our team though...
What's wrong?
I hate this.
- Why? - I love our team.
You guys look great together.
- You do. - Really?
That color suits you as well.
- Even your caps are the same color. - It's perfect.
We thought that we made a great team.
- We'll win for sure today. - Of course.
It's funny how the teams give off different vibes.
Team Yu Na...
looks as if a distant niece of Jong Kook's...
who he doesn't even remember...
came to the broadcasting station with him.
To remedy the awkwardness, he called Se Chan.
Yes, to keep things fun.
- That's how it feels. - "Yu Na, are you having fun?"
I always ask friends over when things get awkward.
Right? That's how you are.
Well, that's how it feels. Meanwhile...
This is the team that'll peel persimmons.
(The team that'll peel persimmons)
- They must, right? - I'm getting that vibe too.
We don't have any advantage.
I can already smell the persimmons on my hands.
- It's driving me crazy. - Persimmons have a strong smell.
What about us then?
- We... - The tall one,
- the fool, and... - The three losers.
That's what you are. The three losers.
(Losers?)
How can you call us losers?
The tall one and the fool?
- The tall one and the fool? - That's what she said.
- Together, we're the losers. - No way.
The first game is Find the Word.
Find the Word?
One member from each team...
will randomly open the dictionary and choose a word.
The entire team will then...
try and locate the word within the area. The first team back wins.
Are you ready?
All right. Ready, set...
(It's important to open to a page where there are many common words.)
Go!
- Look. - There's "dog."
- Dog. - Yes, dog.
There's "dog."
(Let's find a dog!)
- A dog? - You'll bring a puppy?
A dog won't be easy.
You can't bring a puppy. It has to be a dog.
The two are different.
Right, they're different.
Over here, buddy. Good job.
That's it. Come on.
Over here. Good dog.
They actually brought a dog.
- Come on. - It's an actual dog.
It's a real dog.
- Over here. - Come on.
It's a dog.
- Here it comes. - They found an actual dog?
They brought a real dog.
That was fast.
I found "car."
- How can we bring a car? - Right?
How are you going to bring a car?
- A car? - Hey!
They can have my respect if they manage to bring a car here.
(Fools...)
- Wait, it made a right turn. - Here it comes.
- That's what they're in? - Here comes a car.
(Here comes a car.)
- A car? - It's a real car.
- Here comes a car. - I salute them.
Sir!
(They received help from a nearby citizen.)
Sir, could you briefly give us a ride?
They brought a dog and a car.
They're bringing the big guns.
(Imposing)
(They brought a car right in front of the director.)
This definitely counts.
- I agree. - Me too.
This is hilarious.
- Look. - See?
- Nice. - This round is ours.
(Team Tiffany is in 1st place.)
Thread.
A short thread. Let's look for that.
- A thread? - It's on our clothes.
- A thread. - Right.
- An undershirt. - An undershirt.
An undershirt?
Hold on.
- Come with us. - Take him with us.
- What? - A thread.
- Wait... - Here it is!
- Here. - A thread.
Look, he's wearing an undershirt.
Where? Okay, take it off him.
Why? What's going on?
- Hurry. - Why?
What are you doing?
- Guys! - Hold on.
What is this?
(What are you doing?)
(Smooth)
Why are you doing this to me?
- Hey! - An undershirt.
Here's an undershirt.
- It's an undershirt. - What is this?
My gosh.
- Good job. - Here you go.
Goodness.
We have his undershirt.
Kwang Soo, here you go.
- A thread. - It's on his sweatshirt.
- I accept that. - Yes!
Again?
(He enters a coffee shop to find a charger.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Could we perhaps borrow a charger?
A charger.
Your phone would be nice too.
Thank you.
- We'll bring it back shortly. - It won't be long.
- This will put us in the lead. - It's over now.
That's what we need?
We won.
- I accept. - Okay!
Are we good?
They're done then.
- Are you done? - We're good.
- You're done? - We're done.
Are we in last place then?
Nice!
(Except for the team in last place, the three play for the badges.)
(Current Number of Persimmon Badges)
(Team Yu Na, Team Tiffany, Team Chi Yeul, Team, Mina)
Three Losers.
I like the nickname.
- Three Losers. - There it is.
I always say this,
but one day, someone we wave to today...
will come up to us and say that they were here...
- after becoming a celebrity. - You're right.
That's true.
You all know Son Yeon Jae, right?
- When she was young... - Son Yeon Jae?
She wanted my autograph, so I signed her one.
That's right.
- He told her to go first though. - So she came back with her friends.
- And that was Yeon Jae? - So I told her to go away.
That girl became the Son Yeon Jae we know.
It really happens. Yu Na...
- It happened to me too. - Right?
- So... - Who was it for you?
I took a photo with you in middle school.
What?
You were filming an episode of Running Man.
What did I tell you?
- No way. - These things happen.
Why did you take one with him of all people?
I'm a fan.
- Of his? - Yu Na, where was it?
- Where did we take it? - At Dongdaemun.
- Dongdaemun? - Which episode was it?
It's been so long.
Jackie Chan was a guest.
- What? - Jackie Chan was with you.
It could happen, right?
I'm a fan.
(6 years ago in Dongdaemun,)
(Running Man was running around as usual.)
(The guest was Jackie Chan, and Yu Na was there too.)
- Were you there? - That's unbelievable.
- That's crazy. - Seriously.
And today,
- Yu Na is here on Running Man. - Exactly.
Give her a big hand!
- That's beautiful. - Her dream came true.
This happens sometimes.
- That's incredible. - Really.
When Jae Seok had just debuted,
some people were getting his autograph.
And Shim Sin passed by.
Jae Seok was giving his autograph,
and the people took the paper away from him.
(Jae Seok remembers that day.)
- Jae Seok was willing to sign... - I wanted to give it,
but they took the paper away.
When that happens,
- it hurts. - That's sad.
"Give me the paper. I'm almost done."
"Just give it to me."
That's so sad.
(It's when he was an unknown grasshopper.)
Back then, you didn't look so good.
Looking back, my looks weren't the problem.
My skills weren't good either.
(He reflects on himself.)
- As a host... - You were nervous.
I didn't know how to smooth things out.
- I want to know when that was. - I think we're here.
(They arrive at the second mission.)
- It's really big. - It's huge.
That's Haha.
- That's Haha. - It looks just like him.
That's Haha, and that's Seok Jin.
- It looks exactly like him. - They look like them.
- It really looks like me. - This is Haha.
Over here. Exactly.
In the second mission, you can earn persimmon badges...
by singing.
- It's the Korean Song Contest. - Korean Song Contest?
- We have Mina. - Mina is a good singer, right?
English probably isn't allowed.
Out of the four songs prepared by the production team,
one song will be randomly picked.
You have to change any foreign lyrics to Korean.
The team with the lowest score loses.
- You need to know English. - Chi Yeul...
I have no chance at this.
I could change the lyrics, but...
Each time you fail to change foreign words to Korean,
- you lose five points. - Tiffany has an advantage.
- Tiffany will be good at it. - We have Tiffany.
- She'll be able to translate. - But it'll come up suddenly.
Se Chan, you can't translate English into Korean.
- What? - Can you?
But I know all the famous songs.
You'll have to translate things like "cheer up" into Korean.
You can look up the lyrics for 30 seconds before you start singing.
Seok Jin hadn't talked in a long time.
Why did you have to cut in?
- Why did you do that? - Why?
- I was talking. - I mean...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- I wanted to speed things up. - Seok Jin is going to...
text me later.
- What is he going to say? - "What do you think..."
"was Chul Min's intention?"
Chul Min made it clear that he was going to edit it out.
Don't do that.
You got the wrong idea.
This is so funny.
After looking up the lyrics for 30 seconds,
you'll start singing.
We can look up the lyrics?
Because you don't know how much of the lyrics are in English...
Let's decide the order.
Pick 1 from these 4 songs.
Pick one and show it to the camera.
- Mina is a good singer. - Please!
That team has Tiffany.
What happened?
(Mina's song is "Pick Me" by I.O.I.)
"Pick Me" by I.O.I!
("Pick Me" is I.O.I's most famous song.)
(Including the title, the song has many English words.)
(Will she be able to change all the English words to Korean?)
- Hold on. - "Pick Me".
You have 30 seconds to look up the lyrics.
- Start. - Hold on.
Can't we see the English lyrics?
"We're girls with a dream..."
What's "shining light" in Korean?
- Shining light - Shining light
Soft light
- Pick me, pick me - Should we step back?
Hold on.
- What's with your moves? - Is this wrong?
- I'm a pushover. - Is that it?
- I'm a pushover. - This is Apink.
Is this Apink?
(It's pushover dance.)
Get your microphone.
- "Feel me..." - "Beautiful..."
"Show you my paradise..."
- "Show you my paradise." - "Show you my paradise."
- Get your microphone. - All right.
I.O.I!
- Mina is one of them. - We get to hear this!
(Mina feels shy.)
That's Mina!
(Mina winks.)
(This is the moment we share our dreams)
- For you who is sweet - For you who is sweet
(She has to translate "shining light" into Korean.)
Shining light
(She did well.)
(It's your day, hey baby)
Hey baby
Show you my paradise
(She successfully translated all the English words.)
It has a lot of English words.
- I want you - I want you, pick me up
Pick me, pick me, pick me up
(She sings in Korean instead.)
- Pick me, pick me, pick me up - I love this!
- This is amazing! - I like it!
- Pick me, pick me... - This is nice!
You can't help but sing in English.
Show us the dance.
(They dance during the interlude.)
- This is hard. - Look at So Min.
Way to go!
(So Min shows off her moves.)
Look at So Min's hips.
So Min...
(So Min moves her hips.)
(The best dancer ever)
The song won't start!
(So Min's dance is so cute.)
- Pick me, pick me, pick me up - Pick me, pick me, pick me up
(She keeps moving her hips.)
(She's doing the same moves the whole time.)
(So Min's boring moves continue.)
(The song is nearing its end.)
So Min is hilarious.
Pick me, pick me, pick me up
That was funny.
Pick me up
"Pick me up"?
- Pick me up - I want you
- Pick me up - Pick me up
(So Min shows off her talent.)
Pick me, pick me, pick me up
- They got 95 points. - 95 points.
- Pick me, pick me, pick me up - Pick me, pick me, pick me up
- So Min is so funny. - Look at her.
- That's not how you dance! - Pick me, pick me, pick me up
No?
It's so annoying.
It's ridiculous.
You got 95 points.
And you failed to translate...
(Each time you fail, you lose 5 points.)
4 times, so you lose 20 points.
- 4 times? - Your final score is 75 points.
- We did well. I'm relieved. - It was hard.
It was really hard.
- Pick me up - Pick me up
(It's addictive.)
That's perfect.
- Whose turn is it now? - It's my turn.
- It's better to go first. - We have Tiffany.
(What song will Team Tiffany sing?)
- What song is it? - "Gangnam Style".
(Team Tiffany will sing "Gangnam Style".)
("Gangnam Style" by PSY was loved all over the world.)
(Foreigners could easily sing along...)
(because the song has many English words.)
Does this song have English words too?
- It doesn't have many. - "Style"...
- How should we translate "style"? - You have 30 seconds.
- What's "style" in Korean? - What's "style"?
Gangnam "meot-jaeng-i"
- "Mo-yang-sae". - "Mo-yang-sae".
- Gangnam "maep-si" - Gangnam "maep-si"
I'm Gangnam "maep-si"
("Maep-si" is a Korean word that means a "nice appearance".)
Try Gangnam "mo-yang-sae".
- "Mo-yang-sae". - Yes.
In 10 seconds, the song will start.
How should we translate coffee? Bean water?
- Bean water? - Here we go.
- The music starts. - What should we do?
"Mo-yang-sae".
("Gangnam Style")
(Foreign words are spread throughout the song.)
(Will they be able to translate them all into Korean?)
A woman who is kind and friendly in the day
A woman who can enjoy a cup of bean water
(He translate "coffee" as "bean water".)
- A woman with that kind of twist - A woman with that kind of twist
I'm a man
In the day, I'm just as kind as you are
- Bean water! - I'm that kind of man
I "one-shot" my bean water before it cools down
("One-shot")
That's English!
(She said English words.)
(They missed it!)
(She should have translated it into Korean.)
I'm Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"
(The part with English words begins.)
- Gangnam style. - Gangnam style.
I'm Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"
- Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"? - Gangnam style.
Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"
Gangnam "maep-si"!
I'm Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"
He's such an old man.
- He looks so old. - Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"
What's with his moves?
He looks so old.
(What's with Ji Hyo?)
What's that?
I've never seen moves like those.
Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"
What are those moves?
(Their moves look weird.)
What's that?
(Sexy lady)
Sexy lady
(He translated "sexy lady" into Korean.)
(Sexy lady)
Sexy lady
- Is this a trot song? - He's good.
Baby, baby, I know something
(The next part has a lot of English words.)
(Will Seok Jin be able to translate the words into Korean?)
- I know something - You know what?
You know what I'm saying? I'm Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"!
(You know what I'm saying? I'm Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"!)
(Perfect)
(Seok Jin pulled that off?)
(This was actually incredible.)
(They finished "Gangnam Style" without making many mistakes.)
- I'm Gangnam "mo-yang-sae" - I'm Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"
(You did a good job.)
- That was hard. - You struggled in the beginning.
That was incredible.
(What will be the karaoke score?)
- "Baby". - 91 points.
You scored 91 points.
- You got six parts wrong. - We missed the beginning.
With 6 wrong parts, you scored 61 points.
We missed the beginning.
- You scored 61 points. - We missed the beginning.
- We have one team below us. - As long as we're not last.
- We didn't place last. - Take points off for their dance.
- Don't be ridiculous. - What was this?
- Hey. - What was this?
- How was I supposed to dance? - Ji Hyo looked like Ppak Gu.
You looked like...
- Ma Ppak. - The dance looked ridiculous.
The dance looked ridiculous.
- How was I supposed to dance? - Ma Ppak.
The third team.
Ma Ppak.
- Yu Na. - Take the center.
Go forward.
- Please let it be... - Let's go.
- It's a hard one. - It's a hard one.
- Girls' hip-hop song. - What is it?
- What is it? - Give them a hip-hop song.
"Heartbeat" by 2PM.
("Heartbeat" by 2PM)
(English)
(More English)
(It might as well be a pop song.)
I don't know the rap.
Music, please.
- "It's beating for you." - Grab the microphone and begin.
"It's beating for you."
- We need to start! - We're waiting for you.
(The song has already begun.)
- The intro passed in a blur. - We need to start!
- We're waiting for you. - We need to begin now!
(Heartbeat)
Heartbeat
"Heartbeat"!
- Heartbeat - Let's go!
You are good.
Why is this song depressing?
(I don't know the rap.)
No matter how hard I try to forget No matter how many people I meet
There you go!
(She fires off the rap without any emotions.)
(They copy the dance perfectly.)
(They are good.)
It's Korean.
- Come on. - It's Korean.
(They sing together because the lyrics are Korean.)
They are good.
Read the lyrics.
(I don't know why I think you might come)
Here it comes.
- Here it comes. - Come on.
Here comes English.
Listen to my heartbeat
- "For you". - For you. Listen to my heartbeat.
(They continue to get points deducted.)
"Listen to my heartbeat."
(They continue to get points deducted,)
(but Se Chan is excited.)
(What is up with him?)
Se Chan.
(Overly emotional)
(Not knowing what lies ahead of him,)
(he becomes absorbed in the song.)
(The most difficult English part awaits Se Chan.)
(How will he get by?)
Otherwise, I will die
- Stop - No.
- Woman - No! No!
(Stop)
(It's game over for that team.)
Hey, come on.
Oh, no.
What are you doing?
He missed so many lines.
She erased all of me
Why can't I do the same?
"Listen to my heartbeat."
(It's another English part.)
- My heartbeat - "Listen to my heartbeat."
- "It's beating for you." - For you!
- "It's beating for you." - It's waiting for you!
(I still don't know it's over)
(It looks like they gave up.)
(I give up.)
I don't understand why it's like that
"Listen to my heartbeat."
- Listen to my heart - "For me".
- "It's beating for you." - It's beating for you... Me
(Thoughts of you)
Me! You!
Thoughts of you
(What are they going to do?)
- Heart - "My heart is beating."
My heart is beating faster
- "Faster and faster." - Faster and faster
Come on. Let him do it alone.
It's almost over.
- Let him do it alone. - Keep going.
"Faster and faster."
(Se Chan tries to sing,)
(but the song ends.)
(His heart stops.)
- Bravo, bravo. - Bravo.
"Me! You! You!"
"Me!"
- 36 points! - They got 36 points!
(Their karaoke score is 36 points.)
- They will get a negative score. - We won't place last.
We definitely won't place last.
You will get 75 points deducted for getting 15 parts wrong.
You got 15 parts wrong.
- Come on out. - How did we do so badly?
There was cardiac arrest.
- At the end of the song... - Beep.
- That's right. - At the end of the song...
We died.
- Seriously. - The last team.
We need to read the lyrics.
- I hope it has English lyrics. - We need to look up the words.
"Red Flavor" by Red Velvet.
("Red Flavor" by Red Velvet)
(It's much easier than "Heartbeat".)
(However, there are English words that are written in Korean.)
- "The corner candy shop" - "The corner candy shop"
- "Look for it" - "Look for it"
Stop using the phone.
(Red flavor, I am curious)
- "Baby". - Baby
(They have a shaky start.)
"Baby"?
(The corner candy shop)
(Look for it, baby)
It's "The corner candy shop", not "The corner shop".
They translated "Honey" wrong too.
1, 2, 3.
(Red flavor)
"Honey".
(I am curious, honey)
- When I bite into it - "The taste of strawberry".
- The taste of strawberry spreads - The taste of strawberry spreads
- The corner candy shop - The corner candy shop
- "Look for it, baby." - What I like the best is
(We are doing great!)
The taste of summer
(Peach)
What?
What is this?
- Hold on. - Here it comes.
Here it comes.
(Peach juice, sweet and sour mix)
(Mood, brew red to make a cocktail for you)
What?
(Brew red to make a cocktail for you)
- Hold on. - Here it comes.
Here it comes.
What is this?
The feelings beyond imagination Up and down, bang
Let's shout, I like you to be honest
Gosh, what is this?
We fall in love
(We might not place last!)
Please get it even if I don't use words
He is using a dialect.
(The cheerful song suddenly takes on a homey vibe.)
What I like the best is the taste of summer
What I like the best is you in summer
We might not place last.
- This is good. - We might not place last.
- The karaoke score. - What's the score?
What's the score?
(What could be Team Chi Yeul's karaoke score?)
It will be okay as long as we don't place last.
(Please let it be a low score.)
- 81 points. - It's good.
It's a good score.
(Their karaoke score is 81 points.)
It makes no sense that we scored 36 points.
How did we get a score in the 30s?
From 81 points, you will get 55 points deducted...
- since you got 11 parts wrong. - We placed 1st!
Your score is 26 points.
(We managed to avoid placing last.)
We placed first!
(Team Mina placed 1st.)
Thus, Team Yu Na placed last.
(Team Yu Na placed last.)
I'm speechless.
(The current number of persimmon badges)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Team Yu Na, Team Chi Yeul, Team Tiffany, Team Mina)
Let's move on to the final mission.
What is this?
(Four boards suddenly enter.)
Rip off other teams' name tags...
(Rip off other teams' name tags)
to obtain a letter you need in the Korean Letters on My Back.
Is it the Name Tag Elimination?
(Korean Letters on My Back)
All four teams will play the Name Tag Elimination.
Each team will choose 1 out of 4 sentences.
Fill in the blanks by ripping off name tags...
and obtaining a letter at a time.
Complete the sentence so that it makes sense.
The team that completes the sentence last places last.
(It will be hard.)
If you need multiple letters from one name,
you need to rip off the name tag multiple times.
(You need to rip off the name tag multiple times.)
- No one gets eliminated. - No.
If you need another letter from So Min's name,
rip off her name tag again.
Seok Jin's words were hilarious.
(What did I say?)
After listening for a while, he went, "What is he saying?"
(What is he saying?)
(The producer was explaining the rules.)
- What is he saying? - For example...
(What is he saying?)
Getting your name tag ripped off doesn't remove you from the game.
However, everyone must stop for a few seconds.
Even if you complete your sentence,
you must participate in the game...
until the last team is decided.
You need to provide the name tags.
The team that finishes first...
- could decide to help other teams. - I see.
Are we allowed to rip off our team members' name tags?
(Are we allowed to rip off our team members' name tags?)
(Can we finish off our team members?)
Of course not.
Did you have to embarrass Ji Hyo like that?
- For goodness' sake. - Don't be mistaken.
My face turned red.
This team is really slow.
(This team is really slow.)
(They don't know the rules.)
They drive me crazy.
I bet you don't know the rules either.
They are so slow.
Let's check the sentences.
Okay.
(Team Tiffany's sentence)
"She..."
"She likes 'Blank',"
"so her nickname is 'Blank'."
"There was no 'Blank' for the date,"
"so I borrowed 'Blank'."
"I met my date at 'Blank'..."
"and became surprised since she resembled 'Blank'."
"I like my lover's 'Blank', but I hate my lover's 'Blank."
(Team Mina's sentence)
- We need to fill in both blanks. - Yes.
(All teams check the sentences.)
We need to complete this sentence...
with the letters from other people's names.
Young... Young... Youngkwang!
- What? - Youngkwang!
(Young from Mi Young and Kwang from Kwang Soo)
- Okay, okay. - We are set.
- We are set. This is great. - We are set.
Whose name contains "Kwang"?
(He makes his intentions clear.)
Run from me.
(He gives a warning.)
If your name contains Kwang, Soo, or Lee,
I will teach you a lesson.
It's a warning.
- Hey. - My goodness.
What?
(Slapping)
- What? - You have Jong Kook on your side?
Be careful.
Move to your spot.
(Words to fill in the blanks)
We should try to get all the letters from one team.
- Let's rip the name tags. - Yes.
Hold on. Isn't Haha's last name Ha?
- Jeon. - Jeon and Ha. Then we need Jee...
to make "Basement".
(Team Yu Na can get three letters from Team Mina!)
That's right.
We just need to go after that team.
- Last letter for "basement" is... - That's right.
I'm Jan So Min.
(I'm Jan So Min?)
We just need theirs.
I'm annoyed.
Once we get the names from that team, we're done.
I like my lover's "teeth",
- but I hate my lover's "plaque". - I hate my lover's "plaque".
We just need Team Fools' name tags.
Those fools are strong.
She likes "teeth", so it's "plaque".
(Team Tiffany is going after the same letters.)
All right.
- Jae Seok. - It's perfect.
Hurry.
There were no "side dishes", so we borrowed "fritters".
(They complete the sentence with Jae Seok's idea.)
(He realizes something important.)
Chi Yeul.
You don't have to smile.
- Go after "chan" and "jeon". - This is great.
It's the best.
Who should we go after?
Se Chan and So Min.
(Team Chi Yeul's targets are Se Chan and So Min.)
I'll count down for the race. 10,
- We have to do it quickly. - nine,
- eight, - Let's go after So Min first.
- So Min? - seven,
- So Min. - Four.
Use your looks and tear like this.
Race starts.
Let's start from there.
(Race starts.)
We're going after each other.
(They go to look for their prey.)
There are letters that overlap.
If that's the color I see over there,
- it's Haha. - It's Haha.
- We have to tear it. - Go after So Min.
Jae Seok.
For every name tag you give me, I'll hand over a letter.
(He'll exchange a name tag with a letter?)
We should exchange name tags.
Which letter do you need?
- What? - Whose name tag do you need?
For now, I need Chi Yeul's.
- Mine? - Yes.
(He's after Chi Yeul.)
Okay, then give us one as well.
- I won't betray you. - Really?
- Yes, sir. - We don't need anything else...
except for one person's.
- Whose is it? - So Min's.
- Really? Do you need "jeon"? - Yes.
- We only need "jeon". - Right?
Hey, are you working as a team?
- By the way, - You can't do that.
Haha, we have two women on our team.
You also have two women on your team.
(They keep a distance.)
- We hid it. - Are you targeting us?
(The prey came on its own.)
(Team Tiffany is after "lee", "chi", and "seok".)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(Hwang Chi Yeul)
(Yu Jae Seok)
(Their target is the entire Team Fools.)
Kwang Soo, they're looking at you.
- I'm not it, am I? - Kwang Soo.
Jessica looked at you.
(Jessica looked at you.)
She's not Jessica. She's Tiffany.
(Her real name is Hwang Mi Young.)
- I'm sorry. - She's not Jessica.
Mi Young, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(I caught you.)
(He attacks Chi Yeul while he bows.)
(He turns around quickly.)
I'm sorry.
(He's startled.)
- Are you after Chi Yeul? - No, I just gave it a try.
- By the way, - His name doesn't work.
we have two women on our team.
- Be careful of Haha. - Do something about it.
Do you need something?
They're all over there.
Everyone is over there. Wait.
Should we get Haha's first?
- Wouldn't that be best? - I think so.
Go after Haha.
- Haha. - You startled me.
- Hey, be careful. - Protect me.
- Be careful. - Protect me.
- Protect me. - They're going around that way.
(Jong Kook)
- Be careful. - Whose name do you need?
Whose do you need?
- They're making a move. - What's wrong with you?
Why is everyone...
- staying together? - What's wrong with you?
(Right then)
(Haha's bad hand starts to move.)
Go.
(He attacks Chi Yeul for his name tag.)
Come here.
(He tore it.)
I got it.
(This is what betrayal is.)
(The joy of betrayal is sweet.)
Goodness.
Aren't they fools? I knew that he'd tear their name tag.
Which letter will you take, Haha?
"Chi".
(He gets "chi" from Chi Yeul's name tag.)
(I hate my lover's "chi" something.)
As he obtained "chi", the race will stop temporarily.
(They stop for 10 seconds.)
Haha.
- How could you? - I'll do it.
- I'll keep my promise. - Wait.
I'll keep my promise.
- You promise? - I promise.
Keep your promise.
She's hiding.
(Is Haha doing well?)
I promised you, so trust me.
- I gave it to you out of trust. - I know.
I promise you.
(He laughs at those fools.)
In 10 seconds, the race starts again. 10.
Let's hurry and go up.
Jong Kook, shall we separate ways?
We can move together. It doesn't matter.
- Wait. - 10.
- You have to run away fast. - Why?
I'm powerless.
- Eight. - Keep quiet.
- Okay. - Seven.
Jong Kook, can you make Seok Jin be the last?
(The traitor approaches his predators.)
Okay.
- Okay. - Then I'll help you.
- Four. - Do you need me?
(Do you need me?)
(Look at him.)
(Temporary pause is over.)
- Temporary pause is over. - What do you need?
Wait a minute. Let's talk. What do you need?
(They attack him without saying anything.)
(Tearing)
(Jong Kook tears Haha's name tag.)
- I got it. - My goodness.
(What traitor Haha says)
My goodness.
He got his taken so easily.
(That's unbelievable.)
It's because he was alone.
Okay, I'll take "dong".
(He obtains "dong" from Dong Hoon's name tag.)
(I was surprised by "dong" something.)
Gosh, that team is merciless.
Temporary pause is over.
- Five. - We need his name tag again, right?
- Yes, once more. - Don't we need "ha"?
Okay, let's go.
(They go after Haha again.)
Are they after us? Let watch this.
Wait.
(Hey, Seok Jin.)
- We need you. - Is it me?
- Yes. - Why is it me again?
(Is it me?)
(Why is it me again?)
Why is it me again?
(Traitor Haha gets his name tag taken again.)
Darn it.
(Darn it!)
What's wrong with you?
(Haha is very popular.)
(It's his second time.)
What's wrong with you?
- Temporary pause. - We want "ha".
(Team Yu Na gets "ha" from Haha.)
My goodness.
(He's in tatters.)
I'm so sad.
Please do the countdown.
- We have to go again. - 10.
Is it me again? No, right?
(There's no way.)
Where is So Min?
So Min.
Jae Seok, shall we go that way?
- Shall we? - So Min.
Shall we go around?
- We need to get at least one. - We do.
Hey.
We have "dong" and "ha".
- "Dong, ha". - Right.
Should we pretend to go after Jong Kook's?
Should we?
Yes, that would be better.
Haha's name has both letters?
(They approach them secretly.)
(Chi Yeul's plan starts.)
(He approaches Jong Kook.)
- Wait a minute. - Go away.
(As planned, Chi Yeul attacks Jong Kook.)
(He's after Jong Kook.)
(Se Chan is vulnerable.)
(Now is our chance.)
- Wait. - We have to tear off Jong Kook's.
Jong Kook's.
(Their fake hunting starts.)
- Wait. - Tear it.
Be careful, Jong Kook.
(Two teams are facing each other.)
(Be careful, Jong Kook.)
(He catches him.)
(They steer their attention to Jong Kook.)
(He tears it off.)
(He first fakes him.)
I got it. Stop, stop, Jae Seok.
(Did they trick us?)
You should have been careful.
Which letter do you choose?
Are you talking to us?
- Which letter? - "Chan".
- "Chan". - "Chan"?
(They obtain "chan" from Se Chan's name tag.)
Pause.
We'll resume in 10 seconds.
Let's hurry.
- I'll do it. - 10.
Let's go first.
We have to meet up.
Eight.
(The remaining three teams are in a hurry.)
Hurry up.
They're almost done.
The letters...
(Team Chi Yeul only needs one more letter.)
Two, race starts.
- Me again? - Go that way.
Why is it me?
(As soon as the race resumes, they hunt down Haha.)
(Why is it me?)
Why me?
(Yes, it's you again.)
(We can say that we met in "Hadong".)
(That makes sense.)
(Let's take Haha's name tag three times.)
(Our goal is you.)
(Why? Why is it me?)
(What's going on over there?)
What? How many times is that?
Which letter do you want?
We'll take "dong".
- Okay. - You took it before.
- There's another one. We need it. - There's another one.
("I met my blind date in Hadong.")
(They complete Hadong with their second "dong".)
I thought about it, and I verified it.
It works.
She likes "fritters",
so her nickname is "Jeon".
"Jeon"? "She likes fritters, so her nickname is Jeon"?
- Is that possible? - Yes.
- We need So Min. - We have to tear hers twice.
Where's So Min?
You rip off her name tag, okay?
Come out, So Min.
(We need Jeon from So Min.)
She isn't here.
It might end while we look for her.
(Everyone's number 1 target is So Min.)
Where is So Min?
(Where is So Min?)
So Min!
(He yells her name.)
(It's like searching for Mr. Kim in the middle of Seoul.)
Stay hiding. I'll go out first.
If I don't come back,
you should run away secretly.
(So Min goes to see what's going on.)
(Will it be okay?)
(Moving quietly)
(She doesn't know that she's everyone's target.)
(She moves carefully towards the group.)
- 10. - You rip off her name tag.
- Nine. - Where is she?
(When everyone is looking for So Min)
- Hey. - There she is!
(I told you to stay hidden.)
Let's go and catch her.
Don't get caught!
(Team Yu Na begins the hunt.)
(Are they coming after me?)
Why me?
You fool!
(She instantly becomes prey after coming out of hiding.)
Why are they coming after me?
(Stop right there, Jeon So Min.)
(They run after her.)
(My legs, save me.)
(While giving chase, Se Chan takes a different route.)
(I got you!)
Haha! Haha!
(So Min gets cornered.)
Haha!
(You didn't know I could do this.)
- Come here. - Why are you doing this?
- Why are you doing this? - Rip off her name tag.
(Haha joins the group.)
(Will she get her name tag ripped off?)
- Which letter do you need? - Rip off her name tag.
Okay!
(Yu Na succeeds in ripping off her name tag.)
- I should have held out. - I came this way.
- Good job. - I got mine ripped off three times.
I came out because you were nowhere to be seen.
- We will take "Jeon". - Why do you need "Jeon"?
- "I met my date..." - "I met my date..."
- "at Hadong..." - "at Hadong..."
"and became surprised since she resembled a coin."
Jong Kook's team has completed the first sentence.
- But you are still in the game. - We know.
- Help us. - What do you need?
- Who do you need? - We need...
Kwang Soo and either Seok Jin or Jae Seok.
Okay.
- We will catch them. - We will catch them.
Thank you.
Mina should come out now.
(The current status of the sentences)
Jeon Seo Min. There she is.
Jeon So Min. Let's rip off her name tag twice.
There is Seok Jin.
Let's join forces.
We can't do this by ourselves.
- We need "Chi". - We need "Chi" too.
- You need a letter from us, right? - It seems that way.
- Do you need a letter from us? - We are done.
What do you mean?
- Are you done? Then help us. - We are done.
(Haha and So Min attack first.)
(Team Yu Na helps Team Mina as promised.)
- Are you done? Then help us. - We are done.
Come on. Help us.
Rip off his name tag.
(It's 2 against 1.)
Haha! Haha! Hurry up!
(Haha grabs the name tag.)
Haha, hurry up and rip it off.
- Rip it off. - He ripped it off.
(Seok Jin rips off a name tag first.)
- All right. - I ripped it off.
How could you fail?
- Gosh, it hurts. - How could you fail?
- Are you okay? - Game is on pause.
- Game is on pause. - For goodness' sake.
Everyone is over there.
"Jeon".
(Seok Jin gets "Jeon".)
We just need to rip off So Min's name tag once more.
Haha.
(This team's target is So Min too.)
(We need Kwang Soo.)
When you run into Kwang Soo, use yourself as bait...
and rip off his name tag.
He might rip off my name tag first.
- We need to avoid placing last. - Haha.
(The two teams meet.)
What?
I will give you my name tag.
- We made a deal earlier. - When did we do that?
We made a deal earlier.
Haha! Haha!
- Haha! - Rip off the name tag first.
(Rip off the name tag first to get a letter.)
(It's 2 against 2.)
- Haha! - Rip off the name tag first.
- Me? Me? - No, no.
I didn't get my name tag ripped off.
(So Min protects her name tag and Haha and Mina attack.)
(It's the final match between the two teams.)
(Whose name tag will come off first?)
(So Min's or Kwang Soo's?)
I didn't get my name tag ripped off.
- I did it! - I ripped it off!
(Did they rip off the name tags at the same time?)
Rock-paper-scissors.
Gosh, I did it first.
You need to win. You need to win.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - I will go.
Mina, are you good at rock-paper-scissors?
- One round. - Hold on.
- Come on. - Men pick rock!
(It's a psychological attack.)
(Chi Yeul, please win.)
(What will be the result?)
Men pick rock! Rock-paper-scissors!
(Rock versus Scissors)
Okay!
(We won!)
(For goodness' sake.)
Did he play scissors? Is he a fool?
- Is he a fool? - What a loser!
Chi Yeul, you are a loser.
What a loser!
Which letter would you like?
- We want "Lee". - "Lee".
- "Lee". - Yes.
You got "Lee".
Thank you.
(I like my lover's "teeth", but I hate my lover's "Blank".)
- Please count down. - 10.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin?
- We need Seok Jin. - Please protect So Min.
- We need So Min. - So Min.
- We need So Min. - Yes.
We need to get So Min.
So Min, run away.
If you protect So Min, they won't be able to win.
Where should I go?
(Let's hide.)
- Jeon So Min. Jeon So Min. - So Min.
- So Min. - So Min.
- So Min is running away. - Hey.
Let's go. Let's join them.
We need to rip off her name tag.
(It's a matter of who catches So Min first.)
Haha promised to hand So Min over.
- Haha promised. - Are you sure about that?
Come on.
- We got it! - We got it!
- Are you sure about that? - Come on.
(Kwang Soo ripped off Jong Kook's name tag.)
- Jae Seok! - What was that?
Jae Seok!
(They changed the target to Jong Kook.)
- Which letter would you like? - "Kook"!
Did you rip it off?
- "Kook"! - "Kook"!
(We got "Kook"!)
Let's complete the sentence.
(Team Chi Yeul got "Kook" instead of "Jeon".)
"There was no side dish for the date..."
(Did they complete the sentence?)
"There was no side dish for the date,"
- "so I borrowed soup." - "So I borrowed soup."
- We will accept that. - Okay!
(They successfully complete the sentence.)
(We came in 2nd!)
Now, it's a match to decide who comes in last.
Where is she?
Where is So Min?
(The first team to acquire a letter will avoid placing last.)
(Team Tiffany's target is So Min.)
Let's go.
(We just need "Seok".)
Start! Congratulations.
It's incredible that you used only two letters.
- I am disappointed in you. - Haha.
You didn't keep your promise.
I am sorry,
but would you help me so that I won't place last?
What do you want me to do?
- If your team wins... - What do you need?
What do you need?
Me? I need Jae Seok.
(I need Jae Seok.)
- Hold on. - We can't give you his name tag.
Hold on.
- You can't do this. - You can't do this.
(Jong Kook continues to help his ally.)
(Will they acquire "Seok"?)
Jeon So Min! Where is she?
Where is she?
She disappeared.
Focus on her name tag no matter what.
(She was right in front of them.)
My goodness.
(It seems like they didn't see her.)
The three of them are together.
- You can't do this. - You can't do this.
Come on.
- You can't do this. - Let go of me.
(Right then)
(Team Mina just needs "Seok".)
(Will they acquire the letter before Team Tiffany?)
I got it! I got it!
(Haha ripped off the name tag!)
- I got it! I got it! - You can't do this.
(They succeeded to acquire the last letter first.)
(I can't believe I handed over the name tag like this.)
I got it! I got it!
You can't do this.
- What was that? - Look at...
- What was that? - Look at Seok Jin's face.
How could you hand over your name tag like that?
Which letter would you like?
- "Seok". - "Seok".
"Seok". Please complete the sentence.
"I like my lover's teeth,"
"but I hate my lover's plaque."
We will accept it.
(They completed the sentence as they planned.)
It was perfect.
- Does that mean we placed last? - Yes.
- So Min! - Yes?
(So Min shows up belatedly.)
Where were you?
She hid from us.
Thank goodness you hid from them.
Thank goodness.
Do we need to peel persimmons?
There is the last step.
(It's time to decide which team places last.)
So Min, you ran away so diligently.
Good job, So Min.
Please bring in the persimmon badge trees.
The top three teams will choose the tree.
You can choose 1 of the 5 persimmon trees.
The persimmon badges will be divided equally...
among the members who choose the same persimmon tree.
You play as a team and for yourself.
If 1 member chooses number 1, he or she will get 20 badges.
If more members choose it, they will get zero badges.
(Persimmon tree number 1 is important.)
The team that placed last will guess which tree will be...
the most popular.
We have six badges.
You might have more badges than us after this.
If a member of Team Mina gets all the badges of number one...
Would you let us have number one?
(Speaking politely)
- All right. - Number one.
Pick me, pick me, pick me up
(Pick me, pick me, pick me up.)
(We need to do something too.)
- We are Gangnam "mo-yang-sae". - Gangnam "mo-yang-sae"
Sexy woman
(Singing)
(The two teams at the bottom act cute to avoid losing.)
This is bad. I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do.
(The four teams think hard before making the last choice.)
We don't need to put ourselves at risk.
- Let's stay safe. - Number 3 or 4.
Number 2, 3, or 4.
Multiple people will choose number one.
- Is anyone choosing number 1? - Number 2, 3, or 4.
I can't tell you that.
Let's go. Number five.
Number five was chosen by...
(Number 5 has 4 badges.)
- one person, Lee Kwang Soo. - Okay!
- Okay. - I knew it!
- Let's go. - This is good.
Kwang Soo didn't choose number one!
Thank goodness I didn't choose number five.
I almost chose it.
- This is good. Let's go up. - Let's go up.
- Let's go. - Number four...
with six badges was chosen by...
one member, Park Yu Na.
(Number 4 with 6 badges was chosen by Yu Na.)
- How are you so good at this? - That's incredible.
How are you so good at this?
- Goodness. - How could she?
- I know. - She turned the tables around.
Good job.
Yu Na.
Number three.
Number 3 with 8 persimmon badges...
I hope that it's only two.
was picked by three people, Jong Kook, Haha, and Chi Yeul.
(Three people pick tree number 3.)
Okay, it's okay.
3 to 3 to 2. 1 person gets 2.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - 1 person gets 2.
It's better to take three.
Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay. - Haha.
(Haha wins and gets 3 persimmon badges.)
(Team Yu Na wins three more.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Men play rock.
I don't know how it'll turn out.
There are four of you left.
Number two.
(4 members and 2 persimmon trees remain.)
Those who picked 10.
It's over if everyone picked number two.
(Number 2 has 10 persimmon badges.)
Jae Seok, Mina, and Se Chan.
(3 people picked number 2 tree.)
(Only So Min remains.)
So Min.
So Min picked number one.
(She takes 20 persimmon badges.)
(This is amazing.)
(Team Mina gets 20 more.)
(How is this possible?)
Did no one pick number one?
- Did you not? - Why didn't you?
I definitely thought that you picked it.
- I thought too much. - What's your place?
We didn't place first.
- No. - It's not possible.
Goodness.
As a result,
the winner changed.
With a difference of one, the winner changed.
Team Mina won 32 badges.
(Team Mina turns the tables around.)
Team Yu Na won 31 badges.
- We did? - 31 badges.
We won so many.
You won 31 badges, and they won 32.
(We can't believe that we won.)
Congratulations. Team Tiffany placed last with 21 badges.
The one with the most badges in the winning team gets...
- to register her handwriting. - That's amazing.
So Min will register her handwriting.
(So Min gets to register her handwriting.)
Congratulations.
I'm about to cry.
You're the winner.
- Life can change in one go. - You're impressive, So Min.
I'm about to cry.
So Min might make her debut as a writer.
Yes, it might be soon.
College reports can be written in So Min's handwriting.
Really?
Team Mina won.
(The final winner is Team Mina.)
Except for those to be penalized, you may go home.
- Thank you for your work. - Good job.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(There are 100 persimmons.)
- Seriously. - It's a mess.
I didn't think that I'd be penalized.
I'll think that both of you helped me be on TV longer.
Yes, when else would you peel persimmons?
- Right. - I can't believe I'm peeling them.
You can't peel persimmons when you're in the US.
You're right.
I didn't know that I had such a talent.
Look at how I peeled it.
- Isn't it pretty? - It's very pretty.
It's so pretty.
We might finish before So Min.
This is a penalty.
I didn't know that I had to study the rest.
What I wanted was to go home early.
That's funny.
You shouldn't write carelessly.
That's the charm of handwriting.
I think we're at 100. How many are there?
I'll count.
- 99. - 99.
- 100. - 100.
Success.
Three of you who have finished the penalty...
- may go home. - Okay.
So Min.
- See you. - Being the winner isn't good.
I still have a lot left.
- Thank you. - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
Thank you for your work.
- How did I write L? - Good job.
Make sure to fill the blanks.
Wait,
I'm the winner.
(A tour of tasty restaurants with Jong Kook)
(Stir-fried sundae)
(While they're set on going to the tasty restaurant,)
(something happened.)
(Those who run away all of a sudden)
(Those who can't get caught)
(One who is after them)
(Get down.)
(If they're careless for a moment,)
(everything will disappear.)
(What will be the result of the chase?)
(What Happened in Anyang?)