(On an autumn day with ripe fruits...)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hi.
(Staring)
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Did your style change?
I came back this morning from LA. So I'm in my LA outfit.
In fact, this is my own outfit.
(His LA outfit is different from his all-black outfit in Korea.)
My gosh. Look at this tiger.
(It's hiding behind a cute puppy character.)
- I caught a tiger. - You caught a tiger.
- I got a tiger. - I saw him from the back first.
I was in my car, and I saw him going up.
I was wondering why he wore a vest with the tiger pattern.
- I didn't know. - I realized that it wasn't a vest.
- I only saw Snoopy in the front. - Look at that tiger.
I didn't check the back.
Before you start your mission today,
two guests will be joining our show.
- Are they here? - My gosh.
Let me introduce the lead stars of a new SBS drama...
- Who are they? - to you.
All right. Come on out.
- The drama will be a hit. - Right.
(Who are today's guests?)
- It's Go Min Si. - I see.
- Hello. - And Hwang Bo Ra is here.
- Oh, right. - She's in "Vagabond".
- Hello. - hi.
- Please come to the center. - Hi.
- You're in "Vagabond". - We've met before, Bo Ra.
- Have you been well? - Hello.
(Giggling)
Why is she happy to see Kwang Soo?
Min Si, can you introduce yourself to the viewers?
Hello. My name is Go Min Si.
(This new talented actress...)
(will lead the second half of "Secret Boutique.")
(She's the scene-stealer with her sly role in "The Witch".)
- I was Myung Hee in "The Witch". - Right.
The heroine had a friend.
- Right. - That friend?
She's the friend.
- She was really good. - She spoke with a dialect.
- You ate eggs on the train. - That's right.
- You were that friend? - That's right.
- You were that friend. - My gosh.
I know who you are.
- She's that friend. - You're so pretty now.
- I didn't know she was this pretty. - Is that so?
You're so pretty now.
- She was so good in the movie. - By the way...
Do you die at the end of the movie?
- Pardon? - Do you die?
- Me? I lived. - Yes.
You did? I'm sorry.
(She's surprised.)
- Why did you kill her role? - You didn't watch the movie.
- I'm sorry. - You should look it up online.
- I'm sorry. - Come on, Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. What's up with you? - I'm sorry.
A lot of people died in the movie.
- Right. - A lot of people died in the movie.
- She was in "Live" with me. - Really?
- Yes, we worked together. - Is that so?
What was that drama about?
- What? - "What was that drama about?"
("Live"?)
(What?)
Are you serious right now?
- Haha. - Are you serious or what?
- "Live". - What "Live"?
- I get that I film... Gosh. - I didn't see you sing live.
- You completely ignore me. - Are you talking about "Today"?
- What? What are you talking about? - That's not the same show.
He meant live streaming on Instagram.
(Not that. It's live streaming on Instagram.)
I don't do live streaming on social media.
- It's called "Live". - What "Live"?
- It's not that. It's a drama. - Live streaming on Instagram.
Live streaming on Instagram.
(Min Si's brief introduction is over.)
- This is crazy. - It's hilarious.
It's not on social media.
Min Si is joining us today.
- Bo Ra will also join us today. - Right.
(This irreplaceable scene-stealer puts on superb performances.)
(She's an excellent actress with heart-moving performances.)
(The versatile queen, Hwang Bo Ra)
- Well, Bo Ra worked with Kwang Soo. - Right.
- She was in "Entourage". - That's right.
- What's that? - What's that?
- What? - I see. You wear clothes in large.
- Stop it. - I'm serious. What does that mean?
- Did you hear him? - It says, "Entou" here.
He definitely wears large clothes.
He wears extra-large.
- It's the name of a drama. - It's a drama?
I didn't know you debuted 17 years ago.
- Yes. - I read that you debuted...
after getting hired as the 10th class by the SBS.
- She was hired by the TV station? - You debuted after getting hired...
(Back then, the TV stations used to hire actors and actresses.)
- She was a talent. - She was hired by the station?
- You were on the traditional path. - Right.
I was on the traditional path.
Nowadays, TV stations don't hire actors and actresses.
- They don't? - No, they don't.
- I used to get paid 300 dollars... - My gosh.
and go to work at the SBS station in Tanhyeon.
She's old.
- I see. - Do people say that a lot?
(Hwang Bo Ra, also known as the Oldie)
She's really kind. Earlier, we talked about...
Wait, am I "molder" than you? Sorry, I meant, "older".
- Am I older than you? - Yes, you are.
- Really? - I was born in 1985.
I see. My gosh, I'm so old.
She was born in 1982.
I was born in 1983. My gosh, I'm so old.
(She was born in 1982.)
Anyway...
- You were born in 1983? - Yes.
You weren't born in 1984?
No, I was born in 1983.
- You have a lot of anger in you. - Yes.
- Yes, I do. - She has a lot of anger in her.
- Right. - It's very important.
So you survived in your movie,
- and you were born in 1983. - Yes.
Gosh, Seok Jin. He rarely feels uncomfortable around the guests.
I haven't seen you gather your hands like that for a while.
- No, that's not true. - His ears are so red.
- He's known to be bossy. - No.
- He's really bossy around guests. - Is that so?
I've never seen him retreat.
He leaned back like this.
- There's a gap between them. - You must have a goal then.
(Butting in abruptly)
That came out of nowhere.
That's an odd interview.
You didn't get any sleep last night, did you?
- Did you sleep well? - I slept really well.
- You did? - I went to sleep at 8pm.
I see. You did. I can't get along with them today.
I went to bed early.
What time did you go to bed, Min Si?
I couldn't go to sleep.
- Why not? - Since I have a lot of anger,
I go to yoga early in the morning.
- What time do you go to yoga? - So...
I woke up at 4 a.m. today.
- You went to yoga at 4 a.m.? - Yes.
Why do you go to yoga at 4 a.m.?
I have a lot of anger inside me.
- "Anger"? - To calm your anger?
Yes. When I release energy...
Does your instructor come at 4 a.m. too?
Yes. We do yoga together.
That must be really hard on your instructor.
(Getting territorial)
He's starting now.
- He started. - He'll do that to her.
Here's what I think.
She might get home really late, so she might sleep on her yoga mat.
When Min Si comes, she gets up and says hello to her.
("Extreme Job: How to Be Min Si's Yoga Instructor")
- Goodness. - She's the client, after all.
That's an extreme job.
- Extreme job. - Yes.
Today, you'll divide into 2 teams of 5.
Today's race is called Catch the Thieves Right Under Our Nose.
- I see. - Among you,
- there are two thieves. - Who are they?
- There are thieves? - Shouldn't we start the race...
after catching the thieves first?
Why am I the thief again?
It's really not me.
- You look like a thief today. - No, I'm not.
- I'm not a thief. - You dressed up like one too.
No, it's not true. This outfit is for autumn.
I'm not a thief.
- Your outfit tells that you are. - No, I'm not.
Only the members,
excluding the thieves, will receive 10 gold bars.
The race consists of four rounds.
For each round, the thieves must do hidden missions against the members.
And they can steal the gold bars from the members...
every time they complete a mission.
If the combined number of stolen gold bars goes over 10,
the thieves will win.
However, if the two thieves are on the same team,
all of their completed missions will not count.
And the number of gold bars for the members will not change.
- They can't be on the same team. - We must be smart when we team-up.
(For them to gather gold bars, they must be on different teams.)
We must be smart when we team-up.
My gosh, seriously.
- He sounded really awkward, right? - How...
He didn't mean any of what he said.
"We must be smart when we team-up."
What?
- We can tell right away. - Are you AlphaGo?
After each round,
the number of the gold bars stolen will be revealed to everyone.
And you can find out how many gold bars you have...
after the 2nd and 4th rounds individually.
And the winning team can switch...
a member with another member of the other team after each round.
If you catch both of the thieves,
and their combined stolen bars is under 10, the members will win.
The member with the highest number of gold bars will get a prize.
And the member with the lowest number...
will face the penalty with the thieves.
- Bring in the table now. - There's a table.
What's that?
(What is that?)
What? "Dialect", "Dance".
- "Flexibility". - What's this?
I'll go for the dialect.
All right. Starting now,
the thieves will begin their hidden missions.
- Starting now? - You can start your missions now.
There are hidden missions.
- What are you doing? - I was stretching.
There are hidden missions. What are you doing?
- I was stretching. No, it's not me. - That was so random.
I was just stretching.
Jong Kook just rubbed his eyes.
Hold on. This is ridiculous.
When I was touching my nose, she looked at me.
So I stopped for no reason.
(So Min looked at him when he touched his nose.)
(My nose is itchy.)
(Is that the mission?)
- All of a sudden, - I mean...
- he flinched. - when she looked at me...
But if that's the hidden mission, it's too easy.
It'd be obvious.
The first mission will decide your teams.
It's called Pick Me Up.
The guests will be the team captains...
and scout four members to their teams.
The members will choose 1 out of 4 keywords for talents.
Two members and the two guests who chose the same keyword...
will have a battle of the talent, and the winner of the battle...
will get one point.
And the winner can pick the team for the member who chose the word.
(Smirking)
(Approaching while the rule is being explained)
- I'll go for this. - Same here.
- This is mine. - Me too.
I got it.
I ought to go for this.
Hey, give back the dialect badge.
- Give it back. - I need that too.
- Jae Seok, go for the dance badge. - Stop it.
- You should go for that. - Hey.
Do you need a beating to come to your senses?
(Speaking with a dialect all of a sudden)
"Do you need a beating to come to your senses?"
My gosh, Jae Seok.
- Listen. That belongs to me. - "Listen"?
I said, "listen".
- "Listen"? - "Listen. That belongs to me."
My gosh, she's speaking with the dialect.
- "Listen". - She just spoke with the dialect.
I'm really awful at this.
- Do we just pick one? - Special talents?
- There's nothing to pick from. - Just like this?
- I hate dancing. - Yes.
- I hate dancing too. - Why...
- I'm not flexible at all. - I'm stuck with this.
Ji Hyo chose the dance badge.
- Hey. - There's nothing I can do here.
But she's pretty good at dancing nowadays.
- She's pretty good now. - Yes, that's right.
(Dancing? That's a piece of cake.)
(Dialect: Jae Seok and Jong Kook, Dance: Ji Hyo and So Min,)
(Flexibility: Seok Jin and Haha, Tricks: Kwang Soo and Se Chan)
All right. As for the first talent,
- it's the battle of dialect. - I see.
- It's the dialect. - Use the members' names...
to do an acrostic poem while speaking with a dialect.
- The best poem will win this round. - I see.
- Jae Seok, why are you there? - Why did you pick that?
I chose the dialect badge.
- I'm good at that. - Use the members' names?
(Jae Seok will go up against Jong Kook.)
The members who chose the dialect badge and the guests...
- will play this round. - The four of us?
- I see. - The best member will win.
Go ahead, Bo Ra.
Hold on. This is all very sudden.
Why don't you run your mouth now?
(Launching the first attack)
- What did you say? - Run your mouth now.
Why don't you run your mouth? Go ahead.
No, we don't say that. No one uses that expression.
They sound so awkward. Why are they speaking with a dialect?
(She's blunt.)
You guys are terrible.
Jong Kook sounds a bit awkward, right?
- No. - They are awful.
- You guys are terrible at it. - They are terrible.
- You're awful. - We're good.
- We're good at it. - Then...
Who wants to go first?
- I'll go first. - Okay, Min Si.
- I'll use Kwang Soo's name. - Kwang Soo's name?
- Let's do this. - Okay.
- Speak with the dialect. - Okay.
- L. - L.
(Exclamation)
(She starts smoothly with an exclamation.)
- K. - That's the Jeolla dialect.
Kwang Soo? I know him.
Isn't he that guy?
- S. - S.
(It's going quite well. How will she finish the poem?)
Sorghum straw.
(He's a sorghum straw.)
- She's good. - He's a long stick, sorghum straw.
- She's good. - Yes, she's good.
- That's the Chungcheong dialect. - Isn't he a sorghum straw?
Sorghum straw.
That was great.
You're up, Bo Ra.
Bo Ra, aren't you good at speaking with a dialect?
Yes, I'm from Busan.
Well, speaking with a dialect is a piece of cake.
- You're from Busan? - That's the authentic dialect.
I'll do a poem with Jae Seok's name.
With my name? Great.
All right. Y.
Yu Jae Seok's work...
J.
J... Hold on.
- Are you finished? - Hold on.
It's been a while since I saw a guest's chin shake like that.
(Shaking)
Bo Ra, you can do it.
(Her acrostic poem isn't as good as her dialect.)
- Bo Ra's chin... - Just say something.
Jae Seok's work... J...
- I'll use Min Si's name. - I see.
All right. G.
Gosh, enough. I've had it enough.
M.
(Gosh, enough. I've had it enough.)
(Impressed)
Man, what are you doing in the folk village?
- S. - S.
(She just needs to finish the poem with the last syllable.)
(Will she be able to redeem her reputation as the local from Busan?)
Stream water.
You scared me for a second.
(A random line)
She just made it sound bold. That's it.
- She's just saying whatever. - She's just blurting it out.
- I almost had it. - She said whatever she thought of.
Jae Seok, show them what you've got.
- Go for it. - Shall I?
Jae Seok, go for it.
- The problem is... - Which dialect?
- his acrostic poems are awful. - They are awful?
(His acrostic poems are awful.)
What should we do? Should we change your talent?
- He might be good at the dialect. - Should we let you change?
Be quiet.
- Just give me anything. - Do one with Bo Ra's name.
- Hwang Bo Ra? Okay. - Yes.
- All right. Here we go. H. - H.
Hwang Bo Ra. I've been watching you.
(What kind of dialect is that?)
You know what? Let me take a good look.
- I think I've seen you somewhere. - He's trying to think right now.
I keep getting confused about where I've seen you from.
- B. - I think it was around Haeundae.
(I'm not done yet.)
- Hey, move onto the next syllable. - I might've seen you there.
- Or I might be mistaken. - B.
Right now, he's scared of B the most.
Banging my head against a wall,
I was still confused if it was Bo Ra or not.
Are you doing pansori?
- R. - R.
Are you on the radio show too?
(That was the simplest way to wrap up the poem.)
He only thought of the last line.
But he couldn't come up with the second line.
- Hey, be quiet. - You only thought of the last one.
- But you did it. - You'd better be quiet.
- Let me do it with Seok Jin's name. - This is hard.
- J. - J.
"Jee" thinks he's a comedian or whatnot.
He was acting all pretentious.
- "Pretentious"? - S.
- S. - S.
Seok Jin. You're not a comedian.
- He sounds like a drunk. - J.
(It's a poem by a drunk, not a man with a dialect.)
Join another industry before it's too late.
(You should've quit being a comedian long ago.)
(The 54-year-old comedian is knocked out.)
Are you drunk?
- Hey. - Are you drunk?
You should've changed your profession long ago.
Jae Seok. Don't try to win with your quantity.
I'll do one with Kwang Soo's name.
- You have one for him too? - Kwang Soo.
- My gosh, he's a master. - I'll do one with his name.
- L. - L.
Lost your tooth?
- K. - Kwang Soo.
- S. - S.
(Will he be able to wrap up his poem well this time?)
Soo Bin is your girlfriend, right?
Who's Soo Bin?
(Is his girlfriend's name "Soo Bin" using the dialect?)
Who's Soo Bin? Who is she?
(You'd better clear this up. She'll get the wrong idea.)
Who is she?
(Jae Seok is number 1 when it comes to bold poems.)
- This is hilarious. - Soo Bin?
- I think he got the wrong name. - I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Not yet.
- I'm sorry. - Old men often get the names wrong.
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook should go next.
What should I do?
- I'll go with... - That was so funny.
- Min Si's name. - Min Si's name.
- Min Si's name. - G.
Gosh, what is your name?
(Gosh, what is your name?)
(He starts the poem with a heart-melting line.)
- He's going for the romantic vibe. - That was heart-fluttering.
- M. - M.
Min Si... Was that your name?
"Was that your name?"
- S. - S.
Spare me some of your time for a cup of tea.
(Do you want to have a cup of tea, Min Si?)
My gosh, you've still got it!
(You're a man!)
(Approaching)
Why?
Why are you teasing me?
- Jong Kook, you still got it! - Okay.
It's been a while since he had a love interest.
Her reaction was great.
- This isn't "Mom's Diary". - "Mom's Diary".
- All right. You can evaluate them. - Okay.
We do?
1, 2, 3.
(They need to pick the better one.)
(Who gave the better acrostic poem?)
- Go Min Si! - Oh, Go Min Si?
(He's greatly disappointed.)
You shouldn't have kept your hopes up.
- Were you anticipating? - Why do you look so lost?
It's neither of you two.
- I'm flabbergasted. - Goodness.
Fine.
What does she need to do?
She can pick one of you as her teammate.
He'll probably pick Jong Kook.
- Min Si. - We don't know.
They're anticipating.
(Whom will she pick?)
It must be a dilemma.
I bet she already made a decision.
(Will she choose a romantic partner or more screen time?)
I pick...
- Jong Kook. - Okay!
(She picks Jong Kook.)
Thank you.
- I knew it. - That's great.
- We meet again. - Right.
This is great.
The next category is dance.
- Dance? - Dance?
- Nice. - That's terrible.
This time, it's Ji Hyo and So Min.
- This is painful. - They're back.
We will play some songs randomly.
One person will dance at a time, and the best dancer wins.
Shall we start with the guests?
- Shall we? - Do they all have to do it?
We all have to dance?
My gosh.
I'm terrible at dancing.
- Oh, no. - She's nervous.
(They're shooting right now.)
She's so laidback.
(But she acts comfortably in front of the camera.)
- She is. - She is.
- Every time she moves, - She was officially recruited.
I smell leather.
(Every time she moves, I smell leather.)
- Really? - It smells really strong.
He's right.
- All right. - Who will go first?
This time,
- you should go first. - I'll go.
- Give me some music. - Give her some music.
Don't you have any?
She was on "Love Letter" before.
- Right. - She's experienced.
- What is this? - "Single Ladies".
This is such an old song.
I don't know how to dance to this.
- I'll go. - Really? Gosh.
(Min Si intercepts.)
- Min Si. - She's amazing.
(She transforms.)
(It's Min Si's time.)
She's good.
(She moves her hips.)
- She's good. - Look at her.
She wanted to brag.
(I'm the best dancer.)
- She's like So Min. - She's the type...
who'll brag about her talents.
(The music changes.)
They used to play these songs at the club back in the day.
(She tries again.)
- The songs are difficult. - She's good.
- She's a good dancer. - You're right.
Right?
(The leather jacket lady grabs their attention.)
Dance to the song.
(Here comes the leather jacket lady.)
Gosh, Bo Ra.
- Gosh, Bo Ra. - Look at her.
- We can't beat her. - What's up with your mouth?
She wasn't always like this.
- I can't beat her. - What's up with her mouth?
(She's brazen.)
- Good job. - What's up with her mouth?
How can we beat her?
(It's a more upbeat song.)
(She's on a roll.)
Hold on.
What's wrong with your mouth?
Why do you keep pouting?
- She looks so annoying. - She's so brazen.
She's so brazen.
- Look at how brazen she is. - You're the best.
- Look at her. - My gosh.
(She gave it her best.)
Who's next?
(It's a children's song.)
How do I dance to this?
(Let me show you.)
(She performs a cute dance.)
- 1, 2, 3. - Good.
Her dance skills have improved.
They have improved. She can choreograph her dance moves.
So Min, what are you doing?
(She feels competitive.)
My gosh.
I can't stand her.
Who dances like that to children's songs?
This song is for children!
- My gosh. - That's so provocative!
- Ji Hyo is shocked too. - My gosh.
I'm astonished.
What's wrong with you?
Dream watches our show!
(My son watches this show!)
(For now, it's a show for adults.)
- My gosh. - I can't believe her.
(Flip the channel for a minute, Dream.)
What's wrong with you?
Go inside.
- Go. - What are you doing?
(She never listens.)
- Go. - Go away!
(He's afraid.)
- What is she doing? - I said, go away.
(I am the sexiest dancer.)
The most annoying part was...
not only her dance but when she did this.
(She sang, "knock, knock".)
- It was so annoying. - She said she's so sexy.
I know how that feels.
I was so sexy.
I think there are two people who were good.
- You're right. - I was amazed at Bo Ra.
Please evaluate them.
(Whoever gets the majority of the picks wins.)
I feel like So Min did better.
- Pick Bo Ra. - Okay.
Okay.
- I knew it'd be her. - Pick between her...
- and So Min. - Okay.
- She was invincible. - So Min was just doing her job.
(So Min was just doing her job.)
Right.
Isn't she an actress.
- No, she isn't. - I was working.
- I was working. - She was.
- Bo Ra. - Let's shout it out.
- 1, 2, 3. - Bo Ra!
(Bo Ra wins.)
Thank you.
- Do I pick? - Yes, between those two.
I pick So Min.
(She picks So Min.)
- She picked someone similar. - She did.
The dancing queens have met.
- Goodness. - They're similar to each other.
- She always picks someone similar. - I see.
It'd be chaotic if both of them danced.
- Let's watch. - Can we...
watch them dance?
To children's songs.
Dancing is the way to go.
They'll definitely win all dancing matches for the day.
Here we go.
This is a celebratory dance.
- A celebratory dance? - Are we dancing?
- I can't wait to find out. - How sexy will they be?
(Shall we start off cute?)
(She refuses.)
Look at her mouth.
(Everyone is fixated on her.)
(They're on fire.)
Why are you following her?
- Wait. - My gosh.
- What's wrong with her mouth? - What's going on?
That's enough. Stop the music.
(They refuse to calm down.)
That's enough. Go back.
What's wrong with your mouth?
Both of them...
start dancing with their faces.
(Their facial expressions do most of the work.)
- That was hilarious! - They looked...
- They looked so content. - My gosh!
- They're the worst. - She wasn't like this before.
So this is how she is now.
- She was always like this. - Really?
(Min Si picks Seok Jin, and Bo Ra picks Haha.)
Isn't that a bad thing?
- Really? It's bad? - Yes.
This category is trivial tricks.
Min Si told me...
that she could open a bottle with her toes.
With her toes?
I'm sure the bottle can be opened easily.
- Maybe you need to turn the cap. - Is it a can?
(These are real glass bottles.)
- With a bottle opener. - Oh, I see.
Gosh, how many is that?
- How is that possible? - My toes will cramp up.
- My toes are naturally... - How is this possible?
- very strong. - That's true.
He's right.
If Kwang Soo is going to do it,
- you need to censor it. - Why?
- Why? - His toes are rotten.
(He exposes a secret.)
- They're not. - Really?
- Yes, they are. - No, don't be ridiculous.
- Really? Let me see. - His big toe is rotten.
There's nothing to see. It's not rotten.
(This is the story behind his toes.)
(His best friend, Gook Ju, confirmed it.)
It's just injured!
(They mistook his bruised toe as rotten.)
It looks like moss growing on a tree.
I suddenly don't like him too much.
It's not rotten.
(She doesn't like him.)
- It's not rotten. - I suddenly changed my mind.
Gosh, he really turned me off.
It's not rotten.
- He's using full care for it. - It's not like that.
- It was bruised. - He's using full care.
- What? - "Full care"?
- It's not true. - What's the name of that ointment?
- The full care is doing him well. - It's not rotten.
- Foot care. - Foot care.
- Is it foot care? - Foot care.
What's "full care" then?
My gosh.
Whoever opens the most bottles in a minute wins.
How do you do it?
How do you open it?
She practiced this at home.
- That's right. - No, I haven't.
Get ready.
- Set... - Go.
It works.
(The bottle makes a refreshing sound.)
- It works. - No way.
(The master is here.)
Keep going.
She's so strange.
(Why is she so good?)
- How is she so good? - This isn't a useful skill.
- Five. - How much time is left?
- Ten seconds. - What?
- Eight. - It's not easy to grab onto it.
This should be on "What on Earth!"
You're right.
(She opens them easily.)
- 10 bottles. - 10 bottles.
She opened 10 bottles.
It's 1 every 10 seconds.
- It's 1 every 10 seconds. - How is she so good?
That was quick.
- Next up is Kwang Soo. - I have trust in you.
Let me see your big toe.
(His foot is revealed.)
No, no.
- No, it's not rotten. - Let me see it.
I injured it.
No, it's not rotten.
Let me see it.
- Good. - You got a pedicure.
This isn't embarrassing. It's not rotten.
(He's embarrassed to show it.)
You look so embarrassed.
Here we go.
Get ready, set...
(His rotten toe is on the line.)
- Your toe is too close. - Don't use your hand.
- It shouldn't be close up. - It should be far.
- Grab it from a distance. - Grab it from a distance.
Good. You'll get more force that way. Good.
Hurry up!
(Jae Seok is slow.)
- Put it over it. - We should copy him.
That's good.
What's wrong with you?
What? I'm handing it over to you.
That's good.
(Screaming)
(He's busy.)
(He's so hilarious.)
- That's good. Put it over. - He's so funny!
There's no more.
(There's no more.)
It's behind you!
Really?
(Why is he in a hurry?)
- Get one more open. - It's going well.
That's too bad.
- Right. - That was close.
- Unbelievable. - You did well though.
- But... - Here we go.
- Ready... - Ready, set...
Why is he holding it that way?
(Pop!)
(A clear sound)
Is it easier that way?
(His foot is faster than his hand.)
Gosh.
He's so good at this.
It seems so natural.
Could the sound be any more appetizing?
(100 percent automated system)
- He doesn't even need his hands. - No way.
My gosh.
Can you believe this?
(A human conveyor belt)
(Yang Se Chan, factory worker)
Go, Se Chan!
It's as if he's using his hands.
Can you get me 10 more bottles?
(He has already popped all the allocated bottles.)
(The factory is on a roll!)
- Hurry! - I can't believe this.
He's so good at this.
Just like that. Exactly.
Are you done?
That was 37 seconds.
(Anyone can tell that he won.)
(He popped 10 bottles in 37 seconds.)
You might be able to pop about 18 bottles.
(He should get a medallion for his performance.)
- That was amazing. - You were great.
- That was awesome. - Se Chan...
This is what you call talent.
Se Chan, you can choose your team.
I...
choose Team Bo Ra.
(Se Chan joins Team Bo Ra.)
Right.
You still have it.
So you chose to be with your girlfriend.
Come on.
You chose your girlfriend.
(Gosh, I almost took her hand.)
Gosh, I almost took her hand.
I almost responded.
- Why didn't you take it? - That's not it.
- It's not what you think. - My gosh.
No, not like that. Take my hand like this.
(Clasp our fingers together.)
Let me go over the rules again.
If the thieves are on one team,
the hidden missions so far will be null and void.
If the thieves are on different teams,
they will have stolen the gold bars from others.
It also means that the hidden missions were carried out.
If the thieves are on the same team,
- one will want to switch teams. - Okay.
- Right. - So let me reveal...
the total number of gold bars that the thieves have.
- The thieves started off with zero. - Right.
They win if they end up with more than 10.
All right. The number of gold bars that the thieves currently have...
(The number of gold bars that the thieves currently have...)
They have four.
(They have four.)
- What? - So they succeeded four times?
They have four.
- Hold on. - I think it's Se Chan.
It has to be. It's Se Chan.
- I'm 100 percent sure. - Me too.
- These two. - Hold on a second.
Do they steal one gold bar per hidden mission?
- Yes, 1. - Yes, 1 for 1.
- So they succeeded four times. - Kwang Soo...
punched Jae Seok in the stomach a few times.
The dialect Jae Seok spoke in...
How many times did Kwang Soo punch his stomach?
- I counted four. - Wait, that's...
(Was punching Jae Seok's stomach a hidden mission?)
- No way... - That could've been it.
(Is Haha trying to frame Kwang Soo or has Kwang Soo been caught?)
It doesn't mean that one thief succeeded four times.
- It was split. - The 2 thieves did it 4 times.
It could be 2 and 2 or 3 and 1.
One thief could've succeeded four times as well.
(The thieves could've collectively carried out the missions.)
Who did the most missions? It was Jae Seok.
- What do you mean? - You did the most.
You spoke all the dialects.
- You're right! - Jae Seok...
- He's right. - It can be Jae Seok.
He kept speaking in a dialect.
Captain Hwang, you must think this through.
Don't easily jump to conclusions.
But Jae Seok spoke in a lot of dialects.
- Hold on. - Which of the teams...
Min Si, who do you think is the thief?
Who's the most suspicious?
- Out of everyone here... - These two.
- Me? - Then leave them on one team.
They must be on the same team for us to protect our gold bars.
Put them on one team.
Min Si, pick a teammate.
Yes, let's get this over with.
- I choose Se Chan. - Me?
Why?
(Min Si chooses Se Chan!)
- Me? - Why?
- I'm bringing him to my team. - Right.
- I want him on my team. - You don't suspect me, right?
- I don't. - Your choice startled me.
- Who will you kick out? - Then...
I'll kick Seok Jin out.
- Me? - This isn't right.
- What? - Why him?
- There's no reason for this. - Why?
- He's not a thief. - It won't be Seok Jin.
Hear me out.
I don't think he's the thief.
Then I choose Kwang Soo.
- Nice. - Wait, hold on.
You should choose who you think is the thief.
Yes, you.
- Then... - Kwang Soo, get over here.
Am I staying? All right.
- Mr. Thief? - Hold on a second.
- What now? - If Kwang Soo isn't a thief,
then having him will increase our chances of winning games.
- Exactly. - You have a point.
Come on, just make a decision!
(Hurry up and make a decision!)
Seok Jin, wait.
Seriously?
I'm sorry, but can we play this game without him?
Hurry up already!
It's better if he doesn't play.
- Seok Jin, we're sorry. - I'll just follow...
the original decision.
- Having Kwang Soo is better. - It's done, then.
- It's done. - It's been decided.
Okay, it's over.
- Okay. - We have other rounds.
You'll now get changed and begin Round Two.
- Okay. - Nice.
Why do you keep doing this?
Guys, let's go.
Once again, the thieves can carry out their hidden missions.
- Okay. - I should keep my eyes peeled open.
It's hard to see when seated like this.
Round Two is all about the chemistry between teammates.
This is Protect One's Name.
- Protect One's Name? - Does it involve name tags?
- What is it? - Two from each team will compete.
One will head to Gongdeok Station in disguise...
and carry out a mission while having...
their names being called the least.
While wearing a simple disguise?
- Hold on. - You shouldn't get recognized.
- At a subway station? - The team with the member...
who had his or her name called the least wins.
We should make Kwang Soo do it.
It has to be Kwang Soo. He stands out too easily.
- Kwang Soo. - Then we choose Jae Seok.
He can't cover his mouth though.
Don't take off your glasses either.
- You can't ask that. - Why not?
Captain?
Let's choose Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok, yes. - We'll choose Jae Seok.
Okay, it'll be Jae Seok.
- Yes, Jae Seok. - Then the two will be...
- Kwang Soo and... - Jae Seok.
This will be neck and neck.
I'm slightly feeling the pressure though.
- Kwang Soo's height... - Exactly. He's so tall.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are ready to go.)
Hey, it's Jae Seok!
It's Jae Seok.
There's Yu Jae Seok.
- Yu Jae Seok! - It's Jae Seok.
Anyone can tell it's Jae Seok.
I mean...
Are you an idiot?
How is this a decent disguise?
Wait, there's Kwang Soo!
I can't tell if it's him.
You can't be sure it's him.
Kwang Soo looks like a foreigner.
You can't tell, right?
I really can't tell.
- No, it's Kwang Soo for sure. - Your stride gives it away.
Walk with a wilder stride.
Wide and clumpy.
- But... - That's it!
- I can't tell that it's him. - Nice.
Meanwhile, you look exactly like yourself.
Who can grow a mustache like this?
Is it even possible?
I told you to not go too far.
His mustache seems real, but yours doesn't.
No one will recognize me.
- As if. - They won't.
You will now head to Gongdeok Station.
Many who look like this stroll around.
- We're done for. - It's over.
You don't know what your mission is yet.
- Right. - Take these two objects.
A smartphone and a transportation card.
- Okay. - Even a smartphone?
Find the mission in Gongdeok Station and carry it out.
- In Gongdeok Station? - Yes.
We'll count how many times your names get called.
(They head inside Gongdeok Station curious about the mission.)
(A wild stride)
No one recognizes me.
What did I tell you?
(Jae Seok's proud of his disguise.)
(There aren't many people on the way to the station.)
(The two will head to different exits.)
- Jae Seok... - Kwang Soo!
Yes?
(Jae Seok openly yells Kwang Soo's name.)
Jae Seok, good luck.
(Kwang Soo fights back.)
(Luckily, the people didn't hear them.)
(While the two head to Gongdeok Station...)
Do I go in there?
The others will play Cham, Cham, Cham.
- All right. - Got it.
(What's with the Cham, Cham, Cham?)
While the two carry out their missions,
you will be playing a game indoors as well.
This is an upgraded version of Cham, Cham, Cham.
A member from each team will play at a time wearing these gloves.
Even though you get slapped,
if you maintain a smile,
it'll be counted as a successful defense.
The winning team will spin the wheel once...
while the losing team will spin it twice.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo must carry out the penalties.
How about the ladies? Ji Hyo will go first.
Ji Hyo and Bo Ra then.
This will be neck and neck.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
I'm not good at this game though.
Grab it tight.
She's not someone predictable.
- Her reactions, right? - Yes.
- Reaction Queen. - Hold on.
Bo Ra's digging a hole in the foam.
- Look at her hand. - Is that allowed?
Her hand will come out at the other end at this rate.
Do the same thing, Ji Hyo.
Bo Ra sure is competitive.
Rock-paper-scissors, guys. With your left hand.
Ji Hyo, you're playing rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(Bo Ra wins and will play offense.)
Cham, cham, cham
- What? - Hey, hold on.
- She won. - Bo Ra, it's your turn.
(Bo Ra should be playing offense.)
(But Ji Hyo played offense instead.)
(She's clueless when it comes to the rules.)
Did she win?
Did she? Hold on.
- Even I was confused. - Me too.
She was supposed to be on the offense.
Did I win? Really?
- My gosh. - Seriously?
Didn't you know?
Am I playing offense?
- I just sat there. - Play Cham, Cham, Cham.
Play Cham, Cham, Cham.
Cham, cham, cham
(Bo Ra wins and gets a chance to slap Ji Hyo.)
- What? - Cham, cham, cham
- Wait, you won. - You won!
(Bo Ra won so she gets to slap you!)
(Why are you playing Cham, Cham, Cham again?)
You won.
- Do I slap her? - Yes.
Why are you so bad at this?
- You won, so slap her. - I see.
(Thump)
(Can Ji Hyo smile after this?)
(Smiling)
- Hold on. - Are you all right?
(Ji Hyo...)
- Gosh, I'm sorry. - You slap her and then apologize?
- I'm sorry. - Okay. Go again.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Bo Ra wins.)
Cham, cham, cham
(Bo Ra wins another slap.)
- Nice. - Are they idiots?
- Unbelievable. - This is fun though.
Ji Hyo's still smiling.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Bo Ra wins for the third time with paper.)
- Hold on. - Cham, cham, cham
(She wins for the third time with the same direction.)
- Cham, cham, cham - Hold on a second.
Ji Hyo, is it impossible to look the other way?
Look this way too. Why are you only looking that way?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- Now... - Cham, cham, cham
- Gosh. - Okay.
- Start right away. - Cham, cham, cham
(Bo Ra loses this time.)
Okay! Hit hard.
(Let me pay you back this time.)
- Hit as hard as you can. - Smack her!
- Smack her! - Smack her!
(Will Bo Ra be able to keep a smile on her face?)
(Smack)
(She fails to keep a smile.)
- Ji Hyo wins. - Ji Hyo wins by hitting hard.
(Knockout)
Ji Hyo wins by hitting hard.
- I failed to smile, right? - You failed to smile.
- You're out. - You didn't smile?
Ji Hyo.
I think you still lost.
- Why do I feel like I lost? - How many times did you get hit?
How many times did you get hit?
- I feel... - Good job.
- How many times did you get hit? - She got hit many times.
Spin the roulette wheel now.
I'll spin it.
(What penalty will be given to Kwang Soo?)
- A cartwheel would be the easiest. - Not the name tag, please.
(Fan-meet group dance)
No!
- Fan-meet group dance. - That's...
How long does he have to dance?
For 30 seconds.
For 30 seconds?
The group dance?
Spin it.
The machine gun, please.
(Jae Seok will be given 2 penalties.)
- Laughing out loud for 10 seconds. - Wait.
Laughing out loud.
- Spin it one more time. - Spin it again.
Spin it hard. 1, 2, 3.
- Please. - We get two penalties.
- Okay. - Asking for directions.
- Asking for directions. - That's not good.
My goodness.
I'll let them know now.
(Jae Seok is satisfied with his disguise.)
(No one will recognize me, right?)
(He manages to go into the station without being noticed by others.)
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
You're given a penalty.
Gosh.
You get two penalties, actually.
Why do I get two?
One is to laugh out loud for 10 seconds.
And the other is to ask for directions.
You have to perform both of them.
My goodness.
The thing is...
I do look suspicious,
but no one seems to recognize me.
(This is going pretty well so far.)
- Do the group dance for 30 seconds. - What?
(The producer approaches him.)
(And he walks away.)
The group dance?
(In the middle of the street?)
Where?
(The other members can see them through a video call.)
There they are.
That's Kwang Soo, and that's Jae Seok?
That's Kwang Soo, and that's Jae Seok.
It's fun to watch someone secretly.
- Right. - It's always fun.
Gosh.
(Jae Seok is whining without knowing he's being watched.)
(Just then)
(Surprised)
Aren't you Yu Jae Seok?
(His name has already been said once.)
(The disguise expert faces his first crisis.)
(Laughing)
(Faced with a crisis, he starts laughing out loud.)
(He's attracting attention.)
He's laughing out loud.
(Yes, I'm Yu Jae Seok.)
(Captain Hwang has given up now.)
(Naturally, more and more people come to see him.)
(It wouldn't be strange even if the police showed up.)
Right?
(A textbook example of laughing out loud)
(Embarrassed)
(He's done laughing out loud for 10 seconds.)
(It's time to ask for directions.)
Well... Excuse me.
How do I get to Gongdeok Station?
- This is Gongdeok Station. - It is?
- You're Yu Jae Seok, right? - Yes.
(He ends up having a conversation.)
Can I get a picture with you?
- There. - They recognized him.
- Two people recognized him. - My goodness.
They're taking a picture with him.
They're taking a picture with Jae Seok. Nice!
Can I get a picture with you?
I'm not Yu Jae Seok right now.
- You're not? - No.
- I think you are. - I'm not.
I can't be.
- Please ignore me. - I want a picture with you.
Please ignore me. I beg you.
I'm sorry.
I'm carrying out a mission.
- He's Yu Jae Seok, right? - No.
- Are you Yu Jae Seok? - No.
Please imagine I'm not.
(Yu Jae Seok appears, but he is not Yu Jae Seok?)
No, I'm not.
(I'm sorry.)
(I have to walk boldly.)
What's with Kwang Soo's walk?
Why is he walking like that?
(His height and weird way of walking are attracting attention.)
(I even have to dance here?)
[VIU Ver] SBS E474 Running Man
"Catch the Thieves Right Under Our Nose Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(He starts dancing in the middle of the street.)
(What is that?)
(Even the other members feel embarrassed.)
- Someone is taking pictures. - Who?
(- That's Lee Kwang Soo! - What is he doing?)
(He even dances better than at the fan-meet.)
(He tries to look cool.)
(He even sweeps the streets around Gongdeok Station.)
You're done.
(He's done dancing for 30 seconds.)
(He finally realizes people have been watching him.)
(Citizen 1)
(No one has said his name yet.)
(Suddenly)
Are you Lee Kwang Soo?
Pardon? How did you...
How did you know?
(He becomes a Pied Piper.)
(Lee Kwang Soo's fan-meet is held at Gongdeok Station.)
- Pardon? - You're Lee Kwang Soo, right?
You're Lee Kwang Soo.
Please stop saying that.
(Surprised)
I'm carrying out a mission.
Bye.
(If he doesn't finish his mission, his name will keep being said.)
(Jae Seok is going to look for a mission on the platform.)
I see something.
(A lot of artwork is displayed on the platform.)
(He scans the picture with the phone that the staff gave him.)
(What are these works of art?)
Oh, it's moving.
This person is dancing.
This must not be the mission.
(Is today's mission hidden among the artwork?)
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo is looking at the artwork too.)
Lee Kwang Soo!
(Attention, everyone!)
You're Lee Kwang Soo from Running Man.
You're Lee Kwang Soo, right?
(Panicking)
(Restless)
(What?)
Isn't that Yu Jae Seok?
(Jae Seok runs away.)
Wait.
(Jae Seok notices something and stops.)
There's this one too.
(There are pictures on the other wall too.)
(The man looks somewhat awkward.)
(He scans the picture with his phone.)
(He swipes the screen.)
(The lethargic-looking assistant director appears.)
(The banner reads, "Find me.")
(The hidden mission for Round 2 is to find the assistant director.)
(Hurrying)
Is he done?
(Where is he going?)
I saw him.
(Jae Seok passed by this booth earlier.)
(Why is he back here?)
I found him.
(Jae Seok finds the assistant director.)
(I found you.)
You've completed your mission.
(Jae Seok has completed his mission.)
My goodness.
- I'm burning up. - Kwang Soo.
Let me announce the final result.
The number of times their names were said.
- I can't wait. - Kwang Soo's name was said...
- eight times. - That's not a lot.
- It's only eight times. - That's not a lot.
- Is it not a lot? - The thing is,
people were suspicious, but they didn't say my name.
(He looked way too suspicious.)
Jae Seok's name was said...
(How many times was Jae Seok's name said?)
Twenty times.
(It's a complete defeat.)
(Because of his clumsy disguise, many people said his name.)
You were so sure no one would recognize you.
Not many people recognized me.
Did you count the ones who whispered too?
Some people said his name after he passed by.
The next representatives will be sent out now.
- How about we send female members? - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo and So Min. - That sounds good.
So Min should go.
- Ji Hyo should go too. - No one will recognize me.
No one recognizes me when I'm alone.
I need Se Chan and Kwang Soo to be recognized by people.
- When I'm alone... - I think So Min...
(Who will win the second match?)
How about they don't cover their faces?
- That sounds good. - That'd be fair.
(They look like they're going to a convenience store.)
We eat it a lot.
That's Song Ji Hyo. They must be shooting Running Man.
My goodness.
(That's Song Ji Hyo.)
(They're recognized only 5 seconds in.)
- What did she say? - "They're shooting Running Man."
I'm having regrets.
- Is my jacket too bright? - You stand out too much.
My eyes are hurting.
Let's start the game.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok wins the chance to initiate Cham, cham, cham.)
- Cham, cham, cham. - Jae Seok, you can start.
- Cham, cham, cham - Okay!
- Continue. - You can attack now.
Cham, cham, cham. Okay!
(Jae Seok loses.)
- Smack him! - Do it!
(Laughing)
(He puts on a big smile.)
There you go. He passes.
- It's not easy. - He passes.
- This feels so nice. - He passes.
Okay.
Cham, cham, cham
Good job.
(He changed the direction right away.)
Did you say, "Good job"?
- Jae Seok. - You did a very good job.
Is this allowed?
- Is this allowed? - He changed the direction too late.
- It's allowed. Jae Seok fooled you. - Right.
Cham, cham, cham
(It's my turn.)
(Kwang Soo succeeded at first.)
(Cham, cham, cham, cham?)
That's cheating.
What?
Hold on.
- He smiled, so it's okay. - I definitely...
(Is this allowed?)
It's my habit.
- Is it really okay? - It's just my habit.
Why do you have to say "cham" only three times?
- You can say it 5 or 14 times too. - Okay!
- I won't do it again. - Okay!
Cham, cham, cham, cham, cham...
Why aren't you moving?
(Jae Seok isn't moving.)
(Aren't you going to play the game?)
It's just my know-how.
(Kwang Soo tries his know-how again.)
(Jae Seok succeeds.)
(Jae Seok sees through Kwang Soo's know-how.)
That was close.
Hey!
Why didn't you continue?
- You should have continued. - Hey!
- Exactly. - Why did you end it?
Cham, cham, cham...
(He ends up following the hand.)
(He fails to smile.)
(He quickly puts on a smile.)
Kwang Soo failed.
Kwang Soo isn't a fool!
- All right. - Kwang Soo isn't a fool!
- Kwang Soo. - I did it.
- Cham, cham, cham. - I am good at this game.
You really are good at this game.
(The results of the roulette are sent!)
How is it that no one recognizes me?
So Min, please stop for a second.
Is it time to do the mission?
Pretend to get shot by a machine gun realistically.
- Here? - Yes.
(She gets into the emotion.)
How should I do it?
(Shooting)
(Did Ji Hyo get hit?)
(Having gotten the cartwheel as a penalty,)
(Ji Hyo jumped in as soon as she saw So Min.)
(It's a cartwheel.)
(It looks like she has been shot.)
(It's an intense battle between the two actresses.)
- I am dying. - I am in tears.
I am dying.
(They watch a scene from a war movie together.)
Was that a cartwheel?
That was a cartwheel.
I am dying.
It's Jeon So Min!
(After revealing So Min's identity, Ji Hyo escapes...)
(and begins to do the group dance.)
(Ji Hyo's dance doesn't look perfect anymore.)
That hurts.
They're filming Running Man!
That's Song Ji Hyo! No way!
(She freezes on the spot.)
- This is incredible. - They're filming Running Man.
(She runs away.)
(She catches her breath.)
It's Song Ji Hyo! How cool!
(Ji Hyo, you are the best.)
Ji Hyo, I am a fan!
(A younger male fan appears.)
Thank you.
(She shows her popularity at Gongdeok Station.)
(Meanwhile, So Min)
(She is looking for her mission in an orange top.)
It doesn't work. It doesn't work.
(She moves through the crowd to complete her mission.)
I can't believe this. How is it that no one...
I'm taking off my cap. No one is calling my name.
(It's about time someone calls my name.)
No one called my name on my way here.
I keeping my cap off.
Hold on. You need to carry out two penalties.
Do three cartwheels...
and laugh out loud for 10 seconds.
Please do them now.
I will laugh out loud first.
(Laughing)
(She keeps her movements big to catch people's attention.)
So Min wants people to recognize her.
That's why she took off her cap.
- They aren't sparing her a glance. - Did she take off her cap?
What is going on?
The passers-by must be scared.
Gosh, my stomach hurts. How funny!
Jeon So Min!
Jeon So Min! Jeon So Min!
How funny! Jeon So Min!
(How did that young woman go crazy?)
(Embarrassed)
(Is this a hidden camera prank?)
- I will do a cartwheel. - Do three cartwheels.
(Will people recognize So Min this time?)
(It's Jeon So Min.)
(There are a lot of strange people at the station today.)
(There is only silence.)
No one knows who I am.
- People don't recognize her. - How is this possible?
How is this possible?
Let her wear her name tag on her forehead.
People just think she is a lunatic.
She is invincible.
(She can protect her private life perfectly.)
I haven't...
I haven't heard my name once on my way here.
Can I take this off?
(Meanwhile, the daughter of Mapo-gu is loading up her machine gun.)
(Pretend to get shot with a machine gun.)
(Shooting)
(This man is startled.)
(Shouting)
(My goodness.)
I am so embarrassed.
(While they are wandering around the station)
This round should be...
- between Seok Jin and Se Chan. - Se Chan.
Go ahead, Se Chan.
Se Chan is really strong.
(I need to intimidate him.)
Se Chan and Seok Jin.
(Ouch.)
(This is how Seok Jin intimidates.)
Why did you hit me?
Why are they hitting each other?
- What is going on? - Hey.
- What is up with this atmosphere? - What is going on?
What is wrong with you?
That's not how you play this game.
Sit down.
- Seok Jin. - Sit down.
Do you have anger management issues?
- Seriously. - Why did you beat him up?
- Why did you do that? - What's wrong?
- Why did you do that? - I don't know.
All right.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan gets a chance to do cham, cham, cham.)
(Nervous)
Cham, cham, cham
(He gets caught.)
(Smacking)
(Even Se Chan becomes surprised.)
(Seok Jin manages to smile.)
(Seok Jin, are you okay?)
He put so much power into it!
I feel dizzy.
I got goosebumps.
Good job.
- Good job. Okay. - Yes.
Okay.
Yes!
(The atmosphere becomes heated up.)
That was a good blow.
All right.
Cham, cham, cham
(Seok Jin fails.)
I got chills.
Cham, cham, cham
(Seok Jin gets caught again.)
(Se Chan gets ready.)
(Smacking)
(Laughing)
(He is scary.)
- He is scary. - Don't cry.
(Will you introduce me as the Big Nosed Joker?)
(I thought my life was a comedy.)
My goodness.
- He isn't laughing. - I give up.
(You can't give up.)
Did you laugh?
I laughed at first, didn't I? I did it once. Sit down.
- Seok Jin. - Sit down.
- You didn't cry, did you? - No.
- My goodness. - It's okay.
Rock-paper-scissors
Cham, cham, cham
(Laughing)
Just end the game.
(We lost.)
No, no. You can't do that.
- You can't do that. - Come and sit down.
No, no.
No, Seok Jin.
- Sit down. - He will die.
Sit down!
Sit down.
Let me hit you just once.
- Se Chan, you went too far. - What?
- This is a game. - You jerk.
- Let me hit you just once. - Stop it.
Stop it.
- Stop it. - My goodness.
I am so good at this game.
You are so good at this game.
You don't need to spin the roulette since they completed the mission.
They will be here shortly.
(You don't need to spin the roulette since they completed the mission.)
- Why did we do this? - Why did we play this game?
(Flustered)
Why did we play this game? Why?
They just completed it.
My stomach hurts from laughing.
Kwang Soo, did you do the mission?
Yes, I did.
(Yes, I did.)
- What mission? - What?
- What are you talking about? - What did you say?
For goodness' sake.
(Did he confess that he did a mission as a thief?)
- Hold on. - It's not like that.
- They don't even hide it! - Hold on.
They don't even hide it!
I was talking about the mission at the station.
Kwang Soo is a thief!
The mission at the station.
- The mission at the station. - Forget it.
- It's game over. - You startled me.
It's a misunderstanding.
This is all because of you!
I am not a thief.
- The mission at the station. - Stop it.
That mission.
The two of you are suspicious as you are.
- I can't believe them. - The mission at the station.
- Ji Hyo. - She is back.
(The daughter of Mapo-gu comes back.)
You must have completed the mission first.
You became haggard.
- Ji Hyo. - I even received a flyer.
- Really? - Yes.
(She didn't suspect Ji Hyo's identity.)
(She must have really looked like a non-celebrity.)
The part-timer...
- You even received a flyer. - didn't recognize me.
- A practical nursing academy. - That's the flyer.
I even received a flyer.
She thought you should become a practical nurse.
- So Min. - Yes?
- Jeon So Min. - It's okay.
So Min.
- Jeon So Min! Jeon So Min! - It's okay.
- It's all right. - Jeon So Min!
- So Min. - Jeon So Min!
Work hard.
I worked hard. I had my name tag on, but no one called me.
Not even once.
I'll announce how many times your name was called in Round Two.
Are you going to tell us?
Ji Hyo.
Six times.
- Was I called 6 times? - You were called 6 times.
So Min was called twice.
Once she asked what her name was, so it won't be counted.
(Do you know my name?)
Jeon So Min.
I wanted someone to call me, so I asked.
So Min, you shouldn't be singing at festivals.
Members of Team Bo Ra were called a total of 21 times.
Members of Team Min Si were called 14 times.
- Who won? - Team Min Si is the winner.
(Team Min Si wins.)
- Okay. - Okay.
I didn't gain anything. I was barely called, and we lost.
- I know. - Starting from now,
thieves will stop temporarily their hidden mission.
It's a temporary stop.
I'll announce the thieves' current number of gold bars
What?
If the number is the same, the thieves are on the same team.
- Okay. - How many gold bars thieves have.
(After the first mission, the thieves had 4 gold bars.)
(How many gold bars do they have after the second mission?)
- They have four. - The number is the same.
(They still have 4 gold bars.)
(The number didn't change which means...)
- They're on the same team. - They are.
I told you. All of them are on this team.
They're on the same team.
- Seok Jin... - Are these the two?
- and Jae Seok. - They aren't on this team.
It's these two.
When I was tearing it off, he denied it.
Captain Hwang.
Why are you approaching me?
- Come on. - He said, "It's not me."
- Captain Hwang, it's not me. - Calm down.
- Calm down. - Did I get excited again?
- Wait. - They aren't on our team.
- Wait a minute. - They could be on that team.
When Se Chan and I were playing a moment ago,
Se Chan picked this team.
However, he joined our team despite his choice.
I don't think that's it.
What do you mean? He joined our team.
(Stop, Kwang Soo. That's not it.)
(He gets furious.)
What do you mean?
I'm making a good inference. What do you mean that's not it?
(Jae Seok gives Kwang Soo a hard time.)
He's like a poisonous snake.
He waits until Kwang Soo talks and attacks him...
right away.
It's possible that the thieves intended not to clear the mission.
- It's possible. - Right.
- I agree with that. They didn't. - That's amazing.
- I also thought so. - Were they pretending?
Yes, I also thought so.
The situation wasn't apt for the mission.
- They meant to skip it. - Round Two is over.
I'll announce the number of individuals' gold bars.
- Individual? - How many we have?
I'm really curious about this.
- Did we start with 10? - Yes.
Kwang Soo.
(Members find out how many gold bars that they have.)
(It's announced to 9 members.)
(Last is Jae Seok's turn.)
(Jae Seok listens to the director.)
Who stole...
(He raises his voice suddenly.)
- What? - Jae Seok.
- What is it? - Stop acting.
- Stop it. - Don't act.
You're acting very strange.
Who stole mine?
- Yours? - He's acting strange.
- He's acting. - I'm serious.
- He's definitely acting... - Think about it.
- based on the tone of his voice. - Only four got taken.
Many people must be protecting their gold bars.
Mine got stolen.
I was a target for someone's mission.
- What? - Someone stole from me.
Did yours get stolen?
Yes.
I was also a target. Mine got stolen too.
I'm thinking carefully.
- How many do you have? - I have nine.
- I have nine. - I got one stolen.
- I have 9. - I have 9.
Who's the last person?
That's nonsense.
I have eight.
(Two of his gold bars were stolen.)
- What? - That's nonsense.
- Wait. - Seriously.
- All of you are liars. - Wait a minute.
- One of you is a thief. - It's one of us.
- There's definitely one among them. - Please.
- I swear to you. - How can it be five?
- Listen. - I swore.
Stay out of it, Se Chan.
- Wait a minute. - I'm being honest.
One of them is definitely a thief.
- Jae Seok, I swear to you. - It's one of them.
- I'm being honest. - I swear.
Listen, there should be four.
Someone who said that they're missing one is...
pretending.
- He's a culprit. - What about you?
- Why did you exclude yourself? - Why aren't you a thief?
No, Seok Jin.
Don't you trust me?
What's with the tone?
(Gosh, don't you trust me?)
(What's with his tone?)
Seok Jin.
- What was that? - "Don't you trust me?"
Why are you talking like that?
Do you trust him?
- I have eight. - He sounded like a woman.
- Are you a woman? - I have eight.
The winning team can swap one member.
- It's one of them. - This is driving me crazy.
- Goodness. - I have a feeling that...
- it's him. - Who?
- Se Chan. - I agree.
We'll swap Se Chan with Seok Jin.
Okay, we can swap these two.
- Let's see who aren't thieves. - Like this?
- Then we can decide. - All right.
- Let's put them on one team. - Right.
- Will you swap him with So Min? - With So Min.
- Go over there. - All of us are thieves.
- Why are we all thieves? - I'm not it.
- No way. - Isn't that too harsh?
- We're ready. - All right.
Se Chan and So Min will change their outfit.
We'll get in the car and move to the restaurant.
(Next, they go to eat.)
Team Min Si gets to eat and switch team members.
Yes.
- Let's go. - It's a grilled eel restaurant.
Will they be eating next to us?
Yes, they will be next to us.
That's pitiful.
This is so harsh.
They get that and we get this?
(Boiling spicy catfish stew)
It must be catfish stew.
Gosh, what is it? It's eel.
- It's eel. - Goodness.
Excuse me, could you add sesame oil in soy sauce?
Spicy chili in sesame oil is very delicious.
Will Min Si give some to us?
Min Si.
- Min Si, can you give me some? - Can you give me some?
Can you give me some?
That's for him.
Min Si.
(As she delivers the food, Seok Jin grabs her.)
(Seok Jin blocks her.)
How could you?
(How could you take it?)
How could you, Seok Jin?
What is this?
- What? - What is this?
- Viewers. - It's just ginger.
It only has ginger inside.
That's amazing.
Nice, Min Si. That was great.
- Good job. - It was ginger.
I never had a ginger wrap before.
Goodness.
- Seok Jin. - That was annoying.
That's amazing.
- That ginger is strong. - Gosh.
(She delivers eel.)
- Thank you, Min Si. - Min Si.
- Have some. - Min Si.
- Let's share it. - Yes, let's share it.
Min Si, thank you.
I got some.
(It looks delicious.)
(He blocks him completely.)
(It's so delicious.)
(Why can't he eat any?)
Goodness.
(You terrible boys)
(They don't know how to react to such a compliment.)
I wanted some because my tongue was burning after the ginger.
My goodness.
- Ask Min Si. - Make an acrostic poem with Min Si.
Okay.
Freshwater eel.
I hate it.
(Freshwater eel, I hate it.)
(Laughing)
Can you give me some?
- He's so arrogant. - Give me some.
- I'll do it. - Okay.
"Give me some"?
(Seok Jin gives it a try.)
- "Min". - Min Si's face.
- "Si". - Beautiful beyond time and space.
(Min Si's face, beautiful beyond time and space)
(She's satisfied with his acrostic poem.)
Isn't it too old-fashioned?
He sounded like an old fart.
Min Si gave a lot.
(Their fight for eel is beyond time and space.)
(He defends the eel with all his might.)
- I want some. - I want some.
Hey!
I want some.
(He couldn't eat any.)
(The bitter taste of ginger remains in his mouth.)
(That's hilarious.)
It was my acrostic poem.
(It's so delicious.)
How dare you?
(Life is more bitter than ginger.)
That's funny.
Wait, is the hidden mission still happening?
- What? - What are we doing?
Right? Wait, look carefully.
(Are the thieves on their hidden mission?)
I don't think there will be any change.
Everyone, you finished eating.
Thieves will temporarily stop their hidden mission now.
- Did they clear it? - Did they clear it again?
If they did, I'd be surprised.
I'll announce the thieves' current number of gold bars.
I bet it's still four.
The current number of gold bars that the thieves have...
(There won't be any change if all thieves are on one team.)
(The current number of gold bars that the thieves have)
- They have 10. - What?
(The current number is 10.)
(10 gold bars?)
When?
Did they finish all the missions?
Did they clear all six missions?
- When did they do it? - They're doing well.
What's the name of today's special?
Catch the Thieves Right Under Our Nose.
- "Thieves"? - What?
- The nose. - What?
Is it touching the nose?
Is it touching the eyes or the nose?
- Jong Kook. - What?
You kept touching your eyes.
(You kept touching your eyes.)
(Is Jong Kook the thief?)
What did he do, Ji Hyo?
Jong Kook kept touching his eyes.
- It's okay to touch your own eyes. - Right.
- You have to touch other people's. - Ji Hyo.
Who switched with Se Chan?
I got switched.
- So Min and Se Chan switched. - I got switched.
- Wait. - No.
It's either Se Chan or So Min.
Me?
- All right. - It's not me.
- I think it's So Min. - That's right.
- I think it's So Min. It's creepy. - Right.
I pretended to tear off her name tag like this...
a moment ago as if I was on a mission.
However, she didn't react at all.
She's a thief, so she knows who it is.
Is that why she isn't scared?
- She knows who the thief is. - I think it's Se Chan.
I think it's Se Chan.
- Is it Se Chan? - It's because in the beginning...
- No. - you chose a team.
So Min is suspicious.
Why do you keep saying that it's me, Kwang Soo?
- I'm not it. - If it's So Min...
I'm not it.
The thieves have completed their task...
and will win as long as they aren't arrested.
With the last round remaining, Team Min Si has the right...
to switch members with the other team.
The situation needs to change for the better, right?
What's the point of switching team members?
Only the arrested thief's gold bars...
- get taken away. - I see.
Even if one thief gets arrested,
- the other one can meet the number. - You are right.
(They can't let their guards down until the next game.)
- I want to switch So Min... - Why me?
Why me?
- with Jae Seok. - Me?
(She switches So Min with Jae Seok.)
Then this team will be too weak.
How are we supposed to compete?
Now,
Team Bo Ra will be the weakest.
If Jae Seok leaves and So Min comes...
(Mumbling)
(Se Chan becomes hasty when the members are switched.)
So Min...
(A few hours ago)
Do the calculations.
Today, you will divide into 2 teams of 5...
and participate in Catch the Thieves Right Under Our Nose.
The two of you are thieves who want to steal gold bars.
Se Chan, this is your hidden mission.
Say a member's name followed by a popular line of a movie.
Jae Seok, come here. This is incredible.
So you chose to be with your girlfriend.
Nice! Min Si, this is incredible. Good job. Good shot.
(He carried out the hidden mission without getting caught.)
- Let's change. - Once the two of them change,
- we will move to the last location. - I have no idea.
I know what this is.
Isn't that a trampoline? What is that?
- It's a volleyball. - Isn't that a trampoline?
It's not a trampoline.
This is quite popular these days.
- Really? - Yes, it's quite popular.
I will explain the rules.
The thieves can do their hidden missions from now on.
The final mission is Spike Man.
- What? - Spike Man.
We prepared this game thanks to Haha's tip-off.
It's spikeball. We will show you the video.
Can everyone see it?
Bounce the ball off the net and receive it like volleyball.
(Use the trampoline to toss the ball to the opposing team.)
(If they fail to receive the ball, you score a point.)
- You have to bounce it off the net. - I see.
- Can you use your head? - You can only use your hands.
- This man used his head. - Really?
You can use every part of your body.
It's like a combination of volleyball and table tennis.
It's like volleyball.
- That's right. Try it. - Try it.
- There you go. - Receive the ball.
(He needs to receive the ball.)
(The ball goes past him.)
Receive the ball.
- It flew towards my chest. - Go and get the ball.
Go and get the ball.
- Kwang Soo went. - Why won't you go and get it?
You never go.
- Seok Jin, come here. - You are an old fart.
(Stop getting scolded and come here.)
We are weak.
Since there are no boundaries, you need to receive the ball...
no matter what.
We should spread out. One person in the back.
I understood the rules now.
The winning team will receive a hint on the thieves.
We need to watch the ball.
- Go back. - Let's go.
We can't hit it right away, right?
- You need to hit it onto the net. - I see.
(With Jae Seok's serve, the game starts.)
There you go.
(Seok Jin receives the strong serve.)
- All right. - Get it.
(They need to bounce the ball back now.)
(He misses big time.)
What are you doing?
- We scored. - Okay.
- They are really bad at this. - The score is 1 to 0.
What was this?
(You're the one who introduced the game.)
Wasn't that a dance move?
Haha.
That startled me.
- Should I serve? - Yes.
He might hit it hard. No, he will hit it lightly.
(When Seok Jin moves back,)
(he gives the ball a gentle tap.)
- Okay! - Come on.
Seok Jin, I told you he will hit it lightly.
- Come on. - My goodness.
Don't use that kind of trick.
Why? It was really fun.
- Don't play dirty... - Everyone was impressed.
when you are a big guy.
Give it to me.
Everyone was impressed.
(Here you go.)
(He takes out his anger on Jae Seok.)
What are you doing?
Why are you taking out your anger on Jae Seok?
- It was a fake. - You are a bully!
It was a fake.
- Okay, okay. - He is a bully.
Okay.
Let's go.
(Team Min Si serves again!)
(Jong Kook serves fast towards Seok Jin.)
Why does it keep coming to me?
(He writhes to survive.)
You did it! You did it!
(However)
Why does it keep coming to me?
(It lands in the corner of the net.)
(Seok Jin's survival instinct gave the team the first point.)
He touched it twice.
It hit his head.
- We did it. - It hit his head.
- That was incredible. - This is hilarious.
Right?
- Let's go. - Okay.
Let's go.
I will serve.
(Seok Jin serves.)
- There you go. - I will serve.
(The 54-year-old serves.)
There you go.
(It hits Jong Kook's face.)
(This could be a meme.)
There you go.
They touched the ball twice.
(Overjoyed)
(Gosh, Min Si.)
(A herbivore suddenly runs around the field.)
It hit his face.
Because it hit Jong Kook's face,
- Kwang Soo is happy. - He is on the same team.
(He manages to stay calm.)
- Nice. - So Min.
Let's double it!
(Se Chan carries on with his hidden mission.)
Haha, let's double it.
- Haha, let's double it. - Okay.
My goodness.
(While everyone is absorbed in the game,)
(he says the famous line of a movie.)
Seok Jin, you should have doubled it.
Don't blame me.
- You should have doubled it. - Seok Jin.
I bet I am good at this.
- Go ahead. - The ball...
should be hit with your fist.
Come on out.
Okay. Kwang Soo, you are up.
(Will Se Chan do a good job?)
Serve.
(Team Bo Ra serves!)
Okay.
- There you go. - Nice.
- What? - Hold on.
(She grabs the ball...)
(and tosses it as if nothing happened.)
You touched the ball...
- Are you kidding me? - for too long.
- We didn't know. - We didn't know.
- Jong Kook, we are losing anyway. - They explained the rules.
- We didn't know. - We never played this game before.
Let's hear it from here. Are you sure you didn't know?
I didn't know.
(Cute)
Really? Are you sure you didn't know?
- All right. - It wasn't a mistake.
- We didn't know. - It won't happen again.
It won't happen again.
Don't do that from now on.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's go.
We are winning.
I will serve.
Let's have a rally.
- That's good. - Okay.
(Now that they have warmed up, the rally continues on.)
Okay.
- Check the camera. - Okay, okay.
(Jae Seok put the ball in the corner!)
(It was an incredible shot.)
Okay. Okay.
That was good.
- Okay. - It hit the camera.
It was cool.
It was impressive.
- All right. - It was a good save.
He is like Maria Sharapova.
(Why did he suddenly mention Maria Sharapova?)
- Maria Sharapova? - Maria Sharapova?
- Maria Sharapova! - What?
Maria Sharapova.
- This is good. - All right. Okay.
This won't do.
- Women should enter the game. - That's right.
(Why don't the women play as well?)
- We won't add women. - We will go with this combination.
- What? - We will go as we are.
(Flustered)
All right.
We will go as we are.
(A powerful serve)
- Okay. - Nice.
- Okay. - Send the ball towards Ji Hyo.
- Send the ball towards Ji Hyo. - That's right.
(They are so petty.)
- Change the members. - What?
- Change the members. - We are healthy players.
For goodness' sake.
I know they are on my team, but they are so shameless.
For a while, don't check out the website's massage board.
(Massage board?)
You mean the message board.
(Seok Jin should take a break.)
What's the massage board?
Don't appeal to our sympathy that way.
- Do you need a break? - No.
(He stutters because he is scared.)
That's hilarious.
- That's hilarious. - The message board.
- Let's switch the players. - Yes.
Let's go. Let's go.
(The original members enter!)
Okay.
Kwang Soo, it's yours.
- You got it. - There you go.
(Neck-and-neck)
(The rally continues on.)
(Their skills have been upgraded.)
(At that moment)
- Okay. - This is incredible.
(Jae Seok misses the net.)
- We are winning. - Are we winning?
We can do this.
- We need 1 more point. - We need 1 more point.
This is your chance to look cool.
He is tying his shoelaces. Let's serve now.
(The cheating trio serves right away.)
(The game starts before Jong Kook gets ready.)
(It's a fierce match.)
(The onlookers become excited.)
(The ball goes back and forth.)
(Se Chan's attack...)
(succeeds!)
(Team Bo Ra takes a win from behind!)
- Hold on. - He was tying his shoelaces.
- He was tying his shoelaces. - He was tying his shoelaces.
- We won! - I am happy, but you are shameless.
- You are shameless. - We beat you.
He was tying his shoelaces.
- Come on. - We won't count that point.
I am impressed that they still received it.
(Team Bo Ra has 20 points and Team Min Si has 19 points.)
- Let's go. - I am out of breath.
I will give it to you.
(The blocking is fierce since they have one point to go.)
- No. No. - No?
Kwang Soo, you need to do well.
(Seok Jin's sudden serve...)
(gets returned by Jong Kook.)
(Jae Seok smashes the ball when it's in the air.)
- No, no. You touched it twice. - It's perfectly acceptable.
- What? - It's perfectly acceptable.
- We did it right. - It's perfectly acceptable.
- You are right. - That's right.
(I can't believe him.)
- You can touch it multiple times. - That's right.
- I am sorry. - It was between them.
I got confused for a second.
- Should we cancel? - Should we do that?
What do we do?
(Maybe we should cancel and say that we won.)
Did you make a reservation at a restaurant or something?
If we do that now, people will criticize us twice.
- Seriously. - If people criticize us twice,
- we won't be able to get back up. - Really? Okay.
"We won't be able to get back up."
We won't be able to get back up.
Since we are tied now, one point remains.
It's time for a matchpoint. There won't be a deuce.
- This is our last chance. - A matchpoint.
This is our last chance.
We can't back off.
We can't lose.
A matchpoint.
- We can't lose. - We have to win.
(Which team will win and receive a hint on the thieves?)
(Kwang Soo's sudden serve)
Seok Jin.
- Please. - Come on.
(Team Bo Ra carried out an attack flawlessly.)
(Jong Kook passes the ball to Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo's smash)
(The ball heads towards the corner.)
(If they score, Team Min Si wins.)
(If not, Team Bo Ra wins.)
(Which team will win this competition?)
Kwang Soo.
- We got it. - Okay.
(The ball smashes into the camera in the corner.)
(Nice shot)
(It hits the camera.)
(Team Min Si scores.)
Did we win?
- We won. - We won!
Now...
(Team Min Si wins.)
Team Min Si wins.
(Did we lose?)
- That was good. - Goodness.
The thieves will temporarily stop their hidden mission.
I completely forgot about it.
- We were busy with the game. - All right.
I'll announce the number of thieves' gold bars.
- Was it 10 a moment ago? - Yes.
The number of gold bars stolen by the thieves is...
How many is it?
It's 19.
What happened?
- Did they do it during the game? - What did they do?
What did they do?
We have to arrest them.
The thieves have succeeded in stealing more than 10 gold bars.
You'll find out how many gold bars you each have and get a hint.
- Then vote for the thieves. - Okay.
- Check how many you have. - Look at this.
Se Chan, you have...
(Everyone finds out how many they have.)
Team Min Si.
Come here and take a look at the hint.
- Really? - This is important.
It's important.
A hint about the thieves?
Here you go.
Thieves are...
(Thieves are Running Man members.)
(Min Si and Bo Ra are exempted.)
- What's the hint? - What is it? Can you share it?
Let's share it.
- Bo Ra and... - The guests are exempted.
The guests are exempted.
- They're two of the members. - I predicted that.
I lost more.
I got 3 stolen, so I have 7 left.
- You got three stolen. - How about you?
- I got two stolen. - Then...
I got two stolen.
- No way. - Really?
I got five stolen. What's wrong with you?
Why do you keep lying, everyone?
I got five stolen.
- How many is it in total? - I got three stolen.
I got two stolen.
- What about you? - The total is already 11.
- I still have nine. - Still?
I got three stolen.
All right, the voting will start.
- I have no idea. - I don't know.
If you pick both thieves correctly,
the members will win.
The one with the most gold bars wins a prize.
The one with the least gold bars will be penalized with the thieves.
Even if the thieves win,
members who correctly picked both thieves won't be penalized.
They won't be penalized?
- I have no idea. - Who is it on our team?
I think it's Se Chan.
Why does he keep suspecting me?
- It's Se Chan. - I think it's you.
What did I do?
Se Chan is one.
(He keeps acting until the end.)
Wait.
Just know that it'll be over.
I don't know who it is on the other team.
(Who is the other thief?)
I think...
(His sixth sense starts to work.)
It's Jae Seok on this team.
- Right. - I think it's Jae Seok.
- I swear that it's not me. - Also...
(Is Jae Seok a thief as Haha thinks?)
I don't think it's Jae Seok.
- Is it not? - I don't think it's him.
It's not me.
I'm really not it.
Why would I make it so obvious when clearing a mission?
(If Jae Seok isn't a thief...)
Is it Jong Kook?
I didn't do anything.
Isn't it you?
Kwang Soo, isn't it you?
I don't know who it is on my team.
- I don't think it's Kwang Soo. - It's because...
I have no idea who it is on my team.
I have no idea at all.
Please hand in your vote.
(Everyone votes for the thieves.)
I changed my mind so many times.
We'll move to the final judgment stage.
It'll be easy to get penalized this time.
- I'll announce the result. - This is very difficult.
One of the thief candidates received seven votes.
The one with seven votes...
(The one with seven votes)
- It's Se Chan. - Gosh.
Is it not you?
Did he only get seven votes?
The candidate to get the second most votes received five votes.
(Which thief candidate received 5 votes?)
It's Jong Kook.
Is it me?
- Did he get five votes? - Me?
He got more votes than I thought.
(Is it Jong Kook?)
(I voted for Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook is one of the final candidates.)
- Jong Kook. - Did you pick me?
Give me your jacket.
I voted for you.
(Goodness)
My goodness.
- Let's start with Se Chan. - Why did you pick me?
1, 2.
(Se Chan is a thief.)
It's him, right?
It was me.
It was Se Chan.
Se Chan's mission was...
saying a member's name and a famous line from a movie.
He kept doing it.
Saying lines from movies was very hard for me.
The difference in score wasn't two,
but I kept saying, "Make it a double."
You said that a lot today.
The number of gold bars that Se Chan obtained was...
eight.
- What about 11? - What?
(He obtained 8 gold bars.)
What about 11?
If it isn't Jong Kook...
If Jong Kook isn't a thief, thieves win.
Did I do anything?
- Was I suspicious? What did I do? - I don't know.
- What did I do? - I don't know.
Why did you vote me?
Among members on our team, it isn't me.
What did I do? Was yours stolen?
I got seven stolen.
- Seven? - Yes.
- Did I do something to you? - I don't think so.
- I don't think you did anything. - Did you vote for me?
- Yes. - Why did you?
It must be Kwang Soo.
It could be Kwang Soo.
- As you said... - It's not me.
Actually, I suspected that...
it was either Jong Kook or Kwang Soo.
I have no idea.
- Let's find out. - Okay.
- Let's reveal his identity. - This is amazing.
If Jong Kook is a thief, the members arrested the thieves.
If not, the thieves win.
Tear it off, Ji Hyo.
- 1, 2. - I didn't do anything.
(Is Jong Kook a thief or is it someone else?)
Three.
It must be Kwang Soo.
(Will the thieves who played to the end win?)
(Or will the members who arrested Jong Kook win?)
(Thief)
(Jong Kook is a thief.)
- What is it? We're right. - We're right.
We're right.
See? We're right.
You're right.
We're right. Kwang Soo.
I was acting.
Jong Kook, your hidden mission is...
patting the head of a member from whom you want to steal.
- Okay. - Thank goodness.
Thank goodness.
That's easy.
I'll pat Seok Jin's head.
(Jong Kook picked a target.)
(Smacking)
(He hits him.)
(Then he pats his head.)
(When the ball falls on Ji Hyo's head,)
(he acts sweet and pats her head.)
(Seok Jin's head)
(He pats his head quite aggressively.)
That's creepy.
- It's creepy. - Goodness.
- When did Jong Kook do that? - I didn't do anything.
- I did it inconspicuously. - He didn't do anything.
I thought that Jong Kook was heartwarming.
- Like a friend... - I thought...
he was fixing my hair because it was messy.
The members won.
The member with the most number of gold bars is...
Bo Ra with 20 gold bars. She gets a prize.
(She's so excited.)
- Bo Ra is so excited. - I love it.
She likes it.
The member with the least number.
Most people arrested Se Chan,
but there's one member didn't vote for any of the thieves.
- Who is it? - Min Si.
She's the worst.
She voted for Jae Seok and Seok Jin.
Min Si.
- Did you vote for me? - You're terrible.
Min Si will also be penalized today.
Poor Min Si.
Water will fall in the count of three.
1, 2, 3.
(The water bomb is launched.)
There it is.
(Splashing)
Oh, no.
- Gosh. - Thank you.
My goodness.
(Prepared to get back the members' appetite)
(Running Man's Michelin Guide restaurant)
(Park Ji Hyun and Hong Hyun Hee also join.)
(A special way to order at Running Man Michelin restaurant)
(An order of a stew course meal, please.)
(One order of Shindang tteokbokki)
(You serve your own water.)
(Members fill up their stomach with water.)
(However)
(Ruining a fancy meal)
(Big eaters infiltrated.)
Why are you sitting next to me?
(They lose their dignity.)
(They start to get suspicious.)
(Running Man gourmets become extremely sensitive.)
(Ruining fancy meals)
(Who is the big eater?)
(Running Man Michelin Gourmet Eaters)