(In April, spring is in the air.)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- We started. - You...
- My gosh, seriously. - I should talk about this today.
- This is... - Jae Seok, don't even bring it up.
- Jong Kook is the angriest one. - He won't do it today.
- He has to know his limit. - The thing is that...
he can't cross the line. Otherwise, we can't talk about this.
- Come on, know your limit. - But he has gone too far this time.
When I was wearing the leggings and the pants, I felt weird.
- Right. - I see.
Is it the pants?
What if your boyfriend wore that outfit?
Let's hang out at home today.
(Going out has been banned.)
(Don't get the wrong idea.)
You don't want others to admire it.
Ji Hyo, if your boyfriend wore that, what would you tell him?
Please be honest.
I can't put up with the other stuff, except for those long johns.
But that must be really warm.
If the long johns were black...
(Taking off)
What are you doing?
(The anger catalyst takes off his clothes on his own.)
What are you doing? What? What is it?
- What's wrong? - No, it looks better without them.
- I mean... - It looks better without them.
What was that?
- Yes, yes. It's much better. - That looks much better.
- That's much better. - The pants were the problem.
It was the pants. The pants were the problem.
- I mean... - It looks nice.
- Don't do it. - His outfit looks much better.
- Stop it. - Haha.
- You can't do that, Haha. - Don't do it.
- The pants are gone. - He just took them off.
Hey, they are taking videos now.
- This is a video. - Haha.
(If they tease him more, he might be completely naked.)
- Don't do it. - My goodness.
Today, on the day this episode airs,
from 5pm to midnight,
the most searched team online will be the winning team.
(The most searched team online wins the race.)
(Running Man)
- Us? - Us?
- What should we do to go viral? - Well,
- Usually, guests go viral online. - That's right.
- "King of Mask Singer" goes viral. - That's right.
- There are other shows too. - That's right.
If we try to go viral by ourselves,
- it would be hard. - Right, it won't be easy.
It's hard.
We have invited popular guests who will try to be the most...
searched team online with you.
Four teams are waiting for you.
- This will work. We'll form teams. - They have to join us.
- That's right. - It might be possible then.
2 members of Running Man and 1 guest member...
will form a team and proceed with matches.
The search word that each team must make to go viral is...
"Running Man and the name of the guest".
It has to be "Running Man" and the name of the guest must follow.
- It must be the name of the guest. - Running Man and so and so?
- We help the guest to go viral. - That's right.
Right.
- Our partner will matter a lot. - That won't be easy.
All right. We'll bring in the first guest. Come on out!
(Who is the first guest that's about to be revealed?)
- My gosh. - Hello.
(The icon of irreplaceable singers who climb up the charts)
- It's Hani and Solji. - It's been so long.
Hello.
(The legendary girl group with songs that climb up the charts)
(On stage, she's irresistible.)
(In real life, she's down-to-earth and approachable.)
(Yawning)
(Hani showed all sorts of her charms 4 years ago.)
(She's ready to show off her irresistible charms today.)
- They're finally here. - It's Solji.
My gosh.
- It's Solji's first time here. - Right.
- We've seen Hani a lot before. - You're all better now.
But isn't this your first time joining us, Solji?
Yes, this is my first time being on Running Man.
I can already feel their names trending up online.
- You can feel that, right? - Yes, I can feel it.
Solji is joining us today.
- This is good. Solji will go viral. - Listen.
- It's your first time here, Solji. - Yes.
After seeing your friends being on this show,
did you think that you should've been invited before?
And have you ever been upset that we didn't invite you before today?
Well, I do think that you guys invited me a bit too late.
When I thought that it was about time that you'd invite me,
- you still didn't invite me. - When was that?
When was the time that you thought you would be on our show?
- When I made my comeback. - I see.
- Right. - I went viral after my comeback.
- Right. - Yes.
Right. It was great. I really liked your comeback.
When Im Won Hee was doing well on "Mom's Diary"...
(All of a sudden, he talks about her lookalike, Im Won Hee.)
- I thought it would be then. - My gosh.
- She resembles Im Won Hee. - Im Won Hee.
- It was when he was doing well. - You look like him.
What just happened?
- Here we go again. - If it stays online for too long...
Everyone, please look up "Solji and Im Won Hee".
She can even impersonate Won Hee.
- Really? - Yes.
- I'd be worried if I do it. - Do it just this once.
(Will Solji do Won Hee's lines from "Dachimawa Lee"?)
A lot of people tell me that my jawline looks similar to his.
Yes, people say that a lot.
"I don't think we need to introduce ourselves."
- What was that? What? How? - This is it.
- My gosh. - No way!
(What was that? She sounds just like him!)
- That was amazing. - "I don't think so."
- Did I sound like him? - Yes, you did.
- You sounded just like him. - I see. Thank you.
I had no idea.
- She has a special talent. - By the way,
- she's great at harmonizing. - She's amazing at it.
She used to be a vocal coach too.
- That's right. Yes, that's true. - Really?
Actually, Solji used to be a vocal coach.
- My gosh. - What about Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo is good at harmonizing with other singers.
- But... - I'm good at it.
- He's not good. He likes it. - I like doing it.
- He likes doing that. - Kwang Soo can probably...
- harmonize with Solji for any song. - That's right.
- Do you want to give it a go? - That would be awesome.
- Which song will you sing? - He's going to...
- harmonize for me? - Yes.
- He can harmonize with any songs. - Seriously. I learned how to do it.
- Is that so? - Really?
- What about a sad ballad? - Really?
- He performs well with a ballad. - Yes.
- Like a painful love song. - How about "I Won't Love"?
- That's a great song. - That's great.
- "I Won't Love"? I'll start now. - I will never
(I will never)
(Fall in love again)
- No, no. - Someone like you
(Why is he putting his hand on his ear?)
(Kwang Soo, how low will you sink?)
(We'll disappear in embarrassment just by listening to you.)
- What are you doing? - No.
- You're ruining the song. - What are you doing?
What are you doing?
(Kwang Soo's deadly melody shakes Solji.)
- This is scary. - What are you doing?
- He sounds scary. - I can't listen to this anymore.
(I will never harmonize again.)
- It was his facial expression. - But...
Great. Can you harmonize with Hani?
Can Hani sing a song? And can you harmonize...
- with Hani? - Yes, harmonize with her.
Since both of you are singers.
How about "Baby Shark"?
- Can you sing that? - They can pull it off.
- Can you? Okay. Go ahead. - Start.
(Baby shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo)
(Cute shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo)
(Hey, this is working!)
(Perfect harmony)
- I knew it. It's the piano. - What was that?
(But...)
(It looks like they are harmonizing...)
(But is this it?)
(Did you hear our harmony?)
- I knew it. It's the piano. - What was that?
It wasn't worth making a fuss for.
- Listen. - Weren't we great?
- Yes, it was great. It's the piano. - Baby shark
I'm so proud of us.
- We could do this much too. - My gosh.
(If this is called harmony, we can do it too.)
(Baby shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo)
(The trio sings a melody that's unexpectedly pleasant to listen to.)
(Perfect harmony)
(What? They're actually surprised.)
That's not how you do it.
(Singing)
(This is an a cappella version of the song.)
(As long as you can beatbox,)
(harmonizing isn't hard.)
(He can't believe his ears. Why does it sound pleasing?)
(The Fool, Sly Snake, and Beanpole are a threat to Hani and Solji.)
This is it.
(This is the magic of beatboxing.)
(We'll approve your skills.)
- That was pretty good. - Stop it.
- My gosh. - That's enough.
- We can pull this off together. - Stop it.
- We're a trio. A cappella trio. - We're an a cappella group.
- This is nothing. - Right.
Actually, Hani is famous for her commercial.
- It's famous. - It goes like this.
- It was a very catchy song. - That's right.
- Everyone was singing the song. - It was a huge hit.
- The commercial was a hit. - And the dance too.
I guess singing the song from the commercial might be a bit iffy.
- Why not? - If you can, can you demonstrate?
- She's so down-to-earth. - All right.
- It goes like this. - How about "Awesome Running Man"?
You can sing, "Awesome Running Man".
- I'm a huge fan. - I'll watch this in person.
I'm a huge fan of this commercial.
- 1, 2, 3, 4. Awesome Running Man. - 3, 4.
(Awesome Running Man)
Here it is.
(Here are the dance and the song.)
Yes, this is it.
(She perfectly pulls it off.)
(She perfectly finishes the dance routine...)
(including the kicking dance.)
(How cute and exciting!)
- Yes, this was it. My goodness. - It looked exactly the same.
I knew it. She's the best as this is her commercial.
It looked exactly the same.
Ji Hyo, can you try to do the dance routine?
- Do you want to do it together? - Yes, do it with So Min.
- "Awesome Running Man". - Hey, Ms. Kyeon Mi Ri.
- "Ms. Kyeon Mi Ri"? - In the center...
Do it in the center.
- Her pants match with mine. - It's perfect.
(It's "Awesome Running Man" with Ms. Kyeon Mi Ri.)
It's perfect.
(How will their performance look?)
- "Awesome". - Yes.
All right. 5, 6. 5, 6...
(They dance in perfect sync.)
- This is cute. - Awesome Running Man
(Look cute and adorable.)
(Awesome Running Man)
(It's an awesome ensemble of Ms. Kyeon, Model, and Scary Lady.)
I can't believe I saw this in person.
- This was so fun. - My gosh.
- Up to two guests are allowed. - That was so fun.
- It was so fun. - This is nice.
In my opinion, they are promising front-runners today.
- That's right. - They might be able to win.
Hani and Solji are very strong front-runners of this race.
We'll bring in the next guest.
Come on out.
They're SEVENTEEN.
(Mingyu and Seungkwan of SEVENTEEN, a popular idol group)
Very nice!
(They earned the nickname Masters of Performance...)
(for their sharp dance moves and outstanding performances.)
(They are excellent show hosts and excel on variety shows.)
(They are the all-around idol group that's ready for anything.)
(SEVENTEEN has come to Running Man...)
(to take over the online world.)
- Hello. - Very nice!
- Nice! - This way.
- SEVENTEEN. - You guys are handsome.
- I really wanted to meet you guys. - First of all,
Mingyu and Seungkwan of SEVENTEEN are joining us today.
Let us say hello. Say the name.
- SEVENTEEN. Hello. - SEVENTEEN. Hello.
- I'm Seungkwan. - I'm Mingyu.
- You two have perfect teamwork. - SEVENTEEN.
As soon as they walked out,
- a waft of cologne came in too. - Right, right.
It smells like figs. It's the scent of the figs.
- Isn't it from me? - Figs...
Is your cologne fig-scented?
My gosh, the scent is very strong.
- Not that many singers wear that. - No, it's not yours.
- My gosh. - Yes, this is it.
(She finds the origin of the scent.)
So Min, you keep pushing your hair behind your ear.
- You keep doing that. - No, no.
- Unbelievable. - There you go again.
- She started. - It's the earring.
It's because I'm wearing earrings today.
All right. They will be joining us today.
I think the last time Seungkwan was on our show...
- It was for 100 versus 100. - That's right. He was on our show.
- He was the last one standing. - Yes, yes.
- And was that your last time here? - Was that the last time?
I was up against Lee Won Hee, the athlete.
(He competed against Lee Won Hee, the judo gold medalist,)
(as the last celebrity.)
(The 1-on-1 match to remove each other's name tag)
(When Won Hee spun him around hard,)
(he was frightened out of his senses.)
- That's right. - That's when I joined you guys.
My gosh.
How long has it been?
It was when we had just made our debut.
It's still great news to be here,
but back then, everything was so fascinating.
My agent told us that we'd be on Running Man at last.
We were too thankful, but there were 100 celebrities.
- We weren't the only guests there. - Right, right.
Back then,
when we had our interview,
you asked about our special talents. And I said that I was from Anyang.
- I shook hands with Jong Kook. - That's right. You shook hands.
- That was the end of it. - Are you from Anyang?
- I said this about three times. - Is that so?
(I'll say this for the fourth time. I'm from Anyang.)
Jong Kook usually remembers if you're from Anyang.
- This is understandable. - Are you from Anyang?
- You're starting to forget things. - Right now...
- There will be three clips of this. - Really?
- Hey, you. - Stop it.
- This happened before. - I'm sorry.
- Hold on. - I've never seen him get red.
- You don't care about Anyang now. - No, it's not that.
By any chance, did you mention this on "I Can See Your Voice"?
Yes, I mentioned this on that show.
- My gosh, I got goosebumps. - He doesn't usually get flustered.
- Has your love for Anyang weakened? - No.
- It's because he moved. - It's not that.
- I still love Anyang very much. - Besides...
All right. Do an acrostic poem with Anyang. It's been a while.
(If so, will Jong Kook try an acrostic poem with Anyang?)
- An acrostic poem with Anyang. - Anyang?
- Yes. Anyang. - Go ahead.
All right. "A".
- Anyang has... - "Y".
young thugs.
(Jong Kook's love for Anyang hasn't changed.)
- What was that? - What did you say?
- How... - How could you say that?
- What's wrong with that? - I mean...
- My goodness. - What is it?
How could you say that?
I'm sure that's not the case.
You must have fun when you're young.
All right.
His acrostic poem with Anyang was...
- neat which doesn't happen often. - That was nice.
- You finished it really nicely. - Great, great.
Everyone knows that Seungkwan has a lot of special talents.
- That's right. - Right.
- I'm from Jeju too. - Special talents...
I've never heard anyone agree with that.
"You have a lot of talents."
"That's right."
- That's right. - That's impressive.
- I can't play innocent. - Seriously.
- Show us a few special talents. - Sure, sure.
- Okay, okay. - Let's ask him to do a few.
- Do Lee So Ra's impersonation. - Right.
- She'd be sitting down... - He's really good at it.
with her legs crossed and touch her earphones.
(Getting ready)
He resembles her too.
(I write a letter to you)
(My gosh, he sounds just like her.)
- That sounded like her. - My gosh.
- Look at his facial expression. - Seriously.
(He can even copy the details of her singing.)
(Unclear pronunciation)
(He finishes off with a witty twist at the end.)
- He's a great singer too. - He's good.
When he first did this, he didn't exaggerate it.
- But after being on many shows, - Right.
- this has been tainted a little. - That's because...
- I repeated this so many times. - You...
- You exaggerated at the end. - Yes, I should continue...
- to improve on it. I'm sorry. - Right.
Is there a new special talent?
- He sings Jong Shin's song too. - That's right.
- It's Jong Shin's song. - Don't you do that too?
- It's "Wi-Fi" by Jong Shin. - "Wi-Fi".
He depicted the disconnection of the Wi-Fi by singing.
(The song used the Wi-Fi as a metaphor...)
(to portray a break-up with a loved one.)
(How will Seungkwan's version of "Wi-Fi" sound?)
I will disconnect you
I will disconnect
(He cuts off his singing to portray the disconnection.)
As if I'm quitting smoking
(But the more he sings, the more it sounds...)
(like a folk song.)
(Warning: The signal is very weak.)
(This time, he uses the Wi-Fi to be funny.)
- The song really sounds like this? - Yes.
Actually, you have to use the machine to make that effect.
- The song really goes like this? - Yes, it goes like this.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
- Zico wrote this. - The song goes like this.
He's the one who helped the song climb back the charts.
- Maybe, we shouldn't' have. - My gosh.
What if this song goes viral online?
The Wi-Fi disconnection inspired him.
My gosh, this is so intriguing.
I like this song.
I should listen to the song.
- We must be the most searched team. - Yes, we have to do that.
- We must go for it. - I already mentioned that.
SEVENTEEN.
Since you're here, sing us a snippet of "Home".
- Of course. - Please sing us the song.
- Shall we? - Yes.
- My gosh. - Shall we start?
- Which camera should I look at? - They're so talented.
- They're so talented. - Right.
Do you want to sing without the instrumental?
- Without the music? - Without the music?
(They have to sing without the music when they're already nervous?)
- That might be actually better. - You should sing without the music.
- You should sing without the music. - Yes, go ahead.
- That will grab more attention. - That will go viral.
- Okay. - You must sing it live.
- Sing from the top. - There's no point having music.
You have to sing this live without the music.
Some parts of the song are electronic dance music.
- 3, 4. - I see. This part is EDM.
(Actually, as for SEVENTEEN's song, "Home",)
(a trendy pop melody...)
(and sophisticated EDM accompaniment are the key points.)
- 3, 4. - I see. This part is EDM.
(Seungkwan's voice starts them off calmly.)
(Mimicking EDM)
(There's no problem in singing EDM songs.)
(They do their dance for "Home" as if nothing happened.)
- Great. - It went well with the song.
This will go viral.
(It's very addicting.)
Things like this will go viral.
(They continue to perform like Masters of Performance.)
- There you go. This will go viral. - A place
- This will go viral. - Where you can cry
(All of a sudden, he explodes with his coolness.)
(Mingyu and Seungkwan are well-prepared and talented.)
- That was cool. - The mimicking was great.
- That was so cool. - This will go viral.
Singing it without the song was much better.
This will go viral.
Aren't you curious? It'd be great if you can listen to it.
It's much better if you listen to the song.
That was so cool.
- They were so innocent. - Right.
- That was different. - Great.
- That was indeed different. - That was great.
All right. We have SEVENTEEN and EXID with us.
These two teams are very strong front-runners...
- that could go viral online. - It's a real-time online trend.
- As for the next guest, - Who is it?
I've met this guest before.
But I'm sure some of you haven't met this guest yet.
Please. Come on out.
- Come on out. - Who is it?
(How popular will this guest be?)
- Hello. - It's Hye Yoon.
(She was the leading actress of the Castle Syndrome.)
(She's the trending actress from the trendy drama.)
(Today she joins Running Man to introduce herself as an actress,)
(not as her role, Ye Suh.)
- I really enjoyed your drama. - I see. My gosh.
- Really? - Isn't she Ye Suh?
- Ye Suh. Ye Suh. - Ye Suh is here.
(I can't believe that "Ye Suh" is here.)
Nice to see you again.
- She's different from the drama. - Come this way.
- Listen. - Seriously.
- I didn't recognize her at first. - The name of the role...
- Hye Yoon played was Ye Suh. - Right.
But now that she's in this outfit,
- I bet you didn't recognize her. - She looks so different.
In the drama, she looked like a high school student.
But Hye Yoon isn't in high school.
- She's in college now. - She is?
- I graduated college. - She graduated.
- She graduated college? - That's right.
- Did you graduate this year? - Yes, yes.
- Really? - Congratulations.
(Congratulations on your graduation.)
But she looks younger than her age.
Hye Yoon, please introduce yourself...
- to the viewers. - Okay.
Okay.
Hello. I'm actress Kim Hye Yoon.
- She sounds just like Ye Suh. - Hold on. I...
(Ye Suh's version from "Sky Castle")
Hold on. I...
That was the only drama I watched as it aired.
After the drama, "Sky Castle" ended,
aren't you busy with work?
Now that I graduated college,
I'm unemployed.
- I haven't decided on a follow-up. - I see.
- She hasn't picked one. - Right, right.
- Don't you get many offers? - I bet you get many offers.
I think I should work harder.
She just answered my question.
"No."
(We know how she's doing after the drama through body language.)
- It's not as many as we thought. - It's lower than we expected.
- This happens. - Of course.
- I'll do my best. - It's because... Right.
The thing is that Hye Yoon...
- just started her career. - Right, right.
You must feel the popularity of the drama.
I felt how popular it was because I was invited to this show.
When you invited me here, that's when I felt it.
Everyone really liked it.
Everyone liked the drama,
but things move quickly in this industry.
- So the popularity disappears fast. - I see.
(Shooting out a harsh comment)
- Why did you say that? - Hold on.
- What do you mean by that? - How could you say that?
- What's wrong with you? - You're so cold-hearted.
- What's up with you? - Jae Seok.
Hye Yoon mentioned it first.
- Come on. - I was a huge fan of the drama.
- You know that, right? - Yes.
I even memorized the lines.
Popularity comes and goes for dramas and variety shows.
- Everything changes so quickly. - That's true.
- Aren't I right? - You have a point.
- There are many new dramas. - Your point is valid.
But no drama has been as popular as "Sky Castle".
- No, not yet. - No.
Wherever I went, everyone talked about the drama.
Great. Actually, Hye Yoon,
did you know what kind of special...
- this was before you came here? - Yes.
- You know what it's about today. - Yes.
- We must go viral online. - Yes.
Have you ever been the most searched name online?
It happened when I was on a radio show recently.
Which radio show were you on?
It was "Kim Young Chul's Power FM".
- It was a morning show? - Yes, yes.
It's hard to go viral in the morning.
Actually, it is the easiest to go viral...
- during the morning shows. - Is that so?
(He shoots out his 2nd harsh comment)
(What's going on with him all of a sudden?)
- Can't you disagree just once? - What's wrong with you?
- Why can't you be nice for once? - What are you doing?
- You're being brutally honest. - Say that it's hard in the morning.
- Do it just this once. - Despite that...
(Feeling dizzy)
- By the way, he has his own style. - Come on.
- I like this new style of his. - Right.
- This is right up my alley. - Just this once! Come back!
- Wait. - Take care of your guest.
- Take care of her. - Please.
- Listen to me. - Okay.
Despite that,
becoming the most-searched person isn't easy.
- It's not. - No.
- Right. - Yes.
She played the role of Ye Suh.
- It was an antagonist. - Right.
It's amazing how much...
- people love her. - I know.
Even though she was an antagonist, I didn't hate her.
She was good at acting.
What do you think was the reason?
The reason?
Was that a difficult question?
Stop hurting her feelings!
(What's wrong with you today?)
- What? - Why are you so fast?
- You've become wicked. - Why are you so fast today?
- You're so evil. - Come back!
Come back!
- My goodness. - Was I mean?
Don't stand next to each other!
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook, move away.)
You two shouldn't get along with each other.
I like you today.
Was it all right?
- This is right up my alley. - Do you like it?
- He's so mean. - You should turn it down a notch.
- Should I? - Yes, you were being too mean.
- You shouldn't change so abruptly. - Okay.
This is a mess.
- Fine. - Gosh.
- That was hilarious. - Goodness.
All right. Hye Yoon will also attempt...
to come first place for the real-time trending keywords.
- Goodness. - She's a strong candidate.
- It's possible. - Yes.
- She's a strong candidate. - You're right.
All right. This is our last guest.
Let's bring her in.
Come in.
Han Bo Reum.
(She's full of charms.)
(With her charms, she has conquered the media.)
I really enjoy challenging myself in new areas.
The jungle was a place...
that suited me.
I ride longboards, go bowling, and ride bicycles.
I have various hobbies.
I like to be active.
(Her charms are never-ending.)
Welcome.
Welcome, Bo Reum.
Bo Reum has appeared...
on several variety shows.
And she's close...
- with many of our members. - Right.
She's close with Jong Kook too.
She was on "The Law of Jungle".
Bo Reum has many talents.
I'm close with Eom Hyun Kyung,
and them two are good friends.
She's practically Hyun Kyung's dance teacher.
- Really? - She's very talented.
She's very good at dancing.
- She's good at rapping too. - Right.
She has licenses for skydiving,
- jazz dancing, - Really?
- grooming dogs, - Grooming dogs? What for?
- and making coffee. - Seriously?
She bowls, plays basketball, yoga, and lifts weights.
(She's multi-talented.)
Show us.
Please rap and show us your jazz dance moves.
- Rap for us first. - Rap?
- Rap? - Yes.
We're curious.
Rap four lines for us.
I learned it a long time ago,
- so I don't remember much. - It can be an old one.
It's all right.
(She's shy.)
(Then suddenly, she transforms.)
(Don't care about the others)
(You have only one life to live)
(I can't bear to watch.)
(I can't watch her.)
(This old rap...)
(is too cringy for everyone.)
(They cheer for her.)
- That was good! - Go, Han Bo Reum!
(You did well.)
(I'm so embarrassed.)
- Bo Reum. - I can't stand it.
- Bo Reum. - My goodness.
Look at her.
Bo Reum, I guess you learned that a long time ago.
- You're right. - Did you see her face?
It completely changed when she rapped.
(Her performance was cringe-worthy.)
- Bo Reum. - She was like Yoon Mi Rae.
Now, please show us your jazz dance moves.
- Jazz dance? - Let's clap for her.
(Music starts playing.)
You're amazing.
What should I do?
(She starts dancing.)
- She's good. - She is.
Oh, no.
(Unlike her rapping skills, she looks very professional.)
She's good.
- She is. - Yes.
(She dances alluringly.)
This is jazz dance.
(She makes an elegant turn.)
I'm wearing a skirt.
Her dance moves look professional.
- She's good. - She is.
(However, she fails to do much and finishes.)
Wait.
Bo Reum.
Why couldn't you show us much?
Why are you embarrassed?
- As I have mentioned, - It's disappointing.
Bo Reum is nervous right now.
- I know. - They're all so talented.
I think that's why, right?
Yes.
Let's just say you have ruined your opening.
(He lashes out again.)
(He shoots out a harsh comment once again.)
- Hey! - What's wrong with you?
It was all right!
- I'm scared! - He's becoming weirder.
What's wrong with you today?
Jae Seok, what's wrong with you?
Why have you changed?
- I didn't change. - What's wrong with you?
- It's not like that. - The great Jae Seok has changed.
Why would you criticize her?
- This is right up my alley. - She didn't show us much...
of herself.
- Bo Reum. - I'm disappointed.
He's trying to act like me.
What's gotten into you?
All right. Our last guest was Han Bo Reum.
We have six guests in total.
Please give them a round of applause.
(How will the teams be decided?)
They're all strong candidates.
Everyone here is a strong candidate.
The Running Man members...
can choose the guests they want...
to team up with.
- That's so hard. - However,
the guests are only allowed to pick two of them.
(Only two members can be chosen.)
This is going to be really difficult.
Whom should I pick?
(What will the outcome look like?)
We'll start with SEVENTEEN.
Go.
(They have the chance to become a team with this famous group.)
(Which members will be on their team?)
Go.
(Nervous)
All right, you can look back now. 1, 2, 3.
(Who have come up?)
(Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, So Min)
Great. Very nice.
The moment I saw them,
I knew they were the ones I wanted to team up with.
- Why? - I knew it from the start.
- Good. - My goodness.
How do we do this?
What he just said touched our hearts.
Look the other way, please.
So Min, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo.
(They have a hard time deciding.)
- Kwang Soo, you can be nervous. - Look at Kwang Soo.
- What? - Kwang Soo.
Really?
(Did SEVENTEEN make a surprising decision?)
(What is their choice?)
1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
You're out.
(I'm sorry.)
(So Min and Ji Hyo are chosen.)
(This is what he gets for hoping to win their favor.)
- Nice. - Nice.
- I'm so sorry. - Kwang Soo.
I'm so sorry!
- I'm sorry. - Nice!
Nice!
- It's a nice team. - It is.
- Okay. - Next is Hye Yoon.
(It's Hye Yoon's turn now.)
Hye Yoon.
- They'll come, right? - Hye Yoon.
We're running out of guests.
- You're right. - Yes.
- We're running out of guests. - 1, 2, 3.
2, 3.
(There seems to be a crowd approaching.)
Really?
(Many of them have come.)
There are three duds.
(Hello, little girl.)
Imagine if this was an actual blind date.
It's the worst.
Please turn around in 1, 2, 3.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - It's nice to meet you.
(They're happy to see her.)
Hello.
I'm crying.
All right.
- This is hilarious. - Okay.
- Please come over here. - This is funny.
- Please eliminate one of us. - Okay.
- It could even be 2 or 3. - Okay.
Seok Jin, do pushups in front of her.
- Yes. - Do it.
(You want me to show her my charms?)
Do sit-ups or pushups.
(He gets down.)
(He shows off his strength.)
(He even jumps in the middle.)
(Was this necessary?)
Can you clap midair?
Clap.
(Slamming)
- I heard that! - My gosh.
Clap.
(He slams his chest on the floor.)
- I heard that! - My gosh.
Something broke!
- It hurts. - I heard that.
Something broke in him.
(That's enough.)
This time, I'll do sit-ups.
(I'll show you my sit-ups.)
(Jae Seok follows Seok Jin and shows off his charms.)
All right.
- How is this showing your charms? - What is this?
What are they doing?
I'll join!
(Kwang Soo performs squats.)
(The studio turns into a gym.)
It's working!
My gosh.
(Being healthy is the best for men like them.)
They do look attractive.
(I'll do anything to team up with Hye Yoon.)
- All right. - You're good.
- I've made a decision. - Good.
You can eliminate just one of us.
(After watching them perform, she has made a decision.)
Go.
(She stands behind one of them.)
Are you sure?
(Ji Hyo is surprised by Hye Yoon's pick.)
(She hesitates behind Jae Seok.)
- Really? - I'm sorry.
(Seok Jin is eliminated.)
(He's eliminated even before he can dry his sweat.)
(You've made a wise decision.)
- I feel so bad. - Seok Jin, you did well.
The entire country now knows that you're healthy.
You showed them your strength.
Next is Bo Reum.
(He does pushups once again.)
That's good!
Good!
(He puts down his knees and finally manages to clap.)
(But he is eliminated once again.)
Okay!
- Welcome! - Okay!
- You're my role model! - Welcome!
Come here.
(Team SEVENTEEN, Team EXID,)
- Okay! - Yes!
(Team Hye Yoon, Team Bo Reum)
What is this?
I'm worried.
- There's water. - I know.
(There are 4 water bombs.)
For this round, we have water bombs.
This mission is called a Pyramid Quiz.
(Pyramid Quiz)
- Pyramid Quiz? - Pyramid Quiz?
Pyramid Quiz.
- There are many levels. - It'll get harder and harder.
You need to guess the top songs for each generation.
I'm good at this.
- Oh, are you? - Yes.
- Gosh. - We can do this.
- Yes. - You can do well, right?
- You can do well, right? - We have three generations.
- It's true. - You're right.
If you know the answer, press the buzzer.
Then, we'll show you a scene from a drama.
Whoever can reenact that scene well...
will have the opportunity to answer.
I'll do it.
This is...
Do we have to reenact it well?
- We do? - Okay.
Except for the team that gets it right,
all the others' water bombs will rise a notch.
(The water bombs will go up one notch.)
- My goodness. - Five notches, and it'll pour out.
That's scary.
- This is nerve-racking. - Once it reaches five notches,
it'll pour out.
I'll tell you what the first place winner gets.
From the moment you win...
until the start of the next mission,
your team's name will be shown on the center top of the monitor.
- Goodness. - That'll really help us go viral.
Okay, okay!
- This is good. - This will help a lot.
We'll hear your chants before starting.
- We'll start first. - All right.
- Ready, set, go. - Ready, set, go.
- Han Bo Reum is on Running Man - Han Bo Reum is on Running Man
- She's on Running Man - She's on Running Man
Okay!
- That's so long. - What was that?
- This is our chant. - What's important is that...
- her name should be searched. - Okay, okay.
- Start. So Min. - Ji Hyo.
- SEVENTEEN, very nice! - SEVENTEEN, very nice!
We will come first place
(He ends it with the wi-fi technique.)
(I like their chant.)
All right.
Ready, set, go!
Our age groups are
- Up, down, up, up, down - Up, down, up, up, down
(He's very old, and they're very young.)
That's why we have an advantage!
(Their team is full of various age groups.)
EXID!
- Hye Yoon is the best - Hye Yoon is the best
That's mine!
(They steal her song.)
(Hye Yoon is the best)
- Hye Yoon is the best - Hye Yoon is the best
They're stealing everything!
- That wasn't bad. - You're too harsh!
- No, I'm not. - It's our chant.
Here comes the first question.
I'll show you a scene from a drama,
and if you think you can do it,
- press the buzzer. - Okay.
In 1993...
I was in 11th grade.
I wasn't even born.
On June 27th,
which song came first place on "Inkigayo"?
One. "Anyhow" by Seo Taiji and Boys.
Two. "What I Want From You" by Noise.
(Is this one right?)
Three. "Never Stop" by ZAM.
(This one's not it.)
Four. "What Is Life" by Lee Mu Song.
- The scene for... - The scene isn't out yet.
The scene for this question...
is this.
("Lovers in Paris")
- Let me answer! - What is it?
"Why can't..."
"Why can't you say it?"
- "Why can't you say it?" - "Why can't you say it?"
You need to do it right.
- He's not doing it well. - Do it right.
- There's more to it. - That wasn't right.
(They know the answer.)
(From "Lovers in Paris")
("Why can't you say that I'm yours?")
- "Why can't you say it?" - "Why can't you say it?"
You failed to pull it off. So Min?
"Let's go pig!" No, wait.
"Let's go, baby!"
- Wait. - Where did you get the pig?
- What the pig? - What was that?
(The overweight producer made her say that.)
- Hold on. - I know it!
- Go, Kwang Soo. - It's our turn.
"Why can't you say it?"
- "Why can't you say I'm yours?" - "Why can't you say I'm yours?"
- "Why can't you say it?" - "Why can't you say it?"
"Let's go, baby!"
- Correct. - Okay!
That's not right.
(Why couldn't we say anything?)
(Which choice will Team Hye Yoon pick?)
Hye Yoon, wait.
- It's "Anyhow". - Five,
- 4, 3. - It's number one.
- "Anyhow" by Seo Taiji and Boys. - "Anyhow" by Seo Taiji and Boys.
(They're wrong.)
- It's us. - It's us.
- Okay. - Say the lines.
"Why can't you say it?"
- "That I'm yours?" - "Why can't you say that..."
- "I'm yours?" - "I'm yours?"
"Let's go, baby!"
- "Let's go, baby!" - Hey.
He looks stupid.
- He looks like an idiot. - "Let's go, baby!"
- This doesn't count. - "Let's go, baby!"
Good. It's number two.
- Noise. - Noise.
- It's number 2. - It's "What I Want From You"...
by Noise.
No?
(They're wrong as well.)
- Darn it. - It's us!
- Go, Hani. - "Why can't you say it?"
"Why can't you say that I'm yours?"
- "Let's go, baby." - That's great.
- Okay! - It's number four.
- It's number 4. - It's number 4.
- "What Is Life" by Lee Mu Song. - "What Is Life" by Lee Mu Song.
("What Is Life" by Lee Mu Song)
(They get it right.)
No way.
(We know this song.)
(They have a victorious ceremony.)
(We're the best.)
(We want to be on the real-time trending chart!)
We did it!
- I think we'll win! - Good work.
(What will happen to our team?)
Look at that.
(Their water bombs go up a notch.)
This is great.
(Their water levels rise one notch.)
The water level is rising.
Let's go.
Here's the second question.
In 1992...
That was when I was born.
- I wasn't even born. - You can do it.
"I Know" was released then.
On November 3rd, which song came first place?
One. "You, Who Doesn't Answer" by Kim Jong Seo.
(We do recognize the song.)
Two. "Towards Tomorrow" by Shin Sung Woo.
Hold on.
Excuse me.
Hye Yoon doesn't know either of them.
- She's never heard of them. - Seriously.
Three. "You, in the Fantasy" by Seo Taiji and Boys.
Four. "You Are In My Dim Memory" by Hyun Jin Young.
This is the scene for this question.
("Rustic Period")
What?
(They know this scene.)
Go.
(What scene is this?)
(During a wage negotiation with the American army,)
(Kim Yeong Cheol wanted 4 dollars.)
(He was curt and demanded 4 dollars.)
- "4 dollars". - "4 dollars".
- "4 dollars". - Correct!
- Which one? - It's number one.
- It's number one. - So this is how you do it.
- It's number 1. - It's number 1.
"You, Who Doesn't Answer" by Kim Jong Seo.
("You, Who Doesn't Answer" by Kim Jong Seo)
- It's number 1. - It's number 1.
(Seok Jin's certain.)
(Will they get this one correct as well?)
Number one, "You, Who Doesn't Answer" by Kim Jong Seo.
(They're wrong.)
Let us answer!
- Us! - Us!
- All right. - "Four dollars".
- "Four dollars". - "Four dollars".
"Okay, thank you."
- "Four dollars". - "Okay, thank you."
- "Okay, thank you." - Number three.
"You, in the Fantasy" by Seo Taiji.
He said, "Seo Taiji".
- He said, "Seo Taiji". - Seo Taiji and Boys.
- Seo Taiji and Boys. - Be clear.
- "You, in the Fantasy"... - "You, in the Fantasy"...
- by Seo Taiji and Boys. - by Seo Taiji and Boys.
- Which number? - Number three.
(They articulate.)
(Team Hye Yoon gets it right.)
(I knew it.)
I mentioned that one.
I told you it was that one.
You are
(They have a victorious ceremony.)
(They know the lyrics.)
(Hye Yoon was born 4 years after this song was released.)
(She doesn't know the choreography.)
- Do you know this song? - No.
(She's happy.)
- They're rising. - We did it.
(The other teams' water bombs go up a notch.)
- Hye Yoon is the best - Hye Yoon is the best
- Look at them. They stole it. - Here we go.
- This is a recent one. - Okay.
- In 2018, - I can get this one.
July 8th, which song came first place...
- on "Inkigayo"? - It's definitely TWICE.
- One. - It has to be.
"IDOL" by BTS.
(No, that came out later.)
Two. "Ddudu Ddudu" by BLACKPINK.
Didn't that one come out earlier?
- Three. - I don't think it's that one.
Three. "Bboom Bboom" by MOMOLAND.
It could be that one.
Four. "Love Scenario" by iKON.
The scene for this question is this.
What is that?
- "Trap of Youth". - "I'll..."
(They know it.)
"I'll destroy you."
(Ji Hyo thinks it's right.)
("Trap of Youth")
(I'll destroy you.)
"I'll destroy you."
(She puts her heart into it.)
- You're... You're right. - We'll answer now.
- Which one? - Which one?
- It's 1 of those 2. - Gosh, let me think.
- It's either 4 or 5. - He was the emcee.
I was the emcee and gave the award myself.
(Mingyu was an emcee on "Inkigayo".)
(On that very day, he announced the winner.)
(What is his answer?)
Number three. "Bboom Bboom" by MOMOLAND.
Right, he was the emcee.
Then he'd know for sure.
(He should know.)
("Bboom Bboom" by MOMOLAND)
(He gets it wrong.)
(The emcee fails to remember.)
It's number two.
- It's not number 4. - It's number 2.
- Is it number four? - I'm so mad.
- I think it's number 2. - Number 2?
- Really? - I think that's right.
- Bo Reum. - Okay!
Okay.
"I will destroy you!"
Good job!
(She reenacts the scene perfectly.)
- Good. - Great.
- It's number two. - What do you mean?
- It's BLACKPINK. - Yes.
- It's number 2. - No, it's number 4.
(Which one will they pick?)
It's number two, BLACKPINK.
- "Ddudu Ddudu" by BLACKPINK. - "Ddudu Ddudu".
(She's not confident.)
("Ddudu Ddudu" by BLACKPINK)
We were right.
(They get it right.)
Do you remember the dance move?
(It's time to celebrate.)
(They fire their guns.)
(She mimics it perfectly.)
(He looks silly.)
(They're happy to have gotten it right.)
(I can dance well as well.)
- Okay. - My goodness.
We did it!
We got it right. What a relief.
(The other teams' water bombs go up another notch.)
- I knew the answer. - I know the dance moves.
Hye Yoon would like...
- to dance to it. - She knows the choreography.
- Yes, please allow her. - This is all you need to know.
- This is it. - Yes.
(Give it a try, Hye Yoon.)
(She loads her guns...)
What was it?
(and fires.)
(She did a good job firing guns.)
She's so cute.
(What is this?)
(She looks like she's washing her face with hands.)
(Her moves seem somewhat awkward despite her confidence.)
She's so cute!
She's so cute.
(Even she thinks it's funny.)
- Hold on a minute. - Excuse me, Jae Seok.
- I apologize. - Jae Seok.
- What is this supposed to be? - Sorry, but...
- what is she doing? - Are you introducing someone?
I thought she'd be really good. I'm sorry.
- What is this? - Hye Yoon!
- Why didn't you say you're bad? - Why did you do that?
I'll focus on my acting.
- Hye Yoon, this is... - I'll show you my acting.
Why did you even volunteer to do that?
It seemed like she'd be really good.
(By the looks of it, it seemed like she'd be really good.)
- She went like this. - No.
(While Team Bo Reum was going crazy with the guns,)
(she was acting like a pro. "Gosh! This is right up my alley.")
- She went like this. - Isn't it like this?
Goodness! She's so cute!
- Isn't it like this? - Gosh.
Isn't this the "Bebeto Celebration" from the World Cup?
(Is it the "Bebeto Celebration" from the 1994 World Cup?)
That's so old.
(They look exactly the same though.)
The "Bebeto Celebration"...
That's so old.
- I'll focus on my acting. - Isn't it the "Bebeto Celebration"?
I'll focus on my acting.
- It's been so long. - She's so cute.
It's great to see that again.
Next question.
In 2006...
- It's worth trying. - I'm sure it's Ivy.
- The Germany World Cup. - The number 1 song on August 13?
That was when I watched TV a lot in the army.
Me too. I was also in the army back then.
Number one, "I Won't Love" by Baek Ji Young.
Number two, "You Don't Know Men" by Buzz.
- That's not it. - It's later on.
Number three, "Celebrity" by PSY.
Number four, "On The Street" by Sung Si Kyung.
- It's number two. - The scene for this question...
is this.
- What's this? - I know this one.
(The scene that So Min is so confident about is...)
What is that?
Since when were you this pretty, Gil Ra Im?
Last year?
"Gil Ra Im, since when were you this pretty?"
- Correct. - Hurry up, say the answer.
"On The Street" by Sung Si Kyung.
- "On The Street"? - Is it?
- Number four! - No, wait.
- Number four! - No, wait just a minute.
Trust me on this one...
"Celebrity" by PSY.
- They're fighting. - That's not right.
He went for "Celebrity" by PSY.
Number three, "Celebrity" by PSY!
This is Seungkwan's personal...
- Nice! - We got it!
(See? Wasn't it a good thing that you trusted me?)
- He got it right! - Isn't it "On The Street"?
That's right. It's "Celebrity" by PSY.
That's the answer?
(Something up there doesn't feel right...)
- We need to jump! - I will be your celebrity
(He copies the dance moves.)
(I danced to this song in my earlier days.)
(Singing hard)
(Flip)
(I'll do all the tricks for you.)
(Good job, Seungkwan. Very nice.)
- All together! - It's a concert.
(The uncle fans come forward. I'll be your Bebeto.)
(Is everyone finished dancing? I'll finish it off.)
(What? She suddenly takes her jacket off.)
- Who is it? - Who is it?
- What's up with So Min? - Who is it?
- It's PSY's signature move. - Yes.
Celebrity!
- It's filling up. - We made it.
- Good job! - That's unbelievable.
We're almost there.
- We're doomed. - We each got one right.
- We're all tied. - It's 3 to 3 to 3 to 3.
We're all pretty much the same.
- We can do it. - We can do it.
Let's move on.
In 1996.
That's when you were popular as Turbo.
- It's the era of Jong Kook. - You should know.
It's during the second album of Turbo.
- On February 2, - That's during the winter time.
which song won first place?
Number one, "Sad Promise" by Kim Jung Min.
Now
Number two, "Black Cat Nero" by Turbo.
Is that right?
Number three, "Winter Story" by DJ DOC.
Number four, "Aspirin" by Girl.
- The scene for this question... - This is also an old song.
- is this. - What's this?
- It's "Descendants of The Sun". - It's "Descendants of The Sun".
Kwang Soo will get this right.
He should have it memorized.
(Lee Kwang Soo, an actor in "Descendants of The Sun".)
The lines for this one are hard.
Yes. I saw it, but I don't remember the lines.
Me! I remember a line.
Yes, a famous line.
- "A doctor is..." What? - I'm the soldier.
"If you're a doctor, you must not have a boyfriend."
("If you're a doctor, you must not have a boyfriend.")
"You must be busy, since you're a soldier."
What? Why?
- Your face is too different. - My face is different?
(Sorry, but your face is too different.)
(The staff cannot ignore their conscience.)
- Wait a minute! - Wait!
- Then what should I do? - You can't do this!
Your face is too different.
(Put side by side, it is too different.)
- You do it! - The famous line!
(Jong Kook, the least different, should do it!)
- "I'm able to manage it." - "I'm able to manage it."
"I'm able to manage the difficult."
Correct.
(Correct, since the staff feels less guilty about it.)
- Let's go. - It's number two.
Number two, "Black Cat Nero" by Turbo.
It can't be.
- What? - Press it.
(They are all tied and he picks his own song. Will it be correct?)
("Black Cat Nero" by Turbo is correct.)
- Was it February? - It was February.
- "Black Cat Nero" came out in 1996? - It was right.
(Now Team Bo Reum is in the lead.)
Let's go!
(Calling for Nero for the first time in a while.)
(The perfect coordination of the original singer.)
(Team Bo Reum is the best.)
(The winning cats dance in glee!)
(Let's not mind the water bomb and just dance for now.)
(The naughty cat is bringing up the keyword.)
Are you Turbo?
(Are you Turbo? I'm doing Kim Jung Nam's part!)
I'm Kim Jung Nam.
(Team Bo Reum stays put,)
(while the rest fills up another notch.)
If Team Bo Reum gets another one right,
they win right away.
Okay, let's finish it!
- We can do it. - Let's make them be quiet.
We have to get this one right.
- We should. - We won't come in first, right?
- We can do it. - Still...
Next,
- in 2009. - Oh, 2009.
- We can do it. - It's ten years ago.
- Right. - Yes. I was 14.
- In grade seven. - On May 3,
- which song won first place? - In 2009?
I'll give you the scene first.
For this question, it is...
"I thought I could have you if I acted this way."
What's the answer?
No, he was just testing.
(We didn't hear the choices.)
All right.
- I'll try it, then. - I'll give you the choices.
Number one,
"8282" by Davichi.
- I think this is it. - This is a good song.
Number two, "Sorry, Sorry" by Super Junior.
Number three, "Saturday Night" by Son Dam Bi.
Number four, "Again and Again" by 2PM.
- We're ready! Mingyu is ready! - Us!
- "I thought I could..." - "I thought I could..."
"I thought I could have you if I acted this way."
(From the drama, "Sandglass".)
(The line goes, "I thought I could have you if I acted this way.")
- Come on out. - What number is it?
"I thought I could get it right."
Number four, 2PM.
- "Again and Again" by 2PM. - "Again and Again".
It's correct, right?
(They will tie with Team Bo Reum if they get this right.)
(Will it be correct?)
(Team SEVENTEEN, incorrect.)
- Us! - We know it!
(It's not correct?)
- It's not correct? - It must be "Saturday Night".
"I thought I could have you if I acted this way."
"Because you're mine!"
(He's acting silly again.)
- We can do this. - It's number three.
- "Saturday Night" by Son Dam Bi. - Son Dam Bi.
Say it.
Number three, "Saturday Night" by Son Dam Bi.
If Jong Kook's team gets it right, they win right away.
(The others get the water bombs if they are correct.)
(Fate is within this question. Will Team Bo Reum get it right?)
"Because you're mine!"
(He's acting silly again.)
- We can do this. - It's number three.
- "Saturday Night" by Son Dam Bi. - Son Dam Bi.
Say it.
Number three, "Saturday Night" by Son Dam Bi.
If Jong Kook's team gets it right, they win right away.
(The others get the water bombs if they are correct.)
(Will Team Bo Reum get it right?)
Number three, "Saturday Night" by Son Dam Bi.
(Bo Reum Team gets it correct.)
(The number 1 song on May 13, 2009, "Saturday Night" by Son Dam Bi.)
(The dance move is poking the sky with the right hand.)
Let's go.
Poke it! Poke it!
How do I know this dance?
(A perfect copy.)
You can't do it, Hye Yoon?
- I can do it! - She can't.
I can!
(A total mess)
Saturday night
- Poke it! - Nice.
(The water is full now.)
- Yes! - We won!
We won!
Excuse me. Hye Yoon knows this dance.
(Excuse me. Hye Yoon can pull off this dance move.)
- She really wants to do this. - Yes.
- I'll do this. - She really wants to do this.
Hye Yoon, you have to make up for it this time.
Really?
(I will show you.)
- She knows it. - She's doing it.
- Is it not? - It's right!
Be confident.
[VIU Ver] SBS E448 Running Man
"Tail Catching Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(She was doing well.)
(What is this?)
(Creative dancing Round 2)
- What are you doing? - What was that?
- What is that? - Hye Yoon!
- What was that? - What's this?
- Hye Yoon, how could you... - What is this move?
I was dancing to the beat.
I think you like these kinds of moves.
We can do it!
- Seungkwan knows the dance. - He wants to do it too.
- Dam Bi was in the same agency. - Yes, Seungkwan.
Boo Seungkwan!
(The agency colleague will show how it's done!)
(Possessed by Son Dam Bi)
So sexy!
He's good. He's full of confidence.
He's full of confidence.
(Proving himself Dam Bi's junior, he has good feet movements...)
(and exact hand movements!)
(He plays with the beat like a pro.)
- This is how you do it. - So sexy!
It's perfect.
(A well put ending.)
- Nice. - How talented!
- He even knows the details. - No one got that right!
- That was flawless. - The winner of this mission is...
- Jong Kook, Bo Reum, - What a relief.
(The winner of this mission is Team Bo Reum.)
It will be, "Running Man Han Bo Reum".
Also, everyone,
- the three teams will get bombed. - We will.
- I will give you two questions... - Okay.
- We can get this right. - to single out the last team.
There are no scenes for this round.
- Let's go! - You can come out directly...
after pressing it and say the answer.
Number four, "Honey" by Park Jin Young.
(Thanks to Mingyu who was an emcee of Inkigayo,)
(Team SEVENTEEN wins 2nd place!)
- Good job! - Good job!
- We really have to get this. - Please.
- Let's get this one. - Please, please, please!
In 2008,
- March 16, which song was number 1? - March. That's spring.
It's spring.
During the last cold spell.
Number one, "One More Time" by Jewelry.
(Confused)
I went on a talent show with this song.
Number two,
"Kissing You" by Girls' Generation.
It's number one, "Baby one more time".
- Is it? - Number one.
They'll get a chance if we get this wrong.
- Okay. - This is crucial.
- We got this. - It's really important.
- I'm so nervous! - It's either one.
- Please! - 1, 2, 3!
- Number one, Jewelry's... - Number one, Jewelry's...
- "One More Time". - "Baby One More Time".
- "One More Time". - "One More Time"?
- Say it again? - "One More Time"?
- "Baby One More Time". - No, it's "One More Time".
- It's "Baby One More Time"! - Just stay quiet.
It's "One More Time"!
(Don't say anything and just stay quiet!)
"Baby" is just part of the lyrics!
It's "Baby One More Time". Is it "One More Time"?
- It's "Baby One More Time". - "Baby One More Time"?
- "Baby One More Time"? - Okay.
- Okay. - The answer is?
- "Baby One More Time" by Jewelry. - "Baby One More Time" by Jewelry.
(Team EXID chooses "Baby One More Time" by Jewelry.)
(If they get it right, Team Hye Yoon will get the water bomb.)
(Will Team EXID get it correct?)
(Incorrect)
Let me answer!
(Now Team Hye Yoon has the chance.)
(I'm not sure about the title though.)
"Baby one more time" is the lyrics.
It's just "One More Time".
- Is it? - Seok Jin was right.
- Let me answer. - Number one.
- "One More Time" by Jewelry. - "One More Time" by Jewelry.
(Team Hye Yoon goes with "One More Time" by Jewelry.)
(If they get it right, the water bomb goes to Team EXID!)
- Correct! - Okay!
(Team Hye Yoon gets it correct.)
Why didn't they believe Seok Jin?
- Why, you! - It's okay.
(I'm doomed.)
- No way. - I told you it was "One More Time"!
(I should have listened to him.)
It's this part, now.
- It's coming! - Should we join in?
Kim Hye Yoon!
(It's different this time!)
(She shows off her perfect dance.)
- Oh, no. - It's perfect!
She knows this one.
- You're right! - Am I?
- You're right! - She knows this one.
- You're right. - I danced to this at a talent show!
Okay!
Great job, Hye Yoon!
(Thank goodness, we're saved.)
Okay.
Why can't you be more assertive?
- I kept telling you! - You should have...
(Seok Jin's anger bursts out.)
- said it more definitely! - Hey!
- Baby one more time - One more time
- She's good at it. - You're good at this one.
No, it's all right.
You're good at everything except for "Ddudu Ddudu".
I learned this dance.
For your information, on the top of the monitor,
"Search Running Man, Han Bo Reum" will be displayed starting now.
- It's up now. - Where?
- Where will it say that? - It will be on the right.
- On the right? - Yes.
- Everyone, from now on... - Please.
- Search. - Running Man.
And EXID!
(Please search Running Man, EXID!)
(Splash)
(Please search Running Man, EXID.)
(That was close.)
(Awestruck)
- Now, - Wow.
- we will move on to the next round. - Wow.
(Let's move on to top the real-time trending topic chart!)
Everyone,
this is the final round.
- Really? - Yes.
Is it the final round already?
From now on, each team...
will be making a one-minute promotional video.
- A promotional video? - One minute?
And you will upload it on social media.
Whoever gets the most number of likes...
will be today's winner.
(The team who gets the most number of likes will win.)
That's...
This will be hard. It's hard to make it a minute long.
I never even thought about it.
Well, Hye Yoon...
- was on the dance team. - It's true.
- For real. - She's a dance machine.
Her lullaby dance.
It's 2 o'clock right now.
We will gather again after 30 minutes.
- All right. - But if Solji...
- hits the high notes... - Are we going now?
My goodness, this is hard.
What should we do?
Hye Yoon, which song can you dance to the best?
- The best? - Yes.
Something you learned or you're confident about.
(Any new choreography you learned on your dance team...)
"Tell Me"?
("Tell Me" by the Wonder Girls?)
(That was released 12 years ago.)
Didn't they disband a long time ago?
That's more than ten years old.
(If you want a recent song...)
"Bboom Bboom"?
("Bboom Bboom" by MOMOLAND?)
- You can do that? - Yes.
(Giddy-up, giddy-up)
Yes, I think I can.
That gesture now...
- Isn't it too... - Isn't that from "Gangnam Style"?
- Hye Yoon, if you don't know, - This is "Gangnam Style".
- please just say so! - Isn't that it?
Oh, this one.
Shall we see it, then?
It was...
(The maverick among dancers, what will her dance look like?)
(This is what it looks like.)
Since she was on the dance team.
- That's right. - Yes.
I was on the dance team.
(Fully concentrating)
Here I go.
See?
(Something doesn’t look right.)
Isn't this right?
I don't think your hands are supposed to be...
(What's wrong with your hands?)
Hye Yoon.
It's not this.
- What was it? - Isn't it this?
(You're supposed to put the fingers slightly apart.)
Is it this?
(Sigh)
It's okay.
- Hey. - Why are you sighing?
(Does she really not know why?)
We're supposed to make her an A-list celebrity today!
We're like her agents right now.
- We have to make her popular. - Now I know how agents would feel.
(Now they know what it's like to be celebrities' agents.)
- Listen to me. - How was my dance moves?
When she did this, my heart was broken.
I had no idea how I could make it right..
(After watching the wrong hand motions she learned...)
(from her dance team,)
(Manager Lee, "What am I supposed to do with her?")
It doesn't have to be the latest songs.
How about BTS?
- That would be... - BTS?
(A boy group's choreography would be hard for her.)
"Fire" is actually...
Kwang Soo can pull off "Fire".
- Really? - Yes, I like it.
Do you want to show us here?
Go, Kwang Soo.
(Manager Lee is the only hope to save them from the crisis.)
- Show us, Kwang Soo. - It's not difficult.
- Show us. - It's not hard.
He's really good at it.
(I'll watch carefully and learn.)
(Flap flap)
(Fans of BTS will be shocked...)
(if they watch Manager Lee's creative dance moves.)
(Culture shock)
(Hye Yoon...)
(This is how you should dance!)
He's still good at it.
(Running Man doesn't agree with his reinterpretation.)
- He's good... - Kwang Soo, you did well.
Kwang Soo, you did well.
What do you think, Hye Yoon?
- That was "Fire". - See?
Look how good he is.
He pulled it off.
Right?
You should do something...
that you can enjoy yourself with.
Like Jae Seok said, it should be short.
It doesn't have to be sophisticated.
How about "I'm a shining solo"?
"Solo"?
(She can dance "Solo" by Jennie?)
This is good.
- This is quite recent, isn't it? - Yes.
I'll try the chorus part.
- It's coming. - Get ready.
(What?)
(She's... She's good!)
Oh, great!
(Jae Seok is now satisfied.)
That's all I know.
(Just 2 seconds)
And this.
(That's all I know.)
Hey. Wait.
- This is all I know. - I'm sorry, Hye Yoon, but...
(How can we get likes with only this?)
How can we...
(Their future looks bleak.)
Why don't we go with "HeungBo" by Yukgaksu?
(I'd rather go with "HeungBo" by Yukgaksu.)
"HeungBo" by Yukgaksu?
(Jae Seok is tempted.)
HeungBo is unbelievable
Isn't that how it goes?
(Hye Yoon is unbelievable.)
(They are trying to cover Hye Yoon's lame dance skills...)
(by changing the song lyrics.)
And then, Hye Yoon goes...
Shall we add one line from "Sky Castle"?
- For the finale. How's that? - Yes, for the finale.
- Yes. - You can end it.
- I can do it. - Which line?
Is there a line you can still remember?
(Then is there a famous line you can still remember?)
"Do you want to die?"
(All of a sudden)
I'm offended.
- That's not important right now. - Okay.
- Okay, okay. - It's not for us to feel good.
What are you talking about?
I have a dancer's genes.
Bring Ms. Kim Joo Young.
Bring Ms. Kim Joo Young now!
Okay, good.
- That was short. - And that has an impact.
It's just right.
(Team EXID starts a meeting.)
- Haha makes really good videos. - No...
- It's nothing. - He's really good at it.
- Should we begin with singing? - Singing?
They both sing really well, you know.
They are such great singers.
Hani is the queen of fancam.
I think...
(Seeing Hani, Haha comes up with an idea.)
At first, people will think it's the same old thing.
"They're dancing and doing the same stuff".
- It's the same dances... - Just then!
It will turn out to be something totally unexpected.
- While they are dancing? - While they're dancing,
Solji will sing like this...
and Hani will dance.
I'll go around, shooting, and you keep dancing like crazy.
I'll shoot from your head to toe, like this.
- Up and down, everywhere. - All around.
You keep doing that, and then...
I'll go all the way, like this.
(But...)
Then, he'll start drooling.
Take a look.
(How will Director Ha's unpredictable creation turn out?)
(EXID's performance catches the eye...)
(But...)
(What?)
(Seok Jin's cameraman Yoo Seok is smiling.)
- If he drools... - This is funny.
- This is funny. - This is hilarious.
It was very natural.
(He gets caught while shooting someone else, instead of Seok Jin.)
This is really funny.
I have a suggestion, Yoo Seok.
- You don't need to act. - Can you spit out water?
Do this.
All suggestions are nice.
This is really funny.
- Let's go with this one. - Yes.
Let's go with this one.
I will teach you slowly.
With this foot, put your weight on the ball.
With this foot, put your weight on the heel.
- 1. - 1.
One. Do the same with the other foot.
Okay.
1, 2.
Ji Hyo can do it. So many people can't.
I can't do the steps as well as I would like.
You need to practice.
Rub your feet, So Min.
Keep your feet straight at first.
(Rub my feet? Like this?)
Keep your feet straight.
- Is this what you are doing? - That's right.
(The old steps jump out.)
Ji Hyo, techno was in vogue back in my days.
Do you know what techno is?
No.
It was in vogue back in my days.
This is my first time to feel such an apparent generation gap.
This is my first time to feel it on Running Man.
Seriously.
It won't be funny to see...
all four of us dance as soon as the video starts.
Shall we dance one by one?
Each of us should come from a different place.
- I could sit down. - That's right.
I could sit down.
Let's say I saw you dance while I was passing by.
- I will dance first. - Go ahead.
- Oh Nanana - What?
What is going on?
("Oh Nanana" party suddenly begins.)
We can do the Oh Nanana Dance together.
- It's a good idea. - After that...
I want to provoke you.
- What do you mean? - I want to pass by you...
- and hit you. - I see.
I want to pass by you.
For goodness' sake.
(Do you want to die?)
(Creaking)
(She attacks his eyes with her lousy dance.)
That came out of nowhere.
- That came out of nowhere. - It's like "Swallowtail Butterfly".
She moved like this.
We should have a video call with famous celebrities.
(Team Bo Reum's content is a video call with celebrities.)
(That sounds fun.)
What do you think?
It's a good idea.
- Right? - Yes, it's a good idea.
We can show the celebrities' names first.
- Let's pick a few celebrities. - That's right.
There is Song Joong Ki.
- That's good. - There is also Park Seo Jun.
Seo Jun is quite popular.
EXO members.
If they answer the call,
it will be quite now.
- I will call, so start filming. - We will start filming.
I will do the filming.
All right. Here I go.
I have high hopes for him this year.
(Who is Jong Kook calling first?)
All right. Who are you calling?
(Jackson of GOT7)
(Will Jackson answer when he is busy with schedules?)
Ayo, Jackson!
(Jackson answers the phone.)
(Jackson, hello.)
Jackson!
I can definitely call Ryu Hyun Jin.
(Is he calling Ryu Hyun Jin this time?)
Hyun Jin.
- Where are you? - I am at a shoot for Running Man.
- Hello. - I am at a shoot for Running Man.
Shall I try calling Son Heung Min?
- Jong Kook. - That's incredible.
(Jong Kook catches up with his close friends.)
Here we go. The studio is in a frenzy.
At 2:30pm, what is your star doing?
You are curious about what comes afterward, right?
If we place first in terms of the number of likes,
we will reveal the full video.
- Please press like. - Press it!
There is more!
(In 30 minutes, produce a video that gets likes from the netizens.)
- We should stop here. - That's right.
(Only the team with the most likes gets to reveal the full video.)
Let's go!
(Which team's video will get the most number of likes?)
(Time is up!)
Now, we will upload the four videos...
on Running Man's official social media at the same time.
(Running Man with EXID, SEVENTEEN, Kim Hye Yoon, and Han Bo Reum)
We will check the number of likes in real time.
Now, we will give you the rules for the final race.
Okay.
It's Tail Catching Race.
(Tail Catching Race)
- This is important. - The videos have been uploaded...
and people are pressing likes.
(However)
In the order the teams get eliminated,
the videos will be deleted.
(The teams that are out will get their videos deleted.)
What?
The video needs to remain uploaded to receive more likes.
That's right. That's right.
The team that has the most number of likes wins...
after the race.
That team will receive a big benefit.
What could it be?
Even if you survive until the end, you don't win...
if your team's number of likes is less than the other team.
Then the other team wins, right?
- That's right. - Really?
Each team needs to decide who will be the Tail.
Once the Tail's balloon pops, everyone on the team is out.
- My goodness. - Really?
This is the Tail Catching Race, so Team 1 will attack Team 2.
Team 2 will attack Team 3.
Team 3 will attack Team 4.
Team 4 will attack Team 1.
We can't pop all the balloons.
- You can go. - It will be fun.
(Which team will hold out and get the most number of likes?)
In my opinion,
this race is all about popping the target team's balloon.
Right? We need to figure out our target team...
and the team that targets us.
- That's right. - That's right.
(It's important to figure out the team that targets your team.)
Please reveal the team number.
Okay. We are number four.
(Team Hye Yoon's number is 4.)
Team Hye Yoon's target is the team whose number is one,
Team EXID.
(Seok Jin and Haha are easy targets.)
(Meanwhile, the easy Team EXID)
- Our number is 1. - Team EXID's number is 1.
Your target is...
the team whose number is two is Team SEVENTEEN.
It's doable.
- Our number is 2. - 2.
Your target is the team whose number is three...
is Team Bo Reum.
What should we do?
(Team Bo Reum Feat. Jong Kook)
(This is a disaster.)
How are we supposed to pop their balloon?
We should be thankful that we aren't Jong Kook's target.
- You are right. - This is better.
Your target is the team whose number is four...
is Team Hye Yoon.
- This is great. - Thank goodness.
- It'll be easy. - I'm glad to hear that.
(The target teams have been announced.)
Now, please choose a member...
who will be the Tail.
- You should be it. - You are the best choice, Haha.
- Haha. - I think...
it should be Hani or Solji.
Solji is strong.
How about Solji? It's your first time on Running Man,
- so you should try it. - Give it a try.
- That's right. - Give it a try.
This puts me under a lot of pressure.
No, no. Give it a try.
We just need to pop the balloon of Jong Kook's team.
(Team SEVENTEEN needs to get Team Bo Reum.)
- What should we do? - The Tail should be...
Seungkwan or you.
Then I will be the Tail.
- Okay. - If you can't defend me...
against the other team,
- I will run away. - Okay.
We should attack.
Hye Yoon, take this balloon and hide somewhere.
Okay.
- Okay? - Okay.
- You are fast, right? - Yes.
Jong Kook and I will protect you.
I don't know which team will come after us.
- The race will start in 10 seconds. - Okay.
Hye Yoon, hide well.
Okay.
- Make sure you come back. - We will search fast.
That's good. That's the attitude.
Look for places people can hide.
- Very nice! - Very nice! Let's go!
The race starts.
Don't be nervous.
What color of clothes was Jong Kook's team wearing?
Black.
It was black.
(They don't know which team is targeting them.)
- There they are. - Which team is it?
There.
(They spot Team SEVENTEEN.)
There they are.
- Team Bo Reum. - Where?
- There they are. - They are our target.
- My goodness. - Let's see...
how they react upon seeing us. They are talking among themselves.
Don't make it obvious.
Approach them naturally.
Then we can pop their balloon right away.
- They are coming this way. - Will they come to us?
What?
They saw us watching them.
Are you going to come after us?
I don't know. I will give it some thoughts.
Why don't we share information?
Why would you do that for Tail Catching Race?
Let's be allies.
What's your number?
Our target team...
isn't you.
Then why are you approaching us so confidently?
You could be our target.
(You could be our target.)
Let's say our number is 3. No, 4.
No, number one.
You could be our target. Why are you approaching us?
We have no reason to pop your balloon.
How would we pop your balloon?
- It's now pretty close. - They are coming.
- I think we are their target. - You are right.
I think it's them. I think we're their target.
- Go up. - I think it's them.
(Our plan has failed.)
If we hold out, the number of likes will go up.
- Firstly... - We need to eliminate them.
There is nowhere to hide!
(Hye Yoon is looking for a place to hide.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are looking for Team EXID.)
What's your number?
(What's your number?)
(They find their target, Team EXID.)
(Kwang Soo lies.)
- 1. - Is your number 1?
- He is lying through his teeth. - Seriously.
What's your number?
Give me your number first.
- We are 1. - We are 3.
(They throw out numbers.)
Where is Jae Seok going?
Hold on.
(While Kwang Soo buys time...)
What is he doing?
(Jae Seok approaches carefully.)
Which team is your target?
Why are you coming?
You...
You aren't our target.
Then why are you coming so close?
- Come here. - Something doesn't seem right.
I think it's them.
Don't be like that.
Run away. Run away!
- No, our target isn't Solji. - Don't be like that.
- Our target isn't Solji. - Don't be like that.
Solji, I will protect you.
I am scared.
- Come with us. - Okay.
Come with us.
Right now, go get them.
What?
(Jae Seok goes after Solji, but Haha stops Jae Seok.)
Solji.
(Haha stops Jae Seok.)
Hani.
(They could pop the balloon if they can't be blocked.)
- Run away! - Run away.
(Jae Seok thrusts Haha and chases after them.)
- No. - No.
(Let's run away.)
(Jae Seok chases right after them.)
Jae Seok.
Jae Seok!
(The video is deleted when the balloon pops.)
- No! - No.
(Hang in there, Solji.)
(Popping)
- It popped. - It popped.
(However, the balloon is safe.)
It popped.
Isn't it too early?
(If Solji's balloon didn't pop,)
(then whose balloon popped?)
Whose balloon was it?
(While Jae Seok chases after Solji,)
(Hye Yoon is being chased by someone.)
What is it?
- Are you still alive? - Wait, wait.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan are right after her.)
- Wait a minute. - Come on.
(Popping)
(Team Hye Yoon's balloon is eliminated.)
Where is everyone?
- I don't know. - Where are they?
Hye Yoon, your team is eliminated.
(Team Hye Yoon's video is deleted.)
(Running Man EXID, Running Man SEVENTEEN)
We could have gone together.
We made a mistake.
- I even got on my knees. - You're impressive.
No, I'm not.
(I'm so relieved.)
- That was amazing. - Who is left?
It must be them.
Jong Kook must be after us.
It's Jong Kook. We're in trouble.
We need Team EXID to eliminate Team SEVENTEEN.
(They recognize which team will attack them.)
- That's the best. - Right.
- We should go after Haha. - Yes.
They're here, Jong Kook.
- Are they here? - Ji Hyo is here.
(Team SEVENTEEN appears.)
Hurry up. Run.
Go downstairs. I'll block them.
- They're going downstairs. - They're going downstairs.
Let's go down this way.
- What do we do? - Wait.
Look that way. I'll look here.
(They block the top and the bottom.)
(Team SEVENTEEN carefully approaches the place where Se Chan is.)
(They spot Se Chan.)
Hello.
- Hello. - Let's go downstairs.
Hide. Go downstairs.
Hurry and run away.
Go downstairs.
Go, I'll block the way.
(Team SEVENTEEN chase after them.)
Run away.
Run farther away.
(Team Bo Reum runs away.)
(Seungkwan is chasing right after Team Bo Reum.)
Go, Bo Reum. That's right.
(First obstacle is Se Chan.)
(Seungkwan passes him easily with speed.)
What do I do with him?
(Second obstacle is Jong Kook.)
What do I do?
- I won't go. - Seungkwan.
I won't go.
This is what his strength feels like.
Seungkwan.
- I won't do it. - Wait.
I should keep you on hold.
- I'll keep you with me. - No.
(Se Chan and Bo Reum run away safely.)
(Ji Hyo was after them on a different route.)
Go upstairs.
(She spots Bo Reum.)
(This is her chance.)
Go upstairs.
(Mingyu and Ji Hyo versus Se Chan and Bo Reum.)
What's going on?
(Just then)
(She spots Seok Jin.)
Be careful.
Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo!
(They run after Ji Hyo.)
Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo.
(They're face to face.)
(Will she protect it, or will he pop it?)
(Mingyu lifts him up.)
(Is this his respect for an old man?)
- I was so surprised. - What's going on?
Seok Jin was moving unhurriedly.
(Ji Hyo is now safe thanks to polite Mingyu.)
(Seok Jin tries to chase after her.)
What do I do?
(He's exhausted.)
Close the door, Mingyu.
(Open the door.)
My goodness.
(Ji Hyo barely escaped.)
You startled me.
They're coming up.
- Let's move upwards. - Wait.
Let's move, Bo Reum.
(They're on a strong defense.)
Go upstairs first.
(Bo Reum flees to the top.)
There she is. It's Ji Hyo.
(Haha is chasing after Ji Hyo.)
(He finds Ji Hyo on the first floor.)
- I'm scared so I can't even flee... - Come here.
- I... - Come here.
- I should hide. - You should.
Let's hurry.
(Haha approaches them furtively.)
- Who is it? - It's Haha.
Hurry and run away.
Everyone is here.
(It's a head-to-head fight.)
(Seok Jin also joins.)
Be careful of Team EXID.
They split into two groups.
He's running.
Haha is running.
(He's been waiting for his chance, Haha starts to run.)
Should we go this way?
(They flee to the mountain to avoid Haha.)
Go.
Wait a minute.
Let's take a look first.
Stay still.
Ji Hyo, here.
(Haha and Seok Jin chase Team SEVENTEEN...)
(all the way to the mountain.)
Come on.
- Come on. Go easy on us. - Haha.
(Seungkwan and So Min join the defense.)
(Popping)
(Ji Hyo scratches her balloon against a tree, and it pops.)
Your balloon has just popped.
- It hit the tree. - Really?
Okay.
I'm sure that we have many views.
(Team SEVENTEEN's video is deleted.)
That's unfortunate.
(Order of the targets)
- Isn't it the two of us? - It's just the two of us.
Is it against each other?
They have been eliminated. Let's go and catch Hani.
- Hurry and run. - Hani.
Run.
Tell everyone to climb down. All we can do is fight.
Climb down.
It's only us and Team Bo Reum.
I don't know where Bo Reum is.
(Where is Bo Reum?)
Bo Reum.
We should put her in a room.
- That room? - For a little while.
Come here.
(As Bo Reum hides, Jong Kook and Se Chan search Team EXID.)
Stay seated.
Stay seated for now.
It's over if they come in.
(Will she remain hidden?)
- Jong Kook. - Shall I go upstairs?
- I'll go upstairs. - Go.
I'll go downstairs. Let's hurry. See you later.
(Where is Team EXID?)
Where are they?
Come here. Tell her to go there.
(Team EXID doesn't hide and moves together.)
She shouldn't go alone.
Be careful. There he is.
He saw us.
Bo Reum is missing.
(He spots Team EXID.)
Jong Kook!
They hid Bo Reum.
- Jong Kook. - Don't hide and let's fight.
Kim Jong Kook.
(The number of like keeps going up.)
Let's just fight right away.
- Jong Kook is going up. - Do you want a man-to-man fight?
Hani.
Why are you holding a tree branch?
(Behind them, Solji runs away.)
(Se Chan goes through 3 people and runs after Solji.)
No!
No, no!
(It's over once she's caught.)
(Se Chan successfully chases after Solji.)
Hold him.
(Haha blocks Se Chan.)
Jong Kook.
(She overcomes a crisis.)
Jong Kook, she went one floor down.
There she is.
(Jong Kook hears Se Chan's cry.)
(He runs as fast as he can after Solji.)
(Will she protect the balloon?)
(Or will he pop it?)
We're in trouble.
Where's Seok Jin?
He went to look for Bo Reum.
It's a matter of time.
(Seok Jin looks for Bo Reum.)
Gosh, we don't have time.
(He heads to the room where Bo Reum is hiding.)
(She hears Seok Jin's voice right in front of her.)
(Will Seok Jin be able to find Bo Reum?)
(He passes by.)
Where is she?
(Where is she?)
(I hope that he'll pass by.)
(Jong Kook chases after Solji.)
Who is it?
- What's going on? - Who is it?
- Isn't it Jong Kook? - It is.
(Let's go farther away.)
You go first.
(Whose balloon will pop first?)
Where is she?
What's this?
(He finds the camera light inside the room.)
(He opens the door where the light came from.)
You've been hiding here.
Hey!
Hani, you go first.
(Just then)
Girls.
- No. - Girls.
- No. - Let's end this.
- No. - Hani.
- No. - Solji.
(She tries to block him with all her might.)
Help me!
(She tries to block the door.)
Please help me.
(Both teams are at risk now.)
- Let's end this, Hani. - Go up more, Solji.
(Solji's balloon)
(Or Bo Reum's balloon)
No way.
Go farther, Solji.
(Popping)
(Solji's balloon pops.)
It popped.
(A tree branch pokes and pops her balloon.)
Did it pop?
(Yes, it did.)
It got stuck.
(It's unbelievable.)
(Dejected)
It's okay. You did well.
It got pocked by a tree branch.
(Tail Catching Race is over.)
Everyone.
The last team that has survived is...
- Team Bo Reum. - Okay.
(If only it didn't get poked by a branch)
Videos of other teams were deleted when they were eliminated.
However, Team Bo Reum's video is still online.
Really?
- Ours is still playing, right? - Really?
- When will it stop? - Seriously.
That was close.
I'll announce the result based on the order of being eliminated.
We're first.
- Team Hye Yoon. - Yes.
The number of likes is 23,061.
- If we lasted longer... - That's unfortunate.
If we lasted longer, we'd reach 100,000.
We were so close.
Next is Team SEVENTEEN.
- The number of likes is 18,784. - Yes.
(18,784 likes)
Yes.
(Our number of likes is higher when we were eliminated first.)
Wait a minute.
We don't know yet.
We don't know.
- Ours must be higher. - We'd win if we had a week.
We'd win if we had a week.
Ours would definitely win.
Team EXID.
(Team EXID's number of likes)
- The number of likes... - Please.
- comes at 20,000 and... - It's high.
(20,000...)
(The first digit is the same as Team Hye Yoon's.)
(Will their number go higher than Team Hye Yoon?)
21,284 likes.
(That was close.)
We don't know yet.
- We don't know. - We don't know yet.
- Oh, no. - We have a chance.
Zero?
- Seriously. - Maybe we could win first place.
We've stopped the countdown now.
Just now?
- We've just stopped. - Give us 10 more seconds.
The number of likes.
(Team Bo Reum's video was online for the longest time.)
(Did they record the highest number of likes?)
17,902 likes.
What?
(We have the highest number of likes.)
The winner is...
Team Hye Yoon.
They were eliminated first.
- Yes. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(All the honor goes to our netizens.)
No way.
Her "Solo"?
(The winner volunteers to perform again.)
(We show the full version of Team Hye Yoon's video.)
(Running Man Kim Hye Yoon)
Guys, what are you doing?
Move out of my way.
Move out of my way!
(Running Man Kim Hye Yoon)
How did I look?
You're not that good at dancing as you think.
I have a dancer's genes.
I don't think you're that good.
Then bring Ms. Kim Joo Young.
Bring Ms. Kim Joo Young now!
You're on Running Man.
Kim Joo Young isn't here.
Aren't you on Running Man today?
- Running Man, Kim Hye Yoon - Running Man, Kim Hye Yoon
Please like us.
- Please like us. - Click "Like".
I beg you. Please.
(It's the best race like a drama with a twist.)
This is great.
To Hye Yoon,
we give a golden ring as a prize.
(R-ring is given as a prize to Hye Yoon.)
- I feel great. - Thank you.
Gosh.
(He's proud as a member of his agency wins.)
I hope you didn't forget.
Who's the winner of today's race?
- Based on the real-time... - Most searched trending keyword.
- That's right. - That's the winner.
What's the prize for the final winner?
(A benefit for today's winner)
We'll give you an additional keyword...
of your choice.
That will be added to your time.
Ours is "Kim Hye Yoon".
"Kim Hye Yoon" would increase.
- That's usually what happens. - Right.
- Names are most searched. - We'll pick "Kim Hye Yoon".
- Names are most searched. - Okay.
2, 3.
- "Kim Hye Yoon". - "Kim Hye Yoon".
All right.
Starting today at 5pm...
to midnight, we'll sum the total.
The final result will be announced next week.
(The final winner is announced next week.)
- Okay. - It's up to midnight.
Let's hope for the result.
- Please participate. - "Running Man Kim Hye Yoon".
- It can also be "Kim Hye Yoon" . - "Kim Hye Yoon".
"Running Man EXID".
- "Running Man EXID". - "EXID".
- "SEVENTEEN"! - "SEVENTEEN".
- Please participate actively. - "Running Man SEVENTEEN".
I beg you.
See you next week.
"Running Man Kim Hye Yoon".
"SEVENTEEN".
(Who will be the winner?)
(You can find other team's videos on Running Man's social media.)
(He made his first appearance on Running Man.)
(He's a secret agent of many talents.)
(Yuims Bond)
(January 2015,)
(Yuims Bond failed to find his successor.)
(He left Running Man and disappeared.)
(4 years later)
(A mysterious place that awaits the members of Running Man)
(10 container boxes)
(A prize of 100,000 dollars)
(It's a money game of a huge scale.)
(Or so they thought)
(However)
(Did Yuims Bond return after 4 years of silence?)
(A secret mission that awaits him, and a mysterious client)
(Why did he return?)
I'm curious why you never gave me a second chance.
(Return of Yuims Bond, A Man of 100,000 Dollars)