Hello. Hello, there.
- Hi. - Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
Gosh, what's this?
What's that? That's LED.
It doesn't look like an electronic product, but a piece of furniture.
- Gosh, the TV looks nice. - It looks like furniture.
This will go great in any kinds of homes.
(This will go great in any kinds of homes.)
No, don't do that. You don't have to do that.
- You don't need to go that far. - Kwang Soo.
- I thought it was real. - Kwang Soo.
He said that whatever you say won't help the sales go up.
Why wouldn't that help?
- Look at that. - It doesn't help at all.
That's a painting. It's a frame for a painting.
- That looks nice. - Seok Jin. The condition is...
- How much is that? - that you mustn't talk.
- Hey, hey. - Seok Jin.
(There's no need for you to talk about the product.)
(My gosh. Is that so?)
- Show me the contract. - They don't want you to talk.
- Show me the contract. - No, no.
- The condition is... - Show me the document.
- You should come separately. - that you should be...
- It's too early for your joke. - separated from the product.
- You're asking for me to punch you. - But you're here for the opening.
That's right.
- Okay, I got it. - Right.
- From what I've heard, - Okay.
Ji Hyo sends a coffee truck...
- to her colleagues. - Really?
(Ji Hyo sends a coffee truck? Even Jun Ho of 2PM confirmed it.)
- Hey. - I've never seen that before.
- Coffee trucks? - Kwang Soo is...
in so many dramas and movies,
- but she's never sent one before. - Not even once.
To be honest, I knew about it, but I didn't mention it.
- Is that true? - Yes.
- Hong Jong Hyun. - From what I know,
she sent one for Hong Jong Hyun whom she's not close with.
- Jun Ho of 2PM. - Jun Ho.
- Really? - Yes.
- I have a story behind that. - What's the story behind it?
- Do you not have a story with me? - I...
We don't have a story when it's been a decade?
- Listen. - My gosh.
(We've made so many stories over the 10 years.)
- If that's her excuse... - No stories over the 10 years?
- My gosh, Ji Hyo. That was mean. - I wasn't going to bring this up.
I really didn't want to...
- bring this up. - I give you love instead.
When did you give him love?
- I give you a lot of love instead. - When?
- Kwang Soo, did you send her one? - My goodness.
(Kwang Soo, did you send her one?)
- After that... - Hey, did you send me one?
Did you send her one?
But to be fair, he didn't send it to other people.
- No, he sent one to So Min. - These days, she's really popular.
- No, he sent one to So Min. - There were so many articles.
(He sent one to So Min.)
- Hey, you. - He sent one with Se Chan.
- It was from both of them. - You sent one to So Min?
- It was from Se Chan too. - He and I sent one together.
- You got nothing to complain about. - Hey, you.
- Hey, go back to your spot. - Hey.
How could you? It's been nine years.
- This is understandable. - You guys are the same.
- Go back. - It's been a decade between us.
And you were mad at that?
Be quiet. You're at a disadvantage.
- Why are you mad if you're sorry? - What?
- Why did you do that? - You caused trouble.
We don't need to send each other coffee trucks.
- Right. - Everyone.
Today we're here to prepare...
for the fan-meet for the Ninth Anniversary of Running Man.
It's the 2nd episode of 9 Years of Running Man.
Today, we'll choose two members...
who will perform as a pair during the fan-meet.
- As a pair? - There are two people.
- I remember that it was 2 people. - 2 people?
My gosh, they'll perform as a pair.
As for their performance, the staff will not intervene.
The chosen two members for the performance...
will be responsible for everything regarding the performance.
My gosh, that's a lot of pressure.
- That's a lot of pressure. - It's a lot of pressure.
- Seriously. - That's a lot of pressure.
It's a penalty. It's sort of like a penalty.
It's a penalty. It totally is.
- It's better not to do this. - It's a penalty.
If I get to choose two members,
I'd choose Ji Hyo and So Min.
- Yes, that's a good idea. - Yes, that's good.
- This is a good pairing. - It's nice and fresh.
Besides, there might be good chemistry between them,
- but there's none. - Right.
- That's really strange too. - I'm serious.
- They have to forge chemistry. - It's been two years.
The chemistry between the two is non-existent.
- I've done it. - Hey, we should help them out.
No, you're pushing it onto us because you guys don't want it.
- No. - No, no.
- What are you talking about? - It's a misunderstanding.
- This is definitely a penalty. - It's for you girls.
Before we start today's race,
you'll watch a video that we've prepared.
- There's a video? - We have a video?
- Is that it? - Everyone, please look at the TV.
Where?
- That's the TV? - That's the TV?
- What's this? - I've given one to Se Chan.
- What's it? - What's that?
- Do you have to put it next to it? - Does that stick there?
- What are you doing? - I'm connecting it.
- Hey, something is on the screen. - It's on.
The video in his phone is transferred to the screen.
- I guess. - That actually works.
This is even more interesting. Look.
(The TV can rotate to the side?)
Isn't this amazing?
(They'll play the video on a cutting-edge device today.)
My gosh. Goodness.
- Hey, you must work here. - It's like that horizontal phone.
- It's the horizontal phone! - Right.
- It's so cutting-edge. - This is amazing.
- "To my grandchildren". - "To my grandchildren".
(When they're mesmerized by the device,)
(the video starts playing.)
I bet you guys are all grown up now.
(To my grandchildren)
- "To my grandchildren". - This really rotated.
(I bet you guys are all grown up now.)
(We're their grandchildren?)
Are we their grandchildren?
We haven't seen you puppies for a long time because we went...
on our trip all around the world to fulfill our dreams.
- On a trip around the world? - Someone else must be here.
We've missed you so much as our memories are fading away.
This voice sounds very familiar.
We've climbed the Great Wall.
They went to China.
- We've been to the pyramids too. - Egypt.
- Egypt. - That must've been hard.
And we've traveled through...
- the Almighty the Arctic Ocean too. - The Arctic Ocean?
- They went far. - My gosh.
Did they have to go that far?
We even fought against a group of crocodiles in the Amazon too.
- My gosh. - And at last,
we found a gift for you!
(For us?)
- Is that treasure? - Treasure?
- Treasure? - We found a gift for you!
(Is that some kind of treasure?)
- We found such a precious gift. - Is it treasure?
- It's a card. - It's a blank check.
We managed to find an exemption ticket for the couple performance...
- after 30 years. - What?
(An exemption ticket for the couple performance?)
- Sure, it's so precious. - that's amazing.
- It's very valuable. - It sure is.
- It's valuable. - Yes, indeed.
- It's valuable. - Yes, it is.
Just trust us.
We'll depart for Korea soon.
- Come to our house quickly. - My gosh.
- Where is it? - We miss you very much.
(Their grandparents came back to Korea with the exemption ticket.)
- We have to go to their house? - Where's their house?
Before you set out to your grandparents' house,
you'll decide the rankings and jobs as their grandchildren.
- Okay. - Jobs?
- "Rankings and jobs"? - What do the rankings mean?
I guess we all have different jobs.
"First grandson, studying to take the bar exam for a long time."
- Are these predetermined? - The youngest is in eighth grade.
All right.
"A member of a new girl group".
You're the grandchildren of Family R.
There are 4 grandsons and 4 granddaughters.
- Okay. - There are four granddaughters?
- Four? - What?
- There are 4 granddaughters. - There are 4?
- Yes. - We must dress up like girls.
Eight stickers that tell you...
about the jobs and rankings are hidden all over this building.
Find the sticker. If you put it either on you or another member,
the member will be fixed with the job.
You cannot remove the sticker once you've put it on a body.
That means it's over for that person.
Yes, if there are two stickers on your body at the end of the race,
you will play rock-paper-scissors with a member without stickers.
- And the winner will get to choose. - Okay.
Don't you think the wrestler will have a hard time today?
- Yes, I think so. - It suits you.
I want to be the bar exam student or the lawyer.
- You'd make a good wrestler. - That will be neat.
- Yes, the lawyer sounds good. - I want the zookeeper.
- Zookeeper. - I want to be the zookeeper.
It means war. Great.
(Family Tree of Family R)
Get ready.
All right.
Jong Kook is in the front again.
- Only Haha will benefit from it. - Let's go.
Only Haha will benefit.
- From which floor? - I'll search here first.
(They can put the stickers on themselves or on other members.)
Here it is.
(Kwang Soo has found the envelope with the sticker first.)
What is it?
"First grandson, long-time bar exam student."
Hey!
Hey, give me that.
(I found one too.)
(Jae Seok has also obtained a sticker soon after.)
Right here. Right here.
(I should quickly find one too.)
My gosh, here.
Where is it?
(He gets close to Seok Jin quietly.)
You startled me!
What was that?
You're a member of a top girl group.
Hey! Darn it.
The third-oldest granddaughter, a top girl group member.
You're unbelievable.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook is looking for the sticker furiously.)
(Rushing)
(So Min climbs after Jong Kook.)
(Here's your sticker.)
Hey, she put something on me.
(He's forced to become an eighth grader, the youngest.)
- You're the youngest granddaughter. - Oh, no!
I really don't want to dress up like a girl.
- There's nothing here. - I don't want to dress up.
(Jong Kook finds another sticker, his only hope.)
- Jong Kook. - Did you find one?
- Jong Kook. - My gosh.
My gosh, this is...
- What is it? - This one is bad too.
(He obtains 2 stickers for granddaughters.)
I don't want to dress up, but I have two girl stickers.
(Current Status of Obtained Stickers)
(Long-time bar exam student, lawyer, girl group member, wrestler,)
(zookeeper, fortune-teller, eighth grader, girl group member)
Time is up.
All right, everyone. We'll check now.
Whom am I supposed to play rock-paper-scissors with?
- Jong Kook... There's no volunteer. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- You have to. - Come here if you want wrestler.
- In my opinion, the four of you... - Okay.
- Okay. - I should go for this one.
I should go for this one.
- I want the zookeeper. - If I win, I can choose, right?
- I want to go for the zookeeper. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- I want to try that. - Is that so?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min wins, and Jae Seok loses.)
- So Min, go for the zookeeper. - Okay.
You're going to win.
It's either fortune-teller or the granddaughter.
- rock-paper... - Ready or not,
- rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min loses, and Haha wins.)
Okay.
(Since Haha is the winner, he'll choose one for her.)
(He gives her the sticker for the wrestler.)
Why did you do that?
- Listen, So Min. - It's fun to see her as a wrestler.
- That's right. - Why?
- That's great. - Why did you go for that?
You can't take it off once it's on.
- Right. That's great for you. - Why did you go against Haha?
- You should've gone with Jong Kook. - I wanted to go for the zookeeper.
Choose whichever one you want.
- Hey, it's either fortune-teller... - This is crazy.
Jae Seok, the fortune-teller one is better than the other one.
- No, no. - Rock-paper-scissors
- That's not right. - You choose.
You can never win, can you?
My goodness.
- That one is better. That's better. - Seriously.
- I'm going to... - Yes, you should give that to him.
- Should I be the fortune-teller? - I should be a middle schooler.
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- Watch out. I'm in eighth grade. - What do you have?
Hey, kids in eighth grade are going through puberty.
- I'm at the rebellious age. - We're in big trouble.
I'm at that phase. You'd better watch out.
This is no joke.
(Bar exam student, lawyer, top girl group member, wrestler,)
(fortune-teller, zookeeper, girl group member, eighth grader)
Younger ones, hurry up.
(The grandchildren show up in their disguises.)
I have the most ordinary role today.
All right. 2nd and 3rd siblings. Come on out.
(She bumps her head against the youngest.)
(Come here, you youngest.)
- That's not how you play it. - That's not it.
That's not how you play it.
(The fourth-oldest suddenly wrestles with the youngest.)
Look at you.
- Mr. Lawyer. - Yes, I'm the lawyer.
(Ji Hyo, a member of a new girl group and Haha, zookeeper)
You're so scary. Gosh.
- You look so scary. - Jong Kook looks scary.
- How could you look this scary? - I know, right?
(The scariest eighth grader, Kook Soon)
You're so scary.
My brother.
- Do you work at funerals? - Hold on. Hey.
- I'm a lawyer. - You are?
- You look scary. - I'm a lawyer despite my look.
I thought you worked for a funeral service company.
My gosh, this is crazy.
- What's that? - Seok Jin.
I'm in a girl group.
- Really? - You're in a girl group?
He's in the fife and drum band.
Gosh, he scared me!
What is this?
(Jae Ni, the fortune-teller in pink, shows up.)
It looks good on him. It does.
- Hello. - Look at you two.
I've seen you two from somewhere.
- Who am I? Am I a band leader? - Hold on.
Forget about everything. But Jong Kook is supposed to be a girl?
- Give me an outfit that fits me. - He looks nothing like a girl.
- The sleeves are ripped here. - Seriously.
Iron Min.
Give us better outfits.
- She's in a girl group. - Girl groups don't dress like this.
- He's on "How Is That Possible?". - I've seen him.
(He must be on the show, "How Is That Possible?")
I've seen an old man who dresses up like a girl.
- Right, exactly. - Yes, that's true!
We heard that an old man roams around Seoul in a girl's clothes.
- Hey, I'm in a girl group. - She's really in a girl group?
- I'm in a girl group. - No, that's not true.
Sir, please live a long life!
That's right! Yes!
- I'm not an old man. I'm a girl. - Wait.
You'll set out to your grandparents' house now.
Gosh, I'm on Garosu-gil today.
It's a shame that I might leave now.
Where would you go in this costume?
- That's not a problem for me. - We can...
We can sit at a cafe on Garosu-gil.
- You know? We can sip Americano. - That's right.
People will report you two if both of you are at a cafe.
(People will report you two if both of you are at a cafe.)
- We can observe people. - You'll get reported.
- Let's get going for now. - Shouldn't we do that?
The pink wig looks great on Jae Seok.
- It looks great on him. - Yes, it does.
Pink hair suits you much better than black hair.
(They set out to meet their grandparents in 30 years.)
I wonder where we are going. You know?
By the way, they look like sisters.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin look like real sisters.
Thank you for saying that.
I have a story. Let me tell you.
I'm doing this because my brother likes playing dress-up.
- Hey, hey. - That's why...
(A kind brother and a brother who likes to dress up like a girl)
Stop lying.
- You're ridiculous. - That's so sad.
My brother's story has been on "How Is That Possible?"
- That's sad. - You're very thoughtful.
- I am, right? - You're so kind.
- You almost made me cry. - You're so kind.
- You almost cried, didn't you? - I almost cried.
- His younger brother plays along. - It's a sad story.
- You hope he'll be sane someday. - Right.
Se Chan, what's the case you're working on these days?
- The case I'm defending now? - Yes.
I'm just on a case for my business. It's a construction case.
- What case? - Construction case.
Which construction?
- Hold on. - To buy the property...
- To buy the property... - Do you know what a lawyer does?
I defend my clients, don't I?
Listen.
Tell me about the separation of powers.
What separation?
(What's that?)
- Separation of powers? - A lawyer should know that.
- You don't know that? - Hey.
What's prohibition against double jeopardy then?
- Double jeopardy? - Yes, double jeopardy.
Prohibition against double jeopardy...
You should tell us what it is, sister.
- What? - What's that?
- I know what it is, punk. - What is it?
Don't call me punk, sister.
(Don't call me punk, sister.)
- How could you call me that? - Hey, we're sisters.
- I can't even call my sister punk? - How could you?
- We're sisters. - But...
You can't call me that though.
I used to change your diapers when you were a baby.
Diapers? Stop lying.
You and I have a big age difference.
These days, I'm the one changing your diapers.
- That's so sad. - Exactly.
- She's so nice. - This is sad.
- You're so nice. You are. - Yes, I am.
- I take care of my sister. - You're so kind.
Since you're the fortune-teller, you should read our fortunes.
- Yes, read our fortunes. - Should I?
Tell us what will happen to us.
What do you say? Can I get married this year?
- Will I get married? - You?
- You got married last year. - You're married.
- Really? - Yes.
- You got married three times. - Really?
- I keep forgetting things. - She forgets easily.
And you used to be a guy too.
What? I'm a guy now?
Hey, I'm your sister in this play.
He got out of his role. He got out of his role just now.
- Seriously. - He got out of his role.
- You're confusing me. Stop. - What's up with you?
Are we still role-playing or not?
- Choose one. - My goodness.
- What's your ranking? - I'm the seventh-oldest.
- 7th-oldest. - 7th-oldest? Goodness.
My gosh, our parents...
They created a masterpiece together.
- we are too ugly except her. - By the way,
- She should be in a girl group now. - She's pretty.
- Seriously. - How many years has it been?
- Wait. I'll debut soon. - She still hasn't debuted?
By the way, you've been saying that you'd debut for 20 years now.
She's the whole package as long as no one finds out about her past.
(The youngest is brutally honest.)
(This is a statement from the youngest.)
Actually, the fact that she hasn't debuted might be...
- a blessing in disguise. - That's true.
Let's say that she makes a debut now.
If she becomes popular, people will look her up.
- Hey, take me for example. - That's right.
When I was at my peak,
the scandal with Gong Yoo ruined my career. Look where I am now.
- Seok Jin, what's wrong with you? - What?
(The role-playing is off now.)
- Please! - Stop dressing up like a woman!
I'm your sister!
If there wasn't a scandal with Gong Yoo...
- Poor Seok Jin. - Goodness.
Seok Jin, if you go too far with the role-playing,
we can't go along with it.
(Do it right.)
It was just enough. The scandal with Gong Yoo.
It was totally dope.
- "Dope"? - What's that?
I can't put my finger on it, but don't we look like...
a circus troupe on our way to perform?
- Family troupe to perform a show. - Seriously.
- It's a family troupe. - We're a circus troupe.
- It's the whole family. - Is this it? Did we arrive?
My gosh, look at the house!
Are they over there?
Grandma!
Grandpa!
My gosh, our grandparents are loaded.
- How many houses are there? - They are totally rich.
- I didn't know they were this rich. - My grandma is rich.
Grandma, we're here!
- Grandma. - Grandma!
- We had no idea that you were rich. - Grandma.
Your oldest grandson is here.
- Your second-oldest is here. - Is there...
Is there a big show in the vicinity?
- Is there a show here? - No, this isn't a circus.
Everyone, it's the biggest show on earth!
By the way, we should meet with our grandparents.
(Opening)
- They're here! - Grandma!
- My puppies are here. - My gosh.
Really?
(Grandma Im Soo Hyang, Grandpa Lee Sang Yeob)
(They are our grandparents?)
- You're here. - Grandpa.
(Welcome, my dear grandchildren.)
- Hey, you. - It's nice to see you.
- Why are you wearing that? - Grandpa.
They put on the disguise before their introductions.
Grandma.
(Who is that guy with the yellow wig?)
You look older than Grandma.
(You look older than Grandma.)
Grandpa.
- Why do you look so old? - Grandma.
- Grandpa is wearing nice shoes. - Grandpa.
- He knows hip hop. - I knew he was loaded.
I'm a grandpa who knows hip hop.
You should behave well before the youngest takes your shoes.
- You might lose your shoes to her. - Be careful.
What kind of grandpa is he? He's so scared.
You should act like a grandpa.
(The race starts with their grandparents.)
By the way, we only have five grandchildren.
Why did eight of you come?
(We only have 5 grandchildren. Why did 8 of you come?)
(They only have five grandchildren?)
What is he saying?
What is this?
- What about the other 3? - 3 of us weren't family.
We only have five grandchildren.
- Exactly. - I knew there was a twist.
- I knew there was a twist. Ma'am. - I...
Ma'am? You're an old lady.
(Excuse me, ma'am.)
- She's an old lady. - I knew it.
It's so obvious that these two are fakes.
Hey.
- Run the DNA test! - I knew it.
- I'm their real granddaughter. - Something was off about her.
I'm related to them.
All right. Three of you...
are not the real grandchildren...
who are eyeing exemption ticket for the couple performance.
(3 of them are fake family members.)
(Some of us are fakes?)
- 3 of us... 3 of us... - My gosh.
- It's so obvious. I knew it. - Three of us?
I saw this coming.
Okay. I know who it is.
And among the real grandchildren,
there is the most-beloved grandchild of the grandparents.
- The most-beloved grandchild? - What?
- The most-beloved grandchild? - There's another twist.
(Why is he reacting this way?)
And the most-beloved grandchild...
already knows 2 of 3 fake grandchildren.
(The most-beloved grandchild knows 2 of 3 fake grandchildren.)
- Two of them? - There's a spy here.
That member already knows 2 of 3 fake grandchildren.
That brings me to my next point.
The real grandchildren and the most-beloved grandchild...
must find out who the three fake grandchildren are.
The fake grandchildren must eliminate...
the most-beloved grandchild in order to win.
- The fake grandchildren? - My gosh.
My gosh, this is...
(Real grandchildren versus fake grandchildren)
The most-beloved grandchild is on our side.
- Right. - By the way,
I don't know if I should share this. But let me just say this.
When we were getting off the bus, Jong Kook said,
"Grandpas love the youngest daughters the most."
- That's what he said. - Do you remember that?
- Do you? - I remember it too.
(While on their way to their grandparents...)
Grandparents love the youngest the most.
(Was this a confession?)
I said that when there were no cameras.
- No. - There was one inside.
- There was one inside. - Oh, really?
- I didn't mean much by it. - He's flustered.
- He is. - It's about time he became one.
You're right.
I swear. It's not me.
(Jae Seok interrupts them.)
It was you!
- It was you! - The fortune-teller...
- will reveal the truth! - Calm down.
- You should know the truth. - Right.
- That's right. - You're a fortune-teller.
- He's a fortune-teller. - Come on, perform your ritual.
My goodness.
For today's mission,
you'll be divided into Team Grandpa and Team Grandma.
- Okay. - This is important.
The hints you'll be given will differ.
If Team Grandpa wins,
your grandpa will choose one team member to whom a hint...
regarding the most-beloved grandchild will be given.
If Team Grandma wins,
your grandma will choose one team member...
- One? - who will receive a hint...
regarding the three fakes.
- We should go to Team Grandma. - Right.
- Yes. - We should find out the fakes.
But those fakes...
might team up with Sang Yeob in order to receive hints.
- About the most-beloved grandson? - Right.
Those who are fakes will try to team up with him.
- They're smart. - They'll attempt to do so.
The losing team will receive water bombs.
They will also be confirmed to join the couple performance.
- We must win no matter what. - You're right.
We must win.
Both of the grandparents will also receive water bombs if they lose.
- Shall we do rock-paper-scissors? - Sure.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Results for Rock-Paper-Scissors)
Who won?
- I choose Team Grandma. - Okay.
(He wants to receive hints about the fakes.)
I must go there.
- I must go there too. - I need to find the fakes.
- I should go there. - Then...
- I'll go to Team Grandpa. - From the way I see it...
(Se Chan chooses Team Grandpa.)
- That's strange. Why? - What?
You're being suspicious.
There are fakes among us.
- You must be a fake. - Right.
- You're a fake. - I'm...
- Why did you pick that team? - I need to protect the hints.
There are three fakes among us.
(Is he truly going to prevent the fakes from getting the hints?)
(Team Grandma: Jong Kook, Haha, Ji Hyo, Jae Seok)
(Team Grandpa: Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, Se Chan, So Min)
It's highly likely that the most-beloved grandchild...
is in this team.
- Right. - Because they only need...
to know one more...
- Right. - with the hints.
But they might end up in this team after losing in rock-paper-scissors.
Yes, they might be unlucky.
- That's plausible. - It's a pity.
(Kwang Soo,)
(look at that plane.)
(Why is Jae Seok pointing at a plane?)
- What is it? - The audio...
- was interrupted. - Take that plane and get lost.
(He suddenly tells him off.)
What was that all of a sudden?
Take that plane and get lost.
How dare you talk like that to your older brother?
What?
Wait, I didn't mean that.
(He panics.)
- It's not like that! I swear! - Hey!
- It wasn't like that! - What have you done?
It's not like that! I promise!
- No, no! It was an accident! - How dare you?
- What did you do? - I'm so sorry!
- How dare you? - I'm truly sorry.
- I'm sorry. - You punk!
- Watch out. - Okay, I'm sorry.
Are you three in some kind of super strength performance?
(He's curious.)
Jae Seok, you have no right to ask that in your attire.
(Haha doesn't understand him.)
- Come here. - You're so shameless.
Come here.
(The super strength team is finally complete.)
He's so shameless.
With that attire?
The first match you'll have with a hint on stake is...
Food Name Kung Kung Ta.
You'll take turns...
playing a three-syllable word chain.
However, the final member...
may only say the name of a dish.
(They need to do two rounds.)
The last member needs to do well.
There is no syllable limit for that.
- There isn't? - Only for the final member.
- It's hard. - There is no limit?
- The fourth player is key. - Right.
This isn't about attacking each other. It's teamwork.
- Okay, we'll go first. - Why?
- After you. - We'll go first.
Does she go first?
You may not repeat the words.
- What? We can't? - No, you can't.
I'm really terrible at word chains.
- I'm ruined. - Can we repeat them at least once?
- We have Ji Hyo. - You can take your shoes off.
- Take them off. - Right, they have Seok Jin.
The number of dishes that I know...
- is over 30,000. - Okay!
- Don't be ridiculous. - It'll be a piece of cake.
- He made this game. - Right.
- He's the original creator. - It's been a long time.
- He's the original creator! - He made it.
Excuse me, but are you two married?
- Who? - Their colors look like our flag.
- What do you mean? - The colors.
- Aren't you content creators? - What do you mean?
- How could you say that? - Aren't you on social networks?
- I think I'm right. - I'm a bar exam student.
They're on social networks.
Ji Hyo, you're first. Get ready.
Ready, set, go.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Kung, Kung, Ta, Kung, Kung, Ta
Say a dish at the end
(First syllable is "ko".)
Ko Hyun Jung.
(Ko Hyun Jung)
Water purifier.
- That was so slow. - "Gi"?
Train ticket.
Okay.
Pyo In Bong.
(What's wrong with the rhythm?)
(What are they doing?)
- Hold on. - Pyo In Bong.
- What is this? - Seriously? Hold on.
It's too weird.
Why bother clapping?
- Why would you do this? - They're offbeat.
- Why would you do this? - Come out!
- This won't do. Come out. - Come on.
- You're so slow! - Come out.
- This isn't fair. - Why not?
- Come out! - That's too much.
- Everyone. - Hold on.
- Let us do one round. - Come on.
- Let us do one round. - My gosh.
- Let us do one more round. - Let them go one more round.
We'll let you do it. Sorry.
- Let's do well, guys. - We can do it.
- I'm so disappointed. - Let's do well.
- 1, 2, 3, let's go! - 1, 2, 3, let's go!
This is your last chance.
- Wait. - It's your last chance.
This time, we'll drag you out.
- Let's drag them out. - Ready, set, go.
- Kungs, Kungs, Kungs - It's too fast.
Kung, Kung, Ta, Kung, Kung, Ta
Say a dish at the end
"Midopa".
- What? Hold on. - My gosh.
(What?)
- What was that? - Wait.
- "Midopa"? - I can't take this any longer.
- This is just my style! - Why doesn't this count?
- I like it! - "Midopa"?
- It doesn't work. - "Midopa"?
- It's a department store. - Don't you know "midopa"?
- Right? - Come on.
Why doesn't it count?
- It works. - Let me explain.
- Midopa Department Store... - It existed before.
- was quite famous. - Right.
- It disappeared. - During the financial crisis,
- Right. - they merged with...
- L department store. - Yes, it's no longer existing.
- It's gone. - Right.
- It's not in the dictionary. - It's not.
How sad is that?
- It was in her memories. - Right.
- She's sad it has disappeared. - Yes.
- But the other team is against it. - Come on.
- We can't be any more lenient. - Come on.
- This is your final chance. - Just once more.
It's your final chance. Fine.
Ji Hyo.
You really are old to have remembered that.
- She's very old. - You're right.
I'm sure people are wildly searching for "Midopa" right now.
- I know. - I was startled too.
- "Midopa"? - I didn't know I'd say that.
If we fail this time, we'll acknowledge it.
- Let's drag them out this time. - This is already too weird.
- Ready, set, go. - Drag them away.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Kung, Kung, Ta, Kung, Kung, Ta
Say a dish at the end
Yu Jae Seok.
- Seokguram. - That's good.
(Yu Jae Seok, Seokguram)
"Ambasa".
Photo studio.
(Jae Seok is the 5th player and needs to say a dish.)
Stir-fried "kwanchang".
- Hold on. - Okay.
(Stir-fried "kwanchang"?)
That's tasty.
- It's very tasty. - That doesn't count.
(They can't take this any longer.)
- Come out. - Stir-fried "kwanchang"?
Did you mean "enema"?
- "Kwanchang"? - I meant shellfish muscles.
It's shellfish muscles!
- Stir-fried shellfish muscles! - Shellfish muscles!
- Shellfish muscles! - What's "kwanchang"?
What is that?
- What is that? - I meant shellfish muscles!
That's enough!
- What's "kwanchang"? - I won't tolerate this.
- I won't tolerate this any longer. - Come out.
- It was shellfish muscles. - What was "kwanchang".
- "Kwanchang"? - You meant shellfish muscles.
- We can't be lenient. - That was hilarious.
How does stir-fried "kwanchang" taste?
Be quiet.
(Haha's thinking of a new menu for his bbq restaurant.)
- All right. - Ready, set, go.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Kung, Kung, Ta, Kung, Kung, Ta
Say a dish at the end
Macheon-dong.
Club.
"Imyunsoo".
- That doesn't work. - Marine products.
Why not? "Imyunsoo".
(He mispronounces the word.)
- What's wrong with him? - It's "im".
It's "im".
- Come out. - Give us one more chance.
- Goodness. Give us one more chance. - It's "im".
Give us one more chance.
Hey, I think we should be more clear.
When you're saying a word,
make sure you emphasize the last syllable.
- Be clear. - Emphasize the last syllable.
- We're not bad at this game. - Right.
- We just can't hear well. - Right.
- We know many words. - All right, let's go.
Ready, set, go.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Kung, Kung, Ta, Kung, Kung, Ta
Say a dish at the end
Fish.
Oil sauce.
Was that a "chang" or a "jang"?
- Hold on. - Come on.
(After being stuck,)
(he blames it on Se Chan.)
Come on!
- Of course, it's "oil sauce". - He wasn't clear.
(They're wrong once again.)
(Good job!)
Well done!
(Seok Jin's emphasizing plan goes out the window.)
- Great job. - I'm so irritated.
- What's your problem? - No.
Was that my fault? Was it?
- Jae Seok, am I to blame? - No.
What is this?
- Come on. - I said, "oil sauce".
So Min didn't play this game once.
- Poor So Min. - This is great.
- This is awesome. - He's the spy.
- Everyone understood "oil sauce". - Seok Jin.
Aren't you the spy?
- He said, "chang". - He's the spy.
Don't be so obvious.
- Don't do that. - They can't pass three players.
All right.
Let's succeed this time around. Okay!
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
(Ji Hyo said, "gag".)
Oil sauce.
Crock.
Boss.
(If Jae Seok can say a dish that starts with "im",)
(they'll succeed one round.)
Im Su Yeon's fried rice.
- What? - Im Su Yeon's fried rice.
(Im Su Yeon's fried rice?)
We talked about the "imyunsoo" once before!
(Jong Kook explodes.)
- My gosh. - Im Su Yeon's fried rice!
- This is... - Get out.
- That doesn't exist. - Im Su Yeon's fried rice.
- Such a thing doesn't exist. - Im Su Yeon's fried rice.
- It's... - It's delicious.
- It does exist. - Drag them away!
- It's a franchise. - Who is Im Su Yeon?
- I was... - Don't be ridiculous. Leave.
- Get out. - I'll make you fried rice.
- He wants Im Su Yeon. - Goodness.
- He said Im Su Yeon. - He's so suspicious.
Such fried rice doesn't exist.
- Come on. - Hey, we were talking about...
- They're so mean. - Excuse me.
- We were talking about it before. - Right.
- He's looking at me as if... - He's friendly.
- he's looking at an opponent. - Why?
- That's how he looks right now. - Come on.
- Look at him. - You got it wrong last time.
Look it up.
He was boasting.
(20 minutes ago)
(Jae Seok mentioned the "imyunsoo".)
- But now, look what he's saying. - I couldn't remember it.
- I even helped him out. - He's suspicious.
I chose "boss"...
- to make it easier... - Isn't he suspicious.
- for him. - He's suspicious.
- Goodness. - I'm sorry about that.
I promise to do better next time.
Or can we switch places?
- Wait. - Why didn't you do that earlier?
(His team members suspect him.)
- I still can't believe it. - Ready, set, go.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Say a dish at the end
Bicycle.
Goose liver.
(Bicycle, goose liver)
Soy sauce bottle.
Log.
Salted radishes.
(They finally succeed.)
(They have completed one round...)
(despite being laughing stocks to their opponents.)
Im Chang Jung.
Jeongbalsan.
The foot of a mountain.
A bear's foot.
(After much turmoil, it's Jong Kook's turn.)
(If he gets it right, Team Grandma will win.)
"Bal"...
(Wailing)
(He runs out of time and fails.)
- I thought we'd lose. - "Bal"...
- There's balsamic! - Balsamic!
- Balsamic! - Balsamic!
Balsamic!
(Everyone mourns for balsamic.)
That was so close!
Can they say "goose liver" and "soy sauce bottle"?
"Foie gras" is goose liver.
- Of course, we can. - We can?
- Okay, then. - Okay.
Let's say, "duck liver" too.
- That works too. - All right.
Say, "chicken's liver".
- That was close. - That doesn't work.
- "Cow's liver". - That doesn't work.
- Why not? - It doesn't work.
Do "pig's liver". Do everything.
How about "Seok Jin's liver"?
- "Seok Jin's liver"? - Goodness.
- Do everything. - I thought we'd make it this time.
It was so close.
- Let's keep the same order. - The same?
Can we neglect the dictionary...
as long as whatever we say counts?
Then you'll come up with so many strange words.
And I enjoy having Im Su Yeon's fried rice.
Why doesn't Im Su Yeon's fried rice work?
Who is Im Su Yeon?
- Who is she? - Bring her here!
- Who is she? - Who is she?
- Tell me. - She's a good cook.
Call her immediately.
There are so many Im Su Yeons in this country...
- who make fried rice. - Exactly.
So why doesn't it make sense?
Who is she?
Come on.
- This will cause a ruckus. - Right.
- I'm sure it will. - Right.
You should be prepared.
- Let's hurry. - Okay.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Say a dish at the end
Bowleg.
Handcart.
Car repair.
(Bowleg, handcart, car repair)
Terminal.
(Bowleg, handcart, car repair, terminal)
(It's Jong Kook's turn once again.)
(Will he be able to come up with a dish name?)
Terminal.
Grilled deodeok roots that are made on top of a board.
- Good. - It's so delicious.
(Grilled deodeok roots that are made on top of a board.)
(Haha verifies its taste.)
- Darn it. - That doesn't count!
Why?
(What was that answer?)
(Why is it wrong?)
- Why? - What was that?
- Why? - We got it right, didn't we?
Grilled deodeok roots that are made
- on top of a board. - It's tasty!
- It's delicious. - Wait.
- Hold on. - This counts.
- You must cook it on a board. - It's much tastier.
What was all that about a board?
On top of a board?
(This lawyer is at a loss for words.)
- The board will burn. - No, it won't.
- Then how do you grill it? - The grilled deodeok roots...
were made on the board.
If that phrase comes up online, I'll acknowledge it.
- My gosh. - Come on.
Why bother searching?
No.
- I couldn't find any. - It doesn't make any sense.
There is such a thing!
They're so picky.
We're not close-minded people.
- It just doesn't make sense. - We have some leniency.
- Then how should we eat them? - You're being too strict.
Goodness.
You lack knowledge.
Then I can say,
"kimchi that's in my fridge".
- Sure. - Go for it.
- Say it! - Do it!
- Do it! - Go for it!
- I said, do it! - Let's do it.
- Do it! It must make sense. - Do it.
- It needs to make sense. - Do it!
Our youngest sister will beat you all.
You have to keep the rhythm.
- Don't worry about that. - If you stutter, you'll get hit.
- Hold on. - If you stutter, you'll get hit.
(Jong Kook threatens them.)
What did you say?
Why should we get hit for stuttering?
- We can't stutter? - You must enunciate well.
- You can't say that. - Enunciate.
Keep the rhythm.
I'll make the rules a bit easier.
It just needs to make sense, and you need to make only one round.
Okay.
(The staff makes it easier.)
They made it so much easier.
We just need to make one round.
- We can do it. - One round.
- Focus. - We can do it.
- All right. - Ready, set, go.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Kung, Kung, Ta, Kung, Kung, Ta
Say a dish at the end
Corner of a room.
Seokguram.
Amsa-dong.
Club.
(It's So Min's turn.)
(Will she overcome this pressure and succeed?)
(The fourth word is "club".)
"Riyeokguk". I mean seaweed soup.
- It's seaweed soup. - Darn it.
- What? - It's seaweed soup.
(What is "Riyeokguk"?)
Nothing starts with "ri".
- Why would you say that? - Of course, there are.
"A hotdog with a ribbon".
Good.
- Good job. - "A hotdog with a ribbon".
- "Hotdog from Lisbon". - There are many, So Min.
Don't you dare sit there again.
- There's handcart. - What?
(So Min bursts.)
- She was wrong only once. - There's handcart.
- Don't you sit there. - Right.
What are you saying?
- Seok Jin. - There's handcart.
I only played once so far.
She only got it wrong once.
- This was her first time playing. - I only played once.
- It was just once. - Hey.
He's so coldhearted towards her.
I haven't seen him in a while.
"Don't you dare sit there."
She only played once.
- My gosh. - Isn't he so brazen?
- My goodness. - Goodness.
(This is an obnoxious game.)
Let's win this time.
- Okay. - Let's succeed. Ready, set, go.
Say a dish at the end
Mountaintop.
Lee Bong Won.
Director.
Atka mackerel.
(It's Jae Seok's turn to finish it.)
(Will he make up for the past humiliation?)
I think they'll succeed this time.
(The fourth word is "atka mackerel.)
Tap water.
- That's food too. - Why not?
(He confidently says his answer.)
(Why are we wrong?)
- That's not food. - That doesn't count.
- How is tap water food? - It's food.
- It's not food. - This isn't right.
- Tap water doesn't count. - No, it works.
You could've said, "ramyeon I had at the swimming pool".
- You had many choices. - I was hungry back then!
(He suddenly barges in.)
(Do you know what I've gone through?)
- Yes! - I was tormented by hunger!
- Hey, I was... - I sated my hunger with tap water!
- Come on. - Hey.
- When we were hungry, - I invited you over.
- we drank tap water! - It was like home for me!
- Im Su Yeon! - I did.
Did you drink tap water then?
What do you expect us to eat then?
- Still... - Come on.
You didn't allow us to have Im Su Yeon's fried rice either.
- When we were young, - We can't even have...
- grilled deodeok roots. - we were starving.
- That's why we chose tap water! - We were so hungry.
We would fill up our stomachs with tap water.
- You're pushing it with this one. - Then what will you allow?
Come on. There are many.
- What? - Tell us.
- Sujebi. - Handmade noodles.
- Handmade jajangmyeon. - Sujebi.
- There are many. - You're right.
- Fine, let's pull out. - Okay.
- I accept that. - Do you?
- Do you? - Why would you say tap water?
Aren't we so terrible?
You're the worst.
- I know. - This will never end.
- The sun's going down. - Look at the sky.
Let's just go one round.
They even made it easier for us.
- Okay. Be serious. - Ready, set, go.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Say a dish at the end
- "Yogiyo". - Chef.
(What?)
Is that allowed?
Photo studio.
Wardrobe.
(Seok Jin needs to complete the round.)
(You just need to say a dish.)
Is that allowed?
(Will Seok Jin, who's been making mistakes all day, succeed?)
Stir-fried beef tripe with rice.
(He enunciates clearly.)
(Team Grandpa wins.)
(It's finally over!)
Wait a minute.
Does "Yogiyo" work?
- That shouldn't count. - Does it work?
- We did it! - Excuse me, it doesn't count.
It means "here".
- It doesn't work. - Why not?
- That's not it. - You can't do that.
- "Where? 'Yogiyo'." - Then Im Su Yeon's fried rice...
- should be right as well. - Right.
- You should count that right. - Yes.
No, no.
- "Which way do I go?" - "Yogiyo".
- "Yogiyo"! - That doesn't count.
- You should give us credit too. - Go to your seat while we talk.
- Okay. - If not, give us another chance.
- We'll try again. - "Yogiyo".
It doesn't count.
We'll go again then.
- We'll go again. - We can allow that.
They'll do it over again, so let's pull out.
- They'll do it again. - All right, we'll pull out.
Okay. Let's pull out.
(After successfully threatening them, they pull out.)
- Hold on a minute. - Okay.
- What was that? - What was that?
You can't say brand names.
- We're not being sponsored. - No brand names.
- We didn't know. - We didn't.
Se Chan, it was you, right?
- Yes. - You're suspicious.
We'll do it once again.
Let's go.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Kung, Kung, Ta, Kung, Kung, Ta
Say a dish at the end
J ramyeon.
(He says a brand name.)
- Hey. - Darn it.
(J ramyeon)
- Hold on. - Darn it.
- Are you kidding me? - Darn it.
(They explode.)
- Hey! - How dare you?
- Hey, you! - You can't say that!
- No, wait. - My gosh.
Since I'm banned to say brand names,
- that's the only thing I think of. - I quit.
- I can't think of anything else. - I quit. Consider me out.
- That little... - This time...
I can't stop thinking about brand names.
Hey! You could've said Jindo dog or Qin Shi Huang.
- There are so many. - But that's all I could think of.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Let's succeed this time around.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Get ready. - I desperately want to win.
Ready, set, go.
Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
Say a dish at the end
(Don't say a brand name.)
Shoe rack.
(Shoe rack)
Jean Valjean.
Soy sauce braised beef.
Atka mackerel.
(Jae Seok, who's filled his stomach with tap water, is next.)
(Will he come up with a word that makes sense?)
(It's the same syllable.)
Sujebi.
We did it!
(Team Grandma is the final winner.)
- It's over. - We did it.
- We did it. - We did it.
What is this?
(What is this?)
Success!
- Okay. - Yes!
- And now... - Good job.
Team Grandma has won.
Our team has no fake ones.
- We all worked so hard. - We all worked so hard.
- You'll be given hints about fakes. - Okay.
Grandma can choose...
- a grandchild to look at the hint. - Okay.
Grandma, I tried my best.
- You saw me. - You saw me do it.
You know how hard I tried.
- You saw me. - I worked hard.
- I'm certain. - You saw it right next to me.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - That's the worst game to play.
Let's do it.
(I can't choose.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Ji Hyo has lost.)
But you have to share the hint with me.
- Okay. - Share with me.
When you choose the same one with Grandma, you win. How's that sound?
- That sounds fun. - All right?
- Let's try something new. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Haha has chosen "rock" which is the same as Grandma.)
(The hint about the 3 fakes goes to Haha.)
He's a bad choice.
- He's not a good choice. - Trust me!
- I tried really hard. - Share it with me.
Yes. I'll tell you no matter what.
- I don't think Haha is a fake one. - Haha, I know you tried.
He did well.
I worked really hard.
I'm the one who pushed through Im Su Yeon's fried rice.
"Do not show anyone else."
After all,
we're on the same team.
Can't we see it together?
- No. - I can't trust anyone.
That seems too vague.
("Fakes are 2 men and 1 woman.")
(Seok Jin, Jong Kook, and Jae Seok count as women in this race.)
(And So Min counts as a man.)
That's it for Round One's hint.
- We'll move on to Round Two. - Okay.
(Who are the 3 fakes that are hiding their identities?)
Our team lost the spirit.
- We can do it. - Don't worry.
This mission is...
Mysterious Vocabulary.
- Okay. - What's that?
Both teams will take turns and the winning team...
will have the two-syllable open ticket...
the priority to say the answer.
After opening the two letters,
the winning team will guess the related letters.
When they get it wrong, the chance is passed on to the other team.
The team that gets the two questions right first will win.
(The chance is passed on when one says the wrong answer,)
(and they will play the best of 3 games.)
Okay. It doesn't sound that hard.
Your mission is...
to find the bottle cap in the cups.
(Find the bottle cap in the cups)
Each representative will sit down,
and hide the bottle cap among three cups.
(The game will start by hiding the bottle cap in 1 of the 3 cups.)
They will then shuffle the cups for 30 seconds,
ask each other questions, and answer.
After 30 seconds,
if you find the cup with the bottle cap,
you'll get the 2-syllable open ticket...
and the priority to say the answer.
Okay.
And if you either don't ask a question on your turn,
or don't answer the question,
you will be hit by a toy hammer by the opponent.
- That will make you blink. - That is bad.
- We have to ask questions. - Representatives.
Please come out.
Can our two members with the bright hair do it?
- Me and... - Yes, let's do that.
You have to win this.
- Seok Jin. - It's pink versus yellow.
Who will hit with the toy hammer?
Jong Kook can do that.
Oh, no. Please.
(Jong Kook can do that.)
(His pupils are dilated.)
- You can't do that. - Right. He's going to get hurt.
I'll go easy on you.
I'll avoid hitting the critical area.
- Hit hard so that he can blink. - He's going to get hurt.
But we're still on the same team after all.
- Right. - So I'll go easy.
Choose a cup to put your bottle cap in.
I can't wait to see this.
Okay.
(They both choose a cup.)
Set, go.
How much money do you have in your bank account?
Me? 2.8 million dollars.
Oh, boy.
Wait.
(One of his cups falls.)
(He shows where the bottle cap is.)
Were you surprised?
He can't tell whether I'm lying or not.
- Right. - Ask him a question.
What did you eat yesterday?
Me? I ate jjamppong.
- Jjamppong? - Jjamppong.
Jjajangmyeon is better.
What are you talking about?
(Is Jae Seok giving advice?)
Is this a comic talk?
- You have to ask him questions! - He's just being mean.
Okay.
Do you...
have a girlfriend?
I do not.
- Do you have one, don't you? - I don't.
Of course, I don't.
- Hey! - I don't have a girlfriend.
- I don't have a girlfriend. - What are you doing?
(He's trying to get a grip.)
(Seok Jin shows where the bottle cap is.)
- I don't have one. - There's your bottle cap.
There's your bottle cap.
- Why did you blow it just now? - It was the last question.
The last question is important.
- He just showed him. - What did you do?
- You can't blow the whistle now. - What did you do?
It was a simple mistake.
Choose who will guess first with rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Jin wins.)
I won.
I have to guess the right one.
- We should do rock-paper-scissors. - You still...
You have a good chance to win this.
Use your instincts.
- This one? - This one.
(Seok Jin chooses the cup in the middle.)
The one in the middle.
(The winner of this round gets to attack first in the actual game,)
(win the 2-syllable open ticket and the priority to say the answer.)
(Would he have picked the right one?)
(It's empty.)
(Seok Jin fails in guessing where the bottle cap is.)
- That was close. - I knew it.
(Now it's Jae Seok's turn.)
Where is it?
(You saw exactly it was going in the cup in the middle.)
This one.
(What?)
- What? - That's not it.
(Jae Seok chooses the right one which does not have the bottle cap.)
(Jae Seok fails in guessing where the bottle cap is.)
- Who are you? - Who are you?
What did he do?
- What did you do? - What's going on with you?
(Did he compromise the mission on purpose?)
- I'm suspicious of him. - What did you do?
I'm suspicious of him.
- What did you do? - What was that?
- Seriously. - Why did you...
- This does not make sense. - What was that?
- It was so obvious. - Really.
- It's my turn. - Right.
- I think he's on our team. - Right.
This one.
(Will he guess the right one this time?)
(It's empty.)
- It's not in there. - He chose the middle one before.
It's either this one or that one.
- I'm confused. - This one...
or that one.
(He has the second chance after acting suspicious.)
(Will he guess the right one this time?)
- This one. - Yes.
(He has found it.)
(Jae Seok wins the two rewards.)
He was acting so weird, though.
I mean...
if all of you keep acting weird,
- we can't find the fakes. - You were so weird.
I actually thought this was the one.
- He's acting so weird. - I really didn't know.
- He did it on purpose. - I didn't know.
- Do I have to guess the two words? - Right.
If we make a mistake,
the other team can get a chance too.
We might get this one.
You can't tell by one letter.
- Number 1 and 6? - Yes.
Number 1 and 6.
I choose number 1 and 6.
- Why? - I have to guess two.
Number 1 and 6.
- "Gye"? - "Gye"?
- I think I got it. - I think I got it.
First...
This one's difficult.
(Which two words start with "Lee" and end with "Gye"?)
- It's your turn. - "Lee" and "Gye"?
- It's Lee Gye In. - Lee Gye In.
- It ends with "Gye", you idiot! - Lee Gye In?
How is that Lee Gye In?
It starts with "Lee" and ends with "Gye".
(Sighs)
Come on.
That's not how you play this.
- He was trying to be funny. - It's not Lee Gye In.
- I can't guess with just two words. - You have 10 seconds.
It's "Ogolgye" and something else.
"Ogolgye".
- I think it's "Ogolgye". - "Ogolgye"?
Which related word starts with "Lee"?
The bottom one is "Ogolgye".
(I got it.)
- The bottom one is "Ogolgye". - Four,
- three... - Lee Byung Hun.
(Lee Byung Hun and the movie "New World".)
She's right.
(Was Lee Byung Hun in "New World"?)
- He wasn't in that movie. - He wasn't in that movie.
He wasn't?
- It's Lee Jung Jae! - It's Lee Jung Jae!
(It was Lee Jung Jae.)
I played in "New World".
Lee Kwang Soo and "Ogolgye"!
- Lee Kwang Soo and "Ogolgye"? - "Ogolgye".
How am I related to "Ogolgye"?
Let me answer!
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Lee Jung Jae and "New World". - And "New World".
(Team Grandma: Lee Jung Jae and "New World".)
I never imagined it would be "New World".
Let's move on to the next one.
Se Chan, you go.
Let's go, Se Chan.
(Ji Hyo from Team Grandma versus Se Chan from Team Grandpa)
Set, go.
Are you going to send a coffee truck for Kwang Soo?
No way.
Did you feel good after sending a coffee truck for So Min?
- I loved it. - Didn't you think of me?
Not at all.
You asked two questions.
Ask him a question.
I'm sorry.
- Are you okay? - You...
- Are you okay? - Did you...
(You didn't ask a question and you didn't send me a coffee truck.)
Did you and So Min...
Kwang Soo.
(This is getting personal.)
Buy some time.
Okay, that's it.
(One is happy while the other is sad.)
- Kwang Soo... - Wake up.
(This is because of Kwang Soo's personal feelings.)
What does Jun Ho have that I don't?
What do you see in Hong Jong Hyun?
(He got the coffee truck gift.)
I drink five cups of coffee in a day.
(Do you know how much I like coffee?)
She's going to send you one.
Let's win this.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
The middle one.
(The winner gets the 2-syllable open ticket...)
(and the priority to say the answer.)
(Did Se Chan see where the bottle cap went?)
- Okay! - You did it.
(The bottle cap was in there.)
- That's my Se Chan. - You got it at once.
- Let's go. - At once.
- You're not getting the answer. - Se Chan did it.
- How about number 4 and 8? - The last letters?
- 4 and 8, let's get this. - 4 and 8.
Se Chan!
"Saek" and "Gae"?
- "Saek" and "Gae." - Number 4 and 8 is...
- difficult to guess. - It's difficult.
(What would the words be?)
"A Better Tomorrow".
It's "A Better Tomorrow".
Isn't it?
(If the top word is "A Better Tomorrow"...)
No?
(What would the bottom word be?)
Let me answer!
(Let me answer!)
(He tries to answer right after he heard "A Better Tomorrow".)
(What would his answer be?)
"A Better Tomorrow"...
"A Better Tomorrow",
and "Toothpick".
Kwang Soo!
Correct.
("A Better Tomorrow" and "Toothpick" are correct.)
So Min, we did it!
- Wow. - Kwang Soo.
That was...
You weren't the spy after all.
How did he do that?
He did great.
Let's move on to the last one.
- Okay. - So Min, you go.
It's So Min's turn.
- How did he guess that? - And Soo Hyang.
Right here?
(Hide your bottle caps.)
Set, go.
You have a boyfriend, don't you?
I don't. Do you?
I don't either.
Do you like Sang Yeob?
I don't like him.
(She sounds firm.)
- You just got dumped. - I'm always being dumped.
Do you like Sang Yeob?
I have absolutely no interest.
(She sounds solid as a rock.)
- He got dumped twice. - That was a good one, Soo Hyang.
- Will you date him if he asks you? - No.
- How about you? - Me, neither.
(It has turned into a Sang Yeob dumping competition.)
- When you were shooting the drama, - Yes?
did you ever have feelings for him?
No.
Okay. That's enough.
This hurts too much for me!
(This hurts too much for me!)
- Don't worry. - It's just a game.
- They're just talking nonsense. - It's just a game.
It's not the truth.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - We have a good chance.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Good.
(So Min won!)
That's all right.
(If she gets it right, she will be able to get both.)
Just choose anything.
(Will So Min get it right?)
(She found the bottle cap!)
Great, So Min!
(They won the 2-syllable open ticket and the priority to say the answer.)
You did it!
- Good job, good job. - So Min!
- It's all right. - Okay.
Should we go with 1 and 5?
I think we should go with 1 and 5.
The first letter might be confusing, though.
- "Ki". - "Ki".
- Should we go with eight, instead? - I don't know...
- 8. - Go with 8.
(They decide to open 8 instead of 5.)
This one's going to be hard.
Maybe it's something like the four steps to the conclusion. No?
By the railway track
(By the railway track)
(What?)
- "The hut by the railway track". - "The hut by the railway track".
- Wait a minute. - "The Hut By the Railway Track".
(Seok Ja came up with the answer,)
(But it's Team Jae Ni's turn to answer!)
- "The hut by the railway track". - Let me answer.
- "The hut by the railway track". - "The hut by the railway track".
- Correct! - What were you thinking?
("The hut by the railway track" is the correct answer.)
What were you thinking?
- We got it! - We got it!
- Who said it? - We got it!
- Who said it? - It's the answer!
Who said it?
(Look at Seok Jin!)
(It's like a funeral by the railway track.)
- He's the best at this game. - He's so good.
He's an expert.
- He's so good at games. - This is driving me crazy.
If you choose one person...
from Team Grandpa,
that person will get a hint on the most-beloved grandchild.
- Grandpa. - Grandpa, please.
Choose the one who did their best.
He has to be careful about who he chooses,
or the race is going to get really difficult.
Grandpa, choose me. I'm the safest.
I'm nobody.
Why don't you choose whoever...
chooses the same one in rock-paper-scissors?
- I like it. Let's do that. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
(Sang Yeob, So Min, and Kwang Soo choose rock.)
- Okay! - All right.
- Wait a minute. - The same one, right?
Let's go with heads or tails this time.
- Heads or tails! - Heads or tails!
(Will it be the back of the hand or the palm of the hands?)
(They will have to choose the same one in order to get the hint.)
(Who will be the one to win the hint for the most-beloved grandchild?)
(Sang Yeob and Kwang Soo choose the back of the hand.)
Okay!
(Kwang Soo wins the hint for the most-beloved grandchild.)
(Why is Kwang Soo so happy?)
Kwang Soo, you are...
chosen as the grandparents' most-beloved grandchild.
(Kwang Soo is the most-beloved grandchild.)
I'm my grandparents' most-beloved grandchild in real life.
All right.
In order to win, you will have to hide your identity and find out...
who the fake grandchild is and eliminate them.
I will tell you two among the three fakes...
who are after the performance exemption ticket.
- Three fakes? - Yes.
There are three fakes.
They are...
A and B.
However, once you reveal it to the others,
the fakes will come after you...
because the most-beloved grandchild is the only one who knows it.
(He has to find the fakes without getting caught!)
How could you tell him the answer...
when he's the most suspicious one!
- Grandpa! - I'll give it to So Min.
(I'm going to give the hint to So Min!)
- What? - Darn it.
(What?)
- I'm sorry, but... - He's giving it to So Min.
- I don't think you'll get it. - So Min.
- He's giving it to So Min. - But I won.
- What? - Sang Yeob wants to give it to me.
- Who will you give it to? - So Min.
Then why did we play that game?
- Come on... - It's my choice.
- That's true. - We can't trust Kwang Soo.
He wants to give it to me.
I'm sorry. Give it to me. Let go.
(So Min wins the hint for the most-beloved grandchild.)
What?
It's not me.
(The most-beloved grandchild's blood type is not AB.)
What kind of hint is this?
This can't be it. It's too vague.
Mine is, too.
We will move on to the final race.
- Okay! - Yes!
(They move on to the last mission without much clue on the answer.)
I'm going to catch them, for sure.
We need more information.
You may win the couple performance exemption ticket...
on this last mission.
- Please! - The exemption ticket.
It is the Guest Room Family and the Lodger.
We have to do well in this one.
If the most-beloved grandchild...
or three of the real grandchildren get eliminated, the fakes win.
We need to be careful.
(If three of the real grandchildren get eliminated, the fakes win.)
(They cannot attack anyone without a sure clue.)
We need to protect the most-beloved grandchild.
For the real grandchildren, they will win...
if they can eliminate just one of the fake grandchildren.
Okay.
Let me tell you how you can eliminate someone.
- You each have a job, right? - Yes.
You have to find the object related to your job...
in order to find out how to eliminate someone.
However,
if the game doesn't come to the conclusion...
within the 60 minutes of the race,
the stage that reveals your identities...
will open for three minutes.
(The stage that reveals the members' identities will open!)
- A stage? - If the real grandchildren...
get on stage, the real grandchildren will win,
but if there are any fake grandchildren, the fakes will win.
I'm not sure about today.
We need more clues.
- We didn't get much. - No.
Hints are hidden around regarding the real and fake grandchildren.
(Hints are hidden around this big neighborhood.)
Also, there is...
- a guest room around here. - A guest room?
It only opens at a certain time...
and only the first three people to arrive can enter.
- Okay. - There must be something in there.
If three of the real grandchildren lay on the covers,
an affectionate lullaby will play.
If even one person is a fake,
- weird music will play, - Okay.
so you will be able to find the fake grandchild.
However, you may not use force in the guest room.
Please move on to the starting point.
- Let's go! - Okay!
(They all move to the starting point, full of suspicions.)
We barely have any hints.
(Kwang Soo, the most-beloved grandchild, knows the two fakes.)
This is so hard.
There are so many people I'm suspecting.
I can't be certain about anyone, though.
(He can't eliminate anyone without any hints!)
The race starts now!
I'll have to find the weapon, first.
(He has to find the weapon in order to eliminate the sure fakes!)
I don't see anything, not even a hint.
(Where are the hints or weapons?)
I'm going to find the fakes.
It must be somewhere around here.
(Both the fake and the real grandchildren are needing hints.)
They wouldn't make it too obvious.
Hey, who do you think it is?
I don't think it's among us three.
- Haha, I'm... - Am I right?
- I'm not it, for sure. - Right?
- Am I right? - Yes.
- I don't think you're it, either. - I'm not it. I promise.
Can you let me in on your hint? What was it?
It said, "1 female and 2 males".
- "1 female and 2 males"? - Really?
(Haha was the only one who got the hint on the fakes.)
("Fakes are 2 men and 1 woman.")
(He shares the exact hint...)
(with Se Chan and Kwang Soo!)
That seems too vague.
(He wouldn't have shared a hint on the fakes,)
(if he were a fake.)
- I think it's Jae Seok. - Jae Seok?
And So Min.
(Haha goes to look for another hint after sharing his hint.)
(He finds a hint.)
(Who will it be about?)
(The most-beloved grandchild is not a radio show host.)
(Seok Jin is not the most-beloved grandchild!)
Haha!
(Seok Jin, who has been proved not to be the most-beloved, appears!)
Did you find anything?
Come over here.
(He takes Haha to a private place...)
(and starts to look around.)
(No one is around, right?)
I'm the most-beloved grandchild.
(What nonsense!)
(Seok Jin is confused at the unexpected reaction.)
What's wrong?
You have to keep this a secret.
- Please. - Seok Jin.
You're so...
You're so hilarious today.
Why are you so funny today?
I'm the most-beloved grandchild.
(How is he so shameless?)
Hey, if you don't believe me,
just forget what I said. Forget it.
I can't trust you anymore.
Come on. Protect me.
I need someone I can rely on.
Seok Jin...
(While the fake most-beloved grandchild is spewing nonsense...)
- Kwang Soo! - Yes?
Did you find anything?
No, nothing.
When will you start finding things?
- What? - What?
- What's this? You found anything? - What are you doing, Soo Hyang?
(Soo Hyang found a weapon.)
- Why are you all here? - "Grandma"...
- How did you find this? - "Reading glasses"?
(About this weapon...)
- I found your weapon, Grandma. - Did you?
You're on our team, aren't you?
- You're on our team. - Here?
You found my weapon!
(Jong Kook found Grandma's weapon and led Soo Hyang to it!)
(Soo Hyang obtains her weapon!)
(Grandma: reading glasses)
(Now that she has her weapon...)
You will now be able to...
tear off the name tags of the other members.
I can tear off their name tags and eliminate them?
(She now has her weapon, so she's able to eliminate them!)
- Is there a hint in there? - How did you find it?
- Is it in words? - No.
You have to find your own.
Were you an unemployed person?
I told you many times that I am not a jobless man.
- Your job... - Why do you keep saying that?
- You look like a jobless man. - I will find a job soon.
Really?
I will find a job this year no matter what.
- I am on a job hunt. - You need to find the weapon...
for the long-time bar exam student.
- This is driving me crazy. - You are always...
- either a spy... - I am not a spy!
- or... - I am nothing today.
a swindler.
Soo Hyang, I will share the hint once I find...
(What?)
(He finds a hint as soon as he finishes talking.)
(What is the content of the hint Kwang Soo has found?)
(One of the fakes is a man whose birth date includes 7.)
(The grandchildren whose birth date includes 7 are...)
(Then B is either So Min or Haha!)
- Did you find anything? - No.
Then what are you putting in the bag?
What are you putting in the bag?
A man like me...
always takes notes, studies,
- and observes. - I hate taking notes.
The guest room is open.
(At that moment, the guest room opens.)
(Is the guest room opens?)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - The three of us should go.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- The three of us should go. - Okay.
- All right. - The three of us should go.
- The guest room is open. - Where is the guest room?
Where is it?
(They run towards the guest room.)
Let's hurry up before anyone gets there.
(It's a good chance to figure out the fakes.)
Where is the guest room?
There it is.
(What? It's the guest room!)
The guest room.
(They find the guest room!)
(Is this the guest room?)
(She gains information by chance.)
- The guest room. - Hold on.
We need 3 people. Oh, there are 3 of us.
The three of us...
You can't go in.
(Ji Hyo runs towards the room, but she can't enter.)
- Please. - My goodness.
No, no.
There are three people inside.
- Are there people inside? - For goodness' sake.
- Are there people inside? - The room is full.
- Let's go inside. - For goodness' sake.
What were the rules?
- If... - They are going in.
If all three of them are real grandchildren,
a lullaby will play.
This is nice.
If we hear weird music...
That will be really weird.
(If they are real grandchildren, a lullaby will play.)
- That will be chilling. - Hold on.
- Only we can hear the music, right? - That's right.
(Their hearts beat fast.)
- Grandma and two others went in. - Yes.
I bet the lullaby won't play.
Grandma is in danger.
I am sure Jae Seok and Se Chan are fakes.
Grandma will be eliminated there.
Let's hear which music plays.
(Grandma might be in danger.)
(Will there be a fake as Jong Kook predicted?)
- Grandma, sing us a lullaby. - Grandma, sing us a lullaby.
(Grandma, sing us a lullaby.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E453 Running Man
"Couple Performance"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(If all three are real family, an affectionate lullaby will play.)
(If even one person is a fake, weird music will play.)
(My goodness.)
What?
(It's not a lullaby!)
It's not a lullaby.
(One of them is a fake!)
Then one of us is a fake. Hold on. Hold on.
- Hey. - My goodness.
I can't believe you.
- My goodness. - No way.
- I can't believe you. - No way.
My goodness.
I did think you were suspicious.
Both of you were suspicious...
- from the start. - Will we be the only ones...
to know this information?
(I have to relay this information.)
It wasn't a lullaby!
(It wasn't a lullaby!)
- What? - It wasn't a lullaby!
- One of them is a fake. - It wasn't a lullaby!
We know that Grandma isn't a fake.
- Grandma isn't a fake. - Hold on.
- Okay. - Hold on.
Then one of them is a fake.
Okay.
It's either Jae Seok or Se Chan.
- I am not a fake. - This is...
- What are you doing? - Go.
Go away.
- It's 100 percent. - Go away.
(They don't know who the most-beloved grandchild is.)
Se Chan, I can't believe you.
(However, one thing is certain.)
- In any case, - Okay.
- we got... - It's one of them.
- a rough sense. - We don't know the number, right?
We don't know the number of the fakes, right?
We don't know the number.
We know that Grandma isn't a fake.
It's either one of them.
- It's either one of them... - It could be both of them.
or both of them.
(Se Chan became a strong candidate for a fake after the guest room.)
I haven't found a single hint.
How could they corner me so much...
just because I entered the guest room once?
(Is he a fake who is pretending to be upset?)
Now...
We should remove Se Chan's name tag.
(Is Jae Seok real and Se Chan fake?)
I think he is a fake. His facial expression...
It shows because he isn't a good actor.
Se Chan...
has behaved strangely from the start.
He hasn't asked us...
about the hints either.
It's strange behavior.
For goodness' sake.
(Is Se Chan a fake grandchild as everyone thinks?)
Who is the most-beloved grandchild?
(They can't eliminate Se Chan on a presumption.)
Here it is.
(At that moment, he finds a hint!)
Okay.
Here it is.
(The hint Seok Jin found is...)
(The most-beloved grandchild has appeared in a movie.)
(That means Se Chan isn't the most-beloved grandchild.)
All right.
(They can remove Se Chan's name tag now.)
We should remove Se Chan's name tag.
(Se Chan doesn't know about the new hint.)
(Seok Jin found his weapon earlier and can remove name tags.)
(To make sure that Se Chan doesn't see him,)
(Seok Jin follows Se Chan discreetly.)
(Real grandchildren win if they eliminate one fake.)
(If Se Chan is a fake, real grandchildren will win.)
(He succeeds to grab Se Chan's name tag.)
What?
(Ripping)
(He removes Se Chan's name tag!)
- Let's see it. - Seok Jin.
(Is Se Chan a fake as Seok Jin predicted?)
(Is he a real grandchild who was falsely accused?)
(What?)
- What? - Se Chan isn't a fake.
(Se Chan isn't...)
(a fake grandchild.)
- What? - He isn't a fake.
- Are you serious? - He isn't a fake.
He isn't a fake.
I told you I am not a fake!
- He isn't a fake. - It's okay.
(Did the lullaby not play in the guest room...)
(because Jae Seok is a fake grandchild?)
- For goodness' sake. - That means Jae Seok is a fake.
Jae Seok.
- It's Jae Seok. - I am 100 percent sure.
It's Jae Seok.
(Did they finally figure out the identity of a fake grandchild?)
(Then they must eliminate Jae Seok.)
- It's Jae Seok. - I can't believe it.
- I am not a fake. - It's Jae Seok.
Gosh, this is...
(He finds a hint.)
(What is the content of the hint Jae Seok found?)
(Oh!)
(He becomes shocked upon seeing the hint.)
(What could it be?)
(Did he find the hint on the most-beloved grandchild?)
(Jae Seok found his weapon earlier and can remove name tags.)
(He takes sure steps.)
I can't stop suspecting them.
Think about it.
(He succeeds to get close...)
(to Kwang Soo.)
Is it him?
(At that moment!)
(Jae Seok grabs the name tag that belongs...)
(to Ji Hyo!)
(Why is he trying to remove Ji Hyo's name tag?)
(After a fierce struggle...)
(Ripping)
(Ji Hyo, the real grandchild, is out.)
What? What is going on?
- It's not Ji Hyo. - She isn't a fake.
I told you I am not a fake.
- Ji Hyo. - It's Jae Seok.
I am 100 percent sure.
I am 100 percent sure he is a fake.
- It's Jae Seok. - Come on.
- We need to catch him! - Run!
(He rips off Ji Hyo's name tag and runs away at full speed.)
(Catch Jae Seok!)
- Hurry up! - Catch him!
The guest room is open.
(The guest room opens.)
- The guest room is open. - The guest room!
Run! Come on!
(Jae Seok runs towards the guest room.)
(Once he goes in, people can't remove his name tag.)
Come on!
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
(Right before Kwang Soo catches Jae Seok,)
(he enters the guest room.)
- Go in. - I need to go in.
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
What? What?
What is going on?
Hold on. Why did I...
- Why did I enter? - Wait.
For goodness' sake.
The guest room is full.
So Min should have entered.
I am not a fake.
Hey, why did you enter?
Kwang Soo, Jae Seok, and Sang Yeob entered.
Let's wait and see the result.
Let's not remove each other's name tag now.
What's important is that Jae Seok was in the guest room...
- earlier and now. - Okay.
- Okay. - This is driving me crazy.
It could be Jae Seok's fit of desperation.
- That's what it is, right? - We have seen that many times.
It's a fit of desperation.
This will give us a direction.
- This is driving me crazy. - I will pull the blankets.
This is driving me crazy.
(Kwang Soo is very troubled.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Grandma, sing us a lullaby. - Grandma, sing us a lullaby.
- Grandma. - Grandma.
(Is there a chance...)
(they will hear a lullaby?)
(It's not a lullaby.)
See?
(I knew it.)
(It's just as they thought.)
(Jae Seok must be a fake grandchild.)
The two of you could be fakes.
- The two of us? - Yes.
Jae Seok, I will be honest.
- Hold on. - The production crew...
wouldn't give us such important roles.
(Leave me out. I am the most-beloved grandchild.)
Jae Seok.
(It's a very important role.)
Why?
This is driving me crazy.
- My goodness. - Let's go outside.
It's not me.
Who is it?
- A man... - I think it is...
I am Grandma.
- I... - It wasn't Se Chan.
I thought it was Se Chan.
- I can't believe it. - It wasn't Se Chan.
- Then it's you. - One more thing.
- Come on out. - There is...
a reason why I removed Ji Hyo's name tag.
You...
(Kwang Soo goes back into the guest room.)
- Hey. - My goodness.
My blood pressure is rising.
(Why did Kwang Soo go back into the room?)
(It seems like he found something strange in the room.)
If it wasn't Se Chan, then you're the fake grandchild. No?
If you exclude Grandma and Grandpa...
and combine A's hints, what remains is Ji Hyo.
(If you combine A's hints, what remains is Ji Hyo.)
- Really? - That's why I eliminated Ji Hyo.
(Please believe me.)
(Jae Seok's first hint)
- I'm not a fake. - No.
(What was the hint that Jae Seok found?)
It's about A.
(It's a hint about fake A.)
(It excludes Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and So Min.)
Look at this.
(He finds his second hint.)
(It's the hint that surprised Jae Seok.)
(Fake A is an actor.)
"Fake A is an actor"?
(The second hint is related to fake A.)
(If fake A is an actor...)
Fake A is Ji Hyo then.
(That's why he eliminated Ji Hyo without any hesitation.)
(However, Ji Hyo wasn't fake A.)
(While being suspected as the fake grandchild, Jae Seok is cornered.)
I'm creeped out.
Wait.
That's why I eliminated Ji Hyo.
However, it's not Ji Hyo.
(If it's not Ji Hyo, who could be fake A?)
(Kwang Soo has been staying in the room.)
(He gets closer to a photo.)
What's this?
(Why is he looking at the photo all of a sudden?)
I know what this is.
(The photo looks strange.)
(Grandpa and Grandma were in the photo.)
(However, they look different from the photo.)
(And)
(7 grandchildren are in the photo?)
(We have 5 grandchildren. Why are there 8 of you?)
(She clearly said there are only 5 grandchildren.)
(Grandma and Grandpa are also fake.)
(The number of grandchildren that they said is different.)
(There are 3 fakes including the grandparents.)
(The 3 fakes are Grandma, Grandpa,)
(and 1 fake grandchild.)
(Who is the fake grandchild?)
However, it's not Ji Hyo.
- Why? How? - That's because...
there's Im Soo Hyang.
(Fake A must be Im Soo Hyang.)
(2 hints related to fake A)
(Strange music that was played in the room)
(Fake A is Im Soo Hyang.)
(2 fakes are finally revealed.)
2 out of 3 fakes who are after the exemption ticket are...
Im Soo Hyang and Lee Sang Yeob.
There is one fake among the grandchildren.
- The grandparents are fake. - They're fake.
Members will think that...
there are three fakes grandchildren.
(An important hint to prove 2 fakes)
They'll believe it once they see this.
(Photo that Kwang Soo found will be proof.)
(According to the hint, fakes are 1 woman and 2 men.)
(So, the fake grandchild is a man.)
- Come here, Jong Kook. - What?
(He calls Kook Soon.)
What's this?
(He shares the hint with Jong Kook.)
There are seven.
Grandma and Grandpa are fake.
(Grandma and Grandpa are fake?)
Really?
Then...
- it's not Jae Seok. - It isn't.
(Granddaughters Jae Ni and Seok Ja are not the fake ones.)
- It's not Jae Seok. - It isn't.
(The only grandson who remains)
That means...
It's So Min.
I'm not. I'm a man. I'm really not it.
I'm confused. There are two men.
(And)
It's either So Min or Haha.
(The other grandson is Haha.)
I swear.
I'm really not it.
(Which one is the fake grandchild?)
Here's what's going on.
(Fake grandpa Sang Yeob)
I think people over there mentioned my name.
Soo Hyang.
Go to the mountain.
Run away to the mountain.
(Did people find out?)
I should hide.
(At times like this,)
(hiding is the best plan.)
Gosh, Soo Hyang.
(He feels very betrayed.)
I didn't think that it'd be Soo Hyang.
(They're narrowing down who might be the fake grandchildren.)
(Haha enters the room.)
(Haha sees the photo as well.)
- That photo... - We found the photo.
(The fake grandchild is a man.)
You're on the suspect list.
Okay, you can be suspicious of me. I'm not it anyway.
- You know that you're on the list? - Yes.
Grandpa and Grandma are fake.
(Haha says that he's not the fake one. Then, who is he?)
There's nothing over there.
We shouldn't go where there's nothing.
We should go where there's something.
There's nothing.
(Which one is fake, Haha or So Min?)
Let's go.
Where did Soo Hyang go?
(Feeling betrayed, Jae Seok chases after the fake grandma.)
(She's running away from Jae Seok.)
(He approaches where she is after hearing sounds.)
Soo Hyang.
(Soo Hyang!)
(They finally come face to face.)
I didn't know it'd be you.
- Soo Hyang. - Isn't it you?
- Did you fool me? - Jae Seok.
- Isn't it you? - Did you fool me?
(She can't avoid him anymore.)
- Will you eliminate me? - You're the only one, Soo Hyang.
- Jae Seok. - Soo Hyang.
(It's a fight of who eliminates the name tag first.)
(If she takes off Jae Seok's name tag, the race is over.)
(Right then!)
(Jae Seok grabs Soo Hyang's name tag first.)
Is it Soo Hyang?
(Is it Soo Hyang's scream?)
What should I do?
(Haha moves when he hears the scream.)
(So Min spots Soo Hyang and Jae Seok first.)
So Min.
(If So Min helps Soo Hyang...)
(and eliminates Jae Seok, the race is over.)
(At that time)
(So Min runs towards Soo Hyang.)
Grab her.
(So Min helps Jae Seok.)
All right. Let's talk this out.
It's Soo Hyang.
Did you eliminate her name tag?
- Whose name tag got eliminated? - Who?
Here you go.
- Do you see it? - No.
- It's Soo Hyang. - She's the fake grandma.
(Soo Hyang is the fake grandma.)
(Fake grandma Soo Hyang is out.)
- You know what? - It's shocking.
I'm shocked.
Whose name tag is torn off?
- Soo Hyang's name tag. - Soo Hyang's.
- What? - Soo Hyang's name tag.
What was Soo Hyang?
- Isn't she fake? - Isn't she fake?
(Fake grandpa Sang Yeob is revealed.)
(They still don't know who the fake grandchild is.)
- How could you do this? - How could you?
- How could you do this? - How can you, Grandmother?
Did she get caught?
(He's still trying to understand the situation.)
(At that time)
Did she get caught?
- She got caught. - Hey.
(Haha approaches Sang Yeob.)
Unbelievable.
What?
(Haha knows what Sang Yeob is.)
What's going on?
(He attacks the fake grandpa Sang Yeob.)
- My goodness. - What's wrong?
- What's going on? - What?
(He tears it off without hesitating.)
(Sang Yeob is out.)
- What? - That's right.
- He's fake Grandpa. - Right.
- That's right. - What?
(2 fakes except one fake grandchild are out.)
(Team Grandchildren wins if the fake grandchild is out.)
He's fake Grandpa.
See? He's fake Grandpa.
(So Min helped Jae Seok eliminate Soo Hyang.)
The photo was right.
(Haha has eliminated Sang Yeob.)
(Who could be the fake grandchild?)
- Wait. - Okay.
(At that time)
(Seok Jin attacks So Min.)
- It's not me. - Wait.
- I swear it's not me. - Wait.
- Wait. - It's not me.
- Wait. - I swear it's not me.
- We'll find out when you're out. - It's not me.
- I'm pretty sure it's you. - Tear it off.
There are two left.
- I swear that it's not me. - It's not you?
- He's definitely it. - She's the one.
- It's definite. - It's 1 of the 2.
There are two men.
It's a grandson.
- It's a grandson. - It's a grandson.
- It's not a granddaughter. - Listen.
Tearing off Sang Yeob's name tag is part of his plan.
- It's clear now. - Okay.
He's fake.
- Isn't it you? - Haha is faking his identity.
- I swear to you. - It's not me.
It's 1 of the 2.
Raise your hand... Wait, wait.
I'm not the fake grandson.
- Time is up. - He's the fake one.
- I'm serious. - I swear to you.
I even eliminated Sang Yeob.
(Fake grandchild isn't revealed.)
You're good at acting.
- I approve of your acting. - You're a great actor.
- You're very good at acting. - She's the best.
- I'm learning a lot from you, Haha. - I approve.
- Seriously. - Seriously.
- My movies failed for reasons. - No.
Haha, why did you...
tear off Grandpa's name tag all of a sudden?
I had to.
I saw the photo over there.
We could have gone together, but why did you do it alone?
He was turning away from me.
- It was an opportunity. - He didn't want to be suspected.
Really?
- He didn't want to be suspected. - I'm serious.
What else could I do?
- Why don't you sound desperate? - Are you happy now?
- Why... - Do you know why?
It's because I'm real. That's why I'm not talking much.
Fake ones talk a lot.
- Like him. - If she's fake,
it'll be a big mess. Do you remember last time?
I remember. Fake ones always talk a lot.
Let me say this one last time.
I had to catch Soo Hyang...
to remove my false charge.
I did everything to chase Soo Hyang.
When I called for help,
- So Min came. - I ran over.
- She helped without hesitating. - I helped him.
It could be fake.
- That's what I don't know. - Then Haha was faking himself too.
This is driving me crazy.
In fact,
- Haha gave me all the hints. - I gave him everything.
He did...
because we didn't know about the grandparents.
It could've been a disadvantage, but he shared them.
- He was considering... - Here's what I insisted on.
I asked people to gather around if they aren't fake ones.
I was the first to arrive.
(After the second mission was over,)
(Team Grandpa won a hint.)
- I'll show it to So Min. - What?
(Fake grandpa shared his hint with So Min.)
It's strange that he didn't take initiative.
- I think it's So Min. - I swear it's not me.
(So Min is the fake one.)
- She's the fake? - So Min is a fake grandchild.
I think... Do you think I'm the fake one?
It's too confusing.
You must believe me.
I worked very hard today.
By the way,
- So Min sincerely helped me. - Did she?
- His intuition is correct. - She really did.
- I'm sincere too. - This is so difficult.
(It's confusing to find out who the fake grandchild is.)
It's time to decide.
- You go tear it off. - You tear it off.
- Go ahead. - You tear it off.
It's really not me.
(Is it So Min?)
(Or Haha?)
Go, Kwang Soo!
I don't know what to do.
I can't do it.
It's really confusing.
- I have no idea. - I have no idea either.
Let's just do it.
(Team Fake wins if a real grandchild is out.)
One.
(Who is the fake grandchild?)
Two.
(Is it So Min who finds it unfair?)
(Is it Haha who plays innocent?)
Three.
(What's the result of the race?)
(Tearing)
(Haha is picked as the fake grandson.)
(If Haha is a real grandson,)
(Team Fake wins.)
(What is Haha?)
- Okay! - See?
See? I'm not fake.
(Fake grandson Haha is out.)
(The real grandchildren are the final winners.)
I told you that I wasn't it.
- See? I'm not fake. - I was right.
- I really am not. - I told you.
- It wasn't So Min. - Good job.
(We could have won.)
(Today morning before the shoot)
- Hello. - Hello, hello.
Both of you will be assisting Haha who is a fake grandchild.
You'll pretend to be grandparents...
who aren't back from their trip.
You'll play fake grandparents.
A grandpa?
My goodness. Is this what I should do?
Two of them are too positive.
(They were determined to win by acting passionately.)
Haha is picked to participate in the couple performance.
He has to pick one of you.
(He must pick from real grandchildren.)
(Only 1 paper has X written on it among 7 papers.)
If you pick the one that has X written on it, you'll join...
(What?)
- Wait. - That's wrong.
- What? - That's not right.
What's that?
- Everyone, calm down. - Could it be me when...
I'm the most-beloved?
It's a big picture of the crew.
It's a big picture.
Whoever it turns out to be,
he or she has to perform with Haha.
Let's open it as soon as you pick one.
Yes, open it as soon as you pick.
I'm nervous.
Here you go.
- Do it in the count of three. - It has X written on it.
- "X"? His might be the one. - What if his has X on it?
(Kwang Soo passes.)
Okay.
(He reacts out of joy.)
It's a lot of pressure.
Three.
(Seok Jin passes as well.)
(I didn't want Seok Jin either.)
2, 3.
(So Min also passes.)
- Among the rest of you! - Good job.
I know you were sad today.
I wasn't picked.
Let's have one each.
- I'll give you without looking. - Okay.
I don't know.
Jong Kook.
- Why did you give it to me first? - I don't know what's in it.
(They're very sensitive.)
- Why did you give it to me first? - All right.
- One. - Wait.
Please.
- 1, 2, 3. - It can be anyone.
(Who will do...)
(a couple performance with Haha?)
(Jae Seok is picked.)
(Welcome, Jae Seok.)
(Haha's partner is Jae Seok.)
I knew it would be him.
That's amazing.
This is great.
Thank you.
(We hope to see an amazing performance.)
It'll be great with Haha.
The couple performance will be...
done by...
- Jae Seok and Haha. - Yes.
Let's end it with the water bomb.
- Today, Sang Yeob and... - They worked very hard.
Soo Hyang worked very hard.
(You worked hard today.)
I tried my best not to make Haha dance.
- We'll come to your performance. - We'll come to your performance.
Water will fall in the count of three.
1, 2, 3.
(Splashing)
That was a lot of water.
(We thank Lee Sang Yeob and Im Soo Hyang for joining us today.)
Thank you.
- That was amazing. - Thank you.
(The Devil Wears Running Shirts.)
(Running shirts for the fan-meet are presented.)
(Running Man members design the shirts for their fans.)
(8 members' charms are printed on white shirts.)
(However,)
(8 unidentifiable shirts are presented at the same time.)
(Finally,)
(the race to become a designer starts.)
(Their undying passion for their design)
(Members become extremely passionate.)
(The process is dirty.)
(The result will be full of love.)
(Who will win the right to design?)
(The Devil Wears Running Shirts.)