- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hi.
Hello.
(What?)
- Hi. - Hello.
Right. This will air after the fan-meet.
(A cheerful greeting with the group choreography)
- Stop it. - This feels like ages ago.
Stop it.
Hello.
(Hello!)
- Hello. - It's from ancient times.
- Hello. - Stop that.
(The excitement still lingers on.)
It's from ancient times. "Ancient times".
That feels like ages ago.
- Hello. - My gosh.
- Hi. - Hi.
So Min,
you're not in a good mood today, right?
- No. - Really?
- She seems different than usual. - No.
- No, no. - You seem different than usual.
Seok Jin couldn't get a wink of sleep last night...
because of his first love.
(You're the one who seems different than usual.)
What are you talking about?
That's what you told me as soon as you got here.
Hey, stop making stuff up.
- I definitely heard it. - Stop making stuff up.
- He's a viper. - That was so mean.
Stop making stuff up.
- He's a viper. - You said you were tired.
No, that's not true.
"I couldn't sleep because of my first love."
No, no. I was looking at my yearbook.
- Yearbook? - I was looking at my yearbook.
- When you were in school? - I thought about my teacher...
- and my friends. - You thought about your friends.
- What's your teacher's name? - Pardon?
What's your teacher's name?
Just take care of your teacher.
(Just take care of your teacher.)
"Your teacher"?
- Why did you say it so rudely? - Why are you getting angry?
- I mean... - Why were you so rude?
- Show some respect. - Take care of your dear teacher.
(He's speechless.)
Ji Hyo, do join us after getting rid of the sleep in your eyes.
(Ji Hyo is the easiest target.)
(Why did he speak like that?)
- You keep... - "Do join us"?
(I get that you're flustered, but...)
"Do join us."
"Do start the filming."
He talks as if he's giving out missions.
He might say to his wife, "Do kiss me."
(Do kiss me.)
"All right, my family. Do eat."
- "Do fix me a meal." - "Everyone, do go to work."
"All right. Do have..."
"a meal today."
(He's in a tight spot due to his mistake.)
That's a nice way of speaking.
By the way,
after the fan-meet, we were going to grab a meal together.
- Seok Jin called everyone. - Right.
- Ji Hyo, - A few of us did.
- We went to a nice restaurant. - Se Chan and Haha couldn't come...
- because of work. - Right.
- The five of us had dinner. - That's right.
- We had a nice meal thanks to him. - We had beef.
- Thank you for the meal. - It was a classy restaurant.
- It was a classy restaurant. - It was a barbecue restaurant.
At the end of our meal,
- I thought the beef was so tasty. - Right. Yes, it was.
So I suggested taking some of the beef home.
- He suggested taking new sets. - Jong Kook lives alone and all.
- Right. It was so nice. - I suggested buying a few sets.
But someone was scowling at me.
- I was really surprised. - Right? You saw him too.
Seok Jin was scowling at me.
Do stop!
(Do stop!)
Do stop taking beef home.
- I said I would buy the beef. - Right.
He said, "Okay, then."
(He agreed quickly.)
"Okay, then."
So when we were saying goodbye, we said to Jae Seok,
"Jae Seok, thank you for the food."
- "Thank you, Jae Seok." - But Seok Jin paid for the meal.
We thanked him at the end.
- That's the power of packed beef. - Seok Jin...
- Seok Jin bought us the meal. - Packed beef...
- He stole my thunder. - I stole his thunder.
When I got home,
I only felt grateful toward Jae Seok.
- You should've paid for everything. - My goodness.
- You're so sly. - Listen.
- This is so funny. - No, he's warmhearted.
Everyone thanked him for the food.
And Seok Jin was holding the beef and said, "Jae Seok..."
(And Seok Jin was holding the beef and said, "Jae Seok...")
Come on, Seok Jin.
Where is your pride?
- Really? - You took some too?
- You did? He bought you food. - Yes, I took some beef home too.
- "Jae Seok, thank you for this." - Right.
He left after saying that.
That's why it felt weird for us too.
Why do you look so restless?
(Seok Jin bought the 1st round. And Jae Seok bought the 2nd round.)
- The fan-meet is over now. - Yes.
How do you feel?
It's over now. My gosh.
That day, I was in a daze.
He told me that he felt so wronged...
- because he couldn't cry that day. - I'm serious. That day...
He told me that he wanted to cry just like Ji Hyo.
I was right next to Seok Jin.
As soon as Ji Hyo started to cry,
he said, "Okay, Ji Hyo took it."
("Okay, Ji Hyo took it.")
"Ji Hyo took everything."
After hearing that, I got the chills.
(After the group choreography, she was overwhelmed with emotions...)
(and ended up genuinely crying.)
(Seok Jin was watching this.)
("Ji Hyo took it.")
(He got the chills.)
By the way, like we talked about earlier,
- she was overwhelmed with emotions. - Right.
- She's very sentimental. - Well, she is...
Ji Hyo said this to me on stage.
"Kwang Soo, what should I do? Help me out here."
I said, "Think about how we'll drink later." And her face...
(Smiling)
- I'm serious. It only took seconds. - Really?
(Kwang Soo, do something.)
(Think about how we'll drink later.)
(Smiling brightly)
(A team dinner makes even crying Ji Hyo smile.)
Everyone, for about 100 days,
you've been working so hard to prepare for the fan-meet.
(We had to work really hard, but it was rewarding.)
To reward your hard work,
we've prepared a relaxing vacation.
It's You're All That Matters: Vacation Race.
- This is a bonus episode. - A vacation?
We've prepared a lot of various activities for the vacation.
Please bring in the board.
(All that matters is that you like it. Vacation Keywords)
- "Joo Jin Mo"? - What's "Date with Joo Jin Mo"?
Joo Jin Mo will be on our show?
- "Date with the Stars". - "Date with the Stars".
I want to go on a date with stars.
- "Concert". - Please!
- Another one? - All right.
Among these eight activities,
you will draw three activities and enjoy them.
(All that matters is that you like it. Vacation Keywords)
You will each choose one activity.
And the members who chose the selected activity...
will become the hosts of the activity.
The members will be in charge of the selected activity.
- Is that so? - The hosts do whatever they want.
On the next board, you can see the possible outcomes.
At the end of each activity,
seven members excluding the host...
will vote between "satisfied" or "dissatisfied".
- My goodness. - We have to satisfy the members.
Will that be possible?
- My gosh, that's hard. - It's hard to satisfy everyone.
"If everyone is dissatisfied, the host..."
"and the member of the host's choice will get two penalty badges."
It will be advantageous for you to choose an activity...
that will satisfy the members the most.
At the end of your vacation, the member with the most badges...
will draw an activity among remaining activities...
and carry it out alone instead of going home as a penalty.
- Alone? - Yes.
- Alone? - We can't even choose someone?
I already chose one.
Hold on. Why don't we each choose an activity?
- I... - Who wants to go for the third one?
- Me. I want "Lovely Jam". - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Me too. - "Lovely Jam".
Rock-paper-scissors
(Suddenly joining)
- Okay. - Okay. I won too.
- Why did you join at the end? - I won too.
Rock-paper-scissors
(All of a sudden, Jae Seok participates too.)
- Why did you join at the end? - I won too.
- He did play with us. - I won too.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin wins.)
- Okay. I got "Lovely Jam". - What about the fourth one?
I'll go for "Date with Joo Jin Mo".
You can try out twice?
I get the feeling that Joo Jin Mo won't be joining us.
- Is it Lim Chin Mo? - You know?
Well, if it's a date with him...
But there are two celebrities with the name, Joo Jin Mo.
- The young actor? - There's the young actor.
- And Jjakgwi is Joo Jin Mo too. - Right. That's his name too.
- Stop promoting the movie. - No, I'm not promoting it.
(Why bring up Jjakgwi here?)
No, I'm not promoting it. I'm not doing that.
- No. No, I'm not. - You're not promoting it?
Good luck, "Cheer up, Mr. Lee".
What?
It'd be great if both movies are successful.
- Yes, it'd be great. - Exactly.
- You met Cha Seung Won, right? - That's right.
It'd be great if both movies are successful.
- That'd be great for everyone. - Right.
- Jae Seok will be the host then. - Am I the only one?
- I'll go for it too. - Okay.
- Me too. - Rock...
You don't even know what it is.
Why are you here?
I'm sorry.
(The group choreography has become a part of his life.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo is out.)
Okay!
He got the date with Joo Jin Mo.
"Tag" is mine.
(Jae Seok tries out for "Tag".)
I'll go for "Snowfields".
- "Snowfields"? - Yes.
I'll go for that too.
What?
- Why are you changing your mind? - Let's do this.
- Why... - "Snowfields".
- You said... - "Snowfields".
- He's a fighter. - Rock-paper-scissors
Okay. Go back to your spot.
Rock-paper-scissors. Okay. Go back to your spot.
(Sighing)
(What is wrong with this guy?)
It's mine.
(Vacation Keywords)
Ji Hyo got "Tag", and Se Chan got "Date with the Stars".
Poor you, Se Chan. You need to invite a celebrity.
You know a lot of celebrities. Your brother is one too.
- Se Hyeong is like a small fry. - A small fry?
(Se Hyeong is like a small fry.)
He's a small fry.
- He's acceptable though. - Okay.
I'll explain each vacation activity.
As for the board game,
you can enjoy this activity regardless of the weather...
by using your strong lower body and agility.
- It's an indoor surfing activity. - I knew it.
- It's a board game with surfing. - Surfing?
And as for the second vacation activity, "Date with Joo Jin Mo"...
- I'm curious about that. - What's that?
At the "zoo",
you'll enjoy your vacation while communicating...
with the animals like their "real mothers".
- What? - Real animals?
What kind of animals are they?
I find small animals cute, but I'm scared of big animals.
Gosh, it'd be hard to satisfy us with that activity.
Gosh, I don't think I could do it.
(He's already scared.)
- He's scared of animals. - What is it?
- I don't think I can. - Or we can...
- What about "Lovely Jam"? - As for "Lovely Jam"...
- What is it? - What's that?
You'll harvest lovely peanuts from a peanut field...
and make jam out of the harvested peanuts.
- That sounds hard. - We can experience the process.
- We're going to make peanut butter. - Right. It could be hard.
As for the fourth one, "Abundant Meal",
- This one is Jong Kook. - This may be a bit unfamiliar.
This has twice the protein than beef.
And this is very nutritious and healthy.
You must eat cookies and pizza made of insects.
(You must eat cookies and pizza made of insects.)
(The edible insects are abundant in protein, nutrition, and minerals.)
We're going to eat that?
(This is the best activity for these exhausted members.)
Ji Hyo won't like it at all.
This is the worst.
(Are you sure this is a vacation?)
- We're going to eat that? - I like grasshoppers...
- Or crickets. - and I eat a lot of them.
As for the "Concert",
you will harvest corn from a field...
and put them on the tray.
This one is the best.
You can harvest corns.
- This is good. - Corns?
- The sixth one is "Snowfields". - That's mine.
As for the snowfields,
you'll collect salt in a salt pond.
(Collect salt in a salt pond.)
- My gosh, this is really hard. - Let's not choose that one.
(It's the worst of the worst.)
Let's not do that one. Salt pond...
Salt pond?
(They can collect salt while walking on the snowfields.)
- Salt pond? - Seriously?
We'll get there at night.
- But... - If this is selected,
you must try your best to satisfy the members.
- When will we get there? - Exactly.
- As for the seventh activity, - Okay.
you will go on a date with lobsters at an indoor fishing site.
- I see. - This is...
- Lucky him. - This one is nice.
- The seventh sounds pretty good. - I've gone to one...
- a long time ago. - I should've picked that one.
Going there was a penalty.
Why did I choose the snowfields?
- This is the last activity, "Tag". - Okay.
The best game of tags is Freeze Tag.
You'll carry frozen food in a cold storage at minus 20℃.
- Gosh. - You'll be able to experience that.
Who will be it?
- How could we satisfy anyone? - How can we rest?
If you work me like this, I might collapse.
(Listen to me.)
Don't you know how hard I work these days?
- He's right. - I'm supposed to work here too?
- Jae Seok's always working. - My goodness.
I'm working everywhere these days.
How many jobs does he have?
- Hey. - He's a worker.
Take shows that are easy to do.
(He gives Jae Seok advice.)
Easy shows?
- Pick those shows. - The ones filmed at studios?
- Just chat in the studios. - Hey.
You won't be able to buy tenderloin at that rate.
What do you mean?
(He should work hard and buy meat once again.)
We'll pick the first place.
- "Lovely Jam" is the best. - Then...
- Right. - The "Snowfields" one is the worst.
- Pick "Lovely Jam". - Pick number five.
- Pick the lobster one. - Let's fish.
- Let's fish. - That's good.
- That would be great. - That one's nice too.
- I'd love that. - I've never fished lobsters before.
(Se Chan wishes for "Date with the Stars".)
- What is that? - Pick one.
(He picks one.)
What is that?
(Which one will be their 1st vacation activity?)
"Lovely Jam".
(He picks "Lovely Jam".)
That's not bad.
Gosh.
- But it feels like... - We'll be making jam.
Seok Jin will be the host of "Lovely Jam".
- Let us go. - I hope you will be able...
to satisfy the members.
I'm worried about that.
He's not generous enough to be a host.
I'm serious.
Look at how he acted back at the barbecue restaurant.
- At the barbecue restaurant? - I will make you all happy.
- All right, let's go. - I'm serious.
You're not the generous type. I mean it.
- I'll... - He's just warmhearted.
- If you have sore legs, - He's not generous.
- I can carry you. - Really?
- Yes. I can carry one of you. - My back hurts.
- Carry me. - I can do it.
- I'm the lightest. - Darn it.
(He shares his innermost feelings.)
- Did you say, "Darn it"? - No, I didn't.
All right, let's go.
Let's get going now.
Are you taking me to the car?
I'm fine as long as you're content.
Okay. Thank you.
Hold on.
Thank you.
Please carry me from here.
- Seok Jin. - He wants you to carry him again.
- Hey! - You need to satisfy us.
I'm here!
- You need to satisfy him. - Please do.
(To keep Jae Seok happy, he carries him once again.)
You said you'd carry him.
Right, he did say that.
Why are your legs so thick?
- He's in for some trouble today. - Thank you.
- Here. - Thank you.
- That's enough. - Thank you.
(He makes sure his customer stays satisfied...)
(by blocking the entrance.)
- All right. - He'll be struggling today.
(They depart for the peanut fields.)
I love eating bread with peanut butter.
- Me too. - You also need...
- to apply jam. - And milk too.
- And strawberry jam. - You'll get thirsty.
As the host of "Sweet Jam"...
- It's "Lovely Jam". - It's "Lovely Jam".
(It's "Lovely Jam"!)
- Right. - It's "Lovely Jam".
What is this?
As the host of "Lovely Jam"...
Did you get it confused with that game?
That's a game I used to play when I was little.
I wasn't talking about that.
- You're so boring! - What?
- He's so boring! - He's extremely boring!
- He's extremely boring! - I knew it!
Anyway, I used to play that game when I was little.
- Goodness. - Anyway...
- He's so calm. - He is.
As long as you're satisfied...
- You're terrible. - What?
(You're terrible.)
You're terrible.
- He's terrible. - Are you talking about jeans?
- Right. - Right.
I see. You startled me.
- I have a question. - Okay.
- Do you... - Wait, let me go first.
(Jae Seok suddenly cuts Kwang Soo off.)
- Do you... - Why did you cut me off?
I was talking, you know?
- Look here. - You cut me off.
- Goodness. - It's okay for you to argue.
But you should listen to my introduction to this activity.
Then give me three dollars.
I'll wire you three dollars later.
- Really? - Yes.
I'll send it through ARS.
- ARS? - Is that right?
I'd like 30 dollars then.
- 30 dollars? - Yes, 30 dollars.
- Why 30 dollars? - Why?
I just want 30 dollars.
- All right, I'll wire it to you. - That's enough.
- To my account? - Yes.
- Make sure you give it to me. - Give me your account number.
- All right. - He won't give it right now.
- It's too far. - The service is awful.
Well...
- He said the service was awful. - That was funny.
You're the awful one.
- He is. - Anyway,
I've been doing this...
- for 26 years now. - Really?
I've never had such lovely guests before.
- Did you start in your 50s? - What?
(Did you start in your 50s?)
(He was a celebrity until he was 54.)
- All right. - How old is he?
- How old is he? - Okay.
- In four years... - He retired.
I'll turn 80 in 4 years.
I'm your host for today's "Sweet Jam".
- It's "Lovely Jam". - Right.
- Wait. Are you married? - Yes?
- Not yet. - Not yet?
(You're 76 years old.)
- What do you mean? - Why are you lying?
Why are you lying?
- What's wrong with you? - How could you lie?
- I haven't gotten married yet. - Goodness.
- It'll be Chuseok in three days. - You're right.
Please come cook some pancakes for our family.
- Promise him right now. - Promise him.
- Please cook for me too. - Please answer us.
- He's being battered. - Hold on.
Hold on.
I'm not cut out to be a host.
It's rising inside of me.
So what will you do?
Gosh.
- My happiness is rising. - Your happiness?
- After listening to you guys, - Watch what you say.
I'm becoming happier.
I want to do more for you.
- That's good. - That's how I feel.
- It's best not to become the host. - Exactly.
It's slavery.
(He's tattered.)
This is it.
We're here.
It's a great day to pick the peanuts.
You have arrived at your first vacation activity.
- Let me explain the hidden rule. - There's a hidden rule?
Every activity has a hidden mission.
(Every activity has a hidden mission.)
The mission will be delivered to everyone except the host.
There are missions.
Until the end of each activity, you'll acquire one more vote...
if you succeed in the missions.
(They'll receive one more vote if they pass the hidden missions.)
However, if the host finds out what the hidden missions are,
your extra votes will be void.
The host needs to...
- He can't guess it. - I will get it.
- He shouldn't find out. - No.
- Our votes will disappear. - There's no need to be nice.
(He doesn't need to act nicely.)
- I just need to find it out. - No.
- Okay, bring it on. - All right.
- Bring it on. - I was in agony for 30 minutes.
Only the additional votes will be void.
- Right. - We'll still have the originals.
- I won't forget what you just said. - It's 1 versus 7.
I'll wire you the 30 dollars.
- I'll give it to you. - It's 90 dollars now.
- It increased threefold. - Goodness.
- It increased threefold. - It skyrocketed immediately.
Thirty dollars is difficult since I sell jam to make ends meet.
Will the host leave the car?
Okay. Just me?
Seok Jin's leaving? How sad.
Goodness.
- That's so sad. - Let him leave.
Good work thus far.
- Good work. - Good job.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
Go home safely.
- I'll be leaving alone. - Okay.
All right.
Bye.
- He looks so pitiful. - This is sad.
(The host leaves the car.)
It's so hot. This isn't good.
Your first hidden mission...
is stealing the host's belongings.
- This is easy. - This is hard.
- He doesn't have many. - No, he doesn't.
They could be items he used such as water bottles or sacks.
Anything works.
- It'll be obvious if we all do it. - We need to do something.
We need to distract him.
Hey.
(Kwang Soo picks up Seok Jin's water bottle.)
- Not yet. We haven't begun. - Hey.
My gosh.
- He unbuckled his belt. - Why are you drinking that?
That's So Min's now.
- We need to distract him midway. - Right.
It'll be difficult to take anything that he's carrying.
Let's confuse him by pretending like there are two missions.
Or Jong Kook could knock him out...
and strip him naked.
- That's the easiest way. - Hey.
- How could you say that? - We can take his pants off.
I think he has seven different items on him right now.
Shall we get out?
Let's go.
This way!
It's scorching hot.
(It's very hot out.)
It's going to be hot.
This feels ominous.
The ground is muddy too. Seriously.
It's the worst.
- It's scorching hot. - My gosh.
The ground is steaming.
Everyone.
It's so muddy. My gosh.
(It rained the day before.)
I'm wearing white shoes.
This isn't good.
- I didn't wear sunscreen. - This way.
My goodness.
This is "Lovely Jam", your first vacation activity.
During this activity,
you'll be picking peanuts and making peanut butter.
You need to pick 5kg each.
- That's a lot. - It is.
The activity will end once you fulfill your quota.
The host and the member the host will pick...
will make peanut butter and share it with the group.
- Okay. - Shall we go?
- Let's go. - Is this supposed to be fun?
Over here.
Please come this way.
(Mumbling)
- We shouldn't get caught. - You're right.
We'll be secretive.
- We should be secretive. - We can't get caught.
No, we can't.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
[VIU Ver] SBS E470 Running Man
"You're All That Matters: Vacation Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Let's go.
(Everyone is keeping Seok Jin in check.)
- What? - Why did you touch my name tag?
Your face will get burned.
(It's time.)
What's the mission? Why are you touching me?
Kwang Soo.
Yes? What is it?
- Come here. - I left my hat in the car.
I'll get it for you.
(Don't do this to me.)
I need my hat.
- Don't touch me. - Something's poking out.
(They head to the peanut fields.)
I've never been to a peanut field before.
(These two make a U-turn.)
(They refuse to give up.)
(They each steal a shoe insole.)
(They succeed.)
(Once the staff approves, they will gain a vote each.)
I'm already getting irritated.
- I'm already feeling dissatisfied. - Gosh.
Take your gloves.
- Listen up. - Those who are dissatisfied,
- take your gloves. - I know...
it'll be tough, but harvesting can make you happy.
I'm flabbergasted by this idea of yours.
You can feel happy while harvesting.
I'm so dumbfounded.
(Director, take the insole for me.)
- Lowering my pants? - What?
- It's nothing. - Hold on.
What's that?
- Hold on. - What's that?
- What is it? - Is there a restroom?
Jae Seok, don't make it look obvious.
What's wrong, Jae Seok?
- I want to go to the restroom. - What now?
Why is your butt sticking out?
(Are you kidding me?)
- It's just my mic. - Come and get your garden hoe.
- Shall we? - Over here.
Seok Jin, you're supposed to host this activity.
Tell us what we should do.
Come on, Seok Jin. You're supposed to take the lead.
Do better. Get it? Do better.
Here.
- Unbelievable. - It fell off.
It fell off.
(He manages to deliver the shoe insole.)
You're all acting weird. Let's go then.
- Do we just dig them out? - Yes, just dig them out.
Can you show us first?
- Sure, let me show you. - Great.
All of these are peanuts.
- Right. - Over here!
The owner is over there.
- Right. - Over here.
It's the owner of the field.
So this is how you harvest peanuts.
(Perfect timing)
Right.
Dig with a garden hoe...
on each side.
Here it comes!
Like this.
- Look at the peanuts. - Check these out.
These are peanuts.
Then, you pluck each of them off.
- Got it. - That's done by hand.
Okay!
("Countryside Diary" with Seok Jin and the kids)
- My gosh. - Let me help.
Right.
Why are you helping me though?
Take another.
Why are you suddenly helping me?
These need to be picked off by hand.
Why trouble yourself with frivolous tasks?
My gosh, look at how big these are.
You're right. They're huge.
One would at least have 500g of peanuts.
We'll pick 5kg in no time.
I feel bad picking off ones that are too small.
I know, right?
You must even pick the small ones.
(Says the owner)
- Really? - Even the tiny ones?
- That's right. - Even ones like Haha?
- Of course. - Yes.
Even Haha is a valuable member of society.
This one is like Haha.
Do we throw it away?
- This is Haha. - It's adorable.
- Haha, look. - I mean it in a different way,
but this is how Jae Seok is.
(That's weirdly upsetting.)
(Confessions are thrown while at the peanut field.)
My dream guy from now on is a peanut.
- Why? - They're adorable.
- Your dream guy? - That'll change.
In what way?
- What? - Stop giving it a meaning!
Just keep harvesting.
- I'm just short, right? - I can't believe So Min.
You might think that they're just small,
but they come in bundles.
So Min, do you want me to set you up with someone?
- Who? - I've been eyeing someone.
- So Min's quite charming, you know. - She does.
- Fools. - Of course, she's charming.
"Fools"?
She keeps growing on you.
- That's right. - Jong Kook didn't know at first.
(Jong Kook didn't know at first.)
He didn't.
I just thought she was a weirdo.
Jong Kook would deliberately avoid So Min.
(They now know how charming she is.)
You guys...
I've gotten the hang of it now.
Guys, after you harvest it, shake off the dirt.
(Shaking)
You're getting dirt everywhere!
Also, can you stop talking and work harder?
I always work hard.
We're busy as it is, so why must we work more?
You know,
I'm doing too much labor on TV shows lately.
Isn't this a show on tvN?
No.
I'm doing too much manual labor lately.
The joy of harvest.
(The joy of harvest)
This is the season of harvesting.
We don't have time for that. Keep plucking!
- Hurry up. - Go to tvN instead then.
- What? - Why do that here?
- What do you mean, "Go to tvN"? - My gosh.
- Hey. - Was that really necessary?
You're on a tvN show too though.
But I don't mention it here.
Must you be that way when we're paid by the same person?
If you want, I'll pick them for you.
Here!
Can you help me too?
- With what? - My son's tooth.
Your son's tooth?
Yes, his baby teeth have been falling out.
- Well... - Seok Jin!
- Yes? - Can you dig me out?
(What?)
(He's burying himself.)
Dig me out.
When did you get in there?
I was planted.
- How? - It happened...
while harvesting the peanuts.
- That's kind of you. - You're good at that.
- I can pluck out anything. - Seok Jin?
Can you help my son get elected as class president?
My gosh.
Not everything is possible.
Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
Wear this.
Why are you looking out for me?
- This isn't like you. - Everyone will get one.
- Here. - I don't want it.
I'll take it then!
(He's trying to ruin Kwang Soo's plan.)
- Why you? - Give it to me!
Seok Jin, why won't you take it?
Kwang Soo, go ahead.
That's not how you wear it.
It's the other way around.
(Kwang Soo isn't a fool.)
Is this it?
It's nice!
Isn't it comfortable?
It's what I harvested.
Can someone wipe my eyes?
- Why? - Who wants to join me?
This much is only 1.5kg.
- 1.5kg. - Really?
5kg is more than I initially thought.
- This isn't an easy task. - Tell me about it.
This is exhausting.
- How can you say that? - How can the host say that?
I...
Give me 90 dollars!
(What is this?)
- I want ice cream. - I want coffee.
Get us coffee and ice cream.
- I'd like shaved ice. - It's hot out here.
You can get some if you win first place.
- First place? - Yes.
Must we compete even on a vacation?
(He quickly accepts the complaint.)
I take it back then.
(Seok Jin is pitiful.)
Shouldn't you go to make the peanut butter?
That I should.
- You need a partner. - Choose a partner.
Who wants to come with me?
- Me. - Me.
Me!
I'll take whoever promises...
- to be satisfied. - How can we not be?
If you don't say you're satisfied,
your future projects will never do well.
- Must you say that? - That's fine with me,
so choose me.
Do you promise to be satisfied with my tour?
- Yes, I will. - Unbelievable.
- Over here. - Okay, I choose So Min.
- You promised to be satisfied. - Of course!
- You're going too? - Yes.
Is it good to go?
Of course. It means you're off harvesting duty.
But this...
You're making us work instead?
No matter how I think about it...
- I'm unsatisfied. - How can he do this?
I'm unsatisfied too.
- Everybody! - When will we get our ice cream?
I'll bring your ice cream soon.
Calling this an experience is a joke.
- Exactly. - Where can I buy ice cream?
Will you settle with one satisfied person?
Let's just throw a fit.
Okay, hold on. I'll get you your ice cream.
- I will. - Bring it to us now.
- I... - This isn't 5kg.
Who hasn't worked here before, right?
Forget about it.
Whatever!
(Forget about it. Whatever!)
- "Whatever"? - Forget it!
Be unsatisfied if you want.
(Seok Jin explodes.)
- Okay. - Do whatever you want.
- What's wrong with him? - I'm annoyed too.
- I can't take this anymore. - What is this?
Be unsatisfied and see if I care.
What's wrong with him?
Do as you please!
- Mister! - Mister?
(What?)
What did you just call me?
- Are you insane? - Do as you please.
- What's with Mr. Big Nose? - Whatever.
(The Strife of Big Nose)
- What's with Mr. Big Nose? - Let's go and make peanut butter.
Let's go. At least So Min will be satisfied.
- Of course. - Why didn't you throw it at me?
He's pretending to not have seen you.
You didn't say anything when it really mattered though.
He was able to hold his anger towards you.
(They check the weight again after the commotion.)
I've reached 5kg.
- What are you doing? - Seriously?
I can't believe you pressed down the scale.
- Gosh. - We'll switch it to 3kg.
Good.
I think that we have a peanut thief.
I had a lot in my sack,
but it's been cut down to half. Who took mine?
(Wanted: Peanut Thief)
The truth will come out once we see the video.
Who was it?
(Rewinding tape)
(Mr. Yu seems suspicious.)
(In the commotion, he steals the peanuts.)
(A fistful)
Who was it?
Figure it out yourself.
It was you!
(Busted!)
(He's embarrassed.)
- No way. - Gosh.
Why would I steal them?
Are you the peanut thief?
Look.
It's true that peanuts can identify peanuts.
All right, everyone!
- Mister. - We'll collect...
- what you harvested and... - We're in the middle of a sketch.
- Please butt out. - Hey.
Go and make the peanut butter already.
(Why you...)
Sir, let's go.
- Promise? - Yes.
So Min, good luck on the hidden mission.
We'll go and make the peanut butter.
Kwang Soo, can you help him take this off?
(It's time to steal the host's belonging.)
No, let me.
(It's an opportunity!)
(They run over for an easy score.)
Is it your mission to help me?
(Crowded)
He's not as tactless as he used to be.
Let's go then.
(Haha stole Seok Jin's small name tag.)
(He discreetly hands it in.)
(Haha and Se Chan have won a vote too.)
Look at these peanuts.
(This is a chance to steal another one.)
(It's mine!)
What are you guys doing?
- Who helped him? - Okay, I got it.
- I did. - I helped him too.
- So you're supposed to help me. - Just one.
Helping me is your hidden mission.
You should leave the peanuts.
That's one hilarious mission, right?
How does that even make any sense?
I think we should make him believe it.
Hold on...
Thank you for choosing me.
Oh, right. Gosh, it's hot.
(White bread and crackers go well with jam.)
There's bread. No way.
I see sweet potatoes too.
Thank you.
They must grow sweet potatoes here as well. This is nice.
The field we saw earlier was a sweet potatoes field.
- The one we saw first? - Yes.
- The flat one. - It's warm.
- Have you not seen this done? - Of course.
Look how I'm doing it.
(Picking one up)
Don't eat that.
(Don't just sit there and eat.)
It's fascinating.
(Roast the peanuts in a frying pan.)
- We need to roast them. - Place them in a blender...
- with salt. - And add olive oil.
- Honey is needed too. - That's it?
- Is it this simple? - That's how you make peanut butter.
(She mixes it well to look like she's helping him.)
(How does it taste?)
How does it taste?
- It tastes good. - It's very easy to make.
It tastes really good. It tastes just like peanut butter.
It tastes the same.
(So Min is pretending to help Seok Jin.)
Jae Seok has so much.
Guys, work hard.
- I think we should hurry up. - 3kg...
(It's like they're shooting "Field Experience of Life".)
I'm only halfway through now.
(They're working hard to dig up 3kg of peanuts.)
(Jae Seok approaches the staff.)
Can I buy some of that?
(It's a 5kg sample bag of peanuts.)
Can't I?
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing? - He stole my peanuts for real.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors for peanuts.
Okay?
Let's do this.
We'll each bet some of our peanuts.
- If you win, you get as much. - Okay.
- You make an investment. - Get as much as you invested.
- I have 1.5kg now. - Okay.
- I'll bet all I have. - All in?
(The ants)
I think this will be faster.
(The grasshoppers)
Hey, stop!
You're like One Eyed Jack.
Thanks. Hey.
You're so reckless.
Are you betting your life on this?
- I'm going all-in. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo goes all-in.)
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Okay!
Shouldn't Kwang Soo play Lee Kwang Soo Game?
(Shouldn't Kwang Soo play Lee Kwang Soo Game?)
He's right.
Play, "Jjam or ppong? 1, 2, 3."
- It's Kwang Soo. - Right.
Rock-paper-scissors is no fun.
- He has no sense of responsibility. - Exactly.
- Gosh. - Seriously.
Shall we play Lee Kwang Soo Game then?
What's wrong with you?
Do you have no sense of ownership?
- I'll go first. - You?
- I'm betting all I have. - You're betting 1.5kg.
Somebody told me...
to bet my life.
- Haha. - Who?
One Eyed Jack.
(You're the best.)
- Here we go. - Here we go.
You only get one shot at life. I go all-in.
Then it's either "shot" or "life."
- Okay. - "Shot" or "life".
1, 2, 3.
- Life! - Life!
Nice!
(Haha loses all he has.)
Why did you bet your life on that?
(There's another person who is betting his life.)
You fool.
Do "Tazza".
- Let's do "Tazza". - "Tazza".
It's "ta" or "zza".
1, 2, 3.
- Zza. - Zza.
(They both say "zza".)
(Both One Eyed Jack and his promoter lose all they have.)
Jae Seok.
Don't do it. The energy over there is not good.
(Okay, I'll listen to you.)
- The energy is not good. - I'll just dig up some more.
That'd be better.
- One last try. - You want to try again?
- Will you get a penalty badge? - Yes.
- A penalty badge? - If you lose.
If Haha loses this time,
- he'll get a penalty badge. - Okay.
What's with him?
Somebody told me to bet my life.
It's either "pea" or "nut".
- "Pea" or "nut"? - Yes.
- I'll say "nut". - Okay.
"Pea" or "nut". 1, 2, 3.
- Pea! - Nut!
- Okay! - You win.
(Haha is back where he started.)
Kwang Soo, do you want to try too?
(His gambler instinct comes into play.)
Kwang Soo, you should sweat for it.
I've already come too far.
Just be penalized.
- What? - Just...
You punk!
I'll pick you no matter what.
Let's do "magpie".
It's "mag" or "pie".
(This is my last chance.)
Go.
(If he succeeds, he gets 1.5kg back. Otherwise, he gets a penalty badge.)
It's "mag" or "pie". 1, 2, 3.
- Pie! - Pie!
(Kwang Soo goes bankrupt.)
This is why people go bankrupt.
Hey, try one more time.
(I have a good feeling.)
At least get back to where you started.
Should I lend you some of my peanuts?
- Why would you? - I want to.
That's how you go bankrup.
Just pay me back double.
- Kwang Soo, it's "bankrupt". - "Bankrupt".
Did you think it was "bankrup"?
It's "bankrupt".
- "Bankrupt"? - Yes.
It's not "bankrup"?
We don't have much time.
- Just dig up 2kg. - I'm done.
This is not fair.
I just had 0.5kg to go.
Give me a little.
I still need some more.
But I'm almost done.
(Everyone is motivated by the lowered goal.)
I'm done.
Jae Seok, take the rock out of your bag.
He really pulls all the dirty tricks.
He had a huge rock in there.
- It's so big. - Hey, Rock!
Hey, Rock!
He's unbelievable.
(The petty offender's skills are not good enough.)
- You have a long way to go. - Gosh.
(Is Kwang Soo already done?)
Kwang Soo, shake off the dirt first.
- That's too much dirt. - No.
- This is not okay. - It's just how it looks.
That's too much dirt.
He's not there yet.
This is 1.5kg.
There is a bit of dirt in it.
You almost planted the peanuts back in the dirt.
No, I didn't.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Stop playing such dirty tricks.
- Didn't you put a rock in your bag? - Hey, Rock!
Hey, Rock!
I think I saw a rock around here.
- Rock! - I mean...
Didn't you just get scolded for putting a rock in your bag?
Who says I put a rock in my bag?
You stole my peanuts and put a rock in your bag.
- I had to return 1.5kg. - Hey!
Try one more round.
Do it!
- This is your chance. - Right.
- Bet your life on it. - Just one more round.
Let's do "shot" and "life" again.
- Do it. - "Shot" and "life".
Do you even have any life left to bet?
This is it.
- "Shot" or "life". - "Shot" or "life".
It's "shot" or "life".
(They believe Kwang Soo can't lose for the third time in a row.)
(Kwang Soo is betting his life on it. How will it end?)
- 1, 2, 3. Shot! - Shot!
(They both say "shot".)
That reckless brat.
- This will warn people. - It'll teach people a lesson.
Gambling is dangerous.
(He now has to return even the soil-covered peanuts.)
Ji Hyo might have 2kg.
(Ji Hyo, who's been working hard, weighs her peanuts.)
- It's over 2kg. - It's over 2kg.
- It's just 2kg. - It is?
You pass.
Okay.
(The hard-working people's honest achievements)
Director, I have 2kg.
You can take a break.
It must be almost 2kg.
Let me weigh it.
(Haha and Jae Seok reach 2kg too.)
I'm done.
- It's over 2kg. - I'm finally done.
Everyone is done now.
- Peanut butter is ready too. - Okay.
- You have to stay. - Everyone but Kwang Soo will move.
- Let's go. - Let's go use the air conditioner.
Let's go and have a snack.
- Okay! - Hold on.
Let's go.
Still, I can...
- You don't have time to talk. - Just dig up more peanuts.
- We'll talk. - We'll talk. You dig up peanuts.
Kwang Soo crosses the line too often.
Let's go.
You should appear on "Those Who Cross the Line".
Why should I?
Let's go.
It serves him right.
A young man like you...
(Young man, you should be a man.)
If they hadn't encouraged me...
(Jae Seok stops.)
Wait. Kwang Soo is left alone here.
Jae Seok, thank you.
Thank you.
Kwang Soo, hold this.
(If you're here to help me, why are you taking this off?)
(Kwang Soo punches Jae Seok's bottom.)
(Jae Seok obviously isn't interested in helping Kwang Soo.)
(Get lost!)
That was so loud.
It must hurt a lot.
He's so annoying.
Gosh, that guy.
(Everyone except Kwang Soo gets to try the peanut butter.)
- How does it taste? - It tastes amazing.
- Give me some. - It tastes really good.
It tastes amazing.
(This peanut butter was prepared right at the farm.)
Try it.
- It tastes fantastic. - Oh, my.
(Peanut butter on toast with cold milk)
- Give me a lot of milk. - It tastes even better with milk.
- Kwang Soo is here. - He is?
Kwang Soo, are you thirsty? Try this.
- Give me some water. - Try this first.
You have to taste it.
It must make him even thirstier.
(Thirsty)
All right.
It's time to vote between "satisfied" and "dissatisfied".
If everyone is satisfied, the host wins a prize.
- It's Korean beef. - Oh, my.
- Right here? - Right here.
And the host can pick one person to receive a penalty badge.
If everyone is dissatisfied,
the host and a person picked by the host will receive...
two penalty badges each.
It's not good if everyone is dissatisfied.
If the majority are satisfied,
those dissatisfied will receive a penalty badge each.
If the majority are dissatisfied,
the host and those satisfied...
will receive a penalty badge each.
That's complicated.
It's not good if everyone is dissatisfied.
Let me announce how many votes each member has...
after the hidden mission.
Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, Haha, Se Chan,
Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo succeeded once each and have two votes now.
So Min succeeded 3 times and has 4 votes now.
How did you do that?
If Seok Jin guesses the hidden mission right,
everyone will have only one vote left.
Wait.
I can't do that.
They all must have had different missions.
(They all must have had different missions.)
They all had the same mission.
They did?
They all had the same mission?
Hey, So Min.
Did you carry out the mission here?
(No comment)
The mission was to help me, right?
Of course.
Or was it to steal something?
To steal my belongings?
I'm sure.
Guys, please react to what I say.
- Okay. - To steal my belongings?
(Panicking)
We can't say anything.
You have to guess it on your own.
Say your answer.
What was the hidden mission?
(Will Seok Jin guess the stealing mission right?)
It was to help me.
(He says the wrong answer.)
To help me in an obvious way.
To help you in an obvious way?
Fail.
That was close.
- Gosh, I thought he'd get it. - What's the correct answer?
It was to steal your belongings.
- That was it? - He said it in the beginning.
- Gosh, I was so surprised. - I was panicking.
I was torn between helping me...
and stealing my belongings.
Gosh, that was hard.
Let me hand out the ballots.
It's not good if everyone is dissatisfied.
- We have no choice. - What should we do?
What should I do? I have so many votes.
If you vote "satisfied" and the majority are dissatisfied,
you'll receive a penalty badge.
(The majority... Dissatisfied... Badges...)
He doesn't seem to understand.
(Surprised)
Don't think too much.
Are you satisfied or dissatisfied?
I'll just go with my gut feeling.
Seriously...
Don't think too much. Just be honest.
- Let me announce the result. - It's out already?
Out of 16 votes, how many votes were for satisfied?
- Were there votes for satisfied? - I knew it.
(There are votes for satisfied.)
(The members were pretty favorable to harvesting and tasting.)
(There could be many votes for satisfied.)
(Are many votes for dissatisfied since they worked under the sun?)
(Out of 16 votes,)
(how many votes were for satisfied?)
There are votes for satisfied.
None.
(There were no votes for satisfied.)
(Did everyone choose dissatisfied?)
Who would be satisfied in this weather?
- The weather played a big role. - We had no choice.
Since everyone was dissatisfied,
the host will receive two penalty badges.
The member of the host's choosing will receive two penalty badges too.
(The host and 1 member will receive 2 penalty badges.)
No matter your effort, the situation was too bad.
You are too flippant.
- What do you mean? - You are too flippant.
- It's not like that. - He is too flippant.
Wasn't Jong Kook the worst?
"Peel the sweet potatoes, give me 90 dollars or 30 dollars..."
If you give me penalty badges, make sure to send me 90 dollars.
Make sure to send me 90 dollars.
Each badge is worth 45 dollars.
It would be better to give all of them to one person.
Did Kwang Soo get a badge?
Kwang Soo has one penalty badge.
- He does? - Why?
- Earlier... - He bet his life.
- Then... - You should give them to him.
it's more advantageous for me to give them to him.
(Kwang Soo suddenly becomes a candidate.)
He just cursed at me.
(Laughing)
We should give the penalty badges to one person.
Choose Kwang Soo again for the next activity.
Then he will get more penalty badges.
If you do that,
- it's going to be difficult. - Haha.
(Haha)
Haha.
- Give them to Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- Here you go. - That's the way to go.
- One Eyed Jack. - One Eyed Jack.
- You bet your life. - This is right.
- Strategically, this is right. - This is right.
The first activity ended.
Let's pick the next activity.
I hope he doesn't pick mine. It's too hard to be the host.
The next activity is...
"Date with Joo Jin Mo".
(Haha's "Date with Joo Jin Mo")
- What? - Whose is it?
- It's Haha's. - What?
- Whose is it? - We will go to the zoo.
- A zoo. - "Date with Joo Jin Mo".
- We're going to a zoo? - Yes.
Let's just say we went to the zoo.
I think I will pick Kwang Soo anyway.
Can you give me a chance?
You really bet your life earlier.
I can see myself in five hours.
Is there a way?
You never know.
Kwang Soo, you never know.
- You never know. - You never know.
If Haha gives two penalty badges...
- to Seok Jin... - Seok Jin.
- That's right. - If he gives them to Seok Jin...
- Seok Jin. - That's right, Haha.
What should I do? Oh, my.
Seriously.
Let's get started.
Please give it up for the host of "Date with Joo Jin Mo".
(Bragging)
- I am excited! - You know,
this activity has...
two candidates for the penalty badges.
I will make them say hello.
There are two employees.
("Date with Joo Jin Mo" has two employees.)
He has been a manager for 20 years.
- A manager! - He is Jee Seok Jin.
My goodness.
He is an animal expert.
Don't you have a peanut field?
He has a peanut field. That's right.
Really?
I didn't expect to see the owner of a peanut field.
The second employee...
can connect with giraffes and kiss them.
He is a young employee.
He has worked for 20 years as well.
- His name is Lee Kwang Soo. - Hello.
I plan to take a break today...
- because I am busy. - Okay.
The two of them will take good care of you.
- It's their job. - Give them a big hand.
- Work hard. - It will be fun.
- I get to be the host again? - Of course.
- After the peanut field... - Shall we get going?
- Let's go. - This is giving me a headache.
We are going to the zoo.
(They are near the zoo.)
I am excited.
I haven't been to the zoo in a while. I am excited.
(The zoo makes you go back to your childhood days.)
This is the place.
(Which animals will they act as moms?)
(Mom, hurry over.)
You have arrived at the place...
for the second vacation activity, "Date with Joo Jin Mo".
- Haha, please exit the bus first. - Okay.
Everyone, go easy on me.
All right.
I hope this one will be easier.
The second hidden mission is...
getting on the host's back.
(The second hidden mission, getting on the host's back)
- This is bad. - He would know right away.
He would know.
What could be the secret mission?
(Every time they get on Haha's back, they will get an additional vote.)
Let's do things that are similar to getting on his back.
- That's right. - Things of the same magnitude.
Things of the same magnitude.
Only a few people should try...
No, no, That's not it.
(No, no, That's not it.)
- You didn't even let me finish! - Let him give ideas.
- "That's not it"? - Don't get emotional.
- You didn't even listen to it. - That's not it.
(It's bound to be a useless strategy.)
He means nothing you say will work.
(They enter the zoo after receiving the hidden mission.)
This vacation activity is "Date with Joo Jin Mo".
You will connect with animals as their real moms.
There are four types of animals that need your special attention...
(There are four types of animals that need your special attention.)
- at this zoo. - I see.
(Four types of animals?)
You will split into groups of two...
- and connect with the animals. - Groups of two?
Check the items and split into groups of two.
What's "Norang"?
It's a name. Norang, Sun, Minky, Jollang,
- and Baram are all names. - "Make eye contact."
Making eye contact would be the best.
- "Make eye contact". - "Give a bath"?
- I think I know what Norang is. - This one is the best.
Giving a bath would be the hardest.
All of these tasks are hard.
Pick two representatives for each task.
I will do the task for Norang.
I will give Sun a bath.
- Ji Hyo and I will give a bath. - Okay.
Let's clean the cage.
- Okay. - All right.
(Partners for the activities)
Let's meet the cute Norang first.
(Hold Norang and make eye contact.)
It must be a bird.
- Is it a bird? - It must be a bird.
Norang must be a bird.
- A parakeet? - Parakeets and mynas.
- Where? - This is a nice task.
(They look around the zoo.)
It's an Amazonian fish.
My goodness.
What is that?
It's an Amazonian fish.
- Doesn't this live in the Amazon? - Arowana.
Arowana.
That's right.
- Meerkats. - How cute!
Aren't these the animals in "The Lion King"?
- Look at those rabbits. - Timon and Pumbaa.
- Hello. - Please come this way.
- How pretty! - They are so cute.
There are a lot of animals.
There is a turtle too.
Gosh, look at the turtle poop!
- What? - The turtle poop is so big.
- Where? What is it like? - It's the size of the turtle.
It's really big.
(A turtle poops a lot and squashes it with its body.)
- That's a big poop. - My goodness.
Isn't that charcoal?
It's not charcoal. It's a sweet potato.
(Eating and pooping well is the secret to a long life.)
It's no joke.
Let's tackle the first mission on the list.
The first one is about Norang.
"Hold Norang and make eye contact."
Let's meet Norang, the cutest animal in this zoo.
Norang, come on out.
We should at least kiss it.
(Screaming)
I saw it!
(Goosebumps)
(What kind of animal is the cute Norang?)
(Norang enters.)
(The cute mascot of the zoo, Norang)
(Norang is a 13-year-old albino Burmese python.)
Kwang Soo, come here.
- I am glad I didn't choose this. - It's really big.
- My goodness. - You would die if it strangles you.
I can't even touch it.
- Touch it. - No, no.
- I am getting goosebumps. - It's okay.
It feels like I am touching a bag.
- I am getting goosebumps. - A snakeskin bag.
(The youngest members try touching the snake.)
That's what it feels like.
- Gosh, Jong Kook. - Right?
- That's what it feels like. - Kwang Soo.
(I can't do this.)
Norang is a snake that turned 13 this year.
It boasts its beautiful color and length of 2m and 30cm.
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo, you chose to connect with Norang.
Hold Norang and keep eye contact for three seconds.
(The zoo owner and employee are scared.)
I did it once during the photoshoot for the calendar.
I was dripping in sweat.
(He forgot about...)
(how much he sweated that day.)
(The affectionate snake made Jae Seok very happy.)
Give it a try.
My goodness.
Is anyone not scared of snakes?
Is anyone willing to switch missions?
You should have this experience.
As an employee of the zoo,
you should make the visitors happy.
In my life, I have never touched a snake.
I will go first.
(This is nothing.)
(Norang's muscular mom, Jong Kook steps forward.)
It opened its mouth. It opened a little.
It's smelling the air because it wants to eat something.
(Despite Norang's movements, Jong Kook doesn't hesitate.)
All right.
(He succeeds to get Norang on his shoulders.)
(Kwang Soo is already getting goosebumps.)
- Are you okay? - Of course.
- My goodness. - Like this?
Sometimes...
- You should give it a kiss. - Sometimes,
the snakes constrict.
(Now, he needs to make eye contact with Norang.)
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo is scared.
(I can't do this.)
It's moving.
(Norang moves when it's close to Jong Kook's face.)
(My goodness.)
1, 2, 3. Mission success.
(Relaxed)
Kwang Soo, it was about to show its fangs.
(He scares Kwang Soo right away.)
Kwang Soo, I am serious. It was about to show its fangs.
(Why would you say that?)
Its mouth...
(Norang is angry.)
- You know what I mean, right? - What does it eat?
- This one eats white mice. - It eats white mice, right?
- It eats white mice. - I see.
Then it could eat a person's nose.
If it bites, you will only get two holes on your face.
(You will only get two holes on your face.)
Think of it as a piercing. A nose piercing.
When did it eat?
It ate...
about a week ago.
(Has it been a week ago?)
- A week? - It's time for a meal.
It's time for a meal.
When I held it, it opened its mouth.
(There was a reason why it opened its mouth.)
It opened its mouth.
- I... - Should I put it around you?
My goodness.
If you stay still...
(Screaming)
(He screams before the snake touches his body.)
- Kwang Soo. - My goodness.
- It didn't even touch him. - By any chance... Hold on.
(Can I be put under anesthesia?)
Can I be put under anesthesia?
For goodness' sake.
I mean...
Even children can do it.
- It could bite like this. - In a second...
- It could bite like this. - In a second, it will bite.
I wish I could do this for you, but I was born in the year of the rat.
(Norang eats mice.)
That has nothing to do with this.
I was born in the year of the rat.
I will do it.
(He convinces himself and tries again.)
(He becomes scared as soon as it touches him.)
Would you please count to three?
- I am sorry. - Count to three?
It's okay. Let's go.
(He is very nervous.)
All right.
(Jong Kook pinches him.)
(The smallest contact...)
(makes him sensitive.)
(It's so fun to tease Kwang Soo.)
(It might be faster for him to receive penalty badges.)
- Kwang Soo. - Hang in there.
- I can't do this. - Hold the head.
(His facial expression freezes.)
Kwang Soo, forget it.
- You look like a fool. - Forget it.
- Get up, coward. - I will do it.
I will do it. Let's do it.
I don't think you can do this.
I will do it. I can do it.
This is...
(At that moment)
It's me. It's me.
(He gets shocked for real.)
When I poked his bottom, he flinched.
It's me. It's me.
(Even when he pretends to be strong, he can't hide his fear.)
- It's me. It's me. - He can't do it.
- My goodness. - I will do it.
I will put it around your shoulders.
(He sets his mind and tries for the 2nd time.)
- My goodness. - He is suppressing his fear.
(He succeeds to put the snake around his neck.)
Kwang Soo, make eye contact.
- Where is it? - It's to your left.
- You need to look at it. - Diagonal to your left.
You need to look at it. Look to your left.
- No, no. - It's only three seconds.
- It's at one o'clock. - You just need to look at it.
- You just need to look at it. - The snake is looking at you.
- Come on and look at it. - I am making eye contact.
- No, you are not. - Gosh, what is this?
Gosh, what is this?
(Norang's tail heads to Kwang Soo's crotch.)
(Why did it go over there?)
Are you okay?
I am okay.
Let's begin.
Hurry up and make eye contact.
- Hurry up. - 1, 2, 3.
Three seconds.
- 3 seconds. - 1, 2, 3.
- One, - Come on, Kwang Soo.
two,
three. Mission success.
(1, 2, 3. Mission success.)
Mission success.
(I can't believe a coward like him did it.)
(His soul escaped his body.)
Kwang Soo, good job.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you. - Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Bye, Norang.
I think you need a massage.
(Feed Minky and take a selfie with satisfied Minky.)
Please come this way.
It's your favorite animal, the fennec fox.
It's in "The Little Prince".
- How cute! - That's right.
- How cute! - They are fennec foxes.
- Hello. - They are so cute.
- Would you like to hold them? - Can we do that?
- We can hold fennec foxes. - We can hold them.
I would love to do that.
- They are so cute. - They are like dogs.
They are so cute. They are lying down.
- Don't they bite? - No.
They are like babies.
- They are like babies. - How cute!
Let's move on to the next mission.
So Min, we need to go to Minky.
- Minky? - They are foxes.
(After meeting the fennec foxes, they move on to the next mission.)
- These are crocodiles. - Crocodiles.
- We already met some crocodiles! - Crocodiles?
- We already met some crocodiles! - We already had a similar mission.
(A group of crocodiles appears before their eyes.)
Thank goodness we are up here.
This one is moving. This one is moving.
(The crocodiles gather around the people.)
- They are coming. - They are so big.
They are so big.
This is no joke.
Minky, the crocodile that turned 32 this year,
is the biggest crocodile in this zoo.
We met Chopper.
- We met Chopper. - It's really big.
Jae Seok and So Min, find and feed Minky.
Then take a selfie with it when it's satisfied.
How do we know if Minky is satisfied or not?
- Seriously. - Take a selfie with Minky?
Give Minky raw chicken for dinner.
They won't go down, will they?
They need to do it from here.
(They won't go down, will they?)
- I will die if I go down there. - Jae Seok should go down.
- They will die. - You could go down.
It's really big.
I haven't seen such a big crocodile in Korea.
For your information, the strongest crocodiles eat first.
Really?
Is that one the strongest?
- That's right. - It's the leader.
(The strongest crocodile moves first when dinner is ready.)
- We need... - Take a selfie.
to feed Minky to complete the mission, right?
- Yes. - Is this one Minky?
Which one is Minky?
- This one must be Minky. - The largest one is Minky.
- This one must be Minky. - This one must be Minky.
Like this.
Make sure the crocodile is in the frame.
(The selfie needs to contain the member's face and Minky.)
- Can you get it in the frame? - No, it's too low.
So Min, you should get on the floor.
- Do you know what I mean? - Yes.
Use whatever you can.
(So Min gets into position for the mission.)
There you go.
Hold on. Where is it?
- It's coming. - I will do it.
All right.
Get ready.
- So Min! So Min! - Move it.
You have to take it now. So Min, did you take a selfie?
- It's coming. - You have to take it now.
(It finishes eating in an instant.)
(So Min took selfies when the strongest crocodile came near.)
Jae Seok. I got only a fraction of my face.
- It's a selfie. - It's only a fraction of my face.
- It's still a selfie. - Did you take a selfie?
That crocodile isn't Minky.
No?
(That crocodile isn't Minky?)
Which crocodile is Minky?
Isn't it that one?
Excuse me.
- What? - Excuse me.
Would you please get Minky?
Can you please get Minky?
- Hey. - Where is Minky?
Minky is the third strongest crocodile with a white face.
The third strongest crocodile with a white face.
- Is it this one? - It has a white face.
- It's this one. - Look at its eyes.
- So Min, take a selfie. - Get ready.
- Take a selfie with Minky. - Here I go.
Where is the chicken?
- Here we go. - Where is the chicken? Hold on.
- Here we go. - So Min. So Min.
- Okay. - So Min, come here.
(It misses.)
- Come here. - I am ready. Do it one more time.
Minky, one more time.
- Minky. - I almost got it.
Film a video and take a screenshot.
- Hold on. - Minky, Minky.
- Don't fight. - It's another crocodile.
(Another crocodile approaches.)
- Where is the chicken? - Here is another one.
(Crocodiles eat in the order of the ranks.)
So Min.
- Jae Seok. - Minky, why are you so timid?
(The second strongest approaches when Minky tries to eat.)
(Top strongest is after the chicken because it's still hungry.)
- Jae Seok. - Minky, why are you so timid?
- There are larger crocodiles. - It's below the rank.
- It's intimidated. - But Minky needs to eat.
Minky.
(It only smacks its lips.)
(Minky is surrounded by the 2 strongest crocodiles.)
(Will they be able to capture its mealtime?)
It's opening its mouth.
- That one is opening its mouth. - Where is it?
The strongest crocodile is opening its mouth.
Minky. Minky needs to eat.
Put it against its nose.
- Because of the strongest one, - The strongest crocodile.
It won't eat with the other one there.
It can't eat because of the strongest one.
What should we do?
Lure the strongest one over here.
- Okay. - It will eat.
- No, no. - Hold on.
What will we do if it gets annoyed and breaks the bridge?
(He is such a coward.)
Hold on. Minky, Minky.
- Minky, Minky. - Minky will eat.
(Eating)
That's it. Did you take a selfie?
(Minky eats when the 2 strongest seem uninterested.)
- Did you take a selfie? - Minky ate.
(So Min took selfies at that moment.)
(So Min and Minky should be in it.)
- Minky ate. - Did you take a selfie?
- Did you take it? Minky ate. - I took it.
You took it. Let's see it.
- You did it. - Minky ate.
Let's check the selfie.
My goodness. Minky.
(Did So Min manage to take a selfie?)
You can look from here.
- I am sweating. - Me too.
Why does this one look different?
(Minky is in the selfie.)
We will accept this selfie.
Okay! Thank you.
It looks very satisfied.
It's satisfied.
Take a photo of it in its satisfied state.
(Feed Minky and take a selfie with satisfied Minky is cleared.)
Come this way.
What are they doing? They look cute.
Everyone, this is our last hurdle.
You'll be cleaning Jollang and Baram's cage.
Jollang is a llama, and Baram is a red kangaroo.
Kangaroo?
You have to clean their cage.
We have to clean both of their cages.
(Jollang and Baram)
It looks like you, Jae Seok.
- That llama. - It's Jae Seok.
It looks exactly like you.
- Jae Seok. - It looks exactly like you.
(An exact copy)
(Isn't it a doppelganger?)
They look the same.
(They're so similar that everyone is flustered.)
I was startled.
I thought you were cleaning inside the cage.
Take off your glasses, Jae Seok.
- Hey, what makes it... - They're the same.
- look like me? - You look the same.
(They look the same.)
What makes it look like me?
They look the same.
It's looking at you because you look the same.
- It's angry. - Hey.
It's upset too.
Is the llama upset?
You have to clean quickly so that he can be fed.
We have to clean quickly so that he can eat.
- You have to clean now. - Clean now.
- Where do we go? - You may come in this way.
It's not dangerous, is it?
They could kick you with their hind leg.
(Do they kick with their hind leg?)
- Pardon? - They can kick with their hind leg.
Then I can't do this.
Be careful.
If you aren't careful, they might kick you.
It will hurt if they kick me.
They're coming.
(Coward brothers get fussy.)
What do I do?
He's coming towards me.
- Sweep their poop with this broom. - Okay.
Sweep it up and put it here.
This one is cute. He must be a baby.
- Yes, he is a baby. - He likes to be touched.
Goodness.
I need to feed my family.
- Jae Seok, you have a big family. - What?
You have a big family.
- Jae Seok. - I need to feed my family.
Instead of taking care of your family, you should eat.
You should eat.
(You should eat some grass.)
You should eat as well.
Jae Seok, take care of yourself too.
I'll eat later.
(I'm the eldest, so I feed my siblings first.)
(Let's see.)
Do you know what's funny?
No one is filming us cleaning.
We're working.
We're cleaning.
(One camera is filming them.)
(Cleaning is the main mission, so please film us too.)
We're cleaning.
- Aren't you satisfied? - Yes, man.
That's enough. Go to the kangaroo cage.
We're done here.
("That's enough"?)
"That's enough"?
Come. That's enough.
- There's nothing more to film. - Listen.
Are you making us work?
- I'm disappointed. - Here's what's funny.
Do you know what the zookeeper said to us?
"All you're doing here is cleaning."
- Gosh. - Shouldn't we cover it?
Do you need my help?
- All you're doing here is cleaning. - Yes.
"It's true."
(They're on Running Man for work.)
- Do we need to bring it? - Yes.
Look at him.
He's like a human being.
A kangaroo is lying here. You should be filming here.
- Come here. - A kangaroo is lying.
A kangaroo is lying down like a human being.
Why is he lying down like that?
(Have you never seen a kangaroo lying down?)
Isn't that posture...
when we're watching TV at night?
It's like we lie down on a sofa.
It looks similar.
What kind of condition is he in?
He's very comfortable.
He's not scared.
He isn't interested.
You know what?
I think he's treating you like slaves.
- He's the human. - Yes.
Hurry and clean up.
- The owner of the house is here. - Right.
Take a look at them.
This is interesting.
You may sit next to him and look.
He won't attack.
(He may not attack, but Se Chan is very scared.)
He's looking at you.
- May I touch him? - You may gently.
Don't do it.
He'll hit you with his tail.
Gosh, it's very...
- Is it hard? - It's hard.
I hope he hits you with his tail but not enough to hurt you.
(Get hit by his tail?)
Wouldn't it be funny?
(That would be funny indeed.)
(He's bothered, so he moves.)
(I might get hit at this rate.)
Okay, let's go.
Let's go now.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you, zookeeper.
It was fun.
Llamas were fun to watch.
We put our arms on the shoulders. You should do it too.
Seok Jin gets 3 ballots, and Jae Seok gets 2 ballots.
The rest of you get one each.
- Are you satisfied? - It was great.
I'm very satisfied.
It was good indeed.
- Honestly it was good. - Really?
I wasn't dissatisfied.
(The host and a person of his choice get 2 penalty badges each.)
- I'll follow how I feel. - That's what I did too.
I have three of them.
How I feel will be influential, won't it?
(What's the result of the vote?)
Here's the result of the vote.
What's the result?
How many were satisfied?
All members were satisfied. You won a Korean beef set.
(All members were satisfied.)
(Even the host is surprised.)
- The Korean beef set? - Is it true?
- Really? - Were you that satisfied?
I'm very happy.
All members can be satisfied.
You were really satisfied, weren't you?
Here's an exchange card for Korean beef.
Thank you so much.
Only the person that Haha picks will...
get a penalty badge.
- That person will get one badge. - How many?
Is it one badge?
(Kwang Soo has 3, and Seok Jin has 2.)
(Their situation changes depending on Haha's choice.)
Seok Jin.
The mission you gave me was...
impressive.
I didn't understand it.
Let's be fair.
Ji Seok Jin!
(Haha chooses Seok Jin.)
Bring it to me.
(Seok Jin can't hide his disappointment.)
You bring it to me.
This is all about them two.
Both of them are losing.
- Is it lobster? - Lobster.
- We're catching it. Is it easy? - Okay.
- Are you the host, Se Chan? - Yes.
- Wait, this time... - Isn't it 1 of the 2?
- Right now... - Two badges are on the line, right?
It depends on the result of the vote.
Let's bet multiple badges.
You need to appease me, Seok Jin.
(I can give you a badge.)
- He looks upset. - What year did you start...
- What do you mean? - being a comedian?
Goodness.
Jae Seok, what's this?
He's asking what year I started.
- Come on. - Seok Jin.
What year did you start?
- What year? - Tell us.
I started in the 10th year at KBS.
I started in the seventh.
My goodness.
- That means... - Seriously.
- the difference is three years. - He can't even look at you.
- That's huge. - Yes.
There's no hierarchy when we're playing games.
Seok Jin is such a fossil.
- I hope that... - It's not that.
Seok Jin will continue acting like this.
- You don't understand. - I'm serious.
Who are you afraid of?
I'll call him.
It's Jae Seok.
(It's Jae Seok.)
(Laughing)
- What's wrong? - Se Chan is afraid of me.
- Call him. - Se Chan is afraid of me.
Call him.
- There's no reason not to do it. - Show us.
- He's calling him. - I'm curious.
- He's calling. - I got a call.
- He's picking up. - Wait.
I'm at a shoot, so hang up.
(Hanging up)
(Jae Seok who's three years ahead acts firmly.)
(Unbelievable)
- What did he say? - Why did you hang up already?
- What did he say? - He told me he's busy.
He's at work.
- I see. - Really?
(They head to Se Chan's vacation activity.)
- Seriously. - It's not that.
Host, I think we're here.
Yes, we're here.
- Is this it? - Yes.
All right, everyone.
Get ready to catch lobster.
Are there lobsters here?
(Are there lobsters here?)
This is the last activity of the Vacation Race.
You arrived at "Date with the Stars" spot hosted by Se Chan.
Host Se Chan will get out first.
- Okay. - That was it.
(For the hidden mission to be announced, Se Chan leaves.)
All right.
(What's the hidden mission this time?)
- Here's the last hidden mission. - Yes?
Take a very closeup photo of a part of the host's body.
- What? - Take a photo?
It can be his eye or his ear.
It can also be a closeup photo of his finger.
We can take a photo like we're playing.
If you show me a closeup photo of his body,
you'll get an additional vote.
- The more we take, the better. - Two parts can be...
Listen, Kwang Soo.
Is there a way that someone else can be penalized?
No.
- Is it over? - It's true.
- Is it over? - I thought about it on our way.
- Is it over? - I'm on your side.
Let's go, let's go.
Okay.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(They are off to fish for lobster.)
It's nice that it's inside.
Come this way.
Do you see the lobsters on the bottom?
This is how it's set.
It looks fun.
There they are.
You'll fish for exactly 30 minutes.
It's over once you eat ramyeon at the sashimi restaurant.
(They plan to eat the lobster that they catch.)
The one who catches the least number of lobsters gets a penalty badge.
I'm not good with lobsters.
Hello.
Hello to you too.
- Hello. - Hello, sir.
- Hello. - Hello.
What should we do?
(How do we catch lobsters?)
- There's a hook right here. - Yes.
- Take it out like this. - I took it out.
Then turn it.
There's bait in front of you.
The bait is shrimp.
Take a shrimp and...
- Shall I bait it? - Yes, bait the hook.
Bait it the way you want.
(Everyone is concentrating.)
Hook it gently.
Sir, can we eat these lobsters?
Yes, you can.
- Then? - After you do that, cast it.
(Kwang Soo sees it.)
(He takes a closeup photo of Se Chan's sideburns.)
- Cast it out. - Yes.
I see fish too.
Untie it. When you look right in front of you...
(She takes a closeup photo of his ear.)
Hook it in front of you.
(She takes a closeup photo of the back of his neck.)
He has no idea we're taking photos of him.
He's just stupid.
- He's immersed in the fishing. - Right.
- After doing it... - Then cast it.
(They start lobster fishing.)
- Cast it out. - Okay.
- Cast it directly. - Is that it?
I got something.
(The float is being dragged.)
- I caught something. What do I do? - You got something.
- Did you catch something? - I got something.
(Tight)
- What should I do? - Seok Jin caught something.
- You have to catch it. - You can go back.
Seok Jin caught something.
- It didn't go in. - He caught a fish.
- He caught a fish. - Pull it. Pull it in.
- Bring it up. - I got something.
- What should I do? - He caught a fish.
- He caught it. - He caught a fish.
I caught a fish.
You caught a fish?
(Aren't they supposed to be lobsters?)
You caught 1 of the 2 rockfish in there.
(He caught 1 of the 2 rockfish.)
Only lobsters count.
(Only lobsters are accepted.)
I caught something.
Who caught something?
(The lobster looks at Jong Kook's bait.)
(It falls for it.)
He caught a lobster.
Jong Kook caught one already?
Lobster.
Jong Kook got one?
- Who was it? - It's so big.
You got a big one.
It was Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is the first to show off his skills.)
- It's fun catching them. - I caught one.
Wait.
(It goes up along with Seok Jin's rising hand.)
I caught one.
- Seok Jin. - I caught one.
You hooked its tail.
- I got one, thank you. - Be careful or you'll lose it.
Okay.
I caught one too.
(He gets a lobster after Jong Kook.)
It's a big one.
(Seok Jin shows off his fishing skills.)
I'm in trouble.
They actually bite.
Please eat it.
(The float gets dragged.)
Please take the bait.
(It stops.)
It bit it now.
- Is it right now? - Yes.
Raise it.
(Raise your rod.)
You got it.
(Let's go, Ji Hyo.)
(Dropping)
(What?)
(Kwang Soo picks up the lobster.)
Ji Hyo, I caught it.
- Hey, how can you steal mine? - Hey.
You can't steal mine.
Kwang Soo, you can't do that.
- Pardon? I didn't steal. - Isn't it mine?
I didn't steal it.
I caught it when it was falling.
Kwang Soo, that's wrong.
You can't steal mine.
You can't do that. Give it back to Ji Hyo.
I'm telling the truth.
(12 minutes pass.)
How many did you catch?
I caught one.
(He catches his third one.)
Bring the net.
- Here you go. - Okay, help me with this.
Give me the landing net.
(He pushes down the landing net.)
(Surprised)
Hey.
(He presses it down with the landing net.)
(He releases the lobster.)
It fell off.
(Don't get caught by Seok Jin.)
Did you do it on purpose?
- I didn't know. - I think you pushed it down.
No, I didn't.
- I almost had it. - I didn't know.
(Kwang Soo is impressive.)
It was a mistake, Seok Jin.
- You pushed it. - No.
I got distracted.
- I'm sorry. - Did you see him push it?
Why you...
He pushed down the lobster.
You have 10 minutes left.
I haven't caught one yet.
Everyone next to me is catching them so easily.
I got one.
- How did you catch it? - Did you get it, So Min?
Yes.
I caught one.
(So Min catches one lobster.)
I got it, I got it.
Give me the landing net now.
- I caught one. - Okay.
One lobster.
I caught one.
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo catch one each.)
Please come.
Come just once.
(Only Jae Seok hasn't caught one yet.)
Star, please eat one.
You have 20 seconds.
Okay, I caught it.
(He catches a lobster dramatically.)
It's a big one.
(Time is running out.)
10.
Nine.
(Will Jae Seok catch a lobster?)
Eight.
Seven.
(It falls off.)
(The lobster is free.)
(Swinging)
Time is up.
Do they not like the shrimp?
Jae Seok will get a penalty badge.
- Isn't it fun? - Yes.
- This is my first time. - It's so much fun.
It was good.
- Let's go and taste it. - Okay.
Let's eat.
Is it sashimi? Can you eat it raw?
It's amazing.
(Freshly caught lobsters are eaten raw and steamed.)
Thank you. I'll try some lobster ramyeon.
(Slurping lobster ramyeon)
Enjoy it.
It's so plump.
(Everyone is busy eating.)
Here you go.
Open up.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's to flatter me.
Please film this.
- Eat a lot. - I'm eating.
Kwang Soo is bringing kimchi.
That's attentive.
- What? - It's attentive.
What kind of service is this?
That's impressive.
This kimchi is better than that.
(He keeps things in check.)
Try it.
- What are you doing? - There are flies.
Thank you. I'll remember it.
- I'll remember it. - It's okay.
(I like doing it.)
I'll take a photo of Se Chan eating.
What?
Se Chan is cute.
Open your mouth. Show that you're enjoying it.
(Haha attempts at the hidden mission.)
(Haha obtains an additional vote.)
He's eating lobster in a cute way.
(Is he blatantly taking photos of him?)
It'll be an unforgettable memory.
Let me take a photo of your ugly face.
(Approaching)
(I'm not that blunt.)
- Is this... - Your ugly looks.
the hidden mission?
- Is it the mission? - You're making it obvious.
Let me take a photo of you.
- This must be the mission. - No.
- Do it. - Okay.
Today's Vacation Race is over.
("Date with the Stars" activity ends.)
Here's the current number of votes that you obtained.
So Min succeeded 4 times, so she has a total of 5 votes.
Ji Hyo and Haha succeeded 3 times, so they have a total of 4 votes.
Jae Seok has a total of three votes.
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook have two votes each.
Seok Jin has one.
What?
(What's going on?)
Do I have to send it to him?
No, right?
Is it better to have more?
Seok Jin.
- Excuse me. - He succeeded once.
Did I have to send it?
(He doesn't indicate the subject.)
(Laughing)
What did you do?
- Look. - Did you keep it?
- I don't think he sent it. - What did you do?
What did Seok Jin do?
Wait a minute.
I have 16 photos.
Those don't meet the condition.
They don't meet the condition.
What did he do and when?
If Se Chan guesses the hidden mission correctly,
everyone gets one vote each.
It's taking photos.
What is the hidden mission?
(What does Se Chan think?)
The hidden mission is...
(If he answers correctly, no one gets additional votes.)
(Will Se Chan guess correctly?)
It's taking photos of my gums.
(Taking photos of my gums)
You failed.
(Se Chan fails to guess the mission.)
That's not right?
It's taking a closeup photo of any part of your body.
(Taking a close photo of Se Chan's body)
(He's a fool.)
You fool.
See? I have multiple photos. Right?
You may take the ballot.
(The evaluation voting starts.)
Everyone, you must consider this. Look at it carefully.
Can you analyze it?
It's confusing.
Seok Jin and Kwang Soo.
They're the two candidates today.
This is what Kwang Soo and Seok Jin have to do.
You must make everyone vote "dissatisfied".
- So? - Right.
If the host gives Jae Seok two badges,
- Will it be 3 to 1? - It'll be a fight among three.
- You have a way out. - It'll be a fight among three.
I'll vote for satisfied.
(I'll write "satisfied".)
Just end it here.
They have no way out.
As I do this...
- This is my vote. - You handed in three votes.
I handed mine in.
You're quick at calculating.
There's no need to plan strategies. It won't work.
- There's nothing. - Either way,
Se Chan is the only one with the key.
(Se Chan will choose the final person to be penalized.)
Look how Kwang Soo is thinking.
- We have the vote result. - Okay.
Everyone is satisfied, right?
Those who voted satisfied are...
- All members. - all members.
(Se Chan wins a Korean beef set.)
It can't be helped.
Se Chan gets Korean beef.
(He tries to flatter Se Chan.)
Yang Se Chan, Yang Se Chan
It was a lot of fun.
I wasn't just satisfied, I was completely satisfied.
Se Chan will choose out of the two...
who will be penalized.
The one with the most penalty badges will...
pick one of the remaining activities.
As a penalty,
he will stay behind and finish the activity.
Alone?
- Alone? - You can't pick someone to join?
- All right. - They must be nervous.
It's worse than the bungee jump.
It feels like we're at a cliff.
I feel like I'm standing at a cliff.
- Please. - Please count to three.
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin's managers are very nervous.)
One.
(After the shoot, they'll spend at least 3 hours.)
Here I go.
(The one penalized will work without pay.)
I can't do this.
(Which member will get off work looking at the moon?)
Three!
(Kwang Soo is pushed.)
(But Seok Jin is pushed too.)
(What's the result?)
(The place is surrounded by white walls...)
(and an endless ceiling.)
(And an unidentified member enters this place.)
(It's Seok Jin.)
(Several hours ago, a member was chosen for the penalty.)
(Both of them were pushed.)
- Go home. - Okay!
You should go and do the penalty.
(Se Chan chose Seok Jin.)
- Hey, you. - Goodness.
- I chose one. - 1, 2, 3.
(It's time to choose the penalty mission.)
The best game of tags is Freeze Tag.
You'll work in a cold storage at minus 20℃.
He really has to work.
(Seok Jin has come to this frozen kingdom to work.)
My gosh, this whole place...
The whole place is at minus 18℃?
This is a cold storage in Noryangjin Fish Market.
We can store about 4,000t of seafood.
My gosh, this place is huge.
Today, you're going...
to transport the boxes of salted mackerels...
to the empty lot over there.
This one? My gosh, it's freezing in here.
(A 54-year-old worker starts carrying the boxes.)
Gosh, it's so cold.
(There are no members who can listen to his complaints here.)
(He worked for over 30 minutes,)
(but it's only worth 30 seconds of footage.)
(However, the boxes are piling up now.)
(Stacking them up neatly)
I'm done.
(He speaks for the 1st time after 33 minutes.)
Everyone, was today's episode entertaining?
I'll see you next week. Let's go!
(Seok Jin completes his penalty mission.)
(In autumn, your interests in liberal arts begin to grow.)
(The members will have a poetry contest.)
(Your face is long, Kwang Soo.)
(Your legs are long too.)
(But your knowledge is short.)
(He gets up at Jae Seok's original composition.)
(4 guests have come to participate in the contest.)
(Tiffany, Park Yu Na, Mina, and Hwang Chi Yeul)
(The party begins with this cheerful Pick-Me fairy.)
(And a master of a reciting singing method shows up.)
(However,)
(are these two dictionaries confidential files?)
(The members sense that something is off.)
(They face each other head-on without any willingness to yield.)
(The contest? The karaoke? Where did things start to go wrong?)
(What's the shocking secret the members have witnessed?)
(Secret Code: Autumn Ambush)