(Last week)
This is a project for all, Rice Cake in the Sky.
(Grand New Year Project, the Level Up Race)
(For 3 weeks, fierce battles have unfolded to level up.)
(And today, the final winner will be decided.)
(How will this long journey end?)
Hello. Hi, hi. Hello, there.
- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
- It's very cold. - It's snowing.
(The snow is piling up.)
It feels great to be at a ski resort.
By the way, did you see So Min's poem on her social media?
(By the way, did you see So Min's poem on her social media?)
- Hey, you know what? - She wrote a poem?
- Is she a poet? - That's true.
Have you been writing poems lately?
- Those weren't lyrics? - No, I wrote them myself.
- I was looking at snow in Sapporo. - Why did you suddenly write a poem?
I went on a trip with my parents.
When I was looking at my parents by myself...
You should cherish the moment in private. Why did you post it?
Let me read one of her poems.
- When did you get that? - Let me read her poem.
- I can't understand her. - Come on.
- I just wrote a poem. - Well, this is the poem...
- So Min posted on her social media. - Okay.
"Even if I walk to you all day long, in Sapporo, there wouldn't be..."
"any traces."
- That's what she wrote? - "Even if I walk to you all night,"
- "there would be no traces." - This is so embarrassing.
- "If I stand still, I'll be gone." - This is so embarrassing.
- "If I daze off, all will be gone." - What does that mean?
- What does this mean? - What is this about?
- What is this? - What is she saying?
She wrote this on a piece of napkin and put it next to a cup of coffee.
(This is a true story.)
- She put a cup of coffee there. - You're the worst, So Min.
- She does all sorts of things. - My goodness, unbelievable.
My gosh, this is...
- Could this mean... - What was the background song?
- There was no song. - Freestyle's "Unknown Address"?
(This post was popular on an outdated social media website.)
- It was "Snow Flower". - "Unknown Address"?
(No, it was "Snow Flower".)
It was "Snow Flower".
(Even in the heart of a poet, So Min,)
(white snow of Sapporo has fallen.)
"Even if I walk to you all day long, in Sapporo..."
(Sighing)
(I am lonely like Sapporo.)
(She was walking with heavy steps.)
(She disappeared out of the frame.)
(So Min and the snow are the same. She decides to disappear.)
(Too much emotions can make you cringe.)
(Playlist in Sapporo, "Snow Flower" by Park Hyo Shin)
(Her sentiment in Sapporo brought upon a tragedy on a wintry day.)
Hey, she must have written that for someone.
- No, no. - What's wrong with you, So Min?
- No, I was... - She wrote it for someone.
That was definitely meant for someone.
- That has to be the case. - She must have someone. Look.
You know what? With that point of view,
- this poem is very meaningful. - Yes.
"Even if I walk to you all day long, in Sapporo,"
"there wouldn't be any traces."
- It snowed a lot. - "To you".
- That makes sense. We can trace it. - Exactly.
Last time, So Min asked me to set her up with a guy,
and I heard back from him.
- He did? - He asked if it was meant for him.
- What did you tell him? - I said that it was for him.
"Okay, I see." I said that it was for him.
(He sounds cold-hearted.)
He's younger than you.
- Hey. - "Have a nice meal, Kwang Soo."
- My gosh. - "Have a nice meal, Kwang Soo."
I see.
(I'll set you up next time.)
- You put on your level badges. - Yes.
By the way, don't you think this is too cruel?
- They're both 0. Level 0. - Listen.
- You're Level Zero now. - I won the games last week.
- You have nothing. - I was in the lead by myself.
- He practices non-possession. - This is so mean.
- You're Level 6. - She's Level 6. Seriously?
- What's your level? - Look at Haha's level too.
You're unbelievable, Haha.
- I'm Level Six. - He took Jae Seok's levels.
Today is the final episode of 2019 New Year Project,
- the Level Up Race. - Final episode.
Level 10 Member: Catch-up Partner.
- Partner? - There are partners.
(This is a couple race.)
It's a race with partners.
We'll have partners.
Inside are the partners who will decide your fates.
- Are they inside? - Partners?
Six of your partners are waiting in there.
- Really? - There are six partners.
- You'll go meet them now. - Let's go.
(Let's go!)
- Let's go. - He's running.
(What kind of partners await them?)
(It's time to reveal the partners.)
Come on. Give me a chance.
- I really wish I get a good one. - Same here.
I'll catch up. I'm serious.
Right now, the guests are...
waiting behind the doors.
Is that so?
(The 6 Catch-up Partners are waiting behind the doors.)
On the doors that the guests have chosen,
from 1 to 6, the levels are attached randomly.
(Level 1 to 6 are randomly attached on the doors they chose.)
(The guests randomly chose the levels?)
- Really? - We'll get to take those levels!
- Gosh, we should choose wisely. - We still have a shot.
- We might be able to win. - Exactly.
Someone will reach Level 10 today.
Then we'll bring out the first guest now.
- Who is it? - Come on out, please.
First guest, please come on out.
Who is it?
(What is the identity of the first partner?)
- It's been so long. - It's been ages, Jong Hyun.
(He won over all the hearts of the female viewers.)
(He was also great on the show with his unexpected talent 3 years ago.)
(We're looking forward to his outstanding work today again.)
- It's been ages, Jong Hyun. - Have you been well?
- Hello. - Jong Hyun.
(She heartily welcomes him.)
Why does your hairstyle look like an alien's today?
(Anyway, what happened to your hair?)
My hairstyle is shaped like a lid.
- The hairstyle is exactly the same. - He has your hairstyle.
Don't point that out.
You have Se Chan's hairstyle.
- That hairstyle is from Gangnam. - It's been so long.
- But his hairstyle seems different. - He has Se Chan's hairstyle.
Hey, you two should pair up today.
Why did he copy my hairstyle?
- It looks just like his hairstyle. - Their hairstyles are the same.
- Hello. - Gosh, this is annoying.
This is embarrassing for some reason.
This isn't the hairstylist's problem.
Gosh, this is annoying.
Hey, yours looks just like his.
Gosh, this hairstyle actually looks nice.
- Your hairstyle is trendy. - It's a popular hairstyle.
- It's popular. - Seriously.
We'll bring in the second guest.
Please come on out.
Come on out.
(The second partner is revealed after the handsome alien.)
(What is the identity of this partner?)
- Goodness. - Hey.
- Goodness. - Gosh, this is...
(A genuine reaction)
(She greets the second partner with laughter.)
It's Seungri. Seungri.
(The second partner is Seungri.)
(The Great Seungri, Seungri of BigBang)
(His solo album was a hit, and his business was a hit.)
(What on earth can't he do?)
(The versatile and successful youngest...)
(has returned after 4 months.)
- Seungri is like our family. - Seungri.
(Here's the Great Seungri,)
(but their reaction is somewhat lukewarm.)
- You're here, Seungri. - Wait.
- Why don't you sound more excited? - No, it's because...
When you saw Jong Hyun, you were really happy to see him.
It's been a while since he was here.
You're like our family.
First of all, Jong Hyun and Seungri...
- Guys don't matter. - Yes, they're not that important.
They aren't that important to me.
We're continuing after Seungri and Jong Hyun's introductions.
Third partner, please come on out.
(The third partner is revealed next.)
Here it comes!
Number three, come on out.
(What is the identity of the third partner?)
It's Yu Mi.
(Actress Jung Yu Mi, full of awesome charms)
Jung Yu Mi!
(She has become the queen of TV dramas with her superb acting.)
(She's great on variety shows and radio shows.)
(You can't find an all-around beauty like her anywhere else.)
(Hello)
- My gosh. - Jung Yu Mi!
(Welcoming urgently)
It's been so long. Hello.
- Hello. Hi. - Goodness.
My goodness.
(My goodness)
(Jae Seok, her idol, is right in front of her.)
(Is this really happening?)
- It's been so long. - Me too.
(Feeling shy)
I'm a big fan.
I was trying to shake your hands...
from here, but I ended over there.
- Come this way, Yu Mi. - Hello.
- Hello. - She's never been on our show?
- Hello. Yes. - This is her first time here.
Why do I feel like she's been on our show before?
Is that so?
- I was always with you guys. - Really?
- At home. - My goodness.
What a great mindset. That was so nice.
Goodness, she's a go-getter.
(Jae Seok is excited to meet a fan.)
- We shook hands. How many times? - How many times will you do it?
- Looking at you two like this... - Yes.
You two look like two hosts.
Really? That came out of nowhere.
- It's like "March of the Youth". - That was sudden.
- Do we look like them? - Yes.
- "March of the Youth". - It's your outfit too.
Your outfits match nicely.
Don't you think her outfit is too fancy?
Compared to my outfit?
Can't I wear a fancy outfit?
- It can't be fancy. - Is that so?
By the way, at the beginning of the year,
we had the press conference.
Ji Hyo made an unexpected remark out of nowhere.
- "You have me." - That's right.
A lot of viewers said...
- they made a nice couple. - It's a nice match.
- They make a great couple. - You guys met naturally.
- I'm serious. - This isn't natural.
- It's a very natural way to meet. - It was natural.
- This is the most natural way. - Natural relationship.
But still. Our colors are so different.
How are they different?
- Our colors are very different. - No.
This. This color...
is like the asphalt on the road, and she's the centerline.
(Jong Gook is the asphalt and Ji Hyo is the centerline.)
What are you saying? Why am I asphalt?
That's right.
(Bursting with anger)
- This is the asphalt. - Why is this asphalt?
- She's the centerline. - Why am I the asphalt?
- You're on the road together. - What? Do you hear yourself?
They're the safety zone.
- This is nice. It's nice. - They make a nice couple.
- You look great together. - She's the radish in gimbap.
(He finds another example.)
- My goodness, come on. - She's the radish in gimbap.
- That's right. What else? - Gimbap.
- What other examples do we have? - There are so many.
- What else? - I'm sure there are many.
- Let's stop here. Go back in there. - Okay, okay.
I wonder who the fourth partner is. Let's bring the partner in.
- Come on out. - Who is it?
- Who is it? - Who is it?
(What is the identity of the partner this time?)
- It's Yu Ri. Lee Yu Ri. - I was so startled.
(Actress Lee Yu Ri, sweet and scary lady)
(She has become the best villainess with her excellent acting.)
(She ruled Running Man with her crazy energy...)
(from her tiny build 5 years ago.)
(I'm the number one villainess in this area.)
- Gosh, I didn't recognize you. - Seriously.
- Hello. - Have you been well?
- Your dramas have been successful. - That's right.
Thank you.
Yu Ri has been on our show often.
Why are you shy? What is it?
I was here five years ago.
- Yes, it was 5 years ago. - 5 years ago?
Really?
That has been five years?
- It was the Villainess Special. - Oh, right.
It was the Villainess Special.
- That special was really fun too. - Right.
- Right. - That's right.
All right. 5th and 6th partners.
They'll come out at the same time. Come on out, please.
At the same time?
- Are they a team? - My gosh.
(What are the identities of the last partners?)
(MinA and Jimin of AOA, irreplaceable idol singers)
(This girl group with popular songs always sweeps the charts.)
(MinA, multitalented, hidden gem)
(Jimin, the prettiest rapper)
(AOA has dominated the dramas as well as the variety shows.)
It's AOA. AOA.
- They are MinA and Jimin. - MinA.
(Welcome, isn't this your first time here?)
- You and I are in the same agency. - What brings you here?
(That came out of nowhere.)
- You are in the same agency. - I know that.
Where should we stand?
- Come here. - Okay.
I find...
(Chuckling)
MinA is so funny.
Yes!
She was so happy to see me.
I asked her why.
"We're in the same agency."
(That's the best!)
They must have met for the 1st time. Is it your 1st time?
- Yes, it's my 1st time meeting him. - It's your 1st time. I see.
- She's so funny. - I'm nervous.
Nice to meet you.
- Please take good care of us. - Okay.
All right.
We brought out all of the partners including Jimin and MinA.
We're going to check the partners' levels first.
Getting a good partner is important, but levels are important too.
(The levels are chosen randomly.)
- Right. - This is important.
- Jong Hyun came out of this room. - Yes.
Let's check Jong Hyun's level first.
I wonder what his level is.
(Jong Hyun chose the first door.)
(What is his level?)
It's Level Four.
(Jong Hyun is Level 4.)
- That's high. - That's high.
My goodness, that's great.
Next.
We'll check Seungri's level.
- We'll check Seungri's level. - Seungri.
(Seungri came out of the second door. What is his level?)
(Seungri, Level 2)
- That's low. - It's only two.
- His level isn't... - That's low.
- It's pretty low if it's two. - It's low.
Next.
By the way, why are we standing here? We keep getting pushed.
(By the way, why are we standing here? We keep getting pushed.)
(They stood at the wrong spot to begin with.)
(This is how little by little,)
(they are getting farther away.)
- We keep getting pushed away. - Hey.
Why did we stand here?
(Exactly. Why is this happening to you two?)
- By the way, - It keeps...
- only I can move down. - We have to move down together.
- We keep going back and forth. - We keep getting pushed.
- You two make a great couple. - Exactly. Why...
Ji Hyo, you should lock arms with him and go down.
They are the Gimbap Couple.
- Jong Kook. - You know what?
- Let's go to that side. - You two look great.
We keep getting in the way.
- Roll it nicely - This is weird.
You two make a great couple.
- We keep getting pushed down. - That's so true.
All right. We'll move on.
- This time, it was Yu Mi's, right? - Yes.
It's Yu Mi's. We'll check her level.
(What is Yu Mi's level?)
I think it might be high.
(Yu Mi has the highest level, Level 6.)
(Yu Mi has the highest level?)
- That's so high. - Yu Mi.
(Crowding over her)
- It's not that. - Seriously.
- I really need you. - I'm serious.
- She has the highest level. - Yu Mi.
- Yu Mi, when we choose partners... - Yu Mi.
- I was going to choose you. - Yu Mi.
- I have been her fan too. - My gosh.
Goodness.
She and I are like family. I'm serious.
- Why is she your family? - I'm serious.
She's Level Six.
- That's amazing. - It's hard to choose Level Six.
Next up is Yu Ri.
(It's time to reveal Yu Ri's level.)
- We'll check her level. - Is it Level Six?
We'll check her level.
(What is Yu Ri's level?)
(Yu Ri has the lowest level, Level 1.)
- Level One? - Gosh.
- Gosh. - Goodness, what is she going to do?
But Yu Ri and Jae Seok look great together.
- I'm serious. - You are perfect for each other.
You're Level One.
That's perfect.
Level One is considered quite low.
All right.
- Is this your door, MinA? - Yes.
- Let's see MinA's level. - I hope it's high.
(It has to be high.)
(What is the fifth guest, MinA's level?)
Level Three.
(MinA's level is 3.)
- It's not bad. - It's pretty high.
- Jimin's level... - She's Level Five.
She's Level Five.
(Jimin's level is 5.)
(Nice, my level is high.)
Those with high levels, Levels 5 and 6...
We're desperate to team up with them.
The thing is,
Kwang Soo and I go back a long way.
It's been more than 10 years.
I knew him before he became Asia Prince.
When he was a nobody.
(When he was a nobody)
That's right.
(Asia Prince used to be a nobody.)
You knew him when he was a nobody.
These days, he's so stylish.
What was he like when he was a nobody?
He was pathetic.
(She tells the truth.)
He was.
She was your fan even back then.
Really?
When you got married,
I was so sad.
For the first time in my life...
- Really? - Seriously?
Just like when Brad Pitt got married...
(It made her as sad.)
- When Jae Seok got married... - They're too different.
They're too different. Hold on.
- Why would you bring up Brad Pitt? - She's making fun of you.
You shouldn't be so happy. She's just making fun of you.
- Brad Pitt... - She's making fun of him.
Brad Pitt.
- Is it true? - It's true.
Brad Pitt looked way better than Jae Seok...
- even when he played an old man. - Benjamin Button...
- Stop it. - He looked way better.
Gosh.
You deserve a flying kick.
(The Curious Case of Yu Mi's Taste)
Anyway...
We're so happy to have you here.
In addition,
- she's Level 6. - Level 6.
We're so grateful.
And we have Jong Hyun here too.
- He's handsome. - Level Four.
That hairstyle suits you very well.
- Thank you. - It looks nice.
Hairstyles...
What's important is how your face looks.
- I think so too. - That's right.
It's like that.
Some people look good whether their hair is long...
- or short. - Right.
- Or even all shaved off. - Of course.
Do you want to try an acrostic poem? It's been a while.
(Show off your charms.)
- I'll try with "Jeon So Min". - "Jeon So Min".
(An acrostic poem dedicated to me?)
(She steps forward.)
You don't have to step forward.
She looked annoyingly happy.
(There she goes again.)
All right. "Jeon".
Jeon...
I didn't know this before.
(I didn't know this before.)
- That's a nice start. - She's touching her hair again.
"So".
(I didn't know this before.)
So Min, you look very beautiful in real life.
She looks beautiful.
(Are you asking me out?)
"Min".
(So Min, you look very beautiful in real life.)
Min.
I'll make sure you get to the highest level today.
(Min, I'll make sure you get to the highest level today.)
(Min, you'll get to the highest level today.)
What's wrong with him?
(He can't stand it.)
What's with him? Hey.
What is wrong with him?
"I'll make sure you get to the highest level."
My goodness.
I can't stand these things.
(Was it too much?)
It makes me cringe.
Let me try too.
(So Min is sentimental today.)
- What do you mean? - Let me come up with a poem.
(So Min is a poet today.)
So suddenly?
- Let me try. - Go ahead.
"Hong".
Hong, hong, hong...
(Was it a bad idea?)
"Jong".
My feelings for Jong Hyun are...
(My feelings for Jong Hyun are...)
(My feelings for you...)
"Hyun".
(What is it?)
Still going on.
(They're still going on.)
(The other members react aggressively.)
Why are you hitting me?
Why me?
(The set is in shock.)
Gosh.
It's so annoying.
(With the set full of love, someone looks troubled.)
(He remains still.)
Next up is Seungri.
I heard...
Seungri is joining the army this year.
- Yes. - That's what I heard.
- This year? - Yes.
- When? - Early this year.
- Early this year? - Yes.
It's soon.
And he's still working.
I'll work hard until then.
And then I'll hand over the baton...
to the other members.
He sounds so humble today. Last time, he was like,
"G-DRAGON, are you watching?"
Now that he's joining the army soon, he doesn't say that anymore.
(Sad)
(Last time, Seungri couldn't contain his excitement.)
(White Skull Division, are you watching?)
(Victory Division, are you watching?)
(He didn't hesitate to declare war.)
(He was full of spirit.)
Now that he's joining the army soon, he doesn't say that anymore.
- He sounds so humble. - The others will be out soon.
And it's slowly starting to feel real.
His voice has become so calm.
He sounds so humble.
His voice sounded completely different last year.
He was like, "Are you watching?"
I'll be humble. White Skull Division,
how are you doing?
(I send my regards before enlistment.)
Insert the clips from the last time.
It was so funny.
Last time, it was cheeky of me.
You never know. I might end up in those divisions.
You never know.
Who knows?
If that happens,
they might be like, "Last year, you said..."
White Skull Division,
I wish you all a happy new year.
Take care.
His voice has changed completely.
He is very wise.
The final level-up race,
Catch-up Partner.
The teams will compete in two rounds.
After each round, the team in 1st place will go up 2 levels,
and the team in 2nd place, 1 level.
When anyone gets to Level 10,
that person becomes the final winner...
and the race will be over.
The winning team will receive a tremendous prize.
Defense is important too.
If Haha and So Min win two times in a row,
the race will be over.
- Defense is important. - Really?
- However... - However?
If no one gets to Level 10 before the mission is complete,
the final winners will be determined by the roulette wheel.
The combined levels within the team...
will determine the number of slots they get.
Level is everything.
(How will this race end?)
- Let's decide teams. - Okay.
I'm only interested in Level 3 and above.
The rules are simple.
Each person will announce the requirements,
and the others will try to meet them.
- Anyone can try? - Yes.
Let's start from So Min, Level Six.
- What are your requirements? - Tell us.
(What does she want her partner to be like?)
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
Inside, I'm thinking,
"What is she doing?"
(Their reactions are forced.)
She suddenly said, "Hi."
Hi.
Why are you so worked up?
What's with you?
I'm Level Zero.
I can't believe you're still holding on to hope.
(Wait and see.)
I'm Jae Seok.
He's so optimistic.
My level is high. I like humorous people.
I want my partner to be good at role-playing.
(She wants a partner who is humorous and good at role-playing.)
(Role-playing? Should I try?)
Excuse me.
- Food delivery. - Hello.
Thank you.
(The delivery guy is handsome.)
(Did you order a partner?)
Excuse me. We ordered it. Come here.
(Interrupting)
It's our food. What are you doing?
Come here.
Why did you go there?
Put it here.
You don't recognize your regular customer?
It's our food.
All right. So Min will say a line.
- And we will react to it. - Okay.
We're in a cafe.
I'm waiting for my boyfriend.
(So Min is waiting for her boyfriend in a cafe.)
(This is my chance.)
(She enters the cafe.)
Is he not here yet?
- Honey! - So Min!
- Honey! - Honey!
- "Honey"? - Honey!
So Min!
Honey!
(Swarming)
- Honey! - Sorry I'm late.
Honey, I'm sorry I'm late.
- I've been here since yesterday. - Honey.
- Sorry. - Sorry.
I'm not interested in religion.
- That's not it. - Honey.
- Sorry. - You and I...
Who are you?
- Honey. - Who are you?
(Honey)
(Her real boyfriend appears.)
I'm her boyfriend. Who are you?
(I'm her boyfriend. Who are you?)
(I'm Level 4, honey. Stay away from low levels.)
- Let us be a team. - Hold on.
(Since both our levels are high, shouldn't we team up?)
Honey, what are you doing?
(What is my boyfriend doing here?)
What about me?
Hey, come get the empty bowls. What are you doing here?
(The bowls are at the door.)
- Collect your bowls. - Over here.
What were you doing there?
Okay.
They're over here.
This is strange.
- Please try something else. - Why isn't he here yet?
Come up with something else.
Why isn't he here yet?
My boyfriend is very handsome.
(I'm here.)
(Then I'm not your boyfriend.)
(Jae Seok tries...)
(but then gives up.)
(He is definitely not my boyfriend.)
- Come back. - Is she allowed to do that?
(The other candidates support Jae Seok's decision.)
Is she allowed to do that?
- Is it okay? - She can do that.
- Can she really do that? - She can.
Suddenly...
All right. Fine.
Situation number three.
What about a guesthouse?
- A class trip? - A class trip.
A class trip.
She's alone?
She's waiting for others.
(So Min is drinking with her friends at a guesthouse.)
- Gosh, I drank too much. - She's drunk.
(Dizzy)
So Min, are you okay?
(I'm a senior. A freshman drank too much?)
(It's the popular student, Kwang Soo.)
You're a driver, right?
(She didn't call you.)
Come with us.
We called you.
He's a driver.
What were you doing?
They keep getting interrupted.
(So Min will never meet her boyfriend.)
(So Min tries to focus.)
Let me try.
(The handsome guy, Jong Hyun, steps up.)
I'm getting drunk.
How long has Jong Hyun been sitting there?
Jong Hyun.
(We have to stop him.)
Jong Hyun, I'm not feeling so well.
Do you want to go for a walk?
(Do you want some fresh air?)
- Sure. - I'm...
(What if they become a team?)
Everyone is watching. You go first...
Hello, Professor Hong.
(He is not a senior student.)
(Professor Hong is here too?)
(We didn't call for a driver.)
- Security guard. - Security guard?
I'm not feeling well.
- I'm... - Are you done?
Let me collect the bowls.
(The delivery guy came all the way to the guesthouse.)
Let me collect the bowls. Are you done?
That restaurant is so popular.
So Min will pick...
her partner.
- She is Level Six. - Seungri would be good.
- Level Four would be enough. - Right.
Jong Hyun...
I'll pick someone who was active in the role-playing.
(The old boyfriend, Seok Jin)
(The handsome guy, Jong Hyun)
(The guy who knows he is not handsome, Jae Seok)
(The handsome delivery guy, Seungri)
(Among the four...)
I pick Jong Hyun.
This is not okay.
- The high levels should team up. - Gosh.
Even if I lose...
She just picked someone with a high level.
I had to carry those bowls around all day long!
(Everyone is only interested in those with high levels.)
- I had to carry those bowls around! - You made mistakes.
- Next up is Yu Mi. - I have to try.
(What does Yu Mi want her partner to be like?)
Yu Mi!
- Whatever she wants... - I want to try too.
I want someone who can think fast...
because it'd help me win.
We prepared a game.
Water Cham Cham Cham.
(Water Cham Cham Cham)
Water Cham Cham Cham to find the fastest person.
The rules are the same as usual.
But instead of hitting the other person with a toy hammer,
splash water from the glass.
No one will want to try.
- What are you talking about? - What are you talking about?
(They all want to try.)
(Satisfied)
Like this?
We'll go first.
(Seok Jin versus Jae Seok)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
(The winner gets to attack first.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok gets to attack.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Seok Jin turned his face first.)
Hold on. Why...
(Jae Seok easily wins.)
What was that?
Why did you turn your face?
- My goodness. - Why did you?
(Jae Seok wins.)
- My goodness. - Seok Jin turned his face first.
- I win. - Okay.
(It's Se Chan and Kwang Soo's turn.)
Se Chan versus Kwang Soo?
The winner will compete with Jae Seok.
- It's going to be fun. - Good.
(Serious)
- It's going to be fun. - These cheaters...
- They're cheaters. - Cheater versus cheater.
(Cheater versus cheater)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(It's a big match.)
(Kwang Soo gets to attack.)
Finish it.
(I can't believe I get to watch this big match.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Se Chan looks left.)
(It's Se Chan's turn to attack.)
(He is no easy opponent.)
Se Chan is good at this.
(Excited)
(Se Chan attacks.)
What?
(What's going on?)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Splash)
Okay.
(Se Chan baits Kwang Soo...)
(and attacks.)
(Cheating is my specialty.)
- Good job. - Okay!
- What happened? - You lost.
You turned your face.
You looked right.
(The audience is thrilled.)
- Did I do something wrong? - You did a good job.
- Cham, Cham, Cham. - Nice!
- Okay! - Good job.
I had to be fast.
It happened so fast.
All right.
I'll finish it at once. There's no need to waste time.
We'll finish it at once.
The winner goes up six levels.
This is the chance.
Jae Seok, your glasses...
Why don't we...
(I have a suggestion.)
Why don't we attack with the pot and defend with the cup?
(Attack with the pot and defend with the cup?)
- What do you say? - Let's get more water.
Come on. Let's do it.
- To your eyes. - Okay.
You don't even drink. "To your eyes"?
(You're making a toast?)
- Be quiet. - "To your eyes"?
I guess that's what he says when he drinks water.
He just wanted to say it.
There's not enough water.
It's okay.
It's not much.
- This is going to be... - That looks good.
You'll have to win.
(There is a lot more water now.)
Even if you cover yourself, you'll still get wet.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok gets to attack.)
- Oh, my. - I have to stop him.
(I have to stop him.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(They turn in the same direction.)
(Splash)
You can't help getting wet.
(Se Chan did try to cover his face,)
(but what?)
You can't help getting wet.
- I did block it. - You did block it.
- It counts. - I blocked it.
You blocked it?
- I saw it. - It didn't get to my eyes.
It didn't get to my eyes.
- He blocked it. - I saw it.
- So you can block it. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok gets to attack.)
Just one try.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(If he wins, he can be Yu Mi's partner.)
(I can't let Jae Seok get a high-level partner.)
(They turn in the same direction.)
(What?)
What did you do?
(He succeeded...)
(but splashed himself with cold water.)
(What did I do?)
(He mixed up offense and defense.)
Why did you do that?
What was that?
He tried to block it.
He thought he was supposed to block it?
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - It looked natural.
- Okay. - He's so bad at games.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok gets to attack again.)
(If he wins, he becomes Yu Mi's partner.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Will Jae Seok manage to level up?)
(I have to stop him.)
(They turn in the same direction.)
(Splash)
(Se Chan fails to block it.)
- Jae Seok wins. - Okay!
(Jae Seok manages to level up.)
Okay.
- The situation has changed. - That was close.
- Next up is Jong Kook. - Me?
This game seems fun.
- I want to do it too. - With female guests?
- I think it'll be fun. - It sounds good.
(Jong Kook wants to partner up with a Water Cham Cham Cham master.)
- Should we try? - Let's try.
- We want to try. - We want to try.
(The ace joins too.)
- Ji Hyo wants to try too. - Ji Hyo wants to try too.
A guy can try too. One more person can join.
(A guy can try too?)
You want to try? Okay.
(I want to be your partner today.)
Okay. Good.
(Jong Kook is the best.)
Good.
- Seungri, you should try too. - Kim Jong Kook!
- Kim Jong Kook! - Come here.
(I'm Level 2. Let me try too.)
Seungri, welcome.
I won't be a bad choice.
(Jimin versus Yu Ri, Seungri versus Ji Hyo,)
(Se Chan versus Kwang Soo)
I can't wait to see how they play this game.
- Right. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Hiding?)
Hold on. Are you sure?
(She introduces a new strategy, hiding her hand.)
She is unbelievable.
I swear!
- This is... - This is not okay.
If that was okay, everybody would play like that.
Jimin. Are you sure?
- I swear. - I saw it from here.
Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Yu Ri gets to attack.)
- Wait. - Not now?
(She instinctively tries to splash water.)
- You have to play Cham Cham Cham. - You have to play Cham Cham Cham.
You can't just splash water.
- She's scary. - You can't just splash water.
- Cham, Cham, Cham. - Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors doesn't mean much.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(They turn in different directions.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jimin gets to attack.)
(Jimin attacks.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(The hand turns left.)
(Yu Ri's face...)
(also turns left.)
I blocked it.
(Jimin attacks quickly.)
(Yu Ri defends more quickly.)
- I blocked it. - She blocked it.
- She blocked it. - Good job.
(You aren't angry, are you?)
- She didn't get hit. - She blocked it.
- Do it fast. - Rock-paper-scissors
(Yu Ri gets to attack.)
Let me fill up the water.
- I'll go first. - Wait.
I understand that you're angry,
- but fill it with water first. - What?
(Awkward)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Her faces turns toward her hand.)
(Splashing)
(Villain Yu Ri knows...)
(how to splash water.)
Were you waiting...
for this?
(Yu Ri's fiery and mean snap shown 5 years ago)
(She still has it.)
- That's incredible. - Her look was intense.
She's done it a lot.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
- Oh, no. - All right.
The way she snaps is...
- She did it a lot in dramas. - sharp.
Isn't it different? Next are...
- Ji Hyo and Seungri. - Seungri.
Ji Hyo isn't easy.
Don't think she's easy.
Will it be Seungri or Ji Hyo?
- Will it be Ji Hyo or Seungri? - Seungri.
Will it be Seungri or Ji Hyo? Or will it be Ji Hyo or Seungri?
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo gets to attack.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Seungri is quite fast.)
- Do we play rock-paper-scissors? - No, it's his turn next.
Keep playing.
Without playing rock-paper-scissors?
(They take turns with Cham, Cham, Cham.)
Okay.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Her head turns toward his hand.)
(Splashing and blocking)
(He attacks fast.)
(She blocks him completely.)
(I'm an ace.)
- Nice. - That was quick.
- That's Ji Hyo. - That was quick.
She blocked it perfectly.
She blocked it completely.
(Ji Hyo is an ace after all.)
(She fits her face inside the pot.)
You're amazing.
Keep playing.
(It's Ji Hyo's attack.)
(He turns the opposite direction.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(She turns toward his hand.)
(Splashing and blocking)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(She blocks it completely.)
- She blocked it. - She did.
- She blocked it. - That was good.
(She's like a human shield.)
Seungri is slow.
- I thought Seungri got slow. - Me too.
He was very slow.
Whoever wins this round will be the final winner.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(He turns toward her hand.)
What's going on?
(Splashing)
(Why is she grabbing the pot?)
(She splashes without giving him a chance to defend.)
Ji Hyo wins.
(Ace Ji Hyo enters the semifinal round.)
Next up are Se Chan and Kwang Soo.
It's fun when they compete.
- You start right away. - Come closer.
(They're more serious than before.)
I'll stand like this.
(Their mission is Cham, Cham, Cham with legs.)
(What's wrong with them?)
Like this?
What's going on? Is it a leg fight?
That's great.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo gets to attack.)
Okay.
Let's see if it's okay or not.
(He attacks with confidence.)
(Se Chan's defense is a success.)
I could read him.
Do it right away.
(They're both passionate.)
Which way will you go?
- This way. - That way? Okay.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(He turns toward his hand.)
(Thanks to Jae Seok, it splashes on him.)
(He's quicker than either of them.)
(Jae Seok assists the attack.)
(Why are you involved?)
He won.
(With Jae Seok's help,)
(Se Chan moves up to the semifinal round.)
(Jae Seok speeds things up since they're running out of time.)
It should be over.
We're already running late.
All right, Se Chan will move on...
- to the semifinal. - Okay.
- I'm going to the semifinal. - Okay.
Next are...
Yu Ri and Ji Hyo.
It'll be a neck and neck game.
- It will be... - Tables may turn.
worth watching.
(She blocks any water splashing.)
(Ji Hyo is a human shield.)
(Her attacks pierce through all kinds of shields.)
(Yu Ri is an expert in splashing water.)
This is practically the final round.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo gets to attack.)
(She checks where the water is.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(She turns away from her hand.)
(Turning)
(Yu Ri's attack is quick as it's a big match.)
(Ji Hyo turns toward Yu Ri's hand.)
(Blocking and splashing)
(She turns into a human shield.)
(However, there was a malfunction.)
Wait, are you okay?
- What's wrong? - Are you okay?
(She hit her tooth with the pot.)
Are you bleeding?
(I'm okay.)
We're playing this game to pick our partners, right?
(We're playing this game to pick our partners, right?)
I almost thought the first round was over.
As they were playing...
- We haven't officially started. - Goodness.
- I feel competitive. - It makes me feel competitive.
- Do we play again? - Yes.
(Ji Hyo attacks.)
(Yu Ri turns toward Ji Hyo's hand.)
(Splashing)
Ji Hyo wins.
(Ji Hyo isn't only a human shield.)
(Ji Hyo splashes water quickly as well.)
(Unfortunately, Yu Ri is eliminated and Ji Hyo enters the final round.)
Here's the final round.
It's Ji Hyo versus Se Chan.
Jimin hasn't done it yet.
- She hasn't? - She hasn't done it.
She's Level Five.
- There is Level 5. - Level 5 remains.
There is Level Five.
- Is there Level Five? - Here we go.
Leve 4 and 5 are the same.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(He's very slow.)
(Okay, I'll lose.)
Hey, Se Chan.
- What did you do? - What?
- What's wrong with you? - Let me go.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook are a couple again.)
Why did you play like that?
- My goodness. - I couldn't help it.
I couldn't move.
- You won. - It can be confusing.
What on earth? Okay.
- That was so strange. - Goodness, Se Chan.
Jimin is under the spotlight now.
- I'm sure of it. - It's Jimin.
Jimin, please step forward.
- Jimin is Level Five. - Yes.
I'm Level Five.
I'm addicted to acrostic poems.
(She wants someone who makes excellent acrostic poems.)
You get bonus points if you use my name.
Of course.
- All right. - With two syllables?
No, I'm Shin Jimin.
- Shin? - Yes, Shin Jimin.
- Do we have to include Shin? - Yes.
Can you do it with Shin Jimin?
"Shin".
Shin Jimin.
(Why are you calling me?)
"Ji".
I'm so sick and tired of it.
- All right. - It's boring.
(That's enough.)
- I'm sick of it. - Leave.
(There's no point in listening.)
- I'm sick of it. - There's "min".
- There's "min". - Forget it.
- I'm sick of it. - "Min" remains.
- Kwang Soo. - I'll go.
- All right. - Great.
"Shin".
Shin Jimin...
"Ji".
Protect her.
(She's speechless.)
She's the one that serves and protects.
He's eliminated.
(She's firm on eliminating him.)
You're eliminated.
- It's terrible. - It's terrible.
She's Level Five. This is a rare opportunity.
Can you do it with "Shin Jimin"?
Shin Jimin looks very smart.
(You look very smart.)
- "Ji". - You seem intelligent.
(That's quite good.)
- "Min". - Who's Minister of Civil Affairs?
(Minister of Civil Affairs?)
I'm asking you.
Do you know who the Minister of Civil Affairs is?
(It's a new type of acrostic poem.)
(Everyone is satisfied with it.)
That's funny.
I approve of it.
(Se Chan and Ji Min become partners.)
All right.
- Aren't you Level One? - Yes.
How about this, Seok Jin?
Choose one of the three rooms.
Go inside one of them.
- Three of you stand by the door. - Is it random?
- It is random. - That sounds good.
Seok Jin, go into one of the three rooms.
This is random.
It can't be helped if you're the one.
Please open the door starting with Yu Ri.
(Yu Ri selects the first door. Will there be Seok Jin?)
(Yu Ri opens the door.)
I'm so relieved.
She said that she's relieved.
That's fortunate.
Two of you will open the door at the same time.
(Seungri gets selected.)
Seok Jin got lucky.
(Seok Jin and Seungri become partners.)
You're Level Four?
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri become partners.)
She's Level One.
Change into your team uniform, and we'll start the race.
Come on.
(Final Couples)
(A quest has been discovered.)
Everyone, it's a couple game.
Here's the first mission where you can gain a level.
The first mission is Balloon, Stop Right There.
Each couple randomly chooses a pair of shoes.
They start simultaneously from the opposite side of one another.
The first couple to...
pop the other couple's two balloons wins.
The first place winner gains two levels.
The second place gains one level.
(First place winner gains 2, second place winner gains 1.)
(Tournament Table)
I'll feel the weight first.
Goodness.
- Is one of them heavier? - This one is lighter.
- Which one? - This one is lighter.
- Which one? - You choose that one?
Okay, you grabbed it.
- She grabbed it, so it's over. - I think this is heavier.
Let's look inside.
These are great.
What about ours?
Look at this.
Those are better.
- Are these bad? - They're okay.
Ours are better.
- These are better. - Ours are better.
- These are better. - Are these bad?
Which ones are better?
I think both of them are bad.
Get ready for Round One.
- All right. - Let's go.
- Get ready. - You can do it.
You can do it.
(These two have strength and experience.)
(Will Seok Jin and Seungri win?)
Let's start right away.
(Or will Kwang Soo and Yu Ri win?)
Start.
We'll win.
(They must catch up with the other couple.)
It's good.
Take long steps.
(Going in circles)
Goodness.
Straw shoes are a bit quicker.
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri chase after them.)
We're faster.
We almost caught up.
(Seok Jin and Seungri are at risk and almost caught.)
(Thud)
We caught them.
Come on.
(Let's catch up to them.)
Goodness.
- No. - Get them.
- Go. - Hurry.
- Keep going. - Hurry.
Hurry up.
We're almost there.
(Yu Ri and Kwang Soo are right behind them.)
- What do we do? - We're almost there.
They almost caught them.
(Where are you going?)
(They will catch up to them soon.)
(The first balloon is popped.)
(If they pop one more, Seok Jin and Seungri are eliminated.)
(Slipping)
- What's going on? - Let's go.
- I don't know. - Hurry.
(He falls down again at a crucial moment.)
- Hey, get up. - Let's go.
It's so slippery.
(The couple can't control their bodies.)
- Hurry. - Go.
It's such a chaos.
- They caught them. - Hey.
(Slipping)
My goodness.
(They fall for the 3rd time.)
You can still do it.
Hurry up and go.
Hurry up.
(Legs, keep moving and save me.)
My goodness.
Let's go now.
Be careful.
It's so slippery.
(Panting)
(We won't miss them this time.)
(Popping)
Okay.
(They clear the last balloon.)
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri win.)
It's so difficult.
(They're exhausted.)
(We burnt everything.)
- We won. - Next round is...
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo versus So Min and Jong Hyun.
We're up next.
- Is it us? - Yes.
We're in trouble.
We're competing against the strongest.
(Their opponents are Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
I bet Ji Hyo will do well.
She's quite good.
(So Min and Jong Hyun wear fur slippers.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo wear straw shoes.)
Let's go.
Do we have to wear gloves while holding hands?
(The love frog returns.)
Stop saying nonsense.
What did So Min say?
What's wrong with So Min?
(A warning alert for love frog)
You guys look great.
Interlock the fingers.
Interlocking the fingers is important.
(On the other hand...)
This game is already over.
They're the same.
This couple looks so strong.
They're the most overpowered couple.
(The combination of Jong Kook and Ji Hyo?)
(So Min and Jong Hyun versus Jong Kook and Ji Hyo)
I'm nervous.
Get ready.
Start.
Jong Kook will show us how it's done.
- They're fast. - So Min.
- So Min. - Look at them.
- So Min. - Look at So Min.
(They're hopping.)
Don't slip.
So Min.
Jong Hyun.
Why are you so bad?
- Jong Hyun. - Keep going, So Min.
Don't slip.
Jong Hyun is terrible.
Jong Hyun is being dragged by So Min.
Jong Hyun.
- Jong Hyun. - I can do it.
(He only follows So Min.)
You said that you were confident.
You said that you can do it well.
- It's tiring. - So Min.
Don't slip.
You're faster.
- Never mind. - They are faster.
- That's right. - Jong Hyun.
They look like slave hunters.
- Seriously. - Hey.
- They're like slave hunters. - They look really scary.
Jong Kook is on a hunt right now.
(Love slaves, stop right there.)
- Hey. - They're like slave hunters.
They look really scary.
I thought they were shooting a Korean historical drama.
Are you holding real hammers?
They look frightening.
(We're going to catch them.)
- Jong Hyun. - We can do it.
Ji Hyo.
(He's worried for her.)
You look like a real couple.
You look great.
- You look good together. - You look great.
(Slave hunters fall in love while catching slaves.)
- Interlock your fingers. - Interlock your fingers.
(We cheer for the slave hunter couple.)
They're coming.
Be careful.
(Teasing)
You can't do that.
(Disturbing isn't allowed.)
(Don't you see Ji Hyo behind you?)
(They're jealous of their romance.)
Here they come again.
Let's sing "One Man".
(Being loud)
(There's one man who loved you very much)
(She gets into the song.)
Stop enjoying it.
Stop singing along and skate.
(She starts singing love songs instead of chasing.)
He feels shy.
He's blushing.
(They tease Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
Hurry up, So Min.
It's so difficult.
- It's a fight of stamina. - It's so difficult.
Keep going.
This is how...
(Goodness)
- You're doing a good job. - Hurry.
(What will be the fate of So Min?)
This is how...
- You're doing a good job. - Hurry.
(Slave hunters chase after them faster than ever.)
Here they come.
They smelled blood.
(So Min laid out a bait.)
- Oh, no. - Here they come.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo take the bait.)
Here they come.
They smelled blood.
(The predator couple arrives.)
Stop right there.
(Stop right there.)
(Falling)
We got it.
- Wait. - Come on.
(What will be the fate of So Min's team?)
(Popping)
Keep going.
Keep going. You must go.
You must keep going.
(Popping)
Love won.
(They catch the slaves in love.)
It's okay.
(Good job.)
We tried our best.
Love won.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo couple wins.)
- The power of love. - Love is great.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo enter the semifinal.)
Next is Se Chan and Jimin versus...
- Haha and MinA. Get ready. - Okay.
We can do it.
Wait, MinA.
- Where's MinA's manager? - Why?
She's wearing her helmet like this.
Teach her how to wear it correctly.
She's so cute.
I never saw that before.
Let's go. Do you have strong endurance?
Get ready.
(Haha and MinA versus Se Chan and Jimin)
I don't know who will win.
They're good.
(A competition between...)
(Se Chan with strong legs and sly Haha)
Haha, you don't need to run.
(Slipping)
(MinA slides as soon as they start.)
Come here.
- That's not allowed. - You can't do that.
(She falls for the second time.)
Keep going.
(She hugs her balloon.)
What's going on?
(She's never seen someone like her before.)
Keep going forward.
Why are you coming to me?
Get up.
(Dragging)
Keep going.
Keep going forward.
(Popping)
(Running away)
- He abandoned her. - You can't leave her.
- You can't let go of her hand. - You can't leave her.
MinA, you must get up.
Give me some time to get up.
Stop talking and go, MinA.
- Start. - Let's go.
1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2.
This is so scary.
Who are you?
- Are you a celebrity? - I am.
"Are you a celebrity"?
- It's over. - Who are you?
- MinA gave up. - Are you a celebrity?
Okay.
(The last balloon pops.)
(Se Chan and Jimin win.)
That was the worst.
- What's wrong with MinA? - MinA can't...
even walk.
(What kind of person are you?)
She's the real deal.
Next round is Kwang Soo and Yu Ri...
- versus Jae Seok and Yu Mi. - Yu Mi.
Okay, it's us.
Let's go, Yu Mi.
(Jae Seok and Yu Mi versus Kwang Soo and Yu Ri)
I expect this round to be a dirty game.
Do anything to win.
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri wear straw shoes.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Are they not slippery?
(Jae Seok and Yu Mi wear fur slippers.)
Start.
Let's go.
- They're fast. - Hold my hand tight.
It's over if you fall down.
- Don't fall. - Okay.
Kwang Soo's torso isn't moving.
(His torso is stiff.)
(What's the look on his face?)
- Kwang Soo. - What's wrong, Kwang Soo?
Why are you walking like that?
- He looks like Ki Bong. - It's Ki Bong.
- It's Ki Bong. - It's Ki Bong.
(It's Ki Bong's younger brother Kwang Bong.)
What are you looking at, Kwang Soo?
Breathe through your nose.
My feet are freezing.
- They're coming, Jae Seok. - They're coming.
They're coming.
Turn.
(They catch up.)
(They just have to pop the balloons!)
Good job.
(Falling)
(They fail multiple times...)
(and fall.)
- Run. - What do we do?
- Get up. - It's okay.
- You're safe. - Run.
(It's a narrow escape.)
Get up.
- Hurry up. - Whose toy hammer is this?
Hold hands.
Gosh, Yu Ri.
- Hold hands. - That was close.
- Gosh, Yu Ri. - You almost had them.
- Where? - Come to the side.
Where are you going?
- Oh, dear. - What are you going?
Oh, dear.
(They barely survive and rehydrate themselves.)
(Kwang Soo gets water splashed on him.)
(They drink...)
(some water as well.)
Why does this game never end?
(They're exhausted as well.)
(When does this end?)
(Let's start over again.)
They're coming.
Ki Bong's counterattack.
(Ki Bong attacks again.)
(He caught up!)
Hey.
(I'll end it this time.)
(Floundering)
Hey!
(Popping)
(There's one balloon left.)
(This is a dangerous moment.)
(They can't run away anymore!)
(Last pop)
Oh, dear.
(They collapse.)
Good job.
(That was a great match.)
We won, Yu Ri.
Can you call 911?
We're only Level One right now.
(She must be exhausted.)
This is insane.
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri advance to the final.)
- Where is it? - The flag.
- Get set, ready... - I have to go pee.
(They're about to start.)
- This... - Goodness.
I have to use the bathroom right now.
Use that urgency to run, Se Chan.
- I know that feeling. - You need to go.
It's time.
Se Chan has to use the bathroom.
I really have to go.
(In times like these,)
(things get complicated even more.)
(He goes in circles, and he has to go even more now.)
I feel sorry for you, Se Chan.
- I know. - Oh, dear.
- Oh, dear. - Poor Se Chan.
- Let's go. - Se Chan!
- They're coming. - They got caught.
- They're almost there. - Come!
(Popping)
They got caught.
(Gasping)
Hey.
- They ran out of energy. - Right.
They used a lot of energy in the previous game.
Let's start now!
Come here, Yu Ri! Come!
(Does he want to play the finals right away?)
Come, Yu Ri!
- Where are you, Yu Ri? - Okay, I'm coming.
- Hurry up. - Okay, I'm coming.
- What's going on? - We have to start now. Hurry!
- While they're tired. - Hurry up.
- Do we get straw shoes? - Where's the box?
(I'll pick the shoes. Give me something.)
- They don't have straw shoes. - We'll go left.
Get out. Get out!
(Get out, Se Chan and Jimin!)
Get out of the rink!
- Don't go. - Get out.
- Don't go! - I need to go.
- Don't go. - Let me go.
Don't go.
- Start, Kwang Soo! - Don't go.
- Start right away. - Get started.
- Take it on your way out. - Okay.
Ready...
(The finals start.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are the best in Running Man.)
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are mad.
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri are resolved.)
If you lose now, it's a disgrace, Kwang Soo.
(The finals start!)
My legs don't move.
That's good. His legs don't move.
- You have the advantage. - Will they finally lose?
They're fast though.
(They still won't lose.)
(What?)
- It's Ki Bong! - It's Ki Bong!
Ki Bong!
They're coming.
Kwang Soo.
We have to win. Run.
(This is his specialty.)
They're fast. Kwang Soo is fast.
(He looks funny, but he's fast.)
(Kwang Soo chases them down.)
He's fast.
- Are you okay? - I'm fine.
Come here.
She's mad now.
(They have no energy left, but they speed up as well.)
They're coming!
Kwang Soo.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are mad.
You're almost there.
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri catch up.)
They caught up.
Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri can taste victory!)
They caught up.
This is over.
If you win, you'll be Level Three.
(If they win, they'll be Level 3 as a couple.)
(Will the underdogs win?)
(Hitting)
What's wrong with this?
(He hits the balloon with a hammer, but it doesn't pop.)
This...
- It didn't pop. - Oh, dear.
(Why does something like this only happen to Kwang Soo?)
Why won't it pop?
(Why is the balloon strong too?)
Why is the balloon so hard?
(The balloon is strong like its owner.)
(They're exhausted.)
Run.
Why won't it pop?
(The unyielding pursuit continues.)
It popped.
(The first balloon pops.)
It's over now.
- They're so fit. - It popped.
Run away!
(Hitting)
(How dare you...)
(Kwang Soo provokes him,)
(and Yu Ri attacks suddenly.)
Pop it. It worked!
(Her toy hammer flies away.)
(The last balloon pops. Kwang Soo and Yu Ri win.)
I'm relieved.
- Are you cold? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri gain 2 levels. Jong Kook and Ji Hyo gain 1.)
- I'm relieved they won. - I know. It's a relief.
Kwang Soo, you're now Level Two.
Congratulations.
(He's only Level 2.)
Yes. I'm finally Level Two!
This is the beginning!
(He has a positive attitude.)
He's still Level Two. After all that.
Kwang Soo.
One of you can gain a level.
Who do you want it to be?
(Only one of them can advance to the next level.)
- Do we have to decide now? - Take it.
(Take it.)
No.
- Later on... - You're warm.
How warm!
(He's only nice to his woman.)
- This is fun. - What a warm man!
Love power!
[VIU Ver] SBS E436 Running Man
"RPG Level Up Final Race : Catch-up Partners"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
It's a full moon.
It looks real.
- It's pretty. - It is.
It's pretty.
It's so pretty. They made it so well.
This is the last mission to achieve Level 10.
It's Level Up: King of Chairs.
- "King of Chairs"? - "King of Chairs"?
"King of Chairs"?
It's a couple race to steal the chairs.
There are pairs of chairs in various locations...
with numbers on them.
You must find the chairs and sit within the designated time.
If you can't find seats, you'll be eliminated.
Right away?
- Yes, right away. - Do chairs...
- disappear every round? - Oh, my goodness.
- This... - We have to find chairs to sit on.
With each round, two chairs will be taken out.
- Two? - If there's more than one couple,
the couple whose couple bracelet breaks first...
has to move on to a different location.
It's not name tag elimination.
You have to break the bracelets.
- Here's an important rule. - What is it?
With the conclusion of each round, the couples still in the race...
- will vote. - What?
They'll vote for a leader.
The leader can eliminate one of the couples.
(The leader can eliminate one couple.)
How many people get eliminated at once then?
Two couples will get eliminated each round.
- Two couples? - I see.
- Because we vote. - Right.
Each couple will put on the bracelet.
(The final quest has begun. Please try your best.)
(There are 7 couples in Round 1.)
Ready...
- Which direction do we go? - Start here.
- Let's go. - Set...
What's this?
- I'm scared. - There's one.
- Where? - There.
(There's one over there.)
There's one.
- There's one. - Where?
- There's one here. - Go straight.
(Se Chan and Jimin head for Chair 1.)
Sit down.
- Sit down. - Sit.
Sit. Let's fight.
Come. Come at me!
- Keep going. - Where?
- Give it up. - What's this?
- We're in trouble. Hurry. - Is this how it goes?
- Why? - Do you want to fight?
(So Min and Jong Hyun are after Chair 1.)
They're fighting.
Don't do that!
- No. - Stop it.
We have no other possibility.
- No. - Sit down.
(He uses his long arm to attack from behind.)
Sit down.
- Hey. - No.
- Pull. - No.
Don't block us!
(What's the result of this intense fight?)
No way.
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri are looking for another set of chairs.)
- I should've taken out my insoles. - You have insoles?
It's too high.
Why do you have them now?
- They're so high. - Go.
- Are there chairs? - They're here!
(They're here!)
(They find Chair 2.)
Sit down!
(They throw their bodies on Chair 2.)
- Are there chairs that way? - Yes.
- What's this? - I can't do this.
I have to take my insoles out.
You have insoles?
(She takes off her insoles, and her competitiveness is on.)
When did you put them on?
Throw them out.
(She's resolved to win.)
(That's high.)
Goodness.
(Good thing she didn't fall.)
We can't afford to care about anything else.
You had insoles.
(She ran this fast with the insoles.)
I have to use these later.
(See you later, insoles.)
Where are they?
- There are chairs. - There they are.
(They find Chair 3.)
- Where? - We have to keep going.
- Where? - Where are they?
We're going to get eliminated in Round One.
Where are they?
There they are.
- Where? - There they are.
- Let's sit. - They're cushions.
Let's sit.
(They run 300m and sit on Chair 4.)
I'm so tired.
- I almost died. - Me too.
- There they are. - Let's slow down.
We're almost there.
There are two sets.
There are seats.
- There are? - Yes.
- Where? - Hurry up.
Why are there seats?
- There are. - Why are there seats?
There are seats.
- This is strange. - What's this?
Are they fighting down there?
I see.
They're fighting over chairs.
Give up.
We can't.
I can't.
You're persistent.
(It's been 3 minutes.)
(Jong Hyun tries to ride on Se Chan's back.)
Hold on. Time out.
- Time out. - Give it up.
That's enough.
- Leave. - Go.
(They defend their chairs fervently.)
Goodbye. Go.
Where is Seok Jin?
(They look for a weaker opponent.)
We have to look for weak people.
Weak people.
Why...
would they waste their energy here?
(Se Chan defended himself from Jong Hyun.)
- Did you see that? - I did.
- Did you see Jong Hyun? - He was so strong.
He's strong,
but he doesn't have any skills.
He just uses his strength.
He has a strong lower body.
He got on my back.
His lower body was strong.
(He's a generous person who compliments his opponent.)
I have good legs too, so I fended him off.
(That was the point of this.)
People can't withstand that.
(He's proud of his legs.)
I beat Jong Hyun. You saw that, right?
- I did. - He couldn't rip it. We won.
- Who's that? - Is somebody coming?
It's Jae Seok.
Where's Seok Jin by the way?
(They walk towards Jae Seok's Chair 4.)
You're here now?
- Who is it? - You can't be walking.
- What? - Are you on a date?
Hey.
(They were about to pass.)
(He attacks out of nowhere.)
- What are you doing? - Hey.
(Jong Hyun is as sneaky as So Min.)
This isn't right.
You should go after Seok Jin.
- No, go that way. Hurry. - Go that way.
Jae Seok is Level Zero.
We're Level Zero.
This is like taking candy from a child.
How evil.
This isn't right.
This...
Where's the next one?
- Here. - There they are.
- Not this. - No, no.
- Go. - Yes, leave.
- Can I have your glove? - Go.
- Oh, dear. - Go.
- It ripped. - It did?
- It ripped. - It did.
It ripped.
(The bracelet ripped when they were getting up.)
- You have to move on. - What?
- It ripped. - When did that happen?
It ripped.
We told them to go.
It ripped as we were getting up.
There's one minute left.
- Jae Seok. - There's no time.
There's no time.
- This is not fair. - This isn't it.
This happened as we were getting up.
(They get new bracelets and move on.)
- I'm relieved. - There's no need to hurry.
Right?
- Goodness. - Jae Seok.
What do we do, Yu Mi?
I didn't rip it on purpose.
- It just ripped, right? - Yes.
That's their fortune.
We have to hold hands.
There they are.
We have to rip it.
(They'll get eliminated if they don't rip a bracelet.)
- They're coming. Hold on. - They're coming.
Get ready, everybody.
We're in trouble.
They're coming.
Hide it.
They're passing by.
Hold on. They're going for the male-male couple.
(They don't even look at Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
(They're impenetrable.)
- What are you doing? - What's wrong?
- Why? - What are you doing?
- What's this? - We can't stop, Yu Mi.
Seungri.
This is a mess.
We can't let them.
Seungri, break theirs.
- Where? - Oh, gosh.
Oh, dear.
10, 9, 8...
(A desperate struggle to survive)
3,
- It ripped. - 2, 1.
- It ripped. - It's over.
(Round 1 is over.)
It's over.
(Did Jae Seok rip the bracelet in the last second?)
Did you rip it?
(Is it really ripped?)
(Seok Jin and Seungri's bracelet is fine.)
They didn't rip it.
(He thought it was ripped.)
- Goodness. - That startled me.
- We can't do anything else, Yu Mi. - Jae Seok.
- The leader can be anybody. - It's dangerous for us.
They'll pick us.
I say Haha. He's better.
We don't have an option,
so let's ask Haha for a favor.
I say Se Chan.
- What do you say? - I say Se Chan as well.
- Se Chan will eliminate So Min. - Right.
Who do you want to pick?
- I say Se Chan and Jimin as well. - Okay.
We'll pick Seok Jin.
We'll appoint him as the leader.
- Final. - Yes.
(The voting has concluded. Please gather at the headquarters.)
Everybody, Jae Seok and Yu Mi...
got eliminated...
in this round.
- I can't believe this. - Jae Seok is Level Zero.
(Jae Seok is Level 0.)
- He's Level 0. - We've been doing this for 4 weeks.
- He's not even Level 1. - We started as Level 1,
but he's zero now.
We played so many games.
This should be one of the world's mysteries.
- Does this make sense? - It doesn't.
- We started as Level 1 4 weeks ago. - What did you do?
You talk like your level is really high.
That's not what I meant.
- It's fascinating. - I...
Look. Once this game is over,
I'll show you how I win...
with Yu Mi's Level Six.
(He's all talk.)
- That's... - I met a good partner.
I'll see.
The leader couple you voted for...
Who are they?
Please.
(The leaders have the power to eliminate a couple.)
Seok Jin and Seungri.
(Seok Jin and Seungri are the leaders of Round 1.)
(They got 3 votes and got elected as the leaders.)
- You know who, right? - Of course.
We know.
(High levels get anxious.)
Seok Jin and Seungri,
pick a number...
(Pick a number to eliminate.)
- Number? - from 1 to 6...
- to eliminate. - What?
- Cushion number? - Where we sat?
I think it's where we sat.
- You don't get to pick? - The number?
- We had to memorize it. - You know where we sat.
- I know. - You do.
We have to eliminate So Min...
- or Haha. - Yes.
Please pick a number.
- What number? - Should we say it together?
In 1, 2, 3.
- Number 4! - 4!
- Who was 4? - 4.
Who's that?
Four.
(The couple who sat on Chair 4 is...)
So Min and Jong Hyun are eliminated.
(The couple with the highest level is out.)
We heard.
We heard you fight.
- He remembered. - We heard you fight.
- We heard you fight. - You did, right?
Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok and Yu Mi, and Jong Hyun and So Min are out.)
Let's start Round Two...
with the remaining couples.
There are four sets of chairs.
Let's go ahead with Round Two. Get ready.
Ready, set...
Run!
We can't take that one.
There's none.
(There are 2 less chairs with each round.)
- Where is it? - Where is it?
Is that it?
- There it is. - There it is. Run.
- Sit. - I'm going to die.
(Haha and MinA take Chair 4.)
I'm going to die.
Come. Rip it.
Come here.
Let's see.
(Seok Jin and Seungri attack as well.)
Don't come!
(There are 3 couples for 1 chair!)
Let's work together.
Yu Ri, let's rip Seok Jin's.
(He tries to make an alliance.)
(The male-male couple gets scared...)
(and retreats.)
- There's a seat left. - What?
There's a seat left.
Is there?
(Yu Ri became more fierce after she took off the insoles.)
You're going to get eliminated anyway.
(She attacks endlessly.)
- Haha. - Think carefully.
(There's an intense competition.)
Let go.
- No! - Here it is.
(The remaining couples sit down.)
Sit down.
It's one minute before the conclusion of the race.
(There's only 1 minute left!)
No!
- No! - It ripped.
- I ripped it. - We ripped it.
(She rips the bracelet off.)
Get out.
- I ripped it. - We're sorry.
- Move. - Sorry.
Get off.
I ripped it.
(She got more skilled after she took off the insoles.)
Get out.
Move. These are our seats.
(There's no time, and they have no energy.)
(Thanks to Yu Ri, Kwang Soo and Yu Ri take Chair 4.)
Goodbye.
- Let's go. - That was humiliating.
(They head over to the other chairs.)
We have to rip a bracelet.
Six seconds until the race is over.
- We have to do it. - 5,
- 4... - No, MinA.
- 2, 1. - It's okay, Haha.
- We'll do better next time. - I'm sorry.
(Haha and MinA have been eliminated. Please pick new leaders.)
- We pick... - Se Chan.
- Se Chan and Jimin. - Jimin.
(According to the votes,)
(Se Chan and Jimin get elected as the leaders.)
In 1, 2, 3.
- 3! - 3!
- 3. - 3.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are eliminated.
They're out.
(They were sitting on Chair 3, so they're out.)
If we win another round, we can earn a point.
- This is doable. - That's amazing.
The strong ones are gone.
The best couple is out.
We had to make that decision.
They would have eliminated us.
This is the final round.
There are two chairs left.
We'll go first.
Get ready.
- We should walk slowly. - I know.
- It doesn't matter either way. - Seriously.
- We should go first. - We are bound to meet.
We are bound to meet.
- We can walk slowly. - Hey!
- You said we should walk slowly! - Hey!
- You said we should walk slowly! - For goodness' sake!
(Didn't they say they will go slowly?)
For goodness' sake.
(Did you really trust us?)
Hey, Se Chan. Let's hurry up.
(They run and run...)
(and reach Chair 5 and 6.)
- There are two chairs. - Which one should we pick?
- Let's sit here. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo and Yu Ri sit on Chair 6.)
Put your hand in your pocket.
(Approaching)
Hurry up and sit down.
(They circle around Kwang Soo and Yu Ri.)
(They suddenly change their direction...)
(and walk towards Kwang Soo and Yu Ri.)
- Are you going to get us? - Of course not.
- We just want to talk. - Hurry up...
- and sit down. - We have a suggestion.
When Seok Jin sits down,
help us break his couple bracelet.
Then we will make sure you place first.
Will we be able to break it? Wouldn't it be better to sit down?
There it is.
- Why didn't you sit? - Seriously.
What are you doing?
We have time.
- We have time. - That's right.
Is that why you didn't sit down?
(Are they going to break his bracelet?)
(Se Chan attacks Seok Jin and Seungri.)
We can place 2nd and you can place 1st.
(That can happen if you break Kwang Soo's bracelet.)
- We are serious. - What?
- Hold on. We are serious. - Really?
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Hold on. - Let's go over there.
Let's go.
Are you going to attack us?
- Don't do that. - Hey, I will help you.
(The tables are turned.)
We will help you!
We will really help you!
(They need to fend off four people.)
The race will end in a minute.
(It's the end for us if our bracelet breaks.)
- Se Chan, we can work together. - Break it.
Break it.
It broke! Se Chan's bracelet broke!
(It broke! Se Chan's bracelet broke!)
(Se Chan's bracelet breaks with less than a minute remaining.)
Se Chan's bracelet broke.
- It broke. - It broke.
- Did it break? - Our bracelet is intact.
- Our bracelet is intact. - Se Chan's bracelet broke.
His bracelet broke.
(The end of Se Chan)
- Okay. - Okay.
Okay.
We did it.
They tried to break our bracelet, but theirs broke instead.
Okay.
Now, the couple that got eliminated last,
Se Chan and Jimin...
will rank the two couples.
- Yes! - What?
(Se Chan and Jimin will rank the two couples.)
(They get the right to choose which couple places 1st and 2nd.)
Jimin, come here.
This is nice.
Let's think about what happened earlier.
Gosh, this is a difficult choice to make.
Both Kwang Soo and Seok Jin are my enemies.
Which couple will place first?
(Kwang Soo and Yuri's levels are lower.)
- Kwang Soo and Yuri! - Yes!
We need an equilibrium.
(Kwang Soo and Yuri place 1st.)
Okay. Okay.
They will be Level Five.
We had no choice.
Okay.
(The final level)
We will now choose the final winner...
of Level Up Project.
This is your last chance to make a comeback,
The Last Roulette.
(The very last quest, The Last Roulette)
Running Man members will receive name stickers...
in accordance with the couple's combined levels.
The one with the highest level will choose the slots first.
We will spin the roulette once.
The member who gets chosen...
will be the final winner.
That member's partner will receive a prize.
- Okay. - Okay.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo will receive name stickers...
in accordance with their combined levels.
- If they win, - What happens then?
they will choose whether to stay together...
(They feel embarrassed for no reason.)
- This could be the new beginning. - It's just the wording.
So that I can be with you
"So that I can be with you"?
(So that you can have my levels)
(Love blooms as they exchange levels.)
- What? - Now,
you will get name stickers.
Jae Seok didn't do anything,
but he will get six name stickers...
thanks to his partner.
(He rides on Yu Mi's coattails.)
Yu Mi is my savior.
Yu Mi helped me.
What would you have done without Yu Mi?
We can go after them, right?
(So Min and Jong Hyuk put the stickers first.)
- There are 10. - You either put them together...
or spread them out.
Will you put them together or spread them out?
It's better to put them together.
Right, So Min?
- Skip a slot. - That's right.
- Let's skip a slot. - Okay.
Shall we put one here?
- Put it there. - Here?
Let's spread them out.
- Shall I put one here? - Yes.
Shall we put one between Haha's stickers?
Let's go all in.
- Let's line up all six stickers. - Shall we line them up?
(Everything depends on this roulette.)
- All right. - We spin it once.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Come on!
What will happen?
Get ready.
In 1, 2, 3.
All right.
(The roulette begins to spin.)
Let's go.
- Who will it be? - It's spinning fast.
We spent the last four weeks for this moment.
Please.
(Level Up Race was the most competitive.)
(To level up,)
(they exhausted their bodies...)
(and energy.)
(The past 4 weeks were fierce.)
- A month. - For this...
- Who will it be? - My goodness.
Who will it be?
There is no way of knowing.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
- Let me win just this once. - Our stickers are there.
Red, red.
- Please, please. - Let me win just this once.
Red, red, red.
- All right. - Let me win just this once.
- Please. - Red.
Here, here, here, here.
Here, here, here.
- Here. - It's at our stickers.
It's at our stickers.
- Please. - Come on.
- Please. - It might be us.
- It might be us. - Me! Me! Me! Me!
Come on!
No, no. It will be us!
It will be us!
(Haha and MinA)
No!
Stop.
(Haha and MinA)
(It goes past Haha's sticker.)
(Kim Jong Kook and Song Ji Hyo)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo get chosen.)
(No way!)
How did this happen?
Jong Kook!
(Hugging)
How did this happen?
What was that?
(How did it stop at their sticker?)
Thank goodness we put a sticker there!
How did this happen?
They have one sticker in the middle.
No way.
- No way. - My goodness.
- I can't believe it. - You know,
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo always get the good things.
- No way! - How did it stop there?
What is this?
Didn't the two of you hug...
just now?
(I saw it.)
(We are so happy.)
(Their true feelings came out because they were so happy.)
(Did they hug just now?)
(We won.)
We forgot that...
- they are invincible together. - I thought it would be us.
Kim Jong Kook and Song Ji Hyo won.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo win the race.)
They are too lucky.
Congratulations.
Your prize is a blank gift certificate...
you can use within the SBS card.
- Really? - You get the company card.
May I touch it?
It really is the SBS card.
It really is the prize.
- Really? - What is this?
Let's have a team dinner.
This is incredible.
It's a blank gift certificate.
Thank you for your hard work...
on a cold winter day.
Yu Ri, Seungri, Yu Mi,
Jong Hyun, MinA, and Jimin.
- Let's give them a big hand. - Thank you.
(We thank Yu Ri, Yu Mi, Seungri, Jong Hyun, Jimin, and MinA.)
Today,
the winners are these two.
(The final winners are Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
Congratulations.
(Level Up Race has ended.)
(Would you like to log out?)
(Running Man's New Year Special)
(The government is in a disarray at Running Country.)
(Fake kings appear.)
(A handsome king, Jung Il Woo)
(A crazy king, Jeon So Min)
(A weak puppet king, Jee Seok Jin)
We can take over the country.
(There are people who want to put a fake king on the throne.)
(Only one king can sit on the throne.)
(They work hard to support the king they serve.)
(Running Country is in a disarray without the absolute authority.)
You are no king.
(Find the real king and save Running Country.)
Did they do it?
(New Year Special, I Am the King)