- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Are you working out these days?
- Yes, I'm working out. - You are?
- Look at your arms. - Of course.
- Your biceps are getting big. - They are firm.
- What's gotten into you? - I'm working out these days.
He's looking to get younger.
Look at this. Feel this part.
I don't know about his chest, but his arms impressed me.
But what's wrong with your legs?
(But what's wrong with your legs?)
- What happened to your legs? - I couldn't improve my leg muscles.
Ji Hyo. Hey, isn't Ji Hyo's outfit today great?
- You look cute. - When I said she looked good,
- she said I was teasing her. - If there is a spy among us,
it has to be her.
No.
- Ji Hyo. - She looks like Detective Conan.
Her outfit looks great on her.
She's Detective Conan. Ji Hyo is Detective Conan today.
Everyone, you'd better be careful today.
She's out to get everyone today.
- So Min went to the Czech Republic. - She went to the Czech Republic.
(She went on a trip recently.)
Did you meet any guys in the Czech Republic?
Romance on a trip.
Tell us about Jack.
- Jack? - Jack?
(He suddenly exposes her.)
- You met him at a club. - She met Jack?
Tell us about Jack. You met him at a club.
(Exposing her for the 2nd time)
She went to a popular club in the Czech Republic.
- She met Jack there. - So Min was dancing there.
- A guy approached her. - Okay.
When he spoke English to her, she said, "No English".
When she said that, he used the translation application.
(Using the app on his phone)
- He showed his interest. - It said,
"I like your dancing."
(He uses the translation app after he approves of her dance.)
- He liked this? - Did you dance like this?
This?
(Did you dance like this?)
(Possible dance routines of So Min)
She could have done this.
(Shaking Her Bottom Dance)
(Madonna's Shake-it Dance)
Was it this?
Didn't she do this dance?
(Twisting Her Pelvis Dance)
(She ruled the clubs in the Czech Republic.)
So this is what she said about the meeting.
Under the colorful lights with loud music,
there were only Jack and her.
- Like in the movie "La Boum". - My gosh.
- Right. It was like "La Boum". - Yes.
(It was the moment Jack used the translation app.)
He's like Jack from the movie, "Titanic".
- That's how she described it. - Right.
She went to a zoo the next day.
- Did they meet again? - They ran into each other.
- My gosh. - When you travel,
- that happens. - Is that true? Did she get drunk?
- Is that a lie? Was she drunk? - The itineraries are similar.
No, no. We really met. The otter...
I was looking at otters and thought that they were cute.
It was a bright afternoon.
When I was looking at the otters, I felt something weird.
- That's your point of view. - The wind was blowing.
When the wind was fluttering my hair romantically like this,
- someone next to me said, - That was romantic.
"Hey".
(Laughing)
Someone next to me said, "Hey".
("Who is it? Is it you, Jack?")
And I looked at him.
- No one turns around like that. - "Hey!"
(Starring So Min and Jack)
When I looked at him, he said, "In the club".
- He saw you at the club. - "Jack!" My gosh!
(That's how So Min and Jack encountered again.)
It's funny.
(What's the ending of her romance in the Czech Republic?)
So what happened? You have to tell us what happened.
We exchanged email addresses.
- Emails? - I got his email.
We don't know what's going to happen with this.
Can't we invite him as a guest?
- Let's do that. It'd be awesome. - Sure.
- I will share any news... - Great.
- I get about Jack. - Yes, share with us.
Jae Seok will be the tabloid reporter.
But seriously. You're something else.
Everyone, it's Secret Couple...
- What? - Amid the Battle of Singles.
- Secret Couple? - Yes.
(Secret Couple Amid the Battle of Singles )
(If you say there is a secret couple,)
(it has to be you, Lovesick Giraffe!)
Why is that me all of a sudden? Why me all of a sudden?
- Why is it me? - I got him.
- It could be him. - Listen.
- No, no. - He actually did it.
- It's him. - He did keep it a secret.
- How is that related to this? - You're acting funny.
Kwang Soo is known for secret relationships.
- "Secret couple?" - Look at him.
- No, no. - I caught him.
- I was surprised to hear that. - I got him.
Hold on. You...
- No, no. - Someone better not wear that hat.
- This hat... - It's so obvious.
There has to be a theme for her outfit.
- No one can wear a leather jacket. - No, no.
- It's not me. - It's not?
It's really not me.
If someone wears a similar hat, it'd be so funny.
Everyone, you are all single members.
(Everyone, you are all single members.)
- Did you see that? - No, he's not.
- I... - He's not.
- Did you see him screaming in joy? - It came out before I could stop.
- It was that word, "single". - Everyone was quiet, but him.
The new single members who will join you...
- are waiting for you. - Really?
- That's great. - There are three.
There aren't that many doors.
(Three new single members will join the Battle of Singles.)
There are three guests.
Shall we bring out the first guest?
- First guest, come on out. - Come on out.
- I'm so curious. - Me?
I'm curious.
(Who is the first guest?)
My gosh, it's Jang Hee Jin.
(Jang Hee Jin, good-looking single with shining beauty)
(It feels like I'm the only one breathing.)
(She dominated commercials, photoshoots, and beauty programs.)
(She always looks so stunning.)
- My gosh. - Hello.
- How long has it been, Hee Jin? - Long time no see.
- Come here. - Hello.
- It's been so long. - Hello.
- It's been ages, Hee Jin. - It's been so long.
- Yes, it's been a while. - Exactly.
- After "X-Man"... - "X-Man".
- "Of course". - She was popular during that era.
- Hee Jin. - Right.
- I think it's been a decade. - Yes.
- I haven't seen her after "X-Man". - "X-Man".
- She hasn't changed. - People don't know that show now.
What are you talking about? They all know that show.
- I grew up watching "X-Man". - Really?
- I saw you on the show. - Of course.
- I grew up watching the show. - Her love interest was Jong Min.
- That's right. - Really?
- How did you know that? - I remember everything.
- Really? - It was Jong Min?
- Really? - I can remember everything.
(In 2005, Young Hee Jin was a newbie on variety shows.)
(Young Jong Min was still a veteran on variety shows.)
(Don't cheat on me.)
(Their love interest was so innocent that made viewers happy.)
- This is what he said to me. - What did he say?
He said that he really liked Hee Jin.
- He said he liked me? - He really liked you.
I can't believe Hee Jin is joining us today.
- It's so nice to see you again. - Same here.
I saw you on telly too.
- It's so nice to hear "telly". - What a charming word!
- So nice to see you again! - "Telly"?
- "Telly". She's an oldie. - I'm so glad to see her.
(They're happy to see another oldie.)
- She's an oldie. - She saw us on telly.
- She used that word like a pro. - That's so nice to hear that.
Not that many people use that word anymore.
- It's so nice to see her again. - All right. Hee Jin is joining us.
We'll bring in the next guest. Please come on out.
(Who is the next new single member?)
(They're looking forward to the second guest. Who is it?)
Hello.
- My gosh. - Bona!
(A multitalented single, Bona of WJSN)
(This lead dancer of WJSN is a talented idol singer.)
(She dominated variety shows by starring on "The Law of Jungle".)
(Bona is a versatile single member with many talents.)
- Come here, Bona. - Bona.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Hi, Bona. Nice to see you again.)
- Hello, Bona. - I can't believe I'm meeting Bona.
Right.
She and I went to the jungle.
- Really? - You went to the jungle together?
When you star on that show, you become such good friends.
- Right. - Exactly.
- I kept it a secret from you. - Why?
I didn't tell you I was coming here today.
Do you guys keep in touch?
- There's a group chatroom. - There's a group chatroom.
(Things are going well for you!)
(Look at them. They're keeping in touch!)
It's for "The Law of Jungle".
Are you two the secret couple?
- No, no. Never. - My gosh.
- I can see his gums when he smiles. - I don't know.
- He's smiling so broadly. - He's really blushing.
- I hate things like this. - Why is your face getting red?
- His gums doubled today. - Hey.
- Why is your smile so big? - Why is it so big?
- What? - Why is it so big?
I guess my gums are growing.
- Did you put on fake gums? - No.
- Next guest. - Who's the next guest?
(The last single member will be revealed.)
(Who is the last single member that will follow after the ladies?)
- I saw him... - My gosh.
Seriously? He's too handsome.
(Out-of-the-world handsome single guy, Kim Jae Young)
(He's a top model...)
(who's out of everyone's league with awesome walks and face.)
(He gave off irresistible charms in "100 Days My Prince".)
(He's a new movie star on the rise with "Golden Slumber" and "Money".)
Let me introduce Kim Jae Young to you.
- Come here. - He's so handsome.
- This is my first time meeting him. - Right.
- He's very handsome. - No, no.
He looks like a hybrid of Yun Kyun Sang and Na Yoon Kwon.
(Jae Young is a mix of these two men?)
- Na Yoon Kwon? - You're right.
Yes, he does resemble them.
So Min is taking a step forward again.
(She takes a step forward without realizing herself.)
Go back to your spot.
My gosh, So Min. You're unbelievable.
Originally, you debuted as a model, right?
- Yes, I started as a model. - Right.
- He does look like a model. - He does.
One of our comedians used to be...
- a model too. - I see.
(One of our comedians used to be a model too.)
- Comedian? - What are you saying?
- He was a model. - I'm not a comedian.
You're my junior comedian.
You're my and Seok Jin's junior comedian.
Was it something like this?
You know, for some projects, they only use the models' bodies.
Was that what you did?
Have you ever been on a runway?
What have I done wrong?
(He explodes with disappointment.)
Have you been on one?
- Of course, I have. - Really?
Do it. Do the walk.
- Do the walk. - You can't, can you?
(Acting immature)
- Do the walk. - Go do the walk. Do the walk.
(Do you think I'll let you provoke me like a kid?)
(Yes, he will fall for it.)
Go do the walk. Do the walk.
(I'm a top model of Asia with 13 years of experience.)
(I'm Lee Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo. - Do it.
- See? What is this? - Do the walk.
(Is the top model doing a funny pose for the variety show?)
Do the walk.
- Do the model walk. - Do the model walk.
- Walk. - Walk.
(This is the funny walk for variety shows.)
(I'll show you my 10-year experience on Running Man.)
- What was that? - My gosh.
- Do the walk. - Did you see that?
(This comes from his 10 years of experience.)
This is upsetting. It's so upsetting.
- Jae Young. - Yes.
Did you hear any stories about Kwang Soo from your model friends?
He started way before I started.
I didn't get to hear his stories.
(Did the modeling industry forget about this dinosaur model?)
- Models... - He's trying to make me look nice.
- Okay. - He started way before I did.
- He's very polite. - Yes, he does.
Great. All right.
Please tell us how it feels to be on our show today. I'm curious.
First, I'm really nervous.
- He doesn't sound nervous. - Don't be nervous.
His voice sounds the most relaxed.
- Is that so? - You never know.
I will do my best to entertain the viewers.
I'll do my best not to cause any harm.
Okay. He says everything he wants to say.
- He quietly says everything. - He doesn't hold back.
Great.
Let's give a round of applause to Jae Young.
(Every new single member has joined.)
All right. Right now,
there are 11 single members. And among these members,
there is one couple...
- who are dating in secret. - It's just one couple.
And a relationship virgin is hiding amongst you...
to reveal the identities of the secret couple.
- Relationship virgin? - Relationship virgin?
(1 relationship virgin exists to catch the secret couple.)
- There's a relationship virgin. - Who is the relationship virgin?
(Here's the relationship virgin.)
- He's the relationship virgin? - It's him.
- He's the relationship virgin. - I get the feeling that he is.
- Hey. - I get the feeling that he is.
- So Min. - I can feel it right away.
You're unbelievable.
- Jae Seok. - It's him because he's ugly.
(Even if he isn't one, he's known as the ugly one.)
The single members must join forces with the relationship virgin...
to catch the secret couple and eliminate them to win.
Then, you'll win a prize.
If the secret couple manages to hide their identities to the end...
or find and eliminate the relationship virgin,
the secret couple will win.
Then, they will take the prize.
(If even 1 of them survives, it's their win.)
- It's simple. - Yes, it is.
However, the secret couple...
- must carry out hidden missions... - There are missions.
without your knowledge.
We must watch out for people who disappear.
We should check people who are acting strange too.
My gut feeling tells me that they're wearing matching outfits.
(My gut feeling tells me that they're wearing matching outfits.)
- Those two. - You're right.
You're wearing matching outfits.
- You're right. - It's those two.
It made me wonder if they had a special theme or something.
- We'll go to a restaurant. - Okay, okay.
- You'll do your first mission. - Great, great.
- Okay, let's go. - The three guests...
already acquired top, middle, and low meal cards...
through a preliminary mission in advance.
A preliminary mission?
They acquired top, middle, and low meal cards in advance.
(What preliminary mission?)
- They did a preliminary mission? - What did they do?
We called the three of you before the filming because...
(30 minutes before the opening segment)
This is your first time joining our show.
We called you in because of a special mission we'll give you.
Without revealing your identity,
you must carry out your mission to the members.
Depending on the number of your successes,
the appropriate meal cards for your lunch will be given out.
(She's ready for the mission in disguise.)
Hee Jin distributed the team uniforms...
to you.
- I saw her! - Really?
I remember that!
- I knew it! - I remember that!
- It was when we were in that room! - She was in our room?
You wore a black padded jacket.
(When did Hee Jin carry out her mission?)
- They don't know where I am, right? - Right.
(15 minutes before the filming)
I hope they don't recognize me.
(She enters the waiting room with the team uniforms.)
(Everyone is engrossed in the cellphone game.)
(Hee Jin comes in at a nice timing.)
(But at that moment,)
(did Se Chan see her?)
(Why is he looking at me? Did he already recognize me?)
(Will she be exposed even before her mission?)
I couldn't hide this.
What?
Give this to the first member.
(She starts her mission after averting a crisis.)
(She successfully gives it to Se Chan.)
(With the momentum, she successfully hands it to Jae Seok too.)
(It's 3 in a row. She successfully gives it to Ji Hyo.)
(What?)
(Did Jong Kook see Hee Jin?)
(He did see her, but he didn't recognize her.)
(Hee Jin successfully gave the uniforms to everyone.)
- That was amazing. - No way.
- What a surprise! - You were all talking.
I knew it. She was too pretty!
You were wearing a hat and glasses, right?
- That's right. - The thing is that...
- She turned her head too much. - No.
- I looked at her twice. - No.
- No way. - No.
- I had no idea. - Really?
- We kept playing games. - It was...
That weird guy...
who put on the microphone...
Jae Young...
- put microphones on you. - My gosh, it was you.
- You! I knew it. - I knew something felt off.
Something was off. It was off.
(He perfectly transforms into an audio engineer.)
Put on the microphones, please.
(All right! It's time to set out!)
Where? Where should I go?
(He enters the waiting room when everyone is getting ready to film.)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Jae Seok stares right at him.)
(But he fails to recognize Jae Young.)
(My gosh, what a relief. Unlike his cool composure, he's nervous.)
I'll put on the microphone.
Okay, the microphone.
(His next target is Seok Jin.)
(After Seok Jin, he successfully puts it on everyone.)
(Again, the members show no attention to him.)
- You! I knew it. - I knew something felt off.
(Just like Hee Jin, he gets the top meal card.)
(That was you? You completely fooled me.)
- I had no idea. - I...
- Earlier, he put it on here. - Right, right.
(It's very far from his mouth.)
- Right, right. - He put it on here.
I put it on you.
Seriously.
- You did, didn't you? - But...
- Right? He put it here. - And I ran away.
That's why I asked him if it should be here.
But he...
- I asked him that. - You did?
(When Jae Young put the microphone on Seok Jin...)
You're putting it here?
(It's his first microphone next to his Adam's apple.)
(This is weird.)
- You're putting it here? - Yes.
(He's flustered inside.)
(Gosh, he almost got me.)
That's why I asked him...
if it should be here. I asked him that.
- I asked him that. - You did?
Yes, I did.
- I asked him if it should be here. - I...
When I asked him that,
- I said yes and went away. - he just walked away.
That's why I thought that...
if I was going to sit here and talk to this side only.
(Will I sit on the right and face right only?)
(His calm composure brought a side effect.)
He put it right here.
Shouldn't you have figured it out then?
But...
You should've recognized him then.
Hey, how could I?
And Bona got autographs...
- from you guys. - Right. I remember that.
- When? - She did that.
Really?
(She transformed into a college student.)
(The first member that showed up was...)
(Ji Hyo with the Detective Conan outfit.)
Ji Hyo, can you give me an autograph?
(Rushing)
- Please move back. - Au autograph, please.
(Ji Hyo looks right at Bona.)
Thank you.
(She manages to get Ji Hyo's autograph.)
(The next target is Seok Jin with his microphone on his neck.)
Thank you.
(She also manages to get an autograph.)
I'm a huge fan. Can I get an autograph?
Sure.
March 1.
- Thank you. - Sure.
(Bona gets 3 autographs from Ji Hyo, Seok Jin, and Jong Kook.)
- That's right! - I went, "An autograph, please."
- I wore glasses. - Really?
Therefore,
Hee Jin and Jae Young...
carried out their missions on all eight of the members.
That's why they acquired the top meal cards.
- She only got three autographs. - Oh, no.
- She acquired a low meal card. - Oh, no.
(Bona acquired a low meal card.)
When you go down to the parking lot,
- you'll see three cars. - Okay.
When you get in the cars first,
the guests will look at the members...
and get in the cars of their choice.
- My gosh. - I see.
They'll see who's in the car?
This is great.
It depends on my decision today.
If Bona gets in...
I just have to avoid getting teamed up with Bona.
(What's the result of the random car draw for teams and meal cards?)
- We can't get in right away? - What is this?
What is it? Do we just get in?
Before you choose, break into 2 teams of 3 members...
- and 1 team of 2 members. - 3, 3, and 2.
- We just need to avoid Bona. - Right.
Why don't we just mix it up?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Yes, rock-paper-scissors.
- Shall we? - We can do a random draw too.
Let's do that because...
- the couple might try to team up. - Right, right.
- That's right. - Let's do a random draw.
There is only one couple, right?
- What? - It's a guy and a girl, right?
- All right. - I can't tell you that.
- But there could be two couples. - My gosh.
- They could be the same gender. - They could be the same gender.
There must be two couples then.
(It's you, right?)
What?
- What? - What was that?
- Are you picking a fight with me? - Were you flirting with him?
- It's you, isn't it? - What? My gosh.
That's why I did that.
Unbelievable.
(What is that? Is that a hidden mission?)
(The members who pick the same numbers will make teams together.)
- Right. - I see how it's set up.
- Members... - They can choose members.
- All right. - Please.
(It's time to randomly draw for numbers.)
I'm done.
(Good teams have a better chance...)
(of meeting guests with top meal cards.)
Okay. Ji Hyo.
(This is the random draw of spoons their lunch is at stake.)
- All right. Jong Kook. - Okay.
- Okay. - The middle one.
I'll take whatever is left.
- I'm not good at random draws. - I see.
I hope Hee Jin chooses my team.
What is it?
- What is it? Hey. - Take the leftover one.
(He puts down the leftovers.)
Hey.
You're so mean.
I know. He needs to move a lot.
- He does. - Yes.
- He needs to move a lot. - Why?
- Number 1 or 2? - Who got number 1?
- Me. - Okay.
- I'm with you. - All right.
- Number one. - It's the comedian team.
- You're right. - Yes.
It's the comedian team.
You guys got number two?
We're the young team. What about you?
(This makes the remaining 2 a team.)
(They're Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.)
I can't believe this!
- It's you two? - What is this?
- Come on. - People will think it's planned.
- Don't do this. - This wasn't planned.
- I don't like this. - They're a couple.
(Are they the secret couple?)
Is this fate?
Let's do our chant.
- Team Comedians! - Team Comedians!
- Team Youth! - Team Youth!
- Team Youth! Let's do it! - Let's do it!
We're Team FC!
What is that?
Future Couple.
(The 3rd team is called Team Future Couple.)
That's great.
- Ji Hyo. - That's nice.
- She confessed her love for him. - She's...
You received a mission, right?
- Team FC! - You did, right?
- No. - I knew it.
How about "Hello, honey"?
That sounds good.
- Hello. - Honey.
(Hello, honey.)
(They decide on their team name.)
He listened to her.
- Shall we go? - Okay.
How could we be divided like this?
It's hilarious.
It's strange.
- It is. - It was just the two of them.
It's always the two of them.
- It's like fate. - How is that possible?
We need to hide.
I think they'll be coming soon.
If Bona gets in, we're done for.
You're right.
She got the low meal card.
I hope they get in one by one.
Hee Jin's here!
Please!
She's here!
(Hee Jin got the top meal card.)
- She's here! - Please.
- She's coming this way. - She is?
- She needs to come here. - You're right.
We need her.
She's here.
It's Hee Jin.
- I wish Jae Young came. - Hee Jin's here.
I want Jae Young. I wish he'd come.
Do I just knock, check, and get in?
You can choose not to.
- You can choose not to. - She's coming this way.
(Someone signals for her to come.)
(Come here.)
Aren't you Haha?
I'm actually glad to see him.
- I'm actually glad to see him. - Hee Jin, get in.
You should get in here.
Don't worry. It's the three of us.
- This is a comfortable team. - We're Team Youth.
- We're Team Youth. - You are.
Team Youth!
- We're... - But I don't like Kwang Soo.
What do you mean?
Thank goodness.
Why are you relieved?
She has the top meal card, so why are you relieved?
(So Min's glad Hee Jin doesn't like Kwang Soo.)
(She moves onto the middle car.)
- Hee Jin. - Hello!
It's nice to meet you.
I'm a big fan of yours.
This is a nice team.
- Hello. - Why don't you hop in?
- Is Jong Kook here? - He's back here.
I'm scared of him.
(She doesn't like Jong Kook.)
She's afraid of me?
- She's afraid of you. - Why would she be?
I'm not a scary person.
Goodness.
Jong Kook is a nice person once you get to know him.
(She arrives at the last car.)
I'll hide.
- Hello! - Hello!
Hello!
Get in!
(In order to persuade her, they act extremely friendly.)
- Hee Jin. - Get in.
- Get in. - Hello.
- This is your chance. - Just hop in.
This is Team Comedians!
(He pressures her.)
Let me think about it.
(Hesitant)
(Their chant must not be too persuasive.)
- Goodness. - I shouldn't have said that.
- Why did you say that? - Why did you say our chant?
- We lost some points. - We're a friendly team.
I've made a mistake.
Where should I go?
(She's not interested in any of them.)
My goodness.
(They cry out for her.)
- She's coming! - She's coming!
- She's getting in! - She's getting in!
(She tries to open the door.)
(Why isn't it opening?)
(She won't get in that easily.)
- Get out! - What are you doing?
(So Min locks the door.)
(What are you doing?)
Open the door! Hurry up!
What's wrong with you?
- Get in! - What's your problem?
(Kwang Soo stops her.)
What's gotten into her?
(What's going on? I should leave.)
I should go.
- Hee Jin! - No, thanks.
- Hee Jin! - Hee Jin!
- No, thanks. - We want you!
(They peek from the top.)
- What are you hesitant about? - What is it?
No, you can't get in.
- I can't? - You should join us.
Hee Jin!
- Hee Jin! - Hee Jin!
- Hee Jin! - Smile!
- Smile, smile, smile. - Leave them.
(They change their chant.)
- I'm going to go to that team. - Leave them.
- Where are you going? - Hey!
Listen to me!
- Hear me out! - Hee Jin, it's this way!
- Hey! - Listen to me.
- Hee Jin, it's this way! - Listen to me!
Be quiet!
- Please! - Listen to me!
Welcome!
- Hello. - Okay!
(She picks Team Comedians.)
- High five. - Smile, smile, smile.
(They're happy to have her.)
- You picked us? That's great. - Hello.
- Okay! - Good thinking.
- Close the door. - Okay!
Please!
(Hee Jin, please.)
- So Min, you... - What's wrong with you? Hey.
I mean...
I just want Jae Young to come.
- Haha. - How can we understand her?
You're both in relationships.
- After we finish filming... - She really likes him.
Still, this isn't right.
Hee Jin opened our door. She chose us.
I mean...
Darn it. I'm not doing this.
- I won't do this. - Me neither.
- Gosh. - I'm serious.
Hee Jin came, but...
- So Min locked the door. - She locked the door.
I'm not going to do this. So Min wants to date all she wants.
- I'm so mad that she's serious. - Me too!
What's going on?
- Hee Jin. You got it all wrong. - So Min wants Jae Young.
- Don't be so pathetic. - I mean...
- The door didn't open. - She...
- She locked it. - I didn't.
- So Min did? - She locked it?
- She locked it? - She wanted Jae Young.
No wonder. She told me that I couldn't get in the car.
- Really? - She said that.
So I thought I wasn't supposed to get in there.
I'm sorry, but you can't become a couple with anyone here.
(Seok Jin barges in all of a sudden.)
- I'm sorry. - He's right.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
We are sorry about that.
(All the men are taken.)
(Sullen)
What is this mess?
I'm so frustrated.
- What is this? - I'm actually irritated by you.
What is this? What you did was really weird.
- I don't get this. - Jae Young better come here.
- Promise us. - Goodness.
They better not be the secret couple.
- I'm so vexed. - He's here. Dance.
- Who is it? - It's Jae Young. He's here.
Jae Young.
Go talk to him up there.
Hold on.
(She seems timid.)
- It's Bona! - Go up.
- Go up. - Are they both here?
(Next to Jae Young who's won the top meal card...)
(is Bona with the low meal card.)
Oh, do we go and pick?
They're both here.
Jae Young.
- Hold on. - There she is.
So Min, do you want me?
- No. - Do you want me?
- Hello. - So Min, do you want me?
(No, not you.)
Jae Young. I want you.
- Who's in this car? - Jae Young.
Hello.
I've saved a spot for you.
- Did you? - Who's in this car?
No one's in here.
Go.
Bona wants to get in. What should we do?
Jae Young.
(He looks for another way.)
- Jae Young. - Yes? Me?
Jae Young!
(Haha plays a song for him.)
Let's eat together.
(What is this song?)
Come in!
Jae Young, why are you hesitating?
Let's dance.
Jae Young, let's eat something delicious together!
I have something to tell you.
So Min told Haha that Bona was going to get in.
And he wanted Bona to get lost.
I'm serious. Seriously.
I swear.
Hey, hold on!
(The plan backfires, and Bona is more determined to get in.)
- Hold on. - I'm so dumbfounded.
- I'll get in here. - Okay!
(Jae Young picks Team Hello Honey.)
- Nice! - Jae Young!
- Jae Young! - Please!
- What's wrong with you? - Darn it!
Why?
(They can't believe it.)
They'll beat you up there!
- He's already in here! - Back up.
- Your seat's too close up. - Hello.
- All right. - Good thinking.
(They're exhilarated to have him.)
Let me talk casually to you.
Me too.
Jae Young.
(The three teams have been settled.)
I liked you from the start.
(Team Youth is on their way to eat.)
What I find the most suspicious is that...
So Min didn't allow Hee Jin to get in.
I just really wanted Jae Young to get in.
Then the secret couple could be So Min and Jae Young.
To me, So Min is just a desperate girl.
(It's obvious.)
She wants to date.
But I was rejected. He doesn't like me, right?
- No, not yet. - I chose you guys first.
He told me that I could choose first.
Why did he do that?
I think he chose Ji Hyo over me.
Right, Haha?
We don't know for certain yet.
(So Min's filming a dating show.)
I won't be able to see him for half a day.
- No, you'll see him. - Aren't we going to the same place?
- We're going to the same place. - We are?
But we won't be able to eat.
I didn't know that.
Had I known, I would've allowed Hee Jin to get in.
I didn't have to stop her.
This is nice. This is all right.
- You look happy now. - I am.
(Meanwhile, how is Jae Young doing?)
What's your personality like?
Are you reserved? Or are you...
I'm not really reserved, but I feel inhibited in front of strangers.
It's been a while since I last appeared on on a variety show.
- Right. - So it's difficult.
People like Jae Young are perfect for acting slow...
- when they have a mission. - Right.
People don't usually suspect them.
They bait us when we don't suspect them.
But people who act are naturally good at pretending.
The mission?
When we get missions, we pretend that...
we're not feeling well that day.
We pretend like we're sick.
You're right.
- We act tired. - But...
But you looked pretty sick when you came today.
I'm not sick.
- I was feeling... - You looked sick,
and you're a bit slow.
This is a strange combination.
- I'm just not used to this. - Is that so?
Don't pretend, and show us your real self.
He's suspecting us.
Wouldn't the secret couple want to get in the same car?
- You're right. - Right?
That's possible.
Do we look strange to you?
My goodness.
If you two were a couple,
then you guys probably have a mission to complete.
- Right. - Right.
- Go on, and do it. - We held hands.
- Right? - We held hands.
(Ji Hyo grabs his hand.)
You did.
Why did you do it? Why?
- She just did it. - I just did.
You're not the type to suddenly grab a guest's hand.
- She just... - His skin looked soft.
See? Come on. What's wrong with you?
You've aged.
(She's not making any sense.)
- She'll be 40 soon. - I just grabbed it.
She'll be turning 40 soon.
I just did that because you were suspecting us.
But there's nothing going on.
You're suspicious.
If this isn't a mission, you're interested in him.
I think it's 1 of those 2.
(She says something strange.)
So it's 1 of those 2. Okay.
- But it's really not me. - Sure.
But you know what? He could be the relationship virgin.
Right. Many good-looking people are relationship virgins.
If Jae Seok was the relationship virgin,
it'd be too obvious.
- Jae Seok? - It was strange.
He was distancing himself today.
He acted a bit differently today.
(Jae Seok seemed a bit off.)
- We don't need to worry about food. - Right.
You look 25 years old.
- Really? - She looks really young.
- She looks like a college student. - Why are you smirking?
- Because... - She seems to be in her early 30s.
- She looks really young. - Eat up, senior.
"Eat up, senior"?
- Did you hear her? - I'll eat a lot.
- Okay. - Compared to the past,
- you've become more brazen. - I know.
I'm also an emcee now.
- I used to. - Which program?
I was on a beauty program.
- You're right. - A beauty emcee!
- I... - A beauty emcee.
- I could understand you. - What do you mean?
I knew how hard it was to have a guest...
- like me. - Right.
I replied in short sentences and wasn't too talkative.
- Right. - And I didn't look at you.
(She did her best, but she was still awkward.)
(She was a difficult guest for Jae Seok.)
Now, I understand how you felt.
- It's too late. - What?
(It's a pity.)
- It's been way too long. - What?
- I can't believe... - I did my best, though.
you now understood me.
It's too late.
- I'm sorry. - We're here.
So Min.
This place looks tasty.
- Goodness. - I want a dolsot.
- I want a dolsot. - Hey.
That looks good.
Jae Young must be busy receiving a mission.
- You're right. - He's finally here.
- Jae Young. - It must be hard to do a mission.
- Yes. - Right?
- "Yes"? What was that? - "Yes"?
Hold his hand, Ji Hyo.
- Hey. - It's not like that.
They're suspicious.
- The two of them? - Really?
What is it?
- Hey. - They're the secret couple.
Jong Kook will kill you if you get caught.
You know very well what will happen.
He's the type to dig in.
- It's not me. - He is.
Something happened, right?
They got in the car.
But you all know that...
Ji Hyo's not the type to take care of the guests.
- Right. - She's a loner.
But she was taking good care of him and then held his hand.
(She suddenly held his hand.)
What?
- What's going on? - She's not the type...
- to do that. - I've never seen her do that.
I didn't grab his hand all of a sudden.
It's a bit strange.
I didn't suddenly grab it.
He asked if we were the secret couple with a mission.
He kept cornering me, so I just did it.
Maybe that was your mission.
- No. He kept cornering me. - Right.
One more thing.
- He kept cornering me. - This one's crucial.
Hey, say something.
Ji Hyo doesn't immediately speak casually to anyone.
Right.
She talked to him casually even before he got on.
But even I hadn't spoken casually to him.
Hold on. Did Ji Hyo sleep in the car or not?
(Did Ji Hyo sleep in the car or not?)
- She didn't. - You're suspicious!
(She didn't?)
- You're suspicious! - Ji Hyo!
- Come here. - She's suspicious.
- Hey. - Come here.
- You're caught. - Come here.
She's either the relationship virgin or they're the secret couple.
You didn't sleep?
- It's you, right? You didn't sleep? - She didn't.
- It's not me. - She was...
- very talkative. - No.
- I... - She didn't stop talking.
But hear me out. If we're not the secret couple,
then Jong Kook is being jealous.
- Listen to me. - I'm serious.
(If they're not the secret couple, Jong Kook is just being jealous.)
I'm serious.
- Right? - Yes, I understand.
You need to acknowledge that.
- You need to. - I acknowledge.
Look at how she's saying that since she's being cornered.
- Jong Kook... - That team is suspicious.
(What's the truth?)
You should all eat first.
- Thank you for the meal. - We can eat?
- Let's eat. - Hee Jin, eat up.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
It's pumpkin rice!
It's been a while since I last had a nice, warm meal.
(It's a feast full of nutritious foods.)
(Beef jeongol)
(Grilled yellow corvina)
(Korean-style raw beef)
Thanks to Jae Young...
- I know. - No, it's thanks to Ji Hyo.
Thanks to her, we're having such a delicious meal.
This looks really good.
We can't eat that, but that's not because of you.
Never.
Bona, don't be sorry. Ever.
(He's still mad.)
(But it makes her feel sorrier.)
So Min said she wanted to eat this like this.
You're right.
So Min, would you like some?
(Se Chan suddenly offers his fish.)
- I want it. - Come here.
What is this?
Why is Se Chan being so nice to me today?
Are you being jealous?
What is she talking about?
Eat.
- What are you doing? - Why did you give it to her?
Is it a mission?
(He feeds her.)
Is this a mission?
- Hey. - Are you insane?
I'm just taking care of her as a friend.
- You can't. - You should go now.
This is definitely a mission.
- I'm certain. - What did you do?
This has to be a mission.
It doesn't make sense if it isn't.
- Why did you give it to her? - You can't be like that.
I just wanted her to taste it.
You can't do that.
- You're acting strange. - He's being nice to me.
He's very suspicious.
What's going on?
- What do you want? - What do you need?
I'd like a piece of the vegetable pancake.
(What? The vegetable pancake?)
- Oh, this one? - No, you can't!
(Why are you helping her?)
Why did you get it for her? Why?
Why did you?
I just want it.
Why did he get it for you?
- Because I wanted it. - What's going on?
Look at this.
She could reach it, but she didn't.
- She kept hesitating. - Jong Kook.
- So he got it for her. - Jong Kook.
Up until a while ago, I could understand you.
- But this is jealousy. - No, it isn't.
(I'm speaking objectively.)
- You're making us uncomfortable. - It's not true.
- Jong Kook. - She's not that type.
- You're being too jealous. - Look.
Look. She did this, but she didn't pick it up.
(She wouldn't just accept food from anyone.)
- She did that three times. - Just be quiet and eat.
(You're right. He's jealous.)
(She talks badly about Jong Kook...)
(and receives food in exchange.)
(Stealthily)
(She bites his food.)
She did that three times.
(She's happy.)
Jae Young gave this to me. He put it inside my mouth.
Everyone is suspicious today!
(He can't take it anymore.)
So Min isn't even focused.
(Snatching)
She said Jae Young fed her.
Hey!
And Kwang Soo stole it.
I'm actually a part of the secret couple!
As if! Sit down!
(Sit down, relationship virgin!)
You're the relationship virgin.
Jong Kook can't focus on anything other than those two.
I'm pretty sure that he's just jealous now.
- I hope so. - He's definitely jealous.
That is jealousy for sure.
- Hey. - He's obsessed with her.
If you're not jealous,
please give me some raw beef.
(She suddenly asks for some raw beef.)
- Jong Kook isn't that stupid. - Really?
He won't fall for that.
I heard you danced back in the jungle.
If Bona dances on behalf of her team,
- please give us some raw beef. - Well...
- Okay, we will. - If it's entertaining, we will.
All of us, including me, will be embarrassed.
It's nice. They like that.
- I'll give you the beat. - Really?
Yes.
- 1, 2, - 2.
- She's so adorable. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(What is this fantastic dance that she'll be performing?)
- 2, 3, 4. - 2, 3, 4.
(She flails her arms around.)
(It looks complicated and fancy...)
(Everyone is embarrassed.)
(Why should her team members be embarrassed?)
(Nevertheless, she keeps going.)
Goodness.
- It's her choreography. - Yes.
It's the choreography.
(This dance is...)
(supposed to look splendid like so.)
(But without the music,)
(it looks rather embarrassing.)
- It's the choreography. - Goodness.
- Yes, it is. - She needs to be rewarded,
- Se Chan. - Bona.
You can take one of those shrimps marinated in say sauce.
Thank you for the food.
Bona, you can have this.
This is delicious.
It is.
Go on, try it, Bona.
(Mealtime is finished as a few suspects have revealed themselves.)
They're all good.
- Did everyone enjoy the meal? - Yes!
Your first mission to get hints is...
Paradise for singles, fiery pit for couples.
(Paradise for singles, fiery pit for couples.)
We'll give you questions regarding relationships,
and the team with the right answer...
gets to pour two buckets of water...
into other teams' bowls of their choice.
The team with the bowl full is...
- Eliminated? - eliminated.
The two losing team...
will be soaked in water from the bucket.
You could say I'm a bit...
of a veteran coach of relationships.
He's my coach.
I did help Kwang Soo...
with his relationship.
I signed up for his class too.
(I signed up for his class too.)
- To get advice from him. - You'll be surprised...
by how many celebrities are taking advice from me.
He's my relationship compass.
First question.
According to the research team of the University of Exeter,
A research team, good.
Your lover's "this" makes you live longer.
- Bona! - Let me answer!
So Min.
Your lover's kiss.
(Your lover's kiss.)
- I was going to say that. - I think she's right.
- What? - Let me answer!
Nagging.
- Nagging? - Yes.
- What's he saying? - No, obsession!
- Obsession. - Nagging or obsession?
- Obsession! - 1, 2, 3.
Nagging.
(Nagging.)
(He does not stick to an answer.)
- Choose one. - I'll say your lover's nagging.
Nagging.
- Your lover's nagging? - Let's go with that.
Let me answer!
- Hug! - Hug?
Let her answer!
- She's got it. - Let's go, Hee Jin!
- Let's go! - The queen of love.
- Jealousy. - Jealousy?
Wrong answer.
Wrong answer?
Let me tell you one more time.
Listen carefully.
There's a hint in the question.
It's not "this between lovers".
It's "lover's this" lets you live longer.
Let me answer!
(What's he going to say now?)
Lover's...
fart.
(Fart lets you live longer?)
(What nonsense is he babbling?)
- Correct! - Really?
- For real? - No way!
- No way! - What?
It's correct!
- That can't be right. - Is this for real?
- I wasn't even trying. - No way.
They say the hydrogen sulfide in there...
protects our cells.
- That makes no sense. - It reduces the risk of...
cancer, heart attack, arthritis, and dementia.
I should fart more at home.
We gave out farts when we were little,
it was like giving them vitamins.
It was just vitamins.
You could say you're...
- giving a part of your life. - Right.
- Or your own nutrition. - Right.
Please choose and pour...
two buckets of water.
- That's one bucket. - This is surprising.
- I did not expect that answer. - You're giving it to us?
(You want to give it to us without hesitation?)
Bona.
Let go of your bowl.
She's really cute.
- She is. - Go easy on us.
You don't want to give it to us.
- I'll give you a pass. - Yes!
Here, hold it. I'll let Bona off the hook.
Splash it right on her face!
Splash it!
Help me, So Min. I'm giving one bucket for each team.
- One for each? - One for each?
Hee Jin will give the second bucket.
Give it to a suspicious team.
You have nothing to doubt us about.
(Who she doubts as the secret couple is...)
Good, that's a good choice.
Why us?
(Jae Young and Ji Hyo look suspicious.)
- Fine. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo is depressed.)
Second question.
Who's gone through a breakup should know the answer to this.
According to the research team of Monmouth University in the US,
Monmouth?
- I've never heard of these names. - Monmouth?
- Monmouth University. - Monmouth.
It takes this long to get over...
a breakup with your lover.
How long is this?
Let me answer!
Six months!
(6 months.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Ten years. - What?
(10 years.)
(I will not forget about you for a decade.)
- Seriously? - Let me answer!
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
(10 years is the wrong answer.)
Let me answer! I'm sure about this.
3 months. It's 3 months.
- Why are you so sure about it? - What?
- Why are you so sure? - You know, just average...
Three months is...
- You register a gym for 3 months. - I think he's right.
And then it's six months.
(It's all about the gym for him. 3 months is correct!)
It's usually 3 months.
- That's correct? - Oh, really?
It took more than three months for me.
That can't be right. You guys forget after 3 months?
That's American style.
Three months on average?
But So Min said "10 years".
So you're seeing someone else, and you think about your ex?
But when I meet someone new,
I forget about my ex.
That was the case for me.
Bona, how long do you think...
you take to forget someone?
I'd say...
- I'd say... - I'd say...
(She's at a loss of words because of a sudden question.)
She claims that she hasn't met anyone,
- Right. - so she has nothing to say.
- She's got a lot on her mind. - I will...
tell you in 4 years.
- Your contract ends in 4 years? - Yes, my contract.
She's...
That was smart.
So, it's three months.
It takes 3 months on average.
I feel bitter.
- Why don't you give them around? - Me?
- You choose the teams. - Yes, you should.
We've never attacked your team.
- You should know that. - Jae Young!
- That team's a smarter choice. - Is it?
- No, choose his team! - I mean, that's not right.
- Jae Young. - You don't attack us,
- we don't attack you. - They need a bucket!
- We're going to choose... - No, no!
- the other team. - They want a bucket!
Now you can choose to pour one more there.
Jae Young, it's time for this team.
You don't attack us, we don't attack you.
- Jae Young. - Two buckets?
You pour that bucket in our bowl,
you go out with So Min.
(You pour that bucket here, you go out with So Min.)
Why did you say that?
(She's trying to keep a straight face.)
- Why! - You like it, don't you?
He's not okay with it!
- How do you know? - Jae Young.
You pour that bucket in our bowl,
Seok Jin will be your agent starting tomorrow.
(You pour that bucket in here, Seok Jin becomes your agent.)
(Hello, Jae Young. I'm your new agent.)
You'll have to take care of him then.
It must be awkward.
I'm coming to pick you up,
but you're driving.
Can you trust him with your car?
(Pour a bucket of water,)
(and date So Min.)
(Or pour a bucket of water, and drag your elderly agent around.)
(Jae Young will choose.)
- I'll pour here. - Good!
(He chose to date So Min.)
(It beats having Seok Jin as your agent.)
You and I are going out.
Pour it, Jae Young!
- A new couple! - A new couple!
(He found a lover with a bucket of water.)
Congratulations.
- Okay! - Get his number!
I didn't know pouring water could be this exciting.
(His heart is racing.)
She's excited. So Min likes it.
Kwang Soo is my role model.
(Kwang Soo is my role model.)
- As in dating your guest member? - What are you talking about?
(He broke the walls with the power of love.)
I heard Jae Seok was Kwang Soo's role model.
Because he found his wife at work.
Like the coach, like the student.
- That's right. - That's right.
Now I'm connecting the dots.
It all relates in the end.
(From Jae Seok to Kwang Soo, and now to So Min.)
- Next question. - Let's get this one right.
- So we can pour it to them. - To the pink team.
They only have about two buckets to go.
We're almost there.
According to...
the research team at the University of Sterling in the UK,
(According to the research team at the University of Sterling.)
(They're about to listen to all the reports on relationships.)
Another research?
Research is good.
When people find an attractive person of opposite sex,
this changes first.
- Male or female? - Me!
- What is this? - Let me answer!
My answer is their smile.
- Smile? - Yes.
- Let me answer! - Gender doesn't matter?
[VIU Ver] SBS E445 Running Man
"Secret Couple Amid the Battle of Singles"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
- Let me answer! - Gender doesn't matter?
(Ji Hyo's answer)
Voice.
- She said "voice". - Their voice.
Correct!
That was easier than I thought.
- That was too easy. - Their voice changes?
- That's easy. - Oh, really?
Let's go.
Me again?
Yes, you go ahead.
- Me? - Yes, you choose.
- Fill up theirs. - Yes, fill it up.
- Let's start by eliminating a team. - Right.
Jae Young!
- Think about So Min. - Yes?
If you have a tiny bit of feelings for her...
Oh, please. Stop it.
If you have feelings...
You go watch a movie with her,
have a drink, and take her home, then fine.
(If you're going to ask her out on a date, we'll take it.)
We'll take it.
(Will they able to go...)
(on a date over a bucket of water?)
- I'll pour it over there. - Why?
(He practically asked her out on a date.)
- Why! - What does this mean?
- What does this mean? - He likes you!
Then, well...
- We have no choice but to take it. - Jae Young.
Pour it like a man.
- He did it like a man. - Like a man.
Good.
You have to do it this week.
- It's still not filled up. - It's not.
- It's not. - They need one more.
If we get it right this time, we'll pour it in there.
Allies for this round?
- Sure, allies. - Allies.
- Don't do that. - They need to be kept in check!
Think about the big picture here.
- I'll take them out to be sure. - We got his command.
Are you sure about this?
You pour it in there...
I think it's right to do so.
- Take them out. - No!
- It's far from full yet. - We need to get the next question.
We just have to guess the right answer.
Kwang Soo's going to try harder now.
- I'm going to get the right answer. - Let's get it.
He hurt my feelings.
Next question, please.
According to...
the research of the State University of New York...
Now I know the way Americans date.
When a small argument or conflict...
between a couple is leading up to a breakup,
- Yes. - Yes.
you can overcome the crisis with this solution.
What is this solution?
- I have an answer. - I have an answer.
(Kwang Soo who figured out the American relationship style.)
A passionate kiss.
(American relationship style, a passionate kiss.)
Incorrect.
- Like physical affection... - I have an answer.
I have an answer.
They swear at each other.
(They swear at each other.)
- I have an answer. - They can relieve their stress.
I have an answer. They watch a movie together.
- I can't think of an answer. - Wait.
- I have an answer. - I have an answer.
- I have an answer. - He has an answer.
- Jae Young? - A horror movie.
A horror movie?
(Specifically, watch a horror movie together.)
- That was quite close. - I have an answer.
I have an answer.
They watch a romantic movie.
A romantic movie.
(Watching a romantic movie together is correct.)
- Okay, a romantic movie. - A romantic movie.
(Based on research, they tend to look for something comforting.)
- I got it correct. - That's right.
I did it, Jong Kook.
- Thank you. - Good job.
Let's take them our first.
- I will. - Let's do that.
They need to be punished.
Let's not make it obvious.
- Is this enough? - Seriously.
You're getting married to me if you pour it in here.
- Okay, let's do that. - Wait.
(Let's do that.)
Okay, let's do that.
(The bucket promises their marriage.)
- That's good for me. - I don't want to.
I don't want to.
- They're almost finished. - They are.
That team needs to be kept in check too.
- That team needs to be. - It's okay.
- It's okay. - Take them out.
- Hey. - Take them out.
- Pass a bucket to them. - Pass it to them too.
- Pass it to them too. - You should do that.
Let's not do that, everyone.
Pour it in.
You're violating our contract.
- Pour it in. - We got it.
Okay.
Pour our last bucket in there.
Hey, Team Youth.
- Let's unite. - Of course.
- Of course. - I've never felt...
negative towards your team.
- Okay go on. Unite then. - Unite.
Go on. We can still get our answers right.
We are going to get it right. We're relationship experts.
- Where? Who? - Here.
(Three dating experts)
They are here.
- They received degrees. - Really?
It hurts my pride that I didn't get anything correct.
To those who are at the age for marriage,
listen to this question carefully.
According to Britain's Daily Mail,
when both male and female look for their partners,
they look for those who look like this person.
- I have an answer. - I have an answer.
- I have an answer. - My mother.
- Their parents. - Their parents.
- Their parents. - Correct.
(That is the correct answer.)
(Their partners look like their parents.)
Finally.
That question was way too easy.
If we work together, they're finished.
We could've finished you before but we chose not to.
(We could've finished you before but we chose not to.)
We chose not to finish you.
Give it to that team.
- To that team. - Go on.
(We're going to backstab you guys like what Jae Young did to us.)
We promised to unite together.
Wait, no.
(They break their unification as soon as they unite.)
(Betrayal always comes back.)
Good job.
- Okay. - That's why you can't be nice.
You'll suffer from it.
(The second bucket...)
Let's go.
(goes to the Team Hello Honey who's known to be kind.)
Because that team is suspected to have a couple.
You're right.
- They're suspicious. - You're right.
Now you have to keep the promise.
Okay, everything looks great.
- Let's do this. - Let's do it.
This question requires an exact answer.
I'll be starting.
According to Professor Robin Dunbar of...
Evolutionary Psychology of Oxford in the UK,
people will lose this...
when they start dating.
- What is this? - I have an answer.
(Haha answers.)
- I have an answer. - It's so obvious.
(If Team Youth gets it correct, Team Hello Honey might be out.)
A close friend.
(Will "A close friend" be the answer?)
Best friend.
- Best friend. - Best friend.
- It has to be more precise. - Your closest friend.
- Your closest friend. - Best friend.
(Best friend is correct.)
(People focus on their partners, they neglect their close friends.)
- The answer... - That was...
- Really? - Women are sometimes like that.
Your team is so smart.
It is claimed that you'll lose your closest friend.
- That's quite common. - It is.
They have a bucket left but we have two left.
You should finish them quickly.
It's time for you to finish them.
- That's right. - We have one bucket left.
We have to finish them. Otherwise, we'll be at risk.
- Give it to us. - Firstly...
- What? - Give it to us.
(Give it to us.)
Okay.
(Immediately)
(There's no reason not to if you asked for it.)
Give them a bucket.
They're finished if they get one more bucket.
Game is all about power.
(Think wise)
(He gets scared.)
- Hold on. - Kwang Soo.
Listen. Even after we're finished,
you need to be able to compete with them.
Look at the gap between yours and theirs.
You should give them two buckets.
You have to keep them in check.
You need to balance this out.
- You should've. - You need to balance it.
One bucket won't make a difference.
- We have a long way to go. - We have a long way.
- Wait. - Think carefully.
- You need to compete with them. - When we are out,
- you need to compete with them. - The difference is too big.
- They will win for sure. - That's right.
(Team Honey Hello seems to be saying the right thing.)
- You'll be done soon anyway. - It needs to be balanced.
- Think wise. - But...
- Should we trust you? - Really.
- We gave a lot before so... - Seriously.
- we will accept what you gave us. - Okay.
Let's make a deal this time. Give it to them.
- Really. - We will give it to them next time.
- We promise. - Okay, that's a promise.
If we win, we will win anyway after giving one bucket away.
- You'll be finished. - Yes, you will.
Let's do this.
We have to do this.
Let's go against them until the end.
We're finished anyway if Team Comedians gets it correct this time.
- Both teams will be done. - You're right.
If we get it correct this time,
we can give a bucket each to them.
Both teams will be finished.
Let's get it correct. Let's go, Team Honey Hello.
- We got this. - We just have to try our best.
Next question.
According to the National Centre for Biotechnology in the UK,
couples who have relationships of such...
gain an average of 2kg a year.
- I have an answer. - What kind of relationship is this?
A long distance relationship.
- This... - I have an answer.
A happy couple.
(A happy couple is the correct answer.)
(Seok Jin gets the first and last one right, leading his team to win.)
It was a happy couple.
- A happy couple. - A happy couple who are in love.
- Goodness. - Good job.
- Let's do this. - Seok Jin.
- Give them a bucket each. - A bucket each.
- We need to finish them. - It was about happiness.
Yes, it was.
- Happiness. - A happy couple.
- A couple in love. - Well...
Goodness.
- It's going to overflow. - We have no choice.
- They're finished. - Are they finished?
Now, for the other team.
Go to the other team.
Are they not done yet?
- Finished. - They're the same,
(Followed by Team Youth, Team Hello Honey is out too.)
I have had faith in you now since the first question.
- I know, right. - Seriously.
Should we pass over the punishment to the loser through another match?
Go on.
- What else can we do? - Let's get it correct.
- Let's do it. - Let's get it right.
We have to get it right.
That'll be two buckets.
This is...
That will be too much.
According to Professor Hazan of Cornell University...
He has the same alphabet for his surname as me.
How long does a relationship last before its expiry date?
- I have an answer. - I have an answer.
Let me answer.
What?
Two years and a half?
A year and six months.
I think that's correct.
- I have an answer. - I have an answer.
(So Min, an expert of breakup answers.)
So Min, think about your experience.
When did you...
break up with him? When did he...
(What's wrong with her?)
What are you doing?
- I'll answer it. - That was scary.
- 3, 2... - Come on.
900 days.
(Correct)
Is it 900 days?
(Goosebumps)
- Is it 900 days? - Is it for real?
Did you calculate that?
- She was calculating it. - Did you?
I'm getting goosebumps.
She calculated it.
No, that's not it.
I broke up twice after 900 days.
- Really? - My gosh.
Anyway, So Min did a good job.
Your experience helped us.
She is truly a dating expert.
That was incredible.
That was...
- Let's do this. - Sorry about this.
1, 2, 3.
(Splash)
Wait.
- Is this for real? - What was that?
- What was that? - What were you doing?
I didn't get a drop of it.
- What were you trying to do? - This is unbelievable.
- It was too obvious. - Wait, no...
- It was so heavy. - What did you do?
Aren't they the couple in real life?
- Wait. - Ji Hyo.
- Right. - It was so heavy that...
- I threw it in the wrong direction. - Okay, let's move on.
- Seriously. - Okay.
Okay, next please.
This is...
Are they a couple?
What's up with you and Jong Kook?
- They seem different. - What's going on?
Ji Hyo, why did you do that?
Look at that. Jong Kook looks very happy.
Listen.
- Seriously. - I didn't even think about it.
What was that?
Hey.
Don't go so hard.
Ji Hyo...
Both of you, that was unfair.
We need to suspect them. Do you get what I mean?
We will know after this round.
- We will be watching you. - Was it on purpose?
1, 2, 3.
(If she acts suspicious again, they're definitely a secret couple.)
What?
What are you doing?
(That seemed so suspicious.)
Wait. You should try holding this.
Does it make sense that Ji Hyo can't do this?
- I'm being serious. - Ji Hyo.
- I'm being serious. - That was too obvious.
- That was so unfair. - Try it yourself.
Okay then.
What kind of punishment is that?
Okay, we will ask for a hint.
Only one of the four of you come and get the hint.
I'll go.
Why would you go?
(I'll go then.)
- Let's make this fair. - Rock, scissors and paper.
Rock, scissors, paper.
(The result)
(Hee Jin is chosen.)
- I knew it. - I knew it.
Unbelievable.
- Gosh. - How did that happen?
I chose scissors.
That's annoying.
- That seems weird. - I don't understand...
- Hee Jin. - Yes?
- Let's share the hint. - We should.
- Hee Jin, you should check and... - Yes?
- I don't want to. - Do you not want to?
- "I don't want to" - I like that.
- I like the way she said. - She doesn't want to.
Here are the hints for the secret couple and the relationship virgin.
- You can choose one. - Look at her mouth.
If she picks the hint for the relationship virgin,
she's definitely one of the secret couple.
- He said "relationship virgin". - He did.
- Did she say "relationship virgin"? - I heard she said "virgin".
- I did hear "relationship". - I heard "virgin".
- I only heard that. - Yes.
- Right? - She mouthed "relationship virgin".
- I heard "virgin". - She should share it with us.
Hee Jin.
If you don't share it with us, you're the secret couple.
That makes sense.
- Hee Jin, share it with us. - Okay.
People will think you are the secret couple otherwise.
- The secret couple. - That's right.
- What? - You will be suspected.
- Come on. - I don't want to share it.
(She refuses to share the hint.)
I heard "Relationship virgin".
Okay.
She is the secret couple.
While you were solving the quiz,
the secret couple succeeded in the secret mission.
Really?
(The secret couple succeeded in the secret mission.)
With this suspicion,
- you'll move to the next location. - Okay.
I didn't know there is a school here.
The next mission is...
the Roulette of Fate.
(The Roulette of Fate)
What is that?
- Roulette? - Roulette?
Now, you will play a three-way tug-of-war...
with students.
(A three-way tug-of-war with students)
Tug-of-war...
(Recruit students and play a large-scale tug-of-war.)
Recruit students in a limited amount of time.
The more students you recruit, the more advantageous you will be.
(The team that rings the bell first wins.)
You can only recruit students...
who complete the mission.
(You can only recruit students who complete the mission.)
The mission will be chosen by the roulette.
- Okay. - However,
every team needs one student from a specific major.
- Musical major. Modeling major. - Military science major?
- Military science major. - Military science major.
You need at least one student from your designated major.
Other than that one student, we can recruit...
- as many students as we want. - The major doesn't matter.
- One student. - You can only recruit students...
who complete the mission.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Where are the students of designated majors?)
- Military science. - Military science.
- Military science. - Where is the department?
Where is the department?
Where is the department of military science?
- Military science. - Military science.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Running Man, salute!)
- Hello. - Are you a military science major?
- Yes, I am. - We found one!
(Team Comedians finds a military science major.)
- You are a military science major. - A military science major.
- Let's go. - Hello.
Is he really a military science major?
Military science majors wear a uniform.
- Really? - Yes.
Where is the department? Is it inside?
- Everyone is in the dormitory. - Are there a lot of them?
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- This is incredible. - Let's go.
- How did we get so lucky? - Is there a dormitory inside?
Yes, the first years must live in the dormitory.
- I see. - It took us no time.
It's here.
- This is the dormitory. - I can't believe it.
This is the department of military science.
- We met a student right away. - This is the best.
- It's this building. - Hey, beanpole!
(Kwang Soo, you must be jealous.)
The department of military science.
- Why is it so close? - It's in the separate building.
Where are the musical majors?
(It's their designated major.)
- Where... - This hill is so steep.
- Lee Kwang Soo is handsome! - Lee Kwang Soo is handsome!
(The students are generous.)
(Gosh, girls are following me.)
(Even the girls would be taken aback by his fake fan service.)
They love it.
(Fans, thank you always.)
(Is this a giraffe or a man?)
(He acts like he is in a young adult drama.)
- This is exhausting. - It's that way.
There is a scuba diving club.
That's cool.
- What is that? - Are they musical majors?
- Military science majors? - I think they are musical majors!
- Musical majors! - I think she is right.
Musical majors! Are you musical majors?
It's written on their backs.
- Musical majors. - They are musical majors.
Are you musical majors?
(They find a group of students.)
- Musical majors! - Are you musical majors?
- Come with us! - Are you serious?
They are here.
They are musical majors.
(They run into musical majors in the schoolyard.)
We need all of them.
- Hold on. - Are all of you musical majors?
- Yes! - Yes!
(They have a loud voice and a cheerful spirit.)
(Welcome, Running Man.)
Do you happen to be free? We need to play tug-of-war.
Yes!
(We are totally free!)
- There is a mission. - If you complete the mission...
- Then you can come with us. - Okay.
Since we picked modeling major,
let's go to the department of modeling.
- My goodness. - This is fascinating.
Maybe we can learn how to walk.
Let's go.
Why are there no students?
This is the department of modeling.
Let's go. Let's go.
- My goodness. - My goodness, this is...
My goodness.
Hello, this is...
- Hello. - They don't disappoint.
- They are tall. - I need to be on my tiptoes.
They are so tall.
- Hello. - Hello.
We need your help to complete...
the mission.
(We would love to help.)
It looks like you were practicing.
It looks like you were practicing for the runway.
We were practicing our walk.
Would you show us your walk?
(We want to see modeling majors' walk.)
That came out of nowhere.
We are curious.
(I will show you.)
(His stage manners are the best.)
He must be an ace.
(How good will be the walk of the confident ace?)
(He looks like a model.)
(He walks down the runway with his long legs.)
He is cool.
He is an ace.
He is handsome.
(The ace is chic.)
(Hs is the ace.)
Who else wants to go?
Here comes another one.
Here comes another one. My goodness.
(He has an impressive walk and a chic facial expression.)
(He has stage manners.)
Who else wants to go?
- Jae Young was a model. - He was a model.
(He is a senior model!)
Check out the senior model's walk.
- Senior model! - Walk down the runway.
- Senior model! - Show us.
- Senior model! - Music, please.
It has been years.
- Senior model! - Senior model!
- Senior model! - Here he comes.
Come on out.
(His steps are seasoned.)
(Your senior model is here.)
(He is as cool as he was on the runway.)
(He shows his talent.)
You are good!
(A senior model sure is different.)
You are cool!
(Walking powerfully)
For goodness' sake.
(For goodness' sake.)
(He becomes embarrassed.)
I am sorry.
It's okay. You are cool.
It has been years.
I am seeing a lot of beautiful people here.
- To be honest, our mission is... - It requires strength.
tug-of-war.
As soon as I walked in, I saw him.
(Burly)
(His big build is perfect for tug-of-war.)
Seriously.
He is so big. Is he a model?
What kind of model are you?
- I am a sports model. - I see.
That makes sense. I knew you weren't...
- a regular model. - He has a big build.
How broad are your shoulders?
- Your shoulders are so broad. - Seriously.
We have a mission. It won't be hard.
Please help us out.
(They can only recruit students who complete the chosen mission.)
Please spin it.
In 1, 2, 3. Okay. That's good.
"Fizzy Drink's Dignity".
(Fizzy Drink's Dignity)
(One member and a student will down a fizzy drink.)
(The mission is a success if they don't burp for 5 seconds.)
Since you work out, you wouldn't have fizzy drinks.
- I like them. - Really?
(He loves fizzy drinks.)
That was unexpected. He likes them.
Now... Okay.
- Don't be nervous. - Okay.
Drink slowly.
Otherwise, it might get caught in your throat.
- Drink slowly. - Drink slowly.
Get ready.
- Set. - Drink slowly.
Go.
Drink slowly. It's okay.
Since he is really big,
drinking a can of Coca-Cola won't be a problem.
We picked the perfect one.
Slowly.
He is fast.
- Check the can. - Are you done?
(He feels the fizz.)
- 3, 4, - It's okay.
- five. - Okay.
(He succeeded in holding it in.)
He did it.
- One, - I don't burp.
2, 3,
4, 5.
Okay.
(They succeed in recruiting 1 modeling major.)
(That was close.)
He said he doesn't burp.
(He can go and play tug-of-war.)
- That's utter nonsense. - His lips...
- were trembling. - All right. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- It was nice to meet you. - Thank you.
- Everyone... - Hold on.
All right.
(Hold on. Don't go!)
(A student volunteers for the second mission.)
You should have come out sooner.
We don't know which mission you will get.
Spin it. In 1, 2, 3.
(What will be the second mission?)
From Feet to Waist.
(Using your lower body only, pull up a band on your ankles...)
(to your waist in 1 minute.)
You are so tall. How tall are you?
- I am 191cm tall. - 191cm tall?
He is as tall as Kwang Soo.
He is my role model.
(He wants to be a model-turned-actor who gets mistaken for a comedian.)
Kwang Soo is?
You resemble Kwang Soo.
My nickname has always been Lee Kwang Soo.
(Is it a good thing or a bad thing?)
People like him are strong.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Get ready.
Set, go.
That's good. That's good.
(The band goes up fast thanks to his long legs.)
He is good. He really resembles Kwang Soo.
- It's on my waist. - It needs to go up higher.
(The band stops at his hips.)
- What should I do? - Roll on the floor.
Roll on the floor.
Come here. Come this way.
There you go. Use friction.
- Okay. - 10 seconds remain.
This is hard.
(Struggling)
- Is it not working? - Use the edge of the desk.
- Use the edge. - Use the edge.
(He tries to drag it up.)
That's good. The edge will do the trick.
- Hold on. Get it in your buttcrack. - 3, 2,
- Get it in your buttcrack. - one.
- Your buttcrack. - You did it!
(The band goes up at the last moment.)
You did it. It went up. It went up a lot.
- Count that as a success. - Seriously.
- It went up to the waist. - Count that as a success.
Count that as a success.
- He has short legs. - We will count it as a success.
- Okay. - Yes!
You did it. That was great.
You need to have that spirit.
It was nice to meet everyone. Thank you.
I hear some guys' voices.
(Team Comedians visits military science department.)
Hello.
- Hello, excuse us. - Hello.
(Military science students welcome them.)
- Goodness. - Hello.
- That's right. - Excuse us.
Let us take a moment.
We're shooting Running Man.
We need people to play tug-of-war with us.
Could you help us?
- Yes. - Yes.
Their voices are strong and loud.
All of them look...
- so strong. - They look strong.
Some of them are sturdy.
- They must be strong. - Jae Seok.
- Seriously. - Here's one.
He looks burly.
We need him.
(He checks his arm muscles.)
Seok Jin, we just met them.
So what?
What if we meet for the first time?
We just met...
By the way,
Seok Jin.
(His way of saying hello is physical.)
- Seok Jin... - I was testing him.
works out these days.
He tries to play arm wrestling whenever he meets someone.
It's to test the strength.
We need strong people.
- We'll spin the roulette. - Go ahead.
Let's spin it.
All right.
(What will be Team Comedians' first mission?)
- "Mouth gag"? - Mouth gag.
- It's Gag Speed Quiz. - Gag Speed Quiz.
(Gag Speed Quiz)
(Pass on a keyword with a gag and earplugs on.)
(They must get 6 or more keywords correct within 1 minute.)
(Success)
This is rarely used.
Except on variety shows,
- we don't get to use it. - No one uses it.
All right.
It's strange to wear it outside.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Please turn around.
Tap and turn around.
(Hee Jin answers, and Seok Jin gives keywords.)
Get ready.
(Sizzling)
"Sizzling".
(He hears the keyword.)
We don't have much time.
- "Gargling". - "Gargling"?
(He easily understands.)
"Sizzling".
Here it comes.
That was great.
"Sizzling".
- "Sizzling". - Correct.
(They get 1 correct.)
That was great.
(They must get 5 more correct to succeed.)
"Gurgling".
(I got it.)
(What is he saying?)
That student, Joon Soo, is the problem.
(Thankfully, he understood the correct word.)
(It's a bit worrisome.)
"Gurgling".
"Sliding"?
(The second answer is wrong.)
Please, Joon Soo!
(I'll do better this time.)
"Crawling".
(It sounded accurate.)
"Smile radiantly".
Joon Soo!
(Joon Soo gets it wrong again.)
(He understands the correct keyword.)
"Crawling".
(It's interesting.)
- "Crawling". - Okay.
(They have 30 seconds left.)
Okay, you did well, Joon Soo.
(Get 4 more correct.)
We don't have time.
(Colorful)
(Sticking out his tongue)
"Colorful".
(His pronunciation is accurate, but his face is wrong.)
(They're shocked by his look.)
(I understand what it is.)
(Joon Soo says, "Flare up".)
(Please, Joon Soo!)
(Interestingly enough, he says the correct keyword.)
"Here and there"?
(The answer becomes wrong again.)
(What is he saying? They got this one wrong.)
What?
"Colorful"?
(Her answer is correct.)
That's amazing.
- What happened? - That was good. Keep going.
- What happened? - All right.
(They only have 20 seconds.)
(Gulping)
"Gulping".
(They must answer 3 more correct.)
(They pass on the word accurately and quickly.)
"Gulping".
(They answer 4 correct.)
Answer two more.
(They must get 2 more correct in 15 seconds.)
- We need two more. - "Shivering".
(He also makes a movement.)
(Joon Soo passes it on accurately.)
"Daseul, daseul"?
(However it's wrong.)
("Shivering" turns into something incomprehensible.)
(Will Hee Jin answer correctly?)
"Shivering"?
- "Daseul, daseul"? - "Shivering"?
(She's an expert at interpreting words through gags.)
What's going on?
How did you answer correctly?
(They need to answer 1 more in 7 seconds.)
Hurry up.
- What is it? - Here it comes.
"Panting and puffing".
(They immediately fail if there's an accident in passing on.)
It's the last one.
(If they answer correctly, they can invite 3 of them.)
"Panting and puffing".
(Her answer is correct.)
(They win Gag Speed Quiz.)
(They invite 3 students from the military science department.)
Good job.
(Team Comedians has recruited them.)
Can we take all of them? That's good.
- We got it. - The two work well together.
Goodness.
He kept making mistakes.
Seriously.
He made mistakes several times.
- Goodness. - Though he made mistakes,
she answered correctly.
We got three students.
- It's a success. - Success.
(After many ups and downs,)
(they finish recruiting military science majors.)
Only those who succeed can come with us.
We don't have time.
- Hurry. - We don't have time.
Who wants to go?
Come out if you're strong.
(Everyone who is strong should come out.)
One of you should come.
That's great.
(I want to go.)
Come this way.
Stand here for now.
- Spin it. - Spin it hard.
(Which mission will Team Youth get?)
"From Feet to Waist."
(They must raise the band from the ankles to the waist.)
It'll be better to take off your coat.
You can do it.
Be careful around the bottom.
- You can do it. - Okay, okay.
Start.
- Raise it up. - Raise it up.
- She's fast. - That's good.
You're doing well.
That's great.
(Her dancing can be seen in her flexibility.)
- She's fast. - That's good.
Hurry.
It got stuck.
Please, please.
Please raise it up.
- I can't help you. - Raise it up.
I'm sorry.
- What is he doing? - You're doing well.
(My bottom is so annoying.)
- What's going on? - Haha.
- I got it. - Here you go, Haha.
- Please. - Use my foot.
Please.
(I'll raise it by hooking it around foot.)
- I got it. - Did you get it?
(This is it. Try it like this.)
Put out your foot for her.
Use her foot.
(She uses Bona's foot as a stand.)
- You have 10 seconds. - 10 seconds.
Please, please.
(Struggling)
Be careful.
(Something hurts her.)
Hold on.
She said she would do it on her own.
(I'm sorry for what happened in front of the camera.)
Do it yourself.
(It gets through.)
(She succeeds with a strange movement.)
It's a success.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. - It's okay.
I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
Bona, apologize to her. You only met her a moment ago.
(He feels very apologetic.)
Apologize.
- Apologize to her. - It's okay.
I'm sorry.
(The whole team bows to apologize.)
I'm very sorry.
No, it's okay.
Thank you.
Here it is.
(Another student gets ready to go.)
(Goodness)
This is very difficult.
(Something goes wrong during the mission.)
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Are you okay?
- Are you okay? - She sat down.
She sat down.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
Will you be okay? I'm sorry.
(The student wouldn't have known she'd show slapstick at school.)
(I'm sorry and thank you.)
- Did we succeed, didn't we? - Shall I go?
You go first.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
(Succeed and join us for tug-of-war.)
Let's go. Come with us.
Get ready.
Start.
- Keep going. - They're good.
(The time limit is 1 minute.)
(His long legs are useful for times like this.)
That's good.
(He uses his legs to raise the band.)
- Is this it? - Put your bottoms together.
(He gives useful advice.)
(They get to it.)
Put your bottoms together.
(They put them together.)
(The contact of their bottoms seems mysterious.)
(It probably needs to be blurred.)
(What is going on?)
No.
Hook it if it doesn't work.
Hook it.
(He gives support with his foot.)
(Pulling up)
(He successfully raises the band.)
Hook it for Kwang Soo.
(I'll raise yours too.)
(Pushing)
(There's another accident.)
It's not done yet.
(They're speechless.)
It's gross.
(I'll do it properly.)
Your time is up.
- He got it. This is safe. - Good job.
We'll accept it.
(One more musical major succeeds.)
Thank goodness that you didn't fail.
- He was amazing. - He worked hard.
He did such a good job.
I was startled by how good you were.
(Team Youth recruits 2 students.)
From Feet to Waist.
Seung Woo is...
burly too.
(Se Chan plays with a military science student.)
Get ready.
Start.
- Move a lot. - That's right.
(They move their legs quickly.)
That's right.
- Raise it. - That's right.
- He got it. - Yes.
That's right. You're doing well.
That's good.
That's it. That's it.
(He twists fiercely.)
That's it.
- Hook it. - That's good.
(He uses the doorknob.)
You almost got it.
- Hook it. - You almost got it.
(Seung Woo becomes silent all of a sudden.)
Goodness. Your pants...
Time out.
Wait, his pants...
Seung Woo.
Are you okay?
(The back of his pants is open.)
This is not how to do it.
(His pants burst open due to his fierce twisting.)
Seung Woo.
Are you okay?
His pants...
(Comrade, you fought bravely.)
I'm sorry.
(The mission is stopped.)
(Poor student)
- I heard a loud noise. - Oh, no.
(He testifies it right away.)
We'll accept it as a success.
(His efforts are considered a success.)
You did a good job.
(Thank you.)
- Are you okay, Seung Woo? - Thank you.
Let's do it.
(They pick the last mission.)
- "Master of Facial Expression". - "Master of Facial Expression".
It's Master of Facial Expression.
(By using facial muscles, take off 10 sticky notes...)
(within one minute.)
- Master of Facial Expression. - I'll try.
(Someone volunteers.)
- That's good. - Come out.
- Play, Hee Jin. - Hee Jin.
Go, Hee Jin.
- Jang Hee Jin. - Let's go.
(Okay, I'll try.)
(They stick 10 sticky notes.)
His face is oily.
(This student's face is oily.)
When I stick it, it falls off.
They'll fall off easily.
The more oily his face is, the better it is.
(Is this a good thing?)
All right.
Here we go. Get ready.
- Get ready. - Start.
(The time limit is 1 minute.)
Make facial expressions.
(The sticky notes fall off easily as soon as he starts.)
- That's it. - That's good.
Make facial expressions.
Make a face. That's good.
You're doing well.
That's good. Use facial muscles.
Yes, frown your face. That's good.
- You're doing well. - Hee Jin.
Hee Jin, Hee Jin.
(She shakes her head violently.)
Seong Hwan.
- Seong Hwan. - Shake it.
Shake it and throw your head back.
(It must be the most difficult task he's ever had at school.)
(Take it off, comrade.)
- It's not working. - Kim Seong Hwan.
- They only have one. - Shake it.
No, I got it.
I got it.
- She got it. Next is Seong Hwan. - She got it.
- Seong Hwan. - Seong Hwan.
- I got it. - You have one left.
- Hurry. - You have one left.
- Hurry. - It's the last one.
- Only one left! - Let's go.
Wink.
- Kim Seong Hwan. - Let's go.
- Kim Seong Hwan. - He got it.
(They blow on it.)
It's not working.
Go easy on him now.
I'm dizzy.
(He gives up.)
(He fails after shaking too much.)
- Goodness. - That was so close.
(You still did a good job.)
- Why was it completely stuck? - It wouldn't come off.
You worked hard, Seong Hwan.
Good job.
(They fail to recruit 1 more student.)
(Each team finishes recruiting students.)
Let's check...
the number of members on each team.
There are nine members on Jae Seok's team.
There are 12 members on Kwang Soo's team.
- We can do this. - We have many.
- It's worth playing. - Yes.
- It's worth playing. - This is great.
There are 11 members on Jong Kook's team.
They look so strong.
We lost.
We're through.
Each team will grab the rope.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Which team will be the winner?)
(Jong Kook leads 11 strong young men.)
(Team Comedians and strong military science majors)
(Team Youth and 12 students)
Let's go, Team Youth.
(It's the biggest tug-of-war.)
(The competition starts now.)
(Which team will get closer...)
(to finding out the secret couple?)
(They start to hunt down the secret couple.)
(As the search is narrowed down, they get closer to the couple.)
(A shocking twist surprises the singles.)
(Which tactless couple will ruin the party for singles?)
(And)
(Honey)
(Warm month of April)
(A sweet birthday present for So Min)
(It's a dreamlike date only for So Min)
(At the same time and same space)
(Members are locked in by someone.)
(So Min is behind a series of mysterious events.)
(Even her family and her lover don't know who she really is.)
("Her Secret Personal Life")