(The scents from flowers are heightened on this spring day.)
- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
- Good morning. - Hi.
All right. Please move back. You're too close.
- You look aggressive. - Okay.
- Right. I'm a bit excited. - You flustered me.
We're starting separately today.
- Yes. Everyone starts separately. - Okay.
- It's an individual race today. - It's an individual race.
We prepared today's special episode...
to celebrate the Great Teacher of Korea,
Sejong the Great.
It's a special episode for the Teachers' Day.
It's Sejong the Great's Riddle Race.
Is that so?
How is Sejong the Great relevant to the race?
In 1965,
we decided to celebrate Teachers' Day on May 15...
- which was the king's birthday. - His birthday was on May 15.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Teachers' Day?
(The rules will be announced in light of his birthday.)
In the final round, you will solve a riddle about Sejong the Great.
The member that survives will win the race...
and win the cash prize.
My gosh.
You will be able to win...
Chance Cards at mission spots by accomplishing the missions...
before anyone else.
Chance Cards? Okay.
Four spots for the Chance Cards...
- are labeled by keywords. - Thank you.
"Four Best Chance Cards. Choose a keyword from below..."
"and move to the designated places."
"Science, War, Korean Alphabets, and 10 Dollars".
However, if you're the only one at the mission spot,
you'll receive the Chance Card upon arrival.
However, if there are other members at the mission spot,
you'll have a match, and the member who wins the match...
will only receive the Chance Card.
It's about the mind game. I see.
- If I'm alone, it's a guarantee. - Yes.
I'm sure a lot of people will choose the Korean Alphabets or 10 Dollars.
(Lady Luck thinks those two will be popular.)
I bet a lot of people will go here.
Money, money, money. Gosh, money.
As for War...
(Let's see which member will be compatible.)
It's Jong Kook's.
(He's the king when it comes to war.)
I should...
choose War.
(That's why he goes with War.)
I will go and participate in a war.
Just like that?
I'm not supposed to make a quick decision?
I'll get in the car and feel people out first.
(Everyone heads to the mission spots.)
The keyword, War, grabbed my eyes.
All right. Let's call to find out where they'll be going to.
(Whom will Se Chan call first?)
Hey, punk.
(It's Jong Kook, the most powerful member on the show.)
(There's a man who loves you to the bits)
- Hello, Jong Kook. - Hey.
- Hey, which one will you pick? - Yes?
Doesn't one of the keywords remind you of me?
Remind of you? Is it War?
(Suddenly, there's a riddle to solve.)
(That's correct!)
You'll go with War?
I ought to go for War.
Whoever comes, there will be a war.
I chose the same keyword.
I guess I'm destined to be crushed by you today.
- Right. - Okay.
If you try to survive, you'll die.
- Okay. - If you try to die, you'll survive.
(Come if you can handle me.)
Jong Kook, I'll call you later.
- See you later. - Okay, Jong Kook.
My goodness, Se Chan.
(Since I already checked on the strongest guy...)
I should call the weakling of the weaklings.
(I should call the weakling of the weaklings.)
- Hey, Se Chan. - Hey, Seok Jin.
- Hey. - Where are you?
Don't be a sly rat, and tell me where you're going.
I already talked to Jong Kook earlier.
He said he's definitely going to the spot for Science.
(Actually, he'll be heading to the spot for War.)
(Se Chan gives him false information.)
(Will Seok Jin fall for it?)
If he said that, he'll go by all means.
(His instincts are too weak.)
Exactly. He said he's going there for sure.
With that said, the only member...
I can easily beat is you.
(He's brutally honest.)
- Hey. Do you want to fight me? - I'll go up against you.
- Hey. I might just crush you. - I want to go up against you.
What about 10 Dollars? Meet me at the spot for 10 Dollars.
- Are you really going there? - I'm serious.
I'm already on my way there.
Seok Jin, wait for me. I'll be on my way.
- Okay. - Okay.
Sir, please drive me to the spot for War.
(He fell for Se Chan's trick.)
(After getting tricked by Se Chan, at the spot for the War...)
I suit the keyword well. It'll be war everywhere.
I don't care if he comes or not. Someone is calling.
(This strong guy's phone is ringing off the hook.)
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Hello.
I chose War.
It's been a while.
I see. Jong Kook.
(If you chose War...)
Then, I can only choose from...
Science, Korean Alphabets, and 10 Dollars.
Okay.
When you say you'll do something, you follow through.
Of course. I'm on my way.
Okay. Then, I decided to go to the spot for 10 Dollars.
Yes, the keyword suits you well. It's totally you.
Enjoy the happiness 10 dollars can bring.
- Okay, Jong Kook. - Okay.
(The giraffe hangs up after finding out the tiger's destination.)
I should...
rip off War from this.
He already decided on it.
(Let's not even consider that.)
(Kwang Soo calls someone else after talking to Jong Kook.)
- Hello. - Hi, Haha.
Haha.
Whenever we have these kinds of races, I always end up calling you.
As a matter of fact, I was waiting for you like waiting for an alarm.
- Haha. Where are you? Let's meet. - Yes?
Are you trying to get back at me?
(No good will come from our meeting.)
If that's what you have in mind...
(In Episode 440, the Dirty Brothers joined hands.)
(Snatching)
(Kwang Soo dearly paid for Haha's last-minute revenge.)
- Let's put that behind us. - Haha.
Let bygone be bygone. Think about it.
I couldn't help myself back then because I was angry at you too.
I'll apologize for that.
(We should try living a clean life.)
(Kwang Soo, will you accept my apology?)
If you're still bitter about it,
meet me at the mission spot for War.
Let's meet there, Haha.
(Let's meet there, Haha.)
(He turns down a chance to turn over a new leaf.)
(Will he say yes to this dirty, muddy fight?)
I thought about this, but it's unlikely that I'll be the only one.
(I thought about this, but it's unlikely that I'll be the only one.)
I want to go up against you and Seok Jin.
(I want to go up against you and Seok Jin.)
(Let's have a fair fight with the weaklings.)
Sure. Let's do a tough one like real men.
I'd love to.
- Okay. - Meet me at War.
- Okay. - Sure.
(Come to the spot for War right now.)
Sir, please drive me to the spot for 10 Dollars.
I won't get off there. I'll scope out the area.
If someone gets lucky, he or she can be the only one there.
It's Jae Seok.
Hey, Jae Seok.
Where are you, Seok Jin?
Where do you think? I'm just in the car.
Where are you heading to now?
The guys seem to come to the spot that I'm going to.
(I'm very popular today.)
They don't want to go where Jong Kook is going to.
Okay. Where is Jong Kook going?
He's going to the spot for War.
My gosh. Come on, seriously.
(He lies that Jong Kook chose War, thinking Jong Kook chose Science.)
You were going to choose War, right?
I was about to go there.
My gosh, you can't go there.
Jong Kook will go to the spot for War?
Yes, he will.
We shouldn't let him take the Card all by himself.
No. Just let him have that.
- Okay. I got it. - We should let him.
Okay.
Hey, I might be the only one at the mission spot for War.
My gosh, I should...
I should tell the other members.
I should spread this rumor.
(His plan is to spread the news, so no one comes to the spot.)
Jong Kook is headed to the spot for War.
Then, I'll avoid choosing War today.
Jong Kook is heading to the mission spot for War. Just don't go there.
Is that so?
Then, I should avoid going there too.
- Okay, Seok Jin. - Hey.
See you at War. Wait, no. I won't be there.
(He slips as he's not careful.)
(However, the only downside is that Jong Kook is really headed there.)
(The entrance of the mission spot for 10 Dollars is empty.)
No one is really here.
(Kwang Soo arrives at an empty entrance of Dosan Park.)
Staying here is a way too. Okay.
I'm serious.
(15 minutes before the time is up, he's at the spot for 10 Dollars.)
I just need to stay here for 15 minutes.
(If you think I'm a dirty player, go somewhere else.)
What?
(1 mysterious vehicle approaches the mission spot.)
(Who is it?)
Hey.
Why did you come here?
(Who is this member that showed up in front of Kwang Soo?)
(Jae Seok the Rabbit ran away from Jong Kook the Tiger.)
My gosh.
Why are you here?
I'm guarding this place.
- Why are you guarding this place? - I'm guarding this place.
I'm going to win the Chance Card whatever it takes.
- Get lost. - How could you say that?
What are you talking about?
Let me wait here for a second.
(Seok Jin arrives at the spot for War with 12 minutes left.)
I think the rumor I spread worked.
The rumor that Jong Kook is headed here.
(Seok Jin's waiting at the spot.)
I might be able to get this place all to myself.
This might be all mine.
(However, at that moment...)
Someone is coming.
My gosh, who is it?
(A mysterious vehicle approaches Seok Jin's car.)
Who is it?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(I already got the word out.)
Who is it?
(This member bravely shows up at the mission spot for War.)
(Who is the member that has arrived at this very spot?)
(It's none other than...)
(Jong Kook the Tiger who only had eyes for War.)
Sir. Sir.
Sir.
We must hurry.
Please go to the closest mission spot from here.
I don't care where it is. It just can't be here.
(Take me anywhere that Jong Kook isn't at.)
My gosh, I spread the rumor. Why...
Gosh, that wasn't a rumor.
Let's check if anyone else is here.
(Jong Kook arrives with 8 minutes left.)
(And another car arrives at the spot for War.)
(And the member that arrives this time is...)
(Se Chan.)
(And he spots someone.)
Okay.
(Seok Jin's stylist couldn't tag along.)
Okay. The weakest guy is in there.
Seok Jin is here. Okay.
I hear noises.
- Let's do this. - Someone came.
Mr. 54-year-old.
(Hello, my weak Mr. 54-year-old...)
(No, it's the strongest brother.)
- Hello. - Hey.
You're not Seok Jin.
Jong Kook, what happened?
- Okay. - I mean...
- You really chose this one. - You bet.
You said...
if I tried to survive, I'd die.
- And vice versa. - Right.
After hearing that, I came here to survive.
- But I'll die in the end. - Right.
- I'll die in the end. - See?
- Okay. I don't know what it is. - It's just me?
I'm not sure. Will we have more people?
(Will they start the mission for War like this?)
(Hey! Someone else came.)
Gosh, why did he come here?
(Haha, another guy looking for his grave site)
Gosh, Se Chan.
- Haha is here. - Gosh.
Why did you come here?
I came here to have a war.
This means one of the members will be alone.
(So Min is almost at another mission spot.)
Why are there so many people? Who is it?
Who is it?
Seok Jin didn't come?
Isn't that Jae Seok?
I thought he chose War.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors. Okay!
(Clueless of So Min's arrival, these two keep bickering.)
Wait. Hold up!
Guys!
So Min, why did you come here?
I thought you...
- So Min, listen. - were heading to War.
That's where Jong Kook is.
Why?
Is this how we play this?
- What are we doing? - Good.
So Min, you'll do the mission for the keyword, 10 Dollars.
What are we doing?
(It's settled that three of them will do the mission.)
I cannot believe that Jong Kook came. Seriously.
(This 54-year-old rabbit is running away from the tiger.)
I'm nervous. Who else will be here?
I hope no one is here. Please.
Please. Please.
(The spot for 10 dollars is empty.)
No one is here.
I think no one came.
(He jumps to conclusions again.)
No one came, right?
(He has no idea that the others already went in.)
Where is the spot? Is this it?
Should I go in?
No one is here. Okay.
(Seok Jin keeps assuming today.)
I don't even see the cars. There are no cars here.
(He's excited at the hope of getting the Chance Card.)
No one is here.
- Here. I got it. - Tell us the mission already.
There it is. One more member will join you.
- Who is that? - Is that Seok Jin?
Why is he coming here?
- Why did you come here? - Darn it.
Seok Jin!
Hey, why are you guys here?
(The 54-year-old rabbit runs into the trap he set up.)
Why are you guys here?
- I thought you were taking a walk. - We're doomed.
Why did you come here?
It was because of Jong Kook.
I came here to run away from him.
What about the Korean Alphabets? You should've gone there.
Gosh, this is exhausting.
This means that a Chance Card will be granted to someone right away.
- Yes, that's right. - It's Jong Kook.
- You'll find out later. - Three spots are left.
It's either Science or the Korean Alphabets.
(Science, War, Korean Alphabets, and 10 Dollars)
Is this the spot?
(Ji Hyo arrives at the spot for Science with 4 minutes left.)
Yes.
Since you're the only one who's at the mission spot,
you've acquired the Chance Card.
I told you. Everyone tried to deceive each other.
There's no point in going there.
(She's indeed Lady Luck.)
Among 4 Chance Cards, you can only choose 1.
There's no dud, right? Are they all the same?
(She can choose 1 out of 4.)
Is this it?
(Ji Hyo obtains the Chance Card which will help in the final race.)
Starting my day with these minnows will be exhausting.
The mission for the keyword, 10 Dollars,
is...
Blow for the Money.
(Blow for the Money)
- "Blow for the Money"? - All right.
It will be a tournament in pairs.
You will blow away the flour in the bowl.
And the member who figures out the amount of money...
under the flour will win the match.
(Okay. We understood the rules.)
Even before...
we heard what the mission was, Seok Jin said,
"Do it with me."
(Whispering)
(Just now, the rules were being announced to them.)
(When he said it'd be done in pairs...)
Do it with me.
(Do it with me.)
(The weakest guy picks the weakest girl.)
I'm the weakest here.
Everyone knows here that I'm the weakest.
If this happened on a blind date...
or in a situation like that,
- Right, right. - It's a heart-fluttering moment.
"Hey, do it with me."
(It would've been heart-fluttering.)
(Team up with me.)
This is like...
- holding hands under the table. - Right.
(This is like holding hands under the table in secret.)
- It'd look like that. - But this is a competition.
Gosh, you're so low.
But this is a competition.
Everyone, pair up with an opponent you'll compete against.
All right.
- Should we flip for it? - Let's do that.
- Why? You two can do it. - Let's flip for it.
- Or rock-paper-scissors? - Okay.
(They'll choose their opponent after playing rock-paper-scissors?)
- Okay. That sounds good. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Jin and So Min lose.)
(He won't be able to pick So Min for his opponent.)
I can't ever win.
The winner gets to pick.
(He confirms it once again.)
- We'll pick our opponent. - Yes.
(Looking determined)
I'm very popular when it comes to choosing opponents, you know?
(Weak So Min gets popular.)
But both of you are popular today.
Right. That's so true.
- Both of you are popular. - Stop it.
Get ready.
Rock-paper-scissors.
My gosh. This is intense.
- It's intense for no reason. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Who will be the winner of this intense-for-no-reason match?)
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Okay! So Min!
(Okay! So Min!)
I don't feel good about this at all. Not at all.
You're so petty.
- How could you choose her? - So Min.
So Min!
Okay. Seok Jin.
- So Min and Kwang Soo will go 1st. - They'll go 1st.
You can't be sure. So Min might win.
- Yes, I might win. - You can't be sure.
- Right. - Who knows?
- How are we supposed to play? - The flour...
(The game is set up now.)
All right. Under the flour,
- there's money. - I see.
The one who writes down the amount in the back will win.
(They must blow out the flour to figure out the amount.)
Will there be coins?
There will be coins.
- There are many types of bills. - That's hard.
- The total amount? - Write down the total amount.
That's hard.
- My gosh, this sounds hard. - This isn't easy.
Get ready.
- Set. Go. - Get ready.
(The mission for Chance Card starts.)
(He attacks her with the powder as soon as they start.)
(She'll play dirty too. She retaliates.)
(Coughing)
(The game has changed into Blow for the Flour.)
(As they keep on blowing to ruin one another...)
- I can see it. - I can see it.
(They finally find their first dollar.)
(Let me take a breath.)
(She starts attacking him by exhaling into the white flour.)
- Hey, let's work together. - Yes, you have to.
- Yes. - There's too much.
- Let's work together. - How should we...
(She wanted to look at him when they made up.)
Look at him.
(He can't be polite with this face.)
I can't do this. I can't.
I'll choose War.
Korean Alphabets. I'll choose the Korean Alphabet.
(I'm done too.)
(I'm so glad I didn't go up against them.)
(Let's just blow out the flour instead of looking at ourselves.)
- I can see it. I can see the money. - I see it.
(They find the second dollar.)
(And then, the third dollar.)
Is it a foreign currency?
(So Min attacks him.)
No, it's a Korean dollar.
My gosh.
(He counterattacks.)
(They fight for a while.)
- There's one over there. - You're right.
- There's a five-dollar bill. - There's a lot.
(He finds a 50-dollar bill.)
(They finally see all the bills.)
There's money inside.
(Kwang Soo writes 62 dollars.)
(He's wrong.)
- He's wrong. - He is wrong.
(One 50-dollar bill, one 10-dollar bill, three 1-dollar bills.)
So Min, hurry.
There's no time to rest.
(A coin falls.)
(A coin falls from the tray.)
What? Something fell.
(How much is that?)
- What is this? - Is that a nickel?
Is that a nickel?
(She hides the coin.)
Wait. How much was it?
(He's irritated.)
(She throws it.)
How much was it?
(You can go there and find out.)
They're playing...
- It's a nickel. - very dirty.
(She finds another coin.)
55 cents?
(She throws it before Kwang Soo arrives.)
(They're glad to be watching.)
(Clinking)
(She finds another coin.)
- What was it? - Hold on.
(She picks it up.)
There's so much money.
How much was it? Was it a coin?
(So Min writes down her answer.)
(So Min writes 63 dollars and 65 cents.)
63 dollars and 65 cents.
(Is she right?)
- No. - You're wrong.
(How much did I stash away?)
"63 dollars and 65 cents".
- There's a lot of money. - My gosh.
There's a lot.
(There's quite a bit of money hidden.)
(They need to dig in deeper.)
63 dollars...
How can I do this when she's stashing away the money?
You need to explain the rules to her!
(Don't act like a newbie.)
(A bunch of coins falls.)
They fell.
(The total amount of bills is 63 dollars.)
Hey.
(They need to figure out the amount of coins.)
(Kwang Soo writes 63 dollars and 76 cents.)
- Let me answer! - That's wrong.
You're very close.
(Kwang Soo is close?)
It's not 76 cents.
(So Min writes 63 dollars and 75 cents.)
(If she's right, she'll be in the play-off.)
So Min is right.
Why did you write 76 cents?
(That was the answer?)
(So Min will go to the play-off.)
- I was a cent off? - I saw it.
There was a nickel.
(She hid the nickel.)
(Thanks to this nickel, I've won.)
Next time, reduce the number of bills and the amount of flour.
What is the point of making such corrections now?
(Pale)
- Okay. - Okay.
I'm looking forward to this big match.
(This is the 2nd round between 2 middle-aged men.)
(It's Jae Seok versus...)
(Seok Jin.)
It's a big match.
- Let's do this! - It's a big match.
- Get ready. - Okay.
I'll do this.
(Suddenly,)
What are you doing?
(Jae Seok prepares himself.)
We shouldn't have gone first.
- It's important who goes first. - Yes, we could've been prepared.
- We couldn't prepare at all. - After watching them,
I got some tips.
I had no idea...
- the order was so crucial. - I know.
You're right. We should cover ourselves.
I doubt Seok Jin can blow that hard.
I think he has weak lungs.
Okay.
(They're all ready now.)
(Which one of them will win the victory?)
Ready, set, go.
(He blows the whistle.)
You're strong.
(After giving two strong blows,)
(Seok Jin begins to cough.)
(He's dazed.)
(He's struggling.)
(They feel sorry for him.)
I'll do it instead.
I'm afraid they'll pass out.
- Let me. - Please.
- Please make them stop! - Please stop!
Please make them stop!
(Amidst their painful exhales,)
(a 10-dollar bill is found.)
(Is this it?)
- I can't bear... - Did you get one?
- That's it? - to watch them do this.
- Is that it? - What?
That's it?
(They both run towards their boards.)
Wait.
(Jae Seok finishes writing the answer first.)
(Soon after, Seok Jin follows.)
This is wrong, right?
(Is Jae Seok's answer right?)
- This is wrong, right? - Is that a dollar or 10 dollars?
10 dollars.
Jae Seok wins.
- What? - That was it?
(Jae Seok gets it right.)
- What? - What is this?
(There was only 10 dollars?)
That was it?
- What? - But when...
- we did it, - What is this?
- We had all those coins! - it was harder than this.
- There was a nickel too. - It looked too hard,
so we took it down a notch.
This is why going first is a disadvantage.
(This match was customized.)
(Jae Seok will now have a match with So Min.)
I wrote 10 dollars too, but I was late.
(Which one of them will obtain a Chance Card?)
This is your mission for obtaining a Chance Card.
The mission that befits your keyword, War, is...
Protect the Gate.
"Gate"?
It'll be a tournament with two players at a time.
There will be an offense and a defense.
The offense will need to penetrate a paper door...
by shooting a rubber gun.
The other player will play defense.
The defense must protect the door with his body.
Rubber gun? It's going to sting.
- We'll be bruised. - What's wrong?
- We'll get bruises. - Okay.
This will hurt. This is a war, indeed.
You're right.
Only the last one standing...
- will receive a Chance Card. - Okay.
- But first, we'll play a mission... - Okay.
that'll make you win by default.
- We can do that? - Okay.
- This is the most crucial game. - Yes.
It is.
This is the most important.
It's the Pirate Roulette Game?
- Okay. - This is good.
- This? - Okay.
Haha.
- This is based on luck. - Okay.
We can do this.
This is based on luck.
(Who will win by default?)
The one who makes the pirate pop up will win.
- Okay. - Which means, the order is crucial.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Haha loses.)
(Gosh, I'm last.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins.)
Okay. I'm first.
You must go with your first choice.
- Okay. - You can't switch holes.
I'm the one with the worst luck.
- I'll start. - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
(How will his first attempt play out?)
(The barrel makes a sound.)
(But nothing happens.)
- That's a disappointment. - Okay.
(Go away.)
Jong Kook.
Why did you have to push me?
(General Kim has appeared.)
(I'll win this battle.)
- This is war. - Yes.
(He puts in a sword.)
Okay.
(General Kim fails on his first attempt.)
- Thank goodness. - Okay.
- You can't switch holes. - All right.
I will win.
You can't go back...
- on your choice. - No.
Don't change. You can't.
(He puts in a sword.)
- No changing! - Darn it.
(They each got a turn, and it's back to Se Chan.)
Okay!
- What was that? We're the same. - I didn't hit you.
- I was cheering you on. - Okay.
I'll start.
- You chose your hole. - 1, 2, 3.
(He inserts the sword.)
(He fails once again.)
Okay!
- Just one. - Please!
(There are only 4 holes remaining.)
Just one. Let's just get it once!
- Please! - Please!
I need to win!
Okay, it's my turn!
(General Kim fails again.)
(It's Haha's turn.)
If you fail, I win. It'll be me.
- I hope they both fail. - This is thrilling.
I hope they both lose.
- Okay! - Where will you insert it?
It's either 1 of those 2.
- No, there are 3 holes. - There are 3?
There are three holes.
(Which hole is the door to victory?)
- Please. - This is...
very thrilling.
Okay.
(He inserts his sword.)
Yes!
(Haha wins by default.)
I am the default winner!
(I'm jealous.)
Okay, then.
Jong Kook and Se Chan will have a match.
(These two will go against each other.)
- These are the rubber bands. - We're using these?
These are thick.
My gosh.
It's okay. I don't feel pain.
(It's okay. I don't feel pain.)
Please, Jong Kook. This isn't an actual war.
It's just a Chance Card.
- It's just a Chance Card. - It's okay.
I don't feel pain.
Let's decide on our positions.
(They need to play rock-paper-scissors.)
- Gosh. Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jong Kook wins.)
I won.
Don't worry.
If he attacks and gets a point,
- you'll change positions... - I'll get a turn right?
- and have a chance to make a tie. - Right.
Okay. Do you want to go first?
- No, I'll defend first. - What?
- I want to. - Why?
- Because I won. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do it again. - We just did.
- When? - Just now.
I didn't see it. The camera didn't record it.
Right? Let's play.
Do you want to go to a place where there are no cameras?
Come on.
(Se Chan is terrified.)
- Fine! We did play it! My gosh! - Right?
We did it.
You played scissors, and I played rock.
Let me tell you something.
When I was young, I could even...
target a pen with a rubber band.
- Really? - Yes.
- You're good. - It was back in school.
Look at his eyes. He's so determined.
He's intimidated. That's good.
- Should I hit you in your knee? - Okay.
- You're good. - Hold on.
How about your face?
- How does that sound? - Try it.
Should I shoot now? Okay.
Try it.
(Shoot me in my face.)
Okay.
Se Chan pretended not to hear Jong Kook.
(Haha is sharp.)
(He feels guilty.)
Come on. You could've ignored that!
- He looked elsewhere. - Okay.
(He needs to penetrate this sturdy defense.)
(Shooting)
(He misses.)
(Haha curses at him.)
It didn't work. I should've done this.
- We usually do this. - No, it doesn't fly out.
That's great.
What are you trying to do now?
(Hold on.)
How are you pulling it back?
Like this.
(He's pulling back the rubber band as tight as he can.)
You did this too.
- Over here? - Yes.
His looks more terrifying.
(He's scared.)
- Why does it look terrifying? - What's wrong?
(He's ready.)
Hold on.
(Where should I shoot?)
(Just don't shoot my body.)
Look at his arm.
(He focuses all his energy on his finger.)
(It makes Se Chan dance.)
My goodness.
(This will be over soon.)
(He aims and shoots.)
(It hits his forearm.)
(Jong Kook fails.)
My gosh!
It's so painful! Jong Kook!
(It wasn't intentional.)
(This is a real battle.)
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
You need to aim at the paper.
Of course, I did.
(They switch positions.)
There? I hope this flies.
(He shoots.)
(It hits Jong Kook's lower abdomen.)
(It's a sensitive area.)
Okay. My turn.
He's fine.
- I was accurate. - It didn't make any noise.
(General Kim is back.)
It's not flying the way I want it to.
(If Jong Kook succeeds, he'll go to the play-off.)
Se Chan, put down everything.
If I step forward, he won't have much space.
But it'll hurt more.
It will hurt more.
(He sees Jong Kook's fingers.)
(Dance all you want, you fool.)
I don't think he's aiming at the paper door.
(Just watching him terrifies Haha.)
I hate this.
(The sound is intense.)
What?
Okay.
(It hits the paper.)
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
Okay.
(He aims at the available space...)
(and penetrates the paper door.)
(He crushes the paper.)
I got hit with that!
(Did it hurt a lot?)
That's great.
(Jong Kook goes to the play-off.)
- Okay. - I hate winning by default!
- That's great. - Jong Kook...
- wins. - Okay!
You need to succeed.
I need to.
(Haha is in the offense.)
(He carefully chooses his weapon.)
Get one that looks taut. Okay?
(He picks one.)
Let's do this!
(Haha is no rookie.)
(During practice time,)
(he was just as good as Jong Kook.)
(I can do this.)
(He focuses all his energy on his fingers.)
Do it.
(Will he be able to penetrate this sturdy fortress?)
Graze his skin, please.
Okay.
(The tension is high.)
(Will he block successfully, or will he penetrate successfully?)
Shoot it.
Good.
(He attempts to throw him into confusion...)
(and then fires.)
(Jong Kook blocks it.)
Okay!
Move.
(Did he just block it?)
(If Jong Kook wins, it's game over.)
The one who wins in this match...
will acquire a Chance Card.
- There are no more chances? - Okay.
This is the final play-off.
(Will Haha block successfully?)
(If I block this, it'll be my turn again.)
From my experience,
you need to give him no space. You need to come forward.
Right.
You need to move around.
Come here.
All right.
(Jong Kook gets ready to fire.)
Wait, wait, wait!
(Haha suffers from the aftereffects of Jong Kook's fingers.)
(I'll let you live.)
Hurry up.
(He gets into the defense position.)
There's space below. Good.
There's a lot of space around you. Move your arms.
Put them to the side. Good.
Good.
Okay. Gosh, this is taut.
It's so tight.
(He charges his weapon.)
(Where should I aim this time?)
(Terrified)
(If Jong Kook succeeds, he'll be the final winner.)
(Will Haha block successfully, or will Jong Kook get the victory?)
(While he flails his arms around,)
(Jong Kook fires.)
(What is the result?)
(The paper is torn.)
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
Where? Where did it go?
- It went through. - He penetrated it.
(Darn it.)
He's way too strong compared to us.
Okay! That's great! You're both weaklings.
So why did you pick War?
(He performs a victory ceremony.)
Didn't he just try to wage war?
What?
(So what?)
You look charismatic.
Do you want to do this? You need to do it.
Go and throw it.
- Try it. - Throw it.
Have this.
(This is my gift to you.)
(Thanks)
- Did Jong Kook win? - Okay.
This is so unfair.
(Jong Kook obtains a Chance Card.)
Jae Seok and So Min will go to the play-off.
- They're the final contestants? - It feels great.
- My gosh. - This is unbelievable.
- My pride is hurt. - This is why it's worth...
coming here though the four of us are here.
- Exactly. - This is the land of opportunity.
Okay. The final winner...
will be determined by a game of Line the Coins.
- "Line the Coins"? - "Line the Coins"?
The one who puts their coin...
the closest to the line is the winner.
This is the Coke and Sprite Game.
You need to hit hard.
- This means... - You win.
(So Min's is closer to the line.)
- You won that round. - I think I can win.
Gosh.
Here I go. Start.
- Are you starting now? - You need to say, "start".
(Their practice time is over.)
Start!
- He's starting. - Already?
(How will Jae Seok do?)
(Flicking)
(His coin is almost at the line.)
Gosh, I should've hit harder.
(He's disappointed.)
I should've hit harder.
I should've put more strength into it.
- You just need to pass this. - Well...
Start.
(If So Min's coin gets closer to the line than his, she wins.)
(What will be the outcome?)
I'm a bit concerned.
(If the coin falls, it's a miss. Where did the coin go?)
(She gets it right on the line.)
(It shoots straight out and stops on the line.)
- She won. - I won.
I just won. What should we do?
- This is unbelievable. - It's on the line.
- It went on the line. - My goodness.
No one can beat her.
Mine went on the line. Goodness.
Oh, my. I just won.
(She gloats.)
So Min wins.
(So Min is the winner on this land of opportunity.)
- It's understandable that she won. - Right.
- It's only here where she can win. - This is where...
- she can win. - It's the land of opportunity.
This is the only place...
- My gosh. - where she can win.
I was happy to have been up against them.
- All right. - Thank you.
So Min, the final winner,
will now pick 1 of the 3 Chance Cards.
- She needs to pick? - Do I need to pick one?
- Let them pick first. - You can pick first,
and I'll get the one remaining.
- You two can pick first. - My gosh.
- She's using us. - It doesn't feel that good.
I think the last one will be good.
They're all unlucky.
Pick one each. Which one will you pick?
Then I'll pick this one. Okay.
(She picks the last one.)
- I'll pick this one. - Share it with me.
(What kinds of Chance Cards have they picked?)
- Is it good? - It's a very good one.
It's an excellent one.
(Their first missions come to an end.)
- This is your second mission. - Okay.
While governing, Sejong the Great...
listened to the minority's opinions as well.
Your second mission is called The Minority's Dignity.
- I like this. - Yes.
Sejong the Great's favorite dish was meat.
There are two dishes that go well with meat.
They're cold buckwheat noodles and mixed buckwheat noodles.
(They need to make a choice.)
The one who picks the least popular one wins, right?
The restaurant with the least number of members in the given time...
will be given Chance Cards and Meal Cards.
The restaurant with the majority of the members will not get to eat.
They will also be flogged.
We'll be flogged?
What did we do so wrong?
- We're flogged every week. - Why would you use violence?
- Which one should I pick? - Let's see.
Let me be completely honest.
I'm really craving cold buckwheat noodles.
- I do. - Me too.
I also want cold buckwheat noodles.
- Then... - I'm just going to go with that.
(Haha tries to act tough.)
(He begins his macho act.)
- Haha. - I...
- I'm sick of these scenarios. - What?
- I'm really tired of this. - Me too.
- That's why I'm going to be simple. - I'm going to go with the cold one.
- I already told you. - I'm going to go as well.
- I'm going. - Sure, you can come.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Whoever loses...
will be told where to go.
- Okay. - They'll have to obey us.
Then let's play a Race of Wits.
The last one or the one that overlaps with another...
- will be told where to go. - They have to.
- They must. - You have to obey.
- You must. - All right.
If you don't, you'll get disqualified.
- Okay? - Okay.
- You have to go. - There are no exceptions.
Ready, set, go.
- 1. - 2.
(Seok Jin grunts.)
(Grunting)
He grunted.
(He hates this game.)
What was that?
Jong Kook will choose...
- cold buckwheat noodles. - Hey.
- That's for sure. - He will choose that...
- For sure. - regardless of the game.
- "I don't care. I'm having it." - Seok Jin will go there.
- "I don't care." - He'll go there.
Okay. Seok Jin will go wherever Jong Kook goes.
- You're set. - Let's send one more there.
- Okay. - You're not going there?
- No, we're not. - Me neither.
How about we make two of the staff members play...
rock-paper-scissors...
- and guess who won? - Let's pick.
- Okay. - I like that.
- All right. - Okay.
- So Hyun. - Hyo Im and So Hyun can go.
- Yes. - We'll turn our backs.
(They won't look.)
I wonder who'll win.
Rock-paper-scissors
(They need to study their faces.)
- Are you done? - Are you done?
- Pick. - Look at their faces.
(They study their faces.)
- Hey. - I'm so confused.
- I pick So Hyun. - Pick.
- I pick So Hyun. - Who?
Then go towards that side.
- I pick Hyo Im. - Hyo Im?
- Yes. - I pick her too.
I think...
- I pick So Hyun. - Hyo Im has beaten So Hyun.
What's the result?
The winner of the game was...
Yang Hyo Im.
- Okay! - Okay!
(Kwang Soo and Jae Seok are correct.)
- You'll both go there! - Yes, you will.
Hold. If Jong Kook goes as well, there will be...
three people there.
- Right. - Jae Seok.
Let's have another match.
(Jae Seok! Let's have another match.)
- What did you say? - Let's have one last round.
(Kwang Soo makes a tempting offer.)
Yes, it's better to send...
- three people there. - It will be better.
- We should send three from here. - It will be better.
I will get a better chance of winning if I win again.
That's right.
You have to keep the promise.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors?
- The loser must go with us. - Just one game?
One game.
If I lose here, I'm done for.
- My last chance. - Let's go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
(Kwang Soo wins, Jae Seok has to go with cold buckwheat noodle.)
Yes!
I might win.
What if...
we went with cold buckwheat noodle,
but we win?
- There's no way. - That would be funny.
- There's no way. - That would be hilarious.
There are only two choices. It's impossible.
- It could be four to four. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - We never know.
- We never know - But...
(What will be the fate of Kwang Soo and the 3 losers?)
Are we going to have cold buckwheat noodles, then?
- Yes, - We have no other choice.
But I think...
we shouldn't call the others...
and just surprise them on the spot.
- I think that will be better. - How does that sound?
Jae Seok...
- Yes? - To be honest,
- I like that better than winning. - Right?
Don't call them.
- Let's not tell them. - Okay.
- This isn't just any car. - It's a bomb.
- It's a bomb. - An atom bomb.
- The fusing is burning away. - It's a bomb.
- Let's go blast this bomb! - Yes!
(1st location, the cold buckwheat noodle restaurant.)
(The noodles that cool you down just by looking at it.)
(Ji Hyo enters first.)
(Ji Hyo, who's usually lucky, chose cold buckwheat noodles?)
No one is here yet?
No one arrived.
Please don't come here.
Please.
We discussed this once before,
and Jae Seok said that he liked spicy buckwheat noodles,
while Jong Kook said he liked cold buckwheat noodles.
(That's right. Jong Kook, who likes cold buckwheat noodles, enters.)
It smells good,
but I don't know if I'll be able to eat it.
(Talk of the devil...)
That sounds like Jong Kook.
[VIU Ver] SBS E451 Running Man
"Sejong the Great's Riddle Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
I knew it.
(Jong Kook enters the cold buckwheat noodle restaurant.)
(His preference never changes.)
You have to be the last one.
It's just the two of you until now.
(2 people are at cold buckwheat noodles. How about the rest?)
(2nd location, the spicy buckwheat noodle restaurant.)
(Haha, who preferred cold buckwheat noodles, is here?)
No one's here yet!
No one's here yet.
Awesome!
(Am I the only one? Awesome!)
(It's a good thing I changed it to the spicy buckwheat noodles.)
Awesome!
Why, you...
- Great. No one is here. - Why, you...
Come on.
- You are just... - Come on.
You said you were going to choose the cold buckwheat noodles!
You said you had an upset stomach!
You said you were going to choose cold buckwheat noodles...
and I said I'll choose spicy buckwheat noodles!
- I hope no one else comes. - Please...
Jae Seok will come here, for sure.
I think he could go the other way, though.
Someone else is here!
(Someone else is here!)
(Another car arrived at the spicy buckwheat noodle restaurant?)
No!
Don't come here!
- Who is it? - Please!
You really came here?
(The unlucky Kwang Soo is here.)
- You really came here? - Come on!
(Adding Kwang Soo to the spicy buckwheat noodle restaurant.)
You guys usually go for cold buckwheat noodles!
Kwang Soo.
What's wrong with you?
I need to tell you something.
There were four of us...
and Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and So Min went to the spicy buckwheat noodles.
I mean, cold buckwheat noodles.
- Are you sure? How do you know? - Yes.
Because we played a game...
- and I won. - Ji Hyo changed her mind.
- She went for the cold. - She told me that too.
Jong Kook went there, for sure.
Since the three of us are here, it depends on Ji Hyo.
The last time Jae Seok called,
he said, "We changed our minds."
- He can't do that. - He said they're on their way.
But that can't be happening.
(During the phone call with Jae Seok a while ago...)
Kwang Soo, where are you headed?
I'm almost there.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
We thought about it, and I think we've changed our minds.
(Confident)
Don't play with me.
We're going for the spicy buckwheat noodles.
Stop it.
We just feel that way.
It just happened,
so you decide. I don't know anymore.
We're going for the spicy buckwheat noodles.
- Bye! - Jae Seok.
Fine!
(The bomb car decided to blow up...)
It's impossible.
Don't you think something's wrong, Haha?
Kwang Soo is here...
If they don't arrive in time,
- they're... - They'll be disqualified.
- It's their own fault. - Right.
What?
(Just then,)
(a woman's voice is heard outside!)
Do you usually like cold buckwheat noodles?
I always eat the cold one.
What? Someone's here!
(Is someone else here?)
- Why is there a camera? - There's a camera out there!
No! Come on!
The car turned away!
It a U-turn!
(The filming crew for another show goes in a different direction.)
(It was a U-turn!)
U-turn! U-turn!
- U-turn! - Why did they come this way?
Why are there so many vans that look like that in our country?
(While the cowards were being frightened...)
(in the spicy buckwheat noodles...)
(Knocking)
Right.
I knew it was a girl.
(What?)
(You're not...)
(here alone?)
Goodness.
(Cold buckwheat noodles lost, thanks to the three bombs.)
There were two people here.
- Ji Hyo, why do you look like that? - I see...
- So this is what happened? - I had no idea.
You guys aren't usually...
this obedient.
Well, rules are rules.
- The three of us... - Since when?
(They have never heard of them being so obedient.)
- Gosh. - We thought about it a lot.
- Since when? - We did think about it a lot.
Unbelievable. You usually do what you want to do.
So does that mean...
They're going to be enjoying it so much.
They must be screaming with joy.
(Correct.)
(The spicy buckwheat noodles trio unites.)
Ji Hyo went for the other one.
Nice!
I didn't even keep my hopes up...
after seeing these two.
Please serve us the food.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
- Thank you. - Do we get one each?
(The grilled barbecue bulgogi and chewy spicy buckwheat noodles.)
Gosh.
Thank you for the meal!
(He slurps it up without a word.)
(The chopsticks move around constantly.)
It's so good.
(He regrets even thinking about going for cold buckwheat noodles.)
- The sweet and sour taste is good. - Sure.
(The winners get the sweet and sour taste of the noodles.)
Instead of a meal,
you will get flogged with a stick.
All of a sudden? Right here?
But we didn't even do anything wrong.
You will have to get...
five beatings in total.
Let's make one person get all.
Isn't one each easy enough?
No way.
It's best not to get beat at all.
- Jong Kook. - Then one person gets all five?
- All five. - All?
- All five. - How about 3 and 2?
- There are five spoons here. - Fine, 3 and 2.
Whoever picks 3 and 2...
- Sounds good. - How's that?
- Okay. - Good.
That sounds good.
(That is how the game of spoons started.)
- I'm holding the end. - There.
- Okay! - Okay!
- Jong Kook, show us first. - Me?
- Yes. - It's 3. Or 2.
- Please. You get the beating. - 3 or 2.
- 3 or 2! - Please.
Please get the beating.
- Is it going to be strong beatings? - Please.
- 3 or 2. - 1, 2, 3!
3 or 2.
What is it?
(It's an empty spoon, meaning he is excused.)
(Why does he get away with it all the time?)
Okay!
- This is too... - Why is this happening?
It's unbelievable!
- I just picked one. - I can't believe it.
Why does he get excused?
- I didn't... - So Min, it's your turn.
- So Min. - Froggie.
- Froggie. - Froggie.
(She already looks anxious.)
(It can't be 3...)
- 3 or 2. - 3!
- I want to go home. - 1, 2, 3!
- Don't touch it. - What is it?
(So Min gets 3 beatings.)
You shouldn't have seen it in advance.
(So Min got 3!)
Why does this happen to me?
- She got 3. - The 3 is out.
- Okay. - The 3 is out.
- I don't want to get hit. - 2.
- 2! - 2!
(Will Jae Seok be able to avoid 2?)
- Please! Please! - 2! 2!
- 2! - 2!
(Oh, no.)
(Jae Seok gets 2 beatings with the stick.)
(No one can beat his legendary unluckiness.)
How do you always get it?
- I can't believe this. - It's him!
Seok Jin!
(Wherever they go, whatever they do, the members are always similar.)
It's still your lucky day, though.
You took two beatings.
(It's your lucky day, since you got 2.)
You're lucky today!
- You should buy a lottery ticket. - I felt good for a moment there.
- Think positively! - Yes.
- What he said actually... - You're lucky.
- has a point there. - Exactly.
If I got 2 between 3 and 2, I should be happy about it.
- You should buy a lottery ticket. - It's my lucky day today.
It's your lucky day.
Amazing.
We need to pick well who's going to hit us, So Min.
So Min, who gets three beatings, will go first.
So Min.
What if So Min gets her own name?
- That can't happen. - She gets to choose for herself.
- I get to choose? That's nice. - She gets to choose.
1, 2, 3!
(So Min spins the wheel.)
Please. Please let it be Jae Seok.
Please. Please.
- It's Jong Kook. - It's Jong Kook.
(What? Jong Kook?)
(Gosh, it's Jong Kook...)
(Jong Kook, the famous physical therapist, gets chosen.)
You're totally out of luck today.
It's the worst day.
- It's your worst day. - I guess it's a bad day for you.
- It's your worst day. - It is.
I still have to go.
- Here. - Let's go.
- What if he gets Jong Kook too? - No way.
Jong Kook!
(They hope Jae Seok gets Jong Kook.)
- Jong Kook! - It has to be Jong Kook!.
- Stop! Stop! - Jong Kook!
(Will Jong Kook get to hit Jae Seok as everyone is wishing?)
It has to be Jong Kook.
(Will Jong Kook get to hit Jae Seok, as everyone is wishing?)
I still have to go.
- Here. - Let's go.
- What if he gets Jong Kook too? - No way.
Jong Kook!
(They hope Jae Seok gets Jong Kook.)
- Jong Kook! - It has to be Jong Kook!
- Stop! Stop! - Jong Kook!
(Who will get to hit Jae Seok?)
It has to be Jong Kook.
- Is it Jong Kook? - Is it Jong Kook?
- It's So Min! - It's So Min!
It's So Min.
Why me?
- It's So Min. - Why me?
- It's So Min. - I can't go hard on her.
I'm upset because Jae Seok is so happy about it.
2 hits from So Min.
That's the best scenario possible.
- That's the best case. - Yes.
I'm fine as long as it's not Jong Kook.
- Right. - Ji Hyo would've been fine.
I don't want to hit So Min too hard.
- You have to. - Come on.
She's like a sister to me.
- You know what you said. - Hey!
- Hit hard as much as you care. - Hit hard as much as you care.
What is wrong with me today?
Where...
did it go wrong?
Jong Kook!
(Show us what you got.)
Do it properly.
- It's too narrow. - I don't like this.
- It's going to hurt. - I can't swing properly.
Why don't you move it further?
- Further? - Wait.
Jae Seok.
Aren't you getting a bit too involved?
(He created some space with his foot.)
- That's good. - Okay.
Very good.
- It looks good. - I'm scared.
- I'm scared. - Prepare yourself!
- You can't do that! - Prepare yourself.
I'm so scared.
(And that was...)
(the end of...)
(a neat physical therapy.)
- That was good. - Yes!
- Now, - Oh, no.
So Min, keep that anger inside you.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Okay. - So Min,
don't break your paddle.
I'm going to squeeze my buttocks.
- Hold that anger. - Okay.
You have to hit harder because you're a woman.
- Okay! - So Min...
(Okay!)
Okay.
- Okay. - So Min.
Go easy on me.
So Min, try hitting...
- at the center. - That's the spot.
Hold it like this.
- Like this. - Hey, Jong Kook.
Why are you teaching her?
It hurts less if you hold it closer.
- You must hold it longer. - Hold it longer.
- It hurts more like this. - Hey!
- Stop giving her a lesson. - Hold it like this.
- Stand here and guide me. - Like this.
- Hold it like this. - Why are you teaching her?
- Like this. - Yes, teach me.
- I'm doing it! - Like this.
(What is she doing?)
I'm doing it.
Okay?
- I'm doing it. - Hold it like this,
- and go straight down. - Okay.
- Go up and come straight down. - 1, 2, 3.
(Spanks)
- You did well. - You did well.
(I mean, how hard could she...)
(He cries out in pain.)
- You did well. - You're good at this.
- So Min is good at it. - She's good.
She went straight down.
That felt great.
Go up and come down.
His lesson worked after all.
Why are you giving her a lesson?
- He's angry. - I have to.
Are you guys dating or something?
- No. - Then why?
- Why are you teaching her? - You need to be spanked funny.
Come on.
This isn't a billiard room, take off your gloves!
I mean, come on!
- Hey. - Come on.
- His lesson works. - Why is he doing that?
- Hold it tight. Go for the center. - Yes.
Go easy on me, So Min.
- Like this? - No, hold it closer.
Hold right here.
Hey!
I'm going to poop if you hit me too hard.
- Hold it like this. - You be careful, okay?
- One, - I'm serious.
(He tosses the paddle to So Min right after.)
(They're showing perfect teamwork.)
- You did great. - You did great.
(This is why I spank.)
So Min, you're good at this.
So Min!
That was awesome. You did great.
- See why you should hold it longer? - I understand now.
- You have to hold it longer. - Right.
And you hit the center very accurately.
- I get it. - That hurt so much.
- Jae Seok! - That hurt so much.
(Today is Jae Seok's lucky day.)
(Meanwhile, at the spicy buckwheat noodles restaurant)
- This is so good. - It's tasty.
Don't forget...
(Only one of them can acquire the Chance Card.)
the fact that only one of you...
will be acquiring the Chance Card.
- Sure. - We know.
(They'll choose who gets it with the rock-paper-scissors.)
- Rock, paper, scissors! - Rock, paper, scissors!
(Haha wins on the first game.)
Okay!
So that was it for my luck.
(He realized his reality.)
This is why...
you need to know your place.
And you should know when to stop.
When people keep telling you you're good,
you're going to deceive yourself.
Right, you should know your place.
I was about to go to a rock-paper-scissors contest.
That was it for my luck.
- Okay. - Thank you!
Here's your Chance Card.
Look inside, but don't let them see it.
(This Chance Card will be useful in the final mission later.)
This looks amazing.
Now you've got your Chance Card,
let's move on to the final mission spot.
Let's go!
- Kwang Soo. - I'm nervous.
(They've all gathered at the final mission spot to win the prize.)
- What is all this? - What is that?
(What is that?)
What is all this?
Look at the size.
What is this?
What are we doing today?
(What stands before them is...)
- What is this? - What's going on?
This looks scary.
It looks scary because I don't know what it does.
Look at the size. What is this?
(Each of the eight platforms is facing a cube.)
Look at that.
This is unbelievable.
What are we supposed to do here?
Stand on the platform with the number you like.
I'm scared.
There are cubes behind.
Are we bouncing off of it?
Do you see the cubes at the front?
What are those?
They're going to fly towards you.
Seriously?
(They cannot believe what they just heard.)
Are you trying to kill us?
(The safety is thoroughly checked.)
Wouldn't it hurt too much?
It's going to hurt.
What's it going to be? I'm curious though.
(They're scared.)
(The cubes sway.)
(Swaying)
What is going on?
- It moved. - Those are...
really big.
It's going to be fine.
We're not going to die.
Some of you have gotten the Chance Card,
and some of you have not.
- Yes. - Yes.
Ji Hyo, Jong Kook,
So Min, and Haha has one.
I don't remember getting something like Chance Card?
We'll begin with our final round.
In this round,
you will solve riddles about Sejong the Great.
- I'm finished. - The one who survives...
to the last will be the champion.
- We're solving riddles. - Okay.
I should have studied.
In every round,
one of the members who didn't get the right answer...
will be eliminated.
And the member to be eliminated...
will be chosen by the one who got the right answer.
(They will be eliminated by the member who got it right.)
We're pointing one out?
I think we are.
The winner of each round will write...
one of the platform numbers where the other members are standing...
on the blackboard.
The cube will fly towards...
the appointed platform to eliminate the member on it.
Will the questions be difficult?
(So the cube will fly towards the appointed platform?)
That's harsh.
I'm scared.
But, the rest of the members...
may stay on their platforms...
or change their spots behind the winner.
(They can switch or stay on their platforms.)
(That means the winner cannot know who is standing on which platform.)
So the winner doesn't know...
who will be eliminated.
I might survive!
(If I'm lucky.)
Se Chan, you're supposed to try and guess the right answer.
(You're supposed to guess the right answer.)
You should be trying to guess the right answer.
I'm only trying to survive.
I know I'm not guessing the right answer.
You're only...
- trying to survive? - I got it.
Seok Jin, Jong Kook, and Jae Seok...
have some knowledge of history.
Jae Seok knows a lot,
- so we should get rid of him first. - But we don't know how...
- Come on! - He's right.
We have to get rid of him first.
We should eliminate the ones with Chance Cards.
The ones with Chance Cards.
I think that's a good idea!
We don't know anything even if we have the cards.
I still don't know anything.
(They're not so confident in solving riddles.)
This is crazy.
The riddles will not only be about history.
- There are other areas too. - Sure.
All of the riddles...
will be related to Sejong the Great.
Okay.
Are you ready?
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Who will survive at last?)
I'll try my best.
Let's go. Let's go get it.
I'm nervous.
Here goes the first riddle.
I should have studied.
Which of these places do not have the statue...
of Sejong the Great?
- I already don't know. - Okay.
- I'm done. - That sounds difficult.
Number one, Apgujeong Elementary School.
Number two, National Hangeul Museum.
Number three, Yeouido Park.
Number four, King Sejong the Great Memorial Hall.
Let me answer!
(Jae Seok's attempt)
Number one, Apgujeong Elementary School.
I visit the school pretty often.
- Really? - Then he should be right.
Yes, and they have the statue of Admiral Yi Sun Shin.
(It must be the statue of Admiral Yi Sun Shin.)
It's wrong?
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
(Seok Jin's attempt)
Number four, King Sejong the Great Memorial Hall.
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
Let me answer.
Three, Yeouido Park.
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
(There's only number 2 left.)
There's only one left.
You don't know what it is.
(You don't know what it is.)
You need to say the number and the name of the place.
He can't remember it.
Wait.
I can't remember it either.
- Hold on. - Five!
- Four! - Wait up!
- I can't remember it either. - Let me answer.
Number two,
Hangeul Memorial Hall.
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
- Let me answer! - Kwang Soo, go ahead.
Korea Hangeul National Museum.
(Wrong answer)
Let me answer!
(Haha's attempt)
King Sejong the Great Korean National Museum.
(Another wrong answer)
Let me answer! National Hangeul Museum.
(That is precisely right.)
Okay!
(The rest of them has the statue of King Sejong the Great.)
That's what I said!
We are incredible. All of us avoided the right answer.
- Okay. - For goodness' sake.
Jae Seok, you are the winner. Please come forward.
Okay.
Jae Seok, I think...
you should eliminate those with Chance Cards.
- That's right. - Okay.
Please either change or maintain your place...
in the back.
(Jae Seok has his eyes covered.)
So Min is on Platform Five.
Kwang Soo is on Platform Five.
Please.
(Neither the ones on the platforms...)
(nor the winner who chooses the number...)
All of us should change places.
(knows who will get eliminated until the cube comes flying.)
- All of us should change places. - 3, 2, 1.
Now, you can neither move nor make a sound.
Jae Seok, take off your blindfold.
- I will look at the front. - Look at the front.
I don't know which number I should pick.
The numbers are from 1 to 8, right?
If you pick an empty platform,
- everyone will survive this round. - Really?
(If he picks an empty platform, everyone will survive this round.)
You wouldn't want that.
(Please don't let it be my number.)
(Jae Seok has only one goal.)
(It's the elimination of those with Chance Cards.)
(Will he be able to eliminate someone with the Chance Card?)
I wrote it down.
(He chose a number.)
(Among 7 members who didn't get the right answer,)
Here we go. He wrote a number down.
(who will be eliminated first?)
Who will it be? Shall I take off my glasses?
- Three, - Come on!
Two.
(Towards whom will the giant cube fly?)
One.
(Who will be the first person to get eliminated?)
Shoot.
(The cube is launched.)
(The giant cube is powerful.)
Shoot.
(The first person to get eliminated is Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo was standing on Platform Five.)
(Jae Seok wrote down 5 without knowing anything.)
- 5! - 5!
(Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
Gosh, it's nerve-wracking.
How did you pick five?
Why were you there?
I am so annoyed. I was going to pick Platform Six.
I am so annoyed.
Seriously.
- Is this the end for me? - Kwang Soo.
- Is this the end for me? - It's the end.
Kwang Soo, take the stairs down.
I debated between 5 and 6.
- Kwang Soo, this is for the best. - Bye.
Your mind must be at ease now.
I am so annoyed.
(I could have gotten it right.)
I could have gotten it right.
Seok Jin has an advantage with this problem.
- Really? - What could it be?
Of course. He was alive in the time of Sejong the Great.
(I will get the next question right.)
Here comes the second question.
- Okay. - Please.
Which bill doesn't have...
Sejong the Great?
Which bill doesn't have Sejong the Great?
(Which bill doesn't have Sejong the Great?)
Number 1, 1,000 hwan.
- What's "Hwan"? - It must be the old currency.
Number 2, 50 jeon.
- I have no idea. - Number 3, 100 won.
Number 4, 10,000 won.
- I got it. - I got it.
Haha, go ahead.
- Number one. - What's the answer?
(Number 1!)
Hwan...
1,000 hwan.
- Number one, 1,000 hwan? - Yes. Number one, 1,000 hwan.
(Incorrect)
I got it. Number 3, 100 won.
(Number 3, 100 won!)
- 100 won? - Does it have Sejong the Great?
(Sejong the Great was in the bills that were used from 1965 to 1980.)
Does 100 won have Sejong the Great?
(100 won bill had Sejong the Great.)
I got it. Number 2, 50 jeon.
(Number 2, 50 jeon!)
- It's correct. - Yes!
I will survive for another round!
- My goodness. - This is driving me crazy.
- My goodness. - Number 2, 50 jeon.
- All other options have it. - How did it get it right?
I took a wild guess.
How would I know?
- I am jealous of Se Chan. - Okay.
What should I do?
I need to use the Chance Card.
What should I do if I don't get to use it?
It will be really annoying if you don't get to use it.
I hope I eliminate someone with the Chance Card.
There is no eight.
- Pick a number from 1 to 7. - Okay.
(7 members remain.)
I would rather get eliminated.
1 to 7.
My mind is at ease.
(You must overcome this tension...)
3. 2.
(in order to win.)
One. You can't move now.
Don't make a sound.
(Everyone waits with bated breath.)
(Se Chan chooses a number.)
(Which number did Se Chan choose?)
Which number is it?
Can't you tell us first?
One person will fly.
I am sorry. I don't know who it will be.
- Please tell us the number. - Here we go.
Three.
(The cube is ready.)
- Two. - Please.
(Will someone with the Chance Card get eliminated?)
One. Launch it.
(The cube is launched.)
- Is it Jong Kook? - Is it Jong Kook?
(The cube flies towards Jong Kook.)
Is it Jong Kook?
(Jong Kook, the one with Chance Card gets eliminated.)
(Se Chan picked 4.)
(Jong Kook was standing on Platform 4.)
(The powerful cube makes even the ace member fly.)
Is Jong Kook out?
- Was it five? - Is Jong Kook out?
- Was it four? - I was going to move.
What was the number?
I was going to move.
- Is Jong Kook really out? - This is nerve-wracking.
- This is so nerve-wracking. - I feel like I am going to die.
My heart is beating so fast.
I was going to go to Platform Two.
I eliminated the right one.
- Good job. - I eliminated the right one.
Is Jong Kook's Chance Card gone?
His Chance Card is gone.
- You did a good job. - I eliminated the right one.
Good job.
Can we use Chance Card only one?
You can use it only once.
The next one is a short answer question.
I am ruined.
I love short answer questions.
The following comes from the third verse...
of "100 People Who Made Korea Shine".
Please sing the lyrics in the blank.
Music, cue.
(Music starts.)
(Yulgok Yi with 100,000 soldiers)
(Their bodies react to the music.)
(I need to solve the problem.)
(The good fighters, Gwak Jae U, Jo Heon, and Kim Si Min)
(The man who saved the country, Yi Sun Shin)
- I got it! - I got it!
- Haha, go ahead. - Sejong the Great...
with "Hunminjeongeum"
(Sejong the Great with "Hunminjeongeum")
- That's too long. - I got it.
Ga, gya, geo, gyeo, go gyo
(This question is hard.)
Let me answer.
(Seok Jin gives it a try.)
(The way he sings is too old-fashioned.)
What is wrong with him? What was that?
He ruins the tension of the game.
Am I wrong?
(Seok Jin's song will anger Sejong the Great.)
Chance!
(She finally uses it.)
- What? - What is it?
Tell everyone what your chace is.
- The acronym chance. - Then we will be able to hear it.
Ji Hyo has the acronym chance.
- Can't we answer? - Ji Hyo, come on out...
- and check the acronym. - For goodness' sake.
- I am so jealous. - I wish I had that chance.
Once she says the answer, you will know the acronym.
It will be funny if they continue to fail.
- Then... - They are capable of doing that.
- She might know right away. - Is it that easy?
(Will she be able to get the right answer?)
She doesn't know. Ji Hyo doesn't know.
(What is this?)
I don't know.
- She doesn't know. - Really?
- Ji Hyo, give it to us. - Hand it over.
What is the acronym?
What is this?
- Don't you know? - I don't know.
Ji Hyo, say something that fits the acronym.
Ji Hyo, what's the answer?
The answer is...
(Ji Hyo gives it a try.)
What could it be?
(Everyone waits for the acronym with bated breath.)
"You are Sejong the Great".
(She feeds them the wrong hint.)
- I got it! - What?
- It's not "You are". - It can't be right.
- It's not "You are". - She didn't use the acronym.
"You are"?
(What could be the answer?)
What's the acronym?
All right. It might not say, "Sejong the Great".
I got it! Could this be the answer?
"Hunminjeongeum", Lee Bang Won
(That came out of nowhere.)
Lee Bang Won?
What are you doing?
- It's not "Sejong the Great". - Lee Bang Won?
Surprisingly,
Se Chan's wrong answer contains a hint.
Really? Is it Lee Bang Won?
No way. Lee Bang Won?
You will know the answer if you get the acronym.
- Do you know it? - Do you know it?
- We know the answer. - Do you know it?
We know the answer.
Kwang Soo, is this acronym correct? Please take a look.
Of course it is correct. I gave it to you.
- Oh, I forgot. - It's from the production crew!
- For goodness' sake, Ji Hyo. - I am sorry.
- I am sorry. - Ji Hyo.
This isn't a hidden camera prank for Song Ji Hyo.
I am sorry. I am sorry.
I will give you a really big hint.
This is directly related to the answer.
- Get ready. - Okay.
Spread your right hand.
(Here comes the hint.)
- What about the right hand? - Did you spread it?
- Yes. - Yes.
Fold your fingers one at a time.
- What? - Fold your fingers one at a time.
I got it!
Tae, Jong, Tae, Se, Mun, Dan, Se
Please say it clearly.
- Tae, Jong. - "Tae, Jong"?
- Tae, Jong, Tae, Se, Mun, Dan, Se. - I got it.
Isn't it right? It's right.
- I got it. - I got it.
Tae, Jung, Tae, Se, Mun, Dan, Se.
(Tae, Jung, Tae, Se, Mun, Dan, Se.)
It's not "Tae, Jong".
It's "Tae, Jung".
(She got it wrong because of one word.)
Tae, Jung.
It's Jung for King Jungjong.
Seok Jin is incredible for getting this right...
and Ji Hyo is incredible too for not getting this right.
(An eliminated member chimes in.)
I knew Mun, Dan, Se,
but I couldn't remember the first part.
Please stand on Platform 2 through 7.
(It will be a disaster if I get eliminated.)
(They move carefully so that their footsteps are silent.)
(He listens intently.)
Three. Two.
(Jae Seok moves quickly.)
One.
Did everyone take their place?
Telepathy.
(Everyone takes their position.)
Seok Jin?
Let's eliminate one.
Is it from 2 to 7?
Telepathy.
(Which number did Seok Jin choose?)
I made up my mind. I wrote it down.
(My goodness. No!)
(Did he choose the one who has a Chance Card?)
(Or one without a Chance Card?)
Three.
(Who will be the third to be eliminated?)
(The cube is ready.)
One, shoot.
(The cube is launched.)
- I moved at the last moment. - That's annoying.
(The cube goes to Platform 7 where there's no one.)
(Their hearts almost stopped.)
(Everyone survives in the third round.)
- I moved at the last moment. - That's annoying.
See? I moved at the last moment.
- I moved at the last moment. - Didn't you change?
(Jae Seok moved from Platform 7 to 5.)
How did you know?
- No way. - You made a good choice.
My heart is pounding.
I'd rather get eliminated.
I was so close.
I was very close.
Is no one eliminated then?
(He couldn't eliminate anyone.)
- It's a multiple-choice question. - Okay.
To his eighth son Yeongeung,
- It's too hard. - Sejong the Great gave...
- a pet that was out of ordinary. - How can we know?
What type of pet was it?
- It's a companion animal. - How would we know?
Number one, giraffe.
Number two, flying squirrel.
Three, turtle.
Four, tiger.
Number three! I mean, let me answer.
What's the answer?
Number three, flying squirrel.
(Number three is turtle.)
(Flying squirrel is number 2.)
What is she saying?
- Please concentrate, Ji Hyo. - Is it wrong?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
(Jae Seok gives a try.)
Number two, flying squirrel.
- Say it clearly. - Number two, flying squirrel.
(Jae Seok is certain about the answer.)
(Is number two, flying squirrel, correct?)
Chance.
(At that moment)
(What?)
Chance.
I will steal his answer.
(Chance Card for Stealing Answer?)
I will pick this.
(So Min obtained the Chance Card for Stealing Answer.)
(Chance Card for Stealing Answer)
(She uses her Chance Card when the answer seems correct.)
(Is number 2, flying squirrel, correct?)
(Flying squirrel is correct.)
Thank goodness.
(She uses the chance appropriately and answers correct.)
Thank you.
- I'm so annoyed. - She should use it later.
Goodness.
You may move.
Please move.
(They rearrange their positions.)
(Platform 2 should be safe, right?)
Here we go. Three.
(Don't let it be me.)
Take off your blindfold and write it.
This makes me nervous.
(It's time to choose a number.)
(Please save me one more time.)
(What will So Min's choice be?)
(Platform number 2)
(It's where Seok Jin is.)
All right.
(Gosh, Seok Jin.)
Is it Jae Seok?
1, 2.
(Goodbye, Seok Jin.)
Three, shoot.
It's me.
(The cube is launched.)
(Seok Jin is the third to be eliminated.)
Wait.
Seok Jin.
He jumped off when it didn't even touch him.
No, I didn't.
(The secret behind Seok Jin's elimination)
- We shouldn't let it slide. - I didn't.
- What's wrong with you? - No, I didn't.
(A moment ago)
(Before the cube hit him,)
(he pretends to get hit.)
Come on.
He didn't even blow flour today.
It's really scary.
Goodness.
(He's such a coward.)
- We managed to survive. - Okay.
It's a miracle that I'm still alive.
I can't accept that they haven't gotten eliminated yet.
Seriously.
How are they still up there?
- There's more luck involved. - Right.
- Correct answers aren't important. - Here we go.
The childhood name of Gojong of Korea was...
Dog Poop.
Minister Hwang Hwi's childhood name was...
Pig.
- "Pig"? - Pig.
We can't answer this question.
In that case,
what's the childhood name of Sejong the Great?
This is difficult.
Let me answer.
Dog Poop.
(Dog Poop?)
- It's been said. - It's been said.
What on earth?
- Is she okay? - Seriously.
I'm worried about her.
She's repeating what she heard.
I'm sorry. I was thinking only that.
Let me answer. Chil Deuk.
For your information, Sejong the Great was...
the third youngest son.
(It's a key hint.)
Let me answer.
It's The Youngest.
(His answer is The Youngest.)
- Say it clearly. - The Youngest.
"The Youngest" is incorrect.
Let me answer.
(Ji Hyo tries again.)
(It's obvious that she doesn't know the answer.)
Mak Dong?
Say it clearly.
- Mak Dong? - "Mak"?
- Ttong. - "Ttong"?
- Dong. - Which one is it?
(Is it Mak Dong or Mak Ttong?)
Is it Dong or Ttong?
- Dong. - "Dong"?
- "Mak Dong"? - Yes.
It's correct.
(Mak Dong is correct.)
Is it Mak Dong?
That was so close.
(He almost had the answer.)
It's impossible to guess.
(How can we know it?)
(Ji Hyo picks Platform 6.)
(Se Chan is at Platform 6.)
- Launch. - It must be my end.
Here it is.
(I'll be leaving first.)
(I enjoyed our time together.)
(Se Chan is the fourth to be eliminated.)
I still lasted long.
(I enjoyed it.)
- Now... - We lasted long.
- I'm getting greedy. - Let's go.
- I'm getting greedy too. - I'm getting greedy.
- Let's go. - I can do this.
This is great.
Here's your next question.
Sejong the Great is...
known for his sense of absolute pitch.
Really?
The original was a Chinese traditional instrument.
It was imported during Goryeo dynasty.
In the ninth year of Sejong, for the first time,
it was made as a Korean instrument.
What is the name of this instrument?
Number one, haegeum.
Number two, ajaeng.
Number three, gayageum.
- Number four, pyeongyeong. - Let me answer.
Number four, pyeongyeong.
(He's 100 percent certain.)
(He said the answer with confidence.)
(Will the answer be correct?)
It's correct.
I got it.
Really?
- What's the answer? - Pyeongyeong.
Pyeongyeong. It's the one that jangles.
Is it the sound we hear at a temple?
It's good to eliminate Haha.
Haven't he used his Chance Card yet?
(Jae Seok's target is Haha.)
(Haha still has his Chance Card.)
I have to eliminate Haha.
- 3, 4, 5, 6. - Please stand.
(Jae Seok picks a number.)
Here we go.
(Who will be the fifth to be eliminated?)
(Will it be Haha with a Chance Card?)
(Will it be 1 of the 2 who used their Chance Card?)
Launch.
(The cube is launched.)
(The cube flies towards Ji Hyo.)
Ji Hyo.
(The fifth to be eliminated is Ji Hyo.)
(How did I survive until now?)
This is crazy.
How can he succeed when he didn't answer a question?
I feel very greedy.
Haha might win.
We don't know yet.
I feel very greedy.
We must eliminate Haha no matter what.
- I want to be eliminated. - Listen carefully.
It's a multiple-choice question.
Among subordinates of Sejong the Great,
one of them gave him a headache.
There is a myth that...
his name became a word that means...
something wrong or displeasing.
What is the subordinate's name?
Number one, Go Yak Hae.
Number two, Go Yak Han.
Number three, Moo Rae Hae.
Number four, Moo Rae Han.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Moo Rae Han.
- Which number? - Number four, Moo Rae Han.
(Number four is incorrect.)
Let me answer.
- Number one, Go Yak Hae. - Correct.
(Go Yak Hae is correct.)
You got it.
Number one, Go Yak Hae.
(Though So Min is a weak player,)
(she answered two.)
This is so upsetting.
Which number should I choose?
I answered another one.
(She's proud of herself.)
Stand from 4 to 6.
(They pick a platform from 4 to 6.)
(They can avoid the cube if they pick a good number.)
(I'm determined to eliminate one person.)
Please take your position.
(Right before the time is up,)
(Haha changes his position slowly.)
(Position is rearranged.)
Time is up, So Min.
(She has a chance to eliminate one person.)
(It's her golden opportunity.)
(Which number did So Min pick?)
It'll be his fate.
(It's what Jae Seok wrote earlier.)
(Number 6?)
It'll be his fate.
(Standing at Platform 6 is Jae Seok.)
I picked what was written here.
(It's Jae Seok.)
(Why does she looking at me?)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Launch.
(The cube is launched.)
(He only needed to last a little longer.)
(Jae Seok is the sixth to be eliminated.)
- I feel really greedy. - It's worth playing.
It's really worth playing.
It's worth playing.
- Okay. - It's worth playing today.
I didn't know he was good at quizzes.
He really is.
- Haha. - Your skills are amazing.
You're very smart.
You must have studied a lot.
I just can't believe this.
How can the two of them still be up there?
The funniest is...
Haha.
Did he answer any question?
He didn't answer any.
- He was just standing. - Right.
- How long has he been standing? - Seriously.
I participated in many quiz contests,
but this has never happened.
I never saw anyone small yet big.
She's giant compared to me.
This could be the last question.
Here it is.
Among the given choices,
which anecdote is not related to Sejong the Great?
Number one, when there was no meat on the table,
he pretended to be sick and pass out.
Number two, he gave a tangerine...
to a concubine he liked.
Number three, he lived in a thatched house for two years.
Number four, when he drank a lot, he would cry.
- Let me answer. - What's the answer?
(So Min gives a try.)
Number three, he lived in a thatched house for two years.
(So Min thinks number 3 is correct.)
- I just guessed. - Let me answer.
Here it comes.
(Haha makes an attempt.)
Number two, tangerine.
Say the exact answer.
He gave a tangerine to a concubine that he liked.
(Number two, he gave a tangerine to a concubine he liked.)
(Haha waited for this moment to answer this one question.)
- Haha. - Haha might win.
(Will he be able to win by answering one question?)
(Number 2 is incorrect.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Haha.
Please.
(Haha shouted earlier than So Min.)
No, didn't we call at the same time?
We called at the same time.
(If he answers wrong, So Min can get the correct answer.)
It's either number 1 or 4.
Whether they memorized the answer is important.
(Which anecdote is not related to Sejong the Great?)
Number four.
"When he drank a lot, he would cry."
(Haha remembers the exact words.)
(Is his answer correct this time?)
Correct.
(Number 4 is correct.)
I can't believe this.
(I'm doomed.)
Please!
(He wins a golden opportunity to be the winner.)
- I'll stand where it's empty. - Please.
I'll stand where it's empty.
- No. I still have a chance. - Here it is.
I have a chance.
Choose either Platform 4 or 5.
If she picks well, she can survive.
- She can. - Of course.
She definitely has a chance.
(So Min has to pick carefully.)
If I don't make it, we have to play again.
(Will she avoid the cube?)
(Or will he eliminate So Min?)
(So Min picks a platform.)
(Her final choice is Platform 4.)
Haha, take off the blindfold and write down your number.
(If So Min is eliminated, Haha is the final winner.)
(If she isn't, they'll compete again.)
(A number determines the winner.)
Have you decided?
(Haha picks a number.)
Here we go.
(Will it be over, or will there be a new round?)
One.
Two.
(Everyone holds their breath.)
Three.
(Where is the cube headed to?)
Three. Launch the cube.
(The cube is launched.)
(Two at the same time?)
What?
(Two cubes fly at the same time.)
I heard that...
Sejong the Great loved mixed buckwheat noodles and meat.
(What's the secret to the cube?)
I remembered that.
That's why I run a meat restaurant.
Correct.
(Haha won a Chance Card during a mission at the restaurant.)
(Targeting two people)
(He wins the card that allows him to launch two cubes.)
I think this is powerful.
(Before picking the final number, he uses his Chance Card.)
(It's a dramatic hit that he's been saving for.)
Haha.
I'm the king of quiz.
(Haha wins.)
It's Teachers' Day Special.
Sejong the Great's Riddle Race.
Surprisingly, today's winner is...
Haha.
(Today's final winner is Haha.)
The king of quiz.
You're amazing.
This is a human victory.
Nothing is impossible.
You gave a chance to everyone, Sejong the Great.
Thank you so much.
(Thank you, Sejong the Great.)
To the final winner,
the cash prize...
will be given immediately in cash.
This is amazing.
(Will it be given in cash?)
- Cash? - Goodness.
There are two money briefcases in front of you.
- Does he have to pick? - In one of them,
there are 10 dollars.
In the other, there are 1,000 dollars.
(There are two briefcases of a different amount.)
Pick one briefcase and open it.
- Seriously, Haha. - I hope he gets it.
I hope he wins 1,000 dollars.
- 1,000 dollars? - Try it alone, Haha.
Pick it on your own. You're lucky today.
(Haha won the quiz.)
Pick one.
(Will he still be lucky?)
- He's very lucky. - I think it's the right one.
I've made a decision.
1, 2, 3.
- Okay. - Goodness.
(He picks the briefcase on the right.)
- Isn't it the left one? - It's 100 percent certain.
- It's 100 percent. - Open it.
(Will there be 10 dollars?)
It will be written in it.
- Darn it. - See?
He thought it was the right one.
- His feeling was wrong. - Look at this.
There's a bundle of bills.
(There are 1,000 dollars in the other briefcase.)
Did you see that?
Congratulations.
You won 10 dollars.
The final winner today is Haha.
(Sejong the Great's Riddle Race is over.)
The king of quiz.
You never let us down.
(Jung Cheol Min, returning director)
(Iron Min is here.)
(We'll have a rough time.)
(The first rough task that we prepared)
(Running Man's 9th Anniversary Special)
(Running Man Meeting with Fans, Running Sweats Project)
(Meeting with fans in the country?)
(A special performance by Running Man members in 9 years)
(Running Sweats Concert with Fans)
(A special performance for fans in Korea)
If you lose...
(A shocking concert cue sheet from the director)
(Do they have to prepare an extremely difficult performance?)
(An intense competition with a special performance on the line)
We improved a lot in the meantime.
(8 Running Avengers heroes appear.)
(They've been working together for 9 years.)
(As long as they're together, they aren't afraid of any mission.)
(Even the contest is extremely difficult.)
(A nightmarish meeting with fans is very soon.)
(However)
(The competition until now was only the beginning.)
(The director's wicked whispers tempt the members.)
(Their choice can determine their win or loss.)
(Which members will take the hand of the demon?)
It's too intense.
(Demon's Whispers)