(Geumsan-gun, South Chungcheong Province)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello, everyone.
My gosh, that tree looks like ginseng.
It's ginseng.
That's homemade ginseng wine.
- My gosh, that's so healthy. - We're at a ginseng museum.
- This feels healthy. - Hello.
I have good news. It's about So Min.
She moved again.
(Too much information during the opening segment)
- She moved to a bigger house. - Thank you.
- It's a bigger house. - Where did you move to?
- It's apartment next to old one. - It's apartment next to old one.
It's five steps from my old place. It's right next to my old place.
- Didn't you get one more room? - Yes.
- How many rooms do you have? - Right.
I have three rooms now.
(Feeling proud)
So Min told me how big her place has gotten.
The way she explained it to me...
- was quite shocking. - How?
She said she almost peed her pants on her way to the bathroom.
- Your house is that big? - That's what she said.
- Hey, So Min. - That's true.
Her expression was too shocking.
Actually, if it were Seok Jin, he probably did pee his pants.
(Is this possible for Seok Jin?)
- He would've peed on his way. - That's terrible.
Hey, I'm still going strong. I'm still going strong.
(Given the circumstance, he's almost Seok Jin's doctor.)
Seok Jin has...
- a new nickname. - What is it?
Mr. Residual Urine.
(Before the shoot, he got a new nickname, Mr. Residual Urine.)
- Residual Urine. - Residual Urine.
That's not true.
- That's cute. - My gosh, I'm really upset.
It sounds like he's a fairy.
What he said infuriated me the most.
Before the shoot, even if you don't need to go,
- you'd go to the restroom anyway. - That's understandable.
After hearing it next to me, he told me I was...
Jee Stream.
- Right, right. - Did it just trickle down?
- Seriously. He was quiet at first. - Jee Stream.
Trickling.
(I was there too.)
- I was standing there too. - That breaks my heart.
- At one point... - Hey, hey.
After talking about prostate,
- our conversation has gotten weird. - Right.
- It's unnecessary. - Right.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
- Jee Stream is funny. - That's right.
- That was funny. - By the way, Jae Seok used...
- the app for baby faces. - Oh, that.
I did this with Sae Ho.
- I took one with Sae Ho. - I saw that photo.
That's your mother.
His mother looks just like that.
He looks just like her mother. That's his mother.
His mouth is the same.
- Yes. - You have the same mouth.
- It's the same with you too. - My mouth doesn't change with CG.
Nothing can fix your mouth.
- That's true. - My gosh.
- Haha took one too. - Haha took one too.
My wife uploaded that photo.
- You look adorable. - Your wife did?
Seok Jin should take one too.
(The members start looking for their baby photos.)
I'm really surprised by Seok Jin's photo.
- Why? - This app gives you the baby photo.
- That's just Seok Jin. - It's just him.
- It looks just like Seok Jin. - How can a baby look that old?
- Let me see. - I can see his wrinkles.
It just looks like you put on heavy makeup.
- Ji Hyo, why don't you try it too? - Why are we using this app now?
Ji Hyo will look pretty.
(She smiles to look younger.)
- Let me see. - Wait, hold on.
- Ji Hyo... What is this? - Isn't that Wong Fei Hung?
Half of her face is her forehead.
- Right. You really look like him. - Seriously.
Her forehead takes up half of her face.
She's definitely not from Korea.
- She looks exotic. - She looks like a Chinese girl.
- Hey. - She looks like a Chinese girl.
Let's try one with Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - No, no.
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook, look over here.
- I won't do it. - Come on, try it.
- Just try it once. - Come over here.
- I bet his photo will look great. - His arm...
(He smiles to look young after refusing to take one.)
- You haven't changed at all. - My gosh.
- Hey, he just looks like himself. - My gosh.
This boy looks like a great fighter.
He's only a boy, but he looks so mean.
- This boy looks scary. - He's only a boy.
- He's scary. - He looks scary.
- That was fun. - This is so much fun.
Do we have more news to share? There's none, right?
- We'll just start. - Okay.
- "We'll just start." - The next one was yours,
but we'll just start.
Please talk about me once.
Just one more news. Please.
- People might be curious about me. - Just one more news.
Do we have news about Kwang Soo?
- We do have news about him. - You ripped it off.
(This is the news.)
- Okay, okay. - Kwang Soo didn't...
- send a coffee truck from Ji Hyo. - Did you send one?
Did you send one to Bo Young and Lee Si Eon?
("Kwang Soo Sends a Coffee Truck for Si Eon and Bo Young")
(I see. This was the news.)
I didn't know that was the news. Okay, okay.
- What was that? Why? - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. Sorry. - That was so mean.
You sent one to Bo Young.
- But you do spend some money. - You know...
(Haha summons his new character of Greedy Millipede again.)
There he goes again.
- He doesn't spend money on us. - Right, right. Okay.
- That's nice to see. - He spends money for others.
- There they go again. - You know what?
You know what? I can understand that he'd send one to Bo Young.
- We can understand that. - Say Ji Hyo can understand that.
But Si Eon...
They were filming the drama together.
You sent one for Si Eon, but how could you not send one for Ji Hyo?
Hold on. Didn't you send one to Min Young the other day?
- Yes, I sent one to Min Young. - I did see that too.
(Jae Seok sent a dessert truck to Min Young.)
- Min Young... - Did you send one to Ji Hyo?
("Jae Seok did that?" Her eyes shake.)
Min Young sent me ginger tea, jujube tea, and kimchi.
- She sent you half-dried herring. - Right.
(She sent you half-dried herring every year.)
- Right. - She sent you half-dried herring.
- We got him. - She sent you that.
- Jae Seok. - But you didn't send her a truck?
Why didn't you send her one?
(When things aren't working out for him...)
We have to discuss this.
Ji Hyo sent him so much half-dried herring.
She sent him so much half-dried herring.
It's really upsetting me.
Ji Hyo, I'm really sorry.
Ji Hyo wasn't filming a drama when I thought about this.
Why did you make this worse?
His face is getting red. Now, I feel relieved.
- Both of them are suffering. - Let's switch places.
He wants to switch places.
- Hey, move there. - Why?
- Ji Hyo, just film a drama. - I mean it.
(I can just easily go to you. Hello, Jae Seok.)
(The ghost of coffee truck shows up.)
- I should send one for her drama. - You should stand between them.
- She's filming a movie nowadays. - Come here. It's uncomfortable.
Why is she...
Why aren't you filming a drama now?
You don't send a coffee truck when you're really close.
(Just like us)
- You don't have to send a truck. - That's right.
- I feel shy about that. - Right.
- All right. In that case... - Right. Don't do it.
(The ghost of coffee truck is kicked out before she could speak.)
Why would I send one to my family?
- Right. Don't be so disappointed. - Yes, let's not do that.
- I feel shy about that. - I see you every week.
- It's telling Mom that I love her. - I see Min Young from time to time.
- We see each other every week. - Right. We meet every week.
- Right. - He doesn't see her often.
- Forget about this whole thing. - We didn't do anything wrong.
- I'm sorry. - Right.
- Pretend this never happened. - I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
I couldn't send one because I feel shy about it.
I think you set the mood nicely before we start our race today.
- Right. - Yes.
Before we start the race, you will write down...
more than one modifiers such as words or nicknames...
that remind you of the members including yourself.
- For all of us? - Everyone?
- For everyone? - I see.
Nickname? Like what they're known as?
- Right. - All right.
Okay, let's do this.
"Write down words or phrases that remind you of each member."
"Jee Seok Jin."
(Everyone writes down nicknames for each member.)
"Jee Seok Jin. He's very gentle."
- Come on, are you serious? - "He's gentle."
That's not even funny. Why would you write that?
(Jong Kook is being brutally honest again.)
He said that wasn't even funny.
"English gentleman".
- You're not an English gentleman. - "Gentleman".
You're not like those English gentlemen at all.
- Besides, that's an oldie's thing. - I'm...
(An Outdated Thinking: Cool men are English gentlemen.)
- Seriously. - James Bond.
I'm serious.
- "Lee Kwang Soo". - Kwang Soo? What should I write?
"Ugly Long Legs".
(Childish nickname)
"Ugly Greedy Millipede".
(Or we can go with this.)
Can you just choose one?
Get rid of the millipede then.
"Stage Four Actor Syndrome".
What?
What are you talking about?
You don't have that?
"Cherished Comedian".
(This one will be nice.)
Was Kwang Soo a comedian?
Did you not know?
(He was my junior comedian.)
- You were my junior comedian. - This feels weird.
- You're getting special treatment. - This feels weird.
- Cherished Comedian. - "Comedian".
(Jae Seok's Cherished Comedian, Lee Kwang Soo)
- I'm happy about this. - That's hilarious.
- This feels weird. - This is nice.
Look at this. See how much I adore you.
- That's not a bad one. - That's a nice one.
"Jeon So Min, Crazy Poet".
(Crazy Poet: She usually writes her poems late at night.)
- That's nice. - Yes.
- That sounds charming. - Right. Crazy Poet.
- I sound like a real artist. - Right.
What should I go with Se Chan?
"My Confidence Booster".
(Se Chan is his Confidence Booster.)
Okay.
(He's the source of Jae Seok's confidence.)
You'll get our looks involved?
- You'll present after five minutes. - Okay.
"Haha, The Last Con Artist".
(Smiling)
Great. I'll write down "Fool" under his name.
(This fool who only cares about exercises...)
(is his business partner.)
(All 8 of them finish writing down nicknames.)
All right. Let's present now.
- I'll start first. - Okay, Kwang Soo.
I'll start with myself first. I call myself Abundance of Charms.
- Kind of... - What?
(Kwang Soo wrote down Abundance of Charms for himself.)
Isn't it more of Lack of Charms?
No, Abundance of Charms. I'm Abundance of Charms.
Kind and Comforting Face.
Mine is pretty simple. This is for Seok Jin.
Pees Like a Sparrow.
(He wrote down Pees Like a Sparrow for Seok Jin.)
That's cute. Sparrows are cute. Those birds are cute.
Anyway, those birds pee too. So, he is Pees Like a Sparrow.
- And the next one is Nolbu. - What?
- Why? - Pardon?
- Why? - Nolbu is famous for being greedy.
(He doesn't have a particular reason behind it.)
You're basically criticizing him.
- That's not a nickname. - No, that's not true.
- This is Jae Seok's. - Okay.
Ugly Guy.
- My gosh, that's perfect for him. - Gosh, he's unbelievable.
- He's gone mad. - Okay.
And I wrote down Leggings Lover.
- Leggings Lover. That makes sense. - Right?
He's Yuggings.
And for Jong Kook,
I wrote Thug.
(It's simple.)
How could you call me that?
It's just a nickname.
- That just came to your mind. - Right.
- This is Se Chan's. - Okay.
Ugly Guy Number Two.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Don't clump me with him. - 1 and 2.
- I can't believe his nerve. - Why am I number two though?
(A unit of Ugly Guys is created.)
I'll go.
This is for Seok Jin. His nickname is Honey Punch.
- Honey Punch. - That's right.
- I haven't heard that for a while. - That's cute.
- Honey Punch. - I really think it's really cute.
Death Mole.
- Death Mole. That's right. - I don't have that.
I was just writing mine based on our discussion.
Next up is Jong Kook. Kwang Soo's and mine overlapped.
He wrote, "Thug".
I wrote, "First Generation Thug".
(He's not just ordinary thug. He's 1st Generation Thug.)
(1st Generation Thug)
Yes, he's the first generation.
He's the original.
That means that he's the original thug.
- I wrote, "Romantic Punch". - "Romantic Punch".
- Umigwan's Crew. - That one is nice.
- Crew. - He's the Crew.
- I see. - That's what I aimed for.
- It's Jae Seok's now. - Okay.
- Nutria. - That's perfect.
(His nickname is totally based on facts.)
- That little punk. - That's cute. It's cute.
- I can't get rid of that one. - That's mean.
- That's cute. - We have to include Nutria.
My nickname is...
Handsome Face without the Mouth.
Hottie with Gums.
- I'll approve. - My gosh.
Right.
- That's my list. - Great.
First, I'll start with Jae Seok. It's Jae Seok's.
Yu Brat.
He's so bratty.
He's bratty to the point where he gets annoying.
- This crossed my mind. - What is it?
I thought that he could lend me 200,000 dollars...
if I'm in a tight spot.
(He's a colleague who can lend me up to 200,000 dollars.)
- My gosh. Really? - Gosh.
I think he'll wire me 200,000 to 300,000 dollars.
- Right. - That crossed my mind.
I would have to put your house up as collateral.
(I would have to put your house up as collateral.)
Right. That's the right way.
Anyway, I'll lend him money.
- I should do that. - Right.
And this is Jong Kook's.
I've been keeping this as a secret and haven't told anyone.
Actually, I think I can get him with just one punch.
(Actually, I think I can get him with just one punch.)
(Responding to that is a hassle for him.)
If I hit him at the vital point,
- a punch will suffice. - Seok Jin.
Think how many punches I can land on you when you punch me once.
(Think how many punches I can land on you when you punch me once.)
(A sharp comment from the 1st Generation Thug)
- Hey. - Think about it.
My left hand will be busy.
When I punch you with my right hand, I'll stop your punches with my left.
Like this.
I had to think about this one. It's quite unexpected.
- In my opinion, - Okay.
Jong Kook will lend me up to 50,000 dollars.
- Without any interests. - Me?
- Why are you talking about this? - Why are we talking about money?
- Why are we talking about money? - Did something happen to you?
Seok Jin, do you need money?
- Can't you lend me that much? - Of course.
I lend money to a lot of people.
But if you don't pay me back, you'll dearly pay for it.
- Hey, I always pay it back. - Really?
- He'll do everything to get it. - Really?
He'll do everything to get it back.
All right. This is Ji Hyo's.
Whenever I look at her, she's always dozing off.
Song Sleepy. Song Loner.
- She likes to be alone. - Right.
That's why her nickname is Song Van.
(Her nickname is Song Van?)
She's always resting in her van, so it's Song Van.
(She's named Song Van because she's always resting in her van.)
(Everyone agrees. It's the birth of a new nickname.)
- That's funny. - Whenever she rests,
- That's funny. - she's in the van.
- That's a nice nickname. - I can understand why.
- She's always resting in the van. - Song Van.
- Song Van. - Song Van is funny.
And I think Ji Hyo can...
Since her parents take care of her finances,
I think she can lend me about 20,000 dollars.
Seok Jin, are you fleeing the country?
(Seok Jin, are you fleeing the country?)
(Comedian Jee is spotted from fleeing the country.)
- Why are you talking about money? - Are you leaving with that money?
After talking about Jae Seok and how much he can lend me,
I thought about how much each member could lend me.
(Seok Jin finishes presenting the nicknames.)
- I'll start from here. Me first. - Okay.
"Haha".
- "Stamina King". - What?
(Haha nicknames himself as Stamina King.)
(Haha, Stamina King)
- What was that? - What do you mean?
- Well, he has three children. - Why?
It's Jae Seok's.
AO.
- What? - What's AO?
(Jae Seok is AO.)
Apgujeong Oldie.
- MF. - What's that?
Messed-up Face.
- I can't believe him. - My gosh.
That's a nice word for his face.
- JSG. - What's that?
Jong Shin without Glasses.
(Jong Shin without Glasses)
- He's unbelievable. - Why did you shorten everything?
He's definitely gone mad.
- Jong Shin? - CB.
What does that mean?
Child's Body.
(Child's Body)
Right.
All right. Mines are simple.
Jae Seok is Goofball.
Skeleton.
(Skeleton)
- What? Skeleton? - Skeleton.
- How could you say that? - To Jong Kook, he's a skeleton.
- He's Skeleton. - Hey.
- Are we in elementary school now? - Skeleton.
- Seriously? Skeleton? - I haven't heard that for a while.
- That's original. - We used that a lot back then.
And my nickname is One Man.
(He calls Jae Seok Skeleton. And he calls himself One Man.)
(He thinks he's so cool.)
- That explains everything. - One Man.
Ji Hyo's nickname is Ms. 40.
(Welcome to your 40s. Her nickname is Ms. 40.)
(She's 39 years old.)
Ms. 40?
- Is that Ms. Heart or Ms. 40? - Ms. 40.
- I can't tease her with that. - Ms. 40.
Coffee Truck Lover.
I'll start with Kwang Soo's.
- Loser. - Loser?
(It's simple.)
(Did I hear it wrong?)
- That's so insulting. - Hey, Loser is here!
(Picking on Kwang Soo)
- It's short and insulting. - My gosh, Loser.
It's like "Former Best Friend".
Loser.
And Super Loser.
(He gets Super Loser after Loser.)
(It's a somewhat of an upgrade from Loser.)
She just wrote down curse words.
(Can she do that?)
My gosh, that was strong.
And this is So Min's.
Love Opportunist.
- Love Opportunist. - Love Opportunist is nice.
- He's an LO. - Come on.
Come to me, love.
(Sounding depressed)
- She's a local poet in Yongsan-gu. - Right.
Cool Lady. That's for me.
(She suddenly blurts it out.)
Goosebumps. I got goosebumps.
Seok Jin. Seok Jin's nickname is...
- Don't Cross That River. - What?
Don't Cross That River.
That's a movie title.
(A documentary that depicted last moments of an old couple)
- That's nice. - Add "Jin" in the front.
Add "Jin". Jin...
(Jin, don't cross that river.)
Hey, if someone beckons to you, you can't go there, okay?
- You'll be in big trouble. - Don't say that.
- You can't cross that bridge. - Stop that.
- Jin. - Jin.
- This is Jae Seok's. - Okay.
Yu Kid.
Mouth Like Mount Baekdu.
- "Mouth Like Mount Baekdu"? - "Mouth Like Mount Baekdu"?
(Mouth Like Mount Baekdu)
- Mouth Like Mount Baekdu. - Hey, you.
- I like it. - That's really nice.
(Outstanding poetic line)
- Jae Seok. - She's unbelievable.
Climber Um Hong Gil will contact you.
He will want to climb your mouth.
- Stop that. - What do you mean?
- Stop teasing me. - What do you mean?
How can she call me Mouth Like Mount Baekdu?
- I've never heard of this before. - She's too mean.
- She's indeed a poet. - Mouth Like Mount Baekdu.
- That's nice. - Mouth Like Mount Baekdu.
Se Chan's nickname is Sidekick.
I Don't Like You.
Don't Pretend You Didn't Hear It.
(His nicknames are...)
(I Don't Like You and Don't Pretend You Didn't Hear It.)
(So Min, Love Opportunist, gives soap-opera worthy nicknames.)
Come on.
- Are these really nicknames? - She just said whatever she wanted.
She wrote these down to get them off her chest.
And Mouth Like Mount Halla.
- Mouth Like Mount Halla. - Mouth Like Mount Halla?
- I'm Mount Baekdu. - I'm Mount Halla. Mine is better.
This is all.
Mine is slightly better.
I gave this a lot of thought. I thought about you a lot.
That's why mine is packed.
I'll start with Se Chan.
My Confidence Booster.
Mr. Gums. Se Hyeong's Brother.
Model's Ex-Boyfriend.
What? Model's Ex-Boyfriend?
Wasn't your ex a model?
- Was she a flight attendant? - No.
Let me revise it.
Flight Attendant's Ex.
(Se Chan's nickname is Flight Attendant's Ex.)
- Jae Seok. - No.
That's you.
(Getting up)
Have you gone mad?
(Have you gone mad?)
(Will they start exposing each other's secrets?)
- I'm going to write this down. - Stop it.
- You know what? - Stop it. Stop it.
- Stop it. - I'm going to write that down.
- Stop it. - Don't do it.
- Stop it. Don't dig your own grave. - You don't think I know?
- Really? - This is interesting.
- I'll write that down. - Easy, easy.
(They barely manage to reconcile right before a big accident.)
A lot of secrets will come out.
- Should I write yours? - What? Stop it.
Stop it. That's enough.
- I know her name. I do. - My goodness.
- Be quiet. - I know her name.
(Before a bigger accident happens,)
(8 of them finish presenting each other's nicknames.)
All right. You wrote down nicknames for each other.
Why did you make us write these?
Today, you'll write down lyrics for the theme song.
It's the 4th Episode of 9 Years of Running Man.
It's the Knowing Your Place Race.
(This will determine the lyrics for the theme song?)
- Lyrics? - The theme song?
Lyrics?
(Is it possible that we might use the nicknames we just presented?)
As for the theme song, professional songwriters...
will be taking care of it.
But as for the nicknames for each member,
we'll choose from the ones you just came up with.
(They wrote down each other's weaknesses...)
(without giving much thought.)
(These nicknames may be used as lyrics for the theme song.)
(The members were busy teasing each other.)
- From these? - Messed-up Face.
- Let's go with that. - We'll include these in the lyrics?
That will be in our song?
Mouth Like Mount Baekdu.
You're ginseng diggers who came to Geumsan, home for ginseng.
You will start the race...
with 2 Ginseng Badges and 2 Venomous Snake Badges.
- Ginseng and Venomous Snake? - Yes.
Ginseng Badges mean good nicknames for you.
Venomous Snake Badges mean bad nicknames for you.
At the end of the race, you'll remove Ginseng Badges...
as many Venomous Snake Badges as you have.
And that's how you'll end up with your nickname.
Wait.
What about Seok Jin's nickname, Jee Stream?
Jee Stream.
- This will go down in history. - That one is...
This will be in the lyrics.
We have to get rid of that...
because I didn't have to use the restroom then.
I had a feeling that the shoot would last a long time.
I didn't have to use the restroom back then!
Jee Stream.
At the end of the race,
if you have the same number of both badges,
- we'll include your names. - Okay.
For example, we'll just say so and so and Haha.
- Jae Seok, so and so and Seok Jin. - Like this.
- That's disappointing. - I'd rather have a nickname.
After you change into the uniforms,
we'll start the race.
- Okay. - Let's go, everybody.
Hurry.
1, 2. 1, 2. 1, 2.
- 1, 2. - It's the ginseng digger's outfit.
(There are 8 mysterious bags on top of the table.)
(Forget about the outfits. What are these bags?)
I don't look good in this outfit no matter how much I try.
It looks great on you.
- Aren't you bedridden or something? - Right.
(Does she look more like a patient than a ginseng digger?)
- She's bedridden? - My gosh.
- My gosh, woe is me. - It looks great on her.
- People like her are sick in bed. - My gosh.
You'd be great in historical dramas.
What an awful son I have. I told you not to get married.
(Is she doing a skit out of nowhere?)
- Go away. - But...
why do you always start your skit with a curse word?
(Why do you always start your skit with a curse word?)
- And she hits me. - Why is that?
- It's all her skits. - Your skits start with cursing.
I wanted to do something I can't do in my skits.
- All the diggers are here. - Okay.
Before we go to our location for the first mission,
- I'll tell you an extra rule. - What is it?
There's an additional rule.
In these eight bags...
(8 of the mission bags are placed in front of them.)
In these eight bags,
- there is a Bomb Sticker. - My gosh.
(There's a Bomb Sticker.)
We have to choose one again?
At the end of the race,
as for the member with the Bomb Sticker,
all the Badges the member has will become Venomous Snake Badges.
- No, no. - My gosh.
All the Badges the member has will become Venomous Snake Badges.
(There will be a flood of bad nicknames.)
- That's the worst. - Only the bad ones will remain.
Therefore, the member who has the Bomb Sticker...
must hide it on another member's body
or bags within an hour.
And if the member fails to give it to someone else,
the member will get a Venomous Snake Badge every hour.
(If the member fails, he or she will get the Venomous Snake Badge.)
I didn't know about that.
(Bomb Sticker and Venomous Snake Badge...)
- That's terrible. - If you're caught...
giving the Sticker to someone else,
the member will get extra Venomous Snake Badge.
(If caught, the member will get extra Venomous Snake Badge.)
After every hour which is the time limit,
everyone will find out if the member gave the Bomb Sticker...
to another member.
- Keep an eye out. - Okay.
All right. You'll draw the bags including the Bomb Sticker now.
Take a bag of your choice.
- I'll take the leftover. - Me too.
(Taking the leftover bags is the best.)
I'm sure Kwang Soo will get it.
- No, no. - I'll take this one.
(When everyone is hesitant because of the Bomb Sticker,)
(Jae Seok picks a bag without any hesitation.)
Jae Seok already took the Bomb Sticker.
We can relax now.
You can relax now.
- I don't feel confident about this. - It's always a lot of pressure.
(Everyone picks a bag.)
The Sticker already left. It left even before I chose mine.
Does everyone have an envelope?
(The members are carefully checking the bags.)
I'm sure I don't have it.
The probability is only 15 percent.
It's 12 percent.
All right. We'll start the timer for the hour.
- Okay. - My gosh.
The timer starts now.
- We'll head there by bus. - Okay.
It's just an hour.
But this will be so stressful today.
It's definitely me.
- For an hour... - They'll try to put it on me.
- I have to keep an eye out. - Darn it.
They'll try to put it on me.
(Se Chan taps Jae Seok's back from behind.)
(Keeping his guard)
I just put my hand here.
- Don't be nervous. - Look at him.
Did you hear?
(Everyone gets anxious whenever touched.)
- Do we have to catch that person? - That doesn't matter.
I want you to understand this today.
If you try to put it on me,
I might punch you before I could stop myself.
(He's getting his Honey Punch ready.)
- Your Honey Punch? - It's my reflex.
I'll lick it if you punch me. I'll do that.
- I'll do that if you punch me. - Listen.
- I'll lick your Honey Punch. - Please.
- I'll lick it. - Punch in my mouth.
- I'll lick it. - Listen.
- I won't be able to stop myself. - I'll tell you that in advance too.
- I might punch you. - I'll lick it if you do.
(Which one of them has the Bomb Sticker?)
This must be the place.
Let's get off. Here we go.
- I'm sure you have it. - Thank you.
I'm sure you have it.
(They're checking their bodies if they have the Bomb Sticker.)
What if I don't have it, Seok Jin?
- I'm sure you have it. - What if I don't?
- I'm 100 percent sure. - What if I don't?
I'm too anxious to even walk around.
- I'm really anxious too. - I don't have it, right?
Why do you always make it hard for us to trust people?
They yell at me when I just tapped them.
Gosh, the sight of it looks so hot.
(The ginseng costume is placed in front of the members.)
- Goodness, seriously. - Gosh.
- It must be so hot to be inside. - Seriously.
- This is... - It's heavy too.
Isn't this a dolphin?
(At that moment when they're distracted...)
(Surprised)
What is it?
- What is it? - No way.
- What? - The first mission is...
You know what? The timing is so weird.
- What do you mean? - I was just kidding.
(What just happened?)
(When Haha yelled earlier,)
(everyone was focused on Haha.)
(At that moment,)
(Jae Seok put something on Seok Jin's bag.)
(Everyone scattered around to check if they had the Bomb Sticker.)
(Jae Seok gets the Bomb Sticker.)
Okay.
- My gosh, this is... - Hey!
(Jae Seok was looking for a chance to move the Bomb Sticker.)
(When Haha drew their attention,)
(he managed to put the Bomb Sticker on Seok Jin.)
- What is it? - No way.
(Jae Seok had the Bomb Sticker.)
(So Min also witnesses the transfer.)
Can you move to the center here?
(I put it on Seok Jin.)
- He put the Sticker on him. - The first mission is...
- On who? - On Seok Jin.
What? Really?
(The first mission starts after the Bomb has been transferred.)
You will form 2 teams of 4 members.
You'll invite one merchant.
It's a group match the five of you will have.
- Merchant? - We'll invite a merchant?
It's 4 to 4?
- It will be 5 to 5. - That will be 5 to 5.
The team leader will have a chance...
- to wear the provided costume. - I'd hate that.
(We can't wear that on this hot day.)
- Seok Jin loves being the leader. - But...
- Right? - It's about time he becomes one.
- And he likes that. - Right.
- No, no. I hate being the leader. - Right.
- You must be the authority figure. - I hate being the team leader.
- You should be the leader. - Yes, he ought to.
- No, no. - Let's play Race of Wits.
- It's to pick the team leaders. - Okay. For the team leaders.
- I'll shout number one. - Two people must shout together.
I'll shout number one too.
- Get ready. - I'll say number seven.
- Start. - Seven.
(Hesitating)
One.
- 2. - 3.
(Flinching)
- 4. - 5.
- 6. - 6.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan shouted 6 at the same time.)
Kwang Soo, why did you do that?
Why did you do that?
That was so close.
Okay. Good thing I held back.
I'm glad I held back.
(Team Soo's Ginseng and Team Chan's Ginseng)
- All right. - The youngest members.
Team Soo's Ginseng and Team Chan's Ginseng.
- Team Soo's Ginseng. - Put that on now.
Soo's Ginseng sounds so funny. Soo's Ginseng.
But it's made so that the air is ventilated inside.
- Air can't be ventilated inside! - Right here.
- Right here. - It's so hot in here.
- Really? - Right here.
(Just the sight of them is suffocating.)
Gosh, this is so funny. It's so funny.
- Can you move? - Can you move?
Stop it.
Hey. I can't even hear properly.
Hey, Se Chan looks stable in the costume.
All right. Go and invite a merchant.
- Come back here with them. - Do we just come back here?
We don't know what we're going to play, right?
- Right. - We don't know that yet.
Let's get going first.
- Who should we invite? - It's really stuffy inside.
Let's go, Ginseng.
There are a lot of interesting things here.
There are a lot of medicinal herbs.
Right.
I've heard of fish mint a lot too.
- Hello. - Gosh, look at that.
- I see ginseng wine. - Right.
There's a lot of stuff. Red ginseng jelly.
- Jelly. - Red ginseng candy.
I see red ginseng crackers too.
Crackers?
They have fried ginseng. Let's go over there.
Jae Seok, we have to...
- Right. - invite a merchant.
- We just need 1, right? - Just 1.
By the way, since we're here, we should taste one.
I want to taste a fried ginseng. Just one.
- Right? - Right.
- They sell fried ginseng. - Sir, is fried ginseng ready?
- That looks good. - How much is it?
It's a dollar and a half per each.
- Can we get one each? - Thank you.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Seriously. You're so cool. - My gosh.
Hello.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
Actually, we have to drink...
- ginseng rice wine with this. - That's right. We ought to.
(They also taste rice wine made with ginseng.)
I bet he added ginseng extract.
Look at the color.
- Have a taste. - The color looks different.
- Try it with the fried ginseng. - It totally smells like ginseng.
Drink it when the fried ginseng is ready.
(She's drawn to the alcohol like a magnet.)
- Wait for the food. That's a lot. - Drink it with the food.
- Thank you. - These look beautiful.
- I'm curious. - I can smell the ginseng.
- Try it. - Is this made with red ginseng?
- It's red ginseng marmalade. - Red ginseng marmalade.
- Red ginseng marmalade. - That's red ginseng marmalade?
It's not soy sauce.
It's interesting.
(How does it taste?)
(This is awesome.)
I can smell a hint of ginseng.
(The fragrance softly spreads.)
It's savory.
I deep-fry the whole ginseng. The entire root of it.
I've never tasted anything like this.
- My gosh. - It's my first time too.
What an interesting dish.
If you eat the entire root of it, you'll be healthy for a year.
(One root of ginseng for a year?)
(Is he talking big?)
(I know that this is healthy, but that's exaggerating.)
Fried ginseng is no fattening no matter how many you eat.
Ginseng?
But fried food is fattening.
But this isn't fattening.
(He talks big again.)
(He exaggerates about ginseng.)
Fried ginseng isn't fattening.
It's not fattening when it's fried?
(The owner is funny.)
- Sir. - But fried food...
It's very healthy.
- Really? - Yes.
- He's exaggerating. - Since we're on the subject,
do you want to go and play a game with us?
- Sure. - He can introduce this place too.
Great. Why don't you join us?
(Can the ginseng preacher show the power of ginseng?)
- This way, please. - Let's go.
All right. We've invited the merchants here.
- Please introduce yourselves. - Okay.
I work at the Fresh Ginseng Center. I'm Gil Tae Hwan.
- Okay. - Mr. Gil.
I'm his wife.
- What's your name? - It's Son Eun Ji.
Ms. Son.
The mission you'll do here with the merchants...
is called Our Drawing Link.
(Our Drawing Link)
It has nothing to do with athletic ability.
- You never know. - Okay.
(Ms. Son from Team Se Chan will play as she's artistic.)
She was good at arts.
If it's about drawing, Jae Seok...
(We're doomed.)
Hey, don't you know that I'm good at drawing?
Everyone told me that my drawing has improved a lot.
(I don't see any improvement.)
And all of my people in the drawing are opening up their arms.
(Everyone opens their arms.)
- No one has joints. - Just like this.
- Like this. - They are straight.
Kwang Soo must be so hot.
They are not team leaders.
- They're doing a penalty. - I think so too.
- It's so hot in here. - Why would team leaders do this?
- They are not team leaders. - How are we the team leaders?
Before we start, you can take off the costumes.
- You guys are about to pass out. - Okay.
- By the way, I've done this before. - Pull the head.
- They are the team leaders. - Lower your head.
Lower your head.
(But Kwang Soo the Ginseng...)
Let's dig out the wild ginseng. One.
Two. I mean, ginseng.
(Crawling)
- Come on. - 1, 2.
Why are you always so clumsy?
(Why are you always so clumsy?)
(How could you call me that?)
You're always so clumsy. Goodness.
Pull out your arms.
- Seriously. - But he's the team leader.
- Right. - He's the team leader indeed.
He's sweating a lot.
- He does look like one. - Okay.
All right. I'll give you the rule.
Each team will randomly draw two questions.
You must read the lyrics on the sketchbook.
The four of you will come up with drawings for the lyrics.
The last member must guess either the lyrics or the title.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Okay. Se Chan is good at this. - Hey.
I know new songs.
However,
each member will have...
- only 10 seconds to draw. - See?
- It's so short. How can we do that? - We don't have much time.
But I tend to draw the key features very quickly.
Jae Seok, don't kid yourself. You'll answer the questions.
How dare you think about drawing?
- He'll draw. - Hey, I'm really good at it.
- He always draws Anpanman. - Right.
- He was holding a tray. - Come on.
- Do you remember that one? - Right.
You're unbelievable.
(Team Se Chan will start first.)
All right. Everyone, turn around.
We'll show this to the team in the back first.
- Okay. - This is...
the first question. These are the lyrics for it.
(Team Se Chan's first song, "Alone" by Sistar)
(The four of them must draw to express the lyrics in order.)
(The last member must figure out the title or the provided lyrics.)
(I eat alone, watch a movie alone, sing alone, and cry)
(Oh, this is the song.)
- It's hard. - Is it hard?
- Please. - It's hard.
(The lyrics will be hard to draw.)
Each person has 10 seconds. Get ready. Set, go.
("Alone" by SISTAR)
Draw the important parts.
(Oh, it's this song.)
It won't be hard since Jong Kook...
and Haha can draw.
- 3, 2. - Time's up.
- One. - Already?
Time's up. Change. Now it's Haha's turn.
(Jong Kook draws an angry stick figure.)
- Add details to it. - I think...
we should focus on what Jong Kook and Haha drew.
7, 6.
3, 2, 1. Time's up.
(Haha drew a person who is eating alone.)
What is it?
(Seok Jin is next.)
10, 9, 8.
- Seok Jin. - What are you doing?
(Motionless)
- Six. - He doesn't know the song.
- Five. - What is he doing?
You need to keep going.
- Maybe the words are too small. - You need to keep going.
One. Time's up.
What was that?
- 10. - What are you doing?
- 9, 8. - What are you doing?
Seven.
6, 5.
- Four. - That's a nice detail.
- Three. - That's a nice detail.
(She adds a nice detail.)
- That's a nice detail. - This one is hard.
- 1. - The 1st question isn't easy.
- Can I turn around? - You got this.
You got this.
What is this?
Don't you get it?
Seriously. Although he knows a lot of songs,
his brain doesn't work.
How is my brain supposed to work upon seeing this drawing?
It's a difficult question. It's okay.
It's a difficult question.
- What is 119? - No.
Is there 119?
- 119? - Is there 119?
- 3, 2. - There is no 119.
- One. - Sobangcha.
- Which song? - Last night
- I - It was hard.
It was "Alone".
You should have drawn...
- a television. - Seriously.
- He didn't do anything. - The lyrics are...
He behaved like a spy.
We can't write down numbers.
Then why did you just sit and stare?
(It seems like you know the rules very well.)
What did you do?
He sat and watched for six seconds.
- You failed. - This question was hard.
- It was hard. - Here comes the next question.
Would you like to change the order?
- Would you like to guess? - Yes. Because...
- He can't do it. - It's a bad idea, right?
Really? Then you should guess.
That was cute.
- Should I guess? - Yes.
- Haha is witty. - Haha is witty.
- It's the last chance, right? - All right.
This is the first line of the lyrics.
I will show you the question first.
(Team Se Chan's last question)
(I trusted my friend as much as I trusted you)
(The biggest hit of the 90s, "Wrongful Encounter" by Kim Gun Mo)
(Is it this song?)
- It's so famous. - How will they draw that?
- This is hard. - It's impossible to draw.
- Jong Kook, you should guess it. - It's impossible to draw.
Hold on. Shall we change seats?
Shall I guess it?
Would you like to do that? Okay. Let's change seats.
Okay. Okay.
- Time out. - Time out.
- Time out. I will guess it. - Let's change seats.
- Didn't he see the lyrics? - No, he didn't.
This is hard.
- How will they draw that? - Seriously.
Set, go.
(I trusted my friend as much as I trusted you)
- Let's get this right. - That's what you will draw.
- 5, 4. - This is hard.
3, 2.
- That's right. - One. Time's up.
Pass it to the next person.
(He drew "Wrongful Encounter" in a witty way.)
(It's Seok Jin's turn to draw.)
10, 9.
Why did you see that?
(Hold on.)
- What? - You saw the lyrics.
- He needs to see the lyrics. - Right.
(I am sorry.)
What is wrong with you?
- I am sorry. - What is wrong with you?
Why do you think everything Seok Jin does is wrong?
You did that on purpose, right?
- Time's up. - I am sorry.
Seok Jin couldn't draw anything!
I didn't do it on purpose.
- Come on. - I am serious.
I didn't do it on purpose. I am sorry.
- Seok Jin is a member of this team. - I know.
(It's Se Chan's turn to draw.)
- 5, 4. - Why are you drawing another one?
- Three. - He doesn't work at the market.
Three people.
One. Time's up.
- You didn't draw much. - What is wrong with you?
- Why did you draw that? - What did you do?
Ms. Son.
- What should I do? - Hold on.
Erase that. Erase the blue stick figure.
- This one? - Yes.
(She puts an X-sign over Se Chan's drawing.)
I can't believe Se Chan.
- 2, 1. - All right.
- Make sure you look carefully. - It's all in the drawing.
It's a national song.
- Did you draw well? - I drew the lyrics well.
- He really did. - Did you draw well?
It's a work of art, right?
I drew it by myself. No one else drew.
- That's right. - No one else drew.
- You are right. - No one else drew.
The two of them should play the game.
5, 4.
(He looks at Haha's drawing.)
3, 2,
- one. - Kim Gun Mo's "Wrongful Encounter".
(Kim Gun Mo's "Wrongful Encounter")
How did he know?
(The quick-witted Jong Kook gets the answer right.)
- How did he know? - I got goosebumps.
- The rest of them didn't help. - I got goosebumps.
How did he get this right?
Why did you draw another person? In any case, Jong Kook got it right.
- Thank goodness. - You are the best.
Why did you become confused when I drew three people?
I was trying to draw a more wrongful encounter.
It's more wrongful if there are four people.
There are five members in this team,
but only four of them are happy.
Aren't you happy? Aren't you happy?
Let's do a cheer.
That was incredible.
Jong Kook is the best.
We can do this.
- Let's begin. - Let's go.
We just need to get two questions right.
Here comes the question.
(You watch my rough thoughts and nervous eyes)
(Yim Jae Beom's masterpiece from the 2000s, "For You")
My goodness. How will they get it right?
(What could it be?)
I will get this right.
Let's go. So Min, you are first.
Jae Seok will never get it right.
- How will they draw it? - Set, go.
- Do your best. - What?
(She reads the lyrics and draws quickly.)
How does she draw so fast?
(Rough thoughts and nervous eyes)
Time's up. Pass it to the next member.
(How did So Min describe the lyrics?)
(Crying eyes and staring eyes)
- 10 seconds seemed longer. - Right?
- Let's go. - 10 seconds seemed longer.
- Let's go. - Jae Seok won't get this right.
- One. Time's up. - If Jae Seok gets this right,
I will acknowledge him as a genius.
What is that?
- The singer. - What did he draw?
I see what he tried to draw.
It does look like him, but...
(It's Mr. Lee's turn.)
- Sir, you need to draw something. - Four.
Sir, draw something.
Mr. Lee.
Why did you draw eyelashes?
(Hold on.)
- It's for nervousness. - What?
- I see. Okay, okay. - 10.
Mr. Lee.
- Stop talking. - 8, 7.
(How will I wrap up this drawing?)
4, 3.
- What is Ji Hyo doing? - What is that?
- One. Time's up. - What is that?
It's about watching.
How will he get it right?
(Will Jae Seok be able to get this right?)
(It's a total disaster.)
- This is... - This is impossible.
- He won't get it right. - Jae Seok.
- I was in a hurry. - What is this?
How am I supposed to...
- Still... - It was the hardest question.
Jae Seok, look at the message.
Look. There are tears, right?
(He tries to gain information.)
You can't have a conversation.
(You can't have a conversation.)
- You can't exchange looks. - I didn't do anything.
Keep your eyes on the front and say the answer.
Seriously.
I need to solve this by myself.
Is this arrow for these eyes?
(Think differently.)
Hold on.
- Stop it. - Seriously.
What are you doing?
- Turn around. - Turn around. What are you doing?
5, 4, 3,
- two... - "With..."
- One. - "With My Tears".
("With My Tears")
(Incorrect)
It's incorrect.
(You watch my rough thoughts)
- How could this drawing be... - And nervous eyes
(Look at the drawing carefully.)
(There are nervous eyes...)
(and another set of eyes which watches on.)
(Why couldn't you figure it out?)
Is this the person who is watching?
- Look here. - What is this?
It's Yim Jae Beom.
(Kwang Soo is confident.)
(Is this Yim Jae Beom?)
It looks like him.
- That's right. - He has a mustache.
- It does look like him. - See?
Empty a seat. I will draw. Who will guess the answer?
- So Min, guess the answer. - Make it simple.
The first person is important.
- By the way, - So Min.
Sir. Why did you draw eyelashes?
- Tears. - They represent the state of mind.
- The nervousness. - Eyelashes are a bit...
- So Min, Mr. Lee's drawing is blue. - Okay.
(So Min, Mr. Lee's drawing is blue.)
- Pretend it's never there. - I will keep that in mind.
Hey, hey. Don't do that.
- The blue marker is transparent. - Okay.
Let's put our hands together.
- Let's go. - One.
- Let's go. - 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go. - We will win.
It's a matter of getting one question right.
- Let's go. - Good luck.
This is the question.
(Team Kwang Soo's last question)
(Tonight, the star is me, pick me, pick me)
("Pick Me" by Wanna One was the hottest song in 2017.)
- Gosh, this one is easy. - This one is easy.
Is it really easy?
It's easy.
Jae Seok, you will go first. Get ready.
- All right. - How will he draw that?
- I wouldn't know what to do. - Go.
(Let's see.)
Gosh, it's this song.
- It's easy. - It's so easy.
- It's easy. - It's easy.
- So Min will get it right. - That drawing is a disaster.
(That drawing is a disaster.)
That drawing is a disaster.
- What is that? - One. Time's up.
- We are set. - We are set.
What is that?
(It does look like a person if you look closely.)
Is that person eating carp bread?
- He drew a carp. - That person is eating carp bread.
- Carp bread. - What is that?
One. Time's up.
- There you go. - What is that?
- The drawing is perfect now. - All right.
It was carp bread.
(It's Mr. Lee's turn.)
- Sir, draw. Draw something. - Sir.
Sir, draw something.
Do something.
- One. Time's up. - What?
- What is that? - What is that?
Sir, why did you do that?
(I am sorry I don't know the song.)
(Ji Hyo is the last member.)
- That person is eating carp bread. - My goodness.
(It looks like she drew the moon.)
What?
Out of all the shapes of the moon...
- So Min, guess the answer. - Is it my turn?
Look at the important parts.
Look at the background.
- But... - It's easy.
- What is this? - You can get this right.
It's easy.
I'm the best.
Pick me.
(Did So Min get it?)
Pick me
(That's it.)
You have to either sing the lyrics correctly...
or say the correct title.
- You have two options. - Tonight, the star is me
- Pick me, pick me - What comes next?
(She skipped the third line.)
(What were the lyrics?)
(You're almost there.)
Tonight, the star is me
Are you singing a round?
What are you doing?
You have to either say the title...
- or sing the whole lyrics. - Are you singing a round?
- Is it okay to say the title? - You can say the title too.
(It's okay to just say the title.)
Tonight...
I don't know the title. What should I do?
(I don't know the title. What should I do?)
- What? - I don't know the title.
What should I do?
- What? - Be quiet.
She doesn't know the title?
- Be quiet. - Isn't that strange?
Tonight, the star is me
(She repeats the same part over and over again.)
- Are you Ppak Gu? - Hurry up...
and make up your mind.
It's you, it's you
What's the title? I don't remember it.
- I don't know the title. - That's so funny.
- I don't know the title. - The title is...
- "Pick Me". - It's "Pick Me".
(She's been saying, "Pick me", so many times.)
She kept saying, "Pick me".
That's so funny.
She said, "Pick me", more than 30 times.
What did you do?
The title...
You didn't know the title?
- Is the title "Pick Me"? - Yes.
- Kwang Soo did a good job. - My drawing was on point.
I figured it out thanks to this.
The hand? Kwang Soo drew it.
Jae Seok.
Is that a thumb?
- It's a thumb. - That's so...
- This is a thumb? - Yes.
It says, "Pick me."
I thought he was holding a club.
- Isn't it a fried ginseng? - No.
It isn't.
I thought they were going to get it right.
- We win. - We win.
- We win again. - Okay.
The winning team of Our Drawing Link﻿ is...
Team Se Chan.
(Team Se Chan can take one Ginseng Badge.)
It's simple.
"Wrongful Encounter﻿" was incredible.
While you were enjoying the game, the time limit has passed.
- That's right. - Finally.
(It's been an hour...)
(since Jae Seok transferred the Bomb Sticker to Seok Jin.)
(If you carry the Bomb Sticker for an hour,)
(you automatically get another Venomous Snake Badge.)
(If the Bomb Sticker is still with Seok Jin,)
(he'll get another Venomous Snake Badge.)
The bomb...
has been transferred.
When?
(The Bomb Sticker has been transferred.)
(Seok Jin transferred the bomb...)
(to another person.)
That was so fast.
- What? - What?
(Who is carrying the bomb?)
There was no time to transfer it.
(When Jae Seok transferred the Bomb Sticker to Seok Jin,)
(Seok Jin noticed it right away.)
(Seok Jin knows...)
(Jae Seok transferred the Bomb Sticker to him.)
(Before the mission started,)
(Seok Jin took action.)
(He transferred the bomb onto Kwang Soo's shoe.)
(You'll never figure it out.)
(As Seok Jin expected, Kwang Soo has no idea.)
- So fast? - The new person...
has an hour from now.
It's been transferred?
If the Bomb Sticker is not transferred within an hour,
the person will get another Venomous Snake Badge.
(If Kwang Soo fails, he'll get another Venomous Snake Badge.)
I have to find it.
(Will he be able to transfer the Bomb Sticker within an hour?)
(The time limit for Kwang Soo)
- Are we having lunch? - I'm hungry.
I laughed so much before we got on the bus.
- "You're not stupid!" - "You're not stupid!"
Who was she talking to?
Kwang Soo.
(What happened?)
(They were on their way to the next mission.)
You're not stupid!
"You're not stupid!"
Without realizing it,
I said, "Thank you!"
"You're not stupid!"
Why would she say such an obvious thing?
(Kwang Soo was touched by the female fan.)
(They start looking for the Bomb Sticker again.)
I don't have it.
Who has it?
It's been transferred.
Where could it be?
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo. You won't be able to find it.)
- I want to know. - We can't see our backs.
- We can't ask others either. - Someone must be feeling nervous.
If the cameras are off...
and you don't film it with your phone...
It has to be filmed.
You have to film it with your phone at least.
It has to be filmed?
(Seok Jin suddenly asks a question.)
- It has to air. - Why?
Are you worried?
You didn't film it?
Well...
Don't think I did it.
Why are you so upset?
You should at least tell the producer.
- Right. - If...
Let's say it wasn't filmed. Do we have to retrieve the bomb?
Are you in that situation right now?
(Jae Seok teases Seok Jin.)
- Let's just assume that. - I'm sure it was filmed.
- You can see it if you zoom in. - Were there no cameras at all?
- What? - Were there no cameras at all?
Don't think I did it.
If the person...
It's too late now.
Who did you give it to and when?
Say, "If a friend of mine..."
If the person...
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
As long as the result is filmed, it'll be fine.
And you have to tell the staff.
- Of course. - You have to tell the staff.
"I transferred it."
I'm sure that friend told the staff.
- Did you? - I'm sure he did.
A friend of yours?
- I mean... - Your friend did it?
a friend of mine that I'm as close to as myself.
(He confesses.)
(Seok Jin's best friend is Seok Jin.)
- A close friend of yours? - Yes.
Where could it be?
Mouth Like Mount Baekdu was so funny.
Mouth Like Mount Baekdu and Mount Halla.
So Min sure is a poet.
It was amazing.
I didn't mean to see it, but...
(Did So Min see anything?)
I saw Seok Jin's phone.
- Be quiet. - What happened?
- Be quiet. - He was messaging...
Running Man Producer Jung Chul Min.
- Be quiet. - You just messaged him, right?
- I didn't. - You did.
Be quiet.
(He clenches his teeth.)
Seriously.
- What are you doing? - Please make it fun.
Please don't get caught.
I'm sorry to say this,
but just because your sight is dim...
doesn't mean that no one can see your phone.
It's just that your sight is dim.
- I saw it so clearly. - We all can see it clearly.
I couldn't help but see it.
Hide your phone more properly.
Seok Jin must have transferred the bomb...
to someone he thinks is easy.
Who could that be?
(Will Kwang Soo be able to find the bomb?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(They arrive at a restaurant with a nice view.)
Is it indoors?
Let me look in the mirror.
I want to go to the bathroom.
(Do I have the Bomb Sticker?)
Where could it be?
- Kwang Saeng. - Yam Saeng.
Yam Saeng. Kwang Saeng.
Nam Saeng.
Kwang Soo is suspicious of something.
- The time limit has passed again. - Again?
(The time limit has passed.)
- Again? - Already?
The Bomb Sticker has not been...
- transferred yet. - What?
- The person doesn't know? - The person doesn't know.
That person gets another Venomous Snake Badge in secret.
- What? - How can we not know?
That's absurd.
I can't understand it.
Anyway, I've just texted the person.
- You did? - Yes.
(The person with the bomb has been informed.)
(Everyone checks his or her phone anxiously.)
An hour has passed already?
(The person with the bomb has been informed.)
(Everyone checks his or her phone anxiously.)
An hour has passed already?
You better keep it secret...
if you want to transfer the bomb to another person.
(Kwang Soo's lips twitch.)
That person knows it now, right?
(Staring)
What's wrong with your lips?
- What's wrong? - What's wrong?
- What happened to your lips? - What happened?
- Is it you? - No.
If that person fails to find the Bomb Sticker within an hour,
he or she will get another Venomous Snake Badge.
(The producer tries hard not to laugh.)
Check the soles of your feet.
(Haha talks to Kwang Soo.)
What's wrong?
Can I use the bathroom?
(Let me look for the bomb.)
What's wrong?
- We're shooting. - Why?
- All right. - Okay.
You should focus on the shooting.
Focus.
I guess someone will have difficulty focusing.
In this mission, you'll compete...
for the badge exchange rights and a meal.
It's called Mystery Seller.
- What's that? - Let's eat.
Without knowing what's in the box,
one team will describe the item for three minutes.
The other team can see the item...
and ask the sellers questions about the item freely.
The staff will determine how well the sellers described the item.
The team with the highest score wins.
That sounds fun.
It's just like home shopping channels.
For example, you may ask,
"When do you give this as a present?"
- Okay. - It's going to be fun.
Kwang Soo, will you focus? What's wrong with you?
- Are you okay? - He wasn't focusing?
- Is something wrong? - No.
- Come on! - No, it's nothing.
- You need to focus! - Why aren't you getting along?
Get yourself together!
May I continue, Kwang Soo?
- Yes, I'm sorry. - May I continue?
Then please get into teams of two.
- Should we choose with the spoons? - Let's do that.
- Yes, that's the best way. - The spoons will be good.
(Team Results)
Now, we will reveal it.
- You two can't see it. - Okay.
Only we can.
(The mystery item is revealed.)
(Which item will they have to describe without knowing?)
What will it be?
That's hard.
(Enema)
(This won't be easy!)
- That? - That's hard.
Well, everyone, this item is something I don't...
- usually bring to the show. - Yes.
- I finally brought it to you. - It's something...
- we held back on. - It's that very item!
Why did you hold it back?
Well, it's great for newlyweds!
(Well, it's great for newlyweds!)
- It's so amazing. - "Newlyweds"?
- Yes, newlyweds. - Did you use this then?
We always had this at our house when we were newlyweds.
- Seok Jin! - Really?
This will make you love each other.
- With this? - For example,
if you have a fight with your wife...
It can happen, there can be tension...
- during the early years. - He's right, though.
Whenever I saw this,
I couldn't help but smile.
- Really? - Why?
- It made me so happy. - You feel refreshed?
It's one of my three favorite things.
When was the last time you used it?
- This? - When did you use it?
I used it with my child.
- With your child? - I used it with my child.
- When's the best time to use it? - What?
- When's the best time? - My child used it in the morning.
He...
was bored.
He can overcome his puberty with this.
That's possible.
- It makes people happy. - Yes.
If you don't know this,
then you don't know the happiness of life.
- Yes. - That's right.
I would even survive a deserted island...
with just this.
(I would even survive a deserted island with just this!)
- What? - Just this.
- You only need this to survive? - To be honest,
- this is all I need to survive. - Okay.
I don't need anything else.
I think I could last for three years...
only eating stew made out of this.
- Stew? - Really?
Stew made out of this?
- I love stew so much. - Why would you make stew?
Are you sure you can eat this?
I don't think you can.
(I don't think you can.)
- Nothing's inedible in this world. - Could you recommend it?
How did you feel when you first used it?
- For me... - Yes?
- How did you feel? - Be honest.
- We don't need to hide it anymore. - Right.
- If I have a child in the future, - Yes?
(If a Kwang Soo Junior were to be born...)
(as the result of love in the far future...)
I'd like to name it...
(The child's name.)
I'm thinking about naming it...
(His child's name will be Lee Enema.)
after this, for real.
- This is too much. - No way.
(He explained his first impressions with a tragedy for his child.)
Could you strongly recommend it one last time?
To those of you who are lonely,
to those of you who had a nightmare,
- if you kiss this in the morning, - Yes.
you will be very happy.
Also, to married couples who don't have a great relationship,
- Please don't. - or...
- That's too... - Please...
Families who haven't been talking too much lately.
- Yes. - If you're feeling awkward,
- You really will have a lot to say. - Right.
- You can give this as a present, - A present?
the negative tensions will melt away like snow.
- That was a good pitch. - Okay.
We will end the presentation.
Please check your item.
(Enema)
Your child's name will be Lee Enema.
(Your child's name will be Lee Enema.)
- You kiss it in the morning? - Every morning.
"I would even survive a deserted island with just this."
- I gave you points for that. - Okay.
"We always had this when we were newlyweds."
How about the name?
"I'd like to name it after this." Yes.
- You have to name it that. - Lee Enema.
(Lee Enema)
- Lee Enema. - Lee Enema.
I gave you points for that.
- Let's go. - Now should we give it a go?
Please change the item.
You get points if you're specific.
- You have to be detailed. - Here you go.
- All right. - 1, 2, 3!
(The mystery item is revealed.)
Ta-da! Surprise!
(They have to explain the item without knowing what it is.)
(What is the item they will have to sell?)
(Dog food)
(That won't be easy, either!)
If you don't know this...
- If you don't know this, - Yes.
- there's no point in living. - That's right.
You'll regret later if you have to miss this chance.
- I think... - Do you like this?
- What? - Do you like this?
I'm crazy for it.
(I'm crazy for dog food.)
(News Flash, Yu Jae Seok is crazy for dog food.)
- You're crazy for it? - I...
- If it weren't for the show, - Yes?
I would even go further than that.
I go nuts for it.
- When do you go nuts for it? - Sorry?
- Well, when I'm going to bed, - Going to bed?
my eyes get wide open because of this.
- Really? - Yes.
When did you first get to know this?
I guess it was when I was in elementary school.
- Really? - Since elementary school?
- Yes. - Since back then?
- It's been so long. - Yes.
For those of you who have cold hands and feet,
- this is good for you. - For cold hands and feet?
Yes, when they're cold.
Everyone, do you know why I'm so fertile?
(Do you know why I'm so fertile?)
It's because of that?
(His secret to fertility has finally been revealed.)
- That? - It's all thanks to this.
- That? - Sure.
- You had your second child, too. - We have a total...
- of five children. - Yes.
(They have a total of five children.)
- We have a total of five children. - That's so funny.
- That was your secret? - It's this.
That's so scary.
My wife and mother-in-law are always so busy hiding this.
That's how great this is.
- This is... - I'm always asking for this,
so they're always afraid.
This is a method...
- that isn't widely known yet. - It's a secret.
That's amazing.
It's been passed on for generation to generation in my family.
- My ancestors have used this, too. - That's right.
- Your ancestors? - Yes.
- Your ancestors, too? - Why didn't you let me in on this?
That's why you shouldn't hesitate now.
There's only a limited amount.
How was it when you first tasted it?
How should I put it?
It can be kind of bitter at first.
But there's a sweetness to it the more you chew.
- I kept telling you. - You really tasted it.
I won't sell you anything that I haven't tried.
What's the best way to eat it?
You can just shovel it down,
- Or mix it with water. - or mix it with water.
You can put it on rice or sprinkle it in your stew.
(You can put it on rice or sprinkle it in your stew.)
- Sprinkle it in your stew. - Yes.
- It tastes heavenly. - Sprinkle it in your stew.
- You can have it in any way. - You can make rice balls, too.
(Their sales have come to an end.)
- It all made sense, though. - It did.
- It was right. - Jae Seok is a true fan.
- Please check your item. - I'm a big fan.
It seemed so real.
You put it on rice...
and sprinkle it in your stew?
And in your gimbap?
- It's good. - It all made sense.
It was funny when you said your wife hid it...
because you were crazy for it.
You're unbelievable, Haha.
- This team got a lot of points. - Did we?
"The secret to being fertile is dog food."
- I said that. - He said that.
- Both of us. - "My wife and mother-in-law..."
"are always so busy hiding this."
"It can be kind of bitter at first,"
- "but there's a sweetness to it." - Right.
You can't put it like this unless you've really tried it.
- He's tried it. - I've tried it.
Why don't Ji Hyo and Jong Kook go next?
- Okay. - Sure.
It was dog food.
- It was so funny. - It made sense.
- I thought they saw the word. - It all made sense somehow.
Me, too. I thought they knew it.
We didn't know.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's mystery item is revealed.)
(What is the item the ace team will have to sell?)
(Diaper)
This is...
It's a new item.
(That's a difficult one.)
What kind of product is this?
It's cool, isn't it?
Many people are concerned about their weight, right?
I use this a lot...
when I work out.
(I use this a lot when I work out.)
- Is that true? - Yes.
(Shocking news, "I put a diaper on when I'm exercising.")
I used this too when I was on a diet,
because he recommended it.
- Really? - Amazing!
It's good for people who want to gain muscle mass...
and also for those who want to lose weight.
- You will build a great body. - Really?
- You need this in the summer. - The results are great.
I'm sure there are downsides. What are they?
Well, if you stop in the middle of using this,
(Looking odd)
it may get difficult.
What was that?
If you stop in the middle of using this...
(Twisting her body)
(It may get difficult.)
I think she knows what it is!
What was that face?
She's explaining it with her face.
(If you stop using it,)
(it may get difficult.)
You could practically be a model for that product.
What do you think of men who use this?
They're sexy.
(Men who use this are sexy.)
- To whom would you recommend this? - Well...
- Who would look good in this? - Is there anyone?
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo would look good. - Yes.
If Kwang Soo wears this,
(I would look good in a diaper?)
her girlfriend might get anxious.
- But this... - If he wears this?
- She'd get anxious? - Sure she would.
- His girlfriend would get anxious. - Of course.
She'd get anxious if he wears this?
- For Seok Jin, - Yes?
you can wear it on your head for parties.
- Wear it on his head? - Yes.
He can wear it on his head.
- On my head? - Yes.
- At parties? - You will stand out.
- You'll be popular. - They're right.
- Sure. - It all makes sense.
What do you think about men who wear this to parties?
I'm going to date that man.
(Okay! I'll wear it to parties.)
- That man? - That man.
- It's very neat of him. - Will you share it with him?
Share it?
- Sure. - Will you really share it?
- Of course. That's possible. - Of course.
- Sure, why not? - I'll help him put it on nicely.
You will?
(Ji Hyo doesn't hesitate to reveal her odd tastes.)
Are you serious?
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's sales come to an end.)
- I highly recommend it. - Ji Hyo...
- She's quite bold. - was very fierce.
She was.
- She must know what this is. - Yes.
- You two were on point. - What is it?
- You may look. - Go on.
You may look inside.
(It is time to check the mystery item.)
(They turn their faces away.)
- You use it when you work out. - Why do you use it?
I use it because working out can be hard.
- You wear it and work out. - That's right.
- I might wet my pants. - Ji Hyo, you have to date...
a man in a diaper if you meet him at a party.
- This team scored many points. - Really?
Using it for workouts, using it after Jong Kook's recommendation...
Those comments scored a point.
She also made a sexy face and said it can be hard to stop using it.
That's right. That's right.
She said a man who wears this is sexy.
Kwang Soo looks good in it,
but his girlfriend becomes anxious when he wears it.
Of course she would become anxious.
- She would become anxious. - "Isn't he too young for this?"
- She would become anxious. - It's understandable.
Next come Se Chan and So Min.
- Love your colleagues and country. - Love your colleagues and country.
- Let's see the item. - I will open it.
In 1, 2, 3.
(The mystery item is revealed.)
(Which item will the youngest members describe?)
(A pair of handcuffs)
(It's an intense item.)
- It's expensive. - All right.
When you feel lonely and want to flirt with someone,
- please use this item. - When you are struggling,
- use this item. - Yes.
When should we use this item in a relationship?
I usually use it for the first meeting...
or...
- The first meeting? - Yes.
- I use it before the first meeting. - That's right.
- Before the first meeting? - Yes. When I do that,
- you know, women... - Do women love it?
Women love it.
"Gosh, did you use this?"
I always use this.
- Really? - Me, too.
- In a relationship? - I would die without it.
You always use it in a relationship.
When did you use it for the first time?
I used it for the 1st time in 3rd grade.
- Really? That's early. - Yes.
When did you start using it?
I started using it as an adult at the age of 20.
She is serious.
- She is serious. - She is serious.
- So Min is serious. - What is it?
I used it for the 1st time in 3rd grade.
- In third grade? - Yes.
- Some people are scared of it. - Yes.
What would you like to say to them?
- People are scared of it? - Some people are scared of it.
They should cover their eyes and use it.
- They should cover their eyes? - They should turn off the light.
- They should turn off the light? - They should turn off the light?
You saw the item, right?
(She must be serious.)
- You saw the item, right? - No!
- You saw the item, right? - Turn off the light.
When you turn off the light, it feels like a special event.
(He says anything that comes to mind.)
- This can't air. - It feels like a special event.
What? Why? What is the item?
- What is the item? - What is the item?
I don't know what it is.
- I don't know what it is. - You saw it, right?
Let's check the item and change it.
- What is the item? - It's a pair of handcuffs.
(Startled)
I told you.
(Please forget everything I said.)
- This is insane. - There is no hope for So Min.
- Seriously. - There is no hope for So Min.
I really didn't know.
- There is no hope for So Min. - I really didn't know.
How did you get that kind of an item?
- We got a pair of handcuffs. - Seriously.
- I will reveal the item. - Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
(What will be the new item for the youngest members?)
All right.
(Princess doll)
[VIU Ver] SBS E456 Running Man
"Knowing Your Place Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
We will sell an item men and women of all ages can enjoy.
Isn't it nice? You should use it, Jong Kook.
I wouldn't say...
- it suits me. - Use it after a workout.
If Jong Kook buys this, he will get married.
- Should I carry it around? - Yes.
- If I carry it around... - It will be like a good luck charm.
It does suit Jong Kook...
- a bit. - It does suit him.
Why don't you tell us...
when each of us should use it?
In which situation should we use it?
- Kwang Soo should use it... - He should use it when he is drunk.
He should use it when he is drunk.
It will be nice.
- It suits him very well. - It really does.
That makes sense.
When should I use it?
Use it when you are lonely at night.
(Jae Seok should use it when he is lonely at night.)
You saw the item, right?
- Don't be like that. - I didn't see it.
- For goodness' sake. - I am serious.
It's true!
I didn't see it.
What are you playing at?
I am not...
Jae Seok looks like he got caught.
What are you playing at?
- His face turned red. - Are you crazy?
- How about Haha? - When he wants the fourth child.
He should use it when he wants the fourth child.
You must know something.
- Seriously. - How about Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo should use it soon.
- Use it before you meet someone. - Soon.
- Use it soon. - Use it before you meet a crush.
- Then sparks will fly. - Then you will date him.
You will date him right away.
Before you go to bed, set it on fire and burn it.
(So Min's recommended use of the princess doll)
(Shocked)
- Then you will have... - It's so scary!
It's so scary.
- Go on. - It's a good use.
If you set it on fire and burn it before you go to bed,
- you will have a good dream. - It's so scary.
- Use a torch, not a lighter. - Burn it up.
- A torch? - That's right.
- A torch? - Then it will burn better.
When do you use it?
To be honest, I use it often at night.
- Why? - Why?
I get lonely at night.
(He is sentimental and crazy.)
- I get lonely at night. - My goodness.
- I use it on a trip. - You use it on a trip.
I use it when the scenery is nice.
- Then I feel... - I recommend it.
- All right. Check the item. - Check the item.
- Let's see it. - What is it?
What did I say?
(Incredulous)
(It shouldn't be burned.)
This team won points for comments about burning the item...
- for a good dream. - It was really scary.
- It was really scary. - Seriously.
They also won points for using it for a lonely night.
On the first place is...
Team Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
- That's right. - They deserve it.
On the second place is Team Jae Seok and Haha.
(2nd place, Team Jae Seok and Haha)
- I guess we came in last. - That's impossible.
You came in last. On the third place is Team Seok Jin and Kwang Soo.
- Thank goodness. - The members of the winning team...
can either take someone's Ginseng Badges...
or give away your Venomous Snake Badges.
When the two of them team up...
- They are invincible. - Seriously.
You have a Venomous Snake Badge. Let's see who doesn't have it.
- Give one to Seok Jin. - What?
- Seok Jin doesn't have one. - No, he doesn't.
- He doesn't have one. - You are right.
At this rate, he will be an English gentleman.
- Seriously. - King of consideration, my foot.
- You are right. - You must stop him.
I will give you a Venomous Snake Badge.
For goodness' sake.
Okay. I hold grudges.
- To whom will you give the badge? - Seok Jin.
- Good job. - Don't do that.
I will give it to Seok Jin.
He picks on me so much.
- That's right. - From the team that placed second,
- only one member has a chance. - I'll give a Venomous Snake Badge.
Jae Seok has too many.
That's right., I have too many Venomous Snake Badges.
That's right. Haha has a lot of Ginseng Badges.
- How about Kwang Soo? - I got two just now.
He doesn't have many.
He doesn't have many Venomous Snake Badges.
Hold on.
I will be getting a Venomous Snake Badge.
- What? - He doesn't have many.
Why does he have such a few Venomous Snake Badges?
Another hour has passed.
- What? - For goodness' sake!
(It's past the time again.)
(Kwang Soo spent 2 hours without transferring the bomb.)
The Bomb Sticker hasn't been transferred.
For goodness' sake.
Did you plant it in my body?
(Kwang Soo, look carefully.)
I will give one to So Min.
- Me? - Okay.
(Jae Seok gives So Min a Venomous Snake Badge.)
(Mystery Seller ends without finding Kwang Soo's bomb.)
- My goodness. - Everything looks delicious.
Everything looks delicious.
This is the best meal.
- Everything looks delicious. - Gosh, this is...
(The 1st and 2nd places are happy. The 3rd and 4th places are envious.)
Gosh, he is slurping the noodles.
- My goodness. - He is slurping the noodles.
I will eat jeonbyeong.
Let's eat cleanly.
- That's right. - Give us some food.
Why don't you share the noodles?
I don't think I can do that.
I will make a tempting offer.
- What is it? - I will get a Venomous Snake Badge.
- Really? - Yes.
- Venomous Snake Badge? - I swear upon it.
Se Chan, I will give you a bite of makguksu...
and a dumpling. Will you take my badge?
Of course.
One Venomous Snake Badge won't make a difference.
Okay.
I will give you jeonbyeong, too.
Thank you.
(He gets a Venomous Snake Badge for delicious lunch.)
You can't give it back to me.
Don't worry, Ji Hyo.
Did you find the bomb?
No.
(It's been over 2 hours.)
Search inside your ears.
- Solar plexus. - Under your tongue.
(It's not inside my ears.)
Look at the top of your head.
I looked everywhere.
I will give you a Ginseng Badge.
Okay.
- Take it. - Where are you going?
- The restroom. - Where are you going?
The restroom.
(Instead of going to the restroom,)
(Kwang Soo looks at his shoes.)
- Okay. Ginseng Badge. - Okay.
(At that moment,)
(he finds the Bomb Sticker.)
(This is why he couldn't find it on his body.)
(Now, the Bomb Sticker is in Kwang Soo's hand.)
(Now that I have the Bomb Sticker,)
(everyone should be nervous.)
(Kwang Soo will begin to transfer the bomb.)
(Not too long after he found the bomb,)
(Kwang Soo gets up.)
(He comes back and sends a text message.)
(I transferred the Bomb Sticker.)
(Did he already transfer the Bomb Sticker?)
(On whom did he put the Bomb Sticker?)
(With only Kwang Soo knowing who has the Bomb Sticker,)
(they move to the location of the next mission.)
Okay. We have time.
(Why is he whistling?)
- Kwang Soo is whistling. - This is driving me crazy.
(It's proof he doesn't have the Bomb Sticker.)
- Don't make it so obvious. - Everyone does that.
It's similar to how you burp after drinking a soft drink.
It can't be helped.
- Let's check the shoes first. - Shoes.
We should check the insoles, too.
- Where is it? - There is no way...
I put it on your armpit.
(There is no way I put it on your armpit.)
You never know.
The members keep checking their bodies.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
I will give you 50 cents. Tell me who has it now.
I don't want your lousy 50 cents!
(He gets angry.)
Where did you get those 50 cents?
Gosh, I guess the price rose.
Here. I will add 10 cents. It's tempting, right?
Where are these coins coming from?
He seems like a baby octopus sometimes.
The way he behaves?
What? "Baby octopus"?
Is something wrong with his mentality?
"Baby octopus"?
- Why? - He acts like a baby octopus.
I'm not sure,
but he acts like a baby octopus sometimes.
On whom did Kwang Soo put the sticker?
(On whom did Kwang Soo put the sticker?)
(No one knows where the Bomb Sticker is.)
- This is your last mission. - Good.
After the last mission...
Will it be decided?
When I make the final announcement,
the time will be over.
(If you have a bomb, Ginseng Badges turn into Venomous Snake Badges.)
All right.
- The time limit has passed again. - Okay.
The Bomb Sticker has been...
(Kwang Soo had the bomb.)
transferred to someone else.
(The Bomb Sticker has been transferred to someone else.)
(There was a reason why he whistled.)
Now I see why he whistled.
I'm jealous of Kwang Soo.
To the person who has it,
- Will you text us? - I'll send a text message.
We're watching our phones.
(To whom did Kwang Soo transfer the bomb?)
I sent it.
(The message is sent.)
(Which member has the bomb?)
(Smirking)
(She can't hide that she's perplexed.)
Only one person laughed.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
- It must not be me. - It's not me.
The person who has the bomb...
must do something with it before the mission is over.
If you get caught, you get another Venomous Snake Badge.
- Yes. - If you get caught transferring.
Excuse me.
- I'm going to take a shower. - Now?
(A shower all of a sudden?)
I know.
Kwang Soo.
Where did you hide it?
No, no!
(He's really flustered.)
Are you out of your mind?
When did I?
- I mean... - What are you doing?
"When did I?"
Where did you hide it?
(I can't find it anywhere.)
Their acting is...
too extreme.
- You can't find it. - It's too extreme.
You can't find it.
(Where could it be?)
For Knowing Your Place Race,
here's the last mission.
It's Sit or Stand Race of Wits.
It's Race of Wits.
It's Jae Seok's game.
I love Race of Wits.
At the same time,
members decide whether to sit or stand.
The minority of members wins.
(The minority of members wins.)
(It's very simple.)
Winning members...
can take a Ginseng Badge from another member.
Or they can give one Venomous Snake Badge.
You can turn the tables here.
There will be a twist.
If all members sit or stand, or if it's 4 to 4,
there won't be any badge exchange.
(If it's 4 to 4, there's no badge exchange.)
- It will be decided here. - It will be decided.
- It's confusing. - We have many badges.
Focus, So Min.
(Focus, So Min.)
I worked hard to protect.
So Min is very busy.
She can't focus.
- She can't focus on this game. - We'll start.
Choose whether to sit or stand.
- Everyone chooses at the same time. - Okay.
If you stand up late, you're out.
That's right. Here we go.
One.
- Two. - I'll stand up.
Me too.
(If you win, you can take a Ginseng Badge...)
(or give a Venomous Snake Badge.)
Three.
(6 members stand, and 2 members sit.)
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo win.)
I knew it.
Goodness.
(The lover of Game of Wits is disappointed.)
It's best not to move for a game like this.
You fools.
(He pretends not to hear.)
"You're not stupid!"
(Kwang Soo, You're not stupid.)
- "You're not stupid!" - I'm really not.
"You're not stupid!"
I didn't know you would stand up.
Seok Jin and Ji Hyo.
You may give a Venomous Snake Badge or take a Ginseng Badge.
- Right now? - Yes.
You don't need to give to So Min.
Hers will turn into Venomous Snake Badges.
(Hers will turn into Venomous Snake Badges.)
So Min.
- Where is it? - Just imagine...
- Where is it? - So Min's badges...
will turn into Venomous Snake Badges.
You can't win.
If you find the bomb,
- I'll give you two Ginseng Badges. - Really?
(So Min makes a proposal.)
Yes.
So Min.
You can't win.
I'll explain.
(Kwang Soo raises his hand.)
Will you give me two Ginseng Badges?
- I will... - I'll tell you.
I'll give you two Ginseng Badges.
But there's a rule to follow.
So Min.
- Wait. - Yes?
I'll show you that you can win.
(How will he make So Min win?)
How?
Give me your Ginseng Badge.
(Bring me your Ginseng Badge.)
(Why mine?)
- Ginseng. - Ginseng?
- Ginseng? - Give it to me.
Seok Jin is being mischievous.
If So Min finds the bomb,
he makes it impossible for her to attack him.
(That's his trick.)
(Was that it?)
Seok Jin is sometimes...
(Jae Seok is too quick.)
Did you get your turn, Ji Hyo?
Me?
Give me one Ginseng.
(Seok Jin, give me one Ginseng.)
Why are you taking mine?
It doesn't matter, right?
- All right. - Okay.
- That's good. - What?
- What? I also won. - Fine.
(Ji Hyo takes back her Ginseng Badge.)
Nothing has changed for me.
- Here's the next round. - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
Great.
(Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, and So Min win.)
- Nice. - You win if you sit.
You're like my little brother.
- I'll take it from Jae Seok. - Okay.
(Current Badge Status)
So Min has a lot of Venomous Snake Badges.
It's not anywhere.
I can't find it anywhere.
I don't think he put it in here. It's clear.
- Take it off and check. - He didn't have the time.
Here's the last round.
Can we bet two badges this time?
(At that time)
(She finds the bomb inside her cell phone.)
(How did he hide it here?)
(During a break after their meal)
(So Min leaves her cell phone on the table.)
(She leaves without suspecting anything...)
(to brush her teeth.)
(At that time, Kwang Soo finds So Min's cell phone.)
(To leave a proof,)
(he even films it himself.)
(He almost put it inside the case.)
(Dreaming of a perfect crime,)
(he puts the bomb behind the sticker.)
(It's impressive that So Min found it.)
(Kwang Soo doesn't know that So Min found it.)
- Two badges are on the line. - Okay.
One.
(She pretends not to have found it.)
I'll stand up.
(No one noticed.)
Three.
(3 members stand, and 5 sit.)
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and So Min win.)
(How should I transfer the bomb?)
Congratulations.
- I should have stood up. - Seriously.
Let's see.
I'll give one to Seok Jin.
Okay.
Wait.
What's this?
(Something falls on Se Chan's hand.)
- What is it? - Poop fell on me.
What? Poop fell on you?
(Did poop fall on him suddenly?)
Goodness.
Why did poop fall on you?
It was yellow and long.
Even a bird came.
It looks like a different kind of poop.
(Kwang Soo goes to check.)
(This is a chance.)
What is it?
(She's about to take out the bomb from her bag.)
- Gosh! - What is it?
(She fails because he turned too quickly.)
Something just fell on me.
I'll give one to Kwang Soo.
- Did you give 2? - No, only 1.
You should give out yours.
There are six.
Be honest. If you tell me, I won't give it to you.
(She continues to act.)
- You won't find it. - Goodness.
It's your last chance. I won't give if you tell me.
(Kwang Soo approaches her.)
Listen. On page 23 of the book.
Stop kidding. Tell me just once.
Then I won't give it to you.
(Try to find it.)
Where?
- You will give me one? - Yes.
Fine.
(She couldn't stick the bomb.)
Everyone, I have no Venomous Snake Badge.
I have more Venomous Snake Badges.
(She doesn't have time.)
Let's play one more round.
(If it's not easy to stick it on Kwang Soo...)
(Will she change her target?)
(Haha is showing his back to So Min.)
(She's ready to load her bomb.)
- Last. - How many times will we play?
It's over.
(So Min stands behind Haha as naturally as possible.)
(If So Min secretly sticks it on Haha...)
For the member who has the Bomb Sticker,
all of his or her badges will turn into Venomous Snake Badges.
(Carefully)
(She tries to put the Bomb Sticker on him.)
(Will So Min successfully transfer the bomb?)
What?
(What was that?)
(You startled me.)
(What's going on?)
(He finds something on the ground.)
I caught her trying to stick it on me.
(Look at this.)
- No. - Look.
(I'm doomed.)
- No. - I was right here.
- Don't deny it. - That's not it.
- I even helped her. - Did you find it?
She approached me.
When I turned around, it was on the ground.
How could you?
How did you find it?
Something was strange.
- I didn't put it on you. - Wasn't it strange?
When did you find it?
I found it a while ago.
- It was behind my sticker... - That was almost...
I put it inside the sticker.
(She tries to stick it on again.)
She stuck it on me again.
No.
She did.
She stuck it on me. I can feel it.
Can you feel it?
- She got caught twice. - I put it very lightly.
- She has many Venomous Snakes. - Can you feel it?
Yes.
Everyone will say the last comment.
So Min, try to transfer it without getting caught.
Let's start.
- Say your last comment. - What do we do?
I have two Venomous Snake Badges.
- Ji Hyo. - I have three Ginseng Badges.
I have 3 Ginseng and 2 Venomous Snake Badges.
- Seok Jin... - She's coming.
(They stay away from So Min.)
If she gets caught, she gets another badge.
I have 1 Ginseng and 4 Venomous Snake Badges.
I have...
I can't stick it on.
This is not how we play it.
(She lets out an outcry.)
(How can you do this?)
Get away.
I have three Ginseng Badges.
I have five Venomous Snake Badges.
(He's full of confidence.)
(Approaching)
(She tries to stick the bomb on Seok Jin.)
(Didn't Seok Jin notice at all?)
- So Min stuck it on here. - No.
(He was waiting for it.)
- Here it is. - She got caught.
- No. - Give her one more.
I could feel it. Give her one more.
No.
- I could feel it. - How could you know?
I felt it.
I thought he'd pretend not to know.
How could he...
I was hoping that she'd stick it on me.
- She stuck it on my clothes. - On your clothes?
On my clothes.
Let's finish up.
It'll be all over after So Min's ending comment.
I have 5 Venomous Snake Badges and 2 Ginseng Badges.
(So Min's badge status)
Her Ginseng Badges will change.
- Okay. - Today...
- Isn't it valid on the bag? - She stuck it on the bag.
(Wait a minute.)
(Did she stick the Bomb Sticker on the bag?)
(Before So Min made her ending comment,)
(she put the Bomb Sticker...)
(on someone's bag behind a stool.)
- Whose bag is it? - She stuck it on the bag.
(To whom does the bag belong?)
Whose bag is it?
- Who sat on the fourth stool? - Who was it?
(Whose bag is it?)
Isn't it Ji Hyo's?
- It's Ji Hyo's. - Mine was the third.
(The bag belongs to Ji Hyo.)
It's Ji Hyo's.
(Is it me?)
- It's Ji Hyo. - It is.
- Ji Hyo. - It's your bag, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
- Look. - It's Ji Hyo's bag.
How...
This is a twist.
Is it Ji Hyo's bag?
I put it on a random bag.
Ji Hyo has three Ginseng, but she got the bomb.
- 3 Venomous Snake Badges. - She has 3 Venomous Snake Badges.
(All three Ginseng Badges turn into Venomous Snake Badges.)
(Ji Hyo's final badge status is three Venomous Snake Badges.)
She transferred it at the last moment.
I didn't know that it was yours.
I had no idea.
You got tricked because you let down your guard.
Goodness.
(All of Ji Hyo's nicknames become negative.)
Jae Seok, the winner,
can pick a nickname for each member.
I'll pick Song Van for Ji Hyo.
Ms. 40, Song Van.
Not Close Friends with Kwang Soo.
(Ms 40, Song Van, and Not Close Friends with Kwang Soo)
One of them should be Cherished Comedian.
Add Be As Tall as 3m.
What if I get as tall as 3m?
Unloved Frog.
- Unloved Frog is cute. - Yes.
(Crazy Poet, Really Foolish, and Unloved Frog)
- Romantic Punch. - That's a good one.
- Yes, Romantic Punch. - Romantic Punch?
(Romantic Punch)
Add Sycophant and Petty Greedy.
(Jee Stream, Sycophant, and Petty Greedy)
I'll pick Young Jin's Imitator.
Come on.
(Young Jin is Haha's stylist.)
- I'll pick these 2 and 1. - Okay.
I like Mouth Like Mount Baekdu.
I'll include Mouth Like Mount Baekdu.
(Playful Child, Mouth Like Mount Baekdu, and Kind and Cool Man)
Se Chan is And Se Chan.
- Why? - "And Se Chan"?
Is it just my name?
(Se Chan's is "And Se Chan".)
Isn't that a worse punishment?
- It is funny. - Right.
Se Chan's nickname is funny.
The audience will say, "And Se Chan".
(Thousands of people will shout out his name.)
(He likes it as he hears it.)
It's done.
The nicknames for the lyrics have been picked.
- We'll discuss and make a song. - Then...
- we're leaving. - Where?
- See you tomorrow. - See you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow. - We have work tomorrow.
- We'll see each other tomorrow. - Right.