- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Good morning. - Hello.
"Morning"? It's 1pm now.
- Hello. - Come on.
What is it? Why?
He just said, "good morning".
- It must be morning for him. - Hello.
- It's 1pm right now. - That's right. It's 1pm.
It's 1pm. It's the same for me.
- What's the same? - Whether it's 1pm or 9pm.
What's the same?
My mood is the same.
- Is that what you meant? - I feel the same.
- You're always in a bad mood. - No, I'm good.
You're always in a bad mood.
We started even before we lined up.
- I'm always in a good mood. - Seok Jin.
- It's awful these days. - I always feel good.
- He gets angrier and more annoying. - No.
- But he doesn't know that. - Hey.
- He doesn't know he gets like that. - No. What would I gain from it?
- See? You're angry now. - No, no.
- You aren't angry? - I'm smiling.
(He's smiling to make a living.)
- He has anger management issue. - No, no. Not at all.
- Does he have menopause? - He has anger management issue.
- No, no. Not at all. - But you know what?
He's my junior comedian, but he acts really cheeky with me.
- Come on. - You should teach him a lesson.
- Hey, are you serious? - You should scold him once.
- I'll hold him for you. - Jong Kook said...
- Did you hear what he just said? - What?
He said I should scold you.
- You should scold him. - What?
- Scold me? - A junior can't be that rude.
- My goodness! - He must have boundaries.
- He hates when juniors overstep. - Right.
- There has to be a fixed system. - What about you?
Why are you rude to me?
- Me? I was never rude to you. - Why are you rude to me?
- What are you talking about? - Why do I always gather my hands...
in front of you?
He stuttered. He just stuttered.
- Why am I acting small? - I was never rude to you.
- Why? - I was always nice to you.
- Goodness, I don't know why. - That's funny.
- That was funny. By the way, - That's enough.
Se Chan, did you see the show? So Min...
- has a wish. - Okay.
She wants two guys to fight over her.
She wants a family to fall apart because of her.
(So Min, choose. Is it Se Chan or Se Hyeong?)
These brothers will...
(You'll create a rift between two brothers.)
(Do you know what my wish is?)
(It's to be in a love triangle.)
(My wish is breaking apart a family.)
(So Min is a destroyer of siblings, the promising femme fatal.)
- Hey, don't get my family involved. - She wants brothers to fight.
Don't you see that in dramas?
Se Hyeong told me about that after he finished filming.
- Didn't he say it was hard? - "Hey, So Min is really crazy."
(Her reputation stays true.)
"I can't handle her." He told me that.
Jae Seok. Jae Seok. I'll tell you something funny.
- Last week, So Min... - Why are we talking about this?
- called Jong Kook herself. - Really?
- She asked him out for coffee. - Really?
(So Min Calls Jong Kook in Private for Coffee)
- So what happened? - They've gotten close lately.
- Why did you do that? - Why did you do it?
Why? Why? Why did you two have coffee all of a sudden?
- Why did you do it? - That was crazy.
- We're close now. - You are?
- We're close. - Just the two of you met?
- No, of course, not. - I was alone when it snowed.
I had no one to meet up with.
I always meet up with the same people.
(She means them.)
I wanted to hang out with someone new.
I thought that Jong Kook was relatively new to me.
I asked him to hang out with me in a text.
Jong Kook wrote, "All of a sudden"? But he said yes right away...
and told me to come to this address, so I went.
(She went to the address Jong Kook sent her.)
- There were three handsome guys. - Right away?
- Those guys were there? - It was already set up.
My gosh, So Min.
- And one more man was rushing over. - Let's hear this out.
- Who? - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Why did you go there?
- He ruined everything. - Everything was ruined.
- Everything was ruined. - It was all ruined.
I'm not sure if I should say this on TV.
Jong Kook said it was uncomfortable to meet her alone.
(Jong Kook said it was uncomfortable to meet her alone.)
He told me not to say this, so I wasn't going to say this.
- "So Min suddenly wants to meet." - But still.
- You were uncomfortable. - He begged me to join him.
He used the word, "please".
As soon as So Min texted me,
I called every guy I knew.
You made an effort though.
By the way, every female member...
has become Jong Kook's love interest now.
(He has potentials to date every female member.)
- Look at this. - What are you talking about?
He looks like a playboy.
- Look. - He's a playboy.
(In other words, he's like a playboy.)
- What are you saying? Playboy? - I mean...
My goodness, I feel bad for you, Ji Hyo.
- I feel bad for you, Ji Hyo. - You were with Ji Hyo last week.
- I see them as my family. - Poor you.
I thought So Min would take that title, but I guess I was wrong.
(The playboy character belonged to someone else.)
It was Jong Kook who took it.
He's not the playboy. He's Flirty Kook.
- Flirty Kook? - Flirty Kook.
- He's Flirty Kook. - Listen. Seriously.
- That's not it. - That's funny.
- Sister-in-law. - Brother-in-law.
- Let's go. - Cross!
(All of a sudden, the sister-in-law and the brother-in-law cross.)
- What was that? - "Brother-in-law"?
- Hey. - Look at you.
- "Brother-in-law." - That came out of nowhere.
(Is she finally admitting the relationship?)
She's not happy that she might lose Jong Kook to So Min.
Ji Hyo doesn't want to have him, but doesn't want to give him away.
He called her honey last week.
- He did call me that. - He practically proposed to her.
- He's already her brother-in-law? - I didn't know it moved that fast.
- Hey, you. - That startled me.
- What is this? - Look at you joking around.
(What was that?)
- Hey, you. - That startled me.
(What is this mysterious video on the screen?)
- What is that? - What is it?
Starting now...
(What is this mysterious voice that's talking to the members?)
(Look at you joking around.)
Starting now, I will...
make you extremely nervous as a gift from me to you.
I am a honeybee who came to...
bring you to judgment.
(I am a honeybee who came to bring you to judgment.)
I'm a honeybee.
He's cute. What is this?
He's cute.
- Isn't he trying to copy Jigsaw? - He's cute.
- He's Jigsaw. - He does resemble the character.
- What is he doing? - He looks so cute.
He's cute. What is this?
The first member whom I'll bring to judgment is...
Kim Jong Kook.
(It's Kim Jong Kook.)
- Why? Why? - Who?
- Why him? - It's Kim Jong Kook.
(The first target of the honeybee's judgment is Kim Jong Kook.)
(Why will he be brought to justice?)
Regardless of their age, you dominate them by force.
- That came out of the blue. - That's right.
- All of a sudden? - You terrorize the members...
- with scary comments. - That's true.
I will let you take revenge by giving you a chance...
to eliminate him right away.
I will let you take revenge...
(I will give you a chance to eliminate him right away.)
He'll be eliminated right away?
- Hey. - What?
- We can eliminate him now? - What?
Why would you do that to me?
The method is very simple.
We will have a secret ballot to see if you agree or not.
- If the majority agrees, - No way.
- What is this? - Jong Kook will be eliminated.
However, in order to vote, you need ballots.
If you complete the group mission...
- within your given chances, - Really?
everyone will be given a ballot.
If you fail,
only seven ballots will be given out.
One of them will lose his or her right to vote.
- What is this? - If Jong Kook is eliminated,
one of the members who agreed and members...
who didn't have the voting right will be chosen.
If Jong Kook survives the voting, the next target...
will be chosen by Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook will choose the next target if he survives.)
- Is that so? - My goodness.
- Hold on. - It won't be just Jong Kook.
- We must think carefully. - Goodness.
(If they eliminate Jong Kook, they might be the next target.)
We have to use our brain for this.
Hey, we have to play this right.
By the way, that honeybee...
didn't make groundless accusations.
- Hold on. - To tell you the truth...
It was all correct.
- Right. - The honeybee only spoke the truth.
- Well... - The honeybee wasn't lying.
(The honeybee's report on Jong Kook)
(Hammering)
(Regardless of age, he uses his muscles to dominate over others.)
(If someone is bothersome, he takes them to a blind spot.)
(He shows off his power on a variety show.)
(He makes the show about rescuing the members.)
(The first target is Kim Jong Kook.)
I can already be eliminated?
Already? I get that you'll vote.
There's no reason to eliminate him though.
Yes, why would we eliminate him?
(Look at his facial expression.)
(Who would want to eliminate my dear Jong Kook?)
(He's speechless.)
You'll vote yes, right?
- You'll vote yes, right? - My goodness.
- Right? - You'll vote.
- Won't you vote? - Are you getting things going?
- Look at his face. - He's already...
- setting it up. - Hey.
We can eliminate him from the start?
We didn't finish the opening segment, but he'll go to jail?
(What a lucky day it is!)
(The actor of 10 years is putting on his best show.)
- How could you do this to him? - He's setting it up now.
Why would we want to eliminate him?
I hate that look when he tries to look innocent.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
What an awful honeybee!
Don't you dare test our loyalty!
Hey, let me make myself clear.
If you eliminate him, I won't let you slide.
You.
- I meant it. - Jae Seok.
The corners of your mouth are moving upward.
- He's very playful. - You're smiling.
- You know me, right? - What?
If I catch you, I won't let that slide.
- He's acting weird. - I won't let that slide.
Jong Kook, just trust me.
All right. Today, we have received a request from the honeybee.
And we have prepared Honeybee's Counterattack Race.
- What is this? - Honeybee?
You must get to the bottom of this race's secret.
The moment you eliminate the honeybee,
the race will end.
- Someone is honeybee? - The honeybee is one of us?
Is the honeybee one of us?
- The honeybee is here? - Among us?
- Who is that honeybee? - He's flustered.
You keep moving forward. Are you the honeybee?
What's wrong with your fist?
That's the honey punch.
That's the honey punch. It's the honey punch.
- Hold on. - That's right. The honey punch.
- The honey punch. - The honey punch.
It's not me.
- It's the honey punch. - It's sweet.
He is the honeybee.
- It's not me. - It's the honey punch.
- It's not me. - He's the Suyuri Honey Punch.
You fools. There you go again today.
- Why would that be a honeybee? - Don't think I'm the honeybee.
Isn't he the Suyuri Honey Punch?
We must match the honeybee.
- Match the honeybee? - We should catch it.
What do you mean we should match the honeybee?
It's not me. Don't get the wrong idea.
The group mission to earn the ballots is called...
- Link Between You and Me. - Link.
- It's a link. - Okay.
You will try the mission as pairs.
Within the time limit, if any of the pairs separate...
the intersected ropes which are tied on your wrists,
you have accomplished your mission then.
- That's nice. - Okay.
- We can totally complete this. - We can do this.
Of course.
First, pair up.
Why don't you two pair up then?
Of course, we are so close!
- So Min and I are close. - They are the national siblings.
- Listen. - Jong Kook.
- Use your body. Just untie that. - How should we do this?
- How do we untie this? - Like this?
Can you even untie that?
- This... - Do whatever it takes.
- Get ready. - Ready.
- Ready. - We can do this. Hold still.
- So Min, stay still. - You should just complete this.
Crouch down. Crouch.
(Did he figure out a way to solve this?)
Will that work?
I guess it works.
(He turns around and sits down.)
(And So Min will lift her hands with her wrists tied to the ropes.)
(It looks like he's going to succeed.)
(Will the first pair be able to accomplish the mission in one-go?)
(As if!)
Hold on. Wait. Hold on.
It didn't work.
- Hey, Flirty Kook. - Go inside there.
Hold on. Wait a second, So Min.
So Min. It's getting tangled up.
(As he fails at his first attempt, her reckless side takes over.)
So Min, you're tangling this up. Hold on a second.
- Only one person should move. - Wait.
(The ropes are even more entangled.)
- Hey, So Min. Hold on. - It's more entangled.
What is this?
This will never work, right?
How should we solve this? Wait.
- Wait. Don't move. - How should we solve this?
This...
- I figured it out. - Really?
- You got it? - Let's do your method next.
- Hey, tell us. - I'm right below Mensa.
That's just the ground.
- The ground is below Mensa. - Hey.
- It's just ground. - You little brat.
- There's the ground below Mensa. - In the end...
I'm right below Mensa.
It won't work, right?
(They are still thinking it over.)
- Put it in there. - You should go this way.
- Go inside the yellow ropes. - Did you go inside here?
Yes, jump over the rope.
- Isn't that mine? - Yes, come inside the ropes.
- I'll go in there. - Aren't these yours and mine?
You got it.
That's it. You just need to lift it up.
Lift it and take out your legs.
- Lift it and pull it back. - You got it.
No, it's the same thing.
(The ropes aren't separated.)
- That didn't work. - I thought it was going to work.
Gosh, I thought it would work.
- Is this even possible? Is it? - I thought it would work.
- That's fascinating. - We can try it with these.
The guy with the anger management issue and I will try this next.
My IQ is 138.
We'll complete this mission.
- We'll have a vote then. - Yes.
- Right, right. - That's neat.
I'll make this happen.
(I'll eliminate him. Did you all get that?)
He heard it. I think he heard it.
- No, no. - I could see what you were saying.
Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
- Flirty Kook. - Okay.
- I'll let him survive. - Okay!
- Flirty Kook. - Here we go. Get ready.
Start.
Hold on, Seok Jin.
Should you do the dance move from "Come Back Home"?
- Right. I thought that too. - You know?
Kwang Soo, go like this.
Go through like this.
Jae Seok, shouldn't you do the move from "Come Back Home"?
(Well, as for the dance move from "Come Back Home"...)
(Seo Taiji and Boys made kids who left home return home...)
(with their legendary song, "Come Back Home".)
(A body passing through the circle made with arms is the key point.)
(They'll reenact the dance on the ground.)
- You got it. - Hold on.
Seok Jin, hold on.
- Stay there. - Okay.
(Will they be able to succeed with the move from the song?)
(Chuckling)
(Untying)
We can't use our hands.
My role model is cheating again.
Can you actually separate that?
(This is the cheating of a man with a 138-IQ.)
- It's not working. - We have to go in there together.
- Yes, you must go inside like that. - Put your leg in first.
(Seok Jin pulls up Jae Seok's jacket.)
(Jae Seok gets back at him by pulling up the rope.)
(It's pulling up the ropes, a new ssireum technique.)
(All of a sudden, it becomes a ssireum match.)
This isn't ssireum.
- Why are they fighting? - Hey.
- Why are you two fighting? - That's not how you do it.
We don't have much time left.
- Think about the ballots. - Hold on, Seok Jin.
- Jae Seok, the ballots. - I'll go like this.
Yes, the ballots.
(He comes to his senses.)
- That's the same thing. - Come in.
- Did it work? - I think it worked.
- It worked. - They can get out of it.
- Come inside. - You just need to pull it up.
- Pull it above your head. - This is it.
- Really? - Let go.
- We got it. - I think we got it.
- We'll pull it up. - Hold on.
- Pull it up. - It worked?
(Can they accomplish their mission?)
(No way. They fail just like Jong Kook and So Min.)
(This guy with IQ of 138 have an impeccable memory.)
Hey, this is crazy. I'm so angry.
This won't work.
(The Seoks fail to complete the mission.)
- This is driving me crazy. - Hey.
- This is driving me crazy. - I'm so angry.
Hey, this won't work.
- Okay, you got it. - Kwang Soo.
- You should separate the ropes. - We should...
- We'll go this way. - We'll start.
(They have a realization at the same time.)
(Wait, something just happened.)
- Didn't it just come off? - Yes, it did.
- How? - How?
- This is amazing. Look. - How?
- How? - Look.
- It just came off. - Ready.
(Their last challenge starts.)
(How are they going to solve this?)
(Did they start a way to solve it?)
To that side?
(8 ballots are at stake on this challenge.)
(Wait...)
(Kwang Soo says hello to Se Chan's bottom up close.)
It got stuck.
(Is this your first bottom massage?)
Hold on.
(I knew it.)
(There's no way they'd succeed.)
- That's wrong. - That's not it.
The thing is that...
You must try a method we didn't try.
(Bursting into laughter)
(He aims his bottom right on his face.)
Kwang Soo, put your leg in.
- Put your leg in. - Okay.
I don't think this is possible.
- You should think. - It's unbelievable that it works.
- I can't believe it works. - I don't think that's the method.
Why don't you lie down on this side?
- Lie down here? - Yes.
- Lie down this side. - Okay.
All right. Hold this.
(What are they doing?)
(The Dumb and Dumber unite.)
(Rolling)
(This is not that kind of game. It's turning out to be weird.)
- What is this? - What are you doing?
It won't work with that method.
You still got that part.
(The Dumb and Dumber fails the mission.)
- It won't work. - It won't work.
How could you do this?
- No one could do this. - You try it.
- This is impossible. - You do it.
- All right. - You should try it.
- How could you do this? - This really works?
Does This work?
- Do it fair and square. - How could this work?
- How could this work? - How could you do this?
- If it's simple, I'll be mad. - I'll be annoyed.
- Do it slowly. - Slowly.
Look. The ropes were tied like this.
- Okay. - Here it goes.
- He's tying it. - How?
(Move closer to one another.)
- How? - My goodness.
(Make a loop with one hand.)
(Put the loop into the partner's rope on the wrist.)
(The loop inside the rope is the key point.)
I did think about using the wrist.
(Put the loop around the partner's wrist.)
What do you do after that?
I didn't think about it in detail.
He put it inside there.
(Then you have separated the ropes like this. Ta-da!)
(The ropes are separated like magic.)
- Wait. Hold on. - How did that happen? Wait?
- I can't believe this. - Is he a magician?
(They can't believe it even after watching it.)
- Aren't you Lee Eun Gyeol? - What is this?
What is this? Where is it?
- I can't believe this. - What's happening?
You failed to complete your mission.
You will only receive...
- seven ballots. - Okay.
(1 ballot is taken away for failing the mission.)
Everyone, there are seven ballots among these,
- Is there a dud? - and one empty, dud ballot.
- Okay. - I should go for that.
Jae Seok has to pick it.
I'll spread them, so you can't see them.
You may all pick one.
Okay.
- Seok Jin. - Okay.
(Which member won't be able to vote regarding eliminating Jong Kook?)
All right. You'll reveal it one at a time.
- Here I go. 1, 2, 3. - 3.
Okay.
- You got the ballot. - I got the ballot.
She got the ballot too.
- 1, 2, 3. - This is driving me crazy.
(Will he be able to vote for his elimination too?)
- He got the ballot too. - Okay!
That's interesting.
Oh, no.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(Se Chan obtains a ballot.)
- It's driving me insane. - That's strange.
How could this happen?
- It's Kwang Soo. - It's really not me.
It's interesting.
- Shall we show it together? - One.
- All 3 of us? - 3 of us.
- 3 of us. - 1, 2.
(3 unlucky members reveal the result together.)
(Among competitively unlucky members,)
(who will be the unluckiest one?)
- 3. - 3.
(Seok Jin obtains a ballot.)
(Jae Seok obtains a ballot.)
That's strange.
What's going on?
(Kwang Soo is always unlucky.)
- Goodness. - Incredible. How's it possible?
- Kwang Soo. - Did you plan this?
(Misfortune for unlucky Kwang Soo)
- It's strange. - Kwang Soo. What's wrong with you?
- It's unbelievable. - You should go somewhere.
There's no way.
What's the probability that he's always unlucky?
(Kwang Soo is excluded from voting.)
You will go to each of your spots.
- Then you'll vote in private. - Okay.
It's confusing.
(If most of them agree to eliminate Jong Kook)
- This is... - So Min.
You should think carefully.
I won't vote yes.
I got closer to Jong Kook, so I won't do it.
I can't eliminate Jong Kook. Otherwise, I'll be eliminated.
I won't either.
Kwang Soo doesn't have a ballot.
I might not be eliminated.
(There are a few whom he can trust.)
So Min and I became closer.
Jong Kook.
Do you trust me?
Of course. I already told them.
(Jong Kook survives if the votes are less than the majority.)
No, no.
No.
(What will happen to Jong Kook?)
Never.
(All 7 members finish voting.)
- Did everyone vote? - Yes.
(It's time to announce the result of the vote.)
(Looking around)
I can't let Jong Kook go like this.
(He speaks insincerely.)
(All of a sudden?)
- All of a sudden? - Really?
- I agree. - Are you being honest?
If you didn't agree to eliminate Jong Kook,
just eliminate me next time.
(Recoiling)
Please calm down.
I thought you were acting.
- What are you doing? - He's acting.
Here's the result of voting whether to eliminate Jong Kook.
I'll be fine.
- I won't be eliminated. - Those who agreed.
(Those who agreed to eliminate Jong Kook)
- Five votes. - Goodness.
Five votes?
(5 out of 7 members agreed to eliminate Jong Kook.)
- You're not even human. - Five votes?
- That's harsh. - That's harsh.
You aren't even human.
(Those who agreed aren't human.)
I didn't even vote.
- I didn't vote. - You didn't?
- No. - Really?
- He didn't. - My gosh.
- Five votes? - I didn't vote.
Five votes?
Two members disagreed, but the majority agreed.
Jong Kook is eliminated.
How can we send Jong Kook away like this?
Wait, then two people voted against it.
Jong Kook voted against it, didn't he?
- Everyone agreed except 1. - Except 1?
Everyone agreed except one person.
- I knew it. - Haha is scary.
- Wait. - What's this?
(At that time)
(The honeybee puppet appears.)
- He'll be eliminated. - Am I eliminated?
(Am I really eliminated?)
- Come on. - Wait, honeybee.
- Jong Kook. - No way.
- Don't go, don't go. - No.
- No, Jong Kook. - Don't go!
(No, Jong Kook.)
(Far away)
It's a party.
(It's a party.)
- This is scary. - It's a party.
(They're extremely excited.)
How could they?
They're so happy.
Is he eliminated immediately?
It's unbelievable.
The target candidate to be eliminated...
based on the first vote.
It's six members except for Haha.
That's right.
(In other words)
He'll be eliminated anyway.
(Haha is the only one who voted against it.)
I must survive.
(He predicted that Jong Kook would be eliminated.)
- He's so sly. - He is.
Goodness. Look at him.
(The other 6 members are targets for elimination.)
- How could it be? - What's wrong?
- Hey, we got a text message. - We got a text message?
What is it?
It's from the honeybee again.
(It's a message from the honeybee.)
(The second judgment will start.)
There are two target candidates this time.
(Two target candidates?)
During one hour, meet celebrity friends.
Get them to vote one of the targets to be eliminated.
"Celebrity friends"?
"Meet celebrity friends"?
Based on the result, the member with more votes will be eliminated.
Here are the two target candidates for elimination.
(Who are the two target candidates that the honeybee chose?)
They're Seok Jin and Ji Hyo.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo)
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo are the second targets.)
- Why? - Why?
- Why? - What's going on?
(Why is it two?)
Wait, I can't understand the honeybee.
Is one of us the honeybee?
- I didn't think about the honeybee. - It's impossible to know.
Who's the honeybee?
Honeybee?
- Is it Jong Kook? - That's possible.
- It could be Jong Kook. - It could be Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is taken by honeybee puppets.)
(Is Jong Kook behind everything?)
Jong Kook could be the honeybee, right?
Five members excluding Seok Jin and Ji Hyo.
You will support the candidate whom you think...
won't be eliminated.
The one you don't think will be eliminated?
- Who won't likely be eliminated? - Right.
Who's eliminated is based on your friends' votes.
Those who supported the candidate who doesn't get eliminated...
will obtain an important hint regarding the honeybee.
Do you mean that...
our friends will determine who should be eliminated?
- That's correct. - Okay.
(There's only one way.)
Do we stand behind the candidate who won't likely be eliminated?
(Everyone gathers around Ji Hyo.)
It's pointless to say anything.
(Empty and crowded)
I think it's over.
I'd be surprised if anyone came to me.
It'll be unbelievable.
Teams are determined.
[VIU Ver] SBS E441 Running Man
"Honeybee's Counterattack Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Goodness)
Come on.
(The difference is extreme.)
Don't you know?
- It was obvious. - Do you have no friends?
- The answer was clear. - It was obvious.
- What do you mean? - You have something.
They're bad at predicting.
- If Seok Jin survives, - Only me?
- Seok Jin will... - That won't happen.
Even if Seok Jin gets the hint, he won't understand it.
(He won't understand the hint.)
(His lonely fight against 6 starts.)
What? I'm going to hit you.
- You have one hour. - All right.
He'll come within 30 minutes.
(This person will have time.)
That's true.
Can we meet around 2:40pm?
(They start to invite friends.)
(The one who gets more votes is eliminated.)
You just need to vote.
We'll stop by.
- Do we go right away? - We should go.
(After difficulties of inviting them, they go to meet them.)
Seok Jin got caught in an extreme case.
Right.
Seok Jin versus Jae Seok.
- It's confusing. - It's really confusing.
There's nothing confusing about it.
Today was especially confusing.
Come on, there's nothing confusing about it.
It shouldn't be confusing.
I'm pure and innocent.
It's too much.
(He verbally attacks him in a way that makes sense.)
- Right. - It's too much.
It's always too much.
You deserve some beating.
- He does. - You've been saying that for years.
- Seok Jin, what's wrong? - I never hit anyone,
but I hit very hard. It's like a bee sting.
(A bee sting?)
- What did you say? - A bee sting.
- It's like medicine. - Seok Jin.
Are you the honeybee?
Wait, are you the honeybee?
Is it Seok Jin?
- I sting like a bee. - Are you the honeybee?
It was strange, wasn't it?
- I'm telling you that it's not me. - Why not?
- Tell us. - I'm a honeybee. What?
(Surprised)
- I'm a honeybee. - Are you a honeybee?
"I'm a honeybee."
- What do you mean? - Are you a honeybee?
"I'm a honeybee"?
- "I'm a honeybee"? - Don't tell us that.
Is today's shoot ruined?
I'm not.
- This isn't fun for us. - What's going on?
I'm not the honeybee.
- "I'm a honeybee." You said that. - You said that you are.
I think it's possible that Jong Kook and Seok Jin are...
the honeybees.
Is it not one person?
(Jong Kook is eliminated as the shoot starts.)
(Is honeybee Jong Kook behind it all?)
(Seok Jin says that he's a honeybee.)
(Did Seok Jin say it by mistake?)
- Is it not one person? - It's possible.
Sir.
(Speaking of which)
(The voice was low in the first video.)
(The voice was higher in the next one.)
I should listen to it again.
It's a woman.
(The second honeybee is a woman.)
(Is the second honeybee either So Min or Ji Hyo?)
I think it's a woman.
Is it Ji Hyo?
Me?
It's not me.
- Really? - It's not me.
(Ji Hyo denies it. Could it be...)
Me?
Me? It's not me.
(Candidates start to increase. Who is the honeybee?)
We must be here. We're here.
(They arrive at his house.)
Let's get ready to welcome him.
Let's toss him in the air when he comes out.
How many friends would come out...
- when you call them so suddenly? - Seriously.
That is true.
(He's here.)
- Goodness. - Where?
(Everyone is happy to see the one who appears.)
(Who is the important guest with a ballot?)
Hello.
Come.
(It's comedian Nam Chang Hee.)
(He hasn't been on Running Man for 3 years.)
(He participated in the 1st Unlucky Festival.)
(He returns as a lucky guest to pick the second target.)
Come out first.
- Chang Hee. - Slowly.
- All right. - Slowly, 2, 3.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
- 1, 2, 3. - Welcome.
It's Nam Chang Hee.
(Thank you so much.)
- Chang Hee. - We're proud of you.
- Hello, Chang Hee. - Hello.
It's over...
- Hello. - from the look on his face.
You came on the show after a long time.
Please say hello to viewers of Running Man.
Hello, I was on Running Man's...
special for unlucky people.
- That's right. - Right.
- That's right. Thank you. - I'm back for the second time.
- You have a pimple on your face. - Is that important?
- Yes. - Did you have to mention it?
(What are you doing to a precious voter?)
As a celebrity, you should take good care of yourself.
It can't be helped because you're born with your skin.
- Yes, I understand. - You know that.
- You're born with talking skills. - That's right.
I didn't get such genes from my parents.
(He wasn't born with talking skills.)
I wasn't born with talking skills.
- Chang Hee. - I was born this way.
What's wrong with you?
We don't have much time.
The person whom you vote for...
will be eliminated soon.
You'll play a very important role.
That's such an intimidating role.
I know, but we don't have much time.
They should appeal to Chang Hee since he'll be voting.
Appeal to him? That's so old-fashioned.
- I prepared an acrostic poem. - That sounds good.
(Ji Hyo makes an acrostic poem with "Nam Chang Hee".)
- With my name? - "Nam".
("Nam")
Others won't know.
- "Chang". - Chang Hee's charms.
(What are my charms, Ji Hyo?)
- "Hee". - "Hee".
(Laughing)
(He falls for her laughter.)
- Seriously. - Chang Hee is happy.
I've never seen him smile like that.
- That's his sincere smile. - Ji Hyo did a good job.
(Laughing)
(He fell for her.)
(You won't vote for me, right?)
What's that?
- She thought of him. - He likes it.
Chang Hee, we don't have much time.
- Please vote one of them. - All right.
- Please vote over there. - It's his show today.
Chang Hee.
- Chang Hee. - We don't know who he'll choose.
- He might create a twist. - Chang Hee.
(Which one did Chang Hee vote?)
Chang Hee.
Thank you so much for coming on the show so suddenly.
- Goodbye. - I'll get going.
- Bye. - Good luck, Running Man.
- Thank you, Chang Hee. - Have a good day.
- You can do it. - Director Lee Chang Dong.
- Director Lee Chang Dong? - Yes.
(Director Lee Chang Dong makes a special appearance.)
(When did the director arrive?)
There he is.
- There he is. - I see what it is.
- Goodbye. - He looked exactly the same.
- My gosh. - Bye.
- See you. - See you, Chang Hee.
- Bye, Chang Hee. - Bye.
Jong Kook didn't do much after being eliminated first.
Do people take turns being the honeybee after being eliminated?
He could be watching us from the monitoring room.
- That's true. - He got eliminated too soon.
Did Jong Kook pick me and Ji Hyo?
- I know. - Right.
Is everyone who's eliminated the honeybee?
- I know. - He got eliminated too early.
You have 25 minutes left.
- Is that so? - Will you meet one more?
It's not easy to meet a celebrity.
People might be in Sangam-dong at this hour.
- That comedy rehearsal room? - There are many right now.
Let's pick someone who passes by the comedy rehearsal room.
The one who's about to enter.
- Shall we go there? - Let's go.
(They go to a comedy rehearsal room in Sangam-dong.)
There could be bees other than the honeybee.
- Right. - Right?
(They arrive at the rehearsal room in Sangam-dong.)
- Are we here? - We're here.
Where are you, Je Seong?
(He calls Je Seong.)
Are you shooting? Where are you? Are you in Sangam-dong?
Okay. Come soon.
- That's good. - We have many ballots.
- Seok Jin, you have an advantage. - It's possible.
That's true.
We're meeting comedians who are his colleagues.
It's Bo Young.
(It's Bo Young.)
(Is it Park Bo Young whom we know?)
- It's Bo Young. - Really?
Park Bo Young?
(Park Bo Young?)
(She appeared on 4 episodes of Running Man.)
(Park Bo Young is a cute and lively actress.)
(Is Park Bo Young really here?)
(Actress Park Bo Young is really here.)
Is everyone inside? I'll say hello.
- Bo Young. - Hello.
- Goodness. - Bo Young.
- Hello. - What brings you here?
I'm about to go in.
Really?
- Long time no see. - You still look pretty.
It's been a long time, Bo Young.
Hello, hello.
Where were you going?
- It's so embarrassing. - Why?
(I have no makeup on.)
- I don't know. - By the way,
- today... - Aren't you wearing makeup?
- She isn't wearing makeup. - Is it true?
- You still look pretty. - You look pretty without makeup.
I'm sorry, Bo Young. It was so sudden.
No, it's me who's sorry.
More than anything,
she's like family to us on Running Man.
She's family indeed.
- It's been such a long time. - That's right.
You should come to the show.
- It's because... - I'm enjoying the show.
Bo Young was on the show when it started.
- She worked so hard. - She really did.
We were running so much back then.
As you know, Bo Young joined us at our company dinner.
That's right.
- Right. - Seriously.
She's quite close to Kwang Soo.
- We're close. - Do you call each other often?
- Yes. - We're like family.
- Really? - Your fathers are...
- also close. - They're close.
Are you going to a meeting for a drama?
I have a meeting with the director and the writer.
She was passing by chance.
As we were shooting, she wanted to say hello.
- Is that so? - It's good to see you.
Are you really not wearing any makeup?
(It's unbelievable.)
- I'm hardly wearing any. - Hardly.
(This is my natural look.)
It's the director.
- Is the director here? - That's the director.
- Hello. - Hello.
It's the director of her drama.
I'll be right there.
Please cast Kwang Soo.
(He's a good actor.)
He's a good actor.
- He's not a comedian. Cast him. - Stop it.
- What? - The director told us.
- What did he say? - "I'm sorry."
What do you mean?
(He leaves quickly. You're mistaken.)
- When did he say that? - He came by.
- What? - He said "I'm sorry."
- I saw him. I definitely saw him. - Right?
We can't ask Bo Young to be with us for a long time.
We're voting right now.
Either Seok Jin and Ji Hyo...
- has to be eliminated. - Me and him.
- The one whom I vote? - Yes.
I'll interview you briefly.
What does Seok Jin mean to you?
- Be honest. - It's a general question.
(Bo Young has never thought of such a question.)
(He's a comedian with whom she tackled a few times.)
I watched the show so many times.
- What does he mean to you? - I think of him as big-nosed.
(I think of him as big-nosed.)
To you? That's the best compliment.
- Seriously. - It's the best compliment.
Thank you.
It's the best compliment. What does Ji Hyo mean to you?
Ji Hyo was so warm-hearted to me.
It's already over.
When I was on the show for the first time,
- I was on the same team with her. - That's right.
- I can't forget that she hugged me. - Right.
(I can't forget that she hugged me warmly.)
(Ji Hyo gave her a helpful tip for the race.)
(She gave Bo Young a warm hug to comfort her when she was scared.)
(It's still clear in my memory.)
Bo Young, that's really nice,
- but what does she mean? - I'm sorry.
(Wait a minute.)
(Summarize it in one word.)
That was too long. Please make it short.
- Okay. - What does Seok Jin mean to you?
- He's big-nosed. - Big-nosed.
- What does Ji Hyo mean to you? - She's like my sister.
(Ji Hyo is like my sister.)
(Big-nosed versus sister)
He's in trouble.
- It's over. - He's in trouble.
- No. - Is voting necessary?
What does Kwang Soo mean to you?
(He asks her a bonus question about Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo considers her his family. What does she think of him?)
He's a giraffe.
(Curt)
(To Bo Young, Kwang Soo is just a giraffe.)
- I see. - What?
I thought it'd be a brother, but I was wrong.
- What? - What was that?
To you, Kwang Soo is a giraffe.
Bo Young, please vote.
Seok Jin, do you have something to say to her?
- Say something short. - Something short.
You're always pretty and beautiful.
Your charms are pure and innocent.
- You are... - Thank you.
Was it quite uncomfortable?
(She interrupts him.)
(Was his appeal uncomfortable?)
I never saw Bo Young step back.
- Why are you going back? - She kept stepping back.
She interrupted him.
Even I thought it was fake.
I thought it was a scene from a movie...
- Wait. - when he complimented her.
Goodness, what was the matter?
Did you feel uncomfortable?
Why? Why would you feel uncomfortable with me, my Bo Young?
(He sounds cheesy.)
- "My Bo Young". - "My Bo Young".
I should vote soon.
(I became certain thanks to Seok Jin.)
- All right, please vote. - We never know.
- Bo Young has a meeting to attend. - We don't know.
- Right. - She has to go.
Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
- Stay healthy, bye. - Thank you.
Let's meet again soon.
- Please come on the show. - Thank you and goodbye.
Do I vote for the one who'll be eliminated?
- It's between Seok Jin and Ji Hyo. - Right.
(Seok Jin makes her a little bit uncomfortable.)
(Ji Hyo is like her sister with an unforgettable hug.)
(I'm sorry.)
Happy New Year. Thank you.
Bye, Bo Young.
Have a good day.
It's about a magician...
There it is.
- I think this is it. - This?
- This is it. - It is.
We don't have time. We must ask quickly.
- Je Seong. - Hello, Je Seong.
- Je Seong. - Hello.
(Comedian Hwang Je Seong)
(He's a laughter zombie who makes everyone laugh.)
(Today he is the last voter, who came running after one phone call.)
Just make up your mind. Je Seong, come here.
- Je Seong, are you freezing? - Yes.
(Seok Jin tries to win his heart by lending his jacket.)
Thank you.
We're even wearing almost the same color.
That's right. It's pretty.
- Je Seong. - Yes?
- This is what really warms you up. - Ji Hyo.
(This is what really warms you up.)
(Ji Hyo counterattacks with a hand warmer.)
This is what really warms you up.
(She gives him two hand warmers.)
- Will you be okay? - I'll be okay.
- Je Seong is freezing. - Sit down, Je Seong.
Seok Jin, aren't you cold?
- Aren't you cold? - You look cold.
He put his hands between his legs. He's freezing.
He's freezing.
(He is the only one who is freezing.)
- I'll give you back the jacket. - It's okay.
- Are you sure? - I'm fine.
The thing is,
one of these two will be out...
depending on your choice.
Depending on your choice.
- It's a vote. - Pick one.
- Seriously, - Say what you think.
don't think too much.
- What does Seok Jin mean to you? - This is the first time...
(What does Seok Jin mean to you?)
What does Seok Jin mean to you?
(This time, it will be different.)
(I even gave him my jacket.)
(I'm sure I won his heart.)
(What does Seok Jin mean to him after receiving the jacket?)
He means nothing more than "seok" to me.
- A stone. - A stone?
(He means nothing more than a stone.)
(Seok Jin means a stone to Je Seong.)
A stone?
(Seok Jin is freezing.)
Between Ji Hyo and Seok Jin...
What does Ji Hyo mean to you?
Ji Hyo means "hyo" to me.
- A good girl. - They follow their names.
- They follow their names. - What does "hyo" mean?
You're on fire today.
- You're incredible. - You're so funny today.
You think so? I'm doing good?
- It's high-quality. - Okay.
Seok Jin, do you want to say something to Je Seong?
Je Seong...
Every young comedian I have my eye on becomes popular.
- Like who? - Like who?
Who, for example?
Do you have your eye on someone right now?
- I do. - Who?
- Je Seong, first of all. - Je Seong.
- Je Seong and Na Rae. - He's smiling.
Na Rae is...
Seok Jin, Na Rae is the one who has her eye on you.
(Only Seok Jin didn't know.)
(The popular comedian, Park Na Rae, has her eye on Seok Jin.)
The situation has completely reversed.
Je Seong is already popular too.
- They're both already popular. - Who is watching who?
- What does he even mean? - Who is watching who?
That was funny.
(So cool)
Na Rae is watching me. That was funny.
I haven't laughed this hard in a while.
All right. Let's have a vote now.
He should go back to his practice soon.
You can come to me and leave the note.
Je Seong.
- This is the first time we've met. - What?
- This is the first time, right? - This is the second time.
You don't remember, do you?
(Seok Jin completely loses Je Seong.)
Stop making mistakes.
- Where did you meet? - "The Golden Bell Challenge".
You forgot...
It's "Star Golden Bell", you brat.
I've never been on "The Golden Bell Challenge".
Why do you call him a brat?
- Why do you... - He could be confused.
- Why... - Why do you call him a brat?
Why did you say that?
- I'm just being friendly. - Thank you.
Thank you, Je Seong.
- Je Seong. - Thank you!
You did a good job, Je Seong.
Thank you.
(The vote will determine the second target.)
But we don't know...
- who Je Seong will choose yet. - You're right.
Choose who should be out.
- We don't know who he'll choose. - Choose who should be out.
(The time is up.)
(It is time to decide the second target.)
The time is up.
Let me announce the result.
Seok Jin...
(Who did Chang Hee, Bo Young, and Je Seong think should be out?)
Seok Jin got three votes.
(Seok Jin got 3 votes.)
- What? - What?
(It was a unanimous vote.)
(As expected, Chang Hee voted for Seok Jin.)
(Bo Young also voted for Seok Jin with an apology.)
(Je Seong of course, voted for Seok Jin as well.)
(Seok Jin is the second target.)
(Thank you, voters.)
Everyone.
The second target, Seok Jin,
will be out...
within 30 minutes.
"Within 30 minutes"?
(I'm not out right away?)
Not right away?
He's out anyway.
No one knows...
when, where, how, and by who he will be eliminated.
When he is out,
- we'll select the next target. - Okay.
If he survives for 30 minutes,
he will continue to be the target.
(If he survives for 30 minutes, he will continue to be the target.)
(The target might not change?)
You have to protect Seok Jin...
to remain safe.
- That's right. - We have to protect him.
If Seok Jin...
- We have to protect him. - That's right.
When he is out, one of us will be the target.
We don't know who will be the next target.
So be careful on your way.
- Let's go have some lunch. - Let's eat.
We should be careful on our way.
Someone might pop out and rip my name tag off.
(Will Seok Jin survive the next 30 minutes?)
(They arrive at a restaurant for possibly their last meal.)
No one is here.
(The hall is empty.)
2, 4...
By the way, where is Jong Kook?
Is he really in prison?
(They still don't know where Jong Kook is.)
Ji Hyo survived.
Among Ji Hyo's supporters,
only one can get a hint.
- Among us? - Who wants it?
- Me. - Me.
- Me. - The thing is...
(Me!)
- I mean... - Ji Hyo, you pick one.
Exclude Kwang Soo.
- He gave me an order. - What did he say?
He told me to exclude Kwang Soo.
What's with him?
(Exclude Kwang Soo.)
Does he think we're rivals or something?
- Let's... - Rock-paper-scissors?
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
- Kwang Soo. - Then...
- You're excluded. - You're excluded.
For no reason?
- I mean... - Am I excluded?
- Kwang Soo is excluded. - Kwang Soo is excluded.
- You're excluded. - Okay.
(He feels hurt.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors without Kwang Soo.)
(Jae Seok and So Min win.)
- Okay. - Okay.
The cheaters are out.
So Min, if I cheer for you, will you show me the hint?
- Of course. - Jeon So Min!
(They suddenly start cheering for So Min.)
Jae Seok, if I cheer for you, will you show me the hint?
- What? - Will you show me the hint?
I support you.
(I support you.)
(You too?)
- Yu Jae Seok! - Yu Jae Seok!
(Go, Jae Seok!)
(It suddenly turns into a cheer competition.)
- Kwang Soo, Se Chan. - Yes?
- Yu Jae Seok! - Yu Jae Seok!
(Did you need us?)
Carry me.
(The other team cheers with a song.)
(Will the loudest win...)
(or the tallest?)
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Jeon So Min!
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Ready.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Which of the two will win the honeybee hint?)
(Jae Seok wins.)
(He will get a hint.)
- Yu Jae Seok! - Yu Jae Seok!
(Praise Jae Seok!)
Yu Jae Seok!
Go back to your seats.
- Go back. - Please...
I...
- Sit down. - From the beginning...
- Go back to your seats. - From the beginning,
- I didn't want to see the hint. - Sit down.
- Guys. - Sit down.
(After sending everyone away, he checks the hint.)
Jae Seok.
What's this?
(The hint says, "young".)
- Jae Seok. - Is that the hint?
Show me and Kwang Soo first.
I can't show this to them.
(Jae Seok changes his mind.)
- What? - What?
(I can't show this to them.)
(They can't believe what they hear.)
What did you say?
(Hold on.)
What... What did you say?
- I can't show it to you. - What...
- What do you mean? - Seriously...
Like we did before...
His legs...
(This is what you get.)
(He is punished for not sharing the hint.)
- You said you'd share it with us. - You said you'd share it with us.
You made us carry you.
What does that mean?
- I don't understand the hint. - Hold on.
How are we supposed to protect Seok Jin for 30 minutes?
- His name tag... - Protect me from any threat.
- I hope no one in here attacks him. - Your food is here.
Is it one of us?
Your food is here.
What if someone comes in with the food?
Be careful.
Will someone...
I think someone is in here.
Hello.
- No. I recognize her. - Right.
- Hello. - Hello.
It's a salad.
There is tangsuyuk too.
What's going on?
(They're served with a lot of food not as usual.)
Will we be out if we eat this?
(The staff doesn't usually let us eat this much food.)
What can happen during the 30 minutes?
- The time is almost up. - Nothing is happening.
There are 11 minutes left.
- Only 11 minutes? - What?
(Surprised)
(The waitress...)
(suddenly goes behind Seok Jin.)
(She approaches Seok Jin.)
My goodness.
(They watch every small movement around Seok Jin.)
(But the waitress leaves after serving the food.)
- It's a lot. - What can possibly happen?
There are only 10 minutes left.
- You guys... - Seok Jin, your microphone...
(The audio director suddenly barges in.)
What? No!
(Why did he suddenly barge in?)
- Let me check the power. - No!
- The power... - No!
Let me just check the power.
I mean...
The power is suddenly off?
It's working perfectly fine.
- He checked his name tag. - He did.
He just checked Seok Jin's name tag.
- But... - Really?
That was pretty aggressive. I was scared.
It was definitely aggressive.
(Peeping)
There is nothing outside.
Lock the door.
We could just stand here for the next 10 minutes.
Let's take turns.
- Let's guard the door. - That sounds good.
Let me ask you something. It's not one of you, is it?
- Never. - No?
I'm afraid...
a dozen people will storm in.
There are only five minutes left. It doesn't make sense.
- No way. - Seriously...
- Gosh! - What?
(Another door opens.)
(Jong Kook enters.)
(What is Jong Kook doing here?)
(He is back dressed as a honeybee.)
What's going on?
He is the honeybee.
Come!
- Come! - You're the honeybee?
You're the honeybee?
- He is the honeybee. - Come!
- He is here. - He is the honeybee?
(Is Jong Kook really the honeybee?)
(Everyone became suspicious when he was eliminated so soon.)
(They suspected Jong Kook was the honeybee.)
(Was all of this...)
(Jong Kook's plan?)
Come!
- Come! - No!
(The honeybee's hunt starts.)
- Stop him! - No!
Guys.
(Helpless)
- Where are you going? - Stop him! Guys, stop him!
- Stop him! - Come here!
(The name tag is ripped off.)
(Seok Jin is out.)
- What is this? - Okay.
Gosh.
What are you doing, guys?
(Shocked)
How will this make us look?
- Guys. - My goodness.
What is this?
How could you not stop him?
He stormed in so suddenly.
I could have continued to be the target.
We couldn't stop him.
You fools! How could you not stop him?
There were only five minutes left.
Let's move to the final destination.
In the final mission, identify the honeybee and eliminate him or her.
It's called the Flight of the Honeybee.
- But we don't know anything. - You have a hint.
I don't know what it means.
I'm serious.
It's a very important hint.
- Really? - Yes.
- It didn't seem important. - Share it with us.
- Share it with us. - Really?
- Gosh. - What is it?
(Startled)
Let me announce the candidates for the last target.
The candidates for the last target are...
Jae Seok, Haha, Ji Hyo,
Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and So Min.
What are we supposed to do?
Among those, the two people I choose...
become the final candidates.
They will be announced on social media,
- and internet users... - What?
will decide who will be out through a live vote.
A live vote?
- A live vote? - On social media?
The final two candidates are...
Jae Seok and Haha.
(Jae Seok and Haha)
(They're chosen as the final target candidates.)
- Who is the honeybee anyway? - It's driving me crazy.
Now,
there will be a vote on social media...
to decide which of you two will be out.
My goodness.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I feel so frustrated. - So do I.
We don't know who it is,
but someone is trying to eliminate...
one of us.
Between Jae Seok and me,
who do you think should be out?
One of us has to be out.
- Seriously... - I'm innocent.
- I... - This is unfair.
I really don't want to be eliminated.
- Please. - Please.
- Please. - Who is it anyway?
Who is doing this to us?
(Who should be eliminated?)
(It's a close vote.)
Let me announce the result.
(The votes are in.)
Between you two...
(Who did the voters choose as the final target?)
Let me announce the result.
(The votes are in.)
Between you two...
(Who did the voters choose as the final target?)
The target becomes...
(Who appealed to the voters more effectively?)
(Jae Seok becomes the final target.)
(Jae Seok won 65 percent of the votes.)
Thank you.
What?
("Thank you"?)
Did you see it correctly?
(Who should be eliminated?)
(Oh, no.)
(I was mistaken.)
Jae Seok is the target?
Jae Seok... Oh, right.
(The final target becomes...)
(Jae Seok.)
I mean...
(Bye, Jae Seok.)
My goodness.
(Jae Seok is dragged to somewhere.)
I think the voters misunderstood.
I mean...
(What will happen to the target?)
My gosh.
The target has been decided.
It's Jae Seok.
(The rest of the members get ready for the race.)
The race will start soon.
When you catch the honeybee, the race will be over.
If you fail to catch the honeybee within the time limit,
- you'll be penalized. - This is hard.
(Jae Seok is the only person with a hint.)
The race will start...
in five,
four,
three,
two,
one. Start.
(It's the last chance to identify the honeybee. The race starts.)
We've never had this few hints.
(There is only one hint.)
And only Jae Seok knows the hint.
(Jae Seok is the only one who knows the hint.)
We have to find Jae Seok.
Where is Jae Seok?
(Jae Seok is the only key to identifying the honeybee.)
- Se Chan. - Ji Hyo.
Were you one of the candidates?
- I don't know. - What did you do?
Why do you stride towards us?
Aren't we supposed to find Jae Seok?
He is the target.
Who was the other candidate, though?
- I don't know. - You two weren't, right?
- We? - Yes.
We don't know who the other was, right?
We don't know the other candidate.
We need hints to find the honeybee.
Let's discuss.
We have no hints.
Only Jae Seok has one, so we need to find him.
But...
Only Jae Seok knows, right?
(How are we going to find him?)
To be honest, I'm suspecting Jae Seok.
- I think so too. - Right?
Is all of this his plan?
I can't trust what he tells us.
I'm suspecting So Min because...
I thought the voice was Ji Hyo's.
To be honest, I thought so too.
It wasn't me. And I thought...
it was a woman's voice.
Because I'm not the honeybee, it has to be So Min.
If we...
All the suspicious people are coming here. My goodness.
Were you three here together?
The two of us were here, and Kwang Soo came later.
We'll know if we rip off the name tag.
What about So Min?
- Me? - Should we do that?
(Should we rip off So Min's name tag?)
- Me? What about me? - Should we do that?
- But we have too few hints. - Right.
- We have nothing. - We should find Jae Seok.
- We have to find him. - I'm confused.
How did he become the target?
The important thing is...
Jae Seok became the target...
on social media.
- Between him and me... - Between him and you?
You were one of the candidates?
Yes, I was.
You didn't know that?
- I didn't. - Me neither.
- We didn't. - We didn't.
(They finally find out who the other candidate was.)
- You knew, right? - Why did I know?
- Because you chose us. - I didn't.
(You chose the candidates.)
- The writer told me. - It's so simple.
- The writer told me. - Really?
- I can't believe it. - She suddenly brings up the writer?
The thing is,
the writer told me, I swear.
That's how I knew. Seriously, that's how I knew.
Look at her.
Let's see...
But then the rules would be too simple.
In any case, the target is Jae Seok. We have to find him.
Let's do that. Let's find him first.
- He is the only one with a hint. - But I can't find him anywhere.
If we...
I can't stop thinking Jae Seok is the honeybee.
I'll look this way.
(Everyone is looking for Jae Seok.)
This is giving me a headache.
Before, we got many hints.
But we don't have any today.
- Something must be going on. - Right.
(Someone suddenly appears.)
(The honeybee?)
(The honeybee is here.)
(The others have no idea.)
- Jae Seok... - Let's check the library.
(They all look for Jae Seok.)
Where is Jae Seok?
- Over there, maybe? - What about here?
(With Jae Seok out of sight,)
(the honeybee starts moving carefully.)
(Does the honeybee know where Jae Seok is?)
Jae Seok.
(The others are still looking for Jae Seok.)
Oh, my.
(While looking for Jae Seok,)
(they find someone else.)
(In a remote office...)
Release me.
(They find Seok Jin who had been kidnapped.)
(He is tied up.)
- What happened? - Why should we release you?
- Release me. - Why should we release you?
- Release me. - Hold on.
We shouldn't release him. He was already eliminated.
He was eliminated.
- Why should we release you? - You have to release me.
- He is out. - You have to release me...
so that I can get back in the race.
"Save me. Trust me."
When someone says that, never save that person.
(He has 10 years of experience.)
(Frustrated)
That's not it.
If we release him,
he'll try to rip off our name tags.
This is driving me crazy. That's not it.
What about this?
We release him and rip off his name tag.
- We eliminate him? - Yes.
(Should we release him and then eliminate him?)
- You can't do that. - Who knows?
He might have a hint.
- Hey. - Don't you think so?
- Let's untie him. - Hey.
Why would you rip my name tag?
- We don't have any hints. - Hold on.
- Tell us the hint, and you're free. - I don't know any hints.
- Right, he has no clue. - But I know where it is.
- Where is it? - It's under his name tag.
- No, it's not! - All right.
- We've untied him. - We've untied him.
Now that I'm untied, I've become a part of your team.
- Don't trust him. - It's the truth.
- He's out. - You're right.
Rip it!
- Don't! You shouldn't! - Rip it!
(Will Haha be right and find a hint under his name tag?)
Hey!
(They rip his name tag.)
It's not there. I'm sorry.
Is it over?
(It's empty under his name tag.)
I'm sorry.
Jee Seok Jin is completely out.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
- We're on the same team! - I'm sorry.
Maybe it's under this one.
- I think it is. Rip it. - 1, 2, 3.
(Haha is convinced once again.)
(Is it under the second name tag?)
(Ripping)
(There is nothing there once again.)
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
Jee Seok Jin is completely out.
- I'm sorry. - But why was he tied up?
Why?
You guys are fools!
I told you.
(Why was he tied up?)
(He was confined here by the honeybee.)
(He was banned from shouting or escaping on his own.)
(If the members rescued him, he could join the final race.)
(Seok Jin was telling the truth.)
- It's here. - He was right.
- Let me see. - It's here.
It's here!
It's under his bottom.
- Hold him! - Wait.
Good job.
(They find the hint.)
- I got it. - "Mak"?
You fools. The honeybees are our enemies.
(Only one word is written on the hint.)
- What does this mean? - We needed to escape.
What is that?
("Mak"?)
What kind of a hint is this?
Jae Seok has a hint too.
If we rip him, it'll be killing 2 birds with 1 stone.
I'm sorry. I truly am. No one could believe you.
You guys didn't even understand the rules of this game.
- Let's go. - I have something to say.
Race start.
(He declares the start of the race.)
The real race has finally begun!
- You can do it! - Let's go.
- Let's. - Where can we get the hints?
- How can we get it? - "Mak"?
- What does that mean? - I don't know.
"Mak"?
Where is he?
I'm going down to the first floor.
(Where did Jae Seok go with the hint?)
(Suddenly)
(The honeybee appears...)
(in front of them.)
(They don't know what to do.)
(The honeybee slowly...)
(approaches Kwang Soo.)
(The honeybee...)
(who controlled everything is right before his eyes.)
(The honeybee only had to say one thing...)
(for Jong Kook to be eliminated.)
(Every time it appeared,)
(the members were faced with doom.)
(The very honeybee that they all feared...)
(is standing right before him.)
(He's hesitant to attack it...)
(in case something goes wrong.)
(For now, he runs away...)
(in order to find help.)
Haha!
(He looks for help.)
Goodness, it was right there.
What should I do?
(He needs help.)
Haha. Ji Hyo, come here.
- Did you find the hint? - I saw the honeybee.
- Where? - I saw it. It's here.
But I don't know what to do with it.
Who is it?
Hey.
(He has found the honeybee,)
(but he has no idea who it could be.)
- Did you spot it? - It was just walking around.
- Walking around? - Yes.
It stood still when it approached me.
(The honeybee is gone.)
Hey, where is... There it is.
See?
(Exclaiming)
(The honeybee is in front of them.)
- It's the real... - What should we do?
- It's the real honeybee. - I have the goosebumps.
What is that?
(It slowly approaches them.)
(If they catch the honeybee,)
(the race is over.)
(If they catch it,)
(all this misery will be over.)
If we rip its name tag, wouldn't all this be over?
Wouldn't it?
(There are three of them. They could win the fight.)
Hey.
(The honeybee gives hand signals.)
Him?
- It's the real honeybee. - Me?
(It points at Ji Hyo and Se Chan in order.)
He's the honeybee?
(Nodding)
(Is it trying to dupe them?)
It's weird for the honeybee to be saying that.
I know. Can't we just rip its name tag?
Isn't it odd? Shouldn't we just rip its name tag?
(They decide to do so.)
(If they rip its name tag, this race will be over.)
- Rip it. - What is this?
You're the real honeybee, right?
Hold on.
- Hold it. - Rip it.
- Rip it. - What does it say?
(Ripping)
- What does it say? - What does it say?
(The honeybee...)
(was Jae Seok.)
It's... It's Jae Seok.
(Was Jae Seok the one they'd been looking for?)
- What is this? - What is this?
(Something is written on his back.)
There's something back here.
(The real honeybee is 3435.)
(The real honeybee?)
- Why did you rip mine? - Ji Hyo.
There's something back here.
(What was his identity?)
(After becoming the final target, he was dragged somewhere.)
(Suddenly)
(Someone approached him...)
(and kidnapped him.)
(Sniffing)
(He smelled cologne.)
Jae Seok, please take off your blindfold.
(After taking his blindfold off,)
(he found a fake honeybee costume in front of him.)
(There was no point in resisting.)
(If the members mistook him and ripped his name tag,)
(they would be given 15 minutes to survive.)
- What? - What happened to him?
Tell us a hint or something.
Who is the honeybee?
(The real honeybee was controlling him.)
- What is that? - What's going on?
(A siren is turned on.)
What's going on? What is that sound?
(Perplexed)
Is this some kind of a honeybee repellent?
(Jae Seok, who cannot speak, is frustrated.)
(Jae Seok is out.)
Since you ripped the wrong honeybee's name tag,
you have only 15 minutes left.
(They are given 15 minutes.)
(We have 15 minutes?)
If you catch the honeybee, the race will end.
If you cannot catch it in the given time,
you will be penalized.
(They have to eliminate the honeybee in 15 minutes.)
Hold on. Jae Seok pointed at Se Chan?
(Hold on.)
(Jae Seok pointed at Se Chan.)
Yes.
(He kept pointing at Se Chan when he couldn't speak.)
(Was Jae Seok telling the truth,)
(and is Se Chan the real honeybee?)
(They decide to eliminate him.)
- He's the one then. - Let's eliminate him.
- It's him. - Hold on.
- I have nothing. - Because...
- Jae Seok was a fake one. - He pointed at you.
- It's not me! - Get him!
(Flustered, Se Chan runs away.)
- What if I'm not it? - We only have 15 minutes! Hurry!
- He's the one! - He is!
- It's Se Chan! - Jae Seok pointed at him.
- It's him. - There's no other exit.
(They lose him.)
No? Is it a dead end?
- Is it a dead end? - It is.
(Haha catches up to him.)
(He corners Se Chan.)
Hold on.
This is a serious misunderstanding.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo catch up.)
- Rip it. - Hold on.
I'm being serious. This isn't right.
We only have 15 minutes.
- Rip it. - All right.
Why are you resisting then?
- No! - It's him!
- Get him! - Hey!
(Se Chan resists with all his might.)
(Ripping)
(They remove his name tag.)
There's something on his back.
(Was he the real honeybee?)
(Jae Seok's hint was "young".)
(Or could it have meant 0?)
(Or could it have meant young?)
(If he's the real honeybee, what does this hint mean?)
- We're right! - We were!
(Se Chan was the honeybee.)
(Thanks to Jae Seok,)
(the real honeybee was caught so easily.)
Hello. Hello.
(Se Chan the honeybee)
(This race was made by his request.)
(The person who wore the costume...)
(and controlled the entire situation was...)
(Se Chan.)
(They successfully caught the honeybee.)
Hold on. Is this it?
- Is this the end? - It was too obvious.
- Jae Seok pointed at him. - Is this it?
(It's too weird for this to be the end.)
- By the way... - Honeybee Se Chan is out.
(The real honeybee is finally eliminated.)
However, the race...
- isn't over. - What?
(The race is not over yet.)
(The race...)
(isn't over?)
It's not over?
(What has happened?)
Is there another honeybee?
(Could it be?)
(They still need to figure out who it is.)
What does 3435 mean?
3435?
(What does it mean?)
(This hint was found...)
(under Jae Seok's name tag.)
No way.
- No way. - What is it?
So Min's phone number has...
34 in it, and Jong Kook's has 35.
They're like siblings on this show!
(Are Jong Kook and So Min the culprits?)
- It's them? - 3435.
(Jong Kook suddenly appeared out of nowhere...)
(after getting eliminated.)
(Then he suddenly attacked the second target, Seok Jin.)
(In the second video, the honeybee had a female voice.)
(They suspected So Min.)
(They acted unusually and seemed very closely...)
(during the opening segment.)
We need to find Jong Kook first.
Let's go.
- I'll scream if I find him. - Okay.
- I'll scream, so come find me. - All right.
(The trio decides to look for Jong Kook first.)
(Is 3435 really related to their phone numbers?)
Can I enter here?
(Jong Kook is nowhere to be seen.)
(Suddenly)
(Ji Hyo finds him.)
(He's tied up and confined.)
You startled me.
I'm alone.
(He wants her to enter.)
No. Hold on.
(I'm too scared. I'll come back later.)
Is no one else in that room? Hold on.
I'm so scared.
Haha!
Hurry up, Kwang Soo!
- Haha! - What is it?
(Haha, who was nearby, comes towards her.)
(They go into the room Jong Kook is confined in.)
What is this?
(Untie me right now.)
(No, you could be the honeybee.)
Don't get mad.
(They're unsure of his identity.)
I'll remove this duct tape.
Hey.
Hurry up! What are you doing? Untie me!
(A while ago, Seok Jin was in the same situation.)
(And a hint was hidden.)
First, we need to see the hint. We need more hints.
Okay.
- I've untied you. - Okay.
- Don't eliminate me. - You're not completely out.
- Don't eliminate me. - I won't.
All right, stand up.
- Okay, don't eliminate me. - Okay.
Okay, I'm no longer its puppet.
That honeybee...
(Is he the honeybee or a mere victim?)
How does it feel to be the first one eliminated?
How does it feel?
You have 30 minutes from now...
to rip the second target's name tag.
If you fail to do so,
you will receive a great punishment,
so make sure you do.
(He only eliminated Seok Jin...)
(because of what the honeybee said.)
(He was merely a puppet.)
- What is it? - What?
(Haha finds the hint that was under Jong Kook.)
(The previous hint was "mak".)
- What is it? - Let me see.
(This time, the hint says...)
("nae".)
- Look at this. - What is it?
- It's "mak"... - and "nae".
It means "the youngest".
(The youngest)
(The most crucial hint was...)
("the youngest".)
So Min is the youngest one among us.
- It's Se Chan and So Min! - You're right!
Hello.
(So Min was...)
(the other honeybee.)
- I feel so excited. - United?
(She schemed with Se Chan.)
(There are two targets.)
(Since I'm democratic, I'll give you all a chance.)
(So Min hid her identity...)
(and controlled Seok Jin and Jong Kook.)
(After Jae Seok was eliminated, a 15-minute countdown started.)
- What is that? - I need to hide.
(To protect her cover, she hid from the members.)
- Let's go and catch her. - We have no time.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Is this it for the hints?
(Jae Seok's hint has not been solved.)
3435?
(The real honeybee is 3435.)
What could this mean?
Maybe they're 34 and 35 years old.
(Could it be their ages?)
Their ages?
You're right.
(Se Chan and So Min are...)
(34 years old.)
(Then what about 35?)
Who's 35 years old then?
Isn't that Kwang Soo?
Perhaps there are three honeybees.
34 and 35 years old?
Isn't Kwang Soo a year older?
But he's not the youngest.
He was the youngest before the other two joined us.
(He was the former youngest member.)
You're right.
- He's the oldest among them. - Right.
(Are all the pieces of the puzzle in place now?)
You're a honeybee as well?
There's one more.
Right, there are three chairs.
(The remaining honeybee who decided...)
(to join this scheme alongside the other two was...)
(the former youngest member, Kwang Soo.)
It's him.
You three...
(The youngest trio)
are the youngest members.
- You've been assisting the others. - Right.
It must be hard.
It's obvious.
We're always the ones who wrap things up.
Wait.
You keep saying that we're the youngest members.
(He clarifies.)
- What's wrong? - I'm no longer the youngest.
It's been a while.
- We're only a year apart. - Hey, this is the beginning.
Well... It's true that they don't show me any manners.
I admit to that.
But I don't think I should be a part of this team.
But still, you're the captain of our team.
You should act as our leader.
(Do you not want to?)
- If that's the case... - You're our captain.
- Okay. - You'll be...
(He quickly accepts it.)
He likes it.
We need to team up.
You must feel burdened.
Captain, let's teach them a lesson.
- Lead us. - Yes, please.
(That was how he became their captain.)
(He was deprived of his ballot from the start.)
(They became anxious and regretted assigning him as their captain.)
Where are we going?
(When they were kidnapping Jae Seok...)
(He smelled cologne.)
Is Kwang Soo here?
(Due to his cologne, he almost got caught.)
This is his cologne.
- Why did you spray cologne? - I forgot.
We don't even have guests, so why did you?
I can't believe he's so good at smelling.
(Only Kwang Soo and So Min remain.)
- All right. - We only have five minutes.
We ripped Jae Seok's name tag.
- You did? - Yes.
(The honeybees' identities are revealed.)
So Min!
- Kwang Soo! - Kwang Soo!
So Min, it was Kwang Soo.
I found them!
(The honeybees lose if they get eliminated by them.)
(They need to hold out until the time is over.)
No, no.
I need to hide.
So Min!
So Min, we're all here!
(They need to find the honeybees.)
It was Kwang Soo!
(She also hides from them.)
Where should I hide?
(She goes to the auditorium.)
Here?
(She finds a place in a corner of the auditorium.)
Goodness.
I'm so scared. If I get caught, there's nowhere to run.
Seriously.
(Captain Kwang Soo also looks for a place to hide.)
(He tries to hide by becoming one with the stairs.)
(He thinks he won't be seen.)
Or should I lie there and look out?
- Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo.
(They're not far.)
I heard them.
(Jong Kook is near him.)
No.
(He senses danger.)
(He takes a peek at the direction where the voices came.)
Where are they?
I think I heard them say my name.
(Feeling threatened, he attempts to move.)
(Suddenly)
(Jong Kook looks around Kwang Soo's area.)
I think someone was over there.
(Did he spot Kwang Soo?)
I saw someone.
(He quickly moves towards him.)
(They're both on the same floor.)
(They're getting closer and closer.)
(Kwang Soo hides in an isolated place at the end of the hallway.)
Go, go. Give me the camera and go.
(The staff pulls out not to attract attention.)
(At that time,)
(he spots the staff who was pulling out on Kwang Soo's order.)
(I can hear his footsteps.)
(Jong Kook is searching every place on the route that the staff took.)
(Please go somewhere else.)
Please.
(As he looks around,)
(Jong Kook finds where Kwang Soo is.)
(Will he be able to find Kwang Soo?)
(Jong Kook moves in the opposite direction of Kwang Soo.)
(He's saved.)
(Now, only about 2 minutes remain.)
The time is going so slowly.
(If they can last, it will be Team Honeybee's victory.)
Did So Min get eliminated?
So Min...
Did Kwang Soo eliminate her?
You can't get eliminated, So Min.
(Because we'll eliminate you.)
What is that sound?
(The chasers are getting close to the auditorium where So Min is.)
I'm scared. What should I do?
I'm scared.
So Min.
(Haha and Ji Hyo enter the auditorium.)
(This is where So Min is hiding.)
(Please just go.)
(It's impossible to run away to another hiding place now.)
(At that time,)
(Haha approaches the stage where So Min is hiding.)
(So Min senses danger and moves in deeper to hide.)
(He gets close to where So Min is hiding.)
(However, he's looking up.)
(He fails to find So Min.)
What is this?
(What is this?)
Why are you here, So Min?
It's nothing. It's not what you think.
(I'm doomed.)
What's wrong?
I was just hiding.
Come here. We have to go catch Kwang Soo.
(Come on out now.)
So Min, it's Kwang Soo.
So Min.
- Why did you... - You brat.
Why did you go off on your own today?
I was looking for Kwang Soo.
- Let's go. - I was looking for Kwang Soo.
- We only have five minutes. - Here's Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo...
- You little rascal. - Kwang Soo...
(Giving her a lesson)
(So Min is eliminated.)
How dare you?
- You're the youngest. - Haha.
How could the youngest cause a rebellion?
- No. Hurry. - You rascal.
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo.
Let's hurry. Hurry, hurry.
To be honest, I want to chase people.
Hiding is too scary. It was so scary.
Hiding there was so scary.
1 minute and 30 seconds to the end of the race.
(If he lasts 1 minute and 30 seconds, he'll win the race.)
Gosh, I'm going to lose.
(Not that much time is left.)
Isn't he inside here?
Hey, there's only one minute left.
- Go catch him now. - He's not here.
- He's not here. - He's not here.
We didn't see him come in here.
(I just need to hold out a bit longer.)
(Jong Kook searches the place...)
(where suspicious movements were spotted earlier.)
(He searches the opposite side which he didn't search earlier.)
(And...)
(he finds Kwang Soo who was hiding.)
(The real hunt starts with less than 1 minute left.)
He's right here. He's here!
(These bee-farmers are gathering upon Jong Kook's call.)
He's upstairs.
He's here!
(The last honeybee meets a dead end as he tries to run away in a hurry.)
(Jong Kook stays close, so he doesn't get away.)
- He's here. - How long do I have left?
Just 30 more seconds.
He's here.
- Where? - He's here.
What time is it?
- How long do I have left? - Here.
He's right here. Haha, come here!
(Kwang Soo is completely surrounded.)
- Haha. - 20 seconds before time is up.
Please. Please.
Go over there. Go in there.
Go in there.
I'm sure he'll come to my side.
- 10, 9, 8, - 9, 8,
- 7, 6, - 7...
- Hurry! - 5, 4,
- 3, 2, 1. - 1.
(Kwang Soo tries to hold out with every ounce of his energy.)
- The race is over. - Yes!
(I did it!)
(Kwang Soo, the honeybee, wins.)
(That was so close. I could have won.)
We should've found him a bit earlier.
I had a gut feeling.
I was just going to pass by.
(Kwang Soo withstood their joint attack.)
I won.
At last.
Everyone, the winning team of Honeybee's Counterattack Race...
- is Team Honeybee. - Yes!
(Team Honeybee wins.)
Yes!
(You guys won by a close call.)
- Yes! - Gosh.
You're frustrating.
Hey, Kwang Soo. We all did our part.
We all did our part.
It was good. We did well. We all did well.
Let's wash away our disappointment.
For today's penalty,
the three of the youngest members will each pick a member.
And those three members will face the penalty.
The youngest members will give the chosen members a stick.
(The members are forced to get a stick.)
A stick? Whom should I hit?
Gosh, that's a neat penalty.
I don't think I'll get picked, guys.
(Pretending to be close with them)
(We're close, aren't we?)
- Right? It's not me, right? - It's about time he gets one.
(It's about time he gets one.)
It's about time.
I didn't think the penalty would be that harsh.
When will you have the chance to hit Jong Kook if not today?
Everyone, his bottom is toned up.
He's been running and exercising.
Seok Jin is...
- getting lazy. He deserves a stick. - Seriously.
(Whispering)
Lazy? He said Seok Jin got lazy.
(My gosh, did you just call me lazy?)
Go for Jong Kook, you know? You know?
We will whisper.
(They'll whisper who will get the stick.)
- If that person's name is spoken, - Okay.
- you can just lie down. - Great.
I'll whisper, so others can't hear it.
- Great, great. - We'll have to pass it down?
(My choice is...)
Lie down.
(He reveals his choice right away.)
(Excuse me.)
- Lie down. - Jae Seok.
- Wasn't that meant for you? - You said I had to pass it down.
You lie down.
Jae Seok, please lie down.
- Should I relay this message? - This is funny.
It's my turn.
(So Min chooses...)
Lie down, please.
(Whispering)
(Whom did Se Chan choose?)
- Gosh, Se Chan... - What did he say?
Come here.
(Se Chan chooses Jae Seok.)
It wasn't Jong Kook?
It wasn't?
- It's me? - Lie down.
- Hold on. - Hadn't you pointed at me...
My goodness.
- I can't believe this. - I'll just do my share.
- Okay. - You were eliminated...
- because of him. - I got eliminated because of you.
- He left it at home. - That's nice.
(Slapping)
That must hurt.
Great.
(Slapping)
(It hurts.)
- It sounded nice too. - That must hurt.
(It's So Min's turn next.)
My goodness. That sounded nice.
Are you all right?
Come on.
(It's the grand finale, the finisher's turn.)
(Here comes the last stick!)
(Slapping hard)
(He slaps Jae Seok as much as he loves Jae Seok.)
(I'm fine as long as you youngest had fun.)
- That must hurt. - The sound was great.
- That was great. - My gosh.
- Se Chan, you did well. - Okay.
Today's victory goes to...
- the youngest members! - Okay!
(The counterattack of the youngest is a big success.)
(To celebrate spring, they have an orientation for new students.)
(At this friendly Running Man College,)
(3 new students show up.)
(Hong Jin Young, the master of trot)
I'm trying hard to approach people in a friendly and kind way.
(Han Da Gam, the beauty of Drama Department)
It's Keum Sae Rok.
(Keum Sae Rok, a newbie to variety shows)
(These new students' excitement explodes.)
(It's a collection of games only hip students play at school.)
(Oh, you know how to have fun.)
(But...)
A returning student?
(A clueless returning student is among these new students.)
(Who is this returning student that kills the mood?)
(Who released the orange fart?)
(You farted.)
(Farting)
(What's Wrong with My Class Year?)