(Last week)
(New Year Project: RPG Project, Level Up Project)
(When a member reaches Level 10, the member wins the race.)
(Forming clans is very important in completing the quests.)
(And last week, 4 clans have been formed.)
(Jong Kook and So Min, Seok Jin and Kwang Soo,)
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan, Jae Seok and Haha)
(Attention, members of Running Man!)
(Turn on the camera we gave you right now.)
(Are they receiving the instructions as the program airs?)
Turn the volume up.
Text one of the secrets of your clan to the main producer.
Let me see.
Secret?
(Text my clan's secret?)
(Text one of the secrets of your clan to the main producer.)
You will receive amazing benefits in the order the texts arrive.
What is that?
(The faster I text, the bigger the benefit is?)
My clan's secret?
Seok Jin... Seok Jin's secret?
(4 clans were formed last week.)
(Let's see. Ji Hyo's secret?)
- Hello? - Kwang Soo.
Wait. What is this?
Kwang Soo, tell me Ji Hyo's secret.
(He asks for a secret out of nowhere.)
Hey, Ji Hyo's existence itself is a secret.
How could I know her secret?
If I know her secret, would that be a secret?
But still, Kwang Soo.
Or should I ask her closest friend that I know of?
You should ask Seong Moon. Seong Moon.
(Yes, I can ask Seong Moon.)
Yes, I can do that.
Do you have his number?
- I'll text you his number. - Yes, please.
- Okay. - Okay.
(He acquires Ji Hyo's brother's phone number.)
Yes, I could ask Seong Moon.
Okay. I got one.
(He plans to text Se Chan late.)
While he waits for me to send him the number...
(He will text Seok Jin's secret before texting Se Chan.)
I should send Seok Jin's secret first.
My clan member, Kwang Soo.
(Which secret should I share?)
Gosh, I shouldn't share this.
Se Chan and I...
(The faster it is, the more advantageous it is.)
A mutual friend of Se Chan and I...
(Who shared which secret first?)
That mutual friend of us told me this.
What are you doing?
(Contemplating)
Hold on.
(At that time...)
Here it is.
(Did the first secret arrive?)
The first member to send a text message is...
(The 1st one to share a secret is...)
So Min.
(It is as expected.)
Jong Kook's secret is...
(She is the 1st one to text her clan member's secret.)
- Yes. - You have acquired...
80 dollars for the mission budget.
(She receives the highest budget, 80 dollars.)
- 80 dollars? Is that the highest? - Yes.
80 dollars are given to the first member.
Haha, you were the second member to text a secret.
(Haha was the 2nd member.)
You have acquired 70 dollars...
- for the mission budget. - 70 dollars?
You were the third member to send the text message, Ji Hyo.
You have acquired 60 dollars for the mission budget.
Really?
But you know what?
Se Chan might beat me to death.
(It's for exposing his secret.)
I'm in trouble.
(The order of the mission budgets goes as So Min, Haha,)
(Ji Hyo, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, Jae Seok, Se Chan, and Jong Kook.)
(The second day of Running Man Playing Game has dawned.)
(Jamsil Indoor Gymnasium)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hi. - Is this a press conference?
- What is this? - Hello.
What's going on here?
- Look at this. - I saw this coming.
- Kwang Soo will have it here. - No, no.
- Kwang Soo. - He'll hold the press conference.
- Make your official comment. - Gosh, you romantic.
What official comment?
- Hey, we're doing this for you. - No, no.
- Gosh, you romantic. - What official comment?
Hey, we're doing this for you.
- Hey, sit in the center. - Of course.
Come here. Sit in the middle.
- Come here. - Hello.
- Sit in the middle. - No, no.
- Why would I sit in the middle? - Hurry, and sit down.
(Why would I sit in the middle?)
I've never sat in the middle.
- What a sight. - Just sit next to Jae Seok now.
Sit down.
Sit in the middle.
- Sit down. - Take a seat.
Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
(It's gotten quiet all of a sudden.)
(Let's see...)
(How should we approach this subject?)
Yes, that's true. He's dating her.
- Yes! - Wait.
("His Close Friend Confirms the Relationship")
- Yes, they are dating now! - Congratulations.
He's the giraffe in love!
(Are they going to do it like this?)
She starred on Running Man as a guest.
- Right. - Lee Sun Bin and Kwang Soo...
- developed a special relationship. - My gosh.
How long have you two been dating?
- Please tell us how you feel now. - Why are we doing this now?
We're in the middle of our opening segment.
- Why are we doing this? - This is our opening segment.
- A lot of agencies came by the way. - Right.
As you can see,
there are SBS, SBS2,
- and another SBS agency. - They are all from SBS?
- SBS Plus. - SBS MTV.
- They are all from SBS. - Right.
- Actually, when I read the article, - Okay.
- I was the most worried about... - Okay.
(What was he worried about the most after reading the article?)
"Gosh, how am I going to get through Monday?"
That crossed my mind first.
(Monday is their day of shooting.)
I am going to overcome that big hardship.
- I see. - I braced myself.
- To talk more about this... - I'll overcome it.
Kwang Soo, I'm curious about how you must feel now.
- We'll listen to how you feel now. - Okay.
(Hesitant)
- We don't have time. Hurry. - Come on, tell us.
Thank you.
Are you dating her now? Do you love her?
- Is it true you two are dating? - When did it start?
- How much do you love her? - How long has it been?
(You should answer this.)
- Is it true you two are dating? - When did it start?
(They are full of curiosity.)
Ask one at a time!
(My gosh, ask one at a time!)
Attack me one at a time.
- We'll attack one at a time. - All right.
- I mean... - Right now,
- Let me deal with them one by one. - I'm sure you must have questions.
I have something to brag about.
- What is it? - Okay.
I was the one who brought them together.
(I was the one who brought them together.)
- What? - Really?
I was the one who gave the number.
- You did that, So Min? - You set them up together.
This proves that So Min and Kwang Soo's relationship...
- was strictly business. - That's right.
- It was strictly business. - That's right.
("Their Relationship Was Strictly Business")
- Please don't get the wrong idea. - Right.
All right. I'm sure you must have a lot of questions.
We'll ask questions one at a time.
This is for the viewers of Running Man,
fans who love our show,
- and viewers who were... - That's right.
- interested in Kwang Soo. - Yes, of course.
- They might not watch our shows, - That's true.
- but some are watching for this. - Of course.
That's the thing about these days. A long time ago...
Jae Seok, stop talking, and let him talk!
(Jae Seok, stop talking, and let him talk!)
(Please stop talking, Jae Seok!)
- Are they dating or not? - I agree!
- You got that right! - Hey, hey.
You don't have to.
- Okay. - I'm sorry.
- I like these scandals. - He's excited.
- Jae Seok is excited more than him. - He really likes these scandals.
- Jae Seok... He's excited. - He has to get the vibe going.
- Jae Seok is excited more than him. - I am...
really happy...
when something like this happens to...
- people around me. - Right.
- This is a happy occasion. - I'm so elated.
He was the one who was continuing the character of the playboy.
What will you do with that?
Will you hand over your character to Se Chan?
- I'd like to give it a try. - We...
(Feeling confident)
(I'll take that role.)
- She'll be the first female. - Right.
- Yes, So Min can pull it off. - I can do that.
- I think she can do it. - Yes, it works.
Actually, she might suit the character...
- better than Se Chan. - Yes, let me try that.
- It will suit her well. - She's a romantic too.
(Look forward to Lover Frog's endeavor.)
Great.
What did you do on your 100th day?
- That was sudden. - That was sudden.
(My 100th day with her?)
Jae Seok is leading the interview.
- Don't answer it. - Okay.
Tell him, no comment.
On your 100th day...
No comment. I heard that you do this too on your radio show.
I'm curious about your 100th day.
What did you do on that day?
Actually, both of us aren't big on celebrating anniversaries.
You should have told me. I would've given you 10 cents.
You give out 10 cents on 100th day?
(He can't believe his ears.)
- Gosh, that was so long time ago. - You should've told me.
We used to say that in elementary school.
Gosh, he's such an oldie.
Gosh, that was ages ago.
- I would've given you 10 cents. - What about the 22nd day?
- Jong Kook. - And your 22nd day.
- You gave 100 folded crane eggs. - Exactly.
We'll give you 70 cents to you later.
Just like we said earlier,
please tell us how you want this relationship to blossom.
- In the future? - Yes.
- Tell us about your plan. - Yes, tell us.
- There are many types of love. - Yes.
- Tell us what type of love it is. - What is your definition of love?
Okay.
A lot of people were interested in this and encouraged me.
Actually, love scandals can be...
Hey, let him talk.
(They are frustrated.)
Let him finish.
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy. - We didn't hear a thing from him.
We didn't hear a thing from him.
- I don't want you to misunderstand. - Okay.
- After two days, - That's true.
- people don't pay attention. - Right, right.
You shouldn't say something that might cause a misunderstanding.
- Okay. - The news didn't garner...
- that much attention though. - No, it didn't.
(Laughing)
All you need is love
(He takes the microphone all of a sudden.)
(Suddenly, he starts singing a love song.)
(What does Kwang Soo need now?)
Stop it! Please!
- I'm sorry! - All you need is love
(This is a festival! They can't hear a thing.)
(We support your love, Kwang Soo.)
(Gosh, these members.)
Love story!
(Every conversation ends with the topic of love.)
- Congratulations! - Congratulations!
Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
Congratulations on your new relationship.
(May your relationship last forever.)
All right. Next up is Haha, the father of three children.
My gosh, we should hear more about his story.
- Come here. - My gosh.
We have a lot of happy occasions today.
We finished Kwang Soo's story too quickly.
(Finally, I'm done.)
(Haha moves to the center after Kwang Soo.)
- Goodness. - This is nice.
- Haha was a real man! - No.
Real man, Haha!
- Hey, by the way... - I'm jealous.
(He received a lot of celebratory messages with his announcement.)
- Haha. - This is working fine.
Congratulations on your third pregnancy.
(Congratulations, Haha and Byul.)
- We ought to celebrate this. - At last,
- Seriously. - he's a father of many children.
- To be honest, the third baby... - I agree.
- is such a blessing. - That's right.
- It goes for first babies too. - Right.
- I see many couples... - Right.
with two kids around me.
Having three children or more...
- I'm really jealous. - That's so cool.
- He's so cool. - After finding out about the baby,
you were sorry to your wife.
Yes.
I made a promise to my wife.
I told her that she should be...
- where she belongs now. - That's right.
- I told her to sing again. - Byul...
(He wanted his wife to become a singer again.)
Actually, she belongs to the stage.
- That's right. - Including myself, the fans...
- are waiting for her to come back. - Right.
My gosh.
But...
I couldn't hold it back.
(But I couldn't hold it back.)
- What are you trying to say? - I mean...
(Thanks to his impatience, they received a blessing.)
- They love each other. - Pardon?
Have you thought about a baby name for your third child?
- The baby names became real names. - Yes, yes.
As for our second child,
we all thought that it'd be a girl.
That's why we named him Soul, and we just kept it.
- We have a good feeling about this. - What about your third child?
- We named the baby Song for now. - Song?
S-O-N-G. Song.
- Song? - Song?
- Dream, Soul, and Song. - Song.
- Ha Song. - Ha Song.
- That's so pretty. It's perfect. - The names are great.
- They come up with great names. - Haha is good at naming.
He's really good.
Anyway, congratulations.
(Let's wrap up.)
I love you.
(Is this it?)
Please be healthy.
Say something to Byul.
(The second story is wrapped up quickly.)
We will be happy and healthy.
Go back to your seat.
Go back.
- This is hilarious. - That was enough.
- So funny. - And then...
The winner of two awards,
Jong Kook.
Congratulations.
(Jong Kook won 2 awards for his variety shows in 2018.)
(He accepted the awards while hosting the ceremony.)
(It was his first Producer Award ever.)
(Shy)
(He finished the year as the choice of the producers.)
First of all,
Jong Kook...
received so much love...
from the viewers of "Mom's Diary" and Running Man.
- That's right. - Please say something to them.
Okay. The thing is,
I didn't give a good acceptance speech.
It looks like you have a title match coming up.
(He looks like an MMA fighter.)
Right.
UFC.
Do you have a title match?
Jong Kook will win!
(He will beat everyone.)
K-1.
Jong Kook always says...
it's not that he is not interested in getting married.
- He is. - Right.
- It's driving me crazy. - He always says that.
- Especially these days. - Let me ask you.
Are you interested in getting married this year?
I'm not sure if I can get married this year.
- You should start dating first. - I want to start dating.
- You want to meet someone. - You can get married later,
- but you should start dating. - I really want to...
meet someone this year.
Hopefully, I'll get married next year.
- Next year? - 2020?
Do you want to go on blind dates?
That would be a bit awkward.
You just want to meet someone.
- I want to meet someone by chance. - By chance.
You want to meet someone by chance.
Yes, I prefer that.
Here is someone too.
(I'm here.)
(What?)
- Should we switch seats? - Hold on.
Should we switch seats?
They met by chance.
It doesn't feel natural.
- It does. - No, it doesn't.
- It does. - No.
It does feel natural.
- It couldn't feel more natural. - But...
- it really feels natural. - It doesn't.
Anyway, Jong Kook,
- we hope you'll meet someone... - I'll try.
and fall in love this year.
(We hope your wishes come true.)
(I hope you meet someone nice.)
- Meet someone by chance. - Please meet someone.
- Next up is... - Next...
So Min.
Let's hear from her.
- So Min. - So Min.
When she accepted the Top Excellence Award...
(So Min won the Top Excellence Award.)
Her reaction was a bit over the top.
Did she really have no idea...
- or did she know? - "Can I really accept this?"
(Did you really have no idea?)
(So Min won the Top Excellence Award.)
Running Man, Jeon So Min. Congratulations.
(Me?)
(Crying)
(Sobbing)
(Her tearful speech...)
(surprised many people.)
I was really surprised.
I had never even imagined it.
I see.
I also felt I didn't deserve it...
because...
- You did well. - there were many others.
It's all thanks to Running Man.
Thank you.
I barely managed to win the award the previous year.
It took Seok Jin 20 years to win the Top Excellence Award.
She could have won the Excellence Award first.
Two days later,
I was shooting something.
Suddenly, I got a call from Seok Jin.
- He rarely calls me. - Why did he call?
I was a bit curious. When I answered, he said,
"Congratulations on winning the award."
- Suddenly? - I was so surprised.
I asked, "Are you in a shoot right now?"
That hurt my feelings.
She asked me if I was in a shoot.
It just wasn't like him.
He was speaking with his TV voice.
- His voice itself... - He used words he doesn't use.
It's easy to tell.
I didn't get to congratulate So Min at the ceremony,
- That's why. - but I really wanted to.
I didn't get a chance at the ceremony.
We had a mission yesterday, right?
I called Seok Jin while filming myself.
"Hello."
"Isn't this Seok Jin's number?"
"Yes. What's the matter?"
"Is something wrong?"
"Is the camera rolling right now?"
"Yes." "Hi, Kwang Soo."
(His TV voice is back.)
(His TV attitude is on.)
"What's up?"
(I did that?)
(Last night, they were given individual missions.)
Hello.
Where are you?
I'm home.
Why do you sound so cold?
(Is the camera rolling right now?)
Yes.
Hi, Kwang Soo.
(Hi, Kwang Soo.)
(His TV attitude is on.)
(He hurriedly picks up his camera.)
Your voice changed so fast.
- I mean... - Hey.
I'm so surprised. Gosh.
I'm sweating.
(His voice changes according to the situation.)
Seriously,
- it gave me goosebumps. - Seok Jin is...
- I was so surprised. - Seok Jin is...
(Seok Jin would do that.)
- Seriously. - He is...
(Please make us laugh for a long time.)
He is the worst.
So Min, congratulations again.
Top Excellence Award.
("Running News" will come back at the end of the year.)
Today's race.
2019 Level Up Race, Part 2.
Protect the Secrets.
Protect the Secrets?
Protect the secrets of your clan...
until the end of the race,
and you win prize money.
Fail to protect either secret,
and you will be penalized.
At the end of every round,
additional mission money will be distributed.
With the budget, you can buy a level.
(You can buy a level you want.)
- So it's important to have money. - You can buy a level?
- It's important. - The more money, the better.
- Do a good job. - Jae Seok.
You don't want your secret to be revealed.
Some of the secrets can really hurt you.
- But... - So...
I was serious. I was in a hurry.
Let's protect the secrets.
(Coming up)
(The disclosure war begins.)
(Disclose or protect the secrets.)
(The clan members fall into temptation.)
(How will the disclosure war end?)
(The first quest)
- Basketball... - It's been a long time.
Here is the first mission.
The Last Match.
We have special guests...
- who will play a game with you. - What?
- We have guests? - Is it a basketball match?
No way.
KBL All-Stars, please come out.
Seriously?
- Really? - Really?
Really?
(Really? Unbelievable!)
They are here?
Today, All-Stars will have...
a special match with you.
- Really? - They're here.
Changwon LG Sakers, Kim Jong Kyu.
He is so tall.
(Light steps...)
(followed by a dunk)
(He makes a dunk look so easy.)
He did a dunk.
I've never seen it in real life.
(Kim Jong Kyu)
Incheon Electroland Elephants,
Park Chan Hee.
(He is handsome.)
All-Stars.
He is handsome.
(Fancy feet...)
(finished with a neat lay-up)
(He is amazing.)
- He is good-looking! - That was beautiful.
(Park Chan Hee, guard of the national team)
Nice to meet you.
That was beautiful.
Anyang KGC,
Yang Hee Jong.
He is handsome.
- Mr. Yang! - A three-pointer.
Will it go in?
(He pulls off a 3-pointer.)
(Amazed)
(Yang Hee Jong, forward of the national team)
Seoul Samsung Thunders,
Lee Kwan Hee.
(Lee Kwan Hee)
- He looks amazing. - Another three-pointer?
He looks amazing.
(3-pointer)
(The ball flew in an arc.)
It didn't go in.
(No goal)
Okay!
Lee Kwan Hee.
(He must be nervous.)
Okay! It's okay.
(He tries again and succeeds.)
He's handsome.
(Lee Kwan Hee, Korea's 3rd-highest scorer)
Please come to the center.
Hello.
(He gestures to So Min.)
(You distracted me, so I couldn't score.)
(So Min takes notice of him too.)
So Min looks happy.
He's so handsome.
Busan KT Sonicboom,
Yang Hong Seok.
(Yang Hong Seok)
(He is cute.)
They're all so tall.
A dunk.
(After showing off his skills, he shoots the ball.)
(No goal)
A lay-up.
(Following Lee Kwan Hee, Yang Hong Seok fails too.)
It didn't go in.
(Poor guy.)
(I'm relieved.)
(Super rookie Yang Hong Seok)
Yang! We have many Yangs today.
Wonju DB Promy, Marcus Foster.
(Marcus Foster)
Foster.
He looks amazing.
(He is KBL's best 3-point shooter, but today...)
(He flies up...)
(and dunks the ball.)
(Is he made of rubber or something?)
Amazing.
(Marcus Foster, amazing dunker and 3-point shooter)
KBL All-Stars. Let's give them a big hand.
(Their passion heats up the winter.)
(6 KBL All-Stars)
This is incredible.
Ji Hyo and So Min...
- The two of them are... - They're in love.
They're going crazy.
One of the players must have stolen her heart.
I'm sure.
You all normally play on different teams.
Why are you gathered together?
There will be an All-Star Game in Changwon soon.
As the hottest players of each team...
(We are the hottest players.)
We were chosen...
- You just called yourself... - He said it himself.
He called himself hot.
- It's not easy. - I love it.
You are the hottest players.
- He is handsome. - They are hot.
They look really amazing.
He looks like Beenzino.
- Right. - He's handsome.
He's attractive.
Kwan Hee, please say something.
I'm a fan of two of you.
- Who? - Who?
(Two?)
(So Min and Ji Hyo?)
Who are they?
So Min and...
(I'm sure it's me.)
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin?
(Kwan Hee loves Seok Jin.)
- That's unexpected. - Why?
- I thought it'd be Ji Hyo. - Exactly.
I thought it'd be those two.
- Ji Hyo... - I mean...
I don't like that I was chosen along with Seok Jin.
Be quiet.
Why... I understand So Min,
- but why Seok Jin? - His taste...
He is the perfect example of...
"The one who survives is the strongest."
He exemplifies it.
I don't really like people like Jae Seok.
- Why? - Why?
It'd be too hard to live like him.
- It's not easy. - He's realistic.
It's not easy to live as Yu Jae Seok.
The one who survives longest is the strongest.
Why do you like So Min?
- She is so cheerful. - Cheerful.
She's tucking her hair behind her ears.
So Min is looking for someone to date.
- It's true. - It's true.
- They look cute together. - They look cute together.
- Stand next to him. - Stand next to him.
- Stand next to him. - They look cute together.
(Pretending to be shy, she stands next to him.)
She is our playgirl.
- Playgirl. - Okay.
She is blushing.
Go back to your position now.
Good luck, So Min.
Foster was voted as an All-Star by fans.
How does he feel?
Jae Seok is not good at English.
- I'm not good. - In this global age.
I'd love to be able to talk to him.
Korean, no?
- No. - "Korean, no"?
English, okay?
- Yes, perfect. - English, okay?
- Handsome guy. - Thank you.
- And I said he's my role model. - You like that?
- You like that? - I liked that.
- You like it? - My role model.
He likes it.
It's not easy to say something like that.
But Seok Jin can do it.
The players will randomly pick a number.
- Randomly? - Yes.
You can shoot a ball as many times as the number you pick.
If you pick 3, you can shoot 3 times.
- If you pick 1, only once. - Okay.
Pick a number.
- 3 would be the best. - 3 would be the best.
- I'll take the remaining one. - Hong Seok.
- He is just like me. - That's right.
- Kwan Hee. - I can't wait.
Let's see Kwan Hee's number first.
- What's the number? - Hey.
- It's 1. - I don't need 3 chances.
I just need one.
Just like Seok Jin,
- He is like me. - he is unlucky.
(The numbers of chances have been determined.)
The numbers of chances have been determined.
It's time to recruit players.
The starting bid is determined by the number of chances.
Through a draft, recruit players.
The players will shoot balls.
Every time a player scores,
his team wins 10 dollars.
- First... - This is crazy.
Yang Hong Seok.
He has 3 chances. We should bid 20 dollars.
- Do you score every time? - Yes.
The starting bid is five dollars.
Let's say you recruit him for five dollars...
and he scores. Then you get 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars. - We bid 5 dollars.
- Good. - Five dollars.
- Eight. - Hey.
- Talk to me first. - Eight.
- 10. - 10.
Then you will break even.
- You'll break even. - Hold on. We'll just break even.
- 1... - 12 dollars!
- Then we'll lose money. - 12 dollars.
(Even if he scores, they'll lose money.)
- 12 dollars. - We'll lose money.
- I'm relieved. - Hold on.
- Hold on. - They'll lose money.
- We win only 10 dollars. - 5, 4,
- 3, 2, - Cancel it.
one. Ji Hyo.
- You win. - Hold on.
We'll lose money.
- She wants to... - What are you doing?
Are you interested in him or something?
If Hong Seok scores, the team wins 10 dollars.
But he was recruited for 12 dollars.
Next up is Yang Hee Jong.
- KBL's big brother. - It's a stable number.
Hee Jong has 2 chances. The starting bid is 10 dollars.
- Two chances. - All right.
- It's driving me crazy. - Let's start at 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars. - 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars. - 13.
- 19. - 19.
If he scores twice, you get a dollar.
It's better than nothing.
- 5, 4, 3... - What is this?
- 2... - 19? Gosh.
- 20. - Okay!
- 5... - 22!
- Hey. - 22 dollars.
- It's my last offer. - four,
3, 2, 1. Okay.
Why do we want to lose money?
Next up is Lee Kwan Hee.
Kwan Hee.
Let's start. The bidding starts.
- 5 dollars. - 5,
- 4... - 7 dollars.
- 9. - 9.
- 5... - 15.
15?
(Love?)
(Let me buy it for 15 dollars.)
- 5, 4... - It's personal, isn't it?
- 3, 2, 1. - It's getting personal.
- 15 dollars? - Okay. 15 dollars.
Okay!
- Why did I say 15 dollars? - It was...
- I could have said 10 dollars. - too obvious.
- You'll lose five dollars. - What is this?
Why are we even doing this?
He will succeed.
I believe he'll score.
- Next up is Park Chan Hee. - Good.
- All right. - 11 dollars.
11 dollars. We have to.
- We have to. - 5, 4, 3...
- 15. - 15.
- 5... - 17.
17. 5, 4... Let's speed things up.
3, 2, 1.
- 17 dollars. - Okay.
We'll make money for the first time.
- Next up is Foster. - Foster.
- Hey! Come on! - Come on!
- Come on! - Foster.
Can you please show us a dunk?
- Dunk, please. - Dunk?
- Yes. - Dunk.
Here we go.
(This is...)
(how you dunk a ball.)
(Textbook dunk)
(His price rises.)
Foster. Let's start.
He has three chances.
- Start. - 20.
- 25. - Let's slow down a bit.
- 27. - 30.
- 30. - 31.
- 31. - 5, 4, 3,
2, 1. Foster.
- Okay. - Okay.
They will lose so much money.
What is this?
If Kwan Hee fails, you will go bankrupt.
- They will lose money. - Right?
Lastly, Kim Jong Kyu. Let's start right away.
16.
- 17. - 18.
- 19. - 20.
- 30. - Stop it!
- 30. - 31.
- 31. - 32.
- 33. - Seriously?
- Why does everyone want to lose? - 5, 4,
3, 2,
1. No 35?
All right. He comes to our team.
(The recruitment is finished.)
- We have to succeed every time. - We have the best one.
All success.
The quest begins.
Avoid white hoops and win the mission money.
You can only shoot the balls you chose.
Also, as long as you stay inside the lines,
you can shoot any way you want.
- You can run up if you want. - It doesn't matter?
- You can also shoot where you are. - Okay.
Let's start from the clans with two players.
- Okay! - Park Chan Hee.
Park Chan Hee!
- Chan Hee! - Let's go, Chan Hee!
(1st try out of 2)
Please. The white hoops.
(Can he avoid the white hoops...)
(and win his team 10 dollars?)
Yes!
(It didn't go into the white hoops.)
(He is so exhilarated that his veins stick out.)
- I'm so relieved. - He's so happy.
He's so happy. Okay.
You have one more chance.
One more.
Basketballs are easy to score with.
Go into the white hoops.
- All right. Park Chan Hee! - Fail!
That would be funny.
Okay!
(Goal)
Park Chan Hee.
(This is the guard of the national team.)
(He was recruited for 17 dollars.)
We win 20 dollars.
- 20 dollars. Next. - I'm looking forward to it.
- Kim Jong Kyu. - Let's go!
- You can do this! - White hoops!
- Okay! - Please.
Please. Kim Jong Kyu!
Red hoops.
(The ball bounces off a red hoop.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(I aimed at it.)
(No goal)
It's okay.
- White! - White!
- Bounce. - White.
Bounce into a white hoop.
(I never fail twice.)
(His second attempt was a success.)
He shoots where he aims.
You never know.
Let's go!
Let's go, Changwon!
(He scores twice in a row.)
- Amazing. - Good job.
- That was close. - Okay.
Let's move on to the team with rubber gloves.
It'd be a miracle to score by shooting rubber gloves.
We'll do it the Michael Jordan way.
See if he steps over the line.
- It's okay. - If he does, he's out.
(Without any practice,)
(will he turn his one chance into a miracle?)
(No way, the ball went in.)
My goodness.
Hurry and hit my shoulder.
(Is it an expression of love?)
(He meets So Min's expectation and scores.)
That was amazing.
(Even his role model Seok Jin approves.)
(He makes it in one go.)
- That was great. - Next is...
Foster.
(The second player is Foster.)
- You can do it. - It's okay.
- He was the most popular. - It's okay.
Will it be a dunk?
What's going on?
(The ball reaches the hoop.)
(It goes in between...)
(a white and a red hoop.)
(Will it go in a white hoop?)
He made it.
(It barely goes into a red hoop.)
- It went in. - It did.
It went in.
(No way.)
It's unbelievable.
- Goodness. - It's unbelievable.
- Two more. - You can do it.
How is this possible?
Is it the white one?
(He aims the same hoop and makes it.)
(What's going on?)
This is unbelievable.
- One more. - Do it one more time.
(He's worth selecting after all.)
- He made it to the same hoop. - He looks so innocent.
- It's interesting. - He's better at it than basketball.
- He's better at it than basketball. - Let's see.
(He makes it into the same hoop three times.)
Unbelievable.
(You're going to make us look bad now.)
No way. How is this possible?
This is amazing.
Next is Yang Hee Jong.
- Dried pollack... - Yang Hee Jong.
- Yang Hee Jong. - Please.
Seriously, he's a KBL All-Star.
- Dried pollack is too harsh. - I'm sorry, sir.
Isn't it harsh?
- You can do it. - You can do it.
Let's go, Hee Jong.
You're our team's hope.
(Dried pollack)
(Fly and go into a red hoop.)
(Tap)
Oh, this is bad.
- Okay. - It's out.
(He fails his first dried pollack shoot.)
(He's never felt sorry by not making a pollack into the goal.)
Couldn't you run and throw?
(Don't stand still.)
Stay back.
Why are you complaining?
Can't you jump?
- Give me some time. - White.
- White, white. - White, white.
It'll be amazing if he makes it into a white one.
- It will be incredible. - White hoop.
- Hee Jong. - White hoop.
(His reputation as a national team basketball player is at stake.)
(He will recover his honor with a great shot.)
(It definitely goes into a white hoop.)
(He loses 10 dollars.)
(He wants to run away.)
(Can we get a refund on this guy?)
(They're stupefied.)
- Okay. - That's amazing.
Goodness.
(His pride is shattered.)
That's what happens when anyone joins our team.
Come on.
- It's so strange. - Isn't he a living legend?
Seriously.
- He is a legend. - Then what happened?
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo lose 22 and 10 dollars.)
Let's start again.
- Hong Seok. - Unfortunately, they get one shot.
Bounce, bounce, bounce, white hoop.
(Please bounce and make it to a white hoop.)
(He gets only one chance.)
(A rookie star player throws with confidence.)
What's going on?
(Please go in.)
(It bounces off from the hoop.)
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan earn nothing.)
- That's too bad. - It can't be helped.
(Current mission budget status)
- It's over. - It's over.
After every round,
you get a chance to level up.
Originally, we were planning to give it to the one team that won.
- Do we get one more chance? - Therefore,
Clan Jae Seok and Clan Jong Kook...
- will compete to decide the winner. - By one shot?
I bet Jae Seok and Jong Kook's basketball skills are similar.
- Start. - Start.
(Jae Seok goes first.)
(He throws it while hoping to raise his level.)
(Bouncing off)
(Unfortunately, he doesn't make it.)
This is a sudden death match, right?
If he doesn't make it, you get one more chance.
Do we win if he makes it into a white hoop?
- Yes. - Then we will win.
If it goes into a white hoop, we win.
Don't shoot it into a white one.
- White, white. - Block Jong Kook.
(He throws it with force.)
White hoop.
(It goes in between two red hoops.)
(It hits the backboard and goes into a white hoop.)
(Unbelievable)
(Jae Seok and Haha place first.)
(The Last Match quest is over. Please check the result.)
(We thank the KBL All-Stars for joining us.)
(Jae Seok, Haha place first. Jong Kook, So Min place second.)
The Secret Room quest has become available.
- That's amazing. - What?
What is it this time?
(What's the quest this time?)
Jae Seok and Haha are winners of the first round.
You must choose a secret room each.
(The same clan members must enter different rooms.)
One each?
I guess only one of them can level up.
They must choose wisely.
I guess only one of us can level up.
(What's the secret in the secret room?)
- See you later. - Okay.
(Jae Seok chooses Room A.)
What's this?
(There's a mysterious mission card in the room.)
This is a level-up quest.
Once you reveal the secret of your clan,
you can level up by one.
Will you reveal the secret?
You can level up by one.
- This is harsh. - Will you do it?
Is it starting already?
What happens when I reveal it?
Will he find out...
- about it? - He might be able to guess that.
Our goal is keeping the secrets hidden until the end, right?
- Is that how we can win? - Yes.
(Clan members' secrets must be kept.)
(That's how you win the prize.)
(There's also a mission given to Haha.)
(He's deep in thought.)
(Will it be the clan's victory or raising his own level?)
(What will Jae Seok choose?)
I'll keep the secret hidden.
(Will you reveal your clan's secret?)
Even if I do decide to betray him, it has to be bigger than this.
We just got started.
(He decides to keep the secret.)
(He looks at the bigger picture.)
All right, may I go out?
(Jae Seok's level remains as 1.)
(They meet after making a choice.)
- You didn't, did you? - I knew it.
Of course not.
- Are you wearing the badge? - Yes.
(Are you wearing the badge?)
(Did you reveal the secret and raise your level?)
Do you want to die?
- What do you mean? - Did you reveal it?
Wait.
(He checks the level badge.)
What's wrong?
What?
(After coming out of the secret room, his level went up.)
Mister.
- What? - Did you reveal it?
I didn't reveal it.
You should look at the bigger picture.
Mine was different from yours.
They told me to eat honey rice cakes.
- Wouldn't you have done the same? - I get how it is.
- Fine, I got it. - Honey rice cakes.
- How could you reveal it? - I'd eat any day.
- They're back. - They are here.
Haha looks happy.
Jae Seok doesn't.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
"Will you reveal the secret or not?"
He revealed it, didn't he?
I didn't.
- No, I didn't. - Hey.
I had honey rice cakes.
- Hey, forget it. - I had...
- honey rice cakes. - Forget it.
- I didn't reveal anything. - Stop it.
What did I reveal?
- This is unfair. - Goodness.
- Watch it later on TV. - Stop it.
- Make sure to watch it. - Stop it.
- I swear. - Stop it.
- I really didn't. - Haha.
You'll find out when you watch it.
You'll find out when you do.
(You will advance to the next mission.)
(Location of the next quest)
I think there are secret rooms.
(A quest has been discovered.)
For this round,
4 clans will pick 1 guest each.
A guest will join each clan.
- Really? - They'll help you level up.
Here are the four guests.
Who are they?
(You could level up depending on who you recruit.)
(Who are the guests for this quest?)
- It's Seung Yoon. - Seung Yoon is here.
(Kang Seung Yoon with million reasons for his popularity)
Have you been well?
- How are you? - Millions.
(Lee Seung Hoon with million reasons for his popularity)
(Whenever they release an album, they top the music charts.)
(They are sweeping the charts with "Millions".)
(Seung Yoon and Seung Hoon of Winner)
- Come on. - Hello.
It's been a long time.
Have you been well?
(It's Seung Yoon's return, but it's Seung Hoon's first time.)
- Have you been well? - Hello.
Today is great.
- We are all guys, so... - Don't worry.
I thought you wouldn't like it.
(Not all guests have arrived.)
(Who are the other guests?)
We are all guys, so...
It's Chungha.
(Chungha)
Turn it around, 12 o'clock
(Kim Do Yeon, the face of Weki Meki)
(They worked together for a year as I.O.I.)
(Chungha became a solo artist, and Do Yeon joined Weki Meki.)
(They are doing well individually.)
- Come this way. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
(It's nice to meet you.)
Some are popular, and some are getting popular.
We invited these four as our guests.
(Seung Hoon, Seung Yoon, Chungha, and Do Yeon)
I heard Do Yeon wanted to be on Running Man.
I wanted to ever since I was part of I.O.I.
I wanted to,
but I couldn't.
If you had come then,
Kwang Soo would have welcomed you with so much warmth.
I know.
- Oh, right. - I still welcome her.
I still do.
(I felt welcomed.)
In the past, Kwang Soo would make acrostic poems...
with Do Yeon or Chungha's name.
Things are different now. It's unfortunate.
Why don't you make a poem with Chungha?
Yes, go ahead.
- Will you try with Chungha? - Okay.
Chungha.
"Chung".
Cheonggukjang.
(Cheonggukjang)
(What will he say after cheonggukjang?)
"Chung".
Cheonggukjang.
"Ha".
One serving please.
(One order of cheonggukjang please.)
(Satisfied)
That was funny.
(His poem satisfies young people these days.)
It was...
It was very...
- He let it go. - It's fun.
- He let go of his ego. - It's fun.
This is how you should act.
- Okay. - Exclude love from it.
- I'm trying. - When you exclude love,
your acrostic poems become simple and clean.
This is great.
(I like your simple and clean acrostic poems.)
- Se Chan. - Yes?
Can you make an acrostic poem?
- Make it with Chungha. - Chungha.
Really? Okay.
"Chung".
On Chungha's face.
(On Chungha's face)
(What about my face?)
- "Ha". - I see some of Haha.
(I see some of Haha.)
(There's Haha in Chungha.)
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I was in a hurry.
I prepared it in a hurry. I'm sorry.
(Don't misunderstand, Chungha.)
- That was good. - I'm sorry, Chungha.
It just happened.
It was good.
I'm sorry.
- Okay. - I never thought of that.
(They make good acrostic poems.)
- That was good. - Let's welcome...
Seung Hoon and Seung Yoon of Winner.
They do well every time they release an album.
- Just yesterday, - Yes?
we topped the charts for the fifth time.
(Winner tops the charts with "Millions" for the fifth time.)
That's impressive.
- For the fifth time? - We're happy.
Since they're here, shouldn't we listen to their song?
- Let's watch. - I want to see it.
I want to see it.
It's been a while since Do Yeon and Chungha had been here.
Let's start with "Gotta Go".
Then we'll hear "Millions".
Lastly, we'll hear I.O.I's song.
(Last is "Pick Me".)
- I.O.I. - This is great.
("Gotta Go", "Millions" and "Pick Me")
("Gotta Go" by Chungha)
(12 o'clock with defined moves)
(She shows midnight with her whole body.)
(Defined moves and groove)
(Every detail is perfect.)
(It's a human clock.)
(The clock is key.)
(Energetic)
(Sexy waves)
- That's amazing. - She's like a different person.
(Her presence is powerful even when dancing alone.)
(The clock dance and the waves are key.)
I love this part.
(She falls in love.)
(Please love my song, "Gotta Go".)
(Oh no, it's already midnight.)
This is how it goes.
- The last part was... - You were amazing.
- Thank you. - 12 o'clock.
This was great.
- This is how we used to do it. - Right.
(In 2019, the movement goes up.)
This is different.
(Going up is what's trendy now.)
Next is Winner.
- Winner. - Let's hear "Millions".
(Here's "Millions" by Winner.)
("Millions" by Winner)
(Cute)
(Cute feeling)
(They express the excitement of young boys in love.)
- Their dancing is so catchy. - It really is.
- You're doing well. - This is great.
(It's so good.)
(It's a delicious dance by Winner.)
- It's so delicious. - It really is.
(They dance so well.)
(Winner is a tasty restaurant of dance.)
They dance in a delicious way.
- Thank you. - It looked so delicious.
It goes like this.
- It was sweet. - Like this.
- That was great. - It was sweet.
- It was delicious. - It was sweet.
- Your dance was sweet. - Like a tasty restaurant?
- We enjoyed it. - It's a tasty restaurant.
Did you hear what Seung Hoon said?
I said their dance was sweet.
"It's a tasty restaurant."
Call us Michelin of idol singers.
Their dance is sweet.
It's sweet indeed.
- Finally... - I.O.I.
let's hear "Pick Me".
- "Pick Me"? - It's I.O.I.
(It's a popular song by I.O.I.)
This is insane.
(Let's go back to 2015.)
("Pick Me" by I.O.I)
(They reenact the dance perfectly.)
(Their well-coordinated dance hasn't changed.)
They're back.
(It's been a while.)
(We're also a tasty restaurant of dance.)
This is amazing.
(It brings back memories.)
It's been such a long time.
(Their bodies remember.)
(It's the same angle and turn.)
(The turning is perfect.)
This is it.
(Neither of them forgot the dance.)
(It's been a warm up until now.)
Let's go. Here they go.
(Here comes the insane highlight that shook the country.)
Let's go.
(Prepare your fingers.)
(Start poking!)
Come on.
(Everyone pokes.)
(They get drunk on "Pick Me".)
(I.O.I dance isn't finished yet.)
(It's everyone's favorite crab leg dance.)
This is it.
That's amazing.
(She still has the arm spin.)
(Copy and paste)
(They leave the frame as they dance.)
(Haha is out of it.)
(They finish reenacting "Pick Me".)
That was great.
(It's an addicting dance.)
They dance well.
I remember how moving it was back then.
- How do they turn them? - That's amazing.
How do they do it?
- You can do it too. - I can?
Did I do it?
- What? - That's amazing.
You looked great like an idol singer.
- Did I do it? - You look like an idol singer.
- Did I do it? - That was amazing.
Try it, Jae Seok.
(They succeed in teasing him.)
- He can do it. - I don't know.
Are you taking classes?
- No. - Look at him.
They dance so deliciously.
- It's sweet. - I know.
We're a tasty restaurant.
They're a tasty restaurant indeed.
What do we do now?
Here's your second mission where you can earn mission money.
Door is Falling from the Sky.
A representative from each team reads a different song title.
He or she explains the song by dancing.
The remaining two members guess the correct title to win.
Every time you guess correctly,
doors of other teams are lowered.
(The team whose door is lowered to the bottom loses.)
Tall people have a disadvantage.
All four of them dance well.
Right.
Among four guests, clans may pick...
one each.
- Seung Hoon. - Really?
- Yes. - Do you pick Seung Hoon?
Okay.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo pick Chungha.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Seung Yoon is good. - He dances well.
Seung Yoon is great. Okay.
(Jae Seok, Haha, Do Yeon versus Jong Kook, So Min, and Seung Hoon)
(Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Chungha versus Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and Seung Yoon)
I'm confident about this.
Okay.
- Do we guess the answer? - Seriously.
Doors of other teams come down...
- when we guess correctly. - Let's go. Get ready.
Start.
(Round 1 starts.)
(They start to dance.)
(Do you know the gun shooting dance?)
(They must guess the singer and the song title.)
What is it?
("Gashina" by SUNMI)
(It made everyone shoot guns.)
(She reenacts the key movement perfectly.)
What is it by SUNMI?
"Siren"? What was it?
What was it called?
(Jae Seok and Haha can't remember the song title.)
(Seung Hoon is also dancing.)
(Isn't this dance what I think it is?)
It's...
("DDU-DU DDU-DU" by BLACKPINK)
(The dance is similar, but it has a different energy.)
- Isn't it "DDU-DU DDU-DU"? - What was it?
"DDU-DU DDU-DU" by BLACKPINK.
That's correct.
(As they answer, Jae Seok and Haha's door lowers.)
(The door is lowered.)
What was it?
When they answer correctly, it comes down.
Poor Do Yeon.
What was it?
- What was it? - I can't remember the title.
- "Gashina". - "Gashina".
(Jong Kook and So Min's door goes down.)
It's "DDU-DU DDU-DU".
(I'm confident about this too.)
- It's "Candy" by H.O.T. - "Candy".
This team is doing so well.
(Jong Kook, So Min, and Seung Hoon are doing well.)
(The other team's door is lowered to the second level.)
Take off your shoes.
(The door is way too low.)
(I know this song.)
- I know. - What was it?
- It's by Rain. - Rain.
It's by Rain.
- What was the song? - What was it?
(Come on, it's "Rainism".)
- "It's Raining" by Rain. - "It's Raining".
- Isn't it? - "3!4!".
3, 4.
It's by Roo'ra.
("3!4!" by Roo'ra is correct.)
- Roo'ra. - "3!4!".
(My clan is doing well.)
- I know. - Cheer up, baby
("CHEER UP" by TWICE is correct.)
- Cheer up, baby - "It's Raining".
(The door is lowered.)
(It hits his head.)
When did it come down? Isn't it "It's Raining"?
- "It's Raining"? - "Bad Boy".
"Bad Boy".
- Is it "Cheer Up, Baby"? - Guess the answer.
Take off your shoes.
Take off your shoes, Do Yeon.
"10 Out of 10".
- "10 Out of 10". - That's correct.
Do Yeon is taking off her heels.
Take off your shoes, Seung Hoon.
Pass.
(Look at my heart.)
- "My Heart"... - "Like Being Shot By A Gun".
- It's not. - What is it?
"My Heart"?
- What is it? - Are you cold?
(His heart beats.)
(We know what it is immediately.)
- I know. - I understood.
- That's it. - That's a good expression.
(Don't you know what it is?)
- "My Heart Breaks"? - "Heart Flutters".
- "Heart Attack". - "Heart Attack".
("Heart Attack" by AOA is correct.)
That's right.
What is it? Wait.
Pass.
(She passes "Into the New World".)
(Next is "Adult Ceremony" by Park Ji Yoon)
(The sexy wave is key.)
That?
- I know. It's "Adult Ceremony". - Right.
- "Adult Ceremony" by Park Ji Yoon. - "Adult Ceremony" by Park Ji Yoon.
(It's impossible to stand up.)
What is it?
- What was it? - "Bo Peep Bo Peep"?
"Hot"?
- "So Hot". - "So Hot" by Wonder Girls.
(Lowering)
(She can't even sit down.)
(She gets up and moves her feet.)
I know it. What is it?
(The feet dance is the signature movement of "Alone".)
What is it? Oh, SISTAR!
- It's SISTAR's... - It's "Alone".
I eat all alone
- It's "Alone". - You're right.
It's "Alone".
(This side moves down too as Jae Seok answers correctly.)
- Girls' Generation. - Yes. What was that song's name?
- Girls' Generation. - From where was the arrow dance?
- It's "Hoot". - Right, it's "Hoot".
- Now... - I spend the night alone
- Miss A. Yes or no? - Miss A.
- It's "Bad Girl, Good Girl". - Oh, "Bad Girl, Good Girl".
(She gets completely pressed down by the other team's answer.)
- What? - "Bad Girl, Good Girl".
- "Bad Girl, Good Girl". - What is that?
- They're good. - Please. What should we do?
It's such a close match.
- Are you running? - Are you looking and running?
Are you looking and running?
- I know. It's Wonder Girls. - Are you looking and running?
(Which clan will be the first to shout out the answer?)
- Are you running? - Are you looking and running?
Are you looking and running?
- I know. It's Wonder Girls. - Are you looking and running?
(The left team isn't sure, but the right team got Wonder Girls.)
(Jae Seok and Haha only need to guess the title to win.)
- "Tell Me". - It's this. "Tell Me".
(Jae Seok, Haha, and Do Yeon win.)
Okay. We won.
- That's a relief. - My goodness.
(The door comes down to the last level.)
(He feels sad.)
Hey, it's okay. You did well.
He did well.
- He did really well. - There were many correct answers.
(Jae Seok, Haha, and Do Yeon win.)
- I hope I do it well. - If we lose, it'll be our fault.
- You can do it! - Let's do it!
- Let's win! - Let go!
Let's begin. Get ready.
(Round 2 starts.)
("TT" by TWICE)
- "TT". - "TT".
(The door gets lowered.)
(It's right above me.)
- "Goodbye" by Hong Jin Young. - It's "Goodbye".
("Like a Cat" by AOA)
(He mouths the lyrics.)
- "Like a Cat" by AOA! - "Like a Cat".
Hey, you can't mouth it.
- He mouthed it. - That's a bit too much.
What are you talking about? Nonsense.
Don't mouth it.
("Mr. Chu" by Apink)
"Mr. Chu" by Apink!
(He shouts out the answer very correctly.)
You know Apink indeed.
You know everything about Apink.
(Chungha's door got lowered a lot.)
("Up and Down" by EXID)
- "Up and Down"! - "Up and Down".
Hurry up. Give us the next one!
Just give us the next one!
- Do what you can with the title. - Try anything you can.
- That's difficult. - My goodness.
("We Are the Future" by H.O.T.)
(This song was released in 1997 when Seung Yoon was 4 years old.)
Just try what you can. That's right.
(Since I don't know the song, I'll mouth the lyrics.)
It's "We Are the Future" by H.O.T.
Gosh, how did you get this one?
- My gosh. - It's like he's watching TV.
This is all that I remember.
We're sorry, Chungha!
We're very sorry, Chungha!
- We don't know. - I can't get it at all.
Look at Chungha. She's suffering because of her bad team.
(This side is relaxed because of his good team.)
(This is easy. I can do this.)
("Really Really" by Winner)
(This is our dance.)
It's "Really Really" by Winner!
(Chungha's door falls down to the last stage by his answer.)
Chungha, are you okay?
(I couldn't even start the dance.)
- Chungha, are you okay? - Chungha.
(Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, and Chungha lose.)
- Seung Yoon. - Seung Yoon, you did great.
- We got so many correct. - You did really great.
Chungha, you're going through so much.
This is so...
Why can't you get the answers?
Let's go to the finals.
- Let's go to the finals. - Let go.
(Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and Seung Yoon win.)
When Seung Yoon was in a rush earlier,
(We saw that, Seung Yoon.)
(It was a parade of lip syncs.)
(Good one.)
Why did you do that?
- Let's do this. - We can do this!
- I feel great. - Let's go, Do Yeon.
Their team won once already.
Get ready!
(The finals start.)
(The skilled dance moves are fit for the finals.)
- It's BigBang. - "Bang Bang Bang".
- "Bang Bang Bang". - "Bang Bang Bang" by BigBang.
- You're right! - It's "Bang Bang Bang".
(We need to hurry.)
(I know the title, but...)
- It's I.O.I. - It's "Very Very Very" by I.O.I.
- It's a close match indeed. - What are they doing?
("Bboom Bboom" by Momoland)
- That's... - It's "Bboom Bboom".
- It's "Bboom Bboom" by Momoland. - You're right!
This one's difficult. Se Chan's team has to get a difficult one.
(Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and Seung Yoon got stuck with "Signal".)
You can choose.
You have a bad headache?
(This is our chance.)
(She shakes her hips.)
(The song they sang out was this.)
("Mister" by KARA)
- It's "Mister". - It's by...
The group's name...
- The group Koo Ha Ra is in. - The name is...
That group's agency was DSP Media.
- This is embarrassing. - What was their name?
- KARA! - KARA!
This one. I know this. It's "Gee" by Girls' Generation.
"Gee" by Girls' Generation.
(Getting two answers in a row...)
(brings the door down a lot.)
- That was fast. - I know this.
- It's "Fire" by BTS. - "Fire".
- "Fire". - It's "Fire" by BTS.
(She keeps on with the dance moves.)
I've seen this. What was this?
- It's "Growl" by EXO. - "Growl".
- "Don't Leave Me", Park Jin Young. - Yes, Park Jin Young.
Do Yeon is really good.
- She knows all dance moves. - She's really good.
(The parade of correct answers makes him start lying down.)
My goodness.
(It's this! The kicking dance!)
It's SISTAR. SISTAR!
(We know these leg moves.)
- SISTAR! - No, it's "Genie".
(Can you guess what that is?)
(It's the dance from "Genie" by Girls' Generation.)
(He mouths it again.)
It's Girls' Generation. What was the title?
(What is this?)
- Hold on. - It starts with a G.
What was it?
(He starts mouthing the words.)
This foot?
(The lip sync failed.)
- Hold on. - My goodness.
(What does a foot have to do with this?)
(While Ji Hyo and Se Chan can't get the answer...)
- It looks like a train. - Is it a train?
- Hold on. - What is this?
"Lies" by BigBang.
- No, it isn't "Lies". - It's "Genie".
"Genie".
(They finally got "Genie" by Girls' Generation.)
(No, no.)
- That's "No No No" by Apink. - "No".
Okay. "No No No" by Apink.
(They start catching up on the verge of losing.)
- We don't know how this will end. - Just one more.
- What is that? - Gosh, this one is difficult.
- It's by Brown Eyed Girls. - "Abracadabra".
- "Abracadabra". - "Abracadabra".
Hey, you only need one more.
- They caught up. - We only needed one more.
- SISTAR. - This one is...
It's something by SISTAR.
- Come on. - Come on.
(Jae Seok and Haha only need to get "Shake It" to win.)
- "Look at me"? - What is that?
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan are clueless...)
(while Jae Seok and Haha just need to guess the title.)
- "Shake It". - "Shake It"!
(Jae Seok, Haha, and Do Yeon finally got the answer.)
(It's a narrow defeat for Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and Seung Yoon.)
- We won! - Yes!
I can't believe we lost there.
(Jae Seok and Haha win again thanks to Do Yeon's dance moves.)
- This is amazing. - You and I...
took up too much time here.
- "Genie" was... - We took too long here.
The winner of Door is Falling from the Sky...
is Jae Seok and Haha's clan.
- This is all thanks to you. - I can't believe this.
- Jae Seok is really... - After they teamed up,
they keep winning.
That was great. Seriously, Do Yeon.
- Jae Seok is great for answers. - This team is great indeed.
This is great indeed.
We're a great team.
(I want to join them too.)
The prize money depends on the winning team's guest.
Do Yeon has to do jegichagi,
and the mission budget depends on how many times she succeeds.
How much is it for each kick?
We'll give 10 dollars for each successful kick.
(The mission budget will be equal to the kick count times 10 dollars.)
- Can you do it well? - How many times can you do it?
- I'm not good with jegichagi. - How many times can you do it?
- Gosh, this is... - It's 100 dollars with 10 kicks.
- If she kicks it a lot... - Even two kicks is a lot.
- Even two kicks is a lot. - Of course, that is.
- Let's do this, Do Yeon. - You can do it.
- Just do it three times. - She won't be able to do that.
Just one. One is fine.
- Let's go! - Okay, let's do it well.
- She's getting nervous. - Don't try to be funny.
She's trembling.
Do Yeon, your time has come.
(What?)
(She kicked it only once and gained 10 dollars.)
- Is it just once? - It's just once.
- It was just once. - Once.
- It's okay, Do Yeon. - At least she got one.
(Jae Suk and Haha gain 10 dollars with 1 kick.)
Here's 10 dollars for the mission budget.
Jae Seok won all day long, but he's poor and on Level Two.
No, he still Level One.
Anyway, today's episode is great thanks to the four of you.
- It's great. - Thank you.
(Thank you, Seung Yoon, Seung Hoon, Chungha, and Do Yeon.)
- This is great. - I know, right?
(Jae Seok and Haha are in the lead after Round 2.)
The Secret Room quest has become available.
Choose your room and begin your quest.
- Hey, don't tell them anything. - Okay.
We really shouldn't tell them anything.
- It will end if we do. - That's what I mean.
It's over for us if we reveal each other's secrets.
It's pointless for us now.
- We're done for today already. - That face...
I'm being serious.
But Kwang Soo, that should never happen.
- Are you choosing Room A? - Yes.
- But seriously, this is... - I'm being serious too.
- Seok Jin, we should... - Please don't do it.
We failed two weeks ago. Seriously.
We really have to stick with each other.
Please.
Hello.
(Will they stay together?)
(A quest has been discovered.)
The Secret Room quest.
Will you lower a level of your own...
or reveal your clan's secret?
(The clan that is behind must pick between their level and secrets.)
(He's troubled.)
(Will you lower a level of your own...)
(or reveal your clan's secret?)
I'll reveal the secret.
(He doesn't even read about the quest.)
Please tell us what you will do after thinking carefully.
I'll reveal the secret.
(He's more careful than ever.)
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo both keep their levels.)
- Follow your instincts, So Min. - See you later.
- No pressure. - Okay.
What? I can't open the door. This is locked.
Hello.
(A quest has been discovered.)
(Will you reduce a level of your own or reveal your clan's secret?)
(It's the same question Seok Jin and Kwang Soo got.)
Well, Jong Kook...
(She looks around.)
I would've revealed it if it wasn't Jong Kook.
But...
do you want me to be unable to join next weeks' recording?
(Do you want me to be unable to join next weeks' recording?)
Jong Kook won't reveal the secret, right?
Then...
I guess I can do it.
(Traitor mode on)
Jong Kook won't reveal it anyway.
(Will she betray her clan as her instincts tell her?)
Seriously.
I really wanted to be on good terms with Jong Kook.
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh, if the same question is being asked there too,
what happens if we both choose to reveal the secret?
However,
if So Min sees this question,
I'm sure she will choose to reveal the secret.
(He's sure of betrayal.)
I'm sure she will.
I'm sure she will reveal my secret.
I'm very sure.
I will choose...
to reveal my clan's secret.
(I will choose to reveal my clan's secret.)
In that case,
I'll keep it a secret.
(What?)
(She chooses to keep the secret.)
I know that Jong Kook...
will not reveal the secret anyway...
because of his personality.
I don't want to resent So Min,
so I choose this.
(Why do they never match?)
(Jong Kook keeps his level, and So Min loses her level.)
(Secret revealed)
Don't think about it, Se Chan.
- Which room will you enter? - Room A.
Then I'll enter Room B.
I'm all about pink, right?
Right. Gosh, I was surprised.
(A quest has been discovered.)
You can raise your level...
by revealing your clan's secret.
- Yes? - Choose carefully.
I'm being careful.
I carefully thought about it since this morning.
I become really harsh sometimes.
Hey, I'm harsher.
I might make you take a vacation for about three months.
This might make you stay off programs. Seriously.
What? What is it?
(They seemed to have critical secrets at hand.)
I carefully thought about it since this morning.
I'll choose to gain a level.
(Why do you even ask?)
I really thought about it since this morning.
I should raise my level.
(Tossing)
(Se Chan gains a level by revealing his clan member's secret.)
I should grow up.
I'm trying to grow up, everyone.
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo doesn't know what Se Chan chose.)
"If you eat the honey rice cake in one bite..."
(A honey rice cake?)
If you eat the honey rice cake in one bite,
you can gain a level.
"you can gain a level. Will you challenge to this?"
Of course.
It's done.
(She eats it without hesitation.)
(Song Ji Hyo)
Then do I not need to reveal my clan member's secret?
Yes, you don't need to.
Are you sure I only had to eat that honey rice cake?
(Is it really this easy?)
Then Haha was right earlier.
[VIU Ver] SBS E434 Running Man
"RPG Level Up Race Part 2: Protect the Secrets"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Haha entered the secret room after Round 1.)
Do you want me to eat this in one bite?
(If you eat the honey rice cake in one bite,)
(you can gain a level.)
Of course.
(Unlike the room Jae Seok entered,)
(he only had to eat the rice cake to raise his level.)
Gosh, this is delicious.
(The secret behind Haha's level-up is finally revealed.)
Thank you.
(This is why choosing rooms is important.)
Don't tell me...
I'm being sincere. Really.
- You should... - I'm being honest.
Jae Seok, we're doing good so far.
What is this?
(A quest has been discovered.)
Gosh, seriously.
You can raise your level...
by revealing your clan's secret.
Will you choose to do so?
I can't believe he can still call himself human.
(He's very disappointed.)
How could he choose to do this?
(He doesn't know about the honey rice cake.)
I should've just revealed his secret.
Why did I do that?
(Why did I choose to keep that secret?)
I'll reveal his secret.
(I don't trust him anymore.)
(Jae Seok gained a level by revealing Haha's secret.)
(What question did Haha receive?)
(The final quest has been discovered.)
This is the last mission...
to keep your clan member's secret.
- There's your name. - Yes, it is.
- Is there still a chance? - Yes.
- Okay. - Wait. Didn't you choose betrayal?
Did I just say that I chose betrayal?
(Staring)
Jae Seok is smiling.
I think he kept his level.
Did you choose...
to keep your level?
He gained a level.
Did he gain a level?
Gosh, seriously.
He was blaming Haha so much earlier.
- Did you gain a level? - Wow, really?
(It's a turn of events.)
Gosh, this is why I'm naive.
- Then what about you? - Okay.
Because of Haha's choice,
Jae Seok lost a level.
- What? Why? - What is this?
Did he lose a level?
Haha, please...
- Haha, please change his badge. - What?
- Can you lose your level? - How does that work?
- Is it the secret? - Is it something about his choice?
(What happened?)
What is it?
(Haha entered the secret room before the final quest.)
(You can steal a level away from your clan member.)
(Will you challenge to this?)
Why do I need to think about this?
Of course,
I'll take away his level.
I'll keep doing so.
Congratulations. You gained another level.
Thank you. Let me transform.
Let me transform.
(Haha becomes Level 3 by taking away a level from Jae Seok.)
(Haha has had full control over Jae Seok's level.)
To be honest,
I didn't hesitate even a bit.
You won all day and chose betrayal, but you're still Level One?
(This is unbelievable.)
That's the worst.
You have no right to say anything. You betrayed me too.
- Haha has returned! - No.
- We're loyal to each other. - However,
there is one last chance...
to keep your secrets.
- I'm keeping my secret, right? - Yes.
A last chance will be given for those who have been revealed.
- Okay. - Okay.
This is your last chance. This is...
(What is today's last quest?)
(Shoe Free Throw)
Among the nine areas on the target,
the names of betrayed members are written on notes,
and minus budgets are with them.
You can gain your secret if you hit the area with your name,
which enables you to keep your secret.
If you hit an area with the minus budget,
you lose that much from your mission budget.
If you hit an area with someone else's name,
you may negotiate with the secret's owner.
If you fail to gain your secret by the end of the game,
your secret will be revealed after the game.
- A negotiation? - What negotiation?
You can put up secrets for sale.
- For money? - Yes.
Hey, the target is big.
What? Minus 30 dollars?
Hey, that's too much of a penalty.
Okay, Kwang Soo.
Let's go for minus 50 dollars.
The giraffe in love.
(She's trying to bother him.)
Kwang Soo likes that.
The lover. He's so lovely.
- I think the lover will do well. - I know, right?
He's so lovely.
You can do everything if you have love.
(You can do everything if you have love.)
I can't do it.
(I can't do it.)
- Okay, we won't do it. - Okay, we won't do it.
I think he might hit us.
Okay.
Let's go.
(He pulls himself together.)
(Singing)
I love you
- Where are you? I'm home - I'm home
- If you're not busy - Come out
(I can't take it anymore.)
Your house
(The giraffe shoots his front hoof.)
- That was twice. - I still have another chance.
- You missed. - I still have another chance.
You still missed this time.
(The giraffe is angry.)
He's so passionate.
- He's so cool. - He's great.
- Lively lively - Lively lively
He'll love forever.
- Lively lively - He'll love forever.
- Lively lively - Lively lively
(Kwang Soo throws his show.)
You did it. It's Haha.
(What is the result?)
- Hold on. - What is this?
- What is this? - This should be done again.
(He threw it,)
(but it landed on top of the box.)
This should be done again.
He always does that.
- Do it again. - Why do you always do this?
How can this happen?
- Is this even possible? - Kwang Soo really is...
What should we do now? I think this...
I think this calls for another chance.
This is the power...
- of love. - Of love.
(He's embarrassed.)
It makes the impossible possible.
(Love makes the impossible possible.)
(He uses the power to try once more.)
(Love doesn't falter under any difficulties.)
(Love never dies.)
(The love giraffe died.)
- Okay! - That was clean.
Haha's block will be difficult.
Haha.
Here I go.
(It's Haha's turn.)
(A father of three children shows the power of love.)
30 dollars. Minus 30 dollars.
Take it slow.
- Hold on. - It went in cleanly.
There is no doubt he got minus 30 dollars.
- Here I go. - All right.
Please.
What?
(I hope my clan member does well.)
- What? - Minus 30 dollars.
(It's minus 30 dollars again.)
Look at her facial expression.
(That's too bad.)
Ji Hyo is really annoyed.
So Min.
- No pressure, So Min. - So Min.
Okay, So Min.
She got it.
(So Min kicks off her shoe.)
(The shoe goes into Haha's block.)
(She obtains Haha's secret.)
(She has my secret!)
Wow, 60 dollars.
- 60 dollars? - Yes, buy it.
- Give me the secret. - So Min, get a lot of money.
Get a lot of money. You should get a lot of money.
- 43 dollars. - 40 dollars.
Okay. 40 dollars.
- Thank you. Thank you. - Okay.
For goodness' sake.
- It's too expensive. - You are cool, Haha.
I am set.
- I am jealous of him. - Now that So Min is...
my clan member,
she is doing so well.
It seems like Jong Kook feels bad for So Min.
- It's not like that. - He never says such things.
So Min is nice.
- Kook. - I was mistaken about her.
- Kook. - Min.
- Siblings! - Siblings!
(Kook and Min siblings)
Kook and Min siblings?
- My goodness. - That's lovely.
They are close.
They became close.
- It needs to go into my block. - I'm so happy.
Here I go.
Get minus 50 dollars.
It will be hilarious.
- Seok Jin, get minus 50 dollars. - There you go.
He got it.
(Where will his shoe fall?)
Jeon So Min!
(He gets So Min's secret.)
What am I going to do?
What?
- Jeon So Min! - It's a good thing.
It's nothing.
I will reveal my secret.
(She refuses to negotiate.)
(Freezing)
- Don't do that. - I will reveal...
I will reveal my secret.
Don't do that.
So Min.
(Heartbroken)
- Get 10 dollars if you can. - How about...
- How about five dollars? - I will reveal...
my secret.
- So Min is cool. - I know.
(4 members' secrets will be revealed.)
Please reveal your secret.
(Who will reveal a secret first?)
(Ji Hyo)
In 1, 2, 3.
Yang Se Chan!
(Yang Se Chan!)
I might make you take a vacation for about three months.
(Will her acting career end once the secret is revealed?)
(What could be her deadly secret?)
I am sorry, Ji Hyo.
(What kind of secret was Ji Hyo hiding?)
Yang Se Chan!
- What? - "I have seen Song Ji Hyo..."
"go without a shower for a week when she had no schedule."
My goodness.
It's a tip-off I got from someone who knows her well.
- Really? - For a week?
She went a week without a shower.
Apparently, that person didn't even see her brush her teeth.
- A week? - A week?
Did you go a week without brushing your teeth?
Doesn't that make her Robinson Crusoe?
(Doesn't that make her Robinson Crusoe?)
(She could be a castaway in her next movie.)
Jeon So Min. In 1, 2, 3.
(What's So Min's secret?)
"I have heard So Min ask Kwang Soo..."
"to introduce her to a man."
When did I do that?
That man is...
- Is he someone we know? - He is a celebrity.
(What's important is that the man is a celebrity.)
It's not just any man.
There is someone she wants.
- I see. - It's a big secret.
It's a big secret.
That man must be someone Kwang Soo is close to.
(Is he a celebrity Kwang Soo is close to?)
(Where did he hear this?)
Who is he? I want to know.
Why won't you introduce her to him?
(Why won't Kwang Soo introduce her to him?)
I asked him, but...
(He doesn't finish his sentence.)
- He... - Did he refuse?
You did ask him.
I mean...
(I didn't want to lose a friend.)
I see.
Did he tell you he doesn't want that?
I should have known.
Kwang Soo didn't say a thing even after 3 or 4 months.
He didn't want to hurt your feelings.
That man turned her down.
It's not like that. He was busy.
- Go ahead and think that. - He was busy.
She asked Kwang Soo to introduce her to a celebrity,
but he...
(He doesn't finish the sentence.)
- The next secret... - Both of us were busy.
belongs to Seok Jin.
What's...
(It's time to reveal Seok Jin's secret.)
Does Seok Jin even have a secret?
You said I will seem cool if this secret gets revealed.
- Really? - That's because...
- You will seem cool. - Okay.
Seok Jin. In 1, 2, 3.
It's nothing bad.
(Will Seok Jin seem cool once the secret gets revealed?)
In 1, 2, 3.
(What is Seok Jin's cool secret?)
(Jee Seok Jin)
"Jee Seok Jin has a bank account his wife doesn't know about."
(It's a secret bank account.)
It's true.
It's true!
Don't let your wife watch this episode.
- Hey! - It has been a year and a half.
A year and a half ago,
Seok Jin made a secret bank account and told me about it.
(Seok Jin's wife will begin her search soon.)
He went too far.
I treated you to meals with that money.
(How could you betray me like this?)
- Do you know that? - Seriously?
Seok Jin's wife will be mad...
- when she finds out. - It's been a year and a half.
What is he going to do?
This one is strong.
(Seok Jin's life is hanging by a thread.)
Seok Jin's secret has been revealed.
(Lee Kwang Soo)
Kwang Soo.
This is...
I am curious.
(What did Seok Jin reveal about Kwang Soo?)
You will see how manly Kwang Soo is.
I did this for him.
Kwang Soo.
- I did this for him. - Manly?
What about me?
(What about me?)
How manly I am?
(How manly I am?)
It hit me hard.
(Seok Jin was shocked that day.)
(That day, Kwang Soo's manliness exploded...)
(and something happened.)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
- Kwang Soo. - This is the last one.
- He is a man. - In 1, 2, 3.
(It's a secret that has never been revealed.)
(What is the secret that will show Kwang Soo's manliness?)
Show us.
"Lee Kwang Soo said he can beat Kim Jong Kook in a fight."
What...
(Kwang Soo's secret)
(I see.)
He said it in a drunken state.
Really?
(No way.)
(How could he say that?)
(What are you talking about?)
(This is the first time Kwang Soo is hearing about it.)
I get it.
He said he went easy on you all these years.
- Did he mean it? - What are you talking about?
In his drunken state, he said, "You know I go easy on Jong Kook,"
"right?"
What...
- "If I put my mind to it..." - What are you talking about?
Didn't we hear something similar?
- "If I put my mind to it," - What are you talking about?
"Jong Kook can't win against me."
Okay. Come on out.
(I heard enough.)
It's not like that.
Come on out?
- Come on out. - What are you talking about?
I must have been wasted!
It makes no sense!
(Please forgive me.)
(This is why you must watch your tongue.)
(It's dangerous to have a secret.)
- Okay. - There is no way I said it!
(Keep your friend's secret to the grave.)
- Come on out. - No.
May I film it?
(He wants to live stream the fight.)
What are you talking about?
May I film it?
- I want to record it. - Why would you film it?
- Go ahead. - I want to record it.
Why would you do that?
We enjoyed the four secrets.
- They were pretty intense. - I know.
I will now reveal the final results of the race.
A clan that protected the secrets of all clan members,
Clan Jae Seok and Haha will receive the prize money...
of 100 dollars.
(They win the prize money of 100 dollars.)
- Really? - Will you give us money?
That's a lot of money.
He bought his secret for 40 dollars and received 100 dollars.
- You should have asked for more. - I should have.
(This is incredible.)
We did a good job.
- I had no idea. - We have the best teamwork.
This is incredible.
- I can't believe it. - Now,
a clan that revealed the secrets of all clan members,
Clan Seok Jin and Kwang Soo will receive a penalty.
- This is incredible. - A penalty again?
(They always receive penalties.)
I will now announce the final amounts of money.
(1st Place: 129 dollars, 2nd Place: 124 dollars,)
(3rd Place: 28 dollars, 4th Place: 28 dollars)
Each level costs 50 dollars.
Jae Seok, thank you.
You are less than human.
- I bought a level. - But...
(Jae Seok is Level 2 and Haha is Level 4.)
Kwang Soo.
I want to buy two levels by myself.
So Min, go ahead!
(So Min, go ahead!)
- I am serious. - If you say that,
I will feel too bad.
It's okay. I feel bad about revealing your secret.
In that case...
It's okay because I am Level Four.
Suddenly, Jong Kook...
(Jong Kook pays her back for her loyalty.)
Jong Kook.
Then I won't refuse.
We are set.
(So Min buys 2 levels.)
- Thank you. - I really don't understand why...
I am still Level Two.
We have 20 dollars left.
- We have 20 dollars left, too. - In that case,
let's combine the money...
and buy a level for one member who wins in rock-paper-scissors.
- Can we do that? - Let's do that.
- I am for it. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do it, Jong Kook.
- Really? - Jong Kook, you should sit out.
(Your level is high.)
- Your level... - I must participate...
because I want to buy a level for So Min.
(I want to buy a level for So Min.)
He is so cool.
I must participate.
Gosh, this is... Let's not do this.
What?
- Let's not do this. - What?
- Let's not do this. - Why?
You are being ridiculous.
You want to buy a level for her?
Is she your girlfriend or something?
For goodness' sake.
Are you acting up?
No, I am not.
(He is acting up by 100 percent.)
I must buy her a level because I feel bad.
- Is she your girlfriend? - I have a good idea.
Let's all play rock-paper-scissors and give two levels to a person.
That's a good idea.
- Let's all play it. - I am for it.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
- That sounds good. - Okay.
Okay.
- This is nerve-wracking. - No way.
We each have one-eighth of a chance.
(You succeed if you pick a note that says "2 Levels Up".)
This one is from the middle.
This one is from the top.
This one is from the top. I don't know which is which.
- Shall we take turns? - This is driving me crazy.
I hope this puts an end to everything.
In 1, 2, 3.
(What will be the result?)
(6 members fail to level up.)
I'm so unlucky. I have the worst luck.
See? Because we were nice to each other,
this good fortune came to us.
- Am I wrong, So Min? - You're right.
- That's how we must be. - It happened because we were nice.
- That's right. Look at this. - It happened because we were nice.
- Exactly. - Open it together. 1, 2, 3.
(Which member will be able to level up twice?)
(2 Levels Up)
(So Min's level goes up by 2.)
- Look at this. - My gosh.
I'm in first place.
(I'm jealous. She's Level 6 now.)
(As So Min levels up,)
(Jong Kook doesn't feel guilty about his secret level-up.)
I'm Level Six. How is that possible?
That makes no sense, you punk.
(That makes no sense, you punk.)
Seok Jin, what's wrong?
- What's wrong with you? - Why are you so mad?
I think you were supposed to think that in your head.
Why are you mad all of a sudden?
(So Min is in 1st place with Level 6.)
1, 2...
(This is their first penalty today.)
- 3. - 3.
(Yet, this scene seems very familiar.)
- Good work, everybody. - Good work, everybody.
- Great job. - Good work.
I'm sick of it. I'm so sick of it.
(What is their next adventure?)
(The Golden Days of the High Levels have arrived with the project.)
(It's a coup by the members with low levels.)
(The incident of level fabrication has occurred.)
(Strange suspects have come to Running Man.)
(Ryu Seung Ryong)
(Lee Ha Nee)
(Lee Dong Hwi, Jin Sun Kyu, and Gong Myoung)
(Forget about the fabricated levels for now.)
(They seemed a bit odd, but something is suspicious about them.)
(Suspicious behaviors of suspects are spotted here and there.)
(And they left behind clues about the forger.)
(A forger has outsmarted the members of Running Man.)
(Anyone can be a forger, and anyone can be a victim.)
(Who's the forger that has concealed his or herself among them?)
(RPG: Catch Me If You Can)