(A cool autumn breeze and cool sculptures greet them...)
(at Anyang Art Park.)
- Hello. - Hi.
Hi.
- Hello. - Good morning. Sitting cushions.
What's going on?
Haha...
- What's wrong with him? - He got a flat tire.
- Really? - He's changing the tire.
- Really? - It's taking him some time.
- It could've been bad. - I'm glad he's okay.
He'll be here soon. He's almost here.
What about Seok Jin?
- Seok Jin is already here. - I'm sorry.
- Why? You didn't see me here? - I mean...
- You're so mean. - What's wrong with you?
It's a misunderstanding.
I can't stand this.
(You'll have to translate things like "cheer up" into Korean.)
(You can look up the lyrics for 30 seconds before you sing.)
(Seok Jin hadn't talked in a long time.)
- Why did you have to cut in? - Why did you do that?
(Feeling utterly disappointed)
(Seok Jin is going to text me later.)
(What do you think Chul Min's intention was?)
(Since the last filming, Seok Jin has been disregarded a lot.)
You just don't think about me, do you?
Does it mean the restructuring is around the corner in fall?
(Is it time to change the cast?)
- What did you say? - Is it supposed to be this obvious?
Are you giving us hints every week?
- It's a misunderstanding. - He's pretending.
- By the way, Seok Jin... - Just talk to me.
- quit his radio program. - So I can look for other shows.
- Really? - Really?
- Yes. - I read the article.
- Why did you quit? - Why did you?
Well, I did enough for the show.
Are you sure it was your decision to quit?
(Are you sure it was your decision to quit?)
- Really? You were fired? - Was it the restructuring?
Was it the restructuring?
- You didn't quit? - Was it?
- It's breaking my heart. - Seok Jin.
- What are you talking about? - You got red in the face.
- No, I didn't. - Seok Jin, let's grab a drink.
I guess he really was let go.
Why? I really liked the show.
- Exactly. - Everyone.
I gathered you here to give you a mission in advance.
Jong Kook isn't here yet, and Haha is still working on his car.
I'm supposed to give you...
- the mission without Jong Kook. - Really?
(Without Jong Kook?)
Today, we'll be pretending to go on a tour of...
popular places in Anyang, chosen by Jong Kook, the son of Anyang.
It's Find Kim Jong Kook Race.
(Find Kim Jong Kook Race, a chase in Anyang)
(Find Kim Jong Kook Race?)
What is this about? "Find Kim Jong Kook Race"?
There will be a cash prize of 3,000 dollars.
(There will be a cash prize of 3,000 dollars.)
You will divide into 2 groups of 3 runaways and 5 chasers...
to proceed with the race.
There are three runaways?
Right now, Jong Kook has no idea about this mission.
During the opening segment, we plan to inform you that...
only 1st, 2nd, and 3rd places of the fake mission will be able...
to eat at a restaurant, recommended by Jong Kook.
Only three?
However, the meal isn't the goal of those three members.
(1st, 2nd, and 3rd places will be runaways.)
You'll be chosen as runaways.
- Runaway? - There are three runaways...
and 5 chasers. And 5 chasers will be in Jong Kook's team.
- Chasers? - Chasers are in Jong Kook's team?
Three runaways must run away.
Their advantage is that they will split 3,000 dollars among them.
So they will be getting a bigger cut of the cash prize.
- 3,000 dollars. - Right.
- We should go for runaways. - Right.
- All right. We'll move then. - Okay.
(Will they be runaways or chasers? That's the question.)
(Haha, who joined late, was also informed of this.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Today's weather is amazing.
- This is Jong Kook's turf. - Hello.
I didn't know about this place.
Haha's pants are dangling.
Be quiet.
(They start the opening segment by criticizing each other's outfit.)
(It's impossible not to criticize his outfit though.)
Be quiet.
Everything including the weather is great today.
My gosh, he's...
- Look at Haha's pants. - What's wrong with him?
You're not supposed to make it so obvious.
I don't get his style.
- But... - By the way, I didn't know...
- Anyang developed this much. - Isn't this a nice place?
- Anyang is such a nice place. - Jong Kook's hometown.
Back then, this used to be the amusement park in Anyang.
We used to play Diving Beetle Game in the front over there.
- To see which one would be faster? - No.
- It would choose a slot. - I know what it is.
It would just go into a slot. We played that game a lot here.
- So when I heard that... - Back in the day...
we were filming in Anyang, I knew this was for Jong Kook.
- Right. - By the way,
it's so nice to come here after such a long time.
- It's gotten so much nicer. - If it's Anyang, it Jong Kook.
- If it's Jong Kook, it's Anyang. - Anyang.
- Anyang Tiger. - Yes.
- He is. - Hello.
I'm from Jeongseon.
- By the way... Anyang's celebrity? - Some say I'm Anyang's celebrity.
(Seok Jin becomes invisible as they pretend not to hear him.)
- They're not listening to Seok Jin. - Hold on.
- This won't air anyway. - I mean... He's in the middle.
Even the cameraman didn't get him.
When he said, "Hello, I'm from Jeongseon",
- no one paid attention. - Here's a thing.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
- I've been to Jeongseon with him. - Okay.
- And people there don't know him. - Exactly.
(People in Jeongseon don't know him.)
Besides, you didn't live there...
- for a long time. - I'm serious.
- Seriously. They didn't know him. - You didn't live there for long.
- I went there with Seok Jin before. - Fine.
I came to Seoul when I was three.
- People there don't know. - I came to Seoul when I was three.
But I was born in Jeongseon.
People like him always go back...
and say they are from there when they are running for office.
I won't run for office.
(He'll win votes as the guy from Jeongseon.)
- You'd shake hands at the markets. - I'm serious.
- I won't run for office. - You'd go to the markets.
You don't need to worry about him.
I won't be able to pass the hearing.
(Suddenly reflecting on himself)
(The guy from Jeongseon isn't that upright.)
I can't do it.
- Seok Jin. - I can't.
- Even if you don't pass it... - He's criticizing himself.
(That won't happen in this life.)
- That's funny. - Right.
Are we going to do something with Jong Kook?
Today, we'll be filming the whole episode in Anyang.
We will be going on a tour of popular places,
recommended by Jong Kook, the son of Anyang.
(Giving them a fake mission)
(Reacting zealously to the fake mission)
- Nice. Popular places. - The whole episode is in Anyang?
- Popular places? - The whole episode is in Anyang.
- My gosh. - The whole episode in Anyang.
We'll be visiting some back alleys today.
I want to share my memories about the alleys.
- Anyang First Street. - But those stories can't air on TV.
Take us to the places that can air on TV.
Will we go to restaurants that you handled too?
- Be quiet. - "Handled"?
If you're going to talk today, change your pants first.
(He's banned from talking.)
Okay. Put up with this for the opening segment.
(He can't talk in sagging pants.)
Is there a place you'd like to go in Anyang with the members?
I have a few places in mind.
When you come to a different area, restaurants are important.
- Right. Food is important. - Right.
- So I thought about it. - But...
When I was in school, I didn't...
- have that much money. - Right.
- But I was reminded of this place. - Which one?
Back in the days, Tripe Alley was famous in Anyang.
Back then, for just five dollars,
- the four of us could eat a meal. - Let's eat a lot.
- And we stir-fried rice too. - Five dollars?
- It was that cheap? - Yes.
Wasn't that only for you and your friends?
(Slandering him for the 2nd time)
(That's not it.)
- I don't believe you. - Back then, it was traditional.
But now, it's been modernized.
- It's been around for a long time. - It was like a shantytown.
- There was a second floor. - I bet it was quite scenic.
There was a second floor.
- It sounds like the real deal. - We would go upstairs.
Back in the days, I got into a lot of fights there.
Most of Jong Kook's old memories in Anyang...
end with a fight, at least 50 percent of them.
- Every story ends with a fight. - It's all about fighting.
It was bound to happen. Back then, we were...
- full of energy. - That's right.
- It was a city of youth. - Right, right.
Places like Anyang First Street.
If you come here at like 5 or 6 a.m.,
the place is still crowded.
- Even now? - Yes.
(It's famous for having a lot of fun places for the youth.)
There's this interesting place right next to here.
- All right. Let's stop. - All of...
(Cutting)
(Why are we stopping all of a sudden?)
- My gosh, nice timing. - Right.
- Nice timing. - The story was getting long.
- It was getting long. - That was perfect.
It's because the neighborhood is...
(Feigned laughter)
- This is fun. - Yes, just laugh.
- Laugh it off. - It was funny.
- It was funny. - Number three.
All right.
While we reserve a restaurant in the alley,
you will carry out a mission that only the top three members...
will get to benefit from.
- What is this? - What is it?
(Pretending to be clueless)
(Actually, Jong Kook is the only one who doesn't know about the race.)
(Only the top 3 members will get to have the meal as promised.)
(Actually, those 3 members will be 3 runaways.)
(In other words, this is a mission to choose 3 runaways.)
- Three? - What is it?
(Pretending to hear it for the first time)
Jong Kook, you must also be 1 of the top 3 members to eat as well.
(If he's in the top 3, the member in 4th place will be a runway.)
So only a few of us will get to eat.
Only three of you will get to eat.
- Stir-fried sundae is really good. - Tripe?
It's no joke.
- Stir-fried sundae. - That sounds delicious.
- Stir-fried sundae is the best. - That sounds good.
- It's so good. - After you get into team uniforms,
- we'll start the mission. - Alrighty.
- "Alrighty"? - Come on, Seok Jin.
- Let's go. - The guy from Jeongseon.
(The fake mission set is prepared in the best way it can be.)
(20 bowling pins...)
(and a huge slingshot)
(What kind of mission will unfold?)
Se Chan!
- What's wrong with her? - What's with her?
(Acting cheerful for no reason)
You're going mad because the weather is great.
She's like an elementary school kid.
(Getting excited before the fake mission)
- What's wrong with her? - Are you having fun?
Perhaps, Anyang suits her. She's in a good mood.
- I guess so. - Hey, Anyang must suit her well.
Actually, she stepped in poop earlier.
- You did? It means you'll be lucky. - She did.
- It will be your lucky day. - She'll be lucky today.
- I stepped in dog poop. - On human feces?
- You really did? - Gosh, So Min.
Stepping in poop doesn't happen that often nowadays.
- It's not that easy. - Right.
Nowadays, there isn't much poop on the streets.
- It happened when we were kids. - Right.
- I guess I'm that unlucky. - No, it means you're really lucky.
I told you that only the top three members can eat the meal.
- I have to eat. - Let's win this!
- This place serves great food. - I'm hungry.
- Please. - The mission for the meal is...
- Fly, Grocery Basket. - Okay!
Fly what?
Grocery Basket?
(What's that? Fly, Grocery Basket?)
With the time limit, 10 minutes, you have to put objects...
- around you in the basket. - Around us?
After 10 minutes, you'll take turns...
to fly your grocery basket with this huge slingshot.
The three members that knock down the most pins will win.
The whole basket? The stuff inside will fly out too.
We shouldn't put in heavy things...
- because they won't fly far. - Right.
- Fill your basket for 10 minutes. - Where?
In this case, wouldn't water bottles or beverage bottles be the best?
This is the best. They are hard.
How heavy should it be?
It's heavy.
(These 3 members go straight to a grocery store nearby.)
- This will be more than enough. - Yes. It will be.
(Silver trays and 5 referee uniforms)
Nice.
Okay.
You filled it up.
(He chose 5 toy hammers which suit him well.)
- They'll scatter and fly. - Right.
This will be more than enough.
- Okay. Great. - Okay!
(Order of Members' Turns)
This looks like fun.
- Move back. - Is that how you load it?
Whether it goes well or not,
- it depends on your luck. - Right.
- It's all about luck. - You only get one chance.
Actually, if the basket lands in the center, it's a strike.
- Of course. - If it falls, it's over.
That looks good.
(Pulling the basket)
- That looks good. - Good.
- My gosh. - Good.
(Aiming for the bowling pins.)
Right. I should move it this way.
Okay.
One.
(Haha's basket is full of ice cream.)
- There you go. - Two.
(This will be a strike.)
(How many bowling pins will Haha knock down?)
Darn it!
(What was that?)
(With full of energy,)
(he fails the mission.)
(Rolling)
- We have to aim higher. - We have to pull harder.
- You need to pull downwards more. - That's why the order matters.
- I have to pull harder? - You have to pull harder.
I was going to tell you, but I didn't.
(Haha gets 0 pins.)
My gosh, this...
Jong Kook's basket looks really light.
Jong Kook taped up his basket.
(To make sure it flies as a whole, he wrapped it in tape.)
(Pulling)
Actually, that might be better.
- Will the tape make it better? - I'll go.
Okay.
(How many bowling pins will Jong Kook knock down?)
(It accurately flew toward the bowling pins.)
(It landed right in front of the bowling pins.)
(I was so close!)
Had he pulled a bit harder...
- It fell in front of the pins. - Right in front of the pins.
- Had his basket heavier... - That was close.
- I thought it was a strike. - I should pull harder.
- Same here. - I thought it'd fall in the center.
I thought I was pulling it too hard,
so I moved a bit forward at the last minute.
- I get it now. - Okay.
(Loading the basket, full of plastic plates)
- Here he goes. - My gosh. If the plates...
- fly all over the place, - If they come at us...
- it would be a mess. - Kwang Soo.
I think they might come all the way here.
(Launching a pile of plates)
They all broke.
(Crazy party with plates)
(He still knocks down the pins.)
- He got three pins. - Okay.
(With a large number of plates,)
(he knocks down 3 pins.)
- Okay. I'm in first place for now. - Three?
- What is this? - Hey, clean this up.
- What is all this? - Clean your mess up.
- I'm sorry. - You broke all the plates.
I'm sorry.
But somehow, you knocked down some pins.
I'm so glad.
He got three pins.
(Kwang Soo is in 1st place with 3 pins.)
Three is a pretty good score.
That's not a bad score.
All right, Seok Jin.
- You must give back the ball. - Okay.
(Seok Jin filled his basket with snacks and props.)
(I'll knock them all down with this.)
He's aiming it higher, so the objects will fall from above.
- Right. - Pull it more.
- Pull it more. There you go. - Great, great.
(Launching)
(The snacks are charging at the pins just like the plates.)
Seok Jin.
(Rolling)
- It's food! - Yes!
(This time, it's a crazy snack party.)
This is dalgona.
- This is red bean jelly. - Yes!
(What a generous game.)
(Picking up)
Hey, although...
Seok Jin failed, it was entertaining.
- Darn it. - You know?
- Gosh, Seok Jin. - Darn it.
- I want the chocolate biscuits. - You can have it.
Yes, chocolate biscuits.
- Snacks fell from the sky. - My grandpa liked this.
By the way, this is a festival today.
- Hey, it's Seok Jin's gift for us. - The ultimate gift set.
I should have taped it together.
I'll show you.
By the way, today's game is nice.
- We can have snacks in between. - Right.
- He threw us snacks. - Everyone.
I won't be petty. I'll do it in one go.
You've been living a petty life up to now.
(You've been living a petty life up to now.)
- I'll show you. - What do you mean?
- I'll show you, Jong Kook. - Okay.
- You should aim it higher. - Okay.
(He filled up the basket with noise-making junk.)
Okay.
(Pulling)
- Nice. - I think I can do better now.
Be careful.
He looks really determined.
- Here I go. - He's determined to win.
All right. Here I go. I'll let go now.
(You want to be a runaway, too?)
(Surprised)
(How many bowling pins did Jae Seok knock down?)
- 3. - 3.
(He got 3 pins with maraca's handle.)
(I could've gotten more. I only got 3?)
- Jae Seok. - Goodness.
Jae Seok!
This saved you.
Is that so?
(This small maraca saved him.)
This got you all three pins.
(This clip shows that one maraca got all the pins.)
(Hitting)
(The lucky attack from the handle)
- This saved you. - Is that so?
This got you all three pins. You didn't need anything else.
- I should have opened the basket. - You should have kept it open.
It's Se Chan's turn? I don't think it will work.
That looks promising.
(A bomb with a tray)
This is heavy.
Look at his basket. Do you think that will fly?
Don't forget about the wind resistance.
Because of the wind, it will fall right here. Just watch.
Or it will get stuck and fall right there instead.
Or it will go back and hit you.
I think we're the best at criticizing each other.
How did you guys pull this back?
(This is harder than it looks.)
Figure it out yourself, punk.
(He sounds cold.)
(Hold on.)
Why are you asking us?
Really? You're disappointing me.
- This is a competition. - The thing is...
now that they are in Anyang, they're feeling the vibe here.
I guess everyone is feeling it.
- Just like Anyang Hothead. - Right.
I hope the band snaps and hits your face.
- There you go. - Move.
Hey, why are you helping him?
(Surprised)
- Move. - Hey, why are you helping him?
(How many bowling pins did Se Chan knock down?)
(Hitting)
(4 pins are knocked down.)
- 4. - 4.
(He gets in 1st place with Jae Seok's help.)
I got four pins!
(I'm in 1st place!)
- 4 pins. - So he's in 1st place.
- What? - Hey.
- You know I helped you, right? - I'll remember that.
- That's cheating. - You know that, right?
- No, this is okay. - It's not cheating.
(Why did he help? To get food from him?)
(The remaining runaways will be decided after the last 2 members.)
Gosh, So Min.
She probably can't even pull it. Just leave her alone. Don't help.
- Come on, Seok Jin. - I'll help you.
(I'll be a runaway too.)
(Looking somewhat determined)
- You might fly with the basket. - Ground your feet.
- You have a good angle. - There you go.
(She sits down to aim unlike the other members.)
- That's good. - 1, 2, 3.
(Falling)
2, 3.
(The objects hit the slingshot and fall in front of her.)
(Look at that.)
- Good job. - What were you doing?
- You're the best. - What?
- Wasn't that pretty good? - You're the best.
- What was that? - This flew the farthest.
- Right here. - The gum flew the farthest.
Wasn't I good? Why didn't it fly?
She's the last one.
If she can't hit 3 or more, it's us 3 who win.
- Okay. - You're right.
She just needs to hit less than three.
(I will get 3.)
I think it'll be difficult.
Are you working at a laundromat or something?
She'll either fail horribly or win with flying colors.
She's strong.
(Struggling)
She's acting weak. Don't pretend.
- Sit down. - That's good.
- Am I good? - That's a good angle.
Count to three.
One...
(The runaways' fate could change.)
Two...
(If she can't get 3, the runaways will be decided.)
1, 2, 3.
(What will be the result?)
(Is it a strike?)
(The package flies towards the bowling pins.)
(She misses.)
(She misses by an inch.)
- Your direction was a bit off. - You were slightly off.
It could've been a strike.
- You could've gotten a strike. - It could've been a strike.
Since it's lighter, it flies farther away.
- You're right. - We got the top three.
That's amazing.
They're Jae Seok, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo.
- Okay! - Okay.
(We're the runaways!)
Now, you three will be runaways.
You will begin running.
What?
(They will run?)
(Hold on.)
- What did you say? - What's going on?
Please start.
You're so blatant.
Wait.
- It was a secret. - What is this?
- Go on. - Come on.
- This isn't right. - We'll catch you soon.
All right, please begin.
Are they running?
They're running because they won?
Why are we running?
I'm irritated.
They look like runaways.
You're right.
I can't believe this.
I'm good at catching people, but I do it better in Anyang.
Are we running out in the open?
- I thought we're having tripe? - What's going on?
Are we eating it?
I have no idea.
I'll tell you about the real race.
It's about the son of Anyang...
who knows Anyang like the back of his hand.
It's a pursuit done by Jong Kook.
It's called Find Kim Jong Kook Race.
- Find Kim Jong Kook Race? - Find Kim Jong Kook Race?
Jong Kook and the rest of you are chasers.
Okay.
(The 5 of them are the chasers.)
You are the runaways.
Come on.
Before the chasers catch you,
you must find three places that are sentimental to Jong Kook...
- and have them verified to succeed. - What?
You can search online,
ask his acquaintances, family, and shop owners.
They must be based on their testimonies.
The method of verification will be explained once you get there.
(The method will be revealed once they arrive there.)
You're eliminated if they rip off your name tags.
If even one of you survives and gets all three places verified,
you win.
However, you must move around together.
We need to be together.
If you rip off all of their name tags,
you will acquire 3,000 dollars.
(They will be given the reward immediately.)
And it will be allocated by Jong Kook himself.
- Really? - Yes.
He can choose how much he'll give.
Please change into uniforms for the race.
- Are we changing again? - We're changing?
Tell them to change.
(He's lazy.)
- They already ran away. - Really?
- Got it. - Okay.
Okay.
The surviving runaway...
can allocate the reward as he wishes.
- Are we not allowed to split up? - Wait.
If one of us gets caught, it'll be the end of us.
- Let's do this. - What?
At least one of us should survive...
- and protect the money. - Right.
- And we'll split it equally. - Okay.
(Laughing)
I can see that you're lying.
- I'm serious. - I can see through you.
- Hey. - You're smiling.
Seriously? You guys are frightening.
We're a bunch of petty criminals.
Okay? One of us needs to survive.
Whether it be me, Kwang Soo, or Se Chan.
Let's look it up online.
- Search up "Jong Kook, Anyang". - We could visit his school.
How about Sinsung High School?
No, they'll find us.
I looked it up,
and "Jong Kook fighting" is a related keyword.
I've heard many rumors about him when I was young.
Where did you hear them?
On First Street?
He did go to Anyang First Street often.
Look here. He had a signing event in Anyang before.
- Where? - Jong Kook's signing event.
- Was it recent? - Is this possible?
- Yes. - Really?
- Should we go there? - Let's go there.
I doubt they'll think of this place.
Of course not.
- They'd think of schools. - Right.
Right? Let's go here.
Then we'll go there.
They wouldn't remember the signing event.
- Of course not. - Right.
I doubt they will.
I can't believe I'm always with them...
when I'm running away.
But it suits us.
- We're petty criminals. - You're right.
I'm not the type to run away.
I'm not the type to make such bold actions.
I'm sure you all know that.
I'm...
In a few hours, he'll be hiding behind a minivan.
(He'll be peeking out.)
He'll be afraid.
- Kwang Soo. - "I'm here."
I'm not like that.
(But it actually happened.)
If I was one of the chasers, you guys would be terrified.
- Why do you think that? - If you were a chaser,
you'd team up with Seok Jin and So Min.
Right. He's disposable.
(It's obvious.)
(While the runaways are headed towards Anyang Station...)
All right, then.
There are a few places I can think of off the top of my head.
I have memories...
- of the underground shopping area. - Right.
The underground shopping area.
That's because...
(This shopping area was where many residents used to work.)
(What is his memory of this place?)
- Well... - Did you have a date there?
The mother of my girlfriend in high school...
had a restaurant there.
- Did you eat there? - Whenever we went downtown,
- we'd eat there. - Did you have gimbap?
- We had kimchi fried rice. - That's the place.
- We should go downtown. - Yes, we should.
What about the hair salon?
- What? - The bus station.
That lady who worked there had a crush on you.
(Haha mentions the past.)
- That's it. - He was your first lover.
That was across my school, not downtown.
Is the underground shopping area a sure thing?
I'm pretty sure it's one of them.
So it's the shopping area and the police station.
(I don't have memories there.)
School.
- Your school. - Your school.
- I bet they'll be there. - Do you think they'll go that far?
Isn't your school in Anyang?
- Of course. - Then they'll be there.
They will be there.
Search up news articles online.
- Se Chan may know many places. - I'm sure Kwang Soo is...
up to something.
I think Se Chan will know some places.
- You must be lost. - Yes.
You have chance cards to find out their whereabouts.
- How? - How?
There's the 30-second Listen-in Card.
(30-second Listen-in Card)
Photo of Their Current Whereabouts.
Then there's Runaways Freeze for 20 Seconds.
Every time you succeed in a mission,
you can randomly pick one.
- Okay. That's good. - That's good.
That's good. That works.
- We should do the missions. - Yes.
Your first mission is...
Add or Minus Rock-Paper-Scissors.
You will play rock-paper-scissors with the staff.
All five of you must win or make a draw.
That sounds easy.
If one of you fails, you all fail.
- Really? - You can attempt...
the challenge as many times as you want.
- As many times? - As many times?
However, it's not your average game.
For example, if the staff says "without rock, rock-paper-scissors",
you must omit rock and play either scissors or paper.
And you must win or make a draw.
If the staff says, with scissors, rock-paper-scissors,
you must only play scissors.
Then you'll win.
- How could you lose? - Right, how?
It's impossible to lose. We'll win no matter what.
They must think we're fools.
- You're right. - That's what they think.
If rock is omitted, we need to play scissors.
- It's easy. - Wait.
- Let's say it's without scissors. - Without scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
(They need to play paper.)
(She can't play scissors.)
- We need to play this. - Paper.
- Exactly. It's tricky. - It is.
- It's tricky. - Hey.
- Then... - Without rock, rock-paper-scissors
(They both need to play scissors.)
(Silence sweeps across the area.)
- We needed to play this. - Scissors.
- This is hard. - It's confusing.
- Hold on. Seok Jin. - When I hear without rock,
- I try to beat rock. - With scissors,
- rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They can only play scissors.)
- See? You're a fool. - Oh, right.
- It's not easy. - It's confusing.
Haha goes first.
Let's start.
With paper, rock-paper-scissors
(Play paper.)
Gosh. Here it is!
(He just needs to play paper.)
(But he plays scissors.)
(He quickly changes to paper.)
Gosh. Here it is!
(He's brazen.)
- I did it. - Again.
This is bad.
With rock, rock-paper-scissors
(With rock, rock-paper-scissors.)
(He needs to play rock, but he fails.)
It was "with", so I'm right.
- You should've played rock. - You lost.
- It was "with scissors". - You did it.
- With scissors. - With rock.
Didn't you hear "with scissors"?
(What?)
(It was "with rock"?)
- You said, "scissors". - You said, "scissors".
- It was scissors. - I swear.
(They protest.)
- I heard scissors as well. - I swear.
- I swear. - Me too.
- I'll do it again. - I swear.
Yes, me too.
- I heard scissors too. - Me too.
Then let's say paper instead of rock.
(Then let's say paper instead of rock.)
(What?)
- Let's say paper. - Hey, wait.
- This is rock. - This is paper.
She's stupid.
Why is it so confusing?
- Wait. Rock-paper-scissors. - This is paper.
What's wrong with you?
- I just... - What's wrong with her?
- Just pronounce it clearly. - Rock.
- Rock. - That's good.
- We're good at this. - Rock.
- Okay. - We have great teamwork.
(They start again.)
Start. Without paper, rock-paper-scissors
(He needs to play rock, but he fails.)
You lose.
(What should I say this time?)
- This is so tricky. - Let's start with So Min.
Haha can't do it.
- Do you think she's any better? - Who knows.
I don't even know rock-paper-scissors.
Start.
Without paper, rock-paper-scissors
(She plays scissors like Haha and fails.)
(She was concentrating, but she fails once again.)
(He's not smiling.)
- Will you please get it right? - Get it right.
(She feels wronged.)
- I just did it once. - Do better.
- Exactly. What are you doing? - Let's go again.
I'm getting stressed.
- Get a grip on yourself. - Stay frosty.
Start.
Without paper, rock-paper-scissors
(Scissors again?)
(Just so you know, this isn't a replay.)
Gosh, it's all right.
- Without paper... - It's without paper.
So Min, seriously?
- What's wrong with us? - So Min!
- This is frustrating. - Seriously?
What on earth are you doing?
Rock loses to scissors.
This is so frustrating!
I'm sorry too, you know.
- We're... - Again.
Let's practice first. And go.
Without paper, rock-paper-scissors
(A shy pair of scissors)
- With scissors... - Rock was the answer.
- It's rock. - Without paper...
You got it wrong?
Yes, instead of what wins.
I think I've got it.
- What is it? - If it's without rock,
put out the one that loses to rock.
Try me.
Without rock, rock-paper-scissors
Without paper, rock-paper-scissors
- Okay, I got it. - Me too.
- I get it now. - We'll go again.
- I'll go first. - Sure.
Okay, go ahead.
Without paper, rock-paper-scissors
(Once again)
(Scissors?)
We lost. Game over.
(He's totally embarrassed.)
- But... - Are you kidding me?
You put out the one that loses to the one taken out.
- Right. - Don't think of it like that.
- But... - I can't believe we can't get this.
It's confusing to think what loses to what.
This couldn't be more gratifying. He was like this.
He seemed so confident but...
(He ended up looking like a fool.)
- I get it now. - We'll go again.
With paper, rock-paper-scissors
(He should've put out paper this time.)
- Paper... - Didn't you hear "with"?
- Come on. - With paper!
- With paper. - What?
With paper?
- But... - With paper?
Just so you know...
Why are you pretending not to have heard this?
So we just have to put out "paper" in this case?
Let's be honest. You knew.
- I didn't. - You knew...
- this certain rule. - Earlier...
- I'm disappointed in you. - You and I...
Why isn't anyone saying anything?
I've been telling him off.
It was an honest mistake.
(It was an honest mistake.)
(Nodding)
It's as if we've become fools.
Why are we so bad at this?
We'll start with Ji Hyo this time.
Ready... Go.
With scissors, rock-paper-scissors
(She fails by presenting paper.)
- Scissors. - With scissors!
- Scissors. - Let's get her through this first.
We'll start with Ji Hyo.
This is a practice round.
This is flustering. Okay, I'll go first.
I can't believe this. We'll never be able to leave here.
- Again. - We're doomed.
- I can do it now. - Come on.
(Will they be able to successfully win a hint?)
Must the chasers stick together?
Yes, if one gets caught,
the other two may run for it.
Of course, we should run.
However, you must head to the same location next.
That's why we need to decide on where to go in advance.
- I found a cutlet diner. - Search the web.
Secretaries, get to work.
Search the Internet.
You should too unless you want a beating.
(You jerks...)
I can't believe this. What a nice world it is.
After you search online, I'll give you 10 dollars.
(Please shut it.)
- Manage with that. - Buy a beverage.
(By yourself something to drink.)
Let's see. Kim Jong Kook...
Nothing's coming up.
It's because he's not much of a foodie.
Exactly.
I found a pork cutlet diner.
- Pork cutlet? - Anyang Loser.
Is that the name of a restaurant?
There's a hangover soup restaurant near his house.
- That's right. - I'll ask his stylist.
Yes, ask her. She'll know.
(They'll ask Ji Seon, Jong Kook's stylist of 5 years.)
- Yes? - Ji Seon.
- We're looking for a restaurant. - Right.
There's a gukbap place Jong Kook goes to often.
I don't know where that is.
(Stylist Ji Seon)
- Hey. - Just tell me.
I really don't know.
- Ji Seon, hold on. - Sorry?
- Ji Seon. - Yes?
- It's me. - Right.
You can tell me what you can't tell Kwang Soo.
- There might be a place... - Hold on a second.
Are you perhaps with Jong Kook at the moment?
He's in front of me.
He's in front of you? I'm hanging up.
(Stylist Ji Seon)
(Startled)
Are you insane? Jong Kook's there with her.
They're together?
Jong Kook's right there.
(They almost revealed their destination.)
Why did you call Ji Seon?
- Why Ji Seon of all people? - Why did you call Ji Seon?
(You're so clueless.)
- No one ordered you. - You...
You don't think, do you?
You told me to call.
- Unbelievable. - You almost called Kwak Jin.
- That was close. - So who should we call?
Should we call Jong Myung?
Right.
- My eyebrow... - That's right.
- He made it good as new. - I'll call him.
Yes, call him.
Do you know his number?
I'm calling his workplace.
- Wait... - His workplace?
Don't you know his number?
Jong Kook would never guess that we called his brother.
- Maybe he's with a patient. - Hello?
- Jong Myung. - Yes, hi, Jae Seok.
It's me. What were you up to?
I'm waiting for a patient.
Is that so? Well, I'm glad we have some time.
Thanks to you, my eyebrow is as good as new.
- Really? - Thank you so much.
Thanks to you, my sister is living a new life.
- Oh, gosh. - Thank you so much.
- Just stay quiet. - Unbelievable.
Jong Myung, we must go to three places in Anyang...
that are meaningful to Jong Kook.
In high school, he used to go to Anyang First Street...
- a lot. - Anyang First Street?
So the restaurant is there?
- That's right. - Also, if Jong Kook calls,
please tell him that we didn't call you.
- Of course. - Thank you.
- Have a good day then. - You too.
We should search for restaurants on Anyang First Street.
- Right. - We should ask around.
Jong Kook mentioned Anyang First Street a lot.
Let's head their first. All we need is a photo.
(The shopping mall where Jong Kook's signing event took place)
They might not guess this place.
Right.
You have arrived at a meaningful spot for Jong Kook.
In order to have this place validated...
There must be a certain way.
You must do exactly what Jong Kook did here.
What?
What on earth are you saying?
I just read this,
but he signed autographs for 110 people that day.
(He signed autographs for 110 people that day.)
He signed autographs for 110 people that day.
Before you're caught by the chasers...
How can we hold a signing event when we're on the run?
You must sign 110 autographs combined.
Who suggested that we come here?
(In anger)
- What? - It was you!
What...
- With the people here? - You thought you were so smart.
(20 minutes ago)
(He kept fussing over the signing event venue.)
- You said no one would think of it. - I should've known.
- But... - At a restaurant,
all we have to do is eat.
Before I make rash decisions, you should stop me.
- Right? - But...
- We're done for. - If you went to his school,
- you would've taken a class. - Why didn't you tell us?
A class?
I'm glad we didn't go to his high school.
Isn't it a relief that we didn't go to his school?
It really is.
If we took a class,
- we would've been caught. - As if Jong Kook took classes.
(As if Jong Kook took classes.)
- In high school... - He probably played soccer.
Do we hold the signing event inside?
- The singing event... - We're being chased though.
Have you ever seen people on the run sign autographs?
Once we enter the shopping mall,
our photos will be all over social media.
In real-time too.
- We'll get caught immediately. - Then let's hurry.
- Where do we hold the event? - We'll get caught immediately.
I'll just sign as many as I can.
Hello. Did Kim Jong Kook hold...
a signing event here recently?
- A signing event. - Where?
- On the 2nd floor. - 2nd floor?
- The second floor? - Right down there.
Right down there? Thank you.
It was downstairs.
- Was it here? - Hello.
- Come and get your autographs. - There?
- The stairs? Thanks. - Thank you.
We're here to hold a signing event too.
- You should come by. - Please spread the word.
If it's all right with the customers, I mean.
About 100 will do.
We need pen and paper.
Where are the pen and paper?
Must we get some ourselves?
- Where are they? - Shouldn't you provide that?
Try and get them yourselves.
- Paper... - Guys, sit for now.
- But the paper... - Have a seat.
Where do we get paper?
- Here you go. - Hold on.
- Who has paper? - Slowly, please.
- Hello. - Gosh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
(The Paper Angel comes forward.)
Thank you so much. She gave us paper.
- My gosh. - Hold on.
We're good. Let's get this started.
Also, keep an eye out for the chasers.
Kwang Soo, come on.
I'm sorry, but we need to rush this a little bit.
(The random signing event is a success though.)
We're being chased, so...
- we're sorry. - Sorry.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you!
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- We're in trouble. - Thank you.
- Hello, ma'am. - Hello.
Thank you.
Always stay healthy.
My goodness.
We don't have the time.
- Thank you. - Here you go.
Thank you.
We're being chased, so we could run for it at any time.
We apologize in advance.
Thank you.
(Will they be able to finish the signing event?)
Hold on a second.
Haha, get a grip on yourself.
- We need to do this. - What loses to scissors?
- Scissors? - It's paper.
Without scissors, rock-paper-scissors
(Without scissors, rock-paper-scissors.)
(Finally, Haha wins by drawing with paper!)
Finally, we got it.
- This is so annoying. - Is this something to celebrate?
- This should've been easy. - It was annoying.
I'm actually dizzy.
You can pick a card then.
The one that tells us their whereabouts is best.
So...
(Which card did they select?)
- Conversation... - The Listen-in Card.
- Okay, good. - What a bummer.
(What a bummer.)
(30-second Listen-in Card)
A place that is meaningful to me?
(It's not what they wanted, but they call the chasers.)
- I should listen. - Right.
- All right. - You're down to 30 people.
What? 30 people?
- Yes, you're down to 30 people. - My gosh.
(Why are they saying they have 30 people left?)
30 people left?
My gosh.
(The runaways were signing autographs.)
(The call was connected at a crucial moment.)
Gosh, this isn't easy.
A signing event.
(They have 30 people left?)
(A signing event)
- "Thank you." - A signing event.
It sounds like their signing autographs.
- "They are 30 people left." - Thank you!
- I heard you, I'll give it back. - It's a place with a lot of people.
I'll give it back.
(Haha takes his time.)
Don't you think they're doing a signing event?
It's a signing event.
- It's a signing event. - "There are 30 people left."
- Someone said, "Thank you." - A signing event?
Have you ever done a signing event here?
- I did it recently. - Where was it?
- You did one here too. - Yes.
- Near Anyang Station. - Near Anyang Station.
When was it? Was it recent?
- Let's go to Anyang Station then. - It was near Anyang Station.
Let's hurry.
We have to hurry and catch them.
- Hi. - Hi.
(The signing event is being held at a mall near Anyang Station.)
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Aren't we supposed to be on the run?
We're runaways.
- But everyone can see us. - We're sorry.
If they find us, everything will be over.
We won't be able to do anything.
We're so exposed.
If you see other Running Man members,
please tell us.
(We don't care who comes. We're busy taking photos.)
Check social media.
We're allowed to use it.
Why did he say, "There are 30 people left"?
- What? - 11 minutes ago...
- Someone posted an autograph. - Were we right?
- Where? - It's at the shopping mall.
- Is it? - Look at the floor.
- That's right. It's at the mall. - Someone posted an autograph.
- Unbelievable. How did you find it? - Three people did.
Let's go.
(The chasers even have evidence now.)
We have to leave soon.
How many people are left?
Five people to go.
We have to hurry.
We have to hurry. Thank you.
We can give our autographs to only five more people. Sorry.
We're sorry.
We'll get out here.
The car should go to the parking lot.
Let's go.
I think we should run to the parking lot now.
- Over there. - Are we going up?
Ask people if they've seen the other members.
- Here you go. Thank you. - Thank you.
(Worried)
- Over there. - Have you seen Yu Jae Seok?
Have you seen Yu Jae Seok?
(The runaways speed up.)
- Have you seen Yu Jae Seok? - I saw him on the third floor.
- They're on the 3rd floor! - The 3rd floor?
(They received an important piece of information.)
Let's go now.
The last one.
Would they have gone straight to the basement?
- That was the last one. - That was the last one.
- We're sorry. - Thank you.
We're so sorry. We have to run.
(I must be getting closer.)
Isn't this the place?
(Will the chasers catch the runaways?)
- Isn't this the place? - Is it here?
What...
(What?)
- I saw these stairs in the picture. - Was it here?
Have you seen Yu Jae Seok?
- Have they left? - They did a signing event here.
- They did? - They've already left.
When did they leave?
- 10 minutes ago. - 5 minutes ago?
- They left five minutes ago. - Let's leave.
We should leave.
- Five minutes ago. - We should go.
Your mission was a success at this place.
- Yes! - Let's hurry.
We're really sorry.
- We have to run now. - We're sorry.
- We're sorry. Bye! - Thank you!
- Bye! - Thank you.
- Bye! - Thank you very much.
- I can feel them near. - Guys, see?
(The 3 petty criminals successfully held a signing event on the run.)
I've never been...
so nervous at a signing event.
I don't even know how we did it.
- Should we go to First Street? - Let's go.
We should ask as soon as we enter...
- if Jong Kook has been there. - Right.
We have to be strategic.
There you go again.
Jae Seok is doing it again.
Don't talk so confidently.
Why are we here in the first place?
Our mission succeeded because I brought you guys here.
If I had let you do whatever you wanted,
you'd both be out by now.
At the signing event, you were like this.
(Nervous)
(He was obviously scared.)
Please take us to Anyang First Street.
(The 3 runaways are on their way to Anyang First Street.)
I'll make sure you guys take 1,000 dollars home each.
(Jae Seok is still confident.)
They might show up out of nowhere and stop our car.
(They're on alert.)
- Do you see anything? - Isn't that their van?
They're here.
- They're going up. - Turn off all the lights.
(The runaways even turn off their lights.)
- What's wrong? - They're on the other side.
- It says, "SBS". - Lock the doors.
They're here?
Hey, let's hide.
(They're scared.)
- Guys. - Let's hurry.
We almost got caught.
(They're extremely nervous.)
We should go somewhere else.
(The chasers are circling around the building.)
They might be done earlier than we thought.
Exactly. We have to catch them soon.
We should catch two first.
So Min, give them a call.
They asked Jong Kook's friends too.
- They might go to Jong Kook's home. - My home?
Why?
It's possible.
- I don't think so. - Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
What are you doing?
- Well... - Listen up.
(Haha sees something.)
If you want to catch us, bring 4,000 dollars.
What?
Do you guys see us?
What? Where?
- Is that their van? - Don't you see us?
- Where? - That's their van.
- What? - There they are.
What should we do?
They saw us.
We have to hurry.
- Where? - That's their van.
- Is that their van? - You guys see us, right?
- It's their van. - Really?
Let's follow them.
- It's definitely their van. - It is.
Are you sure?
- Do you see us? There they are! - There they are!
- Should we chase them down? - They're leaving.
- Where are they heading? - Where are they heading?
They're heading downtown.
Let me see where they turn. Are they turning right?
Where are they going?
We have to speed up.
Oh, wait.
Don't honk like that.
They'll find us.
If you honk, they'll find us.
This is not good.
They saw us. If we continue this way,
they'll know we're heading to First Street.
We have no choice.
- They turned in that direction. - They turned in that direction.
- Where are they heading? - It gave me goosebumps.
- They're heading downtown. - Downtown?
- Get in. - Okay.
Is that really their van?
- It is. - Gosh.
- I'm 100 percent sure. - It gave me goosebumps.
How did they pass right by us?
- This is frustrating. - It was like a movie.
We'll have to follow them in that direction too.
They must have circled around...
- to see if we were here. - Probably.
- Or were they watching us? - That's possible.
So they went in that direction?
(Jong Kook is thinking hard.)
Can you think of any places in that direction?
(Where would they go in Anyang?)
Did they go to a pool hall?
(The runaways successfully escaped.)
If we go to First Street, we'll be exposed, right?
- Definitely. - Let me tell you something.
So Min just messaged me.
"If you promise me half of your prize money,"
"I'll make sure..."
"you survive."
She wants to be a spy?
That's the message she sent me.
- Kwang Soo. - But I said no.
- Let me see. - Let me see.
(Kwang Soo refused to betray his team members?)
- "It doesn't sound bad"? Hold on. - That's not it.
"It doesn't sound bad"? Let me see.
Kwang Soo. Seriously.
- Look. "It doesn't sound bad." - Gosh.
- Look. Kwang Soo. - "It doesn't sound bad"?
- Gosh. What is this? - Are you serious?
How could you do this?
I was going to say no.
- We're here. - Where are we?
You are now at First Street.
I think we'll get caught.
- Gosh. - By the way,
- They saw where we were going. - we'll waste too much time, right?
Think about it.
Let's say we eat something here.
It'll be the same even if we go to the seolleongtang restaurant.
(The seolleongtang restaurant?)
(The runaways had contacted Jong Kook's manager.)
- Hi, Se Chan. - Hi. Are you busy?
No, I'm not.
Do you know if there are any restaurants...
Jong Kook often goes to in Anyang?
Or any shops?
There's a seolleongtang restaurant...
near the intersection.
- A seolleongtang restaurant? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
- He goes there often. - Ask him if there's another place.
It's open 24 hours a day, so he often goes there after work.
Which high school did Jong Kook go to?
- Sinsung High School. - Sinsung High School.
Then let's go there.
Okay. Thank you.
(They made the manager believe they were heading to the school.)
- Let's go. - Let's go to the restaurant.
- That'd be better. - The thing is,
if we go in here,
we'll get lost and waste time.
Also, they already saw where we were going.
My IQ is over 100.
(Why does he suddenly reveal his IQ?)
Whose IQ isn't over 100?
I bet not all of us have an IQ over 100.
It's possible.
- Mine is over 100. - It's definitely possible.
I'm on Jae Seok's side.
What are you talking about? There's a reason for suspicion.
- If we divide... - Let's put it this way.
The sum of our IQs might not be over 300.
(It's simple.)
Right?
- Do you feel better now? - I feel better now.
- It's possible. - Okay.
It might not be over 300.
(Feeling better, they head to the seolleongtang restaurant.)
Gosh, this is frustrating.
(Not knowing where to go, the chasers call someone.)
Let's catch them soon.
- Hi, Haha. - Hi, Gap Jin.
- Hi, Gap Jin. - Yes?
- I have many questions for you. - You do?
You want to go home early today, don't you?
- Me? - Yes.
I always do.
- Then give us some information. - It's tempting.
What did you tell them?
- What did I tell them? - Yes.
- Jong Kook's favorite restaurant. - A restaurant?
(He tells them everything.)
- Oh, that place. - You know which one?
Of course, I do.
Isn't it near Jong Kook's home?
It's right next to my home.
- What else did you tell them? - What did you tell them?
That Jong Kook...
- went to Sinsung High School. - That's right.
(He even mentions the school, which was a bait.)
- They probably went to the school. - That must be it.
I love it.
Gap Jin, thank you.
Gap Jin, call me if you remember anything else.
Okay, I will.
Thank you. Get ready to go home early!
- Okay! - Okay!
It's either the restaurant or Sinsung High School.
- What's in that direction? - Is your home there?
Yes, my home is in that direction.
- Let's go there. - The thing is,
it's one p.m. right now.
- They must be going for lunch. - It's lunchtime.
- Should we check the restaurant? - Yes.
- They must be stalling for time. - Let's go there.
(They both head to the same place. What will happen?)
We won't even have time to enjoy the seolleongtang.
We have to drink it.
- Even if we burn our mouths. - Right.
(Glancing)
(Se Chan fiddles with his phone.)
Even if they win...
Hey. What are you doing? Let me see.
It's nothing.
(Se Chan is panicking.)
- It's nothing. - Let me see.
- I swear. - Give it to me.
I wasn't doing anything. Come on.
- Gosh. - "Haha, tell me where you are."
- Seriously, you're unbelievable. - It's not like that.
- It's not me. - If you continue to be this way,
- we will confiscate your cellphone. - Are you going to be this way?
Why did you ask?
I wanted to help the team...
by obtaining information.
Were you going to go there?
- Don't be ridiculous. - Were you?
Hey, I am the youngest member of this team.
No funny businesses. Confiscate his phone.
- This is driving me crazy. - Don't contact anyone.
Then give me your phone.
Give me your phone.
- Give me your phone. - Jae Seok.
Why are you fiddling with your phone?
What are you doing on your phone?
Someone contacted you, right?
- Did someone contact you? - Of course not.
Let's do this. Let's keep our phones,
but keep it out of sight. We need to call if we split up.
That's true.
We need to call each other.
Don't come up with a dirty scheme.
- I will keep my phone in my bag. - I won't take mine out.
Being a runaway is hard enough.
I don't want to have a war of nerves with you guys.
- I wanted to obtain information. - Let's not waste our energy.
Okay?
There is no way to obtain information.
Jong Kook, is there a story related to this place?
This underpass. It looks a bit...
Every place has a story.
(Of course, there is.)
Tell us. Before these apartments got built...
- This place was farmland. - Really?
You know Pyeongchon-dong in Anyang, right?
When I was in school,
Pyeongchon-dong was farmland.
People who owned that land must have become rich.
Is that the only thing you think about?
Seriously, Seok Jin.
It's great that you have such information.
That area became a new town.
If we turn right, we will reach Anyang Stream.
Cherry blossoms are beautiful there.
- They must be beautiful. - He is the guide of Anyang.
(Cherry blossoms make a grand sight along Anyang Stream.)
Cherry blossoms are beautiful there.
Have you had a date there?
- Of course, he has. - Yes, I have.
- When? In high school? - Did you wear a school uniform?
No, no.
- It was after I became an adult. - I see.
With how many people did you take a walk there?
I took a walk there with one person.
I see.
There is Anyang Stream to your right.
It must be beautiful in the spring.
Cherry blossoms are amazing here.
Cherry blossoms are beautiful here.
- This side used to be farmland? - Yes.
(He ruins the atmosphere again.)
(Seok Jin only cares about real estate.)
He only cares about real estate.
I only care about love...
and Seok Jin only cares about real estate.
There's a Starbucks.
A Twosome Place too.
"I should have invested in this piece of land."
- It's a drive-through. - I know.
To your left is Anyang Sports Complex.
We used to have school events at Anyang Sports Complex.
It seems like you liked your school a lot.
My school was a paradise.
I really liked my school.
(His face lights up when he talks about his school.)
Sinsung Festival was really famous.
- I see. - We were like celebrities.
Did singers come to perform at the festival?
No, they didn't. But we were like celebrities.
- Really? - Some students took the stage.
- Did you take the stage? - Of course, I did.
- I was a member of D.L. Boys. - D.L. Boys.
- It was a dance team. - Did you do the b-boying dance?
When D.L. Boys...
- danced... - What does D.L. stand for?
- It has to be about dance. - Dancing Little Boys.
How cute! Dancing Little Boys.
Why did you add "Little"?
The teachers called us...
Dirty and Lazy Boys.
- Dirty and lazy. - Dirty and lazy.
(His memories are scattered across Anyang.)
(Jong Kook's school days make up the biggest part of the memories.)
Dancing Little Boys.
How cute!
(Kim Jong Kook)
My school was a paradise.
I really liked my school. I was proud of my school.
- Is this the restaurant? - We need to park and eat quickly.
(They get out before the chasers arrive.)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Is there a back door?
There is a back door that is connected to the kitchen.
If something happens later,
may we escape through the back door?
Sure.
Is it this way?
What's the mission?
You can just eat.
- We can just eat. - Three seolleongtang.
Since the tables are too close to the entrance,
someone should keep a lookout.
We should take turns keeping a lookout.
- That would be for the best. - I will keep a lookout first.
Tell me when seolleongtang is served.
Three seolleongtang, please.
- Okay. - Three seolleongtang, please.
(He is very wary.)
There is no escape route.
We would like to pay first.
We might need to run away.
Isn't that a van? There is a van.
(He looks to all directions.)
- Jae Seok, run away! - Catch him!
(Jae Seok, run away!)
(Seok Jin suddenly appears.)
- Run away! - Catch him!
Catch him!
(It's a disaster! Let's run away!)
- Run away! - This is the restroom.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
- There they are. - Run away!
(The chasers approach the entrance of the restaurant.)
Hurry up. Hurry up.
- There they are. - Run away!
(The chasers approach the entrance of the restaurant.)
Where is the back door?
- Excuse me. - Where is the exit?
(The chasers who were approaching the restaurant...)
(begin to go after Se Chan.)
Run away!
- Run away! - Catch him!
- Catch him! - Run away!
- Where is the back door? - Excuse me.
Where is the exit? I am sorry.
The floor is slippery.
(They try to escape through the back door.)
Run away!
We need to catch him.
We need to catch Se Chan.
Run away!
(They run through the staff members' cars.)
(Haha is right behind Se Chan.)
Run away!
(In the end,)
(he gets his name tag ripped off.)
- We caught him! - Haha caught him.
- Haha caught him. - Yang Se Chan.
- Did we catch him? - Yes.
Where are the others?
Come here.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo escape through the back door.)
Jong Kook is over there. Jong Kook is over there.
- Hurry up and come here. - He is over there.
(They are less than 50m apart!)
Where is Jong Kook?
Come here.
Hide over here. What are we going to do?
Se Chan is out.
What is going on?
- As soon as we entered... - What is this?
Is this poop?
Hide, hide.
This is driving me crazy.
- Where are the other two? - Did you eat?
- What? - Did you eat?
- Did you eat lunch? - Where are the others?
- Let's go. - Where are the others?
- They must be inside the van! - They could be inside.
They could be inside the restaurant.
(They run towards the restaurant again.)
(I think I hear people running.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are behind the building to their right.)
(However, a truck blocks their view.)
Roll down the window.
They aren't inside, are they?
(They search the staff members' vehicles.)
Let's go up the building.
(Now is our chance!)
(They try to enter the building while they search the vehicles.)
It's over here.
(Are they in here?)
(They safely enter the building!)
There she is. So Min is over there.
There she is.
- I see Se Chan. - Jong Kook.
Thank goodness we didn't go outside.
Then we would have gotten caught.
(They barely manage to hide.)
We can't go to the places...
we talked about so far.
Se Chan will tell them everything.
(He can't help but laugh.)
For goodness' sake.
I can't believe the biggest tattletale got caught.
There are enemies everywhere.
How did they come right away?
They came here instead of the high school.
(Their feint didn't work.)
(What should we do?)
Earlier,
you hid only your head in the alley.
You have no talent in running.
Speak for yourself.
"Gosh, is this poop?"
What was that?
You saw how confident I was, right?
- Confident? - You saw, right?
Did you think they wouldn't see you if you don't see them?
Be quiet.
(He ignores Kwang Soo.)
Let's wait for them to leave...
and go back into the restaurant.
(Will they be able to succeed the mission?)
They escaped through the back door.
- I knew it. - They ordered seolleongtang.
They ordered seolleongtang, but couldn't eat it.
Really?
We should have come straight to the restaurant...
instead of chasing after Se Chan.
They didn't complete the mission.
- No, they didn't. - No.
Then we should go to Sinsung High School next.
You must have information.
- What information? - You aren't on their side anymore.
You are on our side.
You can't get their money anymore. We will share our money.
Really?
Oh, you will get goosebumps when you hear this.
There is a spy among you.
(He makes a shocking confession.)
Didn't you know? There is a spy among you.
Look at her eyes! Look at her eyes!
When he mentioned the spy...
What is going on?
When he mentioned the spy, she went...
There is a spy among you.
Gosh, So Min.
I will remember everything...
and deduct money later.
- You will give me points, right? - Of course.
I will deduct from your share later.
Call the runaways...
on the speakerphone.
- I will give it a try. - This team is much better.
In any case,
I can take money from the spy...
- and give it to you. - Actually, there are two spies.
I will reveal one of them while we finish eating here.
- There are two spies? - What was that?
(Spitting out)
What's wrong, So Min? Eat slowly.
It's not like that.
- Don't be flustered. - I am not a spy.
He didn't say anything.
He keeps looking at me.
Kwang Soo.
- Hello? - Yes.
- Where are you? - I'm elsewhere.
Kwang Soo,
I'm stuck here,
but you sound very calm.
That was expected.
Follow through with our plan, okay?
(He butts in.)
What did you say, Jae Seok?
- Follow through with our plan. - Right now...
Don't say anything else.
Don't say anything else. Follow our plan. That's it.
I'm in jail. He hung up.
(He hung up.)
- What's your plan? - Tell us.
What's your plan?
Sorry. Let's turn the cameras off. In 1, 2, 3.
Let's turn them back on. Turn them back on.
- Hold on. Turn them back on. - I'm going to block the cameras.
Turn them back on.
I'll close the door to the secret room.
(While Se Chan's life is threatened for what Jae Seok said...)
They'll suspect him.
I think...
you're the best in the world with things like this.
I got eliminated several times because of him.
You cause them to fight among themselves.
(That's an idiom.)
Look one way and row another. You know, right?
This is a season of high sky and plump horses.
(He replies with another idiom.)
(That's the only idiom he knows.)
When will you stop saying that one?
I won't.
(I'll use it next fall as well.)
We have to finish the seolleongtang and forget about one place.
It's too difficult to do two.
There's no mission easier than this.
- Right? - Right.
There's nothing easier than this.
Should we get seolleongtang delivered here?
That works.
- Call. - Should I call?
We can take it to go from the back.
- We can go secretly. - Right.
We don't need any side dishes. Just radish kimchi.
- Hello. - Can we...
- order to go? - Yes.
Sorry, but if you can pack them in plastic bowls,
we can pick them up in the back by the kitchen.
We'll eat and return them to you.
- Through the back? - Yes, through the back.
- Please call me. - All right.
- Excuse me. - Thank you.
Can you give us a lot of soup in the radish kimchi?
Can we get one radish kimchi?
Okay.
(They're done ordering seolleongtang to go.)
This is driving me insane.
Plan one.
What's the plan? There's none. But where were we going to go?
His house.
- See? - We were going to go there.
And then his high school.
We only talked about those two.
And Anyang First Street.
We were going to go around Anyang First Street...
and ask people whether Jong Kook came or not.
We were going to start the mission wherever he had been.
So what he's saying is that they didn't pick a certain place.
They were going to decide when they got there.
However,
these places were related to Jong Kook.
(They have no idea that the runaways ordered seolleongtang.)
Here. Be quiet.
Hello?
Yes, hello?
It's ready. Do you want to come to the back door?
Yes, thank you.
Can you put the bowls outside the back door...
like they're jjajangmyeon? We'll eat right there.
- The members aren't there, right? - They're not. I'll put it outside.
- We have to bring it here. - I'll do that right now.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
No problem.
This is driving me insane.
(The 1st hurdle is picking up the seolleongtang.)
Hey.
Let's ask him.
- Can you pick it up for us? - Can you pick it up?
We're sorry.
I'll take the camera.
Can you pick it up for us?
We're sorry.
- I can do it. - Okay, go.
Hurry up. Sorry.
(The cameraman leaves to pick up the seolleongtang.)
If they follow Yoon Sang back, we're dead.
(They're very anxious.)
(He makes it to the back door hidden from the members.)
(He contacts the employee stealthily...)
(and picks up the seolleongtang.)
(He has to deliver it safely.)
We're in trouble.
- Yoon Sang. - He's back.
Thank you.
(He delivered it safely!)
Yoon Sang, are they around?
- They're not. - You didn't see them?
Are they not inside?
- I didn't look inside. - Okay.
I went to the backdoor.
He's a coward as well.
He probably had no courage to look inside.
(Kwang Soo and his cameraman are alike.)
(They start eating.)
It's been 30 minutes since you completed a mission.
Here's the Chance Card Mission.
- Okay. - Okay.
This Chance Card Mission is called, Dice Up and Down.
All five of you will toss a die.
You need to guess whether the total will be greater or lesser than 17.
- Am I not in? - No.
(He's firm.)
He doesn't get to play?
- No. - Five of us?
It's less then.
Will you pick greater or lesser than 17?
- Lesser. - Should we go with that?
- Lesser is better. - I agree.
Isn't there a better chance?
5 times 3 is 15.
I think the chances are similar. That's why they're suggesting it.
- Lesser. - Lesser.
- Should we go with that? - Lesser than 17.
Ji Hyo, get one.
She always gets what she wants.
Here's a die. Go one at a time.
- Who's going first? Should I go? - Try it.
Lesser than 17.
- It's less. - Yes, it's less.
This is awkward to throw.
This is...
(He has to get a small number for a better chance to succeed.)
- 4. - 4.
- Okay. - 4.
(Jong Kook tosses 4.)
- Ji Hyo, go last. - You can't...
toss it all you want, so it's weird.
(Haha is next.)
That's true.
(Haha)
Four.
(Haha tosses 4.)
- 4 times 5 is 20. - Haha got 4.
This isn't good. You have to get 2 or 3.
You can do it.
You have to toss it lightly.
- 4. - 4.
(Seok Jin tosses 4.)
Why is it all 4? Is it the deadly 4?
- How's this possible? - Go.
- 4 times 3 is 12. - It's 12.
- We're at 12. - It's 12.
(So Min and Ji Hyo are left. Their sum has to be less than 5.)
Yes.
(So Min gets 1.)
Jong Kook, my level of contribution.
- 13. - My level of contribution.
- Less than 4. - You have to get less than 4.
Four is okay too.
4 is okay too. It's less than 17.
(Will she get less than 4 and win the mission?)
[VIU Ver] SBS E472 Running Man
"Find Kim Jong Kook Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(They win with a total of 16.)
- We got it, right? - Ji Hyo got three,
so the total is 16. You win.
Okay.
- Ji Hyo. - You did it.
- Pick one. - Go ahead, Se Chan.
I have a good feeling.
(What Chance Card did he pick?)
Okay.
This is good.
(Photo of Their Current Whereabouts)
Wasn't that good?
Will it be a full frame shot?
It has to be a wide shot. It can't be a small one.
(They don't know that the chasers won.)
- This is really good. - I'm going to miss this.
(They're drinking the soup.)
(They cleared the bowl.)
That was really good.
We have to clean up.
Here's a commemorative photo. In 1, 2, 3.
(Clicking)
What? Why did you take a picture of us?
(Why did he take a picture?)
(They don't know why their picture was taken.)
Here it is.
- Is this where they are now? - Where is this?
- What is this? - Where are they? You look.
No way.
- Where is this? What did they do? - They ordered food.
Is that ramyeon?
See where they got it from.
- It's stew. - It wasn't delivered.
- They had it to go. - They ordered from here.
Are they in the back?
The beacon does not shine on its own base.
- That... Hey. - They were going to do the mission.
I think so. They win if they eat this food.
- Right. - That's it.
I think it's the building behind us.
We can go and ask. Let's head out.
This is nearby.
Excuse me. Are these your containers? These?
- This is from here, right? - They had it delivered, right?
- It wasn't delivery. - Delivery.
- They ordered it to go. - We were right.
When was it?
They ordered 15 minutes ago.
What? We were here.
We were here.
- We were eating. - Did they order...
when we were inside?
They called to order.
- Did they call and then pick it up? - Yes.
They picked it up?
While we were inside?
- They're nearby. - My gosh.
This building.
This building. Jong Kook, this building.
Tell everybody to come.
Hold on. We're close.
Were the bowls empty?
- Were they empty? - They already ate.
They already ate? They were done?
Hey.
(They cleaned up, and they're going to go down.)
If we go now, we might get caught.
This is insane. I don't know what's going to happen.
There's a good chance they didn't move from here.
(Where did they hide?)
What? It's the same floor!
(What? It's the same floor!)
(Did So Min find the right building?)
Isn't this the same floor?
(It looks similar, but it's a different building.)
It's here!
(The chasers are certain this is the right building.)
Hey, block the entrance.
This is unbelievable.
(The runaways try to escape from the building across.)
(While the chasers go up to look...)
(He sees the chasers in front of the building.)
(They go inside without noticing Jae Seok.)
This is the place?
This is driving me nuts.
(He sees the chasers go inside and runs in the opposite direction.)
Hold on. Isn't it the basement?
(They have no idea the runaways are outside.)
(Kwang Soo runs away in the opposite direction as well.)
They're so clever.
Jae Seok.
Kwang Soo!
(When they exit the building,)
(Jae Seok gets in the car.)
They're nearby.
(Kwang Soo gets in as well.)
Isn't this it?
(They finally find the right building.)
Jae Seok is here.
- They left. - They left.
They left.
(They missed the runaways by a second.)
We're finally going to Anyang First Street.
We're so close getting the 3,000 dollars.
- We just have to eat pork cutlet. - We just have to eat it.
(We just have to eat pork cutlet.)
Where should we go next?
(The runaways are contemplating their next destination.)
He lived 40 years in Anyang and barely went anywhere.
He has a problem.
(It's difficult to find Jong Kook's favorite spots.)
(He looks up "Anyang" and "Jong Kook".)
Did you find anything?
(They find the pork cutlet diner Jong Kook approves of.)
(That's how they headed to Anyang First Street.)
- Let's rely on our friendship. - Let's do that.
- It's about time we do that. - Jae Seok.
- Let's divide the money in half. - Okay.
I feel bad for Se Chan, but he is with the chasers now.
It was Se Chan's fate.
(They cut ties with Se Chan.)
(What's this!)
It's Seok Jin.
- Answer it. - Should I answer it?
(It's a call from Seok Jin.)
- Hello. - Jae Seok.
Hey.
There are too many people on this team.
I am inclined to join your team.
What do you think? Do you need my help?
(What do you think? Do you need my help?)
Are you really alone?
I am really alone.
- Let's have a video call. - Let's have a video call.
Where are you?
Where are you? Switch over to a video call.
Do you see me?
I don't see you.
How do I do this?
Press the button for video call.
There is a button that is shaped like a camera.
- I am alone. - Where are you? Make a turn.
I am alone. I am on the roof.
- I am alone. Here. - You really are telling the truth.
Hold on. Maybe they're hiding. Tilt the camera to the floor.
I don't have time. I need to go.
What is it going to be?
Seok Jin, how are you going to help us?
We will go to 1 of the 2 places.
- We haven't made a decision yet. - Where will you go?
Anyang First Street or Sinsung High School.
If you lead the team to Sinsung High School...
- Okay. I will do that. - Okay.
Then let's take 1,000 dollars each.
We can't do that.
That's absurd.
You can't do that?
We can't do that when we are struggling this much.
- Seok Jin. - Give me 800 dollars.
The roof of my mouth is burnt.
Take 1,100 dollars each and give me 800 dollars.
Okay. They are coming. I am hanging up.
If this is for real, he will be a big help.
- He will be a big help. - Seriously.
If I take their side,
I would get 500 dollars at the very least.
(Will the runaways and Seok Jin's strategy succeed?)
They are daring.
- They are daring. - While we were in the room,
- they ordered takeout. - They ordered takeout.
It suits their style.
In any case, they completed two missions.
- My goodness. - They have one left.
They ridiculed us.
This is what Se Chan said to me.
When I asked him, "Who are you?"
He said, "We are a team."
"The runaways and I are a team."
- Stop lying. - He said that.
- So Min. - It's on the camera.
You will know once this episode airs.
Don't you remember what you said to me?
Do you know what she said to me?
She asked me to give her 300 dollars.
(She said she will be a spy.)
- When did I say that? - My goodness.
What is going on? Did they abandon you or what?
- We are a team. - Hold on.
Then I will help you.
Give me 300 dollars. Each of you can give me 100 dollars each.
(So Min made an offer to be a spy.)
Gosh, I can't trust So Min.
- Hey. - My goodness.
- Hey. - Gosh, I can't trust So Min.
You asked me to give you 300 dollars.
- Hey. - When did I do that?
Are you really going to be this way?
Shouldn't we hurry up and go somewhere?
I recommend Anyang First Street.
(The former runaway recommends Anyang First Street.)
(I have to lead them to Sinsung High School.)
Jong Kook's memories as a student would be at the school.
They wouldn't go there. I am 100 percent sure of it.
(They don't want to take a class.)
How are we supposed to trust you? We shouldn't trust a captive.
- Let me tell you this. - You know,
he will get some money...
- if they win. - No, I won't!
I don't think it's Anyang First Street.
We have to do the opposite of what Se Chan says.
- The school. - Let's go to the school.
I think we should hurry over to Sinsung High School.
We would be able to check right away.
Let's check and hit the road if we are wrong.
That would be for the best.
I think they went to Sinsung High School. It's close.
(The chasers set out for Sinsung High School.)
- When you get off, - Yes?
make sure people don't notice you.
- You know what I mean, right? - Of course.
We will go to the left.
- Please get moving right away. - Okay.
(They don't want to leave any evidence.)
(The 2 runaways run to the pork cutlet diner.)
Hurry up.
(They will succeed if they eat the pork cutlet Jong Kook ate.)
- No way. - Hello.
- Hello. - No way.
Ma'am,
this is the only exit, right?
- There is another exit. - Is there another exit?
Please give us two pork cutlets.
- All right. - Thank you.
Kwang Soo, the exit is here.
There is a back door.
(They find an emergency exit at the back.)
- This is good. - There is a back door.
There is a back door.
(The back door and the front door)
It's hard to track them down this way.
(The chasers are on their way to Sinsung High School.)
(They try to call the runaways.)
They wouldn't answer.
They wouldn't answer your call.
I am annoyed because we came so close to catching them.
It's a call from Haha.
- Kwang Soo. - Haha.
I could see that you didn't skip a meal.
(Oh, that's right.)
Did you enjoy the seolleongtang?
It was so good.
We will be done after we eat this here.
I have a question, Kwang Soo.
(What did you say just now?)
Do you really think you will win?
Why did you say that?
We will be done after we eat this here.
- I have a question, Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Do you really think you will win? - He hung up.
- What? - Jae Seok keeps hanging up.
(Flustered)
Are you insane?
You gave them a hint!
- Did I do that? - You talked about eating.
- Did I do that? - For goodness' sake.
How could you...
(He confessed that he is at a restaurant.)
Did...
Did Kwang Soo just give me a hint over the phone?
I think he said it without thinking but...
"We will be done after we eat this here."
If he was telling the truth,
they aren't at Sinsung High School.
- That's right. - Gap Jin didn't tell them...
- about Sinsung Festival. - They don't know about it.
He didn't tell them about the festival.
(They don't know that Jong Kook gave a performance at the festival.)
Why don't we go to Anyang First Street?
(Will they go to Anyang First Street?)
If we turn right, we will reach Anyang First Street.
Let's go to Anyang First Street.
Please turn right and go to Anyang First Street.
They are at Anyang First Street.
At the entrance,
we should ask people if they saw them.
Then we will know where they headed.
Let's get off at the entrance. That's the main street.
- Let's do that. - That's the main street.
We will hit the main street right away.
This is Anyang First Street.
We should get off here. Let's get off.
The pork cutlet is here.
- Thank you. - Here you go.
Thank you.
It's a hearty dish.
(This famous pork cutlet was approved by the son of Anyang.)
(The runaways will win once they eat it.)
You know how I eat pork cutlet, right?
I eat one piece by itself and mix the other piece.
I wish there was some corn.
(Peeking)
(They're not here, right?)
Let's pay first.
- We would like to pay. - Okay.
Do you have any corn?
(Do you have any corn?)
- Why are you looking for corn? - We would like to pay.
(We are runaways.)
I usually mix it with rice.
(Running away should come after eating.)
To run away,
we need to pay in advance.
(The chasers search Anyang First Street.)
This street is...
(There is a fast-food restaurant Jong Kook used to frequent.)
They aren't here, are they?
- I don't think they are here. - Did Yu Jae Seok come?
- No. - My goodness.
Is he on the second floor?
- Is no one here? - No one is here.
(The runaways begins to cut the pork cutlet.)
- We need to eat everything, right? - Yes.
You succeed as soon as you are done.
Has anyone seen Yu Jae Seok?
Has anyone seen Lee Kwang Soo?
(While the chasers look for them)
(Peeking)
Let's take a peek outside between bites.
Look closely.
(The chasers begin to close in on them.)
Why is there a crowd?
There is a crowd.
(The street of Anyang is pretty empty,)
(but there is a crowd at one spot.)
They must be over there!
(Something doesn't feel right.)
At this rate, I would get an upset stomach.
- Why is there a crowd? Why? - Why is there a crowd?
What is it? Are they up there?
Up there?
(The residents of Anyang point to one place.)
This is it.
(It's the pork cutlet diner.)
(Startled)
They're here!
(He spots the chasers.)
They're here! Let's move!
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo escape through the back door.)
Jong Kook is here.
What? There they are!
- Where are they? - Where?
Run away!
(Running)
(At that moment)
My goodness.
(Jong Kook enters through the back door.)
(They get caught!)
(Jong Kook charges forward.)
Run!
Get them!
(They run back into the pork cutlet diner.)
(My goodness!)
(Kwang Soo locked the door.)
(I have to survive!)
(The master of betrayal tries to escape through the front door.)
I got you!
(Jae Seok is apprehended.)
So this is where you were.
They were eating.
My goodness.
Kwang Soo locked the door.
(The man who fell behind cries out in desperation.)
Kwang Soo!
- Come here. - Kwang Soo locked the door.
(After showing the true side of their friendship,)
(Kwang Soo escapes the pork cutlet diner.)
(He runs away without the production crew.)
(The production crew filmed this with a cellphone.)
(Kwang Soo-Papillon of Anyang)
- He got out this way. - That's right.
- He's out of the building. - He's out of the building.
- Did he come out? - He came out.
- Did Kwang Soo leave? - Which way did he go?
- Which way did he go? - That way.
He went that way.
(Kwang Soo managed to lose the chasers.)
I remember what Jong Kook said.
He said the mother of the woman he dated in the past...
ran a restaurant there.
(There are a few places I can think of off the top of my head.)
(I have memories of the underground shopping area.)
(His ex-girlfriend's mom ran a restaurant there.)
I can ask people in one of these old buildings.
Hello.
Did Jong Kook ever buy shoes here?
Okay, thank you.
- He's gone far from here. - I think so too.
He won't stay nearby.
Hello, did Jong Kook ever come here?
He didn't come today.
- Did he ever come? - No.
Thank you.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Jae Seok. - He's right there.
- He's right there. - There he is.
Right there.
(Kwang Soo got caught.)
- There. It's Kwang Soo. - There he is.
Darn it.
Good luck!
(He needs one more place to win.)
There!
(The chasers run after him across the street.)
Haha, the traffic light!
(Gosh!)
(The chasers are across the street.)
(They dash across the crosswalk.)
He's too fast!
(7 Running Man members versus Kwang Soo in the middle of the day)
(They're only 50m away from him.)
(Will he get caught...)
(or get away?)
Kwang Soo! It's me.
Kwang Soo!
(He doesn't look back once.)
Opposite side.
Go to the opposite side.
Opposite side! Go to the opposite side.
So Min, go the opposite way.
Opposite side?
- Where? - Right!
Go right, So Min.
Come this way!
(Runaway Kwang Soo enters the underground shopping area.)
Give me money.
Give me money or a credit card. Hurry. Anything.
(The last runaway enters the underground shopping area.)
Excuse me.
(Jae Seok is right after him.)
(They enter through different entrances.)
Food.
Where's the tteokbokki place?
Tteokbokki place.
(He needs to copy one thing Jong Kook did here to win.)
- Where's Kwang Soo? - He went there.
(Will Kwang Soo accomplish the mission?)
Sir!
Anything. Here.
(Jong Kook is sprinting.)
What should I get?
(Jong Kook probably got something from the general store.)
Hurry. Anything.
(Will he buy Jong Kook's favorite toy and win?)
Anything.
(The son of Anyang is here.)
Anything!
(Ripping)
(Kwang Soo is caught.)
(Jong Kook catches Kwang Soo 1 second before he buys something.)
Will you or I win? This is to be continued.
You call yourself a person?
The chasers win!
- All right! - I just had to pay.
I just had to pay.
- Goodness. - Spies are the scariest.
This is the 3,000 dollars as promised.
- Really? - Goodness.
They weren't lying?
I'll give it to you, Jong Kook.
Really? Okay.
Give them 1,000 dollars. That's too much.
Why would you give them 3,000 dollars?
That's why you ran so hard too.
I thought this was so funny.
"Kwang Soo, it's me."
(As soon as the tables were turned)
(Let's split the prize money.)
(Don't forget.)
- 3,000 dollars? - He was so close.
For a moment, I didn't know which side to take.
- I didn't know. - Right?
That's what I thought.
- Seok Jin, - I sped up then slowed down.
you're the worst person, so go to the end.
(You're the worst person, so go to the end.)
(You won't get any money.)
- Do you trust him? - Do I get a chance?
If you have a conscience, come here.
- Do I get a chance? - Yes.
Se Chan was on that team,
and it felt like he cared about them,
- Still. - but he kept saying First Street.
I kept on saying we had to go there.
- You brat. - What?
(I kept on saying we had to go there.)
(Hitting)
- You betrayed me in the beginning. - Look at this brat.
We didn't betray you.
Let me say one thing.
Who locked the door?
When Jae Seok got eliminated, who locked the door?
Are you human? Hey.
The three of us...
- Three of us? - will get 1,000 dollars each.
- What? - All right.
- It's over. - It's over then.
We'll do what we want with the money?
- It's up to you. - Okay.
- Can I get 100 dollars? - You're valuable.
Go ahead.
That's generous.
- You guys. - That's generous.
Share, okay?
(Be good friends.)
- What's wrong with you? - I'll give you 100 dollars.
- What's wrong with him? - Share.
I can't give you more.
You don't have to join if you don't want it.
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
Give me enough to pay for my gas back to Seoul.
Submit a receipt.
(Submit a receipt.)
- I'll send you the money. - What is he saying?
- Submit a receipt. - Is he for real?
- Haha, but I... - Look at the colors.
- I only did my best. - I kept on mentioning First Street.
Isn't this unfair?
- Come here, Se Chan. - Okay.
- He deserves something. - Great work.
- Good job. - Thank you!
- You can go home. - Thank you.
What did he do?
- Hey, why? - He behaves well.
(He behaves well.)
(I'll behave nicely too.)
(Am I cute?)
Who should we pick?
(Pick me.)
Pick, pick
(She tries to act cute using her hips.)
(Pick me up, lift me)
No, not you.
He said it's not you.
(After he's seen everything)
I can't give you any. You're so nasty.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Find Kim Jong Kook Race is over.)
Thank you for the money!
(It's getting chilly out, so they film inside.)
(Food is everything.)
(Each with their embellished dreams, they enter...)
(the Joker's house.)
(The Joker has started playing a game.)
(They can't laugh.)
(They've been doing this on Running Man for 9 years.)
(That was close.)
(Do you think this is over?)
(This is the first time he cried too.)
(Can they resist laughing and find the Joker?)
- What's wrong? - Don't do this.
(Joker's House)