(At last,)
(the day has come.)
(9 Years of Running Man)
(The fan-meet of Running Man is finally held.)
(The race starts.)
(To repay the support of 9 years from their fans,)
(they went on a long journey of 100 days in preparing...)
(the first fan-meet of Running Man in Korea.)
(A fancy transformation of members you can only see here)
(A series of thrilling performances with an explosion of talent)
(For 9 years, the fans have kept Running Man going.)
(And the members share their sincerest appreciation with them.)
(The grand finale of the fan-meet...)
(will be revealed shortly.)
(And last week)
(Solve the Secret in Prophecy: Find the Deity Race)
(Protect the deity of light and the prophet.)
(Eliminate deity of darkness.)
Good job!
(A fierce war to win hints about the deities and prophet.)
(Everyone showed awful dance skills.)
(And the worst dancer shows up.)
(I'm Crazy So Min!)
(Jong Kook and Sunny get a hint after winning the mission.)
(The deity of darkness debuted over 10 years ago.)
(The prophet isn't in his or her 50s.)
(Say a math formula you know.)
(The mention of a math formula spikes up her blood pressure.)
(You must stay calm even when they ask you...)
(flustering questions.)
(He's the calmest.)
(Jong Kook is so calm.)
(Haha and Jang Ye Won wins a hint after a mission.)
(Kwang Soo and Sun Mi win a hint too.)
(The deity of darkness was not born in the Year of the Horse.)
(What?)
(But...)
(there's a picture on the back of the hint card?)
(What do the pictures on the hint cards mean?)
The hint for the deity of darkness is at stake on this group mission.
It's Upgraded Speak with Your Actions.
(Upgraded Speak with Your Actions)
The staff will give you a keyword. All six of you will have...
10 seconds to describe the keyword only through your actions.
The last member will have to get the keyword right.
If you get at least 1 keyword right out of 2,
all six of you will get a hint about the deity of darkness.
- This is important. - It's a good one.
If one of us is the deity, that person will ruin our chance.
- Right. We must do our best. - The deity of darkness.
After discussing it among yourselves, pick your spots.
- Okay. - Okay.
- This keyword is about a place. - Place.
- Okay. - It's a place.
Ready, set, go.
(Public restroom)
Go ahead.
- It must be hard. He just sighed. - He signed.
(Man and woman)
(In a rectangular slot...)
(Checking)
- That's it. Turn around now. - That's it?
- Hold on. - Okay.
- Ten seconds have already passed. - Let me organize my thoughts first.
Is Haha the deity of darkness?
(Public restroom)
(Woman and man)
(She opens up...)
(the rectangular slot.)
There you go.
- Your 10 seconds are up. - There you go. Yes.
(She strikes a pose to do her business.)
- I think I know. Aren't I right? - What is that?
- Yes. You're right. - You were trying to describe this.
Is it that hard?
(It's Seok Jin's turn.)
Just do exactly what I did.
What?
- What? - What?
(Flicking his finger)
Did you do that?
(His finger messes it up.)
(Did you do that?)
Not at all. You saw how I described it.
- Exactly. Seok Jin. - Did he do something weird?
- Your time is up. Ji Hyo, go ahead. - Seok Jin seems fishy.
(What is that?)
- That was so weird. - What do you mean?
Your description didn't make sense.
- What was that? - Did he do something weird?
(Woman and woman, It's getting worse.)
(In a box...)
(Going back and forth)
Ji Hyo.
(After opening the door and entering,)
Your time is up.
(you sit and entice someone.)
(Come on in.)
- What? - What is that?
Ji Hyo.
See, Seok Jin? My gosh. It's 100 percent him.
I didn't get it either.
- Come on. - But how could you not?
(While Seok Jin's finger action is messing it up, Ye Won begins.)
(Confused)
- Hold on. How? What's that? - Your time is up.
(She finishes up with the finger.)
(What's up with the finger?)
- All right. What's the answer? - Hold on.
It's a place, right?
- Yes, it is. - I think I know.
You can figure it out. You can do it.
You and I open up the door and go inside.
(Remembering the description again)
- All right. "Come in"? - "Come in."
See? Because of that, the whole thing changed.
- Wait. It's not that place, is it? - I'll give you five seconds.
I don't get it.
- What are you thinking about? - Come on.
A man and a woman go... I can't say that, right?
Where are you going?
- Okay. I got it. - What's the answer?
The answer is...
5, 4,
- He doesn't know. - Three...
An inn?
(An inn?)
- The answer is the public restroom. - What?
- That was the mildest answer I had. - Hold on. Wait.
Here's why. Seok Jin did this out of the blue.
- That came out of nowhere. - Why did you do that?
- You did that. Didn't you? - I didn't. When did I do that?
- Why do this in the restroom? - I thought...
- You did that too. - Yes.
- I did that too. - What is this?
Gosh, something is fishy about you.
- Something is fishy. - What do you think about that?
- Who wants to go first? - Let's switch.
- Let's switch. We should... - Let's switch.
- Sunny, do you want to go first? - because...
- This is your spot, Seok Jin. - Seok Jin should go second.
You'll know which one seems suspicious from there.
(Seok Jin will go second.)
Here's your next keyword.
The category is food.
Start.
(Jjamjjamyeon)
(How will Sunny describe jjamjjamyeon?)
Right away?
(There's a round bowl.)
(It's halved.)
(As for jjajangmyeon,)
(we slurp the noodles.)
(As for jjamppong, we drink the soup.)
Stop.
Seok Jin. Get ready to describe it.
What on earth is that?
(Half...)
(a circle.)
(Slurping jjajangmyeon)
(That's it.)
(And as for jjamppong,)
(drink the whole cup.)
- What? - Stop.
(The paper cup shows up all of a sudden.)
Please continue.
- I didn't do that. I did this. - Juice.
That's not it. Why did you do that?
(The first step is wrong.)
(Half a square.)
(Drink jjamppong.)
(And roll the jjajangmyeon.)
(And drink it.)
Stop. Next.
(The description is going nowhere. It's unsalvageable.)
(She makes the same mistake.)
(Half the square.)
(She finishes up by drinking the soup.)
- Go ahead. - What?
This has gotten weird again.
I can't memorize this.
(The square is halved.)
(And she drinks it.)
- No, it was weird. - I knew it right away.
All right. Stop it.
Jong Kook, what's the answer?
Hold on. What's wrong with everyone?
- It's a square. Cut it. - You cut it.
But you're drinking a glass all of a sudden.
Then you mix it.
(This round is a dud too.)
Chinese hot pot?
- That's incorrect. - But he got close.
Try to guess from Sunny's descriptions.
- Yes. Try to guess it. - I figured it out right away.
There you go. Yes.
Jjamjjamyeon.
(The answer is jjamjjamyeon.)
I figured it out too!
- Everyone knew it. - Listen.
I thought about saying that as my answer.
I thought it was a watermelon.
- What? - I thought it was a watermelon.
When you have a watermelon, you cut it like this.
- Sunny did a fantastic job. - She's good.
It's not that.
Seok Jin added his own thoughts.
Hey, she ate half of it...
- and drank the juice of the other. - You shouldn't think.
You should have done what she exactly did.
Why did you add your ideas?
I did that because I thought it was a watermelon.
- Don't do that. - It might be wrong.
- Something is fishy about you. - Why was it jjamjjamyeon?
All right. You have failed your second mission.
But we could have gotten the second one.
The way she described it was weird.
Had you not added your own ideas...
Hey, it was so obvious. After this, she did this.
Seok Jin seems suspicious.
- No, it's not me. - I like playing games.
It's not me. It's really not me.
(Seok Jin's identity seems more suspicious now.)
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
- Just do what you saw. - Okay.
Don't add your ideas.
All right. I'll make a clean one.
- The category is food. - Food. That's great.
Start.
(Keyword: pickled radish cubes)
(Gosh, you guys are unbelievable.)
I guess something must have gone terribly wrong.
I guess it's a weird keyword.
Ready, set, go.
(He's explaining fried chicken first.)
(Pickled radish cubes)
(Crunchy)
(What's that?)
(The answer is not...)
(fried chicken.)
(It's the pickled radish cube.)
(His 10 seconds to describe it are over.)
Go ahead.
(She must explain this to Kwang Soo now.)
My gosh.
My gosh. That was such a hard one.
(Fried chicken...)
(is not the answer.)
There you go.
(You...)
(dip the fried chicken in this.)
(After describing the mysterious dipping sauce for fried chicken,)
(it's Kwang Soo's turn to describe.)
(Gnawing)
(Kwang Soo is fiercely eating the ribs.)
(The answer is not that.)
That's wrong.
That's wrong, you punk.
(He couldn't help it.)
He's making the whole thing weird.
Come on, Kwang Soo.
(Gnawing on the meat so there's no morsel left)
(That's not the answer.)
(It's not?)
There you go.
(Gnawing on the ribs just like he saw)
That's not it?
(The round thing is the answer.)
It looks the same. It's not?
(Confused)
You...
(He's losing it at the round meatball.)
I can't believe this.
(Gnawing on the round food)
(It's not the answer.)
(This is the answer.)
(Her 10 seconds are over.)
What's the answer?
You have to get it right. If you don't, we'll suspect you.
You'll be the deity of darkness.
What is it?
It's not hotteok?
My gosh. Kwang Soo ruined everything.
- Seriously. - Name a dish.
- Four, three, - There aren't that many dishes.
- two, one. - Just say something.
- What's the answer? - Hotteok.
- Hotteok? - Hotteok?
(Her answer is hotteok.)
(That's incorrect.)
The right answer is pickled radish cubes.
But why did you describe pork ribs?
- Hey. - Why did you describe that?
- It was right up to here. - No.
- I took out the fried chicken. - You knew the answer, right?
- No. - You didn't know?
- I didn't know the answer. - It wasn't pork rib?
Why did you do this?
- I thought it was pork ribs. - I thought it was a rib.
- That was wrong. - Don't add your ideas.
I copied her exactly the same.
That was a close one.
So Min, why don't you go first?
- Kwang Soo should answer it. - Kwang Soo, you'll answer it.
- Yes, you should answer it. - Let's get it right this time.
- Let's do this. - You keep changing things.
- This time, the category is... - I'm scared.
a place of entertainment.
- Place? - Here we go.
- It's a place. - Place.
- Let's do this. - Place.
- I'll get it right. - Place of entertainment.
Here's the keyword.
(Keyword: Carousel)
Start.
(You get on the wooden horse and it goes around in a circle.)
(The descriptions are exactly the same up to Sun Mi.)
Okay.
(How will Se Chan who seems to have figured out describe it?)
I think he's going to change it.
Come on. That's wrong!
(That's not the carousel. You're horseback riding.)
- When did I do that? - Hey.
That's wrong!
(It's getting worse.)
(This time, it has become horse racing.)
No!
- What is this? - No.
What's the answer?
- The horse racetrack! - It's wrong?
The answer is carousel.
- Gosh, come on. He's unbelievable. - Wait.
- Didn't I describe that? - He's the culprit.
- I knew it was carousel. - Come on.
We will not provide you the hint...
about the deity of darkness.
(They fail to acquire a hint.)
The deity of darkness is here.
- That was so close. - It's definitely one of us.
(Can Se Chan or Kwang Soo be the deity of darkness?)
- We'll start the race now. - Okay.
(They head to the place of the last race with the suspects.)
(They arrive at a place for their last mission.)
My gosh. There's a book.
Actually, you might be able to find some hints here.
"I will depict the deity of darkness in the prophecy in advance."
"Find and eliminate the deity."
- There must be a hint. - I thought so too.
I'm sure of it.
"At some point, the deity began to bother innocent people..."
"and formed an evil group."
- Let's take a photo of him. - Why?
- Just in case. - Why are you taking my photo?
- Take your selfie and send it. - Okay.
I didn't know I could do that.
- I took photos of three members. - Suspicious members?
It's a collection of ugly guys.
(No. It's a collection of ugly guys.)
- You should take a selfie. - You should take a selfie.
Everyone should a selfie.
Take a selfie.
- I collect these kinds of photos. - Is that so?
Yes. I have a collection of ugly guys.
I'm curious about that.
- You should hold an exhibit. - I will.
I'll tell you the rules.
Protect the deity of light. And Eliminate the deity of darkness.
It's War of Black and White: Protect the Light.
Throughout the building,
- there are hints about the prophet, - This is hard.
the deity of light, and deity of darkness.
After an hour, a platform that will reveal the identities...
will be open to you.
Only the deity of darkness should go up on the platform.
If the deity of darkness is on the platform,
humans and the deity of light will win.
If a human or the deity of light goes on the platform,
the deity of darkness will win the race by him or herself.
However, before the platform is open...
if one of the deities gets eliminated, the race will be over.
It will be over?
But if the prophet gets eliminated, you won't get any more hints...
and won't have a way to figure out who the deity of darkness is.
- We must be careful. - We must figure out who that is.
We must protect the prophet.
It's complicated.
- Gosh. - This is hard.
And somewhere in the building, a special temple stands.
At a specific time, the temple will open twice.
Two members who have found the Temple Summons...
can select a member each and enter the temple with them.
When all of the four members put their hands on the platform,
depending on the presences of the deities and the prophet,
the color will change accordingly.
You'll head to the place where your last race will be held.
(Which team will win the final race?)
- Okay. - Let's go!
(Kwang Soo is always the most suspicious member.)
(He checks the hint he won in the previous mission.)
I don't get this one. The photo means the opposite.
(There's a white swan, but the title is "Black Swan".)
Is there a secret behind the photo?
Really? Is there a hint in the photo?
(So Min told him about the back of the hint card.)
(He checks the back of the hint card.)
"White Cat".
(It says "White Cat", but it's a photo of a black cat.)
It's a black cat, but it says it's a white cat here.
I don't get the back of the hint card.
What does the photo mean? It's the opposite of the title.
(So Min doesn't know what it means either.)
(He realized something.)
(Did Se Chan figure out the meaning behind it?)
You know...
This isn't the black swan we think of.
It should say it's white, but it says black. It's the opposite.
So Min told me about this.
Sunny...
S-U-N.
She can be the deity of light.
But the opposite of that is darkness.
(Is Sunny the deity of light?)
I thought that it could be Sunny when we first started.
But Haha...
(But Sunny suspects Haha.)
He's not the deity of darkness, right?
Jae Seok seems a bit suspicious too.
(Their suspicion goes in a circle.)
Jae Seok...
(Everyone keeps suspecting each other.)
4, 3...
(Can they solve the secret and find the deity of darkness?)
Deity of darkness.
Go away!
The race starts.
(The race starts.)
Jae Seok, I thought about who it could be.
- What is it? - The deity of darkness...
can't be Seok Jin or Jang Ye Won.
But the deity of darkness likely took the other bus.
(It's likely the deity got on the bus with the deity of light.)
With that said,
the chances of Haha and Jang Ye Won's winning are low,
but they did their best to win...
because one of them might be the deity of darkness.
- No. - What?
(He sounds firm.)
(What?)
Are you serious? How could you...
I'm sharing my secret with you after thinking about it.
Go on.
But...
I got a hint that Jang Ye Won couldn't be the deity of darkness.
- Right. - That leaves...
- Haha. - It's highly likely that it's Haha.
(This is Kwang Soo's speculation.)
Your detective skill is very elementary.
(After giving it some thought...)
(I can't believe him.)
You're at the first level.
Think harder on it. Okay?
I think you're a human,
but you can walk around and face the penalty later.
Can I wear this?
(Sunny is looking for hints.)
(What?)
(It was hidden inside the prop box for a drama.)
(She's the first one to find a hint.)
(The youngest member of Running Man is not the prophet.)
(What?)
(Prophet, Deity of Darkness, Deity of Light)
(This doesn't apply to Yang Se Chan.)
I'm really surprised right now. Is Se Chan the youngest here?
(The youngest, Se Chan, faces a defeat.)
- So Min wasn't the youngest. - No.
He was born in December.
My goodness.
My gosh, what happened to Se Chan?
There are no hints.
(What?)
(He quickly runs toward something.)
(Jae Seok has spotted...)
There are two.
(Hint envelope)
(Empty hint envelope)
My gosh, someone already...
(The second envelope is empty as well.)
(Sighing)
This is so upsetting.
(This is so upsetting.)
(Meanwhile, So Min was passing by at that time.)
(Knock, knock)
(Knocking)
(It's Jae Seok.)
(Doing her cute act)
(Puffing her cheeks)
Stop it. Stop doing that.
(Aren't I cute?)
So Min. Hold on. She's...
(As soon as she disappears, he starts suspecting her.)
There's Jae Seok. He can be the deity of darkness too.
(So Min suspects him too.)
So Min.
(So Min heads somewhere as soon as she enters.)
(What's this?)
(These are empty.)
- They are empty. - Someone already took them.
(She rips a page from her notebook.)
(She starts writing something down.)
Why would you write, "You're a fool" and put it in there?
(I got you! Silly you.)
I want someone to read it and be annoyed by this.
It's hard, you know.
Gosh, So Min.
Did you find anything?
To me, you're one of the candidates for the deity of darkness.
- So Min. - Yes?
(Speaking in a low voice)
I'm glad you brought it up.
What are you doing?
(Trembling in fear)
I'm...
the deity of darkness.
What are you talking about?
(Glancing)
(You're the deity of darkness?)
- Really? That's not true. - Yes.
I'm the deity of darkness.
No, you're not. Why are you doing this to me?
- Really? Are you? - Yes.
Seriously? Are you really the deity of darkness?
- Are you serious? - I told you.
I told you.
I told you I'm the deity of darkness.
- All of a sudden? - Be quiet.
Spare me.
Spare me just this once. I won't tell anyone. Spare me.
Can you really keep it a secret?
- Are you really the deity? - I'll spare you if you can.
Right now, I have to go look for the deity of light.
Don't lie down there. Don't do that.
(Let me show you another cute act.)
(She flails to survive.)
Get up.
- Jae Seok. You'll tell me... - Yes?
- get up and rip it off, right? - No.
(Jae Seok leaves her without a fuss.)
My gosh.
(He told her that he's the deity of darkness.)
(Was he telling the truth?)
What is this?
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook has been looking for hints.)
(He finds So Min's empty envelope.)
They already opened it.
"I got you! Silly you."
Doesn't it look like Ji Hyo's handwriting?
(It's me, So Min. You were duped once again.)
(Ji Hyo finds So Min's envelope too.)
(You were duped, Ji Hyo.)
What?
(She spots a suspicious-looking picture.)
("Broad Daylight")
Why is there a moon when it's called "Broad Daylight"?
(The picture shows the opposite of its name.)
(There are more.)
(It's called "Dark Clouds", but it shows white clouds.)
What does this mean?
(They all find mysterious pictures.)
"White Cat"?
(Unlike its name, it's a picture of a black cat.)
(They've found a total of 4 pictures so far.)
"Blue Sea in Daylight"?
(Unlike its name, it's a picture of a dark sea.)
(What do these pictures mean?)
All the pictures show the opposite of their names.
Exactly. But I don't know what they mean.
Perhaps, the hints that we got mean the opposite.
Right.
I suspected that too, but why was that necessary?
(Could the hints mean the opposite as well?)
It's called "Broad Daylight".
- But is it dark? - But there's a dark moon.
So I suspect that the deity of darkness...
and that of light are the same person.
Sun Mi is the deity of light.
(Blurting)
No, she isn't.
No, listen.
I got a hint that said she wasn't.
But the pictures and their names mean the opposite.
The hint said that the deity of light...
wasn't in their 20s.
That's why Sun Mi was the sole exception.
But if we think oppositely,
the deity of light is Sun Mi.
(She's very simpleminded.)
Ye Won, I thought you were smart.
I get that.
But if that's the case, we'd know the truth too easily.
So this is what I think.
The hint said the deity of light...
- Goodness. - wasn't in their 20s.
But perhaps, that could be about the deity of darkness.
It could've been a hint about the deity of darkness.
(The deity of light isn't in their 20s.)
(Could the hint be talking about the deity of darkness?)
It's a picture of a black cat, but it's called "White Cat".
It's the opposite.
I think the hints for the deities of light and darkness have switched.
(She's positive.)
Soon, all the humans and the deity of light...
will gather together to check the prophecy.
In this prophecy,
there's a hint about the deity of light and an order...
to get rid of you, the deity of darkness.
If you chant the spell in order to make a fake prophecy,
all the "deity of light" in the prophecy...
will turn into "deity of darkness".
Once the humans read this, they will believe...
that the deity of light is actually the deity of darkness...
and will try to eliminate that deity.
(The hints will be changed as well.)
It's the same for the hints as well.
The hints will be switched.
The hints regarding the deity of light will be...
about the deity of darkness, and vice versa.
Are these hints fake?
- I think the hints are... - I think...
the hints for the two deities have switched.
- It's the opposite. - Right.
- So... - It's so weird.
I think I get it.
- Why isn't she talking much? - Look at the pictures.
The pictures?
- What do you mean? - Look at the hints.
(So Min starts to tell the others about this secret.)
It's the opposite. The hints regarding...
the two deities have switched.
If you think like that...
(Dashing)
(Who is running?)
(Ripping)
(So Min is out.)
So Min, a human, is out.
She's out?
No way.
Who did it?
- I just saw her. - No way.
- She went over there. - Really?
She went that way? That's where she was attacked.
And there...
Who was there?
(Who was in that area?)
I saw Se Chan there.
- Se Chan? - So Min went over there,
and he was there.
- But I just saw her. - Really?
(Is Se Chan the one who eliminated her?)
I think Se Chan is the deity of darkness.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, everyone is suspecting Se Chan.)
Hold on, Kwang Soo.
(He suspects something.)
Why is a moving camera shooting you?
(Why is a moving camera shooting you?)
(It's a customized camera just for him.)
When did you come here?
- I mean... - He keeps following me.
When did you come?
You're too suspicious to hang around with.
Can I not have a moving camera with me?
- I mean... - I'm 35 years old.
Come on. Why are you acting so suspiciously since last week?
Don't be suspicious of things like this.
- I'm not. - What was I last week?
You were a citizen.
And who was the bad guy?
- I'm sorry. - It was you.
(He slaps Se Chan.)
- I'm sorry. - Right?
You were just...
I didn't realize this while watching it...
but come to think of it, it's infuriating.
All right. You can go for now.
But be careful. These could all serve as hints.
Let's find more hints.
Yes, let's do that.
This is what I think.
Everyone, freeze.
The temple's door has opened.
(Finally, the door has opened.)
The temple's door has opened?
Se Chan, you were summoned.
You must go to the temple.
Who summoned me?
You should go there first.
(Unknowing who did it, he heads for the temple.)
He's being summoned since he's suspicious, right?
I'm an innocent citizen.
I don't believe you.
They summoned me?
I wonder who it is.
(Sun Mi was the one.)
No way.
What is this?
What was this again?
(Temple Summons)
I'd like to summon...
Se Chan.
(She summoned the suspicious Se Chan.)
(Suddenly)
Seok Jin?
Did you get a Temple Summons?
- What? - Did you get a Temple Summons?
- What about you? - I have one.
(Seok Jin is the second one to show up.)
(While searching for more hints,)
Okay, okay.
(he found a Temple Summons as well.)
Did you summon me?
No, I didn't.
Then whom did you summon?
I'm about to. I'm still thinking.
- Whom will you pick? - I'll...
I'll summon...
Jae Seok.
(Seok Jin summons Jae Seok.)
Why him?
Why?
(He's been suspecting him for a long time.)
We need to get him in here.
Jae Seok, you've been summoned.
Me?
I'll be back. Remember how I was summoned last time...
and found out who it was?
Just wait. Let me stop by the temple.
(Instead of being flustered,)
(he bravely walks towards the temple.)
I wondered who summoned me.
I summoned you because you seemed suspicious.
You're very suspicious.
- Let's do this. - All right.
(The color on the monitor will change...)
(according to the presence of the two deities and the prophet.)
I'm sure there's one here.
- Do you think so? - Yes.
On the count of three,
the monitor behind you will show a color.
One...
(Will any of them be 1 of the 3 key characters?)
(Which color among the 8 given will show?)
- 2, 3! - 2, 3!
[VIU Ver] SBS E467 Running Man "The Deity of Light, The Deity of Darkness & The Prophet Part 2" -♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Surprised)
(That can't be!)
(What is the result of the first visit to the temple?)
(It's white.)
- What is that? White? - No way!
(That means all 4 of them are human.)
(All human, white)
- We're all human? - It's So Min.
- Seriously? - It's So Min.
- I'm sorry. - This is why I summoned him.
- I'm sorry. - Why did you...
- Hey. - suspect me?
Hey, we should trust each other.
(Prophet Candidates, Deity of Darkness Candidates,)
(Deity of Light Candidates)
Not the deity of darkness means not the deity of light.
(Ye Won uses her brain as an announcer.)
(She's trying to zero in on the deity of darkness.)
(Who could it be?)
- Let's look at it together. - Let me look first.
Let me check it first.
- Hold on. - We're one.
- This isn't how you do it. - We're one.
- No, we're not. - Yes, we are.
- I have the right to show you. - It's done for.
You can't steal it away from me.
(The deity of light doesn't have a "K" in their surname.)
(Kim Jong Kook and Kim Ye Won are excluded.)
(Deity of Darkness)
(Deity of Darkness Candidates)
The deity of darkness...
(The candidates are Haha, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, or Sunny.)
is either Kwang Soo...
(Her sixth sense is tingling.)
or Sunny.
(Did Ye Won guess it correctly?)
(The 4 humans exit the temple.)
Are you going this way?
- Yes. - You should've summoned her.
- Don't rip my name tag. - Come here. You're in trouble.
The hint said that Ye Won wasn't the prophet.
- Her? She isn't the prophet. - Yes.
She's not the deity of darkness either.
- Are you all human? - Yes.
We're all human.
- What about Jae Seok? - He's human too.
Are you sure? I found a lead on the deity of darkness.
- What is it? - I found a lead.
It's either Sunny or Kwang Soo.
(She thinks it's 1 of those 2.)
- Kwang Soo? - It's one of them.
- Are you serious? - Sunny or Kwang Soo?
- Are you certain? - Yes.
I think she's right.
Here comes the deity of darkness!
(Look over there!)
(At that moment, Kwang Soo approaches.)
- Me? Why? - Yes.
- Why? - I think it's you.
(Speak of the devil.)
- Why? - Why do you think so?
- Gosh, it's Jong Kook. - My goodness.
You startled me. Here's the deity of darkness.
(Soon after Kwang Soo appears...)
- It's not me. - Yes, you are.
- It's either Kwang Soo or Sunny. - It's either Kwang Soo...
- Why me? - or Sunny.
- Why? - It's really not me.
No wonder.
On our way down, he chatted me up.
If someone gets eliminated here...
You know the kinds of things the show likes to air.
- Also, he... - It's settled then.
- It's been decided. - A moving camera is tailing him.
(He suspects Kwang Soo too.)
- Since last week... - A moving camera?
Yes, you should have seen it move up and down.
Really?
- Se Chan's been fixated on that. - Hold on.
Who are you following?
Is this for Kwang Soo?
Really?
When did you start...
How is this mine? That's absurd!
- When did you ever... - That's crazy!
- You're wrong. - Let's...
spread out again then.
We'll eventually need the clues.
Sunny...
The two of you were...
(Sunny's upset about being suspected.)
I can't believe this. It's actually making me mad.
I'm really close to exploding with anger.
(Could she be acting?)
Sunny, there you are.
Two cameras are following Sunny.
Why does she have two cameras on her?
Why are two cameramen following her?
(Is it because she's playing an important role?)
(Meanwhile, Sunny searches for clues.)
Sunny!
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for clues.
Have you found any?
I already know...
(She finds everything about Sunny suspicious.)
You're...
(She's sure that Sunny is the deity of darkness.)
I've already narrowed it down.
Sunny...
You have the wrong person.
It's over if I take off your name tag.
Don't do this.
(If Sunny is the deity of darkness, the humans and deity of light wins.)
Why bet on something you're not sure of?
I'm sure of this.
So you're sure that it's either me or Kwang Soo.
Do you know that there's a special camera following him?
Two cameras were following you around too.
I saw it all from above.
I'm sure that you're the deity of darkness.
- I'm not. - I'm sure of it.
That couldn't be more false.
You're barking up the wrong tree.
Sunny, please!
(Sunny suddenly launches herself at Ye Won.)
Gosh.
(She quickly takes off Ye Won's name tag.)
(Tearing)
(Jang Ye Won is out!)
Sunny...
(Sunny suddenly eliminated Ye Won. Which role is she playing?)
Human Jang Ye Won has been eliminated.
Ye Won was a human?
She's out?
(Both will be eliminated if a human eliminates a human.)
How did Ye Won get eliminated?
(Sunny wasn't eliminated after she eliminated Ye Won.)
I'm exhausted.
(She's either a deity or the prophet.)
Those with big mouths are getting eliminated first.
Unbelievable.
Why is everything so twisted this time?
What's this?
(She locates...)
(a clue box that was left in the corner.)
No way. This is huge.
(There's a board with holes in it.)
No way.
I only came here to drink water.
(She doesn't know how to use the clue though.)
First...
Which one is this?
I need to find the book.
I found the most crucial clue.
(She brings it to the prophecy.)
(She places it on top of the page.)
The prophet...
(Certain letters can be seen through the holes.)
Darkness...
(What clue shocked Ji Hyo?)
It's the prophet.
I must find the prophet first.
(I must find the prophet first!)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok searches for clues.)
(He finds...)
(an envelope in a gap.)
It's a Temple Summons.
(A Temple Summons is in the envelope.)
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is searching elsewhere for clues.)
Everybody, pause.
The temple's door has opened.
What?
Do you have a summons?
No, how can I when I'm right here?
Hold on. I'm calling someone on my list.
(Those with Temple Summons can call someone to the temple.)
Sunny.
(He thinks carefully since it's the last chance.)
Kwang Soo.
(Sunny and Kwang Soo...)
(are prime suspects of being the deity of darkness.)
Sunny and Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok chooses...)
I choose Sunny.
(Jae Seok chooses Sunny.)
Sunny, you've been summoned to the temple.
(Sunny, a prime suspect, has been called to the temple.)
It's a good day to die.
You've been summoned.
- Me? - Yes.
This is stressing me out too much.
You need to head to the temple.
Me? I can't believe this.
(Who summoned Kwang Soo to the temple?)
Kwang Soo's here.
- Get over here. - Come on.
Unbelievable.
- What's going on? - Place your hand here.
(Haha summoned Kwang Soo.)
- Right here. - Place your hand.
(While searching for a clue,)
(he came across a Temple Summons.)
I summon Kwang Soo.
(He summons Kwang Soo, the prime suspect.)
I'm sure of it. What did I tell you?
It has to be him.
(Unbelievable. What's going on?)
- Place your hand here. - Place your hand here.
This is your last chance.
What on earth is this?
What's going on?
(Once all 4 of them place their hands on the table,)
(the screen will show a color depending on who's among them.)
- It won't be white. - All right.
- 1, 2, 3! - 2, 3!
Please.
(Which of the 8 colors will appear on the screen?)
(Temple)
(Purple!)
It will turn purple when all three are present.
(Deity of light, deity of darkness, prophet: purple)
What color is this?
Does that mean the prophet is here too?
- Purple. - They're all here.
Darkness...
(All three of them are here.)
- The prophet... - They're all here.
(They're all here.)
- This is crazy. - Isn't this our last chance?
(They're each playing one of the three roles.)
I was proven to be a human earlier.
Who are you then?
(They start interrogating one another.)
I don't trust you.
I'm the prophet.
(I'm the prophet.)
(Haha's the prophet?)
You're the prophet?
(Then either Sunny or Kwang Soo is the deity of darkness.)
I'm just saying there is one.
I'm a little suspicious of Sunny too, but still.
(Who is the deity of darkness?)
Who of the two is it?
The race is now over.
Please join us at the platform of judgment.
(The deity of darkness hasn't been revealed yet.)
(The final decision will be made at the platform of judgment.)
The platform is now ready.
The two deities have not been eliminated yet,
so it'll be decided at the platform of judgment.
The deity of light and humans will win...
if the deity of darkness goes on it.
In all other cases, the deity of darkness will win.
The four of us placed our hands on the table...
and the screen turned purple.
So it's one of you three.
We were able to make a good guess as to who it is.
The deity of darkness...
(What did he find out about the deity of darkness?)
- is the prophet. - That's right.
(It's the prophet?)
(The deity of darkness is the prophet?)
It's the same person.
(He discovered a box while looking for a clue.)
(He found the same board as Ji Hyo with holes in it.)
(He checked it against the prophecy.)
(The prophet's identity was revealed.)
(The prophet...)
(is...)
(the deity of darkness.)
(The prophet is the deity of darkness.)
(The prophet and the deity of darkness is the same person.)
You're the deity of darkness as well as the prophet.
You will make a fake prophecy and say the spell.
Humans will believe you...
and mistake the deity of light as the deity of darkness...
and try to eliminate the deity of light instead.
(The prophet was the deity of darkness!)
It's why I asked who the prophet is.
This just came to mind.
- What? - Earlier...
someone said that he's the prophet.
(Haha said that he's the prophet.)
That's right.
(I'm the prophet!)
(At the temple, he said he was the prophet.)
I am a human.
If I had known about this truth,
I wouldn't have said anything about my identity.
If you knew that they're the same person?
I had no idea.
- The clue about the prophet... - You heard me, right?
I didn't even find that clue.
Are you the deity of light then?
No, I'm human.
Then who's the deity of light?
Sunny, who might you be?
- She's the deity of light. - I'm the deity of light.
Then why did you try your best in the previous games?
It's because I knew the clues were the opposite.
No one knew about that fact...
and I didn't want to look suspicious.
- I think she's right. - Me too.
The others...
didn't even try to contradict her just now.
That's because she's the real deal.
(They aren't saying anything because she's the deity of light?)
It'll look weird if they say otherwise.
- That's why... - She's telling the truth.
I really am the deity of light.
You will be participating in the Find the Deity Race...
to unlock the secret of the prophecy.
(Sunny received a mission.)
You are the deity of light who must shine on the world...
and defeat the deity of darkness.
Really?
(Ye Won mistook Sunny as the deity of darkness.)
(Sunny was cornered, so she had to eliminate Ye Won.)
Let's bring her over to our side.
You have no idea how wronged I felt.
- She's the light of deity. - She is.
No one believed me.
Hey.
She told me that she was the deity of light.
- The truth will prevail. - The truth will prevail.
The truth will prevail.
Let's vote.
I choose Haha.
- Me too. - Me too.
I choose Haha too.
(More than half of them chose Haha as the deity of darkness.)
You couldn't be more mistaken about this,
but I'll still walk on the platform.
If I throw a fit in this moment,
you guys will suspect me even more.
- He's not getting worked up. - Seriously.
Should I get worked up?
Because he's not getting worked up...
It's not that I'm not worked up.
I think he's a human.
I can get worked up if you want me to.
I kept saying it up there.
(The judges are getting confused because Haha looks frustrated.)
Gosh, this is really confusing.
Why didn't you check this, by the way?
Is it even possible that Kwang Soo didn't know what to do with this?
I didn't know.
(Kwang Soo had the same hint as Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
(I had this too.)
(The hint contained a crucial clue.)
(I kept putting it on pictures.)
(Kwang Soo failed to figure out how to use the hint.)
- I didn't know. - Is it even possible...
that Kwang Soo didn't know how to use it?
He's been on Running Man for nine years.
- It's obviously for letters. - He put this on pictures?
He put this on pictures?
He's suspicious.
Guys, you're being fooled right now.
I really didn't know.
You don't know until you actually put it on the page.
(Who is the deity of darkness,)
(Haha or Kwang Soo?)
- Let's take a vote one last time. - Let's do this.
- I vote for Haha. - Haha.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- Haha. - Haha.
(They're still divided.)
This is really frustrating.
- Pick one. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo, who ignored the hint? Haha, who claims to be the prophet?)
Me?
- Is it 2 to 2? - Gosh.
- Why all of a sudden? - Trust me, seriously.
- Jong Kook, hurry up. - What's going on?
I'm not stupid.
- Something just came to my mind. - What is it?
I've heard Haha talk this way before.
- And Haha was the culprit. - That's right.
- Right. - Jae Seok.
It was here on the rooftop of SBS.
That's right.
Is that what you think?
Are you suspecting me?
Is that really what you think?
- Why all of a sudden? - I'm not stupid.
- It's Haha. - Haha.
Listen to the way he speaks.
You...
(The result of their race depends on their last choice.)
(Who will end up on the platform, Kwang Soo or Haha?)
- Haha, step onto the platform. - He's the one for sure.
(If Haha turns out to be the deity of darkness,)
(the deity of light and humans win.)
- His voice gave him away. - I'm not.
Seriously.
I'm not, I swear.
The way he spoke...
You shouldn't decide based on that.
1, 2...
(Is Haha really the deity of darkness?)
(Or is he just a human?)
(Ripping)
(Prophet and deity of darkness)
You punk!
(Haha is the prophet and deity of darkness.)
- You punk! - I told you!
I told you!
I'm a human!
(Haha was the deity of darkness!)
(The deity of light and humans win today's race.)
I could have won.
(What a shame. I could have won.)
- Hello. - Oh, my.
(Before today's shoot)
(Haha met the staff and received the mission.)
Goodness. What is it now?
- You're the prophet... - Right.
- and deity of darkness. - That's what my mom used to say.
"You're a son of darkness."
(That's how Haha became the deity of darkness and the prophet.)
(So Min was spreading the hints everywhere.)
(Ripping)
(So Min is eliminated right away.)
(Ye Won was collecting as many hints as she could.)
(Ripping)
(I asked you to show me.)
(As Ye Won was closing in on him, Haha eliminated her.)
The final winners of the Find the Deity Race are...
the deity of light and Team Humans.
(The deity of light and Team Humans win...)
(the Find the Deity Race.)
The deity of light and Team Humans...
will receive peaches, which are in season right now, as a prize.
- Yes! - Yes!
- This feels nice. - I love peaches!
Our four guests today...
Kim Ye Won, Jang Ye Won, Sunny, and Sun Mi.
They worked very hard today.
Let's give them a big hand!
(Thank you for being with us today.)
We'll meet again at the fan-meet then.
(Running Man's Fan-Meet starts right now.)
See you at the fan-meet!
(And finally...)
(A project to reward our fans for the 9th anniversary)
(Running Man's first fan-meet in Korea, Nine Years of Running Man)
(9th Anniversary Special Project)
(Running Man's Fan-Meet: Nine Years of Running Man)
(Running Man's Fan-Meet 2019)
(Opening song by all 8 members)
(They'll sing a song together...)
(to express their love for their fans.)
(Solo and group performance)
(Each member shows off his or her charms.)
(Each performance will be unique.)
(The dangerous collaboration of Running Man's sexy guys)
(Jae Seok and Haha's duet performance)
(The preparation took 100 days.)
(Apink, Nucksal, Code Kunst,)
(SORAN, Gummy)
(Collaboration with brilliant artists)
(Group dance by all 8 members)
(This performance will be the highlight of the event.)
("Boom and Just Blow" by all 8 Running Man members)
(The group dance by all 8 members...)
(will be the grand finale of the event.)
(Applause and excitement)
(The fan-meet project starts now.)
- Hi. - Hi.
Ji Hyo, you're wearing cycling shorts.
Oh, we were all going to wear them.
Are you trying to get on our teacher's good side?
Fine, I copied her. Do you have a problem?
Is this a sweater or a t-shirt?
It's a t-shirt sweater.
(Ji Hyo is annoyed.)
(They're fighting.)
Is something bothering you this morning?
Why are you picking a fight from morning?
I'm not picking a fight. I'm just talking to you.
They started fighting as soon as we started filming.
- Hello. - You're here.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hi. - Jin Lee.
- Jin Lee and You Jin are here. - You Jin.
I like You Jin.
- Hi. - The three of them...
You're wearing...
- cycling shorts too. - Of course.
- We promised you. - You kept your promise.
I even have a full set.
- Cycling shorts? - I have a cycling suit.
(I have a cycling suit.)
No. It's not good for dancing.
- I'll wear it someday. - It's not good for dancing.
- Is it a diving suit? - Wearing something underneath...
(We'd love to see it.)
Today,
we're going to learn formations.
How to change formations.
- Formations? - It's important.
That's what we're going to do today.
It might be a little complicated...
- at first. - It's getting worse and worse.
You'll stand up on eight.
You on this side will...
Stand up. There you go.
You on this side will move to the right.
Stand up as you slide.
Stand up.
But you'll all stand up at different times.
Let's do this together slowly.
5, 6, 7, 8.
- 1, 2, 3, 4, - 1, 2, 3, 4,
- 5, 6, 7, 8. - 5, 6, 7, 8.
(Is this right?)
(Clumsy)
3, 4.
Yes! Good job.
- Are you sure? - Lia.
- Be serious. - We just did what you told us to.
Did she think we wouldn't be able to do this?
It feels like we're back in elementary school again.
She sounds like a preschool teacher.
(Good job, grown-ups.)
Good job.
You did it.
Let's try again. I think we can do this.
I'm feeling confident.
5, 6, 7, 8.
(Like this?)
- We did it. - We did it.
Give me a pat.
(Did I do a good job? Please give me a pat.)
Let me give you a pat.
(When dancing, they're 7 years old again.)
Give me candy.
(He's like a 7-year-old.)
I pooped!
(It's getting worse.)
- Get out. - What?
- Get out. - I didn't poop.
- Get out. - I didn't poop for real.
- Get out if you pooped. - I didn't.
Call his mom.
(Please use the bathroom instead.)
This is an important part.
Kwang Soo...
(Kwang Soo will be standing in the center.)
You'll come to the center.
- Seven... - That's cool.
Slide to the center.
(Like this?)
That's right.
And then, "come on".
(Come on.)
- "Come on." - It looks annoying.
It looks so annoying.
This is his best part so far.
That was best "come on" part you've done.
Now you'll zigzag down.
Zigzag, zigzag.
But the thing is,
your movement will be very slight.
Zigzag only slightly.
How do you do that?
Kwang Soo.
(It looks like he's getting an electric shock.)
- He's a dancer. - Unbelievable.
He's an amazing dancer.
You have to zigzag very slightly.
You did this part better than the teacher.
(It's as if his neck is possessed.)
Zigzag.
There you go. You're doing great.
Ji Hyo, don't shake your head.
(Who teaches who?)
- Focus on your moves. - Why are you shaking your head?
You try.
Imagine you're in between two walls.
Good. You look great.
(Imagine you're bumping into the walls.)
(Stiff)
You're good.
Good job.
- Are you sick? - You did a good job.
(In his mind, he's a great dancer.)
I'm in trouble.
All right. Kwang Soo, let me show you what you'll do.
You're the one...
who controls the other members.
You're the conqueror.
You'll pretend...
you're pulling them up.
- From the floor. - You're going to mime.
You're good.
- "I'm controlling you." - You're good.
All the way up here.
Higher up. There you go.
Raise your arms all the way up there,
and press them down this time.
5, 6, 7, 8.
Like this. Good.
And the rest of us zigzag down?
Exactly. Zigzag down.
I'm not going down.
Why?
(I'm not going down.)
- Why are you not going down? - I don't want to be controlled.
- You have to go down. - No.
You have to be controlled by me.
I'm going up instead.
Why is he so stubborn?
I'm going up.
- He's so stubborn. - I'm going up.
Next.
You'll make way for Jae Seok so that he can come to the center.
(They'll make way for Jae Seok.)
(It's finally my turn.)
The rest of you will stay still.
Jae Seok will...
will walk forward.
Then you will stretch your arm to the front.
- 1, 2. - 2.
- Then put the other arm up. - What was that?
- Don't stand near me. - Okay.
My movements tend to be big.
- Okay. - Don't stand near me.
- Be careful. - Okay.
One. Throw.
- Then lift up one knee. - Lift it up.
Lift it up and go, boom, boom, boom, boom.
(Lift it up and go, boom, boom, boom, boom.)
(Boom, boom, boom, boom?)
(He suddenly becomes embarrassed.)
- That's... - It's our first chance to laugh.
It's our first chance to laugh.
For goodness' sake.
It's your first chance to laugh.
(Laughing)
That's so cute.
(My goodness.)
He needs to do that as he walks out, right?
He needs to do that as soon as he walks out.
It would be a disaster if you mess up the steps.
This is bad.
I bet he will fall down.
Jae Seok will mess up the steps.
(Floundering)
(Take this!)
(I might do that.)
- I might do that. - Seriously.
(They will have to practice hard.)
I bet Jae Seok will fall down.
He does that when he is pressured.
- Shall we begin right away? - Yes.
Okay.
Go to your positions.
Let's begin right away.
Haha, you will go,
1, 2, 3, and...
You will control everyone else's body.
Is it my time?
You will turn their heads first.
- Heads. - Then you will turn their bodies.
- Bodies. - Then...
the dancers will go...
Let's go. Heads, bodies.
- Let's go. 1, 2. - 1, 2.
(Turn, turn.)
- Yes. - The moves are quite fast.
Then we will go, push, push.
(Move as Haha pushes.)
Okay. One more time. 1, 2, 3, and push, push.
(Turn, turn, push, push.)
- That's incredible. - Does it look cool?
- I can't see it. - It looks cool.
- I can't see it. - I want to see it.
- I stand out so much. - It's very cool.
(I stand out so much.)
(He thinks it's cool because he stands out so much.)
He is so annoying.
In the next move, Haha will look incredibly cool.
(In the next move, Haha will look incredibly cool.)
Until when will he stand in the center?
He already looks cool.
He looks cool in every move.
(I am the best student in dance.)
- He is like his son, Dream. - Dream.
Dream.
Haha, I will teach you your move.
Kick, kick.
Kick to the left then to the right.
To make this look cool,
the kicks should be effortless.
- Effortless. - That's right.
- Effortless. - Effortless.
- Effortless. - Okay.
(Effortless, but cool.)
(Like this?)
- Good job. - He is good.
He did it perfectly.
Good job.
- My goodness. - Now...
- He did a good job, right? - He is good.
He is good.
He is such an eyesore.
Shall we go over this part one more time?
Get ready. Let's start from the beginning.
- Heads. - Let's start from the heads.
Ready, set, go.
1, 2, 3, and 4.
5, 6.
Zigzag, wave.
Wave.
(Effortless)
(You did an amazing job.)
You did an amazing job.
- We made no mistakes, - Are you sure this is going well?
but our expressions showed how nervous we were.
We were so nervous.
Everyone was frozen.
Next, you will spread out.
The two of you won't spread out.
- It's time for the best part. - Yes.
- It's time for the best part. - Here comes the best part.
- This is the beginning. - All right.
This is great.
J.K. and Sopee.
(It's J.K. and Sopee's turn.)
Come on out.
(They are the nicknames from the 457th episode.)
- 1, 2. - Put it on the thigh.
Spread your legs out more.
1, 2, 3.
(When Jong Kook lifts So Min up, she will lift her legs up and turn.)
That was nice, but...
- Your legs should be straight. - When you go up,
you should put your hands on his shoulders...
and your shin on his upper thigh.
- So Min, this is your chance. - Your shin.
(So Min, this is your chance.)
Your shin.
Kick his private part.
Be careful.
I will end you if you kick the wrong spot.
Hang in there.
So Min is heavier than she looks.
You aren't heavy at all, so do what you need to do.
(You aren't heavy at all, so do what you need to do.)
He is the man.
She is very heavy.
(He is a dependable man.)
(I will trust you.)
All right. Let's go.
Let's go.
1, 2.
(Jong Kook holds her hand and spins her.)
(As they learned,)
(they show the perfect move.)
(That was impressive.)
Good job.
- I can't believe they did it. - Sopee and J.K.!
J.K. and Sopee!
- Sopee! Sopee! - Good job.
(They look good together.)
Here comes the next move.
You will spin once.
- 1, 2, 3... - What?
At four, you will put your hands around his neck.
(Spin once and put your hands around the partner's neck.)
- Put your hands around his neck. - Hold on.
Isn't this too sexy? This show is for 12 years and older.
No, it isn't.
We are quite innocent.
You are seeing this in a strange light.
Then comes... 4, 5, 6, 7.
(Jump and get on your partner.)
Stretch out one arm. 7, 8, and 1.
(Spin mid-air and land.)
(It's the most difficult move.)
He is the man!
Sopee!
(Sopee makes a complaint.)
- You can do this. - I need to go on a diet.
- It's okay. - I need to go on a diet.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Go slowly.
My goodness.
(They try to copy what they learned.)
From here...
- 1, 2. - Spin.
- They need teamwork. - Put your hands around his neck.
Jump up.
Look at Jong Kook's face.
- My goodness. - Look at Jong Kook's face.
- Look at Jong Kook's face. - Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, she is heavy, right? - Jong Kook.
- 7, 8. - Jong Kook.
- 1, 2. - He is shocked.
(Shaking)
(He hurriedly puts her down.)
- Jong Kook. - You were a bit...
- Don't be like that. - He gritted his teeth.
(He gritted his teeth.)
- Jong Kook, you gritted your teeth. - Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - I mean...
- They got it on the camera. - I saw your face.
- They got it on the camera. - You gritted your teeth.
- Give them some tips. - Seriously.
- She needs to trust him and let go. - That's right.
- Don't tighten up. - That's right.
- Let go. - It's really okay.
I don't know why you'd tense up.
(Laughing)
Do you like him?
(Do you like Jong Kook?)
(For goodness' sake.)
- You catch me this time. - Why would I hold you?
(Come on, Se Chan.)
Lift me up.
- What? - Lift me up.
What is up with you?
For goodness' sake.
That came out of nowhere.
- That came out of nowhere. - That came out of nowhere.
Se Chan.
(Sliding down)
That came out of nowhere.
(As soon as she puts her knee on his thigh, he slides down.)
What are you doing?
(It suddenly turned into professional wrestling.)
(Se Chan got knocked out.)
(He gets a knee kick.)
Lift me up. Lift me up.
I know you can lift me up.
- It hurts here. - I know you can lift me up.
- This part hurts. - I know you can lift me up.
So Min, what are you doing?
Kwang Soo, give it a try.
- What? - Kwang Soo, give it a try.
- Kwang Soo, give it a try. - I can't do it.
- How? - I can't.
What are you doing?
Lift me up. Lift me up.
Lift me up.
I know you can lift me up.
(Kwang Soo gets a jump kick.)
(She denies the reality.)
(For goodness' sake.)
(They are in tatters.)
I know you can lift me up.
So Min.
Only Jong Kook can lift So Min up.
- You will hurt them. - That was hilarious.
- Hello. - Hello.
Now, So Min and Ji Hyo will come to the center.
(It's the day of practice for So Min and Ji Hyo's part.)
You know,
So Min has a part...
with Ji Hyo.
- They are in it together. - They are in it together.
They do this together.
She is ready for that part.
- She wants to show off. - Look at her.
So Min stretched.
No, no, no.
Stop it.
(Punching)
Why are you fighting again?
You need to stretch your muscles.
- It's okay! - You will be fine afterward.
(Let me play too.)
(Stop it.)
(Hitting)
(She hit Jae Seok's head by mistake.)
Ji Hyo, it's me.
(Jae Seok gets attacked at his attempt to play.)
- I am sorry. - You...
Ji Hyo, you...
I have never seen Jae Seok get hit so hard on the head.
- I heard a loud smack. - Are you okay?
- Ji Hyo, you are incredible. - All right.
Please make this formation.
Ji Hyo is at the front. Ji Hyo, you are at the center.
(After warming up, Ji Hyo and So Min take the center.)
(Ji Hyo and So Min stand...)
(while the others spread out to each side.)
(Then the center's part starts.)
Then comes the pelvic move. Let's go up to that move.
Right, left, right.
- Right, left, right. - Right, left, right.
Left, right, left.
- Left, right, left. - Left, right, left.
- I hate this so much. - This is like a children's dance.
- I hate this so much. - I like it.
- This is like a children's dance. - It will go...
We can't dance like you.
- Let's go over this again. - This is...
Go faster. 7, 8.
Right, left, right. Left, right, left. One more time.
Right, left, right. Left, right, left.
My stomach hurts.
- It's cute. - What?
All right. It's time for the two female members.
(This is when Ji Hyo and So Min do their dance.)
(First, they need to watch.)
(The elegant double wave)
It's so cool.
(Controlled)
(They show a difficult move of leaning back.)
(The decalcomania dance)
(The sequence ends with the powerful arm swing.)
(They are so cool.)
(It's a festival.)
(Hitting)
(My goodness.)
My goodness.
I was too excited.
- I hope they pull it off. - They danced slowly for us.
Did you dance slowly?
Yes. We slowed down the rhythm.
- Haha, they danced slowly. - You can do it.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
So Min, the dance is really cool.
I will do So Min's part, and she will do Ji Hyo's part.
One. Lean back.
Your back should be...
- She took dance lessons. - like this.
- Straighten your knees. - She will break her back.
- She will break her back. - Straighten your knees.
Ji Hyo is as stiff as us.
That's right. Do this.
- She should lean back more. - Ji Hyo is as flexible as Seok Jin.
- They are about the same. - Her body is like a rod.
She can't bend her back.
- Now... - For goodness' sake.
- Bend your back. - You should try it.
- She is doing a good job. - "You should try it."
- What? - Bend your back.
Why would I do that?
My goodness.
- Why would I do that? - You can't do it.
His age is already bent.
(He is at his prime at the age of 54.)
That's true.
Let's resume.
It looks much sexier...
when you put your hand right on your face.
- Is that facial expression okay? - Ji Hyo.
(Grimacing)
- No. - Ji Hyo, you look scary.
"Headache, toothache."
(It's like a painkiller commercial.)
Isn't that a painkiller commercial?
- You should do something like this. - It's like...
It's like this.
(Like this?)
- One more time. - So Min looks like...
she is sad to be behind Ji Hyo.
She is trying hard to show off.
Twist.
So Min.
(Sexy)
(I refuse to see this.)
(Showing off)
Look to the front.
- For goodness' sake. - I see you.
- So Min. - She is unbelievable.
- You are doing great. - She wants to stand out.
"Keep your eyes on me."
It's like, boom, boom.
(It's time to get down for real.)
Move your head.
(The wave begins.)
(Controlled)
(Ji Hyo is one step behind,)
(and So Min is busy showing off.)
(I am the best.)
There you go.
- Hold on. - 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Right, left, right. Left, right, left.
(Right, left, right. Left, right, left.)
- All right. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
Okay.
(What?)
(The three idiots come to the front.)
(We aren't idiots.)
(Anyone would think that they are idiots.)
- What is that? - My goodness.
(We aren't idiots.)
Hey, hey, hey!
We changed the dance to this.
My goodness.
- I like this one. - Right?
We need to make people laugh once.
- Once. - We need to make people laugh once.
She is shocked.
If you allow them to do that, I won't sit still.
What are you going to do?
Okay?
If you allow them to do that, I won't sit still.
You can't do that.
Left foot and right arm. Pull and pull.
1, 2, 3, down.
1, 2, 7, down.
(Difficult moves continue on.)
(What will be the result of their practice?)
(August 26)
(Ewha Womans University)
(Running Man's Fan-Meet: Nine Years of Running Man)
(Kim Jong Kook, congratulations on the 24th anniversary of your debut.)
(They receive support and love from all over the world.)
(Messages of support)
(The 8 members prepared a nice present.)
(Running Man's Fan-Meet: Nine Years of Running Man)
(The competition for the ticket was 60 to 1.)
(2,400 people were chosen through quizzes and stories.)
(The fan-meet is ready to begin.)
(The fans took out their precious time for the event.)
Hello.
- Hello. - Please look over here.
I wanted to make good memories with my daughter.
We only watch Running Man when we meet up.
My grandma wanted to come since I like the show so much.
We took an early leave from school.
I watched the show from the first episode. It's so fun.
Did you apply for the fan-meet for your daughter?
No, for myself.
Running Man, let's go.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Running Man, let's go. - Running Man, let's go.
(The fan-meet is ready to begin with the avid viewers.)
Let's begin the rehearsal.
(The final rehearsal is taking place.)
(The artists for collaborations are ready to go.)
When I think about the stage, my heart beats so fast.
Gosh, I am sweating.
(They become nervous as time approaches.)
(They are extremely nervous about the first fan-meet in Korea.)
(The rehearsal ends as they grow more anxious.)
More than my body,
my mind is exhausted.
I think we will feel empty tomorrow morning.
It's bound to happen.
It will be embarrassing once this airs.
- We will feel empty. - When this episode airs,
I will be outside.
(Jae Seok is outside at this moment.)
This is so embarrassing. My wife wanted to come,
but I told her to stay at home.
(He didn't want his wife to come and support him.)
- This is embarrassing. - This is so embarrassing.
- Knock, knock. Good work, everyone. - Na Eun.
(The woman with a sweet voice visits the tired members.)
What did you bring?
- Na Eun. - Good work, everyone.
- My goodness. - Hey.
- Thank you, Na Eun. - This is a protein drink.
- You should get some protein. - Look at this.
Dancing is an exercise, so you need protein.
- This is coconut flavor. - I need protein.
This could make a hearty meal.
This takes care of a meal!
(The protein drink takes care of a meal.)
(He is ridiculous.)
I will end you if you have a meal today.
(You said this takes care of a meal.)
- Remember what you said. - I won't have a meal.
Don't have a meal. I will keep my eyes on you.
(Thanks to Na Eun's present, they gain energy.)
(1 hour before the fan-meet, the audience begins to enter.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E467 Running Man "Running Man's Fan-Meet 2019" -♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(They get a t-shirt the members worked on...)
(and enter the venue excitedly.)
(2,400 people in total)
(The audience took out their precious time for the event.)
(They await...)
(the eight members of Running Man.)
My voice keeps getting hoarse.
I don't like feeling nervous before an event.
- I know. - What time is it now?
It's about time.
It will start at 7 p.m., right?
Do we have 20 minutes left?
(Four teams of artists are in another waiting room.)
(They wouldn't have felt so nervous had this been their concert.)
(They feel a sense of responsibility for the members.)
(10 seconds before the start)
- Oh, my goodness. - 10 seconds.
- Let's do this. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(The members' present unfolds now.)
(The members appear on the LED screen.)
(Startled)
- Do they see us? - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(The waiting room gets broadcasted live.)
We are on the screen.
- Hello. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
If you see us, please wave.
(We see you!)
(The reaction is extremely enthusiastic.)
This is live.
(They meet through the LED screen.)
- We will meet soon. - Yes.
Running Man's fan-meet that celebrates...
its ninth anniversary will get started in earnest.
Jae Seok, take this.
- What is that? - What is that?
(Is that a cue card?)
- Is there a mission? - What?
- What? - What is this cue card?
Is there a mission?
(What did they give us?)
What is this? What?
- What is it? - Come on!
"There is a spy among you today."
Come on!
(There is a spy among you today.)
(It took 3 months to prepare for the fan-meet.)
(How could there be a spy?)
For goodness' sake.
Let's just have the concert.
How could there be a spy when we are having a concert?
Is this a regular shoot?
- It's absurd. - What can a spy do?
What will you do if we make mistakes on the stage?
I can't believe there is a spy...
- when we prepared so hard. - Seriously.
- This is so hard. - This is driving me crazy.
- There is a spy among us? - For three months...
- Oh! - What?
Ji Hyo used a different waiting room.
(Ji Hyo used a different waiting room earlier.)
(Ji Hyo moved to a different waiting room.)
Why did you use a different waiting room than us?
- Ji Hyo. - I mean...
- I got it now. - It's about her time to be it.
No, it's not me.
(Is today's spy Ji Hyo?)
Ji Hyo is a spy.
(The artists also have to guess the spy.)
- Ji Hyo, you look very nervous. - Jae Seok.
Why are you stammering?
Everyone is listening, so I can't talk.
For your information, fans in the audience know...
who the spy is.
- Really? - How?
(The audience already knows who the spy is.)
I'm not it, right?
- Who's the spy? - I'm not, right?
Can the audience tell us who the spy is by mistake?
That won't happen.
- Is there one spy? - What is the spy doing?
A mission was already given to the spy.
We asked the spy to be the most passionate...
today.
"Being passionate"?
- The mission is... - Passionate.
being the most passionate.
We'll find out during the opening.
(We'll find out during the opening.)
- During the opening. - What did you say?
Are you nervous?
Please breathe.
He didn't breathe.
(His speaking manners are the same in front of the audience.)
Finding the spy will be an individual game.
Once the fan-meet performance is over...
and you vote the right person individually, you win.
Members who don't vote correctly will be penalized on stage.
- Penalized on stage? - Yes.
(They'll be penalized here.)
(We'll see Kwang Soo get penalized.)
Also, if the spy isn't voted as the most passionate person,
the spy will be penalized for failing to clear the mission.
- If he isn't voted? - Yes.
If the audience doesn't vote him, it means that he failed the mission.
How can it be judged?
You'll be given hints about the spy...
starting with your individual performance.
Every time you finish your performance,
the audience's reaction will be measured in decibels.
If it's over 120dB...
(If the shout from the audience is over 120dB, they get a hint.)
you'll obtain a hint about the spy backstage.
- Why are you doing this? - What's this?
- We always do our best. - I know.
We're doing our best.
What if you are less popular?
(What if you are less popular?)
(Everyone gets solemn as he recognizes himself quickly.)
- About decibel... - Seok Jin.
Many people are laughing.
(Who are these kind people responding to his comment?)
My grandmother said that you're the best.
Everyone, help us.
We have to reach 120dB.
(They sympathize his appeal.)
This feels like Running Man.
- It's great. - I know.
They just won't let us perform in peace.
It's my first time performing.
You must go on stage now.
- Okay. - Oh my goodness.
Here's your opening mission.
- Is there a mission? - Forget the mission.
(There's an opening mission?)
- Why are you giving us a mission? - Just let us perform.
We have a lot to do.
- Will someone get eliminated? - What?
- We might not get hints. - People are waiting for us.
- What are they? - They're boxes.
- They're boxes. - What boxes?
It's already difficult without a mission.
- Oh, it's that. - I'm already nervous as it is.
- What is this? - Is this how it's done?
Our names are on it.
- There are names in the front. - You're right.
Kwang Soo, can you open the curtain in the back?
(Kwang Soo, can you open the curtain in the back?)
Here?
- What? - What is this?
(Prison uniform?)
(At the fan-meet...)
They really are prison uniforms.
- Each of you... - Is this a prison?
I told you that it's a prison setup as soon as we arrived.
Right, you said that.
(Is it escaping the room instead of being a fan-meet?)
Inside two boxes given to each of you,
there's a shirt with a photo of your face on it...
and a shirt with Seok Jin's face on it.
Pick one box.
If you pick a shirt with your face on it,
you can keep your current outfit for the opening performance.
- Hey. - If...
(They keep their normal outfit if they pick their own t-shirt.)
(If they pick the shirt with Seok Jin on it...)
If you pick the shirt with Seok Jin...
We took a long time to pick this outfit.
Will we wear that?
If you pick the shirt with Seok Jin's face on it,
you will wear the prison uniform...
- for the opening. - We invited many people.
- What are we doing right now? - Listen.
That doesn't cover you up properly.
Are you telling us to do the opening in this?
For Seok Jin, other than a shirt with his own face,
there's a shirt with Yondu's photo on it.
- Okay. - That's how it will work.
- Do we pick between the two? - Wait.
Why is it Seok Jin? Is there something about him?
Is he a spy?
(Why is it Seok Jin? Is there something about him?)
- Right. - Is he a spy?
Why did they use Seok Jin's face?
- Why would I be a spy? - Is it because...
you were different in our group photo?
Is it because Seok Jin is a dud?
(The t-shirt is perfect as a dud.)
Let's start one by one.
- Go, Haha. - I'll start.
- I'll pick the top one. - It's either 1 or 2.
Between 1 and 2,
I pick number one.
I can't go on stage in that uniform.
Everyone, give me a chance.
(Everyone, give me a chance.)
(Let it be Seok Jin's t-shirt.)
It's interesting.
I didn't look. 1, 2, 3!
1, 2, 3!
- It's Seok Jin. - It's mine.
(He picks Seok Jin's shirt.)
(Haha has to wear the prison uniform.)
Okay.
That's too bad. Haha is dressed well today.
(Prisoner number 1 is born.)
(The audience is happy as long as it's not them.)
Goodness, is this true?
- Yes, it must be true. - It feels like a dream.
I also feel like I'm dreaming.
(Instead of being a fan-meet, it's a race.)
Is it me?
- Which one did you pick? - Number one.
(She picks number 1 thinking that it won't repeat.)
I pick number one.
Three.
It's me.
I'm jealous.
(She proves herself lucky in front of the audience.)
I got mine.
- Let's hurry. I pick number 2. - Number 2.
- Goodness. - It's me.
(He gets a prison uniform.)
I pick number one.
(The audience laughs as the number of prisoner increases.)
- Okay. - It's Kwang Soo.
(Okay, it's my t-shirt.)
Most of them are number one.
(Kwang Soo's careless choice disappoints the audience.)
(So Min picks her own shirt too.)
- It's you. - It's me.
- Seok Jin. - Okay.
- I keep my outfit, right? - Right.
Okay.
I'll finally go out looking handsome.
- I pick... - Jae Seok.
I pick number one.
- Yes, Jae Seok. - I pick number one.
Yes, Jae Seok.
(He picks Seok Jin's shirt.)
(Everyone is surprised when he gets a dud.)
This is the case except for one.
- Nice. - I picked number two.
For those...
who got the prison uniform,
if the audience shouts...
and we hear it in the waiting room,
- you don't have to wear it. - Really?
(Audience decides who wears the prison uniform.)
(It's a mission planned in trust of the fans.)
Everyone, either one is fine with me,
but I'd like...
to dress well if I can.
Shout!
(Shout!)
(Shouting)
- We can hear it. - Do we hear it?
- We heard it. - I heard it.
- We hear the sound. - Thank you.
We wear the prison uniform if you don't shout.
- Who's next? - It's Jong Kook.
Everyone.
- Appeal yourself. - I beg you.
(He begs politely.)
Shout!
(After Jong Kook's polite plea)
1, 2, 3.
(The result will be revealed on stage.)
(The first performance of Running Man's Fan-Meet starts.)
("Only One for Me" by all Running Man members)
(The one to start the performance of Running Man's Fan-Meet is...)
(is the Asian Prince.)
(Audience screams as he looks better than expected.)
(Oh, no. I'm so nervous.)
- He's pretending to be warm. - Suddenly.
(He smiles warmly.)
- What? - He pretends to be a warm man.
(Once Kwang Soo's handsome-looking part is over,)
(Haha appears.)
(I lose my mind, and my eyes close)
(The performance is stable due to Haha's appearance.)
(Ji Hyo's heart is about to explode as she watches.)
(Someone is watching Ji Hyo.)
(It's Jong Kook in a normal outfit.)
(When Jong Kook asks the audience to shout,)
(the audience responds with a big shout.)
- They shouted. - Everyone shouted.
(Well-dressed Jong Kook takes care of Ji Hyo.)
(It's not yet.)
(Ji Hyo goes on stage when Jong Kook gives a sign.)
(Ji Hyo is calm due to the audience's welcoming shout.)
(Ji Hyo's looks put them in awe.)
(The main vocalist of Running Man appears.)
(You're the only one for me)
(Thank you.)
(He acts rashly as he's excited.)
(Embracing awkward members,)
(Running Man fans' sincerely shout out.)
(After the first verse)
(The audience notices something.)
(Prisoner number 1, Jae Seok appears.)
(How is Jae Seok the only one wearing prison uniform?)
1, 2, 3.
(Silence)
Goodness.
(The audience knows what's fun.)
(They agreed in advance to be silent.)
(They're genuine laugh chasers.)
Wait.
We didn't hear anything.
(He was picked by the audience.)
(He becomes the main member today.)
(He's posing after losing his outfit.)
(The audience is very satisfied.)
(He pretends to be sweet.)
(Yu Jae Seok, you're so sexy.)
(Se Chan appears next.)
(Cuteness)
- You were singing so hard. - Pardon?
You were singing so hard.
(Is Kwang Soo being more hardworking than normal?)
You weren't like that before.
I feel like vomiting.
It's not because I'm a spy.
Isn't Jae Seok a spy?
(A few of them are being suspected for singing hard.)
(The part for Frog in Love starts.)
(Her shoulders are crunched due to nervousness.)
(She makes cheesy gestures.)
(However, the audience reacts like they're at a concert.)
(Running Man's eldest member, Seok Jin appears.)
(It's time for everyone to sing together.)
- Scream! - Let's go. Scream.
(You're the only one for me)
(We say hello after long 9 years.)
(We're grateful for Running Man fans who greet us with smiles.)
(We enjoyed every moment over the last 9 years.)
(Our fans were by our side and laughed with us.)
(The eight members' hello was awkward yet warm)
Hello, everyone.
- Hello. - Hello.
Thank you.
Special project for Running Man's ninth year anniversary.
To those who were with us during Running Man's Fan-Meet,
I'd like to thank you again with all my heart.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
There's a lot of heat from the audience.
It's really amazing.
This is just the opening, but for a moment,
I got teary.
- By the way, - Also...
look at your outfit.
- Look at your outfit. - My outfit?
(Look at your outfit before getting teary.)
- What's this? - You should match your outfit.
The audience welcomed me, so I didn't realize it.
I won't be able to look at myself on TV.
I cried a little.
- Why? - I was moved...
- by the shout from the audience. - Really?
(He touches around his eyes.)
(Everyone pretends to fall for his calculated comment.)
Stop it. What's wrong with you?
It's only the start.
- Why are you starting it already? - Your eyes look clearer than ever.
Thank you so much.
Haha will be performing first.
Please get off the stage first.
Okay, I'll see you in a moment.
Yes, man.
This is our first fan-meet in Korea.
- It's the first as a variety show. - Right.
How do you feel?
Ji Hyo?
(How does Ji Hyo feel?)
Hello, I'm Song Ji Hyo.
(Everyone screams. It's Song Ji Hyo!)
(She's so pretty.)
I didn't know that I'd be this nervous.
- I'm so nervous. - You're so pretty!
Thank you.
You're so pretty!
(She's content.)
I'm sorry, but do you have a loudspeaker?
- Did you bring a loudspeaker? - I was so startled.
- He has a very loud voice. - You're so pretty!
- I asked him to do it. - Did you?
Next is So Min.
Hello, I'm Jeon So Min.
(The audience shouts as soon as she says hello.)
Finally, today is here.
I hope that it will be unforgettable today.
It'll also stay in my memory.
Please enjoy!
(The audience responds with a big shout.)
You were about to cry.
Did you get teary?
- I'm very nervous. - Right.
My hands are trembling.
I looked at our outfits on the screen.
I'll be hosting the show today...
Yours is the worst.
(A group of 7 members and one host)
Did you come here as an MC?
(Based on his outfit, he looks like an MC.)
- As an MC. - I was imprisoned but...
- released temporarily to host. - Right.
I'm here to host your fan-meet.
Many of you are here...
to be with us on our fan-meet.
As I told you before,
please exert energy with us until you sweat.
Everyone, are you ready?
(Yes, we're ready.)
With your expectations and support,
we'll start the performance.
Seok Jin will...
announce the start.
(We can't believe that we'll hear this live.)
(He feels their excitement.)
You say "starts" when I say "race".
One shot, one shot.
All right. Race.
- Starts! - Starts!
(The real performance starts now.)
(The real show starts now.)
(The festival officially starts.)
(Love chemistry that's beyond imagination)
(Performances that leave you speechless)
(Artist collaboration is finally revealed.)
(Ninth anniversary fan-meeting gets heated.)
(Members get a mysterious note after the performance.)
(A surprising fact about the spy)
(They narrow down the search...)
(with suspicious proofs.)
(He's definitely a spy.)
(They suspect each other more and more.)
(Who is the hiding spy?)
(Nine Years of Running Man, Spy Game)