I'm sorry.
Can you turn around for a bit? Yes.
That's funny.
You want me to turn around?
- Yes.
- Could you turn around?
- Hello. Excuse me for interrupting.
- Hey.
(Excuse me for interrupting.)
I'll just change the light bulb.
- You need to change the light bulb?
- Yes.
All of a sudden?
We're in the middle of a meeting.
The light bulbs are fine.
But you're going to change them?
(Jong Kook starts crying
to avoid laughing.)
- We should watch him.
- We ought to.
(The moment you watch it,
you cannot stop laughing.)
(A strong aura
of his skit tell them...)
(it will be impossible
not to laugh at his skit.)
(They must play fair
and not avoid watching his skit.)
- We have to watch.
- You need to watch him.
- Something might fall. Watch.
- We have to watch him.
- He's switching the bulb.
- All right.
- Let me see.
- You need to watch him.
(My goodness!)
- You can't close your eyes.
- Something might fall.
(Pounding)
(Five colored toes)
(Wriggling his toes)
Let me see.
(Laughing)
(Since he laughed,
he'll do the penalty.)
(He's in a big crisis as well.)
- Look at his socks.
- My gosh.
(Guiding them through the skit)
(What have I just witnessed?)
(His taste in socks
is quite a shock.)
My goodness.
(At that moment,
Ji Hyo comes back in disguise.)
- Why isn't this working?
- We tightened it.
Darn it. It's not working.
Why can't I get it out?
(Taking off his jacket)
(Shocked)
(Surprised)
(His belly button looks like
a huge Korean melon.)
(Slopping)
Hey, you have to watch him.
- Did you see his belly button?
- I did.
(Another unexpected side
of an ordinary-looking mechanic)
His belly button looks like
a Korean melon.
(Sloshing)
Isn't that a steamed bun?
Jae Suk laughed too.
- Jae Suk, you're out again.
- I didn't laugh.
(Staring)
Is that a garlic clove
on your belly button?
Is that the garlic clove
(Is that the garlic clove
on your belly button?)
- Eun Soo, you're out.
- My gosh.
(I thought
it looked like a Korean melon.)
Isn't that a mushroom?
- Garlic clove.
- No?
- My daughter likes it.
- Isn't that a mushroom?
(The garlic comment crushed her.
Eun Soo will carry out the penalty.)
- Have a good day.
- Okay.
- Bye.
My gosh, that didn't work.
So what will you do
with the water slap?
- Yes, how will you do it?
- Shall we keep going?
Yes. Since we're on the subject,
let's do it.
To tell you the truth, we should...
be doing this with the new producer,
Jae Suk, but he keeps on...
(The new producer, Jae Suk,
enters with the penalty disguise.)
(Holding his breath)
I'm the director.
(A blond director from abroad)
He's the director.
Hello.
(He just looks like a llama
from the US.)
(Bursting into laughter)
- Jinyoung, you're out.
- Were you having a meeting?
- We were having a meeting.
- Yes.
They said water slaps were boring,
so we're coming up with new ideas.
(Waddling)
- Putting on a disguise...
- It's hard.
Things aren't going too well.
Let's give a big hand for everyone.
(The llama has
the biggest front paws.)
(Clapping)
(Why is the American llama
clapping?)
All right.
(Let's keep my mouth shut.)
(I must hold out.)
(Knocking)
(Who is it?)
- Yes?
- Who is it?
- Someone is here again.
- Come on in.
(Who is the guest
visiting the production crew?)
- Do we have a guest?
- My gosh.
Hello,
I'm a newly appointed director.
(But that blue face seems
somewhat familiar.)
Well, she's...
the fish-shaped bun seller.
Have some fish-shaped buns.
(Lady Yondu tried to sell the buns
as if her blue face is nothing new.)
(Do you want choux cream flavor
or red bean flavor?)
(Are you a lady?)
(Yes.)
(Thanks to her determination...)
(as fish-shaped bun seller,
she was appointed as the director.)
(They are about to crack up
at the memory of the bun seller.)
(Laughing)
So Min, you're out.
(So Min's laughter is spotted.)
(Looking invincible)
It looks like the TV ratings are
going up a lot these days. Right?
(Laughing)
It's my first time seeing her
in person. I'm a fan.
I'm your fan. I saw you on TV.
- But...
- The fish-shaped bun seller.
- I'm a fan.
- Oh, no.
I guess you never know
what lies ahead in life.
Well, I'm your fan.
I want to watch her a little more.
- I'm your fan.
- I'm a huge fan.
(Nasal flaring)
(Shutting his eyes)
I'm your fan.
(Farting)
- Nice to meet you.
- Are you a director?
I'm your fan.
(What just happened?)
- Are you a director?
- Yes, I'm a director.
(She keeps farting
when everyone is flustered.)
- Why...
- She keeps farting.
Gosh, I...
(I think I heard...)
She keeps farting.
- Gosh, I have indigestion.
- Eun Soo is out.
- I'm sorry.
- Why do you keep farting?
That's enough to take a dump.
(That's enough to take a dump.)
(Trying hard not to laugh)
(He can't hold in his laughter.)
That's so unexpected.
Who?
(Jae Suk will carry out
the penalty.)
It's just that I have indigestion.
I'm sorry.
Bye, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- We'll do our best.
- Bye, ma'am.
Please remember me.
(Director, please get better.)
The fish-shaped bun seller.
(Knocking)
Wait. Someone is here.
(Wait. Someone is here.)
Hello.
- My gosh. Hello.
- What brings you here?
- He's an anchor.
- Hello.
(The official voice actor
of the show, Kim Yoon Sang)
- I'm here on behalf of anchors.
- Coffee.
(He visited the production crew
with beverages.)
- Coffee. My gosh.
- Hello.
(Surprised)
- What brings you here?
- Isn't that Yoon Sang?
- I heard you were having a meeting.
- You really came to see us?
- I'm here on behalf of anchors.
- Really?
Thank you.
- My goodness. Really?
- He's a handsome anchor.
- I'm Yoon Sang. Hello.
- Hi.
- What's up with your makeup?
- Thank you.
(Opening the lid)
Wait, this isn't coffee.
This is beef radish soup.
- Wait, this isn't coffee.
- This tastes...
This is beef radish soup.
This tastes weird.
(Laughing)
It's beef radish soup.
(Dripping)
You should have brought
instant rice too.
- I like mine cold.
- You can ask for that.
- You should've brought rice.
- You're out too.
- I know the flavor, but it's weird.
- There's one with rice.
- I know this dish, but it's odd.
- You should've brought rice.
Beef radish soup
is my favorite dish.
It's so good.
How could you put it
in the coffee cup?
- Enjoy your food.
- How could you bring it here?
- Thank you.
- Is it good?
I really didn't see that one coming.
Seriously. The beef radish soup.
- When I opened it, I was shocked.
- I was so shocked.
It's my first time craving kimchi
while holding the coffee cup.
(Laughing)
(Strangely, I'm craving kimchi.)
(Thinking about sad things)
- Why do I crave kimchi so much?
- My gosh, Suk Jin.
(Haha will carry out the penalty.)
(Gazing)
Jinyoung, you look good...
- even with that on.
- Right.
- You're the best-looking guy here.
- I want to live for a week...
- with his face.
- I don't have any disguise on.
- What?
You don't?
(I don't have any disguise on.)
(Jinyoung with the beggar disguise
is better-looking than Se Chan.)
- Didn't you put on a disguise?
- No, I don't.
No, I don't have a disguise on.
- I don't have a disguise on.
- Go. You laughed.
- You don't?
- No.
- Really? I thought you did.
- Aren't you on the same team?
- What is this? Jae Suk.
- Is he in my team?
(And at that time...)
- This beef radish soup is great.
- It's really good.
(Surprised)
(The Tape Surgery
over the tip of his nose and lips)
(Laughing)
(Drinking the beef radish soup
without any hesitation)
- What's happening?
- Suk Jin, you're out.
(The beef radish soup
keeps dripping.)
Did you get a Botox injection
on your lips?
(Plump lips)
(Trying not to laugh)
He does that every time,
but it's still funny.
- What's going on?
- Seriously.
What's up with my lips?
I want to buy his face.
(A comedian's point of view)
If I attempt to do something,
I'm worried I might laugh
at my own skit.
- By the way,
- That could happen.
- were you guys doing well?
- Yes.
(Kyung Hwan comes back
with his penalty disguise.)
(Staring)
Had I known this is
what we'd be doing...
Your disguise isn't that funny
given you're a comedian.
Right.
(Your disguise isn't that funny
given you're a comedian.)
Kyung Hwan, you're out.
(He's kicked out
within 1 second of sitting down.)
(Jae Suk laughs after making
a brutally honest comment.)
Jae Suk, you're out.
Darn it.
I'm out because of Kyung Hwan.
It's all because of Kyung Hwan.
- Hello, producers.
- Hello.
(Another guest
has visited the crew.)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- My gosh.
- I'm a CEO of a label.
- I want to introduce a new singer.
- I see.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
(The surprise guest
is the CEO of a label.)
Wait. Give me a second.
He's over there.
I get the feeling
that she's the singer.
(Screaming)
Ta-da.
- I bet it's her.
- No. I'm sorry.
(A man shows up with a group
of high school girls. Who is he?)
Great.
(He'll make the production crew
of "Dalim Man" laugh.)
(It's Han Gi Beom.)
(A huge mosquito bit me)
(It was itchy)
(The moment you see his eyes,
you can't hold it in.)
(As soon as he makes a move,
everyone is bound to laugh.)
(The ultimate killer of laughter
is back.)
Ta-da.
(As the ultimate king enters,)
(they bow down at a 90-degree angle
to welcome him.)
(Kneeling down to ask
for forgiveness of their negligence)
(As he's about to laugh,)
(he asks for help from the staff.)
(A simple method is the best.
I'm not going to watch that.)
(His appearance is enough
to make everyone laugh.)
This is cheating!
Let me introduce my singers
to you first.
- Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Hello, we're Han's Band.
(Hello, we're Han's Band.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Sounding cheerful)
(Hello, we're Han's Band.)
(Gi Beom, what are you doing?)
- This is amazing.
- My goodness.
- Let me watch the skit before I go.
- Hello.
I'm the main vocalist
and the leader.
- I'm Nose Hair, Han Byeol.
- Right.
- Han Byeol. Right.
- She was Nose Hair.
Hello.
I'm the Middle Hair of the team.
(I'm the Middle Hair of the team.)
(Laughing)
(He probably wanted to say
he was the center.)
I'm the center of the national team,
Han Gi Beom.
(Why did he do a cute act
all of a sudden?)
- He's the center.
- Right.
Hello,
I am the unrivaled vocal...
I'm in charge of being
the main dancer.
(Stuttering)
(Laughing)
I'm in charge of being
the main dancer.
- You're in charge of many things.
- I'm the armpit...
(You're in charge of many things.)
I'm in charge of being
the main dancer.
- You're in charge of many things.
- I'm the armpit...
She keeps smelling her armpit.
Why does she stutter so much?
(They have unspecified roles
in the group.)
They've prepared their title song.
- Okay.
- All right.
(Han's Band's title song
will be revealed.)
1, 2, 3, 4!
(With Middle Hair in the group,)
(how will their song turn out?)
(Don't tease me for being young)
Who teased you?
Who teased him?
(Gi Beom was born in 1964.)
(Did you have to go this far?)
- Gosh.
- Why are you doing this?
(He doesn't know the lyrics.)
- Stop.
- I can't hold back.
- Stop it, please.
- I just can't.
Please stop, Gi Beom.
Stop.
- Please cast them.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- We will.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye!
- Goodbye.
They were awesome.
Round one is complete.
It's impossible not to laugh.
- Just imagining it is hilarious.
- That was hilarious.
Team Producer laughed 15 times.
That's not that much.
Team Writer laughed 11 times.
What a relief.
Team New Producer laughed 27 times.
We're weak when it comes
to things like this.
Team Writer wins this round.
(Team Writer wins.)
(The main producer,
assistant director,)
(Coughing Ghost, and
Clacking Ghost are among them.)
(The winning team
may pick one team...)
(and find out how many members
of that team are ghosts.)
- Which team? It doesn't matter.
- I think...
- How about Jae Suk's team?
- Team New Producer?
Yes.
They're competent.
- We pick Team New Producer.
The number of ghosts
in that team is...
(Will there be ghosts in that team?)
- None.
- What?
(There are none.)
- There are none?
It makes no sense.
- They're everywhere but there.
- Right.
This is fishy.
Was the result shocking?
- It's a bit tricky.
- It's a bit difficult.
- Which team did you pick?
- Which team?
We can't reveal that.
It's tricky.
But it's fishy.
- Are half of the members ghosts?
- It's confusing.
The result is confusing.
Please change your uniforms,
and let's move onto round two.
- Okay.
(They move onto round 2.)
(They arrive
at their next location.)
- Suk Jin is in the toilet.
- I see.
I was wondering why it felt weird.
Suk Jin's not here.
We can start without him.
(He wants to start
without Suk Jin.)
(This is how strong
their 9-year friendship is.)
I was surprised
that it felt empty without him.
We can start. It's fine.
Let's clap for him.
I was checking my phone.
(He returns.)
- Suk Jin.
- What? Why are you clapping?
- I'm relieved.
- Why?
Because you're alive. I'm serious.
Let's be grateful
that he's still here with us.
Gosh.
Here is your second mission
to help determine the two ghosts.
Your entire team needs to pass.
It's called the Song Train.
(Song Train)
What is that?
If you get
3 out of 8 questions right,
- we'll give you a hint.
- Okay.
- Let's do well.
- It'll be obvious.
- It'll be very obvious.
- Definitely.
Every round will have six people.
You will all be wearing headphones
and will have to deliver...
the dance moves
to the person in front.
The last member needs to guess
the singer and the song.
Please pick the six members.
Six members?
- Then...
- Let's mix them up.
Those in similar age groups
can play rock-paper-scissors and go.
Suk Jin will have to play alone.
(That means Suk Jin will be alone.)
(He'll be given an advantage
and will perform folk dance moves.)
This is all that he does.
(Suk Jin has been dancing
the same dance moves...)
(for the past 54 years.)
For this game,
I must participate.
Those who know many old songs
must participate.
Will the six members come up?
It'll be us.
We must get it right.
- Right.
- We need to share the hint.
- But...
- It'll be obvious if you fail.
- I'm not sure if there are ghosts.
- I'll suspect any who fails.
- Me too.
- Here we go.
- Get ready.
- Let's do this.
(I know this.)
This is easy...
- because...
- Do you know this?
- You just need to do the body roll.
- Right.
(Which dance move is it?)
If you can't get this,
you'll be suspected right away.
(He pulls the shirt over him
and does the body roll.)
- How will Ri do that?
- That's good.
(It looks a bit disturbing.)
How will she do this?
(How will she pull her shirt over?)
Do another move!
(This body roll is the highlight
of this song.)
("Love Song" by Rain)
(Unlike Rain who has great abs,)
(the strap on Haha's waist
is suffocating his waist.)
(Let's watch a bit more
from Rain's performance.)
from Haha's performance as well.)
How will she do it?
- That was perfect.
- That was.
(Despite having different physiques,
the moves were exact.)
Don't do it!
(She performs the body roll.)
(I got it.)
She's good.
- She got it.
- Good work.
(She uses the skills she got
from traditional dance.)
That's good.
(Will this round be easy?)
(He performs
a different dance move.)
What's wrong with his hip?
- That's a bit...
- That's...
- This is wrong.
- That looks weird.
They're in trouble.
Did you get it?
Why is she dressed
like a grandma underneath?
(It's the 2019
fall and winter look.)
- What does she have on?
- She looks like a tower.
(Nonetheless, she undergoes
her mission.)
He got it.
She has an electric blanket
wrapped underneath.
An electric blanket?
Did he get it?
(She successfully gets
the job done.)
- Good work.
- He's doing it.
(Did Jong Kook get it right?)
Rain.
(Rain)
(He just needs to get
the song right.)
"Rainism".
- That's not it!
- It's Rain.
Come on!
- Jong Kook, did you know?
- Of course, I did.
Gosh. I got the title confused.
- "Rainism" is...
- Those two are very different.
I should've gotten it.
I was sure.
Kyung Hwan and Ji Hyo
shouldn't be next to each other.
Ji Hyo is fine.
- Can you and Ji Hyo switch?
- I'm not a terrible dancer.
No, she did well.
She did well.
- She knew the key points.
- Right.
- It's not about dancing well.
- See that?
- Fine.
- It's about getting the key points.
- Here we go.
- Get ready, set, go.
This one is so easy.
("Up and Down" by EXID)
(Everyone knows this dance move.)
If you don't get this,
you're definitely a ghost.
- Definitely.
- You're definitely...
the Clacking Ghost.
(Up, down, up, up, down)
(She recognizes the dance move,)
(but it's too provocative.)
(He's into it.)
- It's too provocative.
- They have to get this right.
(Choi Ri shows off her dance moves.)
Okay.
(She dances well...)
(but then suddenly adds to it.)
She's so weird.
Why did you add
your own dance moves to it?
You did it at the beginning!
(Grooving)
He's doing it.
What is that?
Why are you overdoing it?
Okay.
You got it? This is easy.
They have to get this one right.
(She does it perfectly.)
Okay, okay.
She's good.
(Jong Kook's dance moves
are precise as well.)
(However...)
- This is...
- Come on.
- This is easy.
- He got it.
What?
You don't know this?
- What?
- You don't know this?
- You should know this one.
- You have to.
- Six...
- Hold on.
- You don't know it?
- Four,
- You don't know this?
- three,
- Don't lie.
- two,
- You need to get this one right.
- one.
- Come on.
This doesn't make sense!
Hold on!
- It's him.
- Are you serious?
- Don't you know this?
- Right! I'm sorry.
Don't lie.
- I'm serious.
- You didn't know that?
It doesn't make sense.
I even performed...
- the exact moves.
- This one was obvious.
This was so sudden,
- so I couldn't remember.
- We danced to this before.
- I'm sorry.
- No way.
- Isn't this too obvious?
- I know.
- He's so suspicious.
- He sure is.
- I'm being suspected too much.
- Jae Suk.
- It's seriously not me.
- There's no explanation for this.
Switch places with me.
The ghost wouldn't be
this obvious.
Exactly.
- There are both ghosts.
- They wouldn't be this obvious.
(Did he do this on purpose
so they won't get a hint?)
We could've gotten two more right.
You got all the singers right.
- The questions were...
- We should've gotten...
"Up and Down" and "Love Song"
correct.
- Jae Suk is...
- I was confused.
- suspicious.
- Let's do this.
Okay, okay!
- You should be at the end.
- Me?
- Yes.
- You just need to copy,
so So Min, go first.
- Se Chan will guess.
- Do you know many songs?
- Yes, more than you.
(Yes, more than you.)
(He doesn't know what to say.)
- That's right.
- Fair enough.
- Then go to the front.
- You're...
- You're not flustered, are you?
- You spoke the truth.
What's terrifying is that
no matter where Suk Jin is,
it won't work out for him.
- My gosh.
- It doesn't matter where he is.
Can you hang up there for a minute?
(He's trying to prevent Suk Jin
from playing.)
- Just for a minute. I know you can.
- No.
- I can do well.
- Where will you put him?
What if he ends up leaving?
- What if he does?
- Let's try this first.
(Se Chan suddenly coughs.)
Are you the Coughing Ghost?
(Coughing)
(Why did he suddenly cough?)
I was just coughing.
- Was that a hidden mission?
- I had phlegm...
in my throat.
- Maybe that's his hidden mission.
- I just had a lot of phlegm.
You're the Coughing Ghost.
Ri was the only one
in high heels earlier.
(Coincidentally, she was the only
one wearing heels.)
I saw that too.
Could she be Clacking Ghost?
That's why he coughed
and she had on high heels.
- Coughing...
- Would I be this obvious then?
Actually, you made it seem
quite natural.
- Really?
- Yes
And Suk Jin must be Trickle.
(Another tip-off)
- No way.
- I'm sure of it.
No, I'm Gushing.
I went to the restroom
with him, remember?
- He's Drizzle.
- Drizzle?
(Drizzle)
- Gushing.
- No, Drizzle.
- Drizzle.
- Gushing.
- Moving on.
- Let's do better, all right?
- We have so many weak links.
- Tell me about it.
Still, So Min's not a bad dancer.
- Yes, she is.
- Right.
- She's a good dancer.
- That's right.
I know this one so well.
("Han" by Chakra)
(Chakra's debut single
that was released in 2000)
(The Indian inspired dancing
is the highlight of the song.)
This won't be easy though.
- That's it.
- No, wait...
Don't make it look too cute.
- No.
- Don't be too cute!
Don't make it look cute.
- However, this dance...
- He won't know this.
is hard to guess correctly.
Also, the two younger ones
are at the front.
Right, they'll never guess it right.
Oh, no.
(However, the dance seems like...)
(Kungkungtta)
That looks good.
(What's with the Kungkungtta?)
Foot of the mountain, kungkungtta
(It's a word relay.)
The foot of a big bear, kungkungtta
- Smelly feet, kungkungtta
- Kungkungtta
(All they did was sing the jingle.)
(It fits perfectly.)
Hurry up already.
(In full power)
Good, this is good.
- What's going on?
- Nice.
(Wow!)
- What's going on?
- This is better.
You're doing great.
He's improvising.
It looks similar.
Nice.
(Floundering)
What...
(What's this?)
- What's this?
- The hands should be together.
He forgot what's important.
(Suk Jin only dances
with his expressions.)
- What's going on?
- Suk Jin's being weird.
Why isn't he putting
his hands together?
- This is bad.
- Chakra.
(Chakra!)
(Se Chan guesses the artist
just by the dance moves.)
(Surprised)
(He just has to guess the song now.)
"Han".
(That is correct!)
(No way!)
(I can't believe it!)
(So Min runs over to him in glee.)
What?
Did I guess it right?
- What's going on?
- How did you know?
Hold on.
Seriously?
Chills just traveled down my spine.
How did you guess it right?
This...
- I have you locked
- You're locked within me
- Seriously?
How did you know?
Is it really "Han" by Chakra?
- No way.
- Just think about it.
Suk Jin didn't
bring his hands together.
- He's red in the face.
- You should've done this.
- This was key.
- How did Se Chan know?
Anyway, this was a tricky question.
Your girlfriend
came by earlier though.
- What?
- When you got the question right.
- Where?
- She was absolutely thrilled.
(The girlfriend who was thrilled)
- Right?
- Hold on.
She was like this.
- That's right.
- You mean So Min?
- Didn't you know?
- His girlfriend.
- That's right.
- So Min.
- Se Chan's girlfriend.
Anyway, she was here earlier.
Wives are never that ecstatic.
She came dashing over...
and enjoyed the victory with you.
She was like
his personal cheerleader.
I was startled, So Min.
Let's move on.
Why don't we have
Suk Jin guess the song?
- Let's change it up.
- He doesn't know many songs.
He'll never guess them.
- You should go first instead.
- Just follow the dance you see.
It's best if he goes after So Min.
We should have So Min
remedy the damage he does.
Am I that big of a weak link?
(He's upset.)
(The weak link explodes.)
- I mean...
- He finally knows.
- Finally!
- I only danced what I saw.
- He finally knows.
- That's not it.
- You don't.
- You never do.
It wasn't what Kwang Soo danced.
But Se Chan guessed
"Han" by Chakie.
Did you just say Chakie?
No, I meant Chakra.
We have people who
can remedy the situation.
I agree that it's best
for him to go first.
Okay, I'll go first
like you all suggested.
Don't hold me responsible though.
What if he does a move
we can't mimic?
- Then...
- His moves...
So Min must try
and remedy the situation.
So Min, do your best
to figure out what the dance is.
Here we go.
Please put on your headsets.
It has begun.
(Which song does
Suk Jin have to dance to?)
("Warrior's Descendant" by H.O.T)
(Suk Jin must mimic
Jang Woo Hyuk's dancing.)
Yes, that's the key move.
- No, we're doomed.
- Why is he working out over there?
Oh, no.
- It's over.
- So Min could know.
She might get the gist of it.
(The stretching exercise version
of "Warrior's Descendant")
- He's doing the key moves.
- That's it.
- He did the key moves.
- That's not part of the dance.
(Jumping)
- That wasn't in the dance.
- Seriously?
I told you this wasn't
going to work.
I already said it'd be a disaster.
This is bad.
The jumping ruined it all.
- Why did he have to jump?
- We need Se Chan.
Look at Jinyoung dance.
- Let's try and guess it right.
- How can one move like that?
Here goes the next weak link.
It's a tricky one.
This is looking weirder and weirder.
(He suddenly goes
for the pelvic thrust.)
(What?)
Are you kidding me?
Why add what you didn't see?
That's not what he danced.
Hey!
- That's it.
- Hold on.
He's just dancing however he likes.
(And now Eun Soo's
doing the wrong moves.)
This?
This? It's Jang Do Yeon's move.
- That wasn't what he danced.
- Why on earth did you add that?
- Isn't it Jang Do Yeon?
- What on earth is this move?
Why on earth did you add that move?
What is this?
Well...
What's the answer?
Hold on. Is it...
H.O.T?
(He guessed H.O.T
after looking at that dance?)
(Will Se Chan make
another miracle happen?)
(Which song by H.O.T?)
"We Are the Future".
- "Warrior's Descendant".
- It was "Warrior's Descendant".
- That was close!
- "Warrior's Descendant"?
- What...
- I'll tell you what happened.
Kwang Soo ruined it all.
Why did you throw
Jang Do Yeon into the mix?
Why did you add that?
- That was so close.
- It just came out.
- This won't work.
- It was added in the middle.
- So Min must go first.
- What about Jinyoung?
- Right, you can copy it.
- Copy the moves.
(Jinyoung will start off
the sixth song.)
This one's too easy.
- It's a done deal.
- It's too easy.
This is a famous one.
("Touch My Body" by SISTAR)
(Its stand-out move...)
(is the hip jerking
that's done turned around.)
Jinyoung will easily do this.
(He dances exactly
what he saw on the video.)
That's it.
(Perfectly copied)
Jinyoung...
copied the move instantly.
So Min just wants
to keep seeing him dance.
So Min, that's enough!
(She has an ulterior motive.)
(After double-checking the move,
she relays it to Suk Jin.)
(She dances the move
Jinyoung showed her.)
Nice. She's a great dancer.
(What? Hold on.)
(Like a traditional dance)
Why is he making moves up
when he saw her dance just now?
You've got to be kidding me.
- Oh, no. This is bad.
- What is that?
We're doomed.
- It's over for us.
- Is he kicking a hacky sack?
- No way.
- He's driving me crazy.
- Let's do this.
- Can I kick him?
I want to fly over there
and kick him.
Okay, that's enough.
Are you kidding me?
(Sungguridangdang sungdangdang)
Just dance what you saw!
- What on earth is that?
- Gosh.
Just dance the moves you saw!
What are we going to do
with those two?
I so want to kick them.
Just dance what you saw.
Those two...
What on earth is this?
(What on earth is this?)
Now Eun Soo's being weird as well.
He'll never get this right.
It's impossible.
Just consider it as a useless hint.
I have no idea.
(I'm going to have to guess.)
SISTAR?
(He got the artist right again!)
What's the song?
(Will Se Chan be able to guess
the song?)
"SHAKE IT"?
- Gosh.
- "SHAKE IT"...
- That was so close.
- Unbelievable.
Why didn't anyone do this move?
- Yes, this.
- They started off with that.
All I needed was this.
- It was his fault, wasn't it?
- Just look.
See how it came down.
Jinyoung, show them.
Go ahead. That's it.
- See?
- So Min, what about you?
(So Min danced it perfectly too.)
Now Suk Jin.
Oh, dear.
(His dancing makes everyone lament.)
And now show them
how you danced it.
How on earth does that become this?
- Are you kidding me?
- Gosh.
Let's take out all the weak links.
- Move.
- We know who is good at this.
Now, Haha, get in line.
- Avengers assemble.
- Haha and Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Eun Soo, stay there.
Avengers assemble.
The Avengers
will play the game this time.
- We need to get this right.
- Please.
If we can't answer this correctly...
- He's right.
- Let's just give up.
- Okay.
- We need to get this right.
This is our last chance.
Now that I see you all,
it makes sense
that Eun Soo is one of us.
(He punches them with hard facts.)
(Two weak links)
You're right.
It's either Eun Soo or Ri.
What about me?
(There's me!)
Ji Hyo...
Well...
After this round,
can we let them do a bonus round?
- I'd like to watch them.
- We're out of questions.
Okay, I get it.
Only Eun Soo has to do a good job.
This is another easy one.
- He's taking a while.
- Jinyoung will know this.
- It's an oldie though.
- He'll know this.
- He can copy the moves.
- That's right.
Look at that.
("Into the New World"
by Girls' Generation)
(There are a lot of moves
that stand out.)
(One of them is the kick!)
(He's copying the moves.)
- Talk about being competent.
- I don't know what it is.
He's too good at this.
(A meeting between a competent man
and a pop dancer.)
(Jinyoung dances,)
(and So Min copies him.)
(Is this right?)
Is that it?
(They communicate through dance.)
(What are they doing?)
(Her boyfriend has no idea.)
(Let me dance this time.)
Is this "Dirty Dancing" or what?
(Is this the movie,
"Dirty Dancing"?)
"Dirty Dancing"?
(The characters in the movie
communicated through dance.)
(They take turns dancing.)
- What is this?
- This is not good.
It's too hard.
(So Min comes out of the romantic
movie and carries out the mission.)
This is way too hard.
(Oh!)
(So Min realizes the answer
and kicks.)
(It's the key move from "Into the
New World" that Jinyoung missed.)
(So Min copies the dance perfectly.)
(She sure is a pop-dance expert.)
Well done.
So Min knows the answer.
(It's So Min's Generation.)
(Thanks to So Min,
Haha knows the answer.)
(He emphasizes the kick.)
That's the key.
- We'll make it this time.
- But...
- Eun Soo doesn't seem to know.
- She does.
(Suk Jin is worried about Eun Soo.)
Go, Eun Soo.
(She kicks twice.)
- She shouldn't kick twice.
- It's only once.
She's suspicious.
Why...
(Kicking)
She must be the Clacking Ghost.
(Suk Jin suspects Eun Soo.)
She's the Clacking Ghost.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
(He suddenly dances the can-can.)
That's not right.
- This is not good.
- What is that?
(Perfect)
(Double kick)
(The dance has become
completely different.)
(Jong Kook's dance looks
too different.)
- What's that?
- That's Park Jin Young's song.
- Park Jin Young.
- "Swing Baby".
- That's wrong.
- It wasn't this? The woman...
- No.
It was "Into the New World"
by Girls' Generation.
- That's why they kicked.
- It was wrong.
You have to kick like this.
- I thought...
- We started off fine.
I thought it was,
"I'm not a little girl anymore..."
- Park Ji Yoon.
- Right.
It was too hard.
There's one question left,
but it's meaningless.
- You've failed every question.
- All right.
You can't receive hints about
Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost.
Then we can't find them.
You've failed this mission.
- Let's move on to the next.
- I think I know.
I'll give you a chance
to win a hint...
- You should.
- about the ghosts.
- Okay.
- We're going to play...
Yes or No, Answer Me.
This is fun.
- It's...
- Gosh.
- It's harder than you think.
- It's confusing.
If I say, "Yes or no, answer me,"
and then "I like Korean food,"
- you say a Korean dish.
- Kimchi jjigae.
If I say, "I dislike Korean food,"
you have to say the name of a food
that's not Korean.
Spaghetti or pasta, for example.
Pizza.
- Pasta I dislike
- Pasta
If you make a mistake,
you'll be suspected.
We'll play three times.
If you succeed once, you win a hint.
For warm-up,
let's start with So Min...
- and continue this way.
- Okay.
Let's start with So Min.
- Yes or no, answer me
I dislike actresses
Lee Kwang Soo I dislike
(She did it right,
but I feel offended.)
I like comedians
Yoo Jae Suk I like
I like male idol singers
Jinyoung I like
I dislike trot singers
- Na Hoon A I like
- It's "dislike."
(He was supposed to say,
"I dislike.")
- "I dislike."
- What?
He said, "I dislike."
You have to say it too.
- But I like them.
- No.
He likes them.
(I like trot singers.)
It's not about
your personal opinion.
- If he says, "I dislike,"
- Some people are stubborn like him.
you have to say it too.
And you have to name
a person who isn't a trot singer.
Give my name, "Yang Se Chan,"
for example.
- Let's start with Ri.
- Okay.
- Let's do this!
- And the last player...
- will be Kyung Hwan.
- Okay.
- Yes or no, answer me
I like African countries
I like Africa
- Gosh.
- What?
(Everyone is complaining.)
- I like Zambia, Morocco...
- Senegal.
- Ghana.
- Senegal, Ghana...
That was strange.
Why couldn't you do that?
- Ri, I'm disappointed.
- But...
This is driving me crazy.
Then let's start back here.
Let's start with Jinyoung.
- Okay.
- Me? Okay.
- Who's behind me?
- Okay.
If you fail this time too,
you'll be suspected.
- Yes or no, answer me
I like tropical fruits
Mangoes I like
I dislike Korean movies
"Titanic" I dislike
I dislike foreign movies
I dislike
(- I dislike foreign movies
- Confused.)
- Time's up.
- What?
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks"!
(If you dislike foreign movies,
say, "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks.")
That was an easy question for us.
(Kwang Soo feels bitter.)
- "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks."
- You're suspicious.
Why would you say
you dislike that movie?
Running Man knows
only one Korean movie.
(They're all fanatics of the movie.)
(Only one Korean movie is allowed
for Running Man.)
Why? Why is that
the only Korean movie?
- Why did you fail?
- It's been too long.
- Let's start with So Min this time.
- Me?
Let's start with So Min.
- Yes or no, answer me
I like red fruits
- Apples I like
- There you go.
I like trot singers
Jin Sung I like
I dislike romance movies
"Tazza" I dislike
(I get it, so please stop.)
I dislike cartoons
I dislike...
"One-Eyed Jacks"
Gosh.
"Tazza" saved two people.
Good.
I like Korean historical figures
I like Yi Sun Sin
I dislike red food
I dislike Korean melons
I dislike Korean pop songs
I dislike...
What? Why?
- Hey!
- "Speechless"!
(Jong Kook is a living witness
of the Korean pop scene.)
- Hey!
- "Speechless"!
You don't know any foreign songs?
- It doesn't make sense.
- No.
- He's suspicious.
- I swear.
- I didn't remember "Speechless".
- Why didn't you say "Speechless"?
I didn't remember the title.
I swear.
Why...
Why did you ask me about pop songs?
You sang...
Let me start.
- Everyone is suspicious.
- Let's play again, starting here.
Forget it. It's over.
You failed to win a hint...
- about the ghosts again.
- Gosh.
The ghosts would be relieved.
This time,
Jong Kook was suspicious.
(They arrive at
the last mission spot.)
This is the last mission
where you can find the ghosts.
- It's called Late Night TV Station.
- What's that?
- We're back here.
- It still looks the same.
Hidden in the TV station
are hints about...
Coughing Ghost, Clacking Ghost,
the producer,
and the assistant director.
To win, the "Dalim Man" staff
has to either eliminate...
Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost...
or find the legendary proposal
and put it in the safe in the lobby.
(They have to either find the ghosts
or put the proposal in the safe.)
Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost
has to either eliminate...
the producer or find and sign
the legendary proposal.
They just need to sign it?
- Yes.
- That's the ghosts' mission.
The losing team will be penalized.
Only the "Dalim Man" staff
can put a proposal in the safe.
If they put in the wrong proposal,
they lose immediately.
Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost
will also lose immediately...
if they sign the wrong proposal.
- There are wrong proposals?
- There must be many proposals.
There are wrong proposals,
- so Kwang Soo, be careful.
- Yes.
- What?
- Keep your eyes wide open.
Also, on the 11th floor...
- is the Ghost Radio Booth.
- What's that?
Three people who won
audience tickets can bring...
one partner each
into the radio booth.
If the producer, assistant director,
Coughing Ghost, or Clacking Ghost...
is in the booth,
you'll hear a special sound.
- What are you?
- What?
Tell me the truth.
- I wasn't told anything.
- You have a role, don't you?
Behind the assistant director's
name tag is...
a crucial hint.
If the producer, assistant director,
Coughing Ghost, or Clacking Ghost...
eliminates two people by ripping off
their name tags,
they will get a protective
shield on their name tag.
(By eliminating 2 people,
they get a protective shield.)
In that case,
they will not be eliminated...
even if their name tag is
ripped off.
- By eliminating two people?
- Yes.
- That's unfair.
- And they become invincible.
Then how do you win?
You find the proposal.
- And put it in the safe?
- You either sign it...
or put it in the safe.
Can you rip off any name tag?
If you happen to rip off
the producer's name tag,
you'll all lose.
The producer will have to
win people over to his or her side.
How about we share the hints
we received?
I'm innocent. Tell me.
Isn't it better to share the hints?
The hint said there's no ghost
on Team New Producer.
- No ghost?
(The number of ghosts
on Team New Producer is...)
(zero.)
The hint said there's no ghost
on Team New Producer.
- No ghost?
Team New Producer, gather around.
I'm here.
- The four of us aren't the ghosts.
- We aren't the ghosts.
That's the hint we got.
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Se Chan‚
and Eun Soo aren't the ghosts.)
So we're the ones left,
including Ji Hyo.
So they're among these eight?
Assistant Director, Producer,
Clacking Ghost...
- Please go to your positions.
- This is hard.
I'm clueless.
- So Min!
- Yes?
You better be careful.
I have to be.
I'd be target number one.
- Aren't you the producer?
- I'm not.
- Are you the assistant director?
- No.
You can't be the Clacking Ghost.
You're the Crazy Ghost.
(You can't be the Clacking Ghost.
You're the Crazy Ghost.)
That's you.
You're the Crazy Ghost.
- See you later.
- On which floor?
(They go to their positions
for now.)
- We'll see.
- Come to the 10th floor.
I'm going to the 18th floor.
- Okay.
Wait, why are there two cameras
shooting me?
Am I getting a sudden mission
or something?
Let me see. There are two cameras.
I'm not supposed to be here.
I was supposed to shoot Eun Soo,
but I lost her.
Can't you just shoot me?
Why do you have to be so honest?
Okay, I get it.
Aren't you getting out?
Seriously?
For Clacking Ghost
and Coughing Ghost...
I suspect Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is suspected again.)
Kwang Soo is always suspicious.
I personally think Ri has...
some kind of a role.
Coughing Ghost would cough...
(Haha makes name-based deductions.)
and Clacking Ghost would wear
high heels.
During the opening,
Ri was the only one...
who wore high heels.
How could someone
who majored in dance...
be so bad at dancing?
I am suspicious of So Min.
I am no one.
You are Clacking Ghost.
Complete Clacking Ghost's mission.
He is so immature.
(Suk Jin is a 54-year-old
who loves these pranks.)
Five,
four,
three,
two,
- one.
- Start.
The race has started.
This is scary.
(As it did in the scary story,)
(darkness falls at the TV station.)
Where is the legendary proposal?
This place is really spooky.
It feels as though
a ghost would come out.
Gosh, it's really spooky here.
(This place is spooky as well.)
It's really scary.
I need to look for hints.
(He talks to himself out of fear.)
(The TV station is eerily quiet.)
Gosh, that startled me.
(He got startled
by his reflection in the mirror!)
(I didn't expect to see myself.)
(After surprise comes...)
(embarrassment.)
Please don't film me for a second.
I am sorry.
(I want to be alone.)
Please leave me for a second.
You can go to the restroom
if you want.
(So Min is busy looking for hints.)
I need to find hints. Hints.
Hints.
(She found one!)
I found it.
(The assistant director is
under 40.)
(Suk Jin, Jae Suk, Jong Kook,
and Haha are excluded.)
(According to the hint, one of them
is the assistant director.)
I will look for more.
There should be more.
I think there will be a lot.
Hey.
- Which floor are you going to?
- The first floor.
The first floor? Me too.
Why are you going
to the first floor?
(Well...)
I want to see what's on that floor.
Hey, So Min.
I am on the sixth floor.
Where are you?
I am going to the first floor.
Why?
It just became that way.
Come on. Why are you doing that?
Come to the first floor.
- I have something to tell you.
- So Min, come to the first floor.
(Baritone voice)
(I recognize that voice.)
I am on my way.
I am hanging up!
- Hey.
- I am on my way.
I need to go down.
(Not knowing how Se Chan feels,
she is excited.)
She only changed her mind
because she heard your voice.
- I will help you.
- What do you mean?
You like her, right?
- You think I like So Min.
- That's the case, right?
Of course not.
(Se Chan shyly shakes his head.)
(What would you say
if Se Chan asks you out?)
(I would definitely say yes.)
(What would you say
if So Min asks you out?)
(I would love that.)
(My goodness.)
(What I want
to achieve this year is...)
(true love.)
(So Min, you heard that, right?)
- That's the case, right?
- Of course not.
As a viewer of the show,
I thought,
"Se Chan really likes So Min."
- "As a viewer of the show"?
- Yes.
- Did it seem that way?
(Jinyoung delivers
the wish of the viewers.)
This is insane.
It's like,
"There is something between them."
It's love that can't be.
- Would you please open the door?
- Okay.
Thank you.
I am good at finding things.
(Finding hints seems to be
as hard as love!)
(The competitive Eun Soo
goes through boxes.)
It can't be in the trash can.
(Ri goes through a trash can.)
The thing is,
one popular hiding place
for the hints is...
(He has been in the races
for 9 years.)
the editing room.
(One popular hiding place
for the hints is the editing room!)
(Glancing around)
What? This is the editing room
for Running Man.
(He looks around the room.)
What? There is a camera.
There must be something in here.
What?
The R sticker.
That's right.
(He takes a look at the laptop.)
What? What is this?
(The assistant director is
under 50.)
What is this?
Am I supposed to see this?
- This is a production crew's note.
- Yes.
I see.
It's not a hint.
(He saw a hint by mistake.)
I didn't do it on purpose.
- Who is that?
- Gosh, that startled me.
Hold on. Is that a moving camera?
Kwang Soo?
(Se Chan spots a moving camera.)
(Kwang Soo must be playing a role.)
- I knew it.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- A moving camera.
- This is so frustrating.
- Someone else is entering.
Jae Suk.
- Did you find a hint?
- No.
- Didn't you find a single hint?
- How about you?
- I found one.
- He found one.
Aren't you Sprinkle?
Sprinkle?
Are you Sprinkle, Squeak, or Sullen?
I am no one.
(His very presence is suspicious.)
All right.
The Ghost Radio Booth is open.
Really?
(The Ghost Radio Booth
is on the 11th floor.)
(3 people who won
audience tickets can bring...)
(1 partner each
into the radio booth.)
(Listen to the sound carefully.)
(If the producer, assistant
director, Coughing Ghost,)
(or Clacking Ghost is in the booth,
you'll hear a special sound.)
We need to find
the audience tickets.
The four of us should go and find
We need those tickets
to enter the booth.
Where are the audience tickets?
There are people
who found the audience tickets.
- Really?
- Who are they?
- Kwang Soo, you have been called.
- Me?
- It's understandable.
- You are suspicious.
Go.
What is this?
(Ji Hyo found
a strange envelope earlier.)
No way. It's an audience ticket.
I choose Kwang Soo.
I choose Haha.
I choose So Min.
- Hurry up and line up.
- Jong Kook, stop suspecting me.
- Hurry up.
- I am innocent.
Stop being that way.
Now, who called who?
- I called Haha.
- You called Haha.
- Why did you call Haha?
- We have similar heights.
(We have similar heights.)
He didn't say that earlier.
- No.
- When I asked him why he chose me,
he said,
"You seem like the producer."
But he said that by mistake.
There is no need to find
the producer.
That means, he is either
Coughing Ghost or Clacking Ghost.
I want to protect the producer.
What? You have no power
to protect the producer.
I am the strongest one
next to Jong Kook.
What?
I learned jujitsu.
Do you want a beating?
(Flinching)
He is ridiculous.
Kwang Soo is a fighter.
You know,
- I am pretty strong.
- Jujitsu.
I won't lose easily.
If the producer, assistant director,
Coughing Ghost, or Clacking Ghost...
is in the group,
the appointed sound will play.
If there are 2 or 3 of them,
will we hear multiple sounds?
Yes. If there is only one of them,
you will hear a single sound.
(All the designated sounds
will be played.)
I will protect you. Don't worry.
Let's attack Kwang Soo first.
Let's check
if there are ghosts in this group.
One.
(The people in this group...)
(will change the sounds.)
(Which sounds will they hear?)
Two.
Three.
(Clacking)
- Clacking Ghost is here!
- Clacking Ghost.
(There is Clacking Ghost among us!)
- Clacking Ghost is here?
- Hold on.
Really?
Is that all? Is Clacking Ghost
the only one in this group?
Clacking Ghost was wearing heels
at the time of death...
- Cut.
- What?
- That's the sound for the producer.
- "Cut."
(They hear "Cut.")
- That's the sound for the producer.
- "Cut."
Haha, I will protect you.
- Haha, it's you, right?
- Hold on.
- What?
- It's you.
Both Clacking Ghost and producer
are in this group.
Clacking Ghost is among us?
The producer is among us as well?
Both Clacking Ghost and the producer
are among us.
(Clacking Ghost and the producer
are among the 6 of them.)
- But... Hold on.
- That narrows down the list.
Hold on. Who are the members
of Team New Producer?
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk,
- Eun Soo, Se Chan,
- Jae Suk, Suk Jin...
- and Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
These four aren't ghosts.
They aren't ghosts.
Hold on.
- Either Ri or Jinyoung is...
- Jinyoung.
Coughing Ghost.
(They were neither at the booth
nor in Team New Producer.)
But we don't know
who the assistant director is...
- and who Coughing Ghost is.
- We don't know that.
(Are Ri and Jinyoung Coughing Ghost
and the assistant director?)
If we use the hint
we received earlier...
Who was the hint about?
"The assistant director
and producer..."
"aren't the youngest."
(The assistant director
and producer aren't the youngest.)
(They received the 2nd hint
in Round 2 that got edited out.)
(The assistant director
and producer aren't the youngest.)
(Ri is neither assistant director
nor the producer.)
Then who is Ri?
Ri is Coughing Ghost.
(Ri becomes
the only Coughing Ghost candidate.)
(Is Ri Coughing Ghost
as the members guessed?)
The race will resume.
It's Ri.
(He becomes certain.)
Ri is Coughing Ghost.
(All the hints suggest that
Ri is Coughing Ghost!)
(Everyone is searching for Ri.)
(Meanwhile,
Jae Suk is looking for hints.)
(There should be something here.)
Oh!
(He finds a hint
in the editing room!)
What is this?
(The box contains
a mysterious USB drive.)
It's a USB drive.
(The box contains
a mysterious USB drive.)
(He checks what's inside
using a laptop in the room.)
The USB drive.
It's a hint.
(There's a hint video
in the USB drive.)
(He checks the video in the USB.)
(What Running Man members
must know for tomorrow's shoot)
Even if it's late, did you tell her
about the ghost story?
How could I tell her
when she just joined our show?
Ri.
(Someone approaches Ri.)
I came back from that place.
Did you hear?
Didn't you guys twist
the story too much?
(This is the preview
from last week.)
- Shall we go? Let's go.
- Yes.
(Ghost Story at TV Station:
Legendary Proposal)
What is this?
(He's disappointed by
last week's preview.)
What am I suppose...
(It's continued by
a mysterious video.)
(What's this?)
(Clacking Ghost, "Where did they
hide the proposal?")
(Coughing Ghost, "People call us
ghosts because we wander at night.")
(Can you not wear those shoes?)
(Clacking Ghost, "Go see a doctor
instead of coughing all the time.")
(Search for it
early tomorrow morning.)
(In the video,)
(the two have
a mysterious conversation.)
It's you.
(Tearing)
Right?
(Choi Ri is eliminated by someone.)
Clacking Ghost and
Coughing Ghost are not ghosts.
Right?
No, I'm not.
(Who is Choi Ri?)
(She's not Coughing Ghost.)
"Dalim Man" production crew
member, Choi Ri is eliminated.
- What?
- Choi Ri is eliminated.
- Ri is part of the production crew.
- What?
(Choi Ri is a regular crew member.)
Was she a production crew member?
What? Aren't they human?
(Clacking Ghost and
Coughing Ghost are human.)
(Coughing Ghost, "People call us
ghosts because we wander at night.")
(Some of you were eliminated
unfairly.)
(You were the producer
who's a ghost...)
(and assisting director,
Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost.)
(Is the producer the only ghost?)
Then it's wrong.
There aren't four ghosts.
(Aren't there 4 ghosts?)
(There are no ghosts
on Team New Producer.)
What?
(Team New Producer's 4 members
were completely exempted.)
(Among the producer,
assistant director,)
(Clacking Ghost,
and Coughing Ghost,)
(none of them are ghosts.)
(Does that mean
only the producer is a ghost?)
(So Min figures out that...)
(there aren't four ghosts.)
(If that's the case, Coughing Ghost
or the assistant director...)
(could still be
in Team New Producer.)
It's Coughing Ghost.
- Coughing and Clacking Ghost are...
- It's one of the two.
- Choi Ri is...
- human. Did you know that?
They were human?
There should be a twist like this.
I'm quite shocked
that Ri was eliminated.
If one more gets eliminated,
one of us can...
- become invincible.
- Right.
(If they eliminate two members,
they win a protective shield.)
I bet they aren't here.
(So Min is looking for
another hint.)
Is there such a thing?
(Did she find something?)
(Proposal)
(The legendary proposal is hidden
somewhere in the TV station.)
(The production crew wins
if they put it in the safe.)
(If Coughing or Clacking Ghost
eliminates the producer...)
(or signs the legendary proposal,
they win.)
(She finds a document
that looks like a proposal.)
Jae Suk. Hey!
(So Min gets eliminated by someone
when she finds the document.)
(Sighing)
I don't think this is the proposal.
(What So Min found wasn't
the legendary proposal.)
"Dalim Man" production crew,
So Min is eliminated.
- Is she out?
- She is.
(Someone is getting closer
to getting the protective shield.)
- My goodness.
- Is So Min's name tag torn off?
Hers got torn off.
(They must hurry and find
Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost.)
(Eun Soo is looking for hints.)
(She finds a hint.)
"Clacking Ghost is"...
(Clacking Ghost is blood type A.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo)
("Clacking Ghost is blood type A"?)
(Those with blood type A)
(Only Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo,
and Jong Kook)
I'll go upstairs again.
(Clacking Ghost candidates are
narrowed down to 3 members.)
Who is it?
It's Kwang Soo. Hello?
Are you alone?
(He checks if Se Chan is alone.)
What's wrong? You're scaring me.
- Are you alone?
- Yes, I'm alone.
I can't see anyone.
I've been walking alone.
I'll go to the ninth floor.
- Okay.
- All right, Kwang Soo.
(Alluring Se Chan,
is Kwang Soo Clacking Ghost?)
(Ji Hyo is walking around
the building.)
(She spots Jong Kook.)
(Both of them are
Clacking Ghost candidates.)
(They guard themselves
from one another.)
Go upstairs.
- Where are you going?
- Is it you?
I'm not. Go upstairs.
Are you going to tear off
my name tag when I do?
If that were the case,
I'd do it already.
(Among the 3,
who is Clacking Ghost?)
Wait, there's something here.
(He finds a hint.)
(The producer is blood type A.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo)
(Is the producer blood type A?)
(The producer is
among the 3 of them.)
(Two of them are the producer
and Clacking Ghost.)
- What's wrong?
- What?
Why did you come here?
I said I'd come downstairs.
(Is he pulling up his sleeves?)
(He's ready.)
(What's going on with him?)
Wait.
Why did you come
to the emergency exit?
There are too many people
over there.
Why did you come here?
Didn't you see me come here
from out there?
- I didn't see you.
- Did you just come?
Go upstairs then.
- The elevator isn't here yet.
- When it comes, go upstairs.
Don't pull up your sleeves.
Don't. You're hurting me, Kwang Soo.
(He takes control over him
immediately.)
(As soon as Se Chan falls over...)
(Tearing)
(He tears off Se Chan's name tag.)
(Se Chan is out instantly.)
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
(Is Kwang Soo Clacking Ghost?)
- Go.
- I don't know where it is.
(As soon as she shows her back...)
Ji Hyo.
(He sees his opportunity.)
(Tearing)
(Clacking Ghost and producer
candidate, Ji Hyo is out.)
Ji Hyo.
(Who is Ji Hyo?)
"Dalim Man" production crew
member, Ji Hyo is eliminated.
I'm sorry.
("Dalim Man" production crew
member, Ji Hyo is out.)
(Ji Hyo was a regular crew member.)
- Are you okay? When I grabbed,
- Yes, but what happened?
you were so strong.
- Who are you?
- I had no other solution.
Are you Clacking Ghost?
(Only Kwang Soo and Jong Kook remain
as candidates.)
No, Ji Hyo.
(One is Clacking Ghost,
and the other is the producer.)
Ji Hyo.
(Who are they?)
I can't trust anyone.
"Dalim Man" production crew,
Ji Hyo and Se Chan are out.
- Goodness.
- Wait a minute.
Two of them have
a protective shield.
(Two of them have
a protective shield.)
(They obtain protective shield
after eliminating 2 members.)
- Wait a minute.
- Okay, Jae Suk.
- Everyone was over there.
- In that case...
Wait a minute.
(Two of them have
a protective shield.)
I don't know who the other one is.
(Who's the other one?)
You startled me.
How could you? That makes me sad.
(His cold reaction makes him sad.)
That makes me sad. You saw me.
You startled me.
Who are you?
I'm nothing.
I'm a production crew member.
I saw on TV that...
- No.
- you're the bad guy.
I'm not a bad guy.
No, it's not me.
- Really?
- Yes.
She's out.
(The rest of the members get
more confused.)
Goodness.
- Is Ji Hyo out?
- I knew it wasn't her.
Did hers get torn off?
I can't trust anyone.
I have to find the proposal soon.
(The way to win the game is...)
I have to do it now. I have to.
- Both of them are invincible.
- Let's split and search.
We have to find the proposal soon.
(Jae Suk was looking for
the proposal.)
(He finds a hint.)
"The assistant director is a woman."
(Ji Hyo, So Min, Eun Soo,
and Choi Ri)
(Is the assistant director a woman?)
Eun Soo... Choi Ri is out.
Is it Eun Soo?
Clacking Ghost.
(The assistant director is Eun Soo!)
(Eun Soo is the assistant director
who made the proposal.)
Today is Ghost Story at TV Station:
Legendary Proposal Race.
You're the assistant director.
How will I find the proposal here?
I have to find Clacking Ghost
and Coughing Ghost quickly.
- Eun Soo is the assistant director.
- So Min's out.
- What?
- Eun Soo is the assistant director.
You're Coughing Ghost.
My goodness.
- Suk Jin, you're Coughing Ghost.
- You're Coughing Ghost.
No.
(What is this?)
I wish I were Coughing Ghost,
but I'm not today.
(He's being honest.)
- What?
- I wish I were,
- but I'm not.
- You may get out.
Let's hold a witch trial.
Tear off one person's name tag,
and if he isn't it,
Coughing Ghost will be
someone out of the two left.
Goodness, we must find out
one of them now.
We have to tear
Coughing Ghost's name tag.
Why are you in such a hurry?
- I'm not it.
- You seem at ease.
Are you Coughing Ghost?
I'm neither of them.
What are you doing?
Then Se Chan isn't it either.
(He spots a camera.)
(What is that camera doing here?)
(Everyone relies on
the location of the camera.)
(There must be something here.)
Hold on. What is this?
What is this?
(There is a file folder
with the R sticker.)
(This is incredible!)
This is incredible.
(He opens the file folder
in secret.)
This is incredible.
(This is incredible!)
(However)
(It's not a proposal, but a security
guard's work schedule.)
"A complaint was made
regarding a coughing sound..."
"in the editing room."
July 16.
"A complaint was made
about litter..."
"such as medicine and masks
in front of editing room number 41."
(The owner of editing room number 41
coughs and takes medicine.)
Room number 40, 41, and 42...
are lined up.
Due to the coughing sound
from editing room number 41,
editing rooms number 40 and 42
made complaints.
Inside that room must be
the information.
(Haha heads over
to the editing room.)
- Take me out.
- Take you out?
Hold on.
- Once you take me out,
- Really?
- you will know.
- He can't be Coughing Ghost.
- Then it's Jae Suk.
Then it's Suk Jin.
- I am not it.
Suk Jin isn't...
- Coughing Ghost.
- Why?
- What?
(Kwang Soo is certain that
Suk Jin isn't Coughing Ghost.)
Hold on. What makes you certain?
What makes you certain
he isn't Coughing Ghost?
(Kwang Soo looks torn.)
(Meanwhile, Haha arrives
at the editing rooms.)
Editing rooms 39 and 30.
Room 41.
This is it.
(He arrives at editing room
number 41.)
It said there was litter...
such as medicine and mask
at the editing room number 41.
What makes you certain
he isn't Coughing Ghost?
The assistant director is under 50.
The assistant director is a woman.
- The assistant director is a woman.
- Eun Soo is the assistant director.
(Is Eun Soo the assistant director?)
She is the assistant director.
(He finds a medicine packet
in editing room number 41.)
(He carefully opens
the medicine packet.)
(Cough medicine?)
"Assistant director".
(The patient is
the assistant director?)
(Does the cough medicine belong
to the assistant director?)
(What?)
(Assistant director)
(Does this editing room belong
to the assistant director?)
- Hold on. Don't do anything.
- Aren't you it?
- Aren't you Coughing Ghost?
- No!
- No? Then it's you!
(Suk Jin rips off
Jinyoung's name tag.)
- No.
- What?
He is out.
(Jinyoung is out.
What could be Jinyoung's identity?)
- Isn't he it?
- "Dalim Man"...
He isn't it!
production crew member,
Jinyoung is out.
(Jinyoung isn't it?)
production crew member,
Jinyoung is out.
- Jinyoung.
- I am not Coughing Ghost.
- You are Coughing Ghost.
- Get him.
- I am not Coughing Ghost.
- Hurry up and get him.
- No!
- It's him!
- He is Coughing Ghost.
- I am really not it!
Listen to me!
Listen to me! He isn't it!
- Get him.
- Listen to me!
(Suk Jin gets taken out
in an instant.)
- I ripped it off.
- Listen to me!
- I am not it!
- We got him.
"Dalim Man" production crew member,
Suk Jin is out.
I told you I am not it!
Listen to me!
(Now, Jae Suk is
the only Coughing Ghost candidate.)
This medicine belongs
to the assistant director.
(Both the medicine...)
(and editing room number 41
belong to the assistant director.)
(If the coughs
that continued on all night...)
(belonged
to the assistant director...)
I got chills.
That means...
the assistant director is...
Coughing Ghost.
(The assistant director is
Coughing Ghost.)
I told you!
The assistant director is
Coughing Ghost.
- What?
- What did you say?
The assistant director is
Coughing Ghost?
- You fool!
- Why didn't you say so earlier?
I told you
not to rip off his name tag!
You should have gotten
straight to the point!
Then Eun Soo is Coughing Ghost!
Is Eun Soo both Coughing Ghost
and the assistant director?
(Eun Soo is the assistant director.)
(Her other name is Coughing Ghost.)
I need to find out
who the producer is.
One of them must be the producer.
(Eun Soo, the assistant director
and Coughing Ghost)
Today, we will have...
Ghost Story at TV Station:
Legendary Proposal.
In the story, the assistant director
got eliminated with the producer.
But the assistant director is
Coughing Ghost.
Eun Soo is the assistant director
and Coughing Ghost.
(She became the assistant director
and Coughing Ghost.)
(Eun Soo)
(Coughing Ghost
and the assistant director)
Where are...
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook?
I told you
not to rip off his name tag!
You should have gotten
straight to the point!
If the production crew
doesn't listen to the producer,
(Kwang Soo confesses that
he is the producer.)
what am I supposed to do?
- The producer?
- I am the producer.
- This is driving me crazy.
That fool!
- Seriously. Hold on.
I knew from the start.
- What?
- I knew from the start.
- Then why didn't you...
- I couldn't tell anyone...
because I didn't know who
the ghosts were.
You...
(Angry Jong Kook appears.)
You are the absolute worst.
- You...
- What?
Seriously.
- What is going on?
- You're Clacking Ghost!
(Furious)
You...
You made a joke about
being Squeak all day long.
- He says he is the producer, right?
- Yes.
I will tell the truth now.
I am the producer.
(What? Jong Kook is the producer?)
- What?
- I am the producer.
Listen.
I didn't tell you anything...
- all day long, right?
- Yes.
I am the producer.
He says he is the producer, right?
Why are you the producer?
Start talking.
Why?
Why are you the producer?
I received the mission this morning.
Is that so?
At what time did you arrive?
I received that mission too.
I arrived at 8 a.m... No, 9:30 a.m.
Then you arrived
at the same time as I did.
- Did you arrive at 9:30 a.m.?
- Yes.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I received the mission here.
Jae Suk, you know
he tricks us all the time.
- Gosh.
- I can't believe it.
When I received the mission,
I hoped...
- Jong Kook wouldn't be against me.
- I can't believe it.
Not too long ago,
we washed a car together...
and rebuilt our friendship.
- This is driving me crazy.
- We washed a car together.
Forget about that friendship.
- I can't believe it.
- Forget it.
- We should leave for now.
- We washed a car together.
Where is Eun Soo?
- Eun Soo.
- She needs to be taken out.
(One of them is the producer.)
Whoever the producer is,
I don't want to be in his show.
- Eun Soo needs to be taken out.
- Hey.
- Rip off Eun Soo's name tag.
- I will do that.
I will do it.
I can't believe you.
You...
(Who could be the real producer?)
(Jae Suk searches
for the proposal.)
What?
(He spots Eun Soo, Coughing Ghost
and the assistant director.)
- Jae Suk.
- Eun Soo, where are you going?
I am looking for the proposal.
Did you find the proposal?
No, I need to find it.
Why did you show up only now?
What?
What do you mean?
Eun Soo, I heard that
you are the assistant director.
- I am the assistant director?
- Yes.
- Now...
- Are you suspecting me?
I am not suspecting you.
Your eyes...
(She pretends to be calm.)
The assistant director is
on our side.
That's right.
I am the assistant director.
Is that so?
(She takes the bait.)
I heard that the assistant director
is Coughing Ghost.
- The producer is Coughing Ghost?
- Yes.
How is that possible?
That's what I heard.
Jae Suk!
Rip off her name tag!
- Rip off her name tag!
- Eun Soo!
Rip off Eun Soo's name tag!
Eun Soo is it. Rip off her name tag.
Jae Suk, Clacking Ghost...
Clacking Ghost, Kwang Soo is
on your way. Be careful.
They think I should take you out.
Me? Why would you do that?
- If you take me out...
- Are you Coughing Ghost?
You are scaring me.
- Stop it. Gosh, stop it.
- Hold on.
- Stop it.
- Hold on. I am sorry, but...
Don't be like that.
- So many production crew members...
- No, no.
- Hold on.
- Jae Suk.
I am not it. I am not it.
- I am really not it.
- Eun Soo. Hold on.
(She lies down on the floor.)
(Struggling)
- Rip off her name tag!
- Hold on.
Hold on.
Rip off her name tag!
- Rip off her name tag!
- Hold on.
Hurry up and rip it off.
- Rip it off. Hurry up.
- Eun Soo.
- Hold on.
- See who rips it off, okay?
Hurry up and rip it off.
Hold on.
- Kwang Soo, rip it off.
- Eun Soo.
Gosh, Kwang Soo. You are incredible.
- Rip it off.
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, see his terrible act.
He is acting
when he can clearly tear it off.
- Rip it off.
- Kwang Soo, move out of the way.
- Look at Kwang Soo.
- Rip it off.
- Look at his act.
- Why aren't you ripping it off?
- Jae Suk, look at him.
- Her hair...
- Jae Suk, he is acting.
- Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo,
why aren't you ripping it off?
You know Kwang Soo is good
at ripping off name tags.
- Kwang Soo, rip it off.
- Look at him.
My goodness.
- Jong Kook.
- I can't believe it.
(He easily takes out Eun Soo.)
(Did you rip it off?)
- All right.
- He is acting.
The assistant director
and Coughing Ghost, Eun Soo is out.
- Okay!
- All right.
(Clacking Ghost's ally,
Eun Soo is out.)
- Okay!
- All right.
- What did I tell you?
- Eun Soo, are you okay?
(Eun Soo showed incredible strength.)
- Eun Soo is so strong.
- Seriously.
Eun Soo is strong.
I am about to go crazy.
Why are you about to go crazy?
Eun Soo, please go to the prison.
Eun Soo, take this.
See you later.
Eun Soo...
must have worked out a lot.
- Kwang Soo.
- Eun Soo, I am sorry.
Kwang Soo.
- You are sorry?
- Why didn't you rip it off?
- You aren't sorry.
- Jong Kook.
Jae Suk, it's as clear as day!
How many times
do I need to tell you?
That's why he's putting on a show.
The situation a moment ago...
- Forget it.
- Did you not know?
- I didn't know.
- I'll look for the proposal.
Then who told you?
Why those...
(Let's find the proposal first.)
We'll find it
and put it in the safe.
(If the producer or production crew
put it in the safe, they win.)
But...
Is Running Man this hard?
- What?
- My head is about to explode.
- Isn't it about to explode?
- I wanted to get a cab and go home.
- I don't care about Clacking Ghost.
- I know.
- I don't care.
- Clacking Ghost.
(The situation stresses him out.)
I'm so stressed out.
Look through everything.
(After looking through everything,)
(he enters the director's office
on the 16th floor.)
(Impressed)
"X-Man."
(Posters of shows that
aired 10 years ago...)
(are on the director's wall.)
(Why are these posters
still on here?)
(Is there something behind them?)
(There's something common
among the three posters.)
"Ki Hae Kwan".
(Is the producer for all of them
Ki Hae Kwan?)
How is the producer Ki Hae Kwan?
(Producer Ki Hae Kwan existed
whom Haha never heard of.)
In that case,
is there a videotape? Wait.
"Ki Hae Kwan".
His name is Ki Hae Kwan.
"Running Man"...
(Is it a trophy for
Producer Ki Hae Kwan?)
"Film Festival".
(Producer Ki Hae Kwan's name is
quite unusual.)
(Jae Suk
who eliminated Eun Soo appears.)
- Haha.
- What?
Do you know that
I eliminated the assistant director?
Did you?
Wait, Jae Suk. We don't have time.
- Let's find the proposal.
- First, look at this.
"Producer Ki Hae Kwan".
The producer is Ki Hae Kwan.
The producer wasn't Ki Hae Kwan
at that time.
- Is this the proposal?
- Producer of the Month is him too.
(Producer Ki Hae Kwan
also received an award.)
("Dalim Man" production crew...)
(must find the legendary proposal.)
(They have to put the proposal
in the safe.)
(Producer Ki Hae Kwan sounds
unnatural.)
(The producer's name is
Ki Hae Kwan.)
(He repeats it one more time.)
This is the proposal.
(This is the proposal.)
(Is this the proposal?)
(Find the legendary proposal.)
(Find the legendary Ki Hae Kwan.)
(Legendary proposal is
legendary Producer Ki Hae Kwan.)
(They must put Producer Ki Hae Kwan
in the safe.)
(The producer must put
Producer Ki Hae Kwan in the safe.)
("Dalim Man" production crew lose
if they put in the wrong producer.)
(Producer crew loses if Clacking
Ghost signs on the producer.)
- It's not a proposal.
- Is it a person?
- We must find Producer Ki Hae Kwan.
- It's Ki Hae Kwan.
We have to find the producer.
We have to put
1 of the 2 in the safe.
If you take a look at this...
What if we put in
the wrong proposal?
Is that person eliminated
or is the whole race over?
If the wrong proposal is placed,
it's over.
Is everything over?
We have to be careful
about it as well.
Jong Kook.
Shouldn't you eliminate
other people?
That Clacking Ghost.
(They have no idea that
the proposal is the producer.)
Don't you think Kwang Soo is
the producer?
Is that why Jong Kook held him?
Who?
Kwang Soo.
(As confessed,
is Kwang Soo the producer?)
No, I was almost certain
that Kwang Soo was the producer.
He was hesitant about
tearing Eun Soo's name tag.
(He still can't understand
Kwang Soo's strange squirming.)
(Kwang Soo isn't so bad
at tearing off name tags.)
Does he have another self?
- Goodness.
- Let's lure him to talk.
Shall we listen
and see who speaks more logically?
All Clacking Ghost has to do...
is find the proposal and sign it.
Clacking Ghost doesn't know that
the proposal is a person.
Isn't it over
once he signs on the person?
Yes, he doesn't know.
- Let's go now.
- Let's go.
(They walk disheartened.)
In that case...
That's why
there was a marker in here.
(Truth or Dare starts
for the producer.)
Who is the producer?
Here's what I think.
The atmosphere will tell us,
so let's call them.
(Clacking Ghost and producer)
- Call the two of them?
- Let's listen to them, but...
(Producer Ki Hae Kwan
and Clacking Ghost appear.)
- Three of them are there.
- There they are.
Is there Jae Suk too?
- Wait.
- Kyung Hwan is still alive.
- They're here.
- Jae Suk.
Wait.
Did you find the proposal?
- Do you mean us?
- Did you find...
- What happened?
- the proposal?
Here's why we came downstairs.
The most important is...
Hurry and put it in now.
Put it in the safe.
- Jae Suk.
- Come on.
If you found it, put it in the safe.
Should we reveal the truth?
If we tell them,
he'll sign immediately.
(They can't reveal
Producer Ki Hae Kwan so hastily.)
Right?
Yes, he will sign.
I'll tell you this.
Who said that...
the assistant director is
Coughing Ghost?
- Who said it?
- You did, Kwang Soo.
(The assistant director is
Coughing Ghost.)
(Kwang Soo reveals that Coughing
Ghost is the assistant director.)
(He confessed it
after two people were eliminated.)
Remember what happened...
when we tore Eun Soo's name tag.
Was it impossible
to tear off her name tag?
(Jong Kook took off
Eun Soo's name tag instead.)
(Perhaps Jong Kook tore it later
pretending to be the producer.)
- It's competitive.
- Think about it.
Would you respect our choice?
- Definitely.
- Of course.
We'll make the conclusion.
Then should we...
(They have a fake proposal
as bait for Clacking Ghost.)
Please pass us.
Go on.
- Should we put it in?
- I'll stay out of it.
I'll stay out of it.
Please put it in.
- Are you sure?
- We found it.
(He approaches the safe
pretending to put in the proposal.)
(Jong Kook hurries them
to put it in.)
(Kwang Soo is frozen.)
Put it in now.
I told you before that
if you put in the wrong...
(At that time)
(Jong Kook attacks him.)
- Hey.
- No.
(Kyung Hwan is eliminated
immediately.)
(He attacks Kyung Hwan
when he's about to put it in.)
Hurry, I found it.
(Clacking Ghost is Jong Kook.)
- Where's Kwang Soo?
- I'm not it.
- It's him.
- Go in.
- Go in now.
- No.
- That's not it.
- Wait.
- It's not him.
- Who is it?
(Jae Suk is eliminated.)
- It's not him.
- Who is it?
- Haha, tell him now.
- Wait.
No, get away.
- It's not me.
- Get Jong Kook.
- What?
- Jong Kook.
Catch Jong Kook.
Catch Jong Kook. It's our chance.
- I knew it.
- Who are you?
It's Jong Kook.
It was him.
We have to catch him.
(If Haha tells the truth,
Jong Kook will find out.)
What is it?
- That's not it.
- What?
We have to put Jong Kook in now.
Catch and put Jong Kook in.
- We have to put Jong Kook in.
- We need to put the producer in.
- The producer?
- What?
We have to put the producer in?
What are you talking about?
(He said it by mistake.)
(Jae Suk said it by mistake.)
Wait.
Both of them are out.
(If Jong Kook signs on Kwang Soo,
Coughing and Clacking Ghost win.)
Did you get eliminated?
Both of them are out.
- I told you.
- We have to catch Jong Kook.
Right?
(Producer Ki Hae Kwan rushes
into the safe.)
(The game is over once
the producer goes into the safe.)
(Clacking Ghost tries to stop him.)
(Race is over.)
Producer and "Dalim Man"
production crew win.
(Producer and "Dalim Man"
production crew win.)
(Coughing Ghost
and Clacking Ghost lose.)
- Hey.
- That was close.
- Jong Kook.
- It was a person.
(However, it was a good fight.)
Today's Legendary Proposal Race...
It was unfair, wasn't it?
You're the producer
who was eliminated wrongfully.
Did Clacking and Coughing Ghost
eliminate me out of jealousy?
(He curses.)
(Kwang Soo who died unfairly
decides to take revenge.)
(He eliminates Choi Ri,
a likely Coughing Ghost candidate.)
(As a result,
one more person dies unfairly.)
(He eliminates Se Chan to obtain
a protective shield.)
(You're the producer?
You didn't have to kick my stomach.)
(This was an action movie.)
(Was I the leading actor?)
(No, I was the leading actor.)
(You're just an extra, Se Chan.)
Jong Kook, you're Clacking Ghost.
(Today's Clacking Ghost
and Coughing Ghost)
(Jong Kook desperately needed
the protective shield.)
(He uses easy So Min
as a sacrifice.)
You're Clacking Ghost.
(Aren't you Clacking Ghost?)
(He eliminates a member easily.)
(He acts with Kwang Soo
until the end.)
Why you...
- It's just the two of us.
- Did they all go up?
Did they go up?
Even if I die,
I won't let you succeed.
Are you Coughing Ghost?
Why would I be?
I'm Clacking Ghost.
Are you the producer?
(The producer and Clacking Ghost
start a war of nerves.)
The final winner of
the Legendary Proposal Race is...
the producer and "Dalim Man"
production crew.
(The producer and the "Dalim Man"
production crew win.)
(The production crew
turned the tables.)
- Good job, Kwang Soo.
- Good job.
(Ki Hae Kwan feels proud.)
(Coughing Ghost is still regretful.)
I saw everything.
It gave me goosebumps.
(Clacking Ghost was
difficult to crack.)
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
One.
Two.
Three.
(They're atoned with
a whipped cream explosion.)
(From wavy dance to whipped cream,
Eun Soo's day was eventful.)
It's mousse.
- Thank you, everyone.
- Thank you.
(We thank Seo Eun Soo, Choi Ri,
Heo Kyung Hwan, and Jinyoung.)
(Humans are thought to have
four types of emotions.)
(Joy)
(Anger)
(Sadness)
(And)
(Fun)
(However,)
(all the happiness and pleasures
in the living world are halted now.)
Please give me some more time!
(They have a limited number
of chances.)
(Is there a chance
to redeem their evil lives?)
(They must repent
of doubting and framing others,)
(come together,
and have a unanimous decision.)
(They must come up with a unanimous
decision for a filling meal.)
(Will all 8 of them come up
with a unanimous decision?)
(A fatal mistake)
(And the collapse
the mistake has brought upon)
(Can these 8 deceased members
shake off the temptation?)
Should I do a good deed?
(Along with Distrust)