- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
It's Seok Jin's birthday.
- His fans sent us a coffee truck. - Coffee truck.
That's why we're having this.
Goodness, how long has it been?
I think this is the first time his fans sent something to him...
- for the first time. - Really?
I would be grateful if his fans sent this for this,
- but if he personally paid this... - Out of his own pocket.
(This is reasonable doubt.)
People did talk about that a lot.
A lot of our staff members talked about the possibility.
- The lady who's serving coffee... - Did you all have a cup of coffee?
looked very similar to Seok Jin.
Did you all have a cup of coffee?
(The man in question shows up at that time.)
- Right now... - What are you talking about now?
- We were saying that the lady... - Okay.
- served us coffee resembled you. - No.
- She could be your relative. - This is my first time seeing her.
- Listen. - Hello.
- You startled me! - My gosh.
(All of a sudden, a dark shadow enters.)
(Who are you?)
- You startled me. - What is this?
What was that, Haha?
- We're filming a show. Go away. - Haha.
- You really scared me. - That was scary.
I can't look Haha in the eyes today. He looks too scary.
- He's a suspect. - He's a suspect.
Is it a criminal?
- This is too much. - Look at his pants.
Take off this hat!
(The national host educates him about fashion.)
(He indeed sets an example for others.)
- Take it off. What is this? - Wait.
(Throwing away)
What is this?
(His outfits are getting more abstruse.)
What's going on with you lately? Have you gone mad?
Hey, Young Jin, come here.
- You said I looked cool! - What is this?
What is this nonsense?
- I've been too lenient on you. - Seriously.
Why are you wearing these kinds of outfits?
Before I tell you the rules of today's race,
I will announce the teams you have chosen yourselves first.
- We chose our own teams? When? - We didn't choose any teams.
Do you remember the order of which you walked in here today?
When we just walked in?
- Jae Seok was 1st. So Min, 2nd. - Yes, I was 1st.
Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Haha,
- Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo. - Okay.
1, 2, 3, and 4 make a team.
5, 6, 7, and 8 make a team.
- No way. - We won.
- This will be an easy win. - It will be easy.
My team is too weak.
- We'll go against them? - My goodness.
- Don't you think it's not fair? - Let us battle each other.
This isn't fair.
- We'll go against each other here. - That would be a fair game.
Today, you must cut your opponent's wire...
for the bomb one by one.
You will win when your opponent's bomb goes off.
The race is called the Bomb Is About to Explode.
"The Bomb Is About to Explode"?
Five wires of different colors are connected to the bomb.
If you cut one of these wires...
(There are 5 wires, and 1 of the wires sets off a bomb.)
- The bomb will go off. - What?
However, in order to cut the wires,
you must carry out a special mission.
What's the mission?
The Korea Tourism Organization ranked...
30 unique Korean dishes that foreigners want to try. uni
We selected 10 dishes out of those and ranked them in order.
You must choose one dish...
and eat one person's serving.
(They will choose 1 dish and eat 1 person's serving.)
However, you must find the dish cheaper than your opponent's.
(They must find a lower price.)
- We have to find a good restaurant. - That's the point.
- We must find inexpensive places. - Cheap food.
When you accomplish your mission,
you can cut your opponent's wires.
When your opponent's bomb goes off,
the race will be over right away.
- Are you serious? - Really?
Gosh, this will be hard.
However, you have hope.
Each team will have one chance card...
to use when you complete your missions.
There are chance cards.
(Discount Card, Lowest Price Card, Changing Dish Card, Rip-off Card)
On top of those cards, each team will have...
- 1 Penalty Exemption Card. - Is that for only 1 person?
(Each team gets 1 Penalty Exemption Card.)
- Someone will be exempted. - Is that for only one person?
Gosh, it's going to get messy here. People in my team will go crazy.
We must end it for good.
As for this, the order is very important.
It's very important which team eats first.
We'll have a simple match...
to decide which team will go first.
Among these 30 eggs,
there is only one raw egg.
- Let's see what will happen. - My gosh.
Each team will take turns. And one member can crack...
up to three eggs.
The team that picks the raw egg will lose.
- Which team should go first? - What should we do?
(Approaching)
- Okay. - He's so scary.
- He must go first. - The suspect is here.
- Do I have to crack it on myself? - That's right.
- Of course. Take off your hat. - We'll blur you out.
We'll blur you out.
(Choosing carefully)
- There's only 1. - There's only 1.
(There is only 1 raw egg among 30 eggs.)
(Haha carefully chose an egg in the center.)
Go, go, go.
There's only one, but he's going to get the raw egg?
This is like 31 Game. Do you know about that game?
I picked one from the center.
Go ahead. 1, 2.
(What's the egg Haha chose?)
(It's a boiled egg.)
- There you go! - Yes.
(Where are you running off to?)
- Crack 1 more. - I'll crack 2.
- That one is not it. - I'm nervous.
Okay.
- Darn it. - He's going to crack one more?
(With the momentum going, he cracks 3 eggs in a row.)
- Excellent! - Okay.
(Haha successfully cracks 3 eggs.)
- It won't make it back to me. - This can't be.
- I'm in trouble. - This can't be.
- We're in trouble. - Kwang Soo.
You should only crack one.
Don't get the raw egg. Please. It's the New Year.
You should crack only one since we're worried about you.
- Crack only 1 egg. - Crack just 1.
Just crack one egg.
Usually, Kwang Soo gets it.
(He has the worst luck when it comes to random draws.)
(The moment his hands touch it, a miracle occurs.)
(This unlucky guy has a knack for picking out raw eggs.)
(Will his back luck continue today?)
(Is that the raw egg?)
(Or is it a boiled egg?)
- Okay. - Okay.
(It's a boiled egg.)
(He successfully dodges the raw egg.)
- Just end it there. - Come on, Kwang Soo.
You should go for three in the beginning.
Come on. Go for three eggs.
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - Hey, Se Chan.
- You should go for it. - Kwang Soo, don't do it.
You ought to go for it.
(You'll do one more?)
Please, no!
(No way!)
(Kwang Soo gets the raw egg out of 30 boiled ones.)
What is this?
- What is this? - Did this really happen?
No!
I can't believe this.
This is why people think our show is scripted.
(This is the miraculous moment Kwang Soo has created.)
(When others urged him to do more, he picked up the second one.)
(He gets the raw egg without fail.)
I told you to crack only one egg.
This is crazy. Why do you do this?
This is unbelievable.
You're something else.
All right. Team Jong Kook will set out first.
- Okay! - Okay!
- Let's go! Nevis! - They're going first again.
Do we get to choose the dish?
Jong Kook, it might be hard...
- to find the food in first place. - You're right.
- We should pick one in the middle. - Something unique.
Otherwise, it might be hard to find.
- 10th place? - We'll win...
- no matter what. - Let's go with the 10th place.
1, 2, 3.
(What's the dish Team Jong Kook has chosen?)
(Pyeongyang naengmyeon)
(They chose Pyeongyang naengmyeon!)
- It's Pyeongyang naengmyeon! - Yes!
(At your first bite, it tastes bland and plain.)
(The more you eat it, the more it captivates you.)
Team Jong Kook, you can set out to find the dish...
- in the price range you want. - Yes!
Team Jae Seok will wait first.
After the first price has been decided,
- you'll set out then. - Let's eat the tastiest one.
- What is this mess? - Kwang Soo.
Why did you risk the game like that?
(An unlucky guy is scolding another unlucky guy.)
- He's getting scolded. - It would've been you if not me.
- Let's go. - We're going to go.
- Let's go. - Let's get going.
- How did that happen, seriously? - Exactly.
Jong Kook, how much do you want to pay for naengmyeon?
- The basic price for that is... - Pyeongyang naengmyeon...
- It costs more than 10 dollars. - Yes, there's a fixed basic price.
Hold on, but still.
I'm sure there's a place with reasonable prices.
Is there? Try to find one.
I found Pyeongyang naengmyeon with a reasonable price.
- The price is... - Is that what the review says?
Yes. It's only 9 dollars and 50 cents.
- See? It's Pyeongyang naengmyeon. - How much?
9 dollars and 50 cents?
- That's not bad. - Hey, hey.
This place is cheaper than other places...
- by 1 dollar and 50 cents. - It's 1.5 dollars cheaper.
- Are you okay with this place? - I like it.
- Okay, good find. - That's a very reasonable price.
Things are smooth with our team.
Okay. Let's go even if we lose.
By the way, the other team might be thrown off.
Usually, that dish costs about 12 to 13 dollars.
That's right. It usually costs that much.
Only a few cents will determine...
- the winning team of today's match. - Exactly.
On a TV show, I ate...
- a lot of Pyeongyang naengmyeon. - Right.
My goodness, the flavors were so varied.
There wasn't a restaurant that had the same flavors.
(He's Pyeongyang naengmyeon expert.)
Which restaurant was the tastiest one out of the dishes you tried?
Look over there now.
- It's their time now. - Okay.
(It's time for them to hold hands.)
(They clump Jong Kook and Ji Hyo together.)
It's their conversation.
She was just asking a good Pyeongyang naengmyeon restaurant.
Why is that important?
- This could've happened. Ask me. - Hey.
Where did you have the best Pyeongyang naengmyeon?
The place I had it with you.
(The place I had it with you)
Nice line!
- Yes, what a nice line. - Nice!
Stop it, guys.
- Let's take it slow for now. - Yes, let's take our time.
- "Stop it, guys." - Let's take it slow.
We won't overdo it.
- It's because our team is the best. - Right, right.
- Everything is so smooth. - Yes.
It's just that we're boring.
Here it is. Okay.
- We can go in there? - Yes.
- Yes, yes. Come in. - Let's go.
(Since they didn't reserve the restaurant, )
(they're not sure if they can film the show or not.)
Shouldn't we inform them first? Wait here.
Should we inform them first?
Could we film the show at the corner?
(Will the owner give them permission?)
- Yes, yes. - We won't film other customers.
- Thank you. - Let's go to the end.
All the way to the end.
(Thank you for your cooperation.)
There's a table at the corner.
There's one at the corner.
(They just need to eat Pyeongyang naengmyeon now.)
It's the lunch rush.
You have arrived at the restaurant now.
As we informed you earlier,
you can only eat one serving at each restaurant.
You can only eat one serving at each restaurant.
- We can order only one serving? - Yes.
- We get to eat one serving, right? - For the whole group?
- No, it's for all of you. - It's for all of us.
- That won't be enough. - That won't be enough.
We'll finish the dish with one bite.
Then let's order a large one.
Then we have to pay more for that.
(Besides, it's 50 cents more expensive than their research.)
- We can order extra noodles. - That costs one more dollar.
- Yes, we can order extra noodles. - Yes, let's get extra noodles.
(And they'll order extra noodles on top of that?)
We should...
- order that. - Yes.
Other restaurants charge 12 to 13 dollars for this dish.
- Yes. - That's still 11 dollars.
- This is our first dish. - Yes.
Paying 10 dollars for this dish is already cheap.
- An extra dollar won't matter. - Right.
- The one with extra noodles. - Extra noodles, please.
- Give us a lot of noodles, please. - Yes.
- We'll get the 11-dollar dish. - We'll get the 11-dollar dish.
- Just one dish, please. - With broth?
- Yes. - Yes.
The price of Pyeongyang naengmyeon is...
11 dollars.
- That's not bad. - That's right.
- This is good. - I told you, didn't I?
You must also set out now.
Please choose a dish that you will pay less than 11 dollars.
Jae Seok, what about the second place?
Actually, there might be cheaper dishes...
- in higher places. - Is that so?
Yes, price-wise, it might be.
All right. Be quiet.
(All right. Be quiet.)
(You want me to be quiet?)
What? I've been quiet the whole time.
- I think what I just said was... - I'm sorry to say this.
- very important. - I'm sorry to say this.
Why are you managing our members like that?
- Why? - "Members".
- Why are you doing that? - Listen. Jae Seok...
pretends he's the team leader when he's with us.
- He thinks he's the king. - Wait.
- Who's the team leader here? - He thinks he's the king.
All right.
Listen up.
Given the members here...
(Bursting with laughter)
Listen. I'm the oldest here.
- I'm the oldest here. - Yes, you are.
but you debuted later than I did.
(Candidate 2, the weakling, Jae Seok)
- I... - I can't believe this.
Hey, I was born before you.
- I was born before you. - I...
- Listen. - How old is your son?
(Asking a question all of a sudden)
(That was sudden.)
- What did you say? - How old is your son?
My son is 10 years old.
My son is 17 years old.
(Seok Jin's son is 17 years old.)
- How dare you? - They're going to use that too?
- What are you doing? - My son...
- Goodness. - What are you doing?
How many kids do you have?
- I have only 1. - I have 2.
- Come on! - He won.
(That was a game changer.)
(Jae Seok is the team leader for having more kids.)
This is so annoying!
- Let's stop here. Let's stop. - This is so annoying!
His second child can't even talk now.
Then...
why don't you choose, So Min?
I think second place might be good too.
- I'd go with 4th place. - 4th place?
How about 8th place?
- What? - Eighth place.
(Booing)
- Stop it! Stop it! - Stop it! Stop it!
(Criticizing Seok Jin)
Okay. 7th place. It's lucky 7.
- "Lucky"? - My goodness.
- Stop it! Stop it! - Stop it! Stop it!
(Going against Seok Jin for no reason)
Unbelievable. Okay.
I'm number three.
- Quit! Quit! - Hey.
(Rejecting him since it's funny)
(Seok Jin explodes.)
Okay. Seok Jin chose...
third place. Let's go with that.
- 3rd place? - 3rd place.
1, 2, 3.
(3rd place of unique Korean food foreigners want to try)
(What's the dish in the upper rankings?)
(Fermented skate)
Fermented...
(A heavy sigh)
See? I told you.
I can't eat that because my nose is sensitive.
- I can't eat fermented skate. - I can't eat that.
(I can't eat that either.)
Hey.
How could you choose fermented skate...
- out of everything? - I can't eat that.
And that's expensive too.
- It's expensive. - It's really expensive.
- We can't buy it for 11 dollars. - It's expensive.
That's a luxurious dish.
(The high price and its unique smell are the barriers to enjoy the dish.)
(It's a rare invigorating nutritious dish with addicting flavors.)
By the way, you haven't had fermented skate before?
I've never had it before.
You've never had it either, So Min?
This is terrible.
We all have to eat it, right?
- You can eat it, right? - I can.
I can eat it.
- That's a lie. - I can.
- Of course, I can. - Just eat the skate itself.
Actually, we don't have money to buy other side dishes for skate.
(Actually, we don't have money to buy other side dishes for skate.)
That's true.
- We can only order the skate. - That's right.
- We can only order that. - We must find a cheap place.
Are we close to Yangjae-dong from here?
- Yes, we're close. - I found...
- a skate restaurant here. - Tell me.
- We must check the price. - The price?
(They must eat the skate under 11 dollars.)
The braised skate is 80 dollars for 5 people.
(The braised skate is 80 dollars.)
- It's 50 dollars for 2 servings. - It's that expensive?
Of course, it's expensive I told you it's a luxurious dish.
- This is a rare dish. - What else?
The fermented skate ramyeon is 10 dollars for 1 person.
(Eureka!)
- There's fermented skate ramyeon? - Fermented skate ramyeon.
- Fermented skate ramyeon? - Is that acceptable?
- If it has skate in it, it is. - Fermented skate ramyeon...
I think I can eat it if it's in ramyeon.
- It's in Yangjae-dong? - Yes.
Let's go there.
Let's go with fermented skate ramyeon.
We have no choice. That's the perfect price for us.
- It's only a dollar difference. - Let's go!
The fermented skate is so expensive.
(Team Jae Seok sets out to the restaurant.)
By the end of February, winter will be over, right?
- It will be warm in March, right? - It will be cold until March.
- Until March? - It will be cold...
until March.
Why are we going far?
You could've found a closer restaurant, So Min.
Why did you get a place so far away?
(Seok Jin ruins the friendly atmosphere.)
- Listen. - It's not that.
- We must pay less than 11 dollars. - The youngest...
The youngest has to be considerate.
There were other restaurants nearby.
- Those didn't serve the ramyeon. - If we had only the skate...
Should I look for one?
(Should I look for a fermented skate ramyeon restaurant nearby?)
- Go ahead. What if you don't? - What if I find one?
- What if there's one nearby? - What if there isn't?
If you can't find it, get a finger flick on your nose.
- Finger flick on the nose. - Get a finger flick.
- Okay. I got it. - It's a finger flick on the nose.
(Looking up cheap skate restaurants nearby)
"Fermented skate ramyeon".
"Naju"?
(That's at least 300km away.)
Naju?
How is it in Naju?
"Eurwang-ri".
Eurwang-ri?
- It can't be closer than Yangjae. - Right.
Let me call them.
If they have fermented skate ramyeon...
(I found a fermented skate ramyeon restaurant.)
- Is it a bossam restaurant? - It's in Bangbae-dong.
(It's closer than Yangjae.)
Hello, this is bossam restaurant.
Do you sell fermented skate ramyeon?
(His nose depends on the answer.)
Yes, we have fermented skate with pork and kimchi.
I mean fermented skate ramyeon.
Fermented skate ramyeon?
(She's never heard of it.)
- You don't have it? - We have seafood ramyeon.
We don't have fermented skate ramyeon.
Okay, thank you.
I never heard of it, sir.
(Seok Jin's nose will get hit.)
Okay, I'm sorry.
(Hanging up)
She never heard of it.
- She was upset. - She was quite angry.
You bothered her when she was busy.
- She thought he was joking. - There's no skate ramyeon.
Fermented skate ramyeon must be uncommon.
- Wait a minute. - Seok Jin.
- We'll hit you at the restaurant. - It will be a nose flick.
Let's go first.
I didn't know fermented skate ramyeon was so uncommon.
There isn't any. I never saw fermented skate ramyeon.
- I'm surprised there is any. - Here it is.
- We're here. - Here it is.
- It must be famous here. - Is this the restaurant?
It's famous. Let's get out.
- Fermented skate ramyeon? - I smell fermented skate.
Shall we go?
This is it. Hello.
This is the smell of fermented skate.
- Hello. - Hello.
There's a mild smell of fermented skate.
Ma'am?
We can only order one portion because we're shooting.
- I'm sorry. - Is there fermented skate ramyeon?
- Ramyeon. - We have fermented skate ramyeon.
We only serve ramyeon to those who order fermented skate.
(There's a condition to the order.)
- Is that so? - Goodness.
(You must order fermented skate to eat fermented skate ramyeon.)
You can only order it as an addition.
(It was on the menu.)
(So they traveled far.)
(Will they fail their lowest cost mission?)
However, I'll serve it to you.
Thank you.
(She serves fermented skate ramyeon especially to them.)
How much is it?
It's 10 dollars per person.
- 10 dollars? - Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It isn't the main menu.
- Right. - It's because...
It's an additional dish.
- It's an additional order. - Let's penalize Seok Jin first.
Let's hit his nose.
- The nose flick. - No way. What are you doing?
- I'll do it on behalf of everyone. - No.
I delegate the task to you.
So Min delegated it to me. Let me hit you once.
The restaurant owner on the phone was...
- very angry. - Right.
She might track your number.
She thought that you were talking nonsense.
It doesn't hurt.
Face sideways.
(He's about to hit Seok Jin's nose.)
(Flicking)
(Screaming)
It must hurt.
- That was the worst. - It sounded like something popped.
(So Min gets even with him.)
(The pain gets worse for Seok Jin.)
It sounded like something popped.
It sounded like a deflated balloon.
His nose dangled.
Are you okay?
His nose moved back and forth about three times.
It really hurts.
His nose vibrated like a punching bag.
I never got hit like this before.
- Is it your first time? - Yes.
This will be our penalty for today.
Okay.
We can only order one?
I thought it meant one portion for each.
- Me too. - Seriously.
It's unfortunate.
Shall we play a game and decide one person who doesn't eat?
- Haha. - One person doesn't eat?
- Two people shouldn't eat. - Shall we exclude two?
- Yes, exclude two people. - That sounds good.
- Okay. - How about this?
Let's compete in teams.
How about based on where we're sitting?
(Haha and Se Chan versus Jong Kook and Ji Hyo)
Be quiet. There are many people.
Come on.
Hold hands, hold hands.
Let's exclude two people from eating.
- Let's do it. - I don't care.
All right.
(How will they pick two people?)
Let's pick a color.
Ask the restaurant owner to pick two colors.
- Shall we? - Okay.
There are five colors.
- Pick any except black. - Except black.
- I pick green. - Green?
I pick white.
- I pick red. - I'll pick blue.
Are the chosen colors excluded or will they get to eat?
They'll be excluded since it's a bomb.
- Mine is green. - Okay.
- The food is here. - Here it is.
(Pyeongyang naengmyeon is served.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Look at the quality.
There are a lot of noodles.
It'll be enough for two people.
Two people will get to eat.
Gosh, look at the quality.
Sir?
(Pyeongyang naengmyeon tastes addicting.)
Since you're here,
there's no other reason.
Do you see these four colors?
Among green, red, white, and blue,
- could you pick 2? - Please pick 2.
Pick one first.
(Pyeongyang naengmyeon depends on his choice.)
(Which color will he choose?)
(The restaurant owner's first pick)
White.
What else?
What else? One more.
Green.
(He picks Haha's color green.)
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Wait.
(Haha and Se Chan who proposed the game get eliminated.)
(Ace and Champion get selected as usual.)
Goodness.
How could I be excluded?
(It's our fault that we played a game with them.)
It's convenient for us to share.
This is creepy.
- We'll try. - We'll try some.
(He wets the noodles in cold broth.)
(He slurps noodles with some broth.)
It's driving me crazy.
(Jong Kook takes a bite.)
You should eat broth right away.
(Ji Hyo takes a bite.)
How are the noodles?
You should eat them when they're still wet with broth.
Dip them in the broth. It's good.
Dip them in?
It's great to see you share a bowl together.
(He keeps teasing them.)
(It only makes him laugh.)
It's nice to see them eat noodles together.
Are you done?
It was delicious.
Everyone, you finished one portion of Pyeongyang naengmyeon.
You may explode the opposing team's bomb.
- Goodness. - Let's do it.
- Red. - Red.
- Yellow. - Yellow.
(If the opposing team's bomb explodes, )
(today's race is over.)
(With one attack, )
(they could explode the opposing team's bomb.)
Is it over if their bomb explodes?
- Yes. - It's over.
(The success rate is 20 percent.)
- We're in trouble. - We're in trouble.
Shall we try to explode the bomb?
(Which colored wire will they pick?)
- The restaurant owner had... - He chose well.
- good intuitions. - He's intuitive.
Let's ask him again.
Sir, last time...
we asked you to pick two colors.
- You picked two colors. - Yes.
Like last time, there's no pressure.
Could you pick one color?
- Just one. - Yes.
Could you pick one?
(His choice could explode Team Jae Seok's bomb.)
(Team Jong Kook tries to explode Team Jae Seok's bomb.)
Just pick one? Okay.
(Which will he choose?)
- White. - White?
(Based on his intuition, )
(Team Jong Kook chooses the white wire.)
(Team Jae Seok must cut the white wire.)
Cut the white wire.
You cut it.
- So Min, you cut it. - Me?
You cut it, So Min.
- Shouldn't he cut it? - I'm scared.
Gosh, I'm scared.
(Is the white wire connected to the bomb?)
- Goodness. - Go.
- Please. - So Min.
Grab it like this.
(As soon as the bomb explodes, the race is over.)
- Use both hands. - I'm nervous.
(Snapping)
- It's okay. - I knew it.
(Team Jong Kook's attack fails.)
What is it that makes me so nervous?
It makes me very nervous.
Right. It's too early to explode.
- It's too early. - Right.
Right.
You failed to explode their bomb.
You'll choose your next menu.
(Pyeongyang naengmyeon and fermented skate are chosen.)
Third was fermented skate.
We picked the on with lower ranks.
- One of these? - Let's choose one of them.
Since we picked the bottom, how about the sixth?
Shall we pick the sixth place?
- Sixth place sounds good. - That sounds good.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Which Korean food ranked 6th that foreigners want to try?)
Jokbal?
(6th place is jokbal.)
(Dark meat that's shiny and moist)
(A combination of skin, fat, and meat that spreads in the mouth)
Isn't this quite expensive?
- Really? - Jokbal is quite expensive.
(Team Jae Seok won 10 dollars.)
Search for jokbal restaurants.
(It has to be lower than 10 dollars.)
- It's 28 dollars. - It's 22 dollars.
10 dollars.
- Is there a 10-dollar one? - Wait.
Jokbal is expensive.
(Team Jong Kook is at risk.)
Jokbal? Wait a minute.
(Can they find jokbal that costs less than 10 dollars?)
All right.
Everyone, you found a fermented skate dish...
for 10 dollars.
- Do you remember the rules? - Pardon?
One of you have...
- a Penalty Exemption Card. - Right.
- You can be exempted... - Even if you lose.
- from a penalty even if you lose. - Right.
How can we gain it?
The person who has it...
at the last moment...
- will be exempted. - I'll hold it.
(Everyone gets defensive.)
The person who has it should decide.
- Put it down. - For now.
- Put it down. - Don't touch it.
We should choose the person who will keep it.
- The one who will keep it? - Yes.
When fermented skate ramyeon is served,
- we'll have some. - Okay.
Anyone who can't eat it,
or anyone who makes a face after eating fermented skate.
It's very delicious.
- Okay. - It really is.
Those people will be eliminated.
You must enjoy it like you're on a commercial.
- For example... - You can't make a face.
You can't make a face. You must smile.
I wonder how fermented skate ramyeon will taste.
- I have no idea at all. - Right.
- I have no idea. - You never tried it.
- It's my first time. - Okay.
I might be at an advantage.
- I wonder. - I can imagine that it's tasty...
- as it's my first time eating it. - Okay, that sounds good.
- It's coming. - There's kimchi.
(Fermented skate ramyeon is served.)
It looks good.
- Gosh. - Rice cakes and mushrooms.
- It looks like... - There's a lot inside.
Is this the smell of fermented skate?
(It looks like regular ramyeon.)
(It's full of fermented skate that tastes stronger as it's cooked.)
(It looks like...)
(That's...)
(She can't finish her sentence.)
Is this it?
(He puts his hand on his nose.)
It starts now.
What do you mean it starts now?
- It started. - Fermented skate is cooked.
It's served cooked.
Of course it's cooked when it's served in ramyeon.
It wouldn't be served raw.
I never thought of cooking fermented skate.
Have a piece.
I'll try fermented skate.
Take one piece of it. Try it.
(She's more nervous than when she cut the bomb wire.)
(Sniffing)
No.
(The smell brings back memories.)
No, that's not it.
- Didn't you make a face? - I didn't.
- Really? - I was short on breath.
- Any minor changes count. - Let's start.
- Take it. - Start.
(He hesitates as he tries to eat it.)
- Gosh. - It's a little...
The smell is already strong.
You must eat it in five seconds.
Try some broth and fermented skate.
Any minor changes or if you don't eat it in five seconds.
5, 4, 3,
- Two. - He ate it.
(His lips are attached to the plate.)
It's strange.
- Goodness. - You have to finish it.
You must eat it in five seconds.
(It's a festival of fermented skate.)
- It smells so strong. - It's very strong.
(The traces of the festival remain.)
He's eliminated.
- Why? - Seok Jin is eliminated.
(He moaned while eating.)
Seok Jin is eliminated.
- He can't eat it. - Seok Jin is eliminated.
Right.
(No one can eat it calmly.)
- Seok Jin. - No one can eat it calmly.
(The smell is very strong without eating it.)
- It's strong when it's cooked. - Seok Jin.
I'm serious.
- Jae Seok is crying. - I can't believe it.
Seok Jin is eliminated.
- You know what? - It must be very strong.
Is there any water?
- I'm sorry. - You can't drink it.
- That's not polite. - You can't drink water.
- Ma'am, please give me some water. - She served the food.
She already did what wasn't possible.
She made it specially for us.
- It's a precious dish. - May I get some water?
- It's not allowed. - Please.
I need water.
You know what?
(He takes quite a lot.)
- This is not easy. - I like ramyeon.
- And? - Also...
I spent my adolescence with fermented skate.
What?
("Yu Jae Seok Spent His Adolescence with Fermented Skate.")
- What? - How?
I had it for the first time at my cousin's wedding.
I became a fan of fermented skate as I couldn't forget its taste.
I have been its fan.
Wait, your nose is running. It must smell strong.
(Are you really a fan of fermented skate?)
He's crying already.
All right. Let's see.
I like fermented skate very much.
It starts now.
(He hesitates.)
I'm smiling because I haven't had it in a while.
My mouth is watering.
Do you know what his expression means?
It's when he's dumbfounded.
My mouth is already watering.
There are many who can't eat fermented skate,
but I like it very much.
Is that so?
(He eats it in one bite.)
(He slurps in the noodles like a noodle fan.)
(It's about time that he reacted.)
Let's watch him until he swallows it.
(He shows a big smile.)
He'll react soon.
He's lying. It's still in his cheeks.
- It's still in his cheeks. - Really?
In his cheeks.
(He's very moved.)
This is what it tastes like.
(Impressed)
(This is what it tastes like.)
This is what it tastes like.
(Surprised)
- Gosh. - Jae Seok.
When he made that sound...
It's like he punched me in the nose.
This is what it tastes like.
It's interesting.
When it's cooked with ramyeon,
- fermented skate tastes piquant. - Does it taste strong?
- It still tastes strong. - Is it piquant?
Next is So Min.
They make it well.
- Here you go. - That's a big piece.
- It's big. - It's too big.
Yours wasn't this big, Jae Seok.
- I know. - This is good.
If So Min endures it, she'll be eligible too.
Yes, all right.
(So Min's laughter is mysterious.)
Try some with ramyeon.
When it's cooked with ramyeon...
I shouldn't have smelled it.
(The smell is strong.)
(It's the first time a smell makes her laugh.)
Isn't it strong?
(Will she give up?)
- It's strong. - You must eat it in five seconds.
I'm in trouble. I can't eat fermented skate.
5, 4.
(She tries it.)
Start.
(Noodles taste like fermented skate.)
The fermented skate is at the bottom.
- It's at the bottom. - She's doing well.
Try the fermented skate.
Eat fermented skate and eat the broth.
(No minor changes are allowed to win Penalty Exemption Card.)
- Is it delicious? - Keep eating it.
(The taste is released.)
Is this it?
(It's been hiding for a long time.)
(Her wrinkles start to form.)
(She stays calm.)
- Let's see. - I think she made a face.
All right.
What's going on? What was that face?
What's wrong with your eyes?
Her whole face is twisting.
(There was a second risky moment.)
- I think she succeeded. - Once you eat that much,
- you can finish it. - Seriously.
So Min passed. Next is Kwang Soo.
- She did a good job. - Come close.
I don't know anything about fermented skate.
This must be your first time.
- The ignorant are brave. - Right.
I can imagine that it's delicious.
- It makes you laugh. - Try it.
- My nostrils opened up. - Mine too.
- Is this your first time eating it? - Right.
Kwang Soo never had fermented skate before.
There are many who never had...
- fermented skate. - Right.
- It's spicy. - Eat it as is.
Don't smell it and just eat it.
- Eat it right away. - Don't hesitate.
Eat it directly.
What did I just smell?
(But what did I just smell?)
What was it?
- Is this fermented skate? - Yes.
- It's how it smells. - Kwang Soo.
- It's interesting. - Do you still taste it?
I never knew that ramyeon would taste like this.
- Okay, I can eat it. - Of course.
There are people who like it.
- People who like it would enjoy it. - Right.
- I'll eat it in one go. - Blood will circulate in your body.
5, 4, 3.
That's right.
(He should feel it by now.)
- Kwang Soo... - You need to chew it.
never had fermented skate before.
His eyes suddenly turned red.
What's wrong? Why did your eyes turn red?
(It's for Penalty Exemption Card.)
- He's eliminated. - Smile.
Isn't it delicious?
(He smiles.)
- You should chew it. - Swallow it. You should chew it.
You should eat it.
(All he has to do is chew and swallow it.)
I can't do it.
(He declares to give up.)
- He's eliminated. - He's eliminated.
- Kwang Soo. - He's out.
Is it normal that your nose becomes runny?
Your nostrils open up.
- Is that why? - Your nostrils open up.
Don't you feel refreshed?
Right, I feel something.
I feel like something is going down.
- Look at this. - Eating it for the first time...
(Two people are addicted to fermented skate.)
(Slurping)
- You really enjoy it. - Right?
- You enjoy it a lot. - It's delicious.
In that case...
(He drinks fermented skate ramyeon.)
He really enjoys it.
(He falls in love with fermented skate ramyeon.)
This is really a delicacy.
(I want to eat it easily too.)
People who like it would love it.
- Gosh. - That's interesting.
Gosh, that was a great meal.
- Jae Seok finished the whole bowl. - He ate it all.
It's interesting that he enjoys it.
It's one of you two.
You can keep it for now.
- Okay. - He enjoyed it the most.
- Right. - I enjoyed it the most.
- Let's see what happens next. - Okay.
Can we make a choice now?
- Yes. - We can pick the wire color.
- It should be snapped. - We have to explode their bomb.
We must snap their wire.
No way, no way.
Which color shall we pick? Pick one, and one that remains will be it.
I pick green.
- Green is excluded. - Green is excluded.
- I pick blue. - Blue is excluded.
- I pick white. - I pick red.
- Exclude red. - Then we must cut black.
(They choose black wire.)
Cut the black wire.
No way. Please.
(Team Jae Seok cuts the black wire.)
No way.
(Haha is the worst coward.)
(Team Jae Seok's first attack)
(Will they explode their bomb?)
(Black wire is...)
(cut.)
(The bomb doesn't explode.)
(Team Jae Seok's attack fails.)
That wasn't it.
It's better not to explode it yet.
- It can't explode in the beginning. - I agree.
- It'll get difficult. - Right.
(Each team has 4 wires left.)
I think it's in the building.
Let's go downstairs.
- Let's go. - Okay.
There are so many restaurants here.
(They go down to the basement of the shopping mall.)
A place like this...
- It's been such a long time. - Right?
Restaurants in the basement...
Incredible. It's this place.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
We'll sit in a corner.
- Okay. - Thank you.
(They found this place after a lot of internet searching.)
Hello. Enjoy your meal.
- It looks nice. - It looks so tasty.
Places like this are usually good.
Hey, this place is perfect.
- A jokbal set costs eight dollars. - There it is.
(A jokbal set costs 8 dollars.)
There it is. Eight dollars.
We'll have a jokbal set.
(Team Jong Kook orders a jokbal set that costs 8 dollars.)
Sadly, the bomb didn't go off.
- All right. - That's good.
- It's okay. - It's still in the beginning.
If it goes off too early, things would get complicated.
And Team Jong Kook's...
next dish is...
- Jokbal? - It's expensive.
- Jokbal is expensive. - Jokbal under 10 dollars...
- would be hard to find. - That'd be hard.
Except at convenience stores.
Team Jong Kook managed to find...
an eight-dollar jokbal set.
- Did they go to a market? - A jokbal set?
- It must be... - Right.
served on a small plate.
- Right. With a bowl of rice. - Yes.
- With a bit of jokbal. - So you can have a taste.
I'm sure beondegi is on the list.
- It has to be. - That would...
lower the price a lot.
- It'd make things harder for them. - Exactly.
- It'd be hard. - I agree.
- What about this one? - Let's go for that.
- You want number five? - Yes. Right above jokbal.
- I don't want to go below. - Okay.
- All right. - Okay.
- Let's go right above. - Number five.
So Min.
- You open it. - I'll...
1, 2, 3.
(Is it something cheap?)
Cheong...
(Cheonggukjang)
(Korean soul food)
(It tastes like home.)
(The strong smell might put you off at first, )
(but you'll love it once you taste it.)
(It's pretty cheap.)
- It's... - It's not bad.
It's good.
It's good, but...
- the smell... - It's too strong.
- This side... - The smell...
It's too strong.
I love cheonggukjang,
but cheonggukjang right after fermented skate?
Our breath will smell so bad today.
- Right after fermented skate... - When we talk...
It's a fermented food day.
- But the price is nice. - It's perfect.
- It usually costs 6 or 7 dollars. - 6 dollars...
We could get a small one.
It's easy to find one that costs six dollars.
- Where should we go? - Do you want to search first?
- We should. - Where should we go?
Do you remember that cheonggukjang place?
- At Sinsa-dong Intersection. - At Sinsa-dong Intersection.
- In Sinsa-dong... - There is a famous place.
- It's open 24 hours a day. - On the food street.
We'd go there after nightclubs.
We went there often.
The cheonggukjang set...
- was amazing. - Yes.
- You went to nightclubs together? - Nightclubs.
- Yes. - Why did you...
have to cause the businesses such trouble?
Hey.
(They should compensate.)
- Hey. - Hold on.
- We were VIPs. - This is crazy.
- My gosh. - You should have gone separately.
(This is how the VIPs looked.)
- You don't seem to know. - It's driving me crazy.
Hey.
- It must have been dark. - Yes.
(The memories are distorted.)
That's right.
(They might have looked okay.)
- Should we go there? - How much does it cost?
I think it costs 6 to 7 dollars.
- But... - If it's cheap...
- it's been too long. - "Handmade traditional"...
- Try calling them. - I'll call them.
- They sell soy sauce crabs too. - That sounds great.
(They call the cheonggukjang place from their memories.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Is this a cheonggukjang place? - Yes.
May I ask how much a bowl of cheonggukjang is?
(He as at least a VIP at this cheonggukjang place.)
(How much is a bowl of cheonggukjang?)
- 1 portion? - Yes.
It's eight dollars.
(8 dollars per portion)
- Okay. - Eight...
That's too bad.
- It's close from here too. - It's eight dollars.
It's a good place.
- Their cheonggukjang tastes great. - Let me try another place.
- Where is it? - I don't know exactly.
It's around Yangjae-dong.
(How will it go this time?)
- Is this a cheonggukjang place? - Yes.
How much is a bowl of cheonggukjang?
(Will it be under 8 dollars this time?)
- It's seven dollars. - Okay.
(7 dollars)
Okay. Is the restaurant open?
Yes.
Thank you.
(They found a 7-dollar cheonggukjang.)
- It's perfect. - We're done.
- It's close from here. - It's close from here.
Let's go.
- Incredible. - Perfect.
(They move to the cheonggukjang place.)
A jokbal set.
Well...
How about the two people the owner chooses eat?
(The two people the owner chooses will eat.)
And let's keep our colors.
- Okay. - Okay.
- We'll keep our colors? - Yes.
(Jong Kook: blue, Ji Hyo: red, Haha: green, Se Chan: white)
- Excuse me. - Sir, will you please...
choose 2 colors out of these 4...
- except black? - Please choose two.
- You want me to choose? - Yes, please.
Please think first.
You can just choose whatever comes to your mind.
Green.
- Your first choice is green? - And the other?
The other?
(His first choice is Haha. Who else will eat?)
White.
(It's Se Chan's color.)
(Haha and Se Chan will eat.)
What is this?
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you.
(It's those two this time?)
It's unbelievable.
I can't believe it.
Hey.
- I was relaxed, right? - You were.
They must be the colors restaurant owners like.
- That's incredible. - Green and white.
- The food is here. - It's here.
- It's here. - It's here.
There's tteokbokki too.
What's that?
This costs only eight dollars?
- It's a lot of food. - Unbelievable.
Is it time for us to enjoy the food?
Okay, well...
- Oh, my. - What is this?
(All the other 2 can eat is the side dishes.)
- There aren't many slices. - The anchovies taste good.
There you go.
(Munching)
(Se Chan takes a big bite.)
It's high-quality.
It's amazing that they have a jokbal set.
It tastes amazing.
The skin is so chewy.
One is not enough.
(Haha wraps some jokbal in lettuce.)
- With some dried radish... - Slow down.
- Why? - It'll run out soon.
(Meanwhile, the other two...)
Then I'll eat the tteokbokki.
Let me have a taste.
Tell us if you want some.
The food is running out.
Who wants some?
- Who wants some? - Raise your right hand.
If you want some...
What should we do?
I'll make them hold hands.
The two of you...
(What is it?)
You'll play rock-paper-scissors.
The winner can eat.
But...
you have to hold your hands.
Forget it.
(Forget it.)
(I'd rather not eat.)
I don't want it.
- Then... - Just your little fingers.
- Just your little fingers. - Make a pinky promise.
- The winner will feed the other. - We're one forever.
You won't run away.
- We're a team. - Play rock-paper-scissors...
Why do we have to play rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's just do it. Let's eat. - Yes!
This is nothing.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo make a pinky promise.)
(This is nothing.)
(There you go.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(It's supposed to be nothing, )
(but why does it make our hearts flutter?)
(The winner is...)
(Jong Kook.)
You won again?
You can eat.
(Casually)
No. You eat.
(Hold on.)
(Why did they even play rock-paper-scissors?)
This isn't what we were expecting.
(No one has to force them anymore.)
I'm okay.
- You won anyway. - I don't even want it that much.
- You can eat. - Then...
Then...
let's have it between you two...
(The game never ends.)
The jokbal game.
- The fun jokbal game. - Fine, I'll stop.
You eat. I'm okay.
- No. - It's okay. Eat.
- It'll be tasty. - Try it.
(While Team Jong Kook is being romantic...)
- Does it taste good? - Really?
- We're here. - I'm craving for cheonggukjang.
- We're here? - I want cheonggukjang.
(An aura of tradition)
It's a good restaurant. Let's go in.
(We're here to try the 7-dollar cheonggukjang.)
- Hello. - Hello.
We're sorry.
- There are other customers. - We're sorry.
A set of cheonggukjang, bossam, and rice with vegetables...
costs only seven dollars?
- That sounds amazing. - That's so cheap.
- Are we getting that? - Of course.
We'll have one portion.
- We're sorry. - We're sorry.
Thank you.
- Let's eat. - It looks amazing.
Let's eat the side dishes.
It looks so good.
(Side dishes prepared with care)
(Bibimbap you can mix with cheonggukjang)
- Oh, my. - It's here.
- Oh, my. - Thank you.
Be careful.
- This is... - That costs only seven dollars?
That costs only seven dollars?
- Oh, my. - There is kimchi too.
- This is great. - And four slices of bossam.
This looks so good.
- I want to eat it. - Put some in...
- You should mix them together. - Yes.
- It's barley rice. - Really?
(The whole cheonggukjang set costs only 7 dollars.)
Well...
How about only one person eats?
- What? - This one.
- What about 2 people? - 2 people?
Everyone seems to want some.
- I want some. - 2 people should eat.
- Yes. Two people can eat. - Okay.
What about this?
- Those who laugh first can't eat. - Okay.
(The first two people who laugh can't eat.)
(All the members are good at making others laugh.)
- If you laugh, you lose. - Yes.
- And... - Two people.
how about only one person can eat?
(The stakes are raised.)
(It's getting too serious.)
- Only 1? - Only 1 person can eat.
That sounds good.
Gosh, I'm not good at this.
- Me neither. - Ready.
Start.
(They start trying to make others laugh.)
(Seok Jin picks up a tissue.)
(What is he going to do?)
(I'll never laugh.)
(It doesn't make you want to laugh at all.)
(What is this?)
(Indifferent)
That's not enough.
(Calm)
(Blowing your nose is not enough?)
(What is she going to do with gochujang?)
(My nose is bleeding.)
(The 1st warning)
(This is not enough?)
(Licking)
(The 2nd warning)
(I almost laughed.)
(Seok Jin picks up some bean sprouts.)
(He wants to do something with it.)
(A bean sprout attack)
(They try hard to ignore him.)
Your nose is bleeding.
(Counterattack)
I know.
(This is an emergency.)
(Staring)
(Snorting)
(Seok Jin almost laughed by himself.)
You just laughed.
(I should get rid of this.)
(He gets rid of the bean sprout.)
You just laughed.
(Just then...)
(Kwang Soo eats the bean sprout.)
(Laughing)
I lose.
(Seok Jin declares his defeat.)
I can't take this one.
(Kwang Soo is a laughter bomber.)
How can you eat that?
(Kwang Soo sacrifices himself to eat cheonggukjang.)
(I have to hold it back.)
I lose.
I can't take it anymore.
My goodness. I can't believe it.
There are two left.
(Only one person can have cheonggukjang.)
(Kwang Soo goes into action first.)
(What is he going to do?)
Kwang Soo is going to do something.
I'm so happy I can laugh now.
(Jae Seok is searching for something.)
Here it is. I found it.
(So Min, use this.)
(This will definitely work.)
Kwang Soo.
Come here.
(Kwang Soo approaches. What is Jae Seok's hidden weapon?)
Now that I've made it this far...
- Okay. - I have to win.
(Kwang Soo approaches. What is Jae Seok's hidden weapon?)
Now that I've made it this far...
- Okay. - I have to win.
(Laughing)
(Kwang Soo laughs right away.)
This is Kwang Soo.
(What made Kwang Soo laugh?)
(A header monster)
(It makes everyone laugh.)
I haven't thought about it for a while.
Put that away.
(Kwang Soo is heading the ball during the soccer match against...)
(the Shanghai All Star team in July 2013.)
- For a while... - This is Kwang Soo.
For a while, all you could get from searching my name was this.
Why do you even have it?
- He is actually heading the ball. - This picture...
Kwang Soo...
(Kwang Soo tried to head the ball during the soccer match.)
(The picture became famous when it ended up in the Chinese media.)
- It was a soccer match. - Kwang Soo...
- was heading the ball. - Doesn't he...
- really resemble Kwang Soo? - It was in an article.
- It is me. - My goodness.
(It's not just a soccer player that looks like me.)
It's really me.
It's not a soccer player that looks like me.
The ball flew at him,
and he tried to head.
- The final winner is... - It's So Min.
- I didn't know it'd be me. - So Min.
Do you want me to mix it for you?
Yes, please. Thank you.
- You can have a spoonful. - Okay.
- Please make it tasty. - Okay.
It looks so tasty.
I haven't laughed this hard in a while.
(The warm cheonggukjang is mixed with barley rice and vegetables.)
It makes a certain sound when you mix it.
- It looks so tasty. - Thank you.
- This is... - Oh, my.
- Gosh. - It's been a long time.
This is a lot of food.
(Jae Seok gets to try a ladleful.)
(This is it.)
- It's crazy. - It was a good game.
I know many games like this.
(It's driving me crazy.)
You can try some.
If you give up your Penalty Exemption Card, I'll let you try.
(A Penalty Exemption Card for a spoonful of cheonggukjang?)
That's appealing.
That's an appealing offer.
- It's a good deal. - It's appealing.
A slice of bossam and the rest of this.
- Even a slice of bossam? - That's definitely appealing.
- In any case... - There's a lot left.
- It tastes amazing. - It's at least a ladleful.
(Inner conflict)
(A Penalty Exemption Card or a half bowl of bibimbap?)
(All I've eaten since the race started is...)
(a bit of fermented skate ramyeon.)
I'll eat.
(Put your spoon down.)
I give up my card.
I give up my Penalty Exemption Card.
This is why I love this team.
I can't help.
(It's all yours.)
- This is why I love this team. - I can't help.
(He exchanged his Penalty Exemption Card for cheonggukjang.)
- It looks so tasty. - Thank you.
- Gosh. - This is...
It tastes so good.
It's crazy, right?
- It tastes good, right? - It's crazy, right?
- Eat this too. - It tastes so good.
Eat this and bossam too.
- I told you it'd be tasty. - Wait.
Where did everything go? It's all gone.
- Where did it go? - It must be delicious.
- It tastes so good. Bossam too. - Right.
- The mission is about food, - It's not enough.
but why are we still hungry?
(Why are we still hungry?)
(Their stomachs are still empty.)
I'm hungry too.
That's strange. The mission is about food, but I still feel hungry.
- I'm hungry too. - That's strange.
Guys, the other team...
has finished their jokbal.
One of your wires will be cut.
- Okay. - Which color?
- Do it. - Which color?
But...
- There is something else? - There is something else?
It's for Jae Seok.
Glasses and nose hair will be drawn on your face.
(Draw glasses and nose hair on Jae Seok's face.)
- That's... - Glasses and nose hair...
(Team Jae Seok ordered Haha's hat to be removed.)
(Haha pays them back with something stronger.)
- Let me do it. - Let me do it.
- You're good at it. - I want to do it too.
(Why did I start this?)
- You draw glasses, I'll draw hair. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo and So Min become enthusiastic...)
(and put a lot of care into the details.)
(Jae Seok's appearance is upgraded.)
You're wearing two pairs of glasses.
Get the bomb ready.
Which color?
(Team Jong Kook attacks Team Jae Seok.)
- We'll give them black too. - They gave us black.
- Black. - Black.
(An eye for an eye. They choose black wire.)
(Team Jong Kook attacks Team Jae Seok's black wire.)
- Black for black? - I think black...
- I don't think it's black. - It's not black.
- No. - It's not black.
- I agree. - It can't be black.
- Let me cut it. - I think...
You can cut it.
Black.
(Trembling)
Here we go.
Do you want to do it, So Min?
1, 2...
(The black wire is cut.)
(If the bomb goes off, they lose and the race is over.)
(What will happen to Team Jae Seok?)
(They survive.)
- It wasn't black. - Two...
(Team Jong Kook's attack fails.)
- It wasn't black. - Gosh.
What a relief.
What a relief. With your Penalty Exemption Card gone...
- I can't do this... - This is too intense.
(Team Jong Kook's black and Team Jae Seok's white and black are out.)
- Guys, did you enjoy the food? - Yes.
- It was delicious. - It was.
We have chance cards.
- There are four types. - Okay.
- What are they? - I see.
There are a Discount Card, a Lowest Price Card,
a Changing Dish Card, and a Rip-off Card.
Discount, Lowest Price, and Changing Dish Cards...
are used for defense.
We want to attack.
- Then you can use a Rip-off Card. - What's that?
You'll carry out a mission.
Depending on the number of your successes,
the price for the other team will be lowered.
- By how much? - They need a five-dollar dish?
Will you use a chance card?
- Yes. - A Rip-off Card?
- Yes. - Of course.
- Here are some rubber bands. - What's that?
Put a rubber band around your head.
Using your facial muscles,
- push it down to your neck. - What?
- Push it down? - What?
- How? - How?
Like this.
Push it down to your neck.
- Like this. - Okay.
Push it down.
- There you go. - Like this?
(Order: Jae Seok, Seok Jin, So Min, Kwang Soo)
It has to be lower in the back.
Okay.
(He suddenly looks decades older.)
- Hold on. - Jae Seok.
(What happened?)
What happened to his face?
- Don't you want to succeed? - I do.
- Ready. - We're sacrificing ourselves...
to rip the other team off.
Ready, start.
(He is given 30 seconds.)
(Wriggling)
- Oh, my. - It's going down.
It's stuck at his mouth. His mouth sticks out too much.
(The rubber band is stuck at his mouth.)
- It's impossible. - Be quiet.
- It's not going to work. - It's like Mount Baekdu.
It's impossible. His mouth sticks out too much.
- That's the Himalayas. - It's too high.
(It'd be challenging even for experienced climbers.)
- It's on the peak now. - It's going down.
- It's going down. - It's on the peak.
- It's going down. - Gosh.
(It's at his lower lip now.)
- It's stuck at his lower lip now. - It's stuck.
It's one thing after another.
It gets worse and worse.
- Use your tongue. - There you go.
- It gets worse and worse. - Use your tongue.
- Use your tongue. - Right.
- Are you okay? - Are you okay?
- It's down. - Yes!
Okay.
(Jae Seok barely succeeds.)
- Okay! - We cleared the mission!
Okay! Did you see that?
- You were awesome. - Did you see that?
Wow, Jae Seok.
- Did we get 50 cents? - Yes.
That was quick.
- The next one is 6.50 dollars. - Okay.
- Okay, okay. - Okay.
I can't believe your mouth protrudes more than your nose does.
(Amazed)
(His lips looked like Mt. Everest.)
Hey, be quiet, will you?
- All right, Seok Jin. - Is it my turn?
- Done. - Ready.
(After putting on the rubber band, he wears his glasses.)
- He's still wearing his glasses. - Be careful.
Set. Go.
You look cute.
(He's a 54-year-old cutie.)
- You're cute. - Oh, come on.
- Don't try to look cute. - I'm not.
- Your nose is too high. - It's not coming down.
(His nose is his problem.)
The rubber band is digging into his face.
- Why can't you do it? - His nose is too high.
(The rubber band is stuck to his face.)
Why can't you do it?
(Frustrated)
- Come on. - It's not moving at all.
He needs to move much more.
(He tries his best.)
Try harder. Try harder.
(He does everything he can.)
- Please. - Please, Seok Jin.
Time's over.
(He fails to move it even 1cm lower.)
- You couldn't do it. - It just wouldn't budge.
To think that you want to receive the Penalty Exemption Card...
It doesn't work. Try it.
- Try it. - I'll do it.
- Go, So Min. - My nose and mouth aren't high.
Ready, set,
- Go. - go.
(Stretching)
- You're doing good. - It went completely down.
- How did you do that? - How did you?
(It's unbelievable.)
- Are you okay? - How did she do that?
- How is it possible? - Look at her.
(Would you like to look at my face again?)
(It was a collaboration between her nose and facial muscles.)
- Good job. - It's going down.
(They realize her true talent.)
- You're good. - How do you do it?
She's so fast.
- How did she do that? - Move backwards.
- Your chin's in the way. - My chin protrudes.
(She's stuck.)
Don't talk! We don't need to hear that.
- Don't talk about your chin. - Why did you?
- Move it backwards? - Everyone including me has...
- secrets regarding their bodies. - Her chin is the problem.
- You can do it. - She's in trouble.
- You're almost there. - You're almost there.
(She only has 10 seconds left.)
- You're almost there. - Her chin is the problem.
Please!
- Please, So Min. - You did it!
Good job.
(So Min barely makes it.)
- Mission complete. - She's good.
I seem to be the problem.
Protruding mouth, protruding nose, and protruding chin.
- It was stuck at my nose. - You had trouble with your chin.
This part is high.
I bet he'll get stuck on his lips because they're thick.
- His lips? - Kwang Soo.
We should get a total of 1.50 dollars off, right?
(I'll show you.)
Look at him.
(He has a fascinating face.)
(Everyone is bewitched.)
You look ugly.
- You really do. - Is your nose boneless?
- Of course, I do. - You're lacking bones there.
(His nose is only made up of flesh.)
- You're boneless. - What do you mean?
- Goodness. - Where are your bones?
You look like a Roman soldier with a helmet on.
- You're right. - Right?
His nose is boneless.
- You don't have any bones. - Hey,
your nose collapsed.
- This type of nose could help me. - You're right.
Ready, set, go.
(He has 30 seconds.)
- That was fast. - He did it.
(His boneless nose does indeed help him.)
- That didn't take long. - He gets stuck on his lips.
- He has thick lips. - You're right.
- You're so ugly. - He's mutated.
- He's a mutant. - He looks like that fish.
He looks like a pollack.
A pollack?
(Human pollack: Appears during the rubber band game)
(They have found a rare species.)
- Or was it a rockfish? - A rockfish?
- A rockfish? - A rockfish?
(His face is about to collapse.)
- It's working. - You have to do this.
- This is the hard part. - Okay.
A bit more, Kwang Soo.
(We cannot dare to describe this face.)
(He is our country's number 1 humorous cultural asset.)
You have to do it, Kwang Soo. Come on.
- Your chin is in the way. - Kwang Soo, please.
- You're right. - Hurry.
We're running out of time.
- Hurry. Hey, hey. - I think it'll work.
- Please. - Come on.
(The cultural asset is malfunctioning.)
- The chin is getting in the way. - Please!
Kwang Soo, please.
He'll succeed if he gets the rubber band down.
- He won't succeed. - You just need to look up.
- Kwang Soo. - One...
(He fails.)
- One... - Yes?
(He only replies well.)
- Time's up. - He failed.
Does your chin protrude that much?
- Why is it so difficult? - It's completely stuck there.
All right. Two of you succeeded.
That team will have a limit of six dollars.
It'll be below six dollars.
(Team Jong Kook will have to go with six dollars or less.)
It's time for you to choose your next menu.
Team Jae Seok has given you a six-dollar limit.
- Really? - We need to pick well.
Shouldn't we pick 1 or 2?
I don't think we should leave them be.
I wonder what the 1st one is.
- Beondegi. - Maybe.
It could be beondegi, raw octopus, or chicken feet.
- Chicken feet? - Yes. Those are my guesses.
- Let's just open it. - Let's open the first one.
Yes, let's do that.
As long as I'm with you guys, I'm not afraid.
How about we fold our hands together...
- before opening this? - I'm down.
(He wants to fold hands together.)
(You little...)
- Jong Kook. - Like this.
- Let's do this together. - Let's do it.
If I do it, I won't be able to open this.
I'll open it with my mouth.
(Sighing)
- All right. - Jong Kook.
- Okay. - Okay. With your mouth.
(They fold hands together.)
Haha wanted to do it badly. This is what he does.
- Open it with your mouth. - Do it.
(He suppresses his anger.)
- Open it. - Open it.
- He's really doing it. - I know.
He is. All this just for folding hands?
- Is this necessary? - Yes.
Why?
Use your front teeth. Good.
It's almost done.
(What is the menu that they chose this time?)
- It's raw octopus! - It's raw octopus.
Raw octopus.
(This delicacy allows you to feel the texture of the live octopus.)
(It may seem extremely unusual to foreigners, )
(but once you have a taste, there's no going back.)
Isn't raw octopus expensive?
- Yes. - It's expensive.
It's very expensive.
- It is. - Let me look it up.
They wouldn't sell it for this price even at the Noryangjin Fish Market.
But we just need 1 portion. We just need 1 octopus.
- One octopus? - Raw octopus is expensive,
but dead octopus is cheap.
- Because... - Can't we perform CPR?
- It's expensive when it's alive. - We can try pumping its heart.
We can perform CPR.
What if we pay our raw money for it?
(He tries to talk smart.)
What?
(It makes him look old.)
- What should we do? - Let's see.
There aren't any.
Do we get no chances?
- So... - All right.
We have several chance cards that'll reduce the price.
There's always a way out.
- Choose one. - There are Discount Card,
- Rip-off Card, Changing Dish Card. - Changing Dish Card.
The Lowest Price Card is the best.
- We need to get this one. - All right.
This is our only way to win.
If we pick the other cards, they'll only counterattack.
Getting something below seven dollars seems impossible.
- Should we do that? - Let's do it.
- We choose this card. - All right.
You chose the Lowest Price Card.
Once you pass the mission,
- you will obtain the card. - Okay.
The mission is called Hello, My Friend.
(Hello, My Friend)
- Hello, My Friend? - Yes.
You need to call a friend of yours.
Visit that friend, and do a mission together.
If you succeed,
you're price will be regarded as a lower price...
- than your opponent's. - That's amazing.
Can we call whomever we want?
- Yes. - Do you know anyone around here?
I can try calling since it's Monday.
- Let's see. Jae Seong... - Hold on.
I wonder what Sang Yeob is doing.
- Oh, right. - He lives in Seorae Village.
He's done filming his drama.
Sang Yeob usually says yes.
He waits for such calls.
(They try calling him.)
We used to call him on Tuesdays, so he might not be ready today.
(No way)
[VIU Ver] SBS E439 Running Man
"The Bomb Is About to Explode Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
I think he's made up his mind to pursue only acting.
(Maybe it's because you called.)
- That's possible. - He's determined.
How about Hong Jin Young?
Do you have her number? You should call her then.
Should I try calling her?
(He decides to call Jin Young.)
- Hello, Se Chan. - Hey, where are you?
I'm filming at the moment.
- Oh, are you? - Team Switzerland!
Team Switzerland is here.
Where?
We're at a jokbal restaurant.
- Really? - Yes.
No way, no way. In broad daylight?
We're also filming right now.
(She thought they were drinking.)
(Don't misunderstand us.)
- Goodness. - Jin Young.
Watch what you say.
You made it sound like we were drinking.
- I see. - We're doing a mission right now.
If you were around Gangnam,
- we were about to come see you. - Right.
I am.
- Really? - Where?
Hey, if we went there right now,
will you be able to make time for us for about 10 to 15 minutes?
(He asks if they can stop by.)
- Sure, come. - Seriously?
(Surprised)
- What is she filming? - What are you filming?
- What is it? - Are you filming yourself?
I'm shooting a commercial.
- A commercial? - We'll be there.
- A commercial? - I see.
You better hurry. I'll be waiting.
All right. We'll be there in a second.
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
Bye.
- She's so laidback. - We did it.
- She said yes. - We did it.
- And she's nearby as well. - She's in Gangnam...
and has full makeup on.
It's our fate.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- We did it. That was smooth. - That was.
(They're about to go meet her.)
- Let's go. - Hold on.
Team Jae Seok has attacked you.
This is the last one.
All right.
Which one of theirs will you cut?
This time, it might work.
- Let's send it off. - I think we should.
Which colors are left.
I'll listen to you guys.
- Whatever you say. - How about the blue one?
- Sure. - The blue one?
1, 2, 3.
- Blue. - Blue.
(They choose blue.)
(Team Jong Kook needs to cut the blue wire.)
Please cut the blue wire.
The blue one?
Hold on.
(It can't explode.)
- I'll cut it now. - No!
One...
(Did Team Jae Seok pick...)
Two...
(the right wire to explode it?)
Three.
(Did Team Jae Seok pick the right wire to explode it?)
(Se Chan has cut...)
(the blue wire.)
(Cutting)
(It's silent.)
(The bomb did not go off. Team Jae Seok has failed.)
We're safe.
(Everyone was anxious.)
- That scared. - Okay.
(They succeed in defending themselves.)
(They can only counterattack once they obtain the chance card.)
Let's go.
Stop.
(They need to succeed the mission with Jin Young.)
I'm so thankful that she could meet us.
- Let's go. - I bet she'll scream.
- I bet she will. - Jin Young!
Don't pretend to be working when you're already done.
(She was monitoring.)
(He starts nagging the moment he enters.)
- I wasn't. - Don't pretend to be monitoring.
I wasn't.
I thought she was shooting "New Late Night E News".
Hello.
Jin Young.
(Jin Young joined the group on a trip to Switzerland.)
(It was a family special.)
(She was like Ji Hyo's sister and Jong Kook's girlfriend.)
We're really thankful.
- We are. - It's all right.
- We had to find someone, - Right.
- but it was difficult to find one. - Really?
But celebrities don't want to appear on TV all of a sudden...
- in no makeup. - Right.
- But you saved us. - I'm always prepared.
- Exactly. - I'm always prepared.
- I'm the best - You're the best
She was holding that all along.
(She's indeed always ready.)
She's the best
(They thank her for her willingness.)
She's amazing.
- She really is. - Thank goodness we came.
- I know. - Right.
All right.
In order for the team to obtain the Lowest Price Card,
Jin Young needs to go through a mission...
called A Solemn Snack.
(A Solemn Snack)
- What is that? - Does she need to eat something?
Do I need to eat solemnly?
We'll lose then.
(What is her mission?)
In 60 seconds,
you need to eat four or more snacks...
that dangle from a crown.
- A crown? - You know how we play that game...
with dried persimmons?
- She'll do well. - That's difficult.
Where did you get that crown?
Doesn't this spin?
- It's hard. - Will you be able to do it?
- Will you? - Does it spin faster?
Look at you two.
(Haha points to Ji Hyo and Jin Young.)
- They're best friends. - I know.
- She kissed her. - I missed you.
- I missed you. - Look at Ji Hyo.
(It's how they greet each other.)
Wait.
- What? - Nothing.
(What were you trying to say this time?)
- We... - This feels weird.
It feels like an American soap opera.
They're from "Mom's Diary", and they're from this show.
Both of them are close to him.
- It's Hollywood. - This is the States.
(It's like they're shooting an American soap opera.)
- Just move on. - All right.
- You should wear it well. - Is this even possible?
- Hold on, let me see. - I can't do it.
How does the crown feel?
It doesn't feel too good.
It's unstable.
But I'll have to withstand the weight of the crown.
(She only has 1 chance to eat 4 in 60 seconds.)
- You can do it! - Let's go!
Good luck.
(Will she be able to make it?)
Go.
- My goodness. - Is this how it's like?
(They finally realize the true nature of the crown.)
- What is that? - Come on.
Is this how it works?
- You have to snatch it. - Bite it.
Bite it, bite it.
- You did it. - Bite it.
(The snack is in front of her mouth.)
That was good!
- It's all right. - It went upwards.
- It's almost touching your nose. - Good, good.
- You're close! - What should I do?
- Jin Young, you have to do this. - What should I do?
- Please! - You have to!
(Struggling)
Goodness.
This reminds me of a zombie movie that I watched recently.
(Do I still...)
(look like Jin Young to you?)
- Good. - Good.
Raise your chin a bit.
Just bite it.
- Don't swear. - Just bite it.
Bite it.
(She bites it.)
- Good. - Well done.
(She finally bites 1.)
- Good. - It's coming.
(She spots another chance.)
(The second snack is right in front of her.)
- Good! - Great!
(She seems to get it now.)
Good!
- Bite it! - Good job.
(She's taking her time.)
It's spinning.
- It's coming. - You just need to wait.
(She has 15 seconds left and 1 more to go.)
(Will Jin Young succeed?)
(The snack is in front of her mouth, )
(but she misses it.)
- Oh, no! - Slowly.
- Yes! - Yes!
(She catches the snack.)
(Jin Young succeeds.)
(I came, and I ate.)
(Worship me.)
You're the great Hong Jin Young!
- Jin Young. - You must trust me completely.
- Rinse your mouth. - Rinse your mouth.
(She's just as competent as her partner Jong Kook...)
(and succeeds the mission.)
I'm the best
(Proud)
- She's hilarious. - Did I succeed?
- Yes, you did. - All right.
We won.
Jin Young did so well.
This was a hard one.
All right.
You will be able to have raw octopus for 5.90 dollars...
which is a lower price than your opponent's.
(They get to have raw octopus.)
Now, we can go eat raw octopus.
- That's great. - Thanks.
- You should come on our show again. - Yes.
- You've been... - All right.
only focusing on "Mom's Diary".
I'll visit you soon.
- Please do. - Come.
Running Man is family.
- Right. - Of course.
You're family.
- Thanks, Jin Young. - No problem.
Thanks, Jin Young.
- I hope the meal rejuvenates me. - Me too.
(They obtain the chance card and arrive at the restaurant.)
Since we don't have a choice in menu,
- shall we just order? - Sure.
- Ma'am. - Ma'am.
We'd like...
a serving that looks more like four servings.
(They can only order 1 serving.)
You want her to give a lot.
- We'd like a really big octopus. - A huge one.
The biggest one you have.
Thank you.
(They'll have it for 5.90 dollars.)
Team Jong Kook has gone down to 5.90 dollars.
- What? - 5.90 dollars?
You can only order dishes that are under that price.
Please pick a menu,
and have it for 5.90 dollars.
Let's just open all of them in this column.
- Let's do that. - Sure.
- Let's go for the fourth one. - Let's pick the green one.
- All right. - I wanted to pick that.
- Fourth one. - Let's open it.
What is it?
(What is the 4th ranking?)
Please.
- Yukhoe? - Yukgaejang?
- I think it's yukgaejang. Yukhoe? - What?
(Yukhoe)
(It may seem too raw to foreigners, )
(but yukhoe is a rejuvenating dish.)
(But will they be able to find one that's under 5.90 dollars?)
- Yukhoe? - That's expensive.
- There's none that cheap. - That's expensive.
- That's expensive. - Yukhoe?
(The meat itself is already expensive.)
It is.
How can we eat this?
- This one's ridiculous. - The cheapest one would be...
seven dollars.
Aren't they usually over 10 dollars?
You're right.
- Your limit is 5.90 dollars. - I think we'll lose.
There's a place in Cheongdam-dong.
Korean beef yukhoe is 36 dollars.
- For bibimbap? - No, not that.
I think we've lost.
- No, that's not true. - We're in trouble.
(Don't lose hope!)
There's one that's 4.30 dollars.
- Where? - Where?
- Where? - Am I wrong?
- It's 4.50 dollars. - Where?
This is...
- in Sejong University? - What do you mean?
Is it inside the campus?
- In the cafeteria? - Hold on.
I found one too,
- but it's six dollars. - It's cafeteria food.
Yukhoe bibimbap that is sold in the cafeteria...
of Sejong University is 4.50 dollars.
- That's so cheap. - It is.
- Let's go. - 4.30 dollars is really cheap.
It's 4.50 dollars.
- Let's go right now. Hurry. - Goodness.
- That's too cheap. - It's so cheap.
- We're here. - The school hasn't...
opened yet for this semester.
They're still on their break.
- Is the cafeteria open, though? - Of course.
I really enjoyed eating cafeteria food.
- Me too. - It was delicious.
It's cheap and tasty.
(Reminiscing)
- Ramyeon were good too. - You're right.
They probably have ramyeon here.
- They have so many dishes. - Things have changed.
- Look at the menu. - It changes automatically.
- Is this a kiosk? - There's a variety.
- Goodness. - Wow.
I see yukhoe bibimbap.
They even have spicy chicken bibimbap.
They look so delicious. I want an omelet as well.
- They have Japanese cuisine too. - I want an omelet.
We can only have one, right?
(They pay through a machine.)
Goodness.
- It's out. - There's...
- a huge variety of menus. - That's your receipt.
- "Rice served with grilled fish." - It looks good.
I suddenly became hungry.
(Team Jong Kook has ordered raw octopus.)
(1st, she stretches the octopus.)
(2nd, she lays it down and cuts it.)
I couldn't eat this back then because it was too expensive.
It's out.
You should dip it in this oil sauce.
(He dips it in the oil sauce before putting it in his mouth.)
(It has a firm texture.)
- It's so delicious. - Listen to the sound.
(Eating it is a blast.)
- I dipped it too much. - It's all right.
(They get to eat it for a very cheap price.)
Hold it.
Good.
(She assists Jong Kook.)
(Gazing)
(He ponders whether or not to tease them.)
He saw you.
(Just when he was about to tease them...)
Jong Kook stared at him the moment he was about to say something.
I was contemplating.
But looking at his face, I don't think I can.
You're lucky today.
You are sitting far from me.
- It's no wonder... - That's right.
he kept asking me to sit in the middle.
(I will hold myself back.)
(Ji Hyo has dried laver on her lips.)
Ji Hyo, you have something on your lips.
Jong Kook, you should...
(Hesitant)
You should check her lips.
Se Chan, do I have something on my lips?
Let me see.
- No, you don't. - Look closely.
(They become nervous.)
- You are set. - Check the person on your right.
Okay.
- Is it a relay? - Yes, it is.
(A relay lip care starts.)
You are set. Check his lips. It's a relay.
- Check his lips. - Check.
(Moving closer)
(Jong Kook, let me check your lips.)
Okay. We have a trailer.
(We did it again today!)
Haha, you are working hard today.
You are working hard today.
(They cleared 1 serving of raw octopus.)
Ji Hyo. You should pick a wire this time.
- A wire? - Yes.
- Should I pick a wire? - Yes.
It's pain to cut a wire.
- It's so nerve-wracking. - Since you and I have done it,
either Jae Seok or Kwang Soo should do it.
I can't do it.
The chance is down to 33.3 percent.
(The chance of the bomb exploding is down to 33.3 percent.)
If our bomb doesn't go off this time, we will win.
We will win.
How many wires do we have left? We have three wires left.
Their bomb has a wire with a different color.
- Let's pick the yellow wire. - The yellow wire?
- What? Good thinking. - You have a point.
There must be a reason why it has a different color.
- The yellow wire. - The yellow wire.
- The yellow wire. - All right.
- The yellow wire. - Okay.
Okay.
(Team Jong Kook attacks the yellow wire.)
- I don't think that's the wire. - You know,
the yellow wire is what I picked the first time.
- That makes me worried. - I have a bad feeling about this.
I think it's one of these two.
- My goodness. - The blue wire...
Hey, hey. Don't cut it without a warning.
Are you going to cut it?
(The chance of the bomb going off is 33.3 percent.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(If the bomb goes off, the race will end right away...)
(and Team Jong Kook will win.)
(What will be the result?)
(Cutting)
(The bomb doesn't go off. Team Jong Kook's attack fails.)
- It wasn't that wire. - Yes!
- It wasn't the yellow wire. - Yes!
No, it wasn't.
- It wasn't the yellow wire. - This is nerve-wracking.
It wasn't the yellow wire.
(That was close.)
- This is incredible. - How did we survive for so long?
We survived.
(There is a 50-percent chance of explosion the next time.)
Let's eat.
- Yukhoe bibimbap. - Now,
their bomb will go off if we eat and cut a wire.
Let's end them.
(Freshly-cooked rice gets topped...)
We only ordered one dish, but there is so much to eat.
(with various vegetables.)
It looks amazing. There are so many toppings.
(A happiness of 4 dollars and 50 cents)
- Sesame oil. - Look at this.
(She is excited.)
This is unbelievable.
- Isn't it hearty? - So Min, it looks delicious.
My goodness.
Can't I eat this?
Can't we have a serving for each?
Eat it with chopsticks.
There is so much yukhoe.
- It's tasty. - It's tasty, right?
(Both Kwang Soo and Seok Jin are satisfied.)
There is so much yukhoe.
It's tasty, too.
All the dishes we had are tasty.
(They finish the dish in an instant.)
(Team Jae Seok cleared 1 serving of yukhoe.)
Is it our turn to choose?
Yes. The other team will have their bomb ready.
- Is it their turn to attack? - Yes.
- It's their turn to attack. - Our bomb?
Let's check the result outside.
- Okay. - It's their turn to attack us.
- They will set off our bomb. - Our bomb.
If we don't end them this round, we will get wiped out.
- If we fail... - There won't be another chance.
There won't be another chance. It's a 50-50 chance.
There are only two wires left.
This game needs to end here.
Which wire should we pick?
Shall we pick a wire we don't have like they did?
We don't have a green wire,
but they do.
(Team Jong Kook's bomb has a green wire.)
I wanted to pick the green wire.
I wanted to pick the red wire from the start.
Red is the color of fire.
Now, let's pick between the green and red wire...
by flipping a coin.
- Let's do it. - Let's use various methods.
- Okay. - This is an important decision.
It's bound to go off in the next round.
- Tail means red. - Red.
- Head means green. - Green.
(Tail means red and head means green.)
(The coin is tossed.)
(The fate of the game lies in his hands.)
- Shall we go? - Yes.
In 1, 2, 3.
(The legendary unlucky man, Kwang Soo picked the red wire.)
(The classic unlucky man, Jae Seok picked the green wire.)
(What will be the result?)
(It's Kwang Soo's pick, red wire.)
- What is this? - It's red.
- Red. - Red.
- Let's go with the red wire. - We choose the red wire.
- Let's shout it. - Red.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Red. - Red.
Team Jae Seok picked red.
- Red? - Yes.
- I don't think it's red. - I think the bomb will go off.
I think the bomb will go off.
Then let's bring our hands together.
- I will hold your hands. - Help me.
- Okay. - Let's bring our hands together.
- Okay. - Hold it this way.
(Team Jong Kook has 3 wires left.)
Why do I feel nervous?
All right. Get ready.
Hold on.
In 1, 2, 3.
(If the bomb goes off, the race will end right away.)
Please. Please.
(Team Jae Seok will win.)
(What will be the result?)
(Exploding)
I knew the red wire would make the bomb go off.
(Team Jong Kook lost.)
- What just happened? Did we lose? - Was it the red wire?
Okay!
(Team Jae Seok won.)
- We did it! - Who needs Penalty Exemption Card?
(The great unlucky man)
(Mom, I am proud that I am unlucky.)
Gosh, this is...
(It's time for the penalty.)
The winner of The Bomb Is About to Explode...
is Team Jae Seok.
(Team Jae Seok wins The Bomb Is About to Explode.)
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
(Disappointed)
How did they find yukhoe?
It was very difficult for us to win.
I know.
- Congratulations. - I thought they would win.
Congratulations.
For Team Jong Kook,
the original penalty we had in mind was the water bomb.
Since the weather is too cold,
(The weather is too cold.)
they will get a water slap from the winning team.
- From the winning team? - Yes.
That's a bit annoying.
- A water slap? - Gosh, my ears are freezing.
My goodness.
(At that moment, Haha moves stealthily.)
- I can't believe it. - Haha won't get the penalty.
- Penalty Exemption Card? - Do you have it?
I did it!
Three people will get the penalty. Who will hit Jong Kook?
(I, Seok Jin, will do it.)
- Those are 3 bowls. - Those are 3 bowls.
Seok Jin, it's obvious those are three bowls.
- He is very angry. - Right.
Gosh, it's cold.
(It's time for revenge.)
In 1, 2, 3. Have a good year!
(Splashing)
- Gosh, it's cold. - It's like a water bomb.
- It was a proper slap. - Water splashed on me, too.
(He is proud that he had his revenge.)
- My goodness. - That's how you do it.
That was nice.
It's Se Chan's turn.
Se Chan.
- It's cold. - I will do this for you.
You need good techniques.
- Use the snap of your wrist. - I will push back your hair.
(Splashing)
(The water slap pushes back his bangs.)
I pushed back his hair.
- That was incredible. - Right?
You need good techniques.
I don't have good techniques.
(He apologizes in advance.)
(Ji Hyo is the sacrifice of the inexperienced Kwang Soo.)
- All right. - Have a good year, Ji Hyo!
(Splashing)
(A textbook water slap without any techniques)
In conclusion, Team Jae Seok won the race today.
(The race ended with the unlucky members' victory.)
This is great.
(Running Man gets dragged away without any information.)
(I am sorry, but where are we going?)
(The 8 members get locked up for no reason.)
(100-minute House?)
(They only have 100 minutes.)
(They must complete missions in 100 minutes to escape.)
(They continue to get missions that are related to 100.)
(Does someone know the secret of 100?)
(Some members want to unearth the secret...)
(while some members want to hide the secret.)
(What is the secret of 100?)
(I got goosebumps.)
(The Secret of 100)