Hello. Good morning.
(Today's shoot begins
a little earlier than usual.)
(Kwang Soo arrives first.)
Right away?
I need to get my makeup done
right away?
(He needs to get makeup done?)
I shouldn't have gone
to the beauty salon.
(He shouldn't have gotten
his hair and makeup done.)
Hello. Hello, everyone.
(What is this place?)
Hello.
(A familiar set
of makeover tools...)
(and a bunch of different outfits
that have no correlation whatsoever)
(And there's an unknown board
on one side of the dressing room.)
(5 days before the day of shoot,
Mok-dong SBS)
Hey, Chul Min.
- Hi, Suk Jin.
- Hey.
This week, we're going to shoot
a year-end special,
and we're going to hold
the 2019 Ggannes Film Festival.
(We're going to hold
the 2019 Ggannes Film Festival)
What's going on?
- "Ggang"?
- "Ggannes Film Festival".
- What is that?
- I prepared scene-stealing roles...
from Korean movies.
You'll each pick a role and race
dressed up as that person.
- We need to dress up?
- Yes.
The male members can choose
from eight characters.
Jiang Chen from "The Outlaws".
Agui from "Tazza".
Jang Kyung Chul
from "I Saw the Devil".
A zombie from "Train to Busan".
Jo Tae Oh from "Veteran".
Mr. Baek from "A Bittersweet Life".
Grand Prince Suyang
from "The Face Reader".
And the mother from "Mother".
What? All of a sudden?
Yes, the female members
can choose from four characters.
Lee Geum Ja from "Lady Vengeance".
Yeo Il from "Welcome to Dongmakgol".
Madam Jeong from "Tazza".
And Oh Dae Su from "Old Boy".
- What?
- Those are the four characters.
I'm guessing we can't choose
the characters.
- We need to pick a number, right?
- Yes.
I'll choose...
I'll go with...
Okay.
Kwang Soo, there's only one left,
so that number is yours.
You'll find out what it is
on the day of the shoot.
I didn't know we'd have to
get changed right away.
(What kind of movie character
did Kwang Soo end up with?)
I shouldn't have gone to the salon.
You're number five.
(What is number 5?)
It's Jang Kyung Chul
from "I Saw the Devil".
(Jang Kyung Chul
from "I Saw the Devil")
It's Jang Kyung Chul
from "I Saw the Devil".
(Startled)
I really love this character.
(I loved him in the movie.)
But I...
(But I don't want
to dress up as him.)
(There's also a zombie.)
The person who got
the zombie role...
should've started
their makeup yesterday.
It does take a while.
(He wears a wig after he finishes
getting his makeup.)
(Taken aback)
Are you sure
this is the right hairstyle?
This is my mom's hairstyle.
(This is my mom's hairstyle.)
(Jang Kyung Chul actually had
a middle-aged lady's haircut.)
I'm pretty sure Choi Min Sik
didn't have this kind of hairstyle.
(The awkward wig
somehow feels very familiar.)
- Hello.
- What are you doing?
(Jae Suk is the second person
to arrive.)
I'm Jang Kyung Chul.
(Are you...)
Are you on your way
to the morning soccer club?
No, I'm a psychopath.
(A psychopath
who likes to play soccer.)
Jae Suk, you picked number seven,
so you're Grand Prince Suyang.
- You're Grand Prince Suyang?
- My gosh.
(Jae Suk will be dressing up
as Grand Prince Suyang.)
The outfit is going to be heavy.
(Will he be able to make it work?)
Do I need to wear this right now?
You may begin getting changed.
I'm beginning to look feminine.
(He's slowly turning into
a very feminine psychopath.)
(The world's prettiest psychopath)
I think I've seen someone
who looks like this.
I can't remember who it was.
Where do I go?
(The next member comes along.)
(Laughing)
(He looks like a middle-aged lady.)
What is that?
- I'm Jang Kyung Chul.
- I saw you from afar.
- I thought you were Han Ki Beom.
- What are you talking about?
(He got a makeover that looks
more similar to Han Ki Beom.)
What number did you choose?
I chose number six. What did I get?
You're the zombie?
A zombie?
(You darn jerks.)
(A ghastly look with blood stains
and weird joint movements,)
(the zombies were amazing
scene-stealers in "Train to Busan.")
I'm a zombie?
(Se Chan's character is
one of the zombies on the team.)
Get changed into zombie clothes.
Zombies don't have clothes.
They do in "Train to Busan."
Kwang Soo, I'm not even kidding.
Can I take a photo of you
from behind?
You look exactly like Han Ki Beom.
(He really looks like him
from every angle.)
- Will you cut it out?
- I'm serious.
There's no doubt about it. Here.
- This angle right here...
- I'm Jang Kyung Chul.
This angle...
It's Ki Beom.
(We dedicate this to Han Ki Beom
for giving us a good laugh.)
(Jae Suk is back dressed up
as Grand Prince Suyang.)
Hello, you tall man.
Jae Suk.
It actually suits you.
(It actually suits you.)
Do I have the face of a king?
To be honest, you'd look much better
in a eunuch's uniform.
- Hey, you punk.
- Jae Suk.
You little punk.
(Eunuch Jae Suk
gets his makeup done.)
(Grand Prince Jae Suk
Didn't Grand Prince Suyang
have a really manly beard?
- What?
- Wait a minute.
Grand Prince Suyang never
looked like a eunuch.
(Tiny mustache)
- Will you be quiet?
- I mean, your mustache...
They look like whiskers on a rat.
Just keep going.
What do they know?
(He wears a cast.)
Kwang Soo, did you hurt your arm?
No, I didn't hurt it for real.
- It's for my role.
- You didn't hurt your arm?
No, I didn't.
- Hello.
- Who is that?
- Who is he supposed to be?
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Who is he?
- Look at you.
- What is that?
Hello. Hello.
- Who are you?
- "I Saw the Devil".
- He's Han Ki Beom.
- No, wait.
- You're Ki Beom.
- No, I'm not.
(It's like we invited him
as a guest on the show.)
No, I'm not him.
Choi Min Sik played this role
in "I Saw the Devil."
- No, it's not that.
- He looks just like him.
- So Min, what's your number?
- It's too early to tell.
I picked number four.
- It's too early to tell?
- We can't be sure yet.
(He looks at the board
and glances at So Min.)
So Min, you're Oh Dae Su.
- You're Oh Dae Su.
- Are you serious?
What am I?
Number 1 and 3 are already taken.
You're only left
with numbers 2 and 4.
- You need to pick...
- What are they?
I obviously can't tell you that.
I'm sorry about this.
But when I count to three,
can you just pick one for me?
In 1, 2, 3!
Two!
(The producer picks number two.)
Then I'll go with number four.
(Then I'll go with number four.)
(So Min tried to outsmart
the producer and picked Oh Dae Su.)
You picked number four, So Min.
Why am I the only guy?
One of the guys picked
a female role as well.
- But the others are all females.
- I'm Agui!
I'm Agui!
I picked number four, right?
- I'm Jiang Chen.
- I chose number eight.
- I just need to slick my hair back.
- What number did you pick?
I need to play Mother?
I picked number eight.
- Suk Jin, you're Mother?
- I need to dress up as Kim Hye Ja?
Hey!
Why are do you keep
doing this to me?
You picked that number.
This is going to be hard.
Shouldn't he be
a grandmother instead?
- Grandmother.
- Hey.
Hey, Kim Hye Ja is older than I am.
- It suits you.
- The outfit is nice, right?
Don't I look okay in this?
- It's nice.
- It looks really nice.
You should always dress like this.
- It looks good on you.
- You want me to dress like this?
So Min, you look
so much better in that suit.
- Really?
- It really suits you.
But I have to say,
judging by Jae Suk's looks,
he wouldn't have been
an aristocrat...
if he were born a long time ago.
(He wouldn't have been
an aristocrat.)
You wouldn't have been
someone with power.
- You'd be a commoner.
- He'd always be bowing to people.
(He's always be bowing to people.)
He'd always be
following his master around.
He'd always be so busy.
This is so annoying.
Why does this look good on me?
(Laughing)
- Granny.
- Why does this look good on me?
(He really looks
like a grandmother.)
- This is so annoying.
- Look at his legs.
- His legs fit perfectly.
- I thought you just came from home.
(Slim)
I thought you just came from home.
I thought it was your own outfit.
- You should...
- Stop laughing.
You should dress
like this more often.
- Why do I look good in this?
- I almost cried.
- Gosh, I shouldn't laugh.
I wanted to be a zombie or something
that makes me look intimidating.
You look more intimidating.
I'll be honest.
You look more intimidating
than anyone here.
(He can suppress the zombie
with his looks.)
I got so angry
when I looked in the mirror...
because the outfit looked
so good on me.
I don't think I need any makeup.
- Your wig.
- I think the wig will do.
Yes, you can start with the zombie.
He already looks old enough.
(He already looks old enough.)
(His makeup is all done.)
Sit down.
Did you get your makeup done
before you came here?
(Already prepared)
(Aging makeup)
He's been getting ready for today.
- Jong Kook.
- You look great.
- You look amazing.
- He looks so normal.
- I still need to get my makeup.
- You need to get your makeup.
If I see him outside,
I'd run for my life.
- I'm serious.
- Look at that fit.
Your hair looks really nice today.
- Jong Kook, you look amazing.
- You look great.
But I still need to get
my makeup done.
But you look so great.
Your hair...
(Laughs)
I mean...
- I wanted to be Oh Dae Su.
- You kind of...
You kind of look like An Young Mi.
(She looks like An Young Mi
in the process of her makeover.)
Hey, everyone looks funny here.
Look at Kwang Soo.
Hey, Kwang Soo got hurt.
I didn't get hurt for real.
- Don't lie.
- I didn't get hurt.
- He hurt his arm.
- This is just a prop.
He came to the shoot
even though he got hurt.
He came to earn money.
No, it's not that.
- It's not?
- It's just a prop.
(He suddenly makes Kwang Soo
seem like he's crazy about money.)
- Ji Hyo.
- You look so pretty.
- What are you?
- Ma'am.
(Song Geum Ja is here.)
Ma'am.
(She also looks exactly like
the character she chose.)
- My gosh, my outfit is too...
- My gosh, Se Chan.
Se Chan, what are you?
(He's getting
his zombie makeup done.)
- What?
- What are you?
- Oh, you're a zombie?
- Hey, are you...
Are you a beggar?
You look more like
a homeless beggar.
I look like I didn't wash.
Are you guys roommates?
- No, I'm not like him.
- Do you live together?
I'm not filthy like him.
Hey, stop it. Kwang Soo is hurt.
No, I'm not! I didn't get hurt!
He's not well.
- No, I'm fine!
- What's the matter with him?
- I didn't get hurt!
- He hurt himself.
This is just a prop!
How many times did I tell you?
It's just a prop.
Kwang Soo got hurt.
- No, I didn't.
- He's hurt.
No, this is makeup.
Suk Jin, So Min, you,
and Kwang Soo...
all live together.
(All four of them...)
(look shabby.)
- I'm serious.
- It's like "Parasite."
Their lives are tough.
They live in a boarding house.
Come on.
(He's taking a photo of So Min.)
(Laughing)
(Why is he laughing?)
Darn it.
What is this?
(Laughing)
Isn't this too much?
- Come on.
- This is hilarious.
What are you doing?
- So Min.
- Come on.
(She turns her head.)
(Jong Kook bursts into laughter.)
(He's at a loss for words.)
Gosh, So Min.
What should we do with her?
- My gosh.
- She is hilarious.
(All the members complete
their transformation.)
- Hey.
- Yes?
You look really scary as well.
I wanted to be Madam Jeong.
- Who's Mr. Baek?
- It's our guest.
What a shame.
(2019 Running Man's
Ggannes Film Festival)
(The biggest film festival
is being held in Sangam-dong,)
(and countless celebrities
have attended.)
(The red carpet is on fire.)
(This is the highlight
of this festival.)
Okay.
This is a film festival.
And we're dressed like this?
My goodness.
(Grandmother from "Mother")
I can't believe this.
(Jeon Dae Su from "Old Boy",
Song Geum Ja from "Lady Vengeance")
(Yang Zombie from "Train to Busan")
Get out of the way!
(He improvises.)
- You just hit me.
- Zombies don't feel pain.
- They don't?
- They get back up.
- What is this?
- Aren't those long johns?
She wore this.
(These scene-stealers
have gathered together.)
Do I have the face of a king?
No, I swear. You don't.
Haha looks like Agui got struck
with lightning...
and turned into a kid.
(He's become small-sized.)
- He's become a kid.
- A kid?
- He's just a kid.
- Daddy.
- He's not Agui.
- That's not Agui's hairstyle.
You have a hunched back.
- Jong Kook looks frightening.
- He does.
He's so scary.
There are many people like him
in Mexico.
He looks like a South American.
He looks like a character
from "Narcos."
- Right.
- I bet he has a gun in his pocket.
(I've seen him before.)
I bet.
- No.
- Hey.
Come here, Pomeranian.
- He's a zombie.
(Barking)
(This kid has a Pomeranian.)
She played along with it.
She did.
She looks hilarious.
Jong Kook has started
his nationwide concert.
It started on December 14.
- Isn't the tour called "Genuine?"
- Yes, that's right.
- December 14?
- Yes.
- It has already started.
- It has begun already.
- We started two days ago.
- You already started.
Yes.
I'm sorry...
- I didn't know.
- That's okay.
I appeared as a guest...
- and as his Turbo partner.
- Right.
I think it was
three stages before mine.
You watched my entire concert?
- I thought I had heard it wrong.
- Why?
All of a sudden,
I heard "Raise Your Voice."
(Jong Kook, Gummy, and Haha
did a collaboration before.)
The one you had performed
with Gummy?
He was singing my part.
(He was singing all of their parts.)
My gosh.
- Really?
- I'm serious.
Meanwhile, he told me to sing
along to Kim Jung Nam's parts!
I'm alive and well!
I was in that green room!
I was the one who sang it,
- Wait.
- but he didn't invite me.
On top of that,
the concert director came to me...
and asked if I was performing it
with Haha.
I said no.
(He refused to perform a duet.)
I said I didn't want him to sing.
Since we're on this topic,
let me say something too.
(Jae Suk wants to add
to the conversation.)
- You know Jeon SORAN, right?
- Yes?
These two are singing it.
(It's a collaboration made
by SORAN, So Min, and Jae Suk.)
These two are singing it.
- Is So Min on Jong Kook's side?
- Hold on.
- Hey. My gosh.
- That's not right.
Where's Jae Suk
in Jeon SORAN and Yoo Jae Suk?
- It's Jeon SORAN and Kim Jong Kook.
- You're right.
- No, we're the National Siblings.
- National Siblings?
- I was disappointed.
- All right.
So Min celebrated
Se Chan's birthday.
- Goodness.
- That isn't it.
- I left a comment.
- I know this. It's a heart.
(This happened?)
That's not it. I didn't know
that it was his birthday.
- So Min.
- I just posted that.
- Don't lie.
- It was just the timing.
I really had no idea.
- Come on.
- I'm serious.
While having beef-bone soup,
I found a heart. I was surprised,
so I posted that photo.
And that day happened to be
his birthday.
- I had no idea.
- Bo Ra told me...
that you enjoy flirting with him.
(After 2 episodes on this show,
Bo Ra said...)
(that So Min enjoyed flirting.)
Bo Ra.
What did Jong Kook write?
"It's a surprise birthday gift
for Se Chan."
- Right.
- I find his actions funny.
He's quite meticulous.
Why do you leave comments...
- on her social media?
- It's not like that.
( - What are you saying?
- My gosh...)
- It's as if he's jealous.
- No.
- Do you like her?
- Her posts...
make me want to leave comments.
Do you know
what will give me goosebumps?
- What?
- If we keep trying...
to root for So Min and Se Chan,
and then one day,
So Min and Jong Kook announce
their marriage.
(Everyone is aghast.)
- What will happen to me?
- Then...
- Don't you get goosebumps?
I'm going to be a hermit
for three years.
- Seriously.
If that happens, I'm going
to take a rest from this show.
- Me too. I'd feel too betrayed.
- They would've fooled us.
- I'd have to take a rest.
- That'd be shocking.
- We will now begin the festival.
- We will?
We have also brought
other guests.
- Really?
- We have guests.
We will bring in
the female guests first.
- Please come on out.
- There was "Welcome to Dongmakgol".
- There was Madam Jeong too.
- Right.
- It's Jun Hyosung.
- Hyosung.
Hyosung!
(She's dressed as Madam Jeong.)
(She is a sexy diva
with 11 years of experience.)
(Being talented, she has also
branched out into acting.)
It's been a long time.
Have you been well?
- Have you been well?
Yes, what about you?
(Who else has visited?)
It's Yoyomi.
- It's Yoyomi.
(This trot singer has dressed up
as Yeo Il.)
(Netizens were the first ones
to recognize her talent.)
(Her cover of Hye Eun Lee's song
has grabbed their attention.)
(Afterward, her song,
"Who is this guy?" became a hit.)
Yoyomi.
- Hey.
- The trot singers have met.
- Hello, Yu San Seul.
- Have you been well?
- Goodness.
- Yu San Seul...
- and Yoyomi have met.
- It suits her.
- Hello.
- Hyosung, come to the center.
- Okay.
- It suits her.
- Yoyomi.
It's been a long time.
- You're right.
- It sure has been.
- It's been ages.
- I know.
- This is your first time here.
- Yes.
- We've talked on the phone.
- This is your first time?
- Yes.
- Are you serious?
Yes.
- You guys are too mean.
- You're too mean.
You're too mean.
Put that back in.
(I won't forgive you all.)
- Stab me instead.
- Come on.
You should've invited her sooner.
It's been 11 years since my debut.
And this is my first time
on this show.
This is unbelievable.
Please say hi, Yoyomi.
Hello, everyone.
I'm a happy virus
and a singing fairy.
- My name is Yoyomi.
- How cute.
- She's so cute. See?
- She is really adorable.
You remember, right?
I told you guys that
she was a promising trot singer,
- didn't I? Right, Jae Suk?
- Hey.
- When did you tell me that?
- Why is your back facing me?
I'm sorry.
My goodness.
- Just step up.
- Come on.
- You should just step up.
- Why do you keep doing that?
Jong Kook, I thought you were
taking out your gun.
- I was startled.
- Me too.
- Why are you doing that?
- I was startled.
I saw Yoyomi for the first time
when she sang...
"Third Han River Bridge"...
- by Hae Eun Lee.
- I watched her singing...
- "You Don't Know".
- She was...
- I was...
- I recognize her!
- I know her.
- At first, I thought...
it was filtered.
She really looks like Hae Eun Lee.
- You're right.
- Right?
- Right.
- Can you sing a bit for us?
Before that,
let's bring out the male guests.
Oh, there are more.
(Let's bring in
the male guests first.)
Suk Jin, come on.
- You were waiting for this moment.
- No, I wasn't.
Why do you always cut me off?
It's not like that.
Who are they?
- They're the male guests.
- Who are they?
Fail to impress me,
and you'll get a taste of my sword.
- Just stab me instead.
- He doesn't suit his character.
He looks too awkward.
- He suddenly changed his voice.
- Who is it?
It's Kyung-hwan?
(Heo Kyung-hwan is dressed up
as Jo Tae Oh from "Veteran.")
(Looking motivated, he appeared
on the show one month ago.)
Hold on.
Why are you in a hurry?
- Yang.
- Yang Se Chan, it's been a while.
Have you washed your face?
Wash your face with cold water.
(He completely ruined
the opening scene.)
- What was that?
- He's known for making...
- his fellow comedians laugh.
- No, I'm not.
I've failed to make this nation
laugh for over 10 years now.
(However...)
(He's come back to save face.)
I'm looking for a chance.
(They're not surprised.)
It's Kyung-hwan?
Who's that behind him?
(Behind the excited Kyung-hwan
is another guest.)
It's Kang Tae Oh.
It's Tae Oh.
I'm sorry.
(He's good-looking and talented.)
I killed him.
(He's acted in various genres.)
(In variety shows, he's showed
his manly and foolish sides.)
- Tae Oh!
- I'll drop this!
It's Tae Oh.
- Hello.
It's Jo Tae Oh and Mr. Baek.
Who are you?
Kyung-hwan, look at you.
(He suddenly stabs him.)
(Exclaiming)
Take that!
They came up with a sketch.
(They're lost in their characters.)
What is it?
- You're right.
- Right?
- It's Mr. Baek.
- Mr. Baek.
- Him and...
- I bet they have more lines.
- It's a sketch.
- Let's wait and see.
What's that expression?
(What's that expression?)
It was wrong of you to seek me out.
What is this?
- It's a sketch.
- What?
They're in the middle
of a boring sketch.
(Awkward and unprepared)
Take that.
You couldn't even do that right?
(Take that!)
- He had more lines.
- Were you Yoo Ah In?
- Yoo Ah In?
- Is that so?
You should've made it
more entertaining.
We were getting there.
Why not add some catchphrases?
It's the worst sketch
I've seen in the past three years.
- It wasn't a sketch.
- It's what it was,
- you know.
- You know.
- We had another scene coming.
- Gosh.
- And so...
- Is that it?
The four will be joining us today.
(Is that it for us?)
Opening acts always fail.
- Quiet now.
- But the producer...
That's enough.
It was the most boring.
Let me first introduce you...
to a rising star
in the trot industry.
It's Park Yeon Ah
who's known as Yoyomi.
- Gosh.
- Yoyomi!
Is Park Yeon Ah your real name?
Yes, that's my real name.
The name suits you.
Is that your usual tone or are you
talking like that on purpose?
- Just so you know...
- It's my usual voice.
This is her first time
on a big variety show.
So this is the character
she made for herself?
- Was it planned?
- It's made-up?
This isn't how you usually talk.
No, this is my usual voice.
- Really?
- Yes,
Yoyomi's voice
is always in this tone.
It's adorable.
Since you're here,
could you perhaps sing...
"Third Han River Bridge"
by Hae Eun Lee...
which I heard on
your personal channel?
The song itself
is actually quite sexy.
I see. So?
It wouldn't quite work
with the outfit I have on.
It's all right. Just look at So Min.
(It's all right.
Just look at So Min.)
- Let her give you courage.
- Is that So Min?
- I look sexy, right?
- That's why...
- See?
- You look like Bob, the painter.
Bob Ross.
Please sing it for us.
Is there a recording ready?
- Is there one?
- I'll sing without one.
- Sure.
- All right.
Here we go.
The river flows
Under the 3rd Han River Bridge
She sounds just like Hae Eun Lee.
(She sounds the same.)
(She touches our hearts even
without instrumental accompaniment.)
(You'd believe that
she's living her 2nd life.)
(Nice!)
Did you hear that?
She sounded just like Hae Eun Lee.
Their voices are identical.
She even looks like Hae Eun Lee too.
Despite her sweet looks though,
she's not as young as you think.
- How old is she?
- In her early 20s?
I'm 26.
She looks 26 too.
(I'm 26.)
That's exactly how she seems.
Did you have
to make things awkward for her?
He looks meaner in that outfit too.
- That's not what I meant.
- Lady!
- Lady, seriously?
- She's not 30...
- Grandma!
- I would've been surprised...
if she were 32.
- What's wrong with her?
- Tell me about it.
Yoyomi, I'm sorry about that.
- Well...
- This is hilarious.
I asked her to sing
"Third Han River Bridge" just now,
but could you sing
about two songs more?
- Two more?
- Yes.
- No instrumental accompaniment?
- Of course.
Your agency wasn't prepared at all.
(He's upset.)
Hold on.
- Lady, what's wrong with you?
- Seriously?
- Just think about it.
- Who are you to say that?
I hate that she's losing out
on a good opportunity.
She's a mean old lady.
Give her a snack to shut her up.
It's a chance
to get herself noticed.
You should worry about
getting yourself noticed instead.
It's a chance to
get yourself noticed.
- Right.
- Get yourself noticed more.
I've already promoted myself
as much as I can.
Keep showing your back to me
and I'll knock you out.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
- Stop it, all right?
- Jiang Chen.
- Don't hold it in.
- I'll knock you out.
Next is the actress
we haven't seen in 11 years.
- Goodness.
- We should apologize first.
- Right?
- Exactly.
It's Jun Hyosung.
- Goodness.
- Hello, everyone.
- It's been a while.
- Long time no see.
For the first time in 11 years...
Tell me about it.
I'd first like to ask
how you've been doing.
- I see.
- What have you been up to?
I've been squeezing myself
and working hard.
Recently...
a web drama series...
They're all like that after
being in the industry for 10 years.
What does she mean
when she says "squeezing herself"?
After 10 years in the industry...
It's nice to know they're human too.
- Unlike her K-pop idol days...
- I love it.
K-pop idols have to refrain
from saying certain things.
- Of course.
- They can't cross the line.
Recently, I released
a song for my fans.
- Really?
- A song?
- It's called "Starlight."
- "Starlight"?
"Starlight".
I wrote it myself.
Kyung-hwan, please listen
when others are talking.
(Kyung-hwan, please listen
when others are talking.)
(Busted)
You're thinking about
your own interview, right?
His mind is still on his sketch.
It's because he failed at it.
Stop thinking about
your own interview.
I heard him say that
they should try again.
- Was it obvious?
- Very.
- I just hated the opening sketch.
- I know.
I'm deeply upset right now.
Don't worry. The viewers won't know.
Really?
- They won't know?
- I'll pay attention.
(Hyosung released "Starlight"
for her fans...)
(to celebrate her 10th year
in the industry.)
You always give me the light
(To no instrumental accompaniment,)
(she sings her heart out
for her fans.)
Why is there no
instrumental accompaniment though?
- What?
- Come prepared, guys!
- How's that important?
- Just let her sing.
I understand Yoyomi
since she's a rookie,
but why didn't you
come prepared either?
Must you brag about being signed
to a decent agency like that?
We're all signed by decent agencies.
Unbelievable.
That was hilarious.
We'll wrap up the sneak peek
of "Starlight" then.
- I want to hear more though.
- Sing a little more.
- Look after Hyosung, will you?
- Don't be like that.
- She sang enough.
- She barely reached the climax.
- Hyosung...
- We should...
Could you do it again
if you're asked to?
- Sorry?
- Your song, I mean.
You should worry about yourself.
What's wrong with him today?
We were all thinking that.
Stick to doing well yourself.
I'm trying to do my best,
- you know.
- You know.
Can we ask you to do
a voice impression of Kim Hye Soo?
(He asks her on the spot.)
(Out of the blue?)
Madam Jeong from "Tazza"?
- You're Madam Jeong today?
- Yes.
I thought you were
dressed as my mom.
(I thought you were
dressed as my mom.)
Your mom?
- Haha's mom.
- She's dressed like my mom.
"Get lucky this year."
(Get lucky this year.)
(She ended up doing
a voice impression of Haha's mom.)
That's actually better though.
It's easier.
I wish it had been
more entertaining though.
- What?
- Hold on.
- Was that your inner voice?
- Jae Suk.
You shouldn't have...
- said it out loud.
- She's fine, you know.
Why don't I just dance
to some music?
We'll give you some music then...
- since you're a great dancer.
- Of course.
- Good luck.
- Goodness.
No one is better than her
at striking powerful moves.
(She's off to an electric start.)
- Her moves are different.
- Exactly.
(Their faces tell us
how good her dancing is.)
Her expression changed
as soon as she started to dance.
She sure is different.
I love that move.
(They all exclaim in awe.)
Lucky her.
She's such a great dancer.
(Her sexiness isn't something
everyone can mimic.)
It's amazing.
(Her sexiness isn't something
everyone can mimic.)
(I'd love to try that too.)
- No way.
- Isn't she good?
She's amazing.
(She commands the festival
with her dancing.)
Jun Hyosung is back!
She's so cool.
- Welcome, Hyosung.
- You were incredible.
- So...
- My goodness.
Hyosung,
the good daughter and singer.
- She's the best.
- No way.
- That was the best.
- This move.
I thought it was cool.
This was my favorite move.
- So Min, how does it go again?
- Show us.
(I loved this move!)
- Unbelievable.
- That move was incredible.
It's hilarious to see her dance
in that disguise.
You looked exactly
like the character you're playing.
(It was like watching "Old Boy.")
That's how Oh Dae Su smiles
in "Old Boy."
- Are you all right?
- Sorry?
- What...
- You're hurting.
- I'm only playing a character.
Kwang Soo was injured.
- No, I'm fine.
- Then go home.
I'm good.
- This is hilarious.
- He should go home?
I should get rid
of at least one competitor.
I'm fine, everyone.
It's just how my character is.
Right.
Gosh, this is hilarious.
Next, we have Heo Kyung-hwan.
(Next up is the nervous
Kyung-hwan.)
I'm back after a month.
A month ago, you joined us
for a legendary episode.
The one with the Coughing Ghost
and Clacking Ghost.
I played an active part
in that episode.
- What?
- It's why I'm back.
You're now active as a member
of MAHEUN5.
- We mentioned it that day.
- Right.
- I even sang the song.
- But it was edited out.
- That's right.
- It was edited out?
The camera crane was used
to shoot the performance, but...
It didn't properly air.
Now that you've officially
released your song,
let's see you perform it.
Finally, we're seeing it
on Running Man.
It'll be a first for me.
- Me too.
- Finally, it'll be on Running Man.
Make it fun so that
it doesn't get edited out.
We released the song as singers,
so we're dead serious.
I see. Show us then.
(Because he's serious,
we're worried it wouldn't be fun.)
(Will he be able
to grasp his second chance?)
Look at me,
is this the face of a 40-year-old?
I'm experiencing deja vu.
Why do I feel like
I've seen this before?
- Was it in my dreams?
- Can you drag him out?
- Kyung-hwan, we have this footage.
- Drag him out.
We have a video of you
performing that.
- Even the angles were the same.
- We have the same footage.
- Then play that footage!
- Also...
- Can't you do better?
- Why won't you play it?
- I mean...
- The pronunciation was off.
(What's with the pronunciation?)
Look at me
- That's how he was like.
- Is it French?
- My part sounded weak.
- All right then.
Perform the choreography for us too.
I have high hopes for the EDM remix.
Let's do this.
Kyung-hwan, believe in the song.
(The beat picks up
and they all get excited.)
- Bring up the excitement.
- Here we go then.
Look at me,
is this the face of a 40-year-old?
(Seriously?)
(His dance lacks creativity
and is old-fashioned.)
Isn't that what he used to do
years ago?
Wait.
Why did they turn down the volume?
Why did they turn it down?
He did it on his own.
- No one told him to.
- You're mean.
- Why was it turned down?
- This is scary.
The sound director turned it down
on his own.
The dance was a bit disappointing.
- It was disappointing. Hyosung.
- Yes.
You're a great dancer.
Can you dance to this song?
That sounds fun.
- Do something powerful.
- Show us your version.
Please play it again.
This is more like it.
(Yes, this is more like it.)
(Kyung-hwan copies her
immediately.)
It's the same song.
(Powerful and sexy)
(Kyung-hwan tries to steal
attention by singing.)
This song should have been hers.
Anyway, thank you, everyone.
Can we see this on TV?
- Can this air? Tell us.
- Please.
- Hyosung saved it.
I'm relieved.
- I mean...
All I did is dance, and you're
skipping three sheets of script.
Does that mean you're skipping
questions for me?
Unfortunately,
we have to wrap things up here.
Why is it always unfortunate?
- Ask him more questions.
- I don't have any.
That's too bad.
The interview with Heo Kyung-hwan.
- Fail!
Please let me be on the show again
in six months.
All right. We're sorry.
Now let's talk to actor...
Kang Tae Oh.
- He's so good-looking.
- He's handsome.
He looks good even in that wig.
You recently appeared
in the drama, "The Tale of Nokdu."
You've become a lot more popular
thanks to the drama, right?
(He shakes his head.)
(I'm not sure.)
- He's honest.
- Then...
Jae Suk is skipping one more sheet.
Just say you have.
Well...
He can't lie.
Tae Oh belongs to the actors' group,
Surprise.
- That's right.
- Seo Kang Jun...
With Seo Kang Jun, Gong Myoung,
Lee Tae Hwan, and Yoo Il.
- With Gong Myoung.
- Yes.
Why did you do all this?
In addition to acting,
- you learned dance too?
- Dance?
- You said it in the interview.
- Well...
I did learn it,
but I'm not very talented
at singing and dancing.
But the other guests danced too.
- Show us a little.
- Okay.
Just dance the way you want.
This song?
"Catallena"?
("Catallena" by Orange Caramel)
He looks so serious.
(His facial expression changes
completely.)
What's this dance?
- That looks cool.
- It's a new version.
(Left and right)
It's new.
It's classy.
- It's very classy.
- It suits his outfit.
(But...)
What is this?
It suits his outfit.
- What is this?
- It suits his outfit.
(Stiff)
What is this?
(Shocked)
(He's extremely serious.)
It looks so silly.
(He's the new dancing machine.)
I thought I was seeing things.
(The dancing machine did
exactly what he learned.)
I thought he was going
to smack the floor with his head.
- I'm shocked.
- You're good.
You went down this low.
- I loved it.
- I was so shocked.
(Unlike Kyung-hwan,
he managed to make everyone laugh.)
- Tae Oh, I loved this.
- You're good.
- Do it again to another song.
- The compression dance.
It looks even funnier
because of that wig.
It's funny because he looks serious.
It was completely my style.
On "X-Man", it would have been
popular for two months.
- Can he dance to this song?
- It's a recent song.
To "Touch My Body"?
Good.
- Here we go.
- He's getting started.
He's warming up.
He's so good!
(The popping dance begins.)
(The song has changed,
but his movements are the same.)
Good job.
(It's officially
the dance of the year.)
That's so funny.
- He's talented.
- He's amazing.
- He's incredible.
- He's something.
I haven't laughed because
of someone's dance in a while.
So Min is showing an interest.
(So Min's last target of the year)
So Min is suddenly showing
an interest.
(Jealous)
- That was hilarious.
- You're incredible.
Kyung-hwan...
It's not going so well for him.
- Try again.
- What's with your face?
- He looks so unhappy.
- I just remembered something.
- What's wrong?
- It's a family matter.
- I mean, his dance...
- Yes.
It shows that he took dance lessons.
It's what you learn
in the beginning. Isolations.
- That's what he did.
- You're right. Isolations.
You look like a director
of a dance academy.
Her outfit...
- "Get lucky this year."
- You look like a director.
"I heard we have someone new."
(Director Jun discovered Tae Oh.)
Including Yoyomi,
you guys could do a show together.
(You guys could do a show together.)
They look scary.
He should be included too.
No, not me.
- Go stand there.
- Not me.
- Kwang Soo should be there too.
- No.
- Come.
- They look so scary.
Join us.
- They look horrifying.
- We're Team Parasite.
(The interview is over.)
It's time to begin the race.
But before that,
let's watch a video prepared for
the Ggannes Film Festival.
Here we go.
- "Poor"...
- "Connection"...
- "Movie World".
Hello, I'm Kim Yoon Sang.
Hello, I'm Joo Si Eun.
- "Poor Connection Movie World"?
- "Movie World"?
Asia's largest film festival,
Ggannes Film Festival, opened
in Sangam-dong, Seoul, today.
The opening was attended...
by the world's greatest
actors and actresses.
To celebrate
the Ggannes Film Festival,
two of Korea's greatest movie
directors are on the line.
- Movie directors?
- They are?
- They must be busy.
- They are.
So who are these movie directors?
Let's find out.
- Hello.
I'm the director of "A Hint to You,"
which will be released soon.
Hello, everyone.
- "A Hint to You"?
Congratulations on the opening
of the Ggannes Film Festival.
I believe the festival will
be an encouragement...
to everyone
in the Korean movie world.
Can I add something?
Why did you guys
turn down our movies?
We've sent you
countless movie scenarios so far,
and you never said yes
to any of them.
Why did you guys
turn down our movies?
- What?
(The directors' attitudes
suddenly change.)
(We rejected your movies?)
- They suddenly changed.
- You've always ignored our offers.
Do you think you guys are the only
ones invited to the festival?
We'll be there too. Be prepared.
Especially you, the stuck-up
and obnoxious national actor.
I'll teach you a lesson.
I'm warning you.
(Serious)
(The national actor?)
That was the interview
with the movie directors.
Thank you again...
for the phone interview.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for watching "Poor Connection
Movie World." I'm Joo Si Eun.
I'm Kim Yoon Sang. Thank you.
They're among us.
- They must be here.
- They snuck in here.
So the festival is about
the movies we've turned down.
Why do you suddenly cut in?
- I've been cutting in many times.
- Many times?
This is the year-end special,
The 2019 Ggannes Film Festival:
The Uninvited One.
You're actors invited
to the festival.
Among you are two directors who
have been turned down every time...
because of their silly scenarios...
and one national actor
who is popular all over the nation.
- One person?
- If the actors find...
and eliminate the two directors,
they win.
If the directors find and eliminate
the national actor,
the race comes to an end
and the directors win.
The losers will be penalized.
Your mission bags
will be handed out.
Spread to different places...
and check your roles,
which are hidden underneath...
- the mini name tags.
- Our roles are hidden there?
- Get your bags.
- They're hidden here?
All right.
Underneath this name tag?
(Careful)
(It's hard to tell.)
(Who are the two directors
and the one national actor?)
The first mission
where you can win hints is...
Movies through the Hole.
Three teams of four will compete
with each other...
- to get the most questions right.
- I'm good at this.
You'll choose a time point
in the movie,
and the movie will play
for 30 seconds from that point.
But you can only watch the movie
through a hole...
in one of the four corners
that you choose.
- I got it.
- We can't see the whole screen?
In every round, we'll count
the number of all the wrong answers.
And the winning team can flick
someone on another team...
just as many times.
The final winners can receive
a hint...
about either the directors
or the national actor.
- Now please decide the teams.
- The teams?
The teams are important.
(Team 1, Team 2, Team 3)
For the first question,
which corner do you choose?
- Let's choose the top-left corner.
- The top-left corner.
Then the hole will be
in the top-left corner.
- We can only see that much?
- It's too small.
Why is it so small?
(They can only see this much.)
- It's way too small.
- Seriously.
(They're so mean.)
- That's...
- It's too small.
If the hole is that small,
we'd have to watch it many times.
- And it'd still be hard.
- Choose a time.
- We have to choose a time?
- Last time,
we did well when we chose
about an hour in.
- Around that point.
- Exactly an hour in.
We choose 58 minutes in.
The movie will play for 30 seconds
from 58 minutes in.
Play it.
(The top-left corner, 58 minutes in)
I see an actor.
(A mustache flashes by.)
I know this.
(I think I know this.)
- Wait.
- I have no idea.
What's that?
- "SBS"?
- Who is that?
- Let me answer!
- Let him answer.
(The clip isn't even over,
and Se Chan wants to answer.)
I think I know.
(The only clue is the mustache.)
(Will he say the correct answer?)
"The Thieves".
You are right.
That's Lee Jung Jae's mustache.
- Really?
- That's Lee Jung Jae's mustache.
- I am 100 percent certain.
- He is right.
(Correct)
- I knew it. I knew it.
- Jong Kook.
- It was Lee Jung Jae's mustache.
- Lee Jung Jae's mustache.
(This part of the screen was shown.)
- For goodness' sake.
- Sorry. Sorry.
I knew it.
It was Lee Jung Jae's mustache.
- Lee Jung Jae's mustache.
- You are good.
- It's before the police come in.
- Right?
- You are good.
Maybe they can see better
from that table.
We can't see much from this table.
- Hold on. Our location is bad.
- Seriously.
They would have been able to see
the top-left corner better.
Let's ignore this round.
They had an advantage.
(You want to ignore this round?)
Seriously. Let's ignore this round.
Don't be ridiculous.
We can't do that.
- You can't do that.
- Let's ignore this round.
- We didn't think this through.
- It was a practice round.
You wouldn't have gotten it right
even if you were here.
I have watched Running Man on TV,
but it's a complete mess in reality.
(It's a complete mess.)
It's usually worse.
We are pretty organized today.
You saw it correctly.
We are nearly the same
on and off camera.
(She figured out the atmosphere.)
Please pick a corner.
- Top-left corner.
Give me the time.
- The time.
- What should we do?
How about 59 minutes?
- Really?
- We choose 59 minutes.
These movies aren't recent.
They are over a decade old.
That's right.
(Top-left corner, 59 minutes)
What is that?
- What?
- What is that?
- Is that the emergency exit?
- The setting is modern day.
Is that the parking lot?
- Is that the moon?
- Hold on.
- That's the parking lot.
- I don't think so.
I think it's
an underground parking lot.
What is that color?
What? It's the shoulder.
It's the shoulder.
- Who is it?
- "New World".
- Let me answer.
- What's the answer?
- They will get finger flicks.
- Can you guess from that much?
Don't talk about finger flicks
when I haven't even answered yet.
Kyung-hwan, say it.
"A Bittersweet Life".
All right.
- One finger flick.
- My goodness.
One finger flick has been added.
- I think I have an idea.
- Go ahead.
Let me answer.
"New World".
Two flicks have been added.
It wasn't "New World."
We're in trouble.
- It's impossible to guess.
- Is that it? Do we get to see more?
- Is that it?
- The next team chooses the time.
- 1 hour and 10 minutes.
- We need to see an actor's face.
- That's right.
We should be able to see faces
at the top-left corner.
- It's a car.
- Car.
- Is that a car?
- Isn't it the rooftop?
Is it the rooftop?
I thought it's inside the car.
- The rooftop.
- What?
- The back.
- Someone with long hair.
(Someone's silhouette passes by.)
It was a ponytail.
Let me answer. "Oldboy".
- I think he is right.
No, no.
- I have no idea.
- This is bad.
- I am frustrated.
- This is fun.
- Let me answer!
- Let me answer.
"Inside Men".
- No.
- It's incorrect.
Four finger flicks have been added.
It may not be a Korean movie.
- It may not be a Korean movie?
- You should have told us sooner.
- I have no idea.
- This is so hard.
- Seriously.
Why does the ceiling look familiar?
- I think it looks familiar too.
- Right?
I have an idea.
"Batman".
(The familiar ceiling)
The ceiling of the place
where he parks his car.
I am sure.
Let me answer.
"Batman".
Please say the exact title.
"Batman Begins".
("Batman Begins" is incorrect.)
- Let me answer!
"The Dark Knight".
It's correct.
("The Dark Knight" is correct.)
(We gave them the answer.)
- We nearly had it.
- They are really good.
- The secret underground lair.
- We did a good job.
(This part of the screen was shown.)
They will hate you for it,
but that's the point of Batman.
He can be the outcast.
We were close.
It has been a while
since I watched it.
(Teasing and being annoying)
We got the answer.
Since five finger flicks
have been accumulated,
why don't you give 1 finger flick
that feels like 5?
- Should we do it?
- Yes. Pick a member.
Kwang Soo has a big forehead.
It's not like that.
You pushed your hair back
for the finger flick.
- They just did it for me.
- Se Chan is good at finger flicks.
- Come on out.
- Whom will you hit?
Hey, we are talking to you.
(Haha has his eyes on someone.)
Would it be okay
if we hit someone in pain?
(Teasing)
I guess we should pick someone
who is already in pain. Come on out.
Hey. I won't say your name.
It's you. Hey.
The man with a bandage
on his forehead.
Excuse me. It's you.
- Me?
- It's you.
You already have a bandage
on your forehead.
- He does look pitiful.
- No, he doesn't.
- Give him 1 finger flick.
- You should hit this way.
- It would be too strong.
It's only one finger flick.
I have gotten
a finger flick from Se Chan.
My brain shook.
I got a bruise.
Just take it.
It's only one finger flick.
Se Chan is really good
at finger flicks.
I am the type to seek revenge.
- Remember that.
- How scary!
Are you trying to intimidate me?
Go ahead.
Sit down.
(Kwang Soo tries to intimidate
with his gaze.)
Remove the bandage. There you go.
My goodness.
Are you getting this on camera?
- Do it from there.
- Can I do it from here?
- Go ahead.
- My goodness.
Here I go.
Should I hold the camera?
Hold his head.
He might move.
This is happening too quickly.
I will give you...
What did he say?
He said he will give me 30 dollars.
30 dollars?
- Do it. Do it.
- Go ahead.
Here I go. I will lightly flick
your forehead,
put your bandage back on, and leave.
- Let's go!
- Okay. Here I go.
Let's go.
(People gave shocking accounts
of Se Chan's finger flick.)
(How powerful will it be?)
(Smack)
The bandage.
(It really wakes him up.)
(Shocked)
It hurts so badly.
- There you go.
- It was a light flick.
It was a light flick.
(If that was a light flick...)
- It hurts so badly.
- I heard the watermelon crack.
His head didn't crack.
It was a light flick.
The sound was terrifying.
Getting flicked on the forehead
made me pee a little.
(He still feels dizzy.)
(The wonders of the body)
Seriously.
It was a fascinating experience.
After I got flicked on the forehead,
(He reveals
his fascinating experience.)
a bit of it came out.
This is what people mean
when they say, "I wet my pants."
That's right,
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo,
if we want to see your revenge,
- we must save up the finger flicks.
- Okay.
- Let's give five wrong answers.
- Let's do it.
It's our turn, right?
(He flicks the table.)
(He practices like
it's the real deal.)
That was powerful, right?
That hurt, right?
I was so surprised.
Kwang Soo is annoyed.
I think my middle finger broke.
Seriously.
I flicked the table to practice
because I was angry.
I hit too hard by mistake.
- My goodness.
- My finger is shaking.
His finger is shaking.
His stupidity goes well
with the costume.
- I was surprised.
- He was surprised.
He hit so hard.
Please pick a corner.
We pick...
Top-left corner.
- Top-left corner.
- Let's do this.
- 35 minutes.
(I will get this right
no matter what.)
35 minutes.
- 35 minutes.
- This is bad.
I will get this right
and hit him again.
This is scary.
- What is that?
- Let's do this.
What? Say anything.
- A gun.
- It's a gun.
It looks old.
The screen is shaking.
(The resolution doesn't belong
to the latest movie.)
- The setting is ancient times.
- No, no.
- I see a utility pole.
- Let me answer.
"Tunnel".
- It's incorrect.
- Let me answer.
"Peppermint Candy".
- Okay.
- Let me answer. "The Terminator".
- What?
- It's correct!
("The Terminator" is an old movie
that involves guns.)
The same team can't answer
twice in a row.
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer. "The Terminator".
("The Terminator" is incorrect.)
"The Terminator".
(They failed to steal the answer.)
For goodness' sake.
(The producer fooled her.)
- Are you toying with us?
- Let me answer.
Are you toying with us?
- "Terminator 2".
("Terminator 2" is incorrect.)
- 4 finger flicks.
- We saved up 4 finger flicks.
Let's watch a little more.
There is a building.
- Is that the sea? What is that?
- That's not the sea.
- It's really old.
- It seems to be an old movie.
- Seriously.
(Other than the movie being old,
they don't have a clue.)
Let me answer. "Memories of Murder".
- That's right.
- No, no.
- It has that vibe.
- The utility pole and...
- It does.
- It has that vibe, right?
Let me answer.
"Mother".
(Se Chan's attempt
makes this man nervous.)
"A Taxi Driver".
(Se Chan's attempt
makes this man nervous.)
("A Taxi Driver")
- What is it?
- Let me answer.
(Thank goodness.)
Let me answer. "The Terror, Live".
You are naming every movie you know.
(They will go all night long
at this rate.)
- What is it?
- Each team will get one chance.
One chance.
You are naming every movie you know.
It's our turn
to choose the time, right?
I think the setting is in the 80s.
1 hour and 15 minutes.
Play the video.
- What?
- They are fighting.
What?
What is that?
- A coffee cup. A coffee cup.
- Do you see a coffee cup?
- It was red.
- Isn't it "Swiri"?
- Flesh.
- "Swiri"?
Let me answer.
"Swiri".
("Swiri")
(An old movie
with a gun-related action scene)
(Is it "Swiri"?)
("Swiri" is...)
(correct.)
(Suk Jin's team gets a chance
to give a finger flick.)
- "Swiri"?
- How did you get it right?
Tae Oh got it right.
- Really?
- Yes. Tae Oh got it right.
Do we get to hit someone?
(As everyone guessed,
"Swiri" was released 20 years ago.)
(The hostage scene on the street
provided a crucial hint.)
Do we get to hit someone?
(His eyes burn.)
(This is a disaster.)
We gave one finger flick earlier.
Let's count 5 finger flicks as 1.
Thus, 2 finger flicks.
Two finger flicks.
(This psychopath
wants to take revenge.)
He practiced a lot.
My goodness.
I will go to you.
- I will go to you. I am scared.
- Look at his eyes.
- I am scared.
I am scared, Jong Kook.
He is so scary.
(I had no idea this would happen.)
It's straight out of a movie.
Se Chan, you are a zombie.
You can distribute the finger flicks
among members.
"Reveal your forehead."
- "Reveal your forehead."
Hold on. My goodness.
Don't hit my eyes.
Wait. I'm scared.
Your eyes.
- I can't hit your eyes?
- Be nice.
(He's asking
if he can't hit Se Chan's eyes.)
- Your eyes are scary.
- I can't hit your eyes?
No, you can't.
- I can't? Fine.
- You look scary.
- Fine.
- Your eyes are scary.
Let's see your forehead.
(Thud)
One more.
- Who else?
- Am I done?
No, sit down.
(Nonsense.)
(Se Chan gets
the second finger flick as well.)
I'll be angry too.
Fine. Sit down.
- I'm a zombie. I can't feel pain.
- Stand.
- Stand?
- Yes.
- Are you hitting me? Can I sit?
- Do it.
- No, just stand.
- Stand?
This is better. Okay, here I go.
(Thud)
- Fine.
- Okay.
Let's do this. I don't feel pain
because I'm a zombie.
(They're so immature.)
I feel no pain at all.
How immature.
- All right.
- This is convenient for us.
It's just between them two.
It's three.
He looks anxious.
- Please get it right.
- Okay.
- Are you all right?
Are you all right?
Tell me which corner you'd like.
I think left is better.
- We'll keep to the top-left corner.
- Okay.
Tell me where you want to start.
- 1 minute 20 seconds?
- 1 hour and 35 minutes.
Play the video.
Let's go.
(I'm going to get it right!)
- It's evening.
- It's probably one of the movies...
we mentioned earlier.
- You can't see anything.
- It's dark.
It's all black.
It's nighttime.
This is only the background,
so you can't tell.
- It's just black. It's dark.
- It's nighttime.
It's darkness.
I have no idea.
Is this a horror movie?
Let me answer.
"Joint Security Area".
We'll keep watching.
Okay, pass. Please give me the time.
52 minutes.
Here's the 52-minute mark.
Halfway point.
- Where's that?
- That's the Joseon Dynasty period.
- "Son of the General"?
- It's a historical drama.
- It's a historical drama?
- Look at the window.
- The pattern.
- Is it?
This is so hard.
(Something just passed.)
Hold on.
- Let me answer.
- Go for it.
- "The Face Reader".
- That's it.
Let me answer.
"The Age of Shadows".
This is not a Korean movie.
- It's not?
- It's not a Korean movie?
It's not?
- Please. I have to get this right.
- Let me answer.
Then 58 minutes.
58 minutes.
Wait. That color.
(Green?)
- Color.
- This movie...
must be really quiet.
That green screen...
(Where did he see the green screen?)
(A foreign movie
with a green screen?)
"The Matrix"?
- That's a good one.
- Good one.
- Good.
- Let me answer.
"The Matrix"?
("The Matrix"...)
(is correct.)
(While everybody is shocked,)
That was amazing.
(somebody is tense.)
Why weren't they jumping?
(They thought this was a historical
drama but it's a simulated reality.)
I won't lie to you, Neo.
That was amazing.
(The finger flick master
gets ready.)
(Come on.)
(Their fates have reversed
once again.)
How did it turn out this way?
There were 9 incorrect answers,
so it's 1 finger flick.
Is this better?
Is this direction good?
- He's calling you.
- Me?
Yes.
Hurry up. Go.
Please have a seat here.
I can't believe they got it right.
You're back.
- My hand hurts.
- What?
It hurts? It's okay.
It won't take long.
- I'm serious.
- It won't take long.
It's just one.
- Can I take this off?
- Sure. It's up to you.
They went back and forth.
I think he'll go at full power.
Se Chan was being nice earlier.
He pulled back only a little.
When you hit me twice,
you were happy.
I'll give you 70 dollars.
He said he'll give me 70 dollars.
(Even 700 won't be enough.)
Fine.
- Just do it.
- Grab your thighs with your hands.
- Do it.
- Let's do this.
- Hold your thighs.
- Go for it.
If I look like I'm in pain,
he'll be even happier.
Fine.
Listen carefully.
(Thud)
(Tearing up)
How do you do that?
- That was strong.
- Are you all right?
That was more like two.
That was two.
- You might be injured.
- That was good. Okay.
How many is this?
Two.
Good. He's okay.
He changed again.
(Look at Kwang Soo.)
When does this game finish?
- He changed again.
- I'm scared.
- Tangsuyuk.
- Here's the last question.
Let's avoid him.
Hey, you didn't need makeup.
- Does it look like makeup?
- Yes.
- Do I have makeup?
I see.
Please give me the time.
55 minutes.
55 minutes?
- Let's watch.
(They pick the top-right corner
for the first time.)
(Top-right corner plays.)
What is that?
That kind of atmosphere and feel.
(This is not a decisive scene.)
Somebody's going back and forth.
- This...
- Let me answer.
- "Sympathy for Lady Vengeance"?
- I think I know.
- Is she right?
- That's one finger flick, right?
One finger flick.
(The finger flick is more important
than the answer.)
Isn't that it?
- What is it?
- Somebody passed by.
Somebody passed by.
(Somebody passed by!)
- Somebody passed by.
- It was a foreigner.
Wasn't it a foreigner?
- Was he Korean?
- I'm not sure.
Let me answer.
"The Chaser".
This team.
Just give a random answer.
"The Battleship Island".
- One more.
- Give me the time.
(Gulping down)
(He's as thirsty as he's worried.)
It's our turn.
Kwang Soo. Let's smile.
What's wrong with you?
Kwang Soo, I'll get it right.
Give him the time.
59 seconds?
- 1 hour...
- 5 minutes.
Five minutes.
(He's exactly like Jang Kyung Chul
from "I Saw the Devil.")
Hey, I think you'll get a movie
for this role.
I have no time for it.
Hey.
(Top-right corner plays
at 1 hour and 5 minutes.)
Sunset.
I see grassland.
Grassland?
(This scene has grassland
in the sunset.)
(What movie is this?)
Let me answer.
"The Wailing".
That was plausible.
- I thought you were right.
- Come on.
Let me answer. "The Host".
Oh, my.
Let me answer. "Harry Potter".
No?
How many wrong answers have
accumulated?
- 9.
It's 2 finger flicks
with 1 more wrong answer.
Please get the right answer.
I will.
Tree.
It's a forest, right?
(It's a movie with the night's sky
and the forest?)
What was that?
For your reference,
that was a decisive scene.
- Really?
- It's just the top-right corner.
Let me answer. "Twilight".
("Twilight" is incorrect.)
(Does Tae Oh have an idea?)
- Let me answer. "Twilight".
- "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"?
(I think you're right.)
- I think you're right.
- Let me answer.
(It's Tae Oh's turn.)
- "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial".
- I think you're right.
(Is there a night's sky
and running in the forest?)
(If he's correct,
Kwang Soo can avenge again.)
("E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"
is correct.)
(Roaring)
The scene was riding a bicycle
to the moon.
Two flicks.
(The scene was flying across
the forest in the night's sky.)
(There was only the background,
so this was a hard question.)
How do you go back and forth?
This is so interesting.
(Their fates have reversed
once again.)
Somebody is looking for you.
Please come this way.
I keep hitting him once
and getting hit twice.
I don't feel good
about Se Chan getting hit.
He's so strong.
- How did this happen to us?
- Kwang Soo.
It's more painful on the side
than the center.
There's a bruise.
- Like this?
- Wait. You'll hurt my eyes.
- What? I'll hurt your eyes?
- Yes.
(He might take a psychopath role
in the near future.)
I'll go for the eyes then.
(Thud)
(That was softer than Se Chan's.)
Se Chan was stronger.
- Se Chan is strong.
- That was weak.
- It doesn't hurt.
- He thinks it's unfair.
(He's possessed by a zombie.)
Keep hitting me. It doesn't hurt.
- That was weak.
- Is this the last game?
- Yes.
- You missed.
(Come out, Jong Kook.)
Is this the last game?
(There was a reason why
the psychopath asked.)
(He wants to hit Jong Kook.)
Thank you.
(Jiang Chen gets invited.)
I can't believe it.
My goodness.
- I can't believe it.
- Thank you.
Kwang Soo is insane.
(He is a true psychopath.)
I can't believe
he is doing this again.
I guess he held grudges.
That came out of nowhere.
(Laughing)
We won't play any games
that involve hitting today, right?
- Okay.
- You know,
Jong Kook absolutely hates
sudden moves like this.
- He is doing this again.
- Unexplainable moves.
Jong Kook absolutely hates those.
How did this happen?
This is rather strange.
Hold on. Your hand should be
on my forehead.
Why are you starting from afar?
I need to gain momentum.
(Must you ask?)
(He wants to hit hard.)
It's hard to understand him.
(Smack)
That annoyed him
without hurting him.
- That annoyed him.
- My goodness.
He hit me with his palm.
- He will remember this.
- Yes.
Of course, I will remember this.
Thank you.
I will remember this.
Team Jong Kook will get a hint
on the national actor or directors.
Our team did nothing.
It's your influence, Kyung-hwan!
I mean...
Choose between the national actor
and directors.
Come to us and we will give you
the hint.
- We need a hint on the directors.
- That's right.
That's the logical choice.
- Haha answered a bit late, right?
- Yes.
- It wasn't like that.
- He got caught.
- I had the same thought.
- Did you realize that?
(Could Haha be a director?)
Please come and check out the hint.
Which hint would you like?
- A hint on the directors.
- Come closer.
So Min looks so cool.
I hope So Min would wear that
regularly.
(Which hint
did Team Jong Kook receive?)
- My goodness.
- We know who the male director is.
(1 director is a man
and 1 director is a woman.)
- My goodness.
- We know who the male director is.
- We figured that one out.
- Seriously.
- Really?
- Yes.
They think it's me.
- All right.
- The hint is on their sexes.
(Who are the directors?)
There are 2 directors
and 1 national actor among you.
- I see.
- That's right.
I figured out
the identity of one director.
- Who is it?
Suk Jin is a director.
Director Jee.
I won't watch his movies.
- I won't watch his movies.
- You will watch them.
You will watch them.
Every movie needs a director.
(Quiet)
(Glaring)
(Kyung-hwan makes
the laughter die down.)
Maybe Kyung-hwan doesn't suit
Running Man.
- What is the problem?
- He is usually funny.
- His hairstyle is the problem.
- To be honest,
- I never liked...
- His hairstyle?
my team.
- Really?
- We never liked you, okay?
Even Jae Suk couldn't give me
enough screen time.
- He watches with enthusiasm,
- Seriously.
but remains speechless.
Since when did you hate me?
Tae Oh,
why did you bring this?
(He is still carrying the spoon
they used to pick a team.)
I lost my chance to give it back.
He is carrying the spoon.
I recognize him now!
- What?
- He is handsome without a wig.
I recognize him now
without the wig.
Didn't you recognize him before?
- He looks completely different.
- Hairstyle matters.
When I said
he looked handsome even in that wig,
- it wasn't true.
- No, it wasn't.
(It wasn't true.)
(Their comment wasn't true.)
- He looks like a different person.
- I know.
(He still looked charming earlier.)
The two of you sat together today.
- It happened that way.
Hyosung was sitting
next to Se Chan earlier.
- So Min pushed her away.
- So Min's hat...
matches the color
of Se Chan's padded jacket.
- Se Chan.
- What?
Why are you sitting at the front
today?
I got on the bus late.
If it's going to be that way,
make an announcement.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Hyosung,
did So Min push you away?
- No.
- I told her to scooch over.
Se Chan told me...
to go away.
(Se Chan's secret operation
is revealed.)
We don't usually tell the guests
to go away.
He says one thing and does another.
Se Chan wanted to sit here.
Se Chan stole glances at Hyosung.
Were you trying
to make So Min jealous?
In my opinion, Se Chan favors
women like Hyosung.
Se Chan favors women like Hyosung.
(The tumultuous romance
at the front row of the minibus)
- Right?
- My goodness.
I took one look...
and figured it out.
It wasn't about So Min.
He made So Min sit there
in order to stare at Hyosung.
It's not like that.
Se Chan doesn't compare to Tae Oh.
Right?
They are trying
to make each other jealous.
In the end,
Tae Oh and Hyosung will date.
(A handsome man
and a pretty woman will date.)
That's right.
- They look good together.
- That's spot-on.
- You attacked with fact.
- They look good together.
Hold on.
I like someone
who gives me a lot of love.
I see.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
Can you give her a lot of love?
I am confident.
Let's go! Let's go! I can do it!
(He shows off his confidence.)
- "Let's go! Let's go!"
- Hey.
This isn't how you reacted
when they asked about me.
- Of course not.
- It's the honest reaction...
versus the fake reaction.
- Don't look at me like that.
- I'm not.
Kyung-hwan can't butt in.
- You know, he isn't...
- I...
as handsome as Tae Oh.
- He is caught in-between.
- I am single too.
He hung his head.
You never know
who women will choose in real life.
I prepared a simple mission to win
an additional hint.
You will get a hint on the directors
if all members succeed.
That means it's impossible.
- It's impossible.
- It will be really hard.
The mission is the Upgraded 3, 6, 9.
It's 3, 6, 9.
Play a game of 3, 6, 9.
- You succeed when you reach 40.
- 40?
When the number contains
3, 6, or 9,
say a word that fits
the given category.
Let's say the category is fruits.
1, 2, pear,
4, 5, strawberry...
It will go like that.
- They are good.
- Is there a lab for the games?
A lab for the games.
It will get really confusing
after 30.
- We can't repeat a word.
- You can't repeat a word.
This is so hard.
If the number is 33,
you must say, "Strawberry, pear."
Say two words.
- You can't pick the same word.
- Two different fruits.
Make sure you remember.
If the number is 33,
you must say, "Strawberry, pear."
(If the number is 33,
you must say, "Strawberry, pear.")
- We know that.
- He just said the same thing.
- Seriously.
I was simply reminding you.
You didn't know.
- Did you know?
- Suk Jin, I know. I know.
- Okay, Jae Suk.
- Suk Jin, I get the game.
When the number is a multiple of 10,
yell, "Hurray."
- What?
- How many rules are there?
- A multiple of 10?
- This is too hard.
Suk Jin will go first.
Go from Hyosung to Jong Kook.
Then go from Ji Hyo to Jae Suk.
That's the order.
What do we do when the number is 30?
What do we do at 30?
- "Hurray."
- Say, "Hurray."
How many times
do we need to tell you?
(Yelling)
- Suk Jin.
- Listen more carefully.
Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, come on.
- Suk Jin, don't be angry.
The category is...
- animals.
- Animals.
- Let's begin.
- 3, 6, 9
- 1.
- 2.
- Giraffe.
- Four.
- Five.
- Chicken.
- 7.
- 8.
Snake.
- Eight.
- Snake.
- Hurray!
- 11.
- 12.
(Suk Jin doesn't answer.)
- What are you doing?
- You are next.
- Didn't you go 1st?
- No, you went 1st.
(Did he alter his memory?)
- Don't make it so obvious.
- Director Jee.
Had you been younger than me,
I would have punched you.
(A punch of love
for better game-playing)
- I am serious.
- I wouldn't have sat still.
This just makes no sense.
- Suk Jin, come to your senses.
- Okay.
- Okay, I will.
- Suk Jin, come to your senses.
Suk Jin, let's go.
- You should go first.
- Okay.
- Go from Hyosung to Jong Kook.
The category is country names.
- Let's begin.
- It's easy.
- 3, 6, 9
- 1.
- 2.
Republic of Korea.
(Yoyomi needs to say "4.")
- 4.
- 4!
Yoyomi.
It was an easy one.
- No, no, no. My brain froze.
- Yoyomi.
- No, no.
- That was so awkward.
- No, no, no.
- Yoyomi.
- That was so awkward.
- Suddenly...
- No. I was in a daze.
- Yoyomi.
- Please pull this down.
- I wasn't paying attention.
Isn't it hot in here?
(Suk Jin takes off
his padded jacket.)
(Se Chan pulls it back up.)
(Why are you putting it back on me?)
- I am hot!
- All right.
- Pull it down.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin is hot.
- I am hot.
Suk Jin, it's andropause.
Andropause!
(He is experiencing
hormonal imbalances.)
- It's andropause.
- Suk Jin is hot.
I am so hot.
When I asked Se Chan to take it off,
he put it back on me.
This isn't working out.
Take out the rule
about the multiples of 10.
- We will take out that rule.
- Okay.
- You mean the rule about "Hurray."
- We don't need to say, "Hurray."
- You don't need to say it.
- It's wrong if you say it.
Then we say a word for 30, right?
- Quiet down.
- What?
(Kwang Soo is asked to quiet down.)
Quiet down.
We need to focus on the game.
This time,
we will start from Kwang Soo.
The category is famous foreigners.
- Famous foreigners?
- Let's go.
Famous foreigners?
The only one he knows is
Alexander Graham Bell.
- 3, 6, 9
- Leave Bell for me!
- 1.
- 2.
Bell.
- 4.
- 5.
Bell.
(Bell is the only one I know.)
Edison.
- 7.
- 8.
(Who else is there?)
- Se Chan.
- That was awkward.
I told you to leave Bell for me!
There is Helen Keller.
- Nightingale.
- Marie Curie.
Marie Curie.
There is Marie Curie.
- Does Napoleon count?
- Of course, he does.
Douglas MacArthur.
Why did you say Bell
when Se Chan asked you not to?
- This is impossible.
- I didn't hear him.
(Ji Hyo could be a director
who wants to thwart their plans.)
- Jae Suk, go first.
- Jae Suk.
(Surprised)
Why are you nervous?
We haven't even begun.
- Am I going first?
- He is nervous.
- Okay.
- All right.
The category is Korean movies.
- Movies.
Let's begin.
- 3, 6, 9
- 1.
- 2.
"Poke..."
"Poke..." "Pokemon".
What was that?
- There are so many movies.
- My bad.
- That was so random.
- What was that, Tae Oh?
I felt the pressure.
There are so many Korean movies.
That was kind of strange, right?
(Staring)
Haha wasn't talking,
and he just did.
(Jong Kook is fixed on Haha today.)
- You said you're not suspicious.
- You said you're not.
You're the director in his heart.
Has it already been decided?
If he says something,
he might get questioned,
so he was resisting all this time.
I think...
this was your timing.
Last time, Jong Kook's guess
was wrong.
Let's see the end of this.
Right? But when Jong Kook doubts
somebody, I get confused.
- I think this is...
- It's not me when I say so.
- But at this point...
- Be quiet.
- Let's be quiet and play the game.
- Fine. Keep doubting me.
Country names this time.
Start with Haha.
- Countries.
- There are so many countries.
- There are so many.
Start.
- 3, 6, 9
- One.
- Republic of Korea.
(1, Republic of Korea)
(He randomly shows his love
for the country.)
(He's agitated.)
- And you think it's me!
- That's my part!
This isn't strange to you?
- Sorry... I got nervous.
- I wanted the camera on me.
- I got really nervous.
- Thailand.
Kyung-hwan's face.
Give Kyung-hwan a chance.
He didn't say a word.
Kyung-hwan's trying so hard
to be funny.
You were number two,
but you got it wrong. It's you.
I was thinking of the categories,
so I thought I had to say it.
My bad.
I'm sure it's him.
- This doesn't make sense.
- It has to be him.
Director Kang and Ha.
You must be so grateful.
(Haha must be grateful to Tae Oh.)
(Me again?)
Haha must be.
Jong Kook. Is it Haha today?
- It's Haha today.
- Is it him?
Gosh, I knew it.
He doesn't know what to do
with his hands. He's doing this.
(His hands are placed politely.)
Should I do this?
(Do I have to do this
for you to not doubt me?)
- Let's start with Suk Jin.
- All right.
- Let's try country names again.
- Slowly. There's no rush.
- Let's go.
- There's no rush.
Start.
- 3, 6, 9
- 1.
- 2.
- Republic of Korea.
- Four.
- Five.
- China.
- 7.
- 8.
- India.
- 10.
- 11.
- 12.
Azerbaijan.
- 14.
- 15.
Chile.
- 17.
- 18.
Korea.
- Hey!
- Yoyomi.
We did Republic of Korea.
- Director Yo.
- I...
Director Yo.
- Director Yo.
- Did we do it?
My gosh.
She's just bad.
If Yoyomi is not the director,
I want her to have a quiz battle
with Ji Hyo.
If she's not.
Kyung-hwan,
have you played this game yet?
He hasn't.
I didn't hear your voice.
Let me talk on the phone first.
Hello?
Hang up.
Just say country names and fruits
you know right now.
I want to eat mangoes in Dubai.
- He wants to eat mangoes in Dubai.
- In Dubai.
- His seat is in the shade too.
- Come down here.
- Come down.
- You're under shade.
That's the only area with shade.
I got pushed away.
- I thought you were a ghost.
- Why is your face so dark?
I want Se Chan's seat.
Let's switch.
This is your last chance.
Let's start with Haha.
- Animals this time.
- That's easy.
That's easy.
Let's go. Start.
- 3, 6, 9
- 1.
- 2.
- Monkey.
- Four.
Five.
- Elephant?
- So Min.
(Time over)
- Elephant?
- So Min.
- You.
- No, no.
- I was thinking of something else.
- Why?
- I'm sleepy.
- Why are you sleepy?
What were you thinking about?
Se Chan?
Were you thinking about him?
- Tae Oh?
- That was odd.
(Were you thinking about him?)
Why is she smiling?
Why are you just smiling?
Say something.
You want his attention.
No, Se Chan...
- So Min and Se Chan.
- What about me?
No, that's not why.
Why did you touch
my fingers earlier?
(Why did you touch
my fingers earlier?)
- What?
- My gosh.
(Why did you touch
my fingers earlier?)
(What's going on?)
Gosh.
What did you just say?
Why would I touch your fingers?
That's nonsense.
How unpleasant.
Hey, rewind the camera.
- Why would I touch her fingers?
- So...
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, how could you?
Jong Kook, she's completely wrong.
- He's a bad guy.
- It wasn't me.
- Stop fooling around.
- Somebody...
Somebody tapped my fingers,
and I looked.
I was wondering what it was,
and it was his fingers.
This is driving me nuts.
- It wasn't me.
- Look.
It was like this,
and you kept on doing this.
You rascal.
You finger killer.
- I didn't touch your hand.
- Was that a signal?
How bold.
(How bold.)
(Is Se Chan bold
when it comes to love?)
Kyung-hwan, can we switch seats?
Hey, it's too late to switch.
You used your fingers?
(That's unbelievable.)
Goodness.
Are you learning the Morse code?
Morse code?
This is exactly what he did.
Tap, tap, tap.
This is Morse code.
- Let's look it up.
- Is this it?
"I love you."
(That's the Morse code.)
(These two old fossils are
happy for them.)
"What do you think?"
So there'll be no hints
regarding the directors.
(They fail to obtain a hint.)
We never won this game
on Running Man.
We have to know who it is.
Everybody was wrong.
Didn't we get many hints though?
I'm suspicious of a few.
Are there two directors?
Yoyomi made three mistakes
in the same situation.
He practically gave it to you.
Tae Oh, what was "Pokemon"?
Directors Kang and Ha.
If it's those two, this is over.
I think there are water balloons.
What's this?
- What's this?
It's a trophy.
I watched you on the bus.
I'm going to give Kyung-hwan
a warning.
- Why?
- You did nothing today.
(You did nothing today.)
(Jae Suk is upset
he's barely there.)
It's not his fault.
- I...
- You're making it worse.
took my back off the seat
multiple times,
but everybody cut it short.
- It's a warning, Kyung-hwan.
- Gosh, today.
He got a warning.
If you get three warnings,
you have to go home.
- Sent off.
- It's important.
- I'll try my best.
- That's our system.
I'll just say I just joined.
- He just joined.
- Okay.
Hold on.
- All right.
- Okay.
(My part starts from now.)
This is a group mission.
This is the second mission
to earn hints about the directors.
It's called Speed Movie Review King.
What's this?
- Movie Review King?
- Movies again?
There are three rounds in total.
Each round has six people...
- completing the mission.
- Okay.
There are 10 questions each round,
and if you get 7 questions or more,
you win.
One person comes forward
and looks at the given movie title.
You must stick your face out and
describe in 1 sentence in 3 seconds.
You win a point
if you get the answer right.
However, you cannot directly mention
the movie title,
the cast or quotes from the movie.
For example,
if the movie is "Harry Potter,"
"A movie where the man without
a nose is obsessed with a boy."
You can say that.
You have to know many movies.
The remaining five players
have to guess the movie title.
If the answer is incorrect,
then the people sitting here can...
throw water balloons at the person
explaining the question.
That's when the answer is incorrect.
It's not easy to explain these.
- Wait. I just got really scared.
- Why?
Tae Oh just smiled like this.
Why are you smiling?
I got really scared.
- Why?
- We were listening and he's like...
Why did you laugh?
(He was explaining the rules.)
(Chuckling)
- Look.
- What's wrong?
- What was that?
- Director Kang.
- What was that, Tae Oh?
- I...
- What was that? Is there a mission?
- Tae Oh.
- Why did you laugh?
- He thinks he was funny.
- What was that?
You're supposed to guess
the movie title.
How's that funny?
- Are we playing this one more time?
- What?
- This is a different game.
Is he crazy?
(Is he crazy?)
- What's wrong with him?
- I got goosebumps.
You can't mention the movie title,
cast, character names or lines.
This is doable.
It can't be unreasonable, right?
- For example?
- The description.
It can't be unreasonable, right?
(As soon as
Kyung-hwan opens this mouth,)
(everybody grows quiet.)
For example?
- Kyung-hwan, you ruined the mood.
- Hey.
Hey.
This is his chance.
Chul Min treats Kyung-hwan...
like Seon Jin now.
He just made a straight face.
- What did you mean?
- Well...
If the description is unreasonable,
people won't guess it right.
- People won't get it right.
- Okay.
He doesn't usually get mad
at guests.
Why are you jumping in?
(He's agitated.)
Just move on.
- He made a straight face.
- Why are you blaming me?
- I got scared again.
- Why?
When we were all laughing,
Tae Oh didn't.
- What's wrong with him?
- What's with this guy?
Director.
("Unanswered Questions",
Two Faces of Tae Oh)
(Everybody was laughing,)
(but he had a straight face.)
("Unanswered Questions",
Two Faces of Tae Oh)
Why didn't you laugh?
Is it a mission?
(Laughing)
What's with you?
(What's with this guy? He's scary.)
What's wrong?
- What's wrong?
- He's scary.
- What's with him?
This is in "Joker."
- That's it.
- It's him.
- Director.
- His neck is red.
I'm really upset.
I wasn't saying anything funny.
- Is that a mission?
- Please be the director.
Tae Oh.
He's supposed to laugh
when other people aren't.
Please pick six people
to play this round.
Six people. Hold on.
Yoyomi, Hyosung,
and Tae Oh.
- Because we're suspicious of them.
- That's right.
- Should we try Haha too?
- He should play.
- Haha should play.
- I'll try my best.
- Kyung-hwan too.
- Okay, good.
Me?
- Just do it.
- You just came. You have to play.
(You just came. You have to play.)
- Of course.
- You just came.
I got the water balloons.
(I'm looking forward to it,
Kyung-hwan)
- Suk Jin too.
- I like it.
Let's start with these six.
(Suk Jin, Haha, Kyung-hwan,
Hyosung, Tae Oh, Yoyomi)
Let's go. Ready...
You have to describe the movie
you see.
- Right.
- We have to guess the answer.
This is easy.
You have three seconds.
Set, go.
(What's the first movie
he has to describe?)
This is a very difficult class
in college.
What?
(This is a difficult class
in college?)
(A difficult class?)
- "Architecture 101".
"Architecture 101".
(Correct)
- Unbelievable.
- Incredible.
- Good job.
- He is a college graduate.
- Haha!
- That was clever.
(Proud)
Nice.
- Unbelievable.
- Good job.
Tae Oh did a good job.
Here he comes, Heo Kyung-hwan!
(The second player is
Heo Kyung-hwan.)
Here he comes,
the incarnation of humor.
The feast of humor.
I'll show you. I'll be funny
and get the question right too.
(I'll make sure this part airs.)
(Kyung-hwan has to describe...)
("The Truman Show.")
("The Truman Show")
He lies.
"Liar".
(He lies? That's it?)
(It's like a lie.)
- What?
(I lied when I said I'd be funny.)
- Kyung-hwan failed.
- What is this?
(The second question fails.)
Fail!
(Even the balloon misses him.)
(Even the balloon ignores him.)
It missed him.
Even the balloon missed him.
- He wasn't hit.
- Even this fails.
- This will be edited out.
- What is this?
It's hard not to be funny
with water balloons.
Why did you aim at my armpit?
It hit my armpit.
It bounced off his face.
- It just burst.
- It should have burst on his face.
- Watch the comedian.
- Be serious.
- Show us.
- Okay. We'll get it right.
Ready, start.
(Suk Jin has to describe
"New World.")
(Well...)
(What is with him?)
- What?
(All he said is an interjection.)
Gosh, what was that?
(They celebrate the comedian's
precious lesson.)
(So this is what
variety shows are about.)
I thought only one of you
was supposed to throw the ballon.
It just slipped my hand.
We didn't decide whose turn it was.
- It slipped my hand.
- We didn't decide.
- Hey, I said I would do it.
- I said I would do it.
I thought it was my turn.
I thought it was my turn too.
I wasn't doing anything.
A candy...
- "Peppermint Candy."
- Well...
(The most suspicious one,
Tae Oh, fails.)
- What is it?
- You don't know this movie?
- Oh, my.
- What is it?
- Nice.
- It's over.
You failed in the 1st round.
Let's move on to the 2nd round.
(Will they be able to
find the directors?)
There are two directors, right?
(Will they be able to
find the directors?)
(A suspicious movement is captured.)
(Using the few hints,)
(they have to find the directors.)
(There is...)
(no easy opponent.)
(The great actors begin
a mind game.)
(They hear something
that shocks everyone.)
(Someone is acting.)
(The situation becomes explosive.)
(No one can be trusted too much.)
(A fierce battle
behind the film festival)
(Will the national actor be safe
from the uninvited ones?)
(Someone is putting on a show.)
(What are the clever tricks
and what is the truth?)
(The Uninvited One)