The weather is great. It's such a nice day today.
- Hello. Hi. - Gosh.
- Hey, what a nice day it is today. - Hello.
- Is it? - You're wearing a summer outfit.
(Jong Kook is the only one wearing a summer outfit.)
- But... - He wears that outfit at home.
This is so comfortable.
That's the outfit he wears at home?
- Hello. - Hi.
The older members went to the restroom.
- Who? - The older members. Seok Jin.
When they get old, they have to watch out for their prostate.
- They have to go there in advance. - Okay.
They must go to the restroom before doing anything important.
I can't talk about this because it's so true.
- But Jong Kook just talks about it. - Of course.
Shouldn't they wear diapers then?
You were taking it slow. I see.
Jae Seok.
You were taking it easy.
- We were just talking. - We were taking it easy.
- You were taking it easy. - Come here.
- I was filming for my channel. - That's great.
- Kwang Soo held an event... - That's right.
for the Children's Day?
- Bumblebee? - Right.
- I'm promoting my movie nowadays. - Bumblebee?
- It was on the Children's Day. - You did it with Ha Kyun.
- You were promoting the movie. - That's right.
If you were wearing that costume, you should've come to my house...
and played with my son, Ji Ho.
- What? - That was an oversight on your end.
Pardon?
- Since you were wearing that... - I mean...
Your house is not far from my place.
- That's true, but... - It would've been nice...
if you came and played with him.
You've become a materialist.
How much more do you want to make?
(How much more do you want to make?)
- Just tell us. Tell us. - "How much more?"
- Gosh. - "How much more?"
Since you wore that outfit, you should learn to share.
You should apologize right now.
I heard you wandered around with the costume on...
after the event.
- Yes, yes. I did that. - Why did you do that?
- To make more money. - To get more attention.
It's not about the money.
(Haha turns him into a materialist again.)
(Kwang Soo the Bumblebee explodes with rage.)
- You wanted to make more money. - I have money.
You wanted to charge 50 cents...
- per photo. - That's enough.
(50 cents per photo, even Ha Kyun and ESom took it)
- 50 cents? - He keeps talking about money.
- Stop it. - 50 cents per photo?
- Why would you say that now? - That's enough.
- You would've done it. - That's enough.
- Unbelievable. - Don't do that next year.
- It wasn't for the money. - Stop it. That's enough.
- You and your money. - That's disappointing.
Ji Hyo, how have you been?
- Me? - She's filming a movie.
- I've been in Jeonju. - The whole week in Jeonju?
- I have to finish first. - When will you finish filming?
- I think we'll finish soon. - Is that so?
- We should go watch it. - Yes.
You should wear that costume and go to the screening.
Come to the movie screening with your costume on.
- I should wear that to your movie? - Will he star in the movie?
- You should go. - Yes, be her guest.
Why do you only wear that for your movie?
Then, whose movie should I wear it for?
You can wear that and support her movie. You'll make money.
Ji Hyo, give him like 50 cents.
- Hey, why would I... - What's that jerk's deal?
(Kwang Soo the Bumblebee explodes.)
(He starts malfunctioning due to the heated discussion of money.)
- I have money. - Stop it. That's enough.
Hear me out.
He keeps talking as if I need more money.
- Just be the bigger man here. - That's enough.
- I didn't do it for the money. - That's enough. Stop it.
Gosh, he keeps bringing up money.
- He keeps mentioning money. - It's because of money.
Well,
Hwan Jin is gone now.
- Cheol Min is back. - Yes.
(Producer Jung Cheol Min is back.)
Cheers!
- Iron Min is back. - Cheers?
- "Iron Min"? - He came back.
- Iron Min. - Iron Min.
My gosh, Iron Min.
You know he'll make this harder on us, right?
- That's true. - He'll torture us.
Yes, it'll be tough for us.
We won't be able to get off work early now.
- I bet he came back with plans. - I'm scared.
Everyone, in May,
families spend time together, and singles go on many dates.
- There are many weddings too. - Right.
I thought about giving you a chance for a special meeting.
- Okay. - Meeting?
("A special meeting?" She's blushing.)
I've prepared a new project today.
- Project? - What's it about?
Running Man has been beloved by the fans for nine years.
The members will prepare...
a fan-meet for the fans. The project is called Nine Years of Running Man.
(The fan-meet of Running Man: Nine Years of Running Man)
- What did you say? - We'll do a fan-meet?
A fan-meet in Korea?
A fan-meet...
You successfully held fan-meets in Asia like Taiwan and Hong Kong.
(To return the generous love from the fans abroad,)
(they held fan-meets in many Asian countries over the 9 years.)
To celebrate the ninth year of the show,
we plan to hold a fan-meet for the fans in Korea in two months.
Really?
We did have many fan-meets abroad,
but we've never done one in Korea.
First, the viewers might be curious about the fan-meets.
I'll show you the schedule of fan-meet you did in Hong Kong.
- This is the actual schedule. - Here it is.
This is the actual schedule.
- This really is our concert. - This really is ours.
This is the concert we held this year.
We did BTOB's "Only One for Me".
(They started off the fan-meet with "Only One for Me".)
We sang this song.
(The much-anticipated first song to greet the foreign fans,)
("Only One for Me")
(Their singing wasn't on a par with their gratitude toward them.)
(This magical song made them sound pretty good though.)
We sang it when we came onto the stage.
- We sang it when we entered. - Right.
- After that, the concert started. - That's right.
For this, Kwang Soo sang...
- "Beautiful life." Do the walk. - "Beautiful life."
I will stay by your side
(He's very embarrassed.)
(Only fans can put up with Kwang Soo's terrible high notes.)
(When he wasn't happy with his singing,)
(he fidgeted with the earbuds, pretending to have a problem.)
(He could only perform thanks to his generous fans.)
- Foreign fans think he's a prince. - That's right.
- We were trying to keep that going. - Prince of Asia.
He sang his own song, "Dang Diggi Bang".
- Se Chan's and So Min's "New Face". - They're so good at that.
- They were so good. - Those two were great.
- Theirs was so much fun. - I thought Se Chan was PSY.
They're good dancers.
Both of them are good.
- Right. - So Min is really good.
And lastly, we do this part with the audience.
- This is the crazy part. - Yes, the crazy part.
- The finale. - Yes, the finale.
We're going to do all of that?
We used this schedule to come up with the fan-meet in Korea,
but we came up with a different schedule.
- You prepared what? - There's another schedule.
- My gosh. - What's that?
"Fan-Meet for Nine Years of Running Man."
- There's a lot on that. - What's that?
What's that?
- What? - Hey, there's a lot.
All right. To prepare for this project,
- we'll have races for four weeks. - What's this?
The new performances you must prepare...
are the group dance of all eight members,
a pair dance that only two of the members will participate,
a joint performance that...
each pair will do with other artists,
and lastly, the group performance with a theme song of the show...
which you will have to write.
- We need to make a theme song too? - We'll write that?
- I always wanted a theme song. - Right.
- I did always want it. - That's true.
Let's talk about the group dance in the first slot.
Is there a group dance you'd like to show your fans?
There's nothing for us to show them.
Yes, there is. We can do a BTS' song.
Their song is too hard to dance to.
- It was so hard. - It's too challenging.
We already learned it.
- We can practice a little more. - Right.
A long time ago, BTS was on our show.
- They did such a terrible mission. - Exactly.
- Right, in the handcart. - That memory still breaks my heart.
(BTS had a tough time on the ground.)
(Spare me, Jong Kook.)
Why did I do that to them?
- Why are you beating yourself up? - Why?
I threw them away.
You took away the handcart from them, right?
But their fans liked it...
because I took off Jungkook's shirt.
- They saw his abs. - Really?
So their fans, ARMY, loved it.
(So their fans, ARMY, loved it.)
- Why are you flattering them? - Hey.
- Those aren't your fans. - You're flattering them.
ARMY, the fans.
We can do a cover for a BTS' song. Or we can research more.
We have a lot of options.
- We do. - However,
you must beat the staff at a match...
to do a performance of your choice.
- We're going up against the staff? - I see.
- What do we do if we lose? - What if we lose?
I'll show you the dance video...
- of the choreography you'll do. - What is it?
- There's a video? - I'm sure it will be a Korean song.
Please take a look.
(What's the group dance recommended by the staff?)
(Running Man's Fan-Meet: Nine Years of Running Man)
(The First Mission: Group Dance)
(1st Nominee: New Urban Dance)
- Urban dance? - Urban dance?
- I see. Urban dance. - My gosh.
(For this dance, genres play no role.)
(You use your own style to dance to trendy pop songs.)
(The dynamic movements stand out in this fast-paced song.)
- Come on. - Come on. That's really hard.
- Jae Seok, this is really hard. - This is too hard.
(The dance becomes more enticing when it's a group dance.)
How are we supposed to do that?
- That's going to be so hard. - It looks really hard.
- I can never pull that off. - Only dancers can pull this off.
Besides, our moves aren't going to look that cool.
(The second nominee is introduced.)
(2nd Nominee: Acrobatic Dance)
- "Acrobatic"? - "Acrobatic"?
- We have no chance at this. - Gosh.
(Let us tell you about this dance with a scary name.)
(The dance combines regular dance moves...)
(with advanced gymnastic moves.)
(Flying)
- My goodness. - We can never pull that off!
("What's that?" They've already given up.)
(Teamwork is the most important factor for this dance.)
If Seok Jin falls from there, it will be a falling accident.
- It will be over for Seok Jin. - How can we do that?
- We can never pull this off. - How can we do this?
- This is impossible. - Who would do that?
- Those are gymnastic moves. - We can't do this.
We have to win the match.
My goodness, we have to win no matter what.
- Mime? - This one?
What's that? It looks interesting.
Hey, this is all about the detail. It's all about the detail.
(Going down)
Hey, this is going to take more than a year.
This is so cool by the way.
(Dancing)
We can even do that now. Look at this. Come here. Come.
Come here. We can do this. Look at this.
Sit down, and try it. Left and right. Start.
Left, right, left, and right.
We did it. We can do this.
- What are you talking? - We can do this one.
- We can pull this off, Se Chan. - You're fooling yourself.
- One. Start. - Start.
Left, right, left, and right.
- We can do this one. - What's this one?
(The fourth dance is introduced.)
That's so cool.
(4th Nominee: Dubstep)
(The dance is based on robot-looking moves to electronic music.)
- That's not in slow motion? - They're not sitting down, right?
It's not in slow motion?
- We have to look cool. - How are we going to do this?
This is so hard.
- But this one... - Hey, we can do this one.
- We can do this. - Come here, Se Chan.
(What?)
See? We did it. Come here, Se Chan.
(That looks somewhat similar.)
- See? We did it. - We can pull this one off.
- We can do this. - We can do it.
- We can do this one. - Yes.
- We can pull this off. - By the way,
- this one is doable. - This one is doable.
But it looks hard.
(Other moves of dubstep intimidate Jae Seok and Se Chan.)
(Starting this point, they can't even copy the moves.)
- My gosh, what an awesome vibe. - This is so cool.
If we can pull that off, we'd look pretty cool, right?
(If the members lose, they will dance one of these at the fan-meet.)
- My gosh. - It was really cool though.
They looked cool when we watched.
The dances looked really cool.
- Watching them was fun. - It's cool because they're good.
Anyway, if we win, we'll get to choose.
- We can choose whatever, right? - If you win, you can choose.
- We have to win no matter what. - We must win.
You'll change into the team uniforms...
and start the race for this project.
- We have to win today. - I must do my best today.
(Which group dance will they get to dance?)
- Hey, Jong Kook. - Yes?
You won't be in an accident, at least.
(You won't be in an accident, at least.)
(The achromatic-color lover came back in a neon color.)
- None of us will be in an accident. - Right.
You look nice all dressed up. You look like a celebrity.
You look lively.
- The uniform gave him a makeover. - Seriously.
- The team uniform is nice. - It gave him a makeover.
(Laughing)
(So Min bursts into laughter as she wanders around in the middle.)
We have to move more.
That was really hurtful.
I just stood there without giving much thought,
but Seok Jin kept pushing me back.
(But Seok Jin kept pushing me back.)
- When did I do that? - Gosh, that was so mean.
When did I do that? I don't remember that. Stop lying.
You filmed that, right? I'm sure you got it on camera.
(So Min stood there without giving it much thought.)
(He tightly blocked the center position.)
(Seok Jin pushed her to the end with his protective instinct.)
- Seriously. - I know what it is.
He pushes you with his shoulders.
Why are you so greedy over petty things?
It's not petty. I was already standing here.
Why did you try to squeeze in?
(Why did you try to squeeze in?)
(Exploding with greed)
Why did you say that?
- Come on, don't be so greedy. - Hold on.
Why is this spot so important?
It's not that.
Everyone.
The group dance is at stake on first episode...
- of the Nine Years of Running Man. - Nine Years of Running Man.
It's Loyalty for the Collateral Race.
What's that?
- Loyalty? - Collateral Race?
- There's "loyalty" again. - Loyalty? Will that work for us?
I'm so nervous whenever I hear that term.
- Can we stay loyal to each other? - My goodness, look at him.
- My goodness, look at him. - No.
- Let's see what it is first. - Come on.
You are given 300 minutes.
There will be eight stops, each with a mission.
Look at the keywords at each stop.
We can pick one.
- If you like the keyword, - Right.
- get off at the stop. - Okay.
You will win if you complete three missions...
in the given time.
(The members will win if they accomplish 3 missions.)
- Three? That's easy. - Seriously?
- That easy? - Okay!
We can spend 100 minutes on 1 mission.
(Jae Seok suddenly barges in.)
Why are you so happy today?
I'm covering Seok Jin's face.
Okay!
Go over there.
(Haha follows.)
We can do it.
(They all cheer in front of Seok Jin.)
(He tries to act nonchalantly while peeking out.)
Look at him.
He peeked.
It was shocking.
You have unlimited attempts to accomplish each mission.
We don't have a limit.
- But we have limited time. - Right.
Right, we do.
If you want to give up on the mission,
pick one member as collateral.
(They can put up a member as collateral.)
We can pick a member?
If that member completes his or her given mission,
it will be acknowledged as your mission accomplished.
(Success of the collateral mission means the success of the game.)
- That's nice. We can do that. - It is.
- Hey. - We can do that.
We should put up someone eligible.
However, the collateral missions won't be easy for you to do.
They will be something unimaginable,
so make a wise decision.
We should put up Seok Jin...
and Kwang Soo as collateral.
(They're the most unreliable members.)
Collateral Yu, what are you talking about?
"Collateral Yu"?
- Collateral Yu sounds nice. - Collateral Yu?
If you fail to succeed in the collateral mission,
a fail sticker will be given.
- Fail sticker? - Three fail stickers will result...
- in the termination of the race. - What?
- It will be the staff's victory. - It's our defeat, no?
(3 fail stickers will end the race.)
- We need to succeed. - The collateral member needs...
to succeed.
There's also a dud stop.
If you choose that stop,
you will immediately receive the fail sticker.
- That's not good. - Does that mean...
we can just pass by that stop?
You can do that.
- Really? - But you must finish three of them.
(Walking)
- We shouldn't get the dud stop. - Okay!
Oh, yes!
(They cheer a lot today.)
We don't know if it'll be a dud.
Hey, at least you're in the group shot.
(Hey, at least you're in the group shot.)
- Hey. - Right.
- How could you say that? - It's okay.
- I hate him the most. - He's in the group shot.
That's right.
That was the cruelest thing I've heard today.
At least you're in the group shot.
We'll head to the first stop now.
- Okay! - Okay!
(They cheer for the last time before getting into the vehicle.)
(The race begins.)
- He's hilarious. - Gosh.
Please start the timer.
- Already? - Already?
- We haven't left yet. - It has started?
(Will they be able to clear 3 missions in the given time?)
Summer is finally here.
It's getting hot.
Seok Jin.
Seok Jin is too weak.
- I'm still stronger than you. - You're so weak.
I'll always be stronger than you.
"I'm still stronger than you."
But we've never actually fought for the past 20 years.
We just keep teasing each other.
"I'm still stronger than you."
(They both hate to feel pain.)
- I'll always be stronger than you. - You'd think...
You'd think we'd fight at least once, but we never have.
- We're here. - Already?
(They arrive at their 1st stop.)
- This is it? - It's the first stop.
- It says "Lunch Telepathy". - Hey.
- Let's go. - "Lunch Telepathy".
(What is this stop's mission?)
Maybe our thoughts...
- need to align. - For example...
Hold on.
There's "lunch" as well.
- I think we can eat here. - Shall we eat?
- I think we're eating here. - We're eating lunch.
- Let's have lunch. - All right.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Please give me an official answer.
Will you get out or pass?
- We'll get out. - We'll go.
Don't say "get out". Say "leave".
(Don't you know it's forbidden to say that?)
Ji Hyo and I don't like the term.
I don't like it.
(Ji Hyo supports him.)
- I'll... - You just caught on.
- I'm going to become cranky. - Hey.
(Flustered)
What do you mean?
You didn't know what it meant!
Will you please stop?
You had no idea what we were talking about.
Okay, let's go!
- You've agreed to leave. - Shall we?
- Okay. - 1, 2, 3.
- We'll leave now. - We'll leave now.
Okay.
Are you sure this is right?
- Let's find out. - Is this...
- Is this... - Fine.
(What kind of mission will be given to them?)
Everyone.
Please choose one person to come out.
(Only one person is allowed to leave.)
- What? - They just want one of us.
- One? - Why?
- Really? - That's how telepathy works.
- Ji Hyo, get out. - Me?
- I'm not good at quizzes. - Just get out.
I'm sure it'll be a quiz.
- Then... - You should leave, Jae Seok.
(They push Jae Seok out.)
(Pushing)
Leave!
Hey!
(Jae Seok is pushed out...)
(after standing in front of the door.)
- Get out. - Hey!
- Go. - Go!
He got out!
What is this?
All right, come here.
I didn't come out willingly. I was coerced.
Please close the door.
- What? - The door will close.
- What is going on? - What should we do?
- Let's watch from here. - Where is he?
What's going on?
(He's left all alone.)
(What is his mission?)
The mission you've chosen is called Lunch Telepathy.
You can do it!
(He cheers for him.)
- You can do it. - Please close the window.
- Please close it. - You can't eavesdrop.
(He obeys.)
He's flustered.
Please choose...
a member who won't come out next.
You'll fail if they do come out.
You'll succeed if they don't.
All eight of you need to succeed.
(They each need to pick someone who won't come out next.)
If that member comes out, you fail immediately.
- So they shouldn't come out. - Correct.
- Then I pass? - Yes.
All eight of you need to succeed.
(Who is least likely to come out next?)
- Yang Se Chan. - Yang Se Chan?
(He picks Se Chan.)
(Se Chan shouldn't come out next.)
(Jae Seok sits down while he waits.)
Please.
(Don't come out, Se Chan.)
Next member, please come out.
(It's time for the next member to come out.)
(Did Jae Seok make the right choice?)
(Next person?)
(Se Chan is spotted rising from his seat.)
(Who will come out next?)
(Fortunately, it's Ji Hyo.)
- Ji Hyo, go next. - Go.
Ji Hyo should go next.
- Go. - Go, Ji Hyo.
(Unaware of the mission, they pick Ji Hyo.)
I hope it's not a quiz.
(He's happy to see her.)
(Jae Seok succeeds.)
He's liking it.
- What? - He's liking it.
- Why is he smiling? - It must be a good thing.
Okay.
(The next candidate is Ji Hyo.)
The mission you've chosen is called Lunch Telepathy.
Please choose a member who won't come out next.
You'll fail if they do come out.
You'll succeed if they don't.
- If they don't come out, I win? - Yes.
- Pick the one who won't come out. - They shouldn't come out.
You can't pick Jae Seok.
- Whom will you pick? - Whom do you pick?
(She needs to pick from the ones in the bus.)
Me.
No, you can't do that.
(She brazenly picks herself.)
- I can't pick myself? - No.
You surprised me.
What was that?
- Ji Hyo. - Seok Jin?
No, I think he'll come out.
Who's sitting in the corner? Is it Jong Kook?
Kwang...
- The one in the very back. - So Min?
I think it's Se Chan.
Se Chan? I picked him too.
(They think he's the least likely to come out.)
- Yang Se Chan. - Okay.
(Se Chan is picked once again.)
Please sit over there.
Please.
Do you get the mission now?
Next member, please come out.
(It's time for the next candidate.)
(If it's Se Chan, they'll all fail.)
(Who has just got off the bus?)
I was so surprised!
- I was so surprised too. - Me too.
(It's Haha.)
Okay.
(The members pick Haha.)
- Haha. - Something feels ominous.
I know. There's a problem.
It feels so ominous.
(The staff is the one who's in trouble.)
(Ji Hyo succeeds.)
Okay. Please pick the member who shouldn't come out next.
You'll fail if they do come out.
Hey, who do you think will come out next?
How were you picked?
This is unbelievable.
We kind of decided on an order.
What is the order?
Should I go first?
- Yes. - Okay.
Should I follow after you?
Yes. All the cunning ones should go first.
Good.
- You should go next. - I'll get ready.
I should go after you.
Okay.
(All three of them said they'd come out next.)
- Wait. - How about Jong Kook?
- I think Seok Jin will come. - No.
Jong Kook might come out next.
I told all the cunning ones to follow after me.
Se Chan.
- He also wants to come out. - We both chose him.
Everyone was getting ready to come out.
(You don't get it.)
This is driving me insane.
What... What is this?
- Jeon... - Whom should we pick?
Jeon So Min.
Don't you think she'll be safe?
Please pick. 1, 2, 3.
Jeon So Min.
(Haha picks So Min.)
(So Min shouldn't come out.)
Jeon So Min.
- Please. - I thought of her too.
So Min will come after this one.
Please, please.
(Who is coming out this time?)
(The next member is...)
(Jong Kook.)
They don't look happy.
(They're relieved.)
- This is good. - Jong Kook.
Please pick a member who shouldn't come out next.
- My goodness. - You'll fail if they do come out.
We chose Se Chan...
and So Min.
We've all succeeded so far.
Whom did you guys decide to send out next?
I was the last one we chose.
- Right. - I told Haha...
- that I'd go after him. - Right.
I remembered correctly.
- One... - Hold on.
You can't look behind you.
But seeing how Se Chan is seated at the corner,
I don't think he'll come out next.
- I think so too. - Pick him.
- Really? Should I pick him? - Yes.
So Min is looking at us.
- She's the closest to the door. - Really?
- Se Chan. - Se Chan.
- Pick Se Chan? - I think that's our best bet.
- Pick him. - Se Chan?
- Yes. - I pick Yang Se Chan.
- All right. - So Min will come out next.
He's not the type to go first.
He only does when he's told to.
- They don't look happy. - Shall we do rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's make it random. - Good thinking.
- The winner goes first. - The winner goes next.
(Why are they playing the rock-paper-scissors now?)
- Rock-paper-scissors? - This is driving me crazy.
Why are they doing that?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(They suddenly decide to pick randomly.)
(Who will come out this time?)
(It's So Min.)
What's wrong? Should I not have come out?
It's So Min.
- My heart skipped a beat. - That was close.
- Good, good. - My goodness.
You can't see anything from out here.
- What's wrong? - All right.
You need to pick a member who shouldn't come out next.
- You'll fail if they do come out. - Seriously?
So Min, how's the vibe in there?
The vibe?
It's suffocating inside, so Seok Jin is frustrated.
- He's struggling in there. - I think...
- you should pick Kwang Soo. - Yes.
- Because of Se Chan... - Pick him.
- They don't know what this is. - Pick him.
But they must think that the last one...
- to come out will lose. - Kwang Soo will want...
to come out last.
1, 2, 3.
Lee Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo shouldn't come out.)
We can't control the outcome. Please.
I don't think Kwang Soo will come out next.
- That's the point. - He shouldn't come out.
- He shouldn't? - No.
(Everyone believes Kwang Soo won't come out.)
Next member, please come out.
(Who will come out this time?)
Is it okay?
(Se Chan comes out.)
You seem to be relieved. What is this?
- See? - So that's how this works?
Yes. You need to pick the one who won't come out.
(They've won 5 consecutive rounds so far.)
(Se Chan is the last one to go.)
- All right. - Okay.
You need to pick either Seok Jin or Kwang Soo.
- The one who'll come out? - If they come out, you fail.
- Kwang Soo will be last. - The last one...
- will be Kwang Soo. - He'll be the last one.
But hear me out. The problem is...
The one who loses the rock-paper-scissors...
is planning to come out next.
They shouldn't do that.
They're planning to do that.
Still, you should listen to us.
- Seok Jin? - Listen to us. Yes.
Kwang Soo.
- Lee Kwang Soo? - Yes.
(Se Chan chooses Kwang Soo who likes to appear last.)
If you pass, the entire team will succeed.
Send Kwang Soo to the corner.
- Next member, please come out. - It can't be Kwang Soo.
(If Se Chan wins, they will succeed in this mission.)
(Who will come out last?)
Already? Goodness.
(If Seok Jin comes out, they'll win. If it's Kwang Soo, they'll lose.)
- Gosh, I can't bear to watch. - I'm about to go insane.
(The next one to come out is...)
(Kwang Soo.)
He's out.
(He's out.)
(They fail their mission.)
(Why did you come out?)
I should've picked Seok Jin.
- What? - Goodness.
(He's confused.)
- He's the worst! - I know.
Why did you come out?
Seok Jin should've come out.
- Go. - Why did you come out?
- Why would you? - Go.
- Go where? - Just go.
- You have all failed. - Just go home.
- What? Why? - Darn it.
(He's lost.)
- Why have we failed? - What was it?
If the person they chose came out next, the team would fail.
So why?
The one you guys chose shouldn't have come out?
- Yes. - And you all passed?
- Yes. - So this was the last round.
- That's right. - Gosh, I was the last one.
(He criticizes him.)
My family will be disappointed in you.
Why are you bringing up your family?
- Why would he say that? - Goodness.
Will you go onto the next round or put up collateral?
- Collateral? - Collateral?
(Will they try again or put up collateral?)
We'll put up collateral.
- We'll pick one of them. - Hold on.
(He points at them.)
(It'll be one of us?)
- Why is it one of us? - Wait a minute.
- Hey! - We didn't know anything!
- Hold on. - What did I do...
- so wrong? - Let's go, Jae Seok!
- Fine, put us up as collateral. - It's 1 of you 2.
Whatever. Put me up as collation.
(His tongue gets twisted.)
- Collation? - What did he say?
- What do you mean? - What's "collation"?
- I meant collateral. - It's collateral.
- Fine, let's put up collateral. - It's either you or Kwang Soo.
Not me.
- But listen to me. - Let me tell you.
- The lateral that... - Lateral?
(He keeps mispronouncing the word.)
(He can't seem to come to his senses.)
- But won't we succeed... - Let's do that.
- Why did you have to play... - in round two?
- rock-paper-scissors? - We were so close.
Will round two be different?
- Yes, it might be. - Right, it might.
- Okay. - Let's move on for now.
- Yes. - But for round two...
(They decide to try again.)
Why did you have to come out?
Please decide on the order.
This is round two of Lunch Telepathy.
One member should come out.
- Go, Kwang Soo. - We need to send him out first.
- I'll be serious. - Kwang Soo.
- Okay. - Hurry up. We have no time.
- Okay. I'll do my best. - Hurry up.
- Hey, hey. - Okay. Okay.
(The first candidate is Kwang Soo.)
I came out first.
Okay.
- Let's see. - Okay.
Watch his reaction.
Why did we send him out first?
Because he's always the one who ruins things.
- He should go first or last. - Right.
- It's better to fail first. - Exactly.
- Here is the mission. - Okay.
You need to guess with which foot...
the next member will step out.
Number 1, left. Number 2, right. Number 3, both.
If you can guess it right, you pass.
If you get it wrong, you fail.
(He's disheartened.)
I shouldn't have come first.
They will put me up as collateral if I don't pass this round.
(He needs to get it right at all costs.)
What should I do?
Okay. Let's just guess.
It's simple. Right, left, or landing on two feet.
Landing on both feet is least likely.
There are two stairs. That means...
They'll turn right and step with their right foot first.
(He thinks they'll land on their left foot.)
Left.
Number one, left. Okay.
This is a scientific approach.
- You can't show them your response. - Okay.
- Don't react. Sit down. - Okay.
(Is his scientific approach correct?)
(He sits down.)
Next candidate, please come out.
This is a scientific approach.
- Should I? - Yes.
- Go. - Okay.
(Haha is the next one.)
Goodness.
(Unaware of the mission, he steps out of the bus.)
(Please land on your left foot.)
(Which foot will he land on?)
(He lands on his left foot as Kwang Soo predicted.)
It's not the same game.
(Kwang Soo's scientific approach was right.)
The game has changed.
(I told you it was scientific.)
(It's Haha's turn.)
For this mission,
you need to guess on which foot the next member will land.
- Number 1, left. Number 2, right. - Darn it!
Number 3, both.
And Kwang Soo guessed it right for you.
Really?
Think scientifically.
- How can this be scientific? - Haha.
Think about the formation of the bus.
Left foot is the most likely one. Both feet are ridiculous.
(He's gullible.)
- Left foot. - Good job.
(Haha chooses left foot.)
You'll get it for sure.
Next candidate, please come out.
- Just try it. - Okay.
- Don't make it too complicated. - I won't.
(Seok Jin is next.)
(Please land on your left foot.)
(He comes down on his left.)
(Suddenly, he switches feet...)
(and safely lands on his left foot.)
(They're relieved.)
They watched him as he came out.
Their reactions are similar to those from the last round.
- I think I know. - They watched him come out.
What is it?
(What do you think it is?)
- Guessing which foot. - What?
They need to guess on which foot we'll land.
I think so because...
- Guessing which feet? - They looked at his feet.
- But we can't do anything. - You're right.
- They looked at his feet. - Right?
- Guess which foot they'll land on. - What?
(Seok Jin is listening to the mission.)
Both of them got it right.
I got it right.
- It's almost always left. - Pick left.
- Think about the bus' formation. - It's almost always left?
The staff has made a mistake.
(If that's so...)
Okay.
I'll choose left foot.
(Seok Jin chooses left foot.)
Left. Yes.
You can't signal anything.
If you say anything, you'll fail immediately.
Even if you get it wrong, it won't be your fault.
- Let's find out. - Next candidate, please come out.
- Ji Hyo? - Go, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - Land on your right.
- Look. - They're looking downwards.
You're right.
(She comes down on her right foot.)
(Do you want this foot?)
(Or do you want this one?)
What's wrong with her?
What's going on with her?
I think she caught onto it.
(What will be her decision?)
Don't look.
(Right? Left?)
(She leaps down.)
(She lands on both of her feet.)
(As a consequence of knowing too much, she fails.)
- What? - Both feet.
- She landed on both feet. - What's wrong with her?
- What are you doing? - What have you done?
- Weren't you guessing which foot? - What have you done?
- You should've just come down. - What is this?
I thought it'd be either left or right, so I landed on both.
- Why would you be weird like that? - Goodness.
- You should've just chose one. - We knew it.
Did she land on both feet?
- I think she did. - She landed like this.
You guys are amazing. They caught onto it.
- How did you know? - How did you know?
You guys kept looking downwards, so she guessed it.
But then, she landed on both of her feet.
My goodness.
Shall we try again?
We'd like to try once more.
- All right, round three then. - Let's do it.
- Let's hurry. - We can do it.
- Let's do it. - Let's go.
- We can win for sure. - Let's hurry.
This is round three of Lunch Telepathy.
One member should come out.
- Go, Se Chan. - Yes, you go first.
Go. Good luck!
Going first is the most important.
- Seriously. - Let's make it this time.
- Okay. - Seriously.
I'm landing on my left foot too.
This is round three of Lunch Telepathy.
(Pressured, Se Chan starts off.)
We will give you a set of initial consonants.
You must make up a word in three seconds.
If you can't, you fail.
And the words may not overlap with the others' answers.
Wait a minute.
- Get ready. - Hold on!
- Get ready. - I don't know the consonants.
- Get ready. No. I'll start. - Give me a minute.
If you can't answer, you lose. Get ready.
Get ready, go.
One,
- "Good job". - two, three, get back to your seat.
I'm doomed.
(I'm doomed.)
This is...
because I have little knowledge.
It was so obvious.
It was so obvious!
Why did I do that?
Next person!
(Who will try next?)
(It's the brain of Running Man, Yu Jae Seok.)
Good.
Get ready.
Go.
1, 2, 3.
"Tabor"!
(That's my Jae Seok.)
"Tabor".
That was difficult.
Next person.
(Se Chan and Jae Seok passed. Who's next?)
(It's Haha. He's similar to Se Chan.)
We're finished.
(We're finished.)
(Is it guessing the right foot again?)
I knew this wasn't it.
I'm going to do it simple.
You all have to say different words with these initial consonants.
(You all have to say different words with these initial consonants.)
You also have to say it in three seconds.
Get ready.
Go.
- One... - "Good job".
(Haha said, "Good job".)
(No!)
- You have failed. - See?
- I told you we're not smart. - Fail!
- Open the door. - Why did you do that?
You have failed round three.
There's "Apple"!
I was going to say that.
But that was the easiest answer.
Round Three was not saying the same words.
That was the mission.
They said, "Good job", "Tabor", and "Good job". And you've failed.
- Se Chan kept telling me... - I told him.
that the ones with little knowledge will say "Good job".
Then Haha said, "Good job" right after.
(Then Haha said the same word in an instant.)
Everyone.
Will you give up or put up collateral?
We're short of time.
We'll put up collateral.
- We have no choice. - Pick a member.
We have to pick the smartest member.
- No. - Seok Jin.
The difficulty depends on the person.
- It depends. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Or should we vote?
Okay, let's vote.
Let's do the whispering votes.
Is there a fixed question,
- or does it depend on the member? - It depends.
(Who will be chosen as the collateral member?)
(Whispering)
He said,
(He's flustered.)
"You do it, punk."
(He whispered, "You do it, punk.")
(He voted with a little push.)
Why did you tell them?
Why did you have to swear?
Why did you swear at me?
No one else could hear it.
3 members have 3, 3, and 1 votes each.
- What? - It's a tie?
Seok Jin has three votes,
I have three votes,
Jong Kook has one vote.
Someone picked Jong Kook?
Right, I didn't vote yet.
Yes.
I vote for Seok Jin.
(He did not think for a moment.)
(He shouldn't have sworn at Jae Seok earlier.)
Seok Jin will be...
- the collateral member. - Okay.
(Seok Jin has been decided as the collateral member.)
- Seok Jin's collateral is... - I wonder what it is.
(What will be his collateral?)
(Cheol Min has already warned them about the collateral.)
(Since they can put up collateral instead of doing a mission,)
(it will be far more difficult than what they can imagine.)
(It will be out of all knowledge.)
(What would be Seok Jin's collateral?)
He needs to call his wife right now,
and tell her the password to his secret account,
expenditures from that account, and one lie he told her.
(He has to confess to his wife.)
(The collateral is out of all knowledge.)
This is it.
(How would I do that?)
- That's too harsh. - That was it?
How is this...
- That's tough. - It is.
When I count to three, you can make your decision.
My secret bank account and what?
The expenditures from that account,
and one big lie you told her.
One big lie?
I never lied to her.
Seok Jin, you can't tell her that.
(You can't tell her that.)
Not that one.
Not the one we know.
- You can't say that on TV. - Seok Jin,
think about it.
- Take your time. - Even if you give up...
Stand by the bus stop and think about it.
Even if you give up,
we'll respect your decision.
- Seok Jin, take your time. - We'll understand.
That's really tough.
It really depends on the person.
(Will he cover everything and give up their mission?)
He seems more discreet than ever.
- He's serious. - Yes.
He's just enjoying the attention he's getting.
(He's enjoying all the cameras filming him.)
(Why did you have to say that?)
Come on!
- Seriously? - Why did you...
Look at him! He's enjoying it.
He's even posing from different angles.
Look, he's even changing his hand gestures.
Seok Jin, time is passing by.
- Hurry up! - Hurry up!
Secret bank account and a lie?
That's fine, the secret account is fine.
But are you going to tell her the lie?
What?
- You're making me look suspicious. - Don't make it bigger than it is.
I didn't told her any lies...
- He's good at fabricating things. - Come on.
Let's go, Seok Jin!
- Cheer up! - You can do this.
- You got this. - One...
I made my decision.
- Is it "O" or "X"? - Make an "O" above your head,
- or an "X" on your chest. - Okay.
One,
(What will he do?)
Three.
I understand.
(He refuses to put up collateral.)
(Now they get their first fail sticker.)
With three of these, the game is over.
Here's your first sticker.
- It's our first. - He does have a secret.
- He's hiding something. - So that lie...
was actually true?
(She's trying to tease him.)
That was true?
When he made the "X", we were all whispering.
What did he lie about?
- This is... - Seok Jin,
it's also weird to say no to this.
I'll call her.
- No. - I have to do this.
Now I see what was weird about it.
- What would she feel like? - I see.
- Right? - He does have a secret account!
It's wrong enough to have a secret bank account,
and you basically told her you won't tell the password.
And you won't tell her a big lie you told her.
- When your wife sees this, - Come to think of it,
- what would she think? - I'd look suspicious.
I don't have all that, honey!
I really don't.
You can keep your secrets.
No, I don't have any secrets!
They're all whispering.
I don't have any!
Honey, I'm as clear as crystal.
You know me!
All right?
Let's get on the bus to get to the next mission.
- Why did you do that? - It became all weird now.
Look at what you've done.
Seok Jin is finished for the day.
(They depart from their first stop.)
What kind of mission was that?
I have nothing to hide.
We should be careful with collateral.
- It's not as easy as we thought. - Yes.
If I told her...
just random numbers and password, how would you guys check it?
- You should have done that. - You should have done that.
Right, and call her afterwards,
and tell her it was just for the show.
That's what you should've done.
You all know how honest I can be.
(You all know how honest I can be.)
- Honest? - Are you serious?
Then why did you made the "X"?
You could have been honest and told her.
I said Cheol Min would make our missions harder.
Let's just move on.
- Yes. - Is it that simple and funny?
- Let's go. - Let's move on.
Let's move on. It's all done with.
Right. That's enough.
It was for the show.
I made the "X" for our show.
- Of course you did. - You were being funny.
- It wouldn't have been funny. - We're here.
(No one can hear him now.)
- it wouldn't have been funny. - We're here.
if I had told random stuff.
(Who am I talking to?)
What's the name? It says "Jeonju Table".
- A table? - There's food.
- It's food. - Everyone!
We have to do this.
Everyone, as we've said,
it could be a mission for lunch, or a dud.
If it's a dud, you get a fail sticker immediately.
Skip this.
There's nothing here, but a piece of paper on the table.
I think the name was a trick.
- Let's pass. - Now,
here's the official question.
Second stop, "Jeonju Table", will you get off, or pass?
- Pass! - Pass!
Okay, pass.
There's nothing but a table with a piece of paper.
- We'll pass by. - Dud?
(Was the 2nd stop a mission or a dud stop?)
(They move on to the 3rd stop.)
- We see things right through. - We're experts.
- We have to win this time. - Right.
Because if we fail again...
I can't do that dance!
You all heard about collateral.
- Right? - Right, it was tough.
It was really shocking.
It says, "Unified Lunch".
- Another lunch? - It's Unified Lunch.
- They're all about food. - Two times in a row.
I think I got it.
It says, "Unified", so we're choosing the same menu.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- We can do this! - I think he's right.
Third stop, "Unified Lunch",
will you get off, or pass?
- We'll get off! - We'll get off!
- Are you sure? - Yes!
I think Haha has a point.
- We're choosing the same menu. - Right.
- Like jjajangmyeon. - Just like last time.
Let's go!
Could it be a dud stop?
You guys must be hungry.
- Yes. - Yes.
- Do you want lunch? - Yes.
At the stop you have chosen, "Unified Lunch",
you will be...
memorizing all 31 words that gets harder by each,
and each person has to say at least one word.
It's Loyalty 31.
- Did he say "memorize"? - Memorize 31 words?
This is bad.
Memorize 31 words that the staff gives you within 2 minutes,
and you win if you say all 31 words after that.
There are no limits...
to the number of words a person can say.
You can raise your right hand, and say 8, 9 words at once.
- We can divide. - No overlapping words?
But if you get one word wrong,
- you fail. - Come on.
All members must at least say one word each.
We're eight people, we can divide the words.
You have two minutes.
- Yes. - We're going to count down.
We can just memorize four words each.
- Right, and from you... - It's 4 words for 1 person.
Here are the words.
We're counting down. Get ready, go!
- Let's go. - What is it?
- Get ready, go! - What is it?
You memorize 1 to 4.
(They're going to memorize by the order of their seats.)
- 5 to 8 for me? - 5 to 8.
I'm memorizing from 29 to 31.
- I'm 21 to 24. - I'm 25 to 28.
What is this?
(What is this?)
They're the name of the colors.
(It's worrisome.)
What am I going to do?
(Full of difficult words)
- This is difficult. - You're 1 to 4, right?
- Yes. - Spring green.
- Goldenrod. - It's difficult.
(They're difficult, but 4 words in 2 minutes should be doable.)
Dark khaki, floral white.
Floral... This isn't easy.
Ocean, navy.
(They're using different methods of memorizing.)
(You have to make a song when you're memorizing.)
You have one minute remaining.
I'll say the words out loud for everyone.
(Cheol Min is trying to disturb.)
Stop! You're confusing me!
Slate gray.
- Be quiet! - Peach puff.
- Come on! - Stop that.
- Stop that. - You're confusing me.
(It's already confusing as it is.)
Saddle brown.
Orange red.
- Hollywood, burlywood. - All right.
Please remove the board.
Take them away!
I'd like to start.
Anyone who holds their right hand may begin.
You may begin, So Min.
Dark khaki, floral white,
and blue violet and burlywood.
- I have my hand up. - Me!
- What a relief. - One moment, please.
- Could you repeat that, So Min? - Sure.
Can't you just replay the audio recording?
(Just replay the audio recording!)
(She gets cranky at the request.)
We're all very sensitive at the moment.
- We are. - We're very sensitive.
Number 21, dark khaki.
Number 22, floral white.
Number 23, blue violet. Number 24...
Could you repeat number 22?
I'm asking you to repeat because of number 22.
Floral white.
- Again. - Come on...
- Come back in. - Don't do it.
Try again later. She'll try again later.
- I can say mine clearly. - Go head.
All right. Spring green.
Spring green. Next?
Goldenrod.
- Goldenrod? - Yes.
(He easily gets two of them correct.)
Olive drab.
(Number 11, olive drab.)
Olive drag.
Please say it clearly.
Take some time off, Jae Seok.
- I'll go next! - Olive...
Olive drab.
- Olive? - Yes. Olive drab.
- Drab. - What's the last letter?
- B. - B?
- Wait a minute! - Don't!
(Wait!)
(He gets confused as the producer teases him.)
- He'll do it over! - All right, all right!
- Time! - I'll go first.
- Try again later. - I'll go next.
- I'll do it later. - I don't think it's right.
- Are you sure it's the answer? - I'll go next.
Dark magenta.
- Deep pink. - Deep pink.
- Slate grey. - Slate grey.
- Crimson. - Crimson.
I'll go next!
I think I might forget them.
- I really want to go now. - This is my limit.
- Se Chan. - I can't hold on any longer!
- He had his hand up first. - I'm going to...
I'm going to relieve myself!
(He starts threatening.)
- I'm serious. - I'm going to forget them!
Pink, moccasin,
chartreuse,
and medium sea green.
- Okay. - Me. I'll go next.
- Seok Jin. - Me, too.
- I really need to go. - It's Seok Jin's turn.
Please...
Please!
Teal.
Sky blue.
(Teal, sky blue)
- What is he doing? - Come back in, Seok Jin.
Think about it again.
- Navy! Navy. - Navy.
Light blue.
There we go. I did it.
- Khaki. - Okay.
(Haha begins confidently.)
I need a minute.
(I need a minute.)
- You only have three! - What's wrong with you?
You can't even memorize three?
Please raise your right hand. Only those who do can go.
- Peach puff. - Peach puff.
- Make sure to get it right. - You have a good memory.
Come on.
And wait a minute.
You can't even memorize that?
Mine was really weird.
How do you even memorize your scripts?
I even managed and you're having a hard time?
You need to put it in a song to make it easy.
Cornflower blue.
Medium slate blue.
Okay!
(Haha gets his three words correct.)
(Kwang Soo, So Min, Jae Seok, and Ji Hyo are the only ones left.)
Saddle brown.
Orange red.
Chocolate.
Dodger blue.
(She says them carefully and gets it correct.)
Kwang Soo.
Medium...
Medium... The quoise?
- What? The quiett? - Medium...
Are you talking about the singer, The Quiett?
Wait a minute!
- Why are you mentioning The Quiett? - I'll go again later.
I'll go again later.
Someone else is bound to get it wrong before me.
I didn't get it wrong.
(He's trying to avoid criticism against him.)
- So Min, you have to go next. - No, I'm...
- You have to go next. - Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok will go first. - So Min.
- Next! - You can go first.
Jae Seok.
I'll begin with the next one.
(I'll begin with the next one instead.)
Fire brick.
- Fire brick. - Okay.
- I have one more left, right? - Yes.
I'll get back to that.
Get it over with!
(He asks for a break after getting one correct.)
Come on!
- Hurry up. - Just do it.
- Hurry up and say it. - I know what it is.
Then hurry up and get it over with.
Olive...
(Olive...)
- Drab. - Drag?
- It's "drag". - Olive drab? Correct.
What? It's correct?
- You're the only one left, So Min. - You go first, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo! - You go first.
I don't think it's "the quiett", Kwang Soo.
You go first. Please.
We're going to be collateral if we fail this time.
Let's hurry up and get it over with.
- It's nothing. - Go on, So Min.
- You can go first. - Go on.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors!
(So Min wins.)
You go first.
- Start! - Medium...
(Medium...)
the quoise.
What are you saying?
(Medium the quoise.)
- That's not it. - What are you doing?
- That's not allowed. - What was that?
I think it's "medium the quoise"...
- Kwang Soo, please... - It's either "de" or "the".
I don't think it's "the".
- I think it's "de". - Maybe it's not "medium the",
- but "medium"... - It's "de".
- It's either "the" or "de". - It's "de".
"De" is more of a Europian language.
It's Europian. D, E.
"The" is English.
- Then, "de"? - By the way...
Kwang Soo, color names come from Europe.
You wouldn't be having a hard time if it was "the quoise".
- He has a point. - You would have gotten it right.
I remember it being hard. It must be "de".
- It's "de". - Go with "de".
- Medium de quoise. - Medium de quoise.
(His final choice is medium de quoise.)
(Incorrect.)
- What's the answer? - Medium turquoise.
- Kwang Soo... - Turquoise.
- It's "Tur"? - He got it wrong!
It's not even close.
You fool!
- His head is full of nothing. - Hey!
- Hey fool! - I'm sorry.
- I admit it, I'm sorry. - Wait a minute.
- Hold on. - I'm really sorry.
- Hold on. Come over here, you two. - You two...
I already got hit.
- I... - The three of you...
Either one of you will have to be the collateral.
Let's do that.
If we have to put up collateral, it's going to be either one of you.
Let's do this one more time!
Are you ready?
- Yes. - We can do this.
- We have to get it right this time. - We will.
(The next category is animals.)
Porcupine.
I got it!
Marmoset...
monkey.
Shrew.
Walrus.
How many do we have left? Are we finished?
- Seok Jin needs to go. - I'll start!
Tasmanian devil.
- "Tas"? - Tasmanian devil.
- Correct. - Okay!
(He gets the difficult one correct.)
We have to get this right.
There's one more left.
Is it humpback whale or backhump whale?
- What? - Humpback.
- It's humpback, right? - I'm 100 percent sure.
- It's humpback. - It's humpback.
- It's humpback. - Are you sure?
It must have a hump on its back.
Why are you asking us? You should be the one to memorize!
(Come to think of it, you should be the one to memorize!)
(Whimpering)
Jong Kook's going to get so mad if you get it wrong this time.
- It's humpback. - Is it right?
- Yes, it's humpback. - Don't fall for it.
Will you give me another chance to call my wife...
if I say the wrong answer?
(He suddenly tries to bargain.)
- What is he saying? - He wants to call his wife.
What do you think you're doing?
We're not going to choose you, anyways.
Can you be chosen the collateral twice?
- You're already done. - Okay.
- It's humpback. - Humpback is correct.
- Humpback whale. - Good job.
- He got it. - It's correct.
It's correct.
- Okay! - Okay!
(They complete "Unified Lunch".)
It's our first win!
We got one.
We need two more wins.
(The members win if they pass two more rounds!)
- You guys won fair and square. - Yes.
We will move on to the next stop.
- Let's go! - Okay!
(They move on to the next round after winning on the 3rd stop.)
(They have 3 hours left and they decides to skip the 4th stop.)
It's a snack bar.
- The next stop it, "Snack Bar". - Let's get off.
- Okay. - We'll get off.
- We need to do this round. - Let's get off.
I have a good feeling about this stop.
Will you be getting off at "Snack Bar",
or skipping?
- We will get off! - We will get off!
- It's a dud? - What?
(They got off without hesitation, but...)
(You may be angry, but why don't you eat at home?)
- It's a dud? - What is this?
"You may be angry, but why don't you eat at home".
- Is it a dud? - It's a dud!
- It's a dud. - What?
- Don't lie. - Come on.
The other stop wasn't the dud?
There was a cooking mission on that stop.
I told you!
- This stop is a dud. - You have two fails so far.
Please get on the bus so that we can move on to the next stop.
If we fail once again, then it's over, right?
- It's our last chance. - It's the end for good.
We have to practice acrobatics.
- We have to... - Jae Seok.
- We have to do acrobatics. - We need to win no matter what.
- How will we win? - We need to win two rounds.
Warm up your backs, everyone.
We need to spin three times in midair.
You should be prepared.
- What do we do? - Jae Seok!
Let's just go.
They said there's only one dud stop.
- There will be no more dud stop. - That's right.
- That's it. - Okay.
- I thought the other one was it. - This stop is the dud.
- I think we'll have... - It's time they gave us food.
- to win next time. - There will be food.
- They should not pass it. - I agree.
- We need to hurry. - Please step on it.
We've passed the dud stop in the first half,
- so now we can enjoy the rest. - That's right.
Great!
We have arrived.
- What's the name of the stop? - What is it?
The sixth stop is, "Food Truck".
- What? - "Food Truck"!
- It's "Food Truck"! - We're getting food.
Will you be getting off?
- Yes! - We're getting off!
- Okay! - Let's go.
- Thank you. - I think it's a restaurant.
I'm so hungry.
I'm sure it's going to be a restaurant.
(What kind of mission will be waiting for them?)
What's this?
- What's going on? - There's a train.
There's something fascinating here!
It says, "Rice", "Laver",
"Pork kimchi jjigae", "Chocolate", "Rolled omelette", "Green chilis",
"Ssamjang", "Black herbal tea", "Stir-fried pork"...
- I think that's what we're having. - I don't think so.
- I think we need to put them in. - We need to put the balls in.
I think we're putting ping pong balls in.
We have to get the balls in.
The keyword "Food Truck"...
is a lunch mission.
- "Food Truck"! - Let's eat!
We will get this.
- Let's do this! - Let's go!
The mission for "Food Truck"...
will be using the "Lunch-deciding Train".
(The 6th mission will go with the "Lunch-deciding Train".)
There are eight items on the moving train.
You will have to spin around five times,
and if all eight of you succeed in getting a ball in one of the items,
you will get the food.
However, if two or more balls fall in the same box,
the food will not be served.
(Overlapping items will be eliminated.)
Two or more than two?
It must not fall in the same box.
(It's a difficult mission.)
In addition,
you'll be given six ping pong balls...
and two iron balls.
The iron balls will have to fall...
in Coach 1 and Coach 8, in order for you to succeed.
Really?
The iron balls will make it difficult.
- This is too hard. - How will we get this?
- We need to get the timing right. - That's right.
It takes time to roll down.
We can try as many times as we wish, so let's give it a try.
- Start! - Start!
We have to roll it when the train is here.
Start!
Get ready.
- Around here. - Go!
- You have to begin! - One.
- We need to set the rules. - Two.
- 3. - 3.
- 4. - 4.
- 5! - 5!
- Put it in! - Hurry!
(What will be the result?)
- It's going to work. - It'll go in one of the coaches.
(They win the food of the coach the ball enters.)
(They fail the mission if the ball misses.)
(Will the ball go into a coach?)
(Haha wins chocolate.)
- Chocolate. - Chocolate.
- What? For goodness' sake. - Chocolate.
We will get the most number of balls in that coach.
Chocolate.
I got the hang of it.
Who will go next?
- I will go next. - Good luck.
Kwang Soo, you need to spin.
- You need to spin. - Spin.
- Hurry up. One. - He started off too late.
- Two. - He is fast.
- Three. - Go slower.
- Four. - There you go.
- Five. - Go.
(Putting in)
- My goodness. - He did it.
This is good.
It will be rolled omelette.
(If it goes into Coach 4, they will lose chocolate.)
(What will be the result?)
- Green chilis. - Yes.
(They acquire green chilis and ssamjang.)
Green chilis. Green chilis.
(They succeeded, but...)
You did it.
- I am dizzy. - You are dizzy, right?
- Seok Jin. - Get pork kimchi jjigae.
It will be incredible if you succeed in one go.
Rolled omelette will be nice, too.
(The train runs towards Seok Jin.)
- Seok Jin. - You need to start.
- Start. - One.
- Two. - Go slowly.
- Three. - Go.
(He spins rather slowly.)
- Put it in. - It's too fast.
- Put it in. - Put it in.
(What?)
- Put it in. - I can't believe him!
- Hurry up and put it in. - Put it in.
(He falls down.)
- It hasn't gone in yet. - What is he doing?
No, no.
That seemed intentional.
No.
We could have gotten stir-fried pork.
That seemed intentional.
- Seok Jin. - Stir-fried pork.
It was strange that you couldn't put it in.
What?
Why couldn't you put it in?
- I was too dizzy. - My goodness.
- You haven't tried it. - You got enough screen time.
Go easy on the slapstick comedy.
Why are you so sensitive?
- He is sensitive. - He got enough screen time.
Seok Jin did many things.
Why does he try to be funny every single time?
Let the others get some screen time.
Let me tell you this. If you think this is impossible,
- pick a member as collateral. - No, we will complete this mission.
- We won't put up collateral. - You will get three side dishes...
if you succeed the collateral mission.
(3 side dishes for a successful collateral mission)
Three side dishes?
Let's try this. In my opinion...
- Let's go. - We can do this.
Haha, you should go first. Go.
(Haha will go 1st on the 2nd try)
Who will use the iron ball?
There are two iron balls.
We should try using it. I will do it.
- Give it a try. - Go.
- Go. - Go. One.
- Two. - I will put it...
- in the stir-fried coach. - 3. 4.
- 4. - The last one. 5.
- The iron ball will be fast. - Five.
- Hurry up. - Put it in there.
(Putting in)
(The iron ball spins.)
- What? - What is going on?
(They didn't expect the delay.)
(The iron ball needs to go in the rice or stir-fried pork coach.)
(They didn't expect the iron ball to spin.)
(Will the spin work to their advantage?)
(What will be the result?)
(Haha acquires stir-fried pork.)
(The miracle of the spinning iron ball)
(The short man who makes the iron ball spin)
(The iron ball spun miraculously...)
(and went into the last coach.)
No way!
(Haha has magic hands.)
- No way. - You succeeded...
- because the iron ball spun. - Seriously.
- Go, go. - It was thrilling.
- It was a movie. - The train is slower now.
It was a movie.
- Seriously. - Go, go.
- Go. - It's time.
(So Min will try to put in a ping pong ball.)
- Go. - One.
Spin faster, So Min.
- 2. - 2.
- You are too slow. - You need to spin faster.
- Go. - Five.
Go.
Gosh, what are you doing?
(The train breaks.)
What is wrong with you?
I couldn't do it.
- So Min. - I...
- Are you serious? - I am really dizzy.
Hold on.
The iron ball...
- went into stir-fried pork. - Did I do that?
- Did I do that? - She broke everything.
Did I do that?
Who else do you think did it?
If the train is broken, you will fail the mission.
We can fix this.
We lost stir-fried pork.
That's too bad.
- We lost stir-fried pork. - That's right.
I won't get the timing right.
It won't happen again. It will be hard.
If we fail a few more times, we should put up collateral.
- This is... - That's our only hope.
We will need to pick someone...
- as collateral. - This mission is impossible.
It's about time we pick So Min as collateral.
If we fail one more time, it will be over.
- So Min... - So Min will succeed.
- It's moving. - Let's do this.
It's moving. Thank goodness it's fixed.
- You will start over. - Okay. Let's do this.
Let's go.
I will try the iron ball first.
- There are two iron balls. - I will try the iron ball first.
He will be a hero if he succeeds.
- Here it comes. - Here it comes.
- Shall I start? - No.
(The train moves toward Jong Kook.)
- Shall I start? - It's time.
- I will start. - Go.
- 1, 2. - He is fast.
- He is fast. - Three.
- Four. - Go.
- It's time. - Go.
- It's time. - Now is the time.
- All right. - I think it's too late.
Hurry up.
(Putting in)
(The iron ball spins again.)
What?
- It will work. - What?
(Will the spin lead to success again?)
- He did it! - He did it!
He did it!
(He spun the iron ball with his careful touch...)
(and got it into the stir-fried pork coach.)
- That was incredible. - I calculated it.
How did you calculate it?
That makes no sense.
I can't believe him.
- How did he do that? - I counted.
Jong Kook.
- He succeeded. - In that case...
We need to get rice now.
- Should I go next? - Go.
- Okay. - Go.
(Haha will try the iron ball.)
You need to hurry up.
Rice. Here I go.
- I know. - You are too late.
If you can't get rice...
- Two. - He is fast.
- Three. - Hold on.
- Four. - Go.
- It's time. - Put it in.
- Put it in now. - Okay.
(He spins fast and puts in the iron ball.)
- Okay. - My goodness.
(Haha spun the iron ball and got stir-fried pork before.)
(Will he succeed to get rice this time?)
(My goodness.)
It was too fast.
- Okay. - My goodness.
- Why was it so fast? - It didn't spin.
Why didn't it spin?
- It spun before. - Is this a different iron ball?
- Why didn't it spin? - It didn't spin.
Is this remote controlled?
It didn't spin.
Had it spun, he would have gotten rice.
Haha dropped it in the middle.
The ball should have touched the wall.
Let's put up collateral.
- Maybe that's the only choice. - Let's put up collateral.
- Okay. - That's the only choice.
Let's put up collateral.
I have a suggestion. I will let you start...
with iron balls in stir-fried pork and rice coaches...
if you put up small collateral.
- Is there such thing? - Shall we do that?
The mission would be easier that way.
If we are going to go down either way, let's try it.
- We will put up small collateral. - Small collateral.
- All right. - Small collateral.
Which member will you pick?
So Min.
(So Min.)
(She must take responsibility for the train wreck.)
Small collateral? Okay.
So Min, here is your collateral mission.
(If she completes the collateral mission,)
(they will try the mission with iron balls in the coaches.)
(What will be So Min's collateral mission?)
When there is a male guest,
wear strange makeup alone for the opening three times.
- What? - Excuse me?
(Wear strange makeup alone for the opening 3 times.)
- Are you serious? - It's only for the opening.
- It's not small collateral. - Seriously.
It's big.
- Alone? I mean... - So Min, you can do it.
So Min, you might look cute.
- It will be better. - So Min,
they will fall for your charms.
Even if male guests come,
they will only work and leave.
I am on Running Man...
because I want to get married through this show.
(I want to get married through this show.)
(She dreams of getting married through a variety show.)
Don't do this to me. I am serious.
It will be hard to do that through Running Man.
This is where I meet male celebrities.
- 3 times. - How about 1 strong makeup?
- That's right. - One strong makeup.
If it's really bad, she can do it only once.
- The opening won't last long. - It doesn't concern you.
Don't say that. We are a family.
- I would do it. - I would do it, too.
- I would do it, too. - I would do it three times.
So Min. One...
Don't take pictures.
- There will be multiple cameras. - Two.
There will be dozens of cameras.
Three.
- Okay. - So Min is the best.
You will wear really strange makeup once.
Don't turn her into a sumo wrestler.
(Don't turn her into a sumo wrestler.)
- That's right. - It could be something like that.
(A sumo wrestler?)
- A sumo wrestler? - It could be something like that.
(She is perfectly in sync.)
(What kind of makeup will she wear?)
So Min will do a good job.
(The 2 iron balls are in the coaches.)
I suffered the same thing.
Let's start over.
- Kwang Soo, you should go. - Okay.
- Don't start yet. - Don't start yet.
- We will have lunch. - Let's have lunch.
Stand up.
(They will succeed if they put ping pong balls in the coaches.)
Here it comes.
- Check the speed. - Come on.
- Go. - That's too fast.
- Faster. - Five.
- It's coming. - Put it in.
(Putting in)
- There you go. - Pork kimchi jjigae!
(It looks like the ball will go in.)
(It's between chocolate and pork kimchi jjigae.)
(Will they get chocolate or pork kimchi jjigae?)
(What will be the result?)
- Pork kimchi jjigae! - Yes!
(They acquire pork kimchi jjigae.)
(The king of meals, pork kimchi jjigae)
You did it.
- You did it. - Okay.
Get rolled omelette.
- Rolled omelette. - Let's go.
When should I start spinning?
- When should I start spinning? - Now! Go!
- Go. - Go.
- Go slowly. - One.
- 2. - 2.
- Three. - Go slowly.
- Four. - Slowly.
- Five. - Go slowly, Se Chan.
- Go, put it in. - No.
- No, not yet. - Put it in.
I need to put it in.
He got it.
- It will be rolled omelet. - Rolled omelet.
(Menu is canceled if the ball drops in the same goal twice.)
(What's the result?)
Rolled omelet!
(He obtains rolled omelet.)
(Rolled omelet is the highlight of a meal.)
- Rolled omelet. - Rolled omelet.
- Nice. - That's insane.
This is like a buffet.
I'm happy. I wasn't sacrificed in vain.
- Next is Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
- How about dried laver? - Go for green chilis.
- I'll go for green chilis. - Dried laver is good too.
- Get ready. - Black herbal tea is fine too.
Get ready.
- Start. - Go.
- 1, 2. - 1, 2.
- Go faster. - Three.
(Running Man's ace, Ji Hyo gives a try.)
- You're done. - Five.
- Wait. - Do I put it in?
Put it in.
No.
No, no.
(Other members' opinions on timing differ.)
- Hey. - It's too late.
- We're doomed. - It's stir-fried pork.
(If she fails, all dishes are canceled.)
(What's the result?)
(What?)
(Oh, no...)
- It missed. - It was too late.
She failed.
Why were you late?
She's the king of destruction today.
What's wrong with you?
She ruins every mission today.
- What's wrong with her? - You guys say different things.
- You should've listened to me. - Others said no.
You flipped the table when I was about to eat kimchi jjigae.
(She destroyed a feast that the others had prepared.)
She's the king of destruction.
Unbelievable, Ji Hyo.
Pick collateral.
- Pick collateral. - Collateral.
- Let's pick one. - Let's go.
Who will pick the collateral?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's be fair.
Rock-paper-scissors is a good idea.
- You play. - We'll just win.
- We can play. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(The king of destruction, Ji Hyo wins.)
- Ji Hyo won. - Only Ji Hyo won.
(After throwing over the table, she becomes the only winner.)
- What? - Get out.
- She won. - You're excluded.
- Ji Hyo won. - You're excluded.
You're excluded, Ji Hyo.
Take a rest, Ji Hyo.
This is so annoying.
- That's impressive. - She's good at this though.
You're really impressive.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and So Min win.)
- Okay. - Okay.
I'm so relieved.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan win.)
- Okay. - Yes.
- Okay. - I'm sorry.
- Here's what I feel. - Hurry.
- I think it'll be Haha. - Keep going.
- It'll be Haha. - I hope it's Haha.
Let it be Haha.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Haha loses.)
I knew it'd be him.
It serves him right.
I knew it, Haha.
Here's your collateral, Haha.
(If they fail one more time, Team Running Man fails.)
(What is Haha's collateral that he must not fail?)
Go to one of your rival barbecue restaurants in Hongdae.
Upload a photo of you eating on your social media.
Write a comment, "It's very delicious."
(Upload a photo of himself and comment that it's delicious...)
(at his rival barbecue restaurant.)
Oh, no.
- It'll hurt his restaurant's sales. - Poor thing.
- That's so mean. - By the way,
you can do it.
- His sense of pride... - His neighborhood should thrive.
- Right. - Do you understand?
- That's right. - Right.
It doesn't work if only your restaurant is successful.
You can do it.
I'm sorry,
but here's what's most important.
Our barbecue restaurant...
has no rivals in Hongdae.
He's confident.
The restaurant at the end of the alley...
- is getting competitive. - Right?
- You should go there. - Go to that restaurant.
He should go there.
As Jae Seok said,
- your neighborhood should thrive. - Yes.
Their neighborhood is already thriving.
Is that so? Is it already thriving?
- Is it thriving? - This is not easy.
Then you should thrive more.
It's either "O" or "X".
- It should be "O". - Of course.
If you succeed, you get a meal with three side dishes.
(What if Haha fails his collateral mission?)
(Team Running Man will fail with 3 fail stickers.)
(They must show the hardest dance moves at the fan-meet.)
(What will Haha decide?)
Let's do it.
- Do it. - He's so cool.
He's cool.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - He's so cool.
This is the restaurant in front of my house.
It's delicious.
You can do it.
(He completes his collateral mission.)
It's delicious.
It's been a while since we obtained the food this easily.
We really have this kimchi jjigae.
I hope you'll be grateful to me.
- Pork kimchi jjigae is delicious. - This is really good.
Rolled omelet is amazing.
It's from a food truck.
- Really? - No.
- He said no. - No?
(It's not from a food truck.)
Does it hurt to say that it is?
(Does it hurt to say that it is?)
Does it hurt to say so?
(54-year-old Seok Jin is short-tempered these days.)
Come to think of it,
none of us says anything nice to Seok Jin...
- including me. - It's okay.
Everyone is alone in life. It's okay.
Including the staff and myself, we should compliment Seok Jin.
I don't like such money pity.
("Money pity"?)
It's not "money pity".
What do you mean by money?
- "Money pity"? - It's "pity".
I don't like pity.
Seok Jin hasn't changed at all.
When Seok Jin was a rookie,
he got upset at me because I made fun of him.
He cursed at me once.
What did I say?
(Do you remember what you said?)
(What did I say?)
You piece of garbage. I'll never see you again.
(He's honest about what he hates.)
(He hates pity and being made fun of.)
- Seok Jin... - It's because he made fun of him.
(His isolated life officially started back then.)
- Stop. What if he cries? - It really happened.
I don't cry.
I have no tears.
When I put onions on my eyes with Jong Kook, I didn't cry.
(He makes himself appealing.)
Shall I make you cry?
(Shall I make you cry?)
(He bursts out laughter.)
Jong Kook can.
What if Seok Jin cries to avoid getting hit?
It's the last round.
You have 35 minutes left.
- What? - What?
You have number 7 and 8 left.
- You can pass one. - Okay.
That's the current situation.
Let's get to the last number.
(Let's get to the last match.)
Let's try number eight.
I love number eight.
In China,
- eight is a lucky number. You know? - That's right.
If we fail, we fail. If we win, we win.
- Okay, let's go. - We can do it.
We must avoid doing the difficult dance moves.
(They arrive at number 8 bus stop.)
The bus stop name is strange.
Why?
(What's the name of the bus stop?)
It's called MSG.
(It's English all of a sudden. MSG?)
The bus stop is called MSG.
- We have to go anyway. - Go, go, go.
- Move. - Or...
- We must succeed this time. - We must win no matter what.
I have a bad feeling. I got hit with whipped cream here.
Will it be hard to avoid? There's a pull-up bar.
(A pull-up bar?)
- What is it? - What's the pull-up bar for?
- What is it? - There's a pull-up bar.
- What are they? - There are water balloons.
Why is this called MSG?
"Water Balloon Game".
Is that why it's MSG?
MSG means Water Balloon Game.
This is the mission that you picked.
MSG mission is...
Water Balloon Game.
Four members will stand in line on each side.
Throw the water balloon over the pull-up bar.
If it doesn't pop, you pass.
Over the pull-up bar?
You'll play in a relay. You'll win if water balloons don't pop.
Bend your knees as you catch.
- Bend at the same time. - You can't simply catch it.
- We can do it. - It's possible.
It's so windy right now.
This much wind won't affect us.
(What are you talking about?)
(Don't use the wind as an excuse.)
- Seriously. - Hey.
- Please compliment him. - Why wouldn't the wind affect us?
- These aren't regular balloons. - Be quiet.
- There's water in them. - Enough.
- Even a golf ball is affected. - Let him breathe.
- Let Seok Jin breathe. - Okay.
Seok Jin might pass out due to high blood pressure.
I have no high blood pressure. Mine is stable.
- Are you angry again? - I'm not.
(He grips his jaw.)
(He sounds angry.)
- Are you sure you aren't angry? - You sound angry.
- Seok Jin. - I'm not angry.
Are you sure that you aren't angry?
"I'm not angry."
The current time is 3:05 p.m. You have 25 minutes left.
- Let's hurry. - Come on. We can win.
Gather around.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3. We got this.
We'll make it no matter what.
We'll win no matter what.
Let's start right away.
All we have to do is finish in 20 minutes.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Kwang Soo.
- Stay low like this. - Okay.
Go.
(Jae Seok throws a balloon to Kwang Soo.)
(If it doesn't go over the bar or it pops, they fail.)
It worked.
(Where they catch the balloon is also important.)
(He throws the water balloon with stability.)
(All he has to do is catch it.)
(He catches it.)
(From Jae Seok to Kwang Soo, they succeed.)
- Good job. - It's possible.
It is possible.
That's right.
(Kwang Soo to Seok Jin)
- I'll start right away. - All right.
(It draws a perfect parabola.)
(Then it pops.)
(Seok Jin fails.)
- Oh, no. - I told you.
Bend as you catch it.
(As soon as he catches it, the water balloon pops.)
I told you. Bend as you catch it.
- I bent with it. - Seok Jin.
(It won't be easy.)
You should hug it instead of catching it with your hands.
It can be misunderstood.
(The wet spot can be misunderstood.)
(The water balloon popped at a misunderstandable spot.)
He peed.
Things are going so terribly for Seok Jin today.
- Gosh. - You need to bend as you catch.
Let me try again.
- Jae Seok threw it so well. - Kwang Soo is good at catching.
- Start again. - Start.
(They succeeded in the first round.)
Goodness.
(They succeed again this time.)
(It's so high.)
Okay, good job.
(He caught it, but it's uncomfortable.)
Doesn't it pop?
- I was startled. It was so high. - Good job.
Kwang Soo, it was dangerous.
- Hold on. - Just let it go.
May I throw it to Jae Seok?
- No? - All right.
He was being mean to me.
- All right. - Let's go.
I'm scared.
You need to make it.
Don't stop looking at it.
[VIU Ver] SBS E452 Running Man
"Loyalty for the Collateral Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(He's been spotted all day.)
What are you doing?
He got it.
- What is he doing? - Oh, no.
Seok Jin.
What's wrong?
- Please. - Get up.
He's on camera a lot today.
What's wrong?
Can Seok Jin go home today?
- What's wrong with you? - What's wrong?
It was slippery.
What's the matter with you?
Do you want all the cameras to follow you all day?
- What's wrong with him? - What's wrong?
He's greedy.
- He's greedy. - He's extremely greedy.
- What's wrong with you? - It was slippery.
You want all the cameras to only film you.
I slipped. My shoes are slippery.
He's greedy about being on camera.
Seok Jin is just unbelievable.
I'll go last. This is so annoying.
You can't catch like this.
- Receive with the whole body. - Absorb the impact.
- It won't be easy. - Throw it to me.
(They start their third round.)
- Let's start. - Start.
(From Kwang Soo to Jae Seok)
(The balloon goes up high.)
It's too high.
- That was good. - Catch it like this.
(He catches the balloon that flies high with stability.)
(He did catch it.)
He threw it up too high.
(Did you catch that?)
- Like this. - Wait.
- You threw it too high on purpose. - Wait.
Why are you taken aback?
We saw through your intention.
- I knew it. - Like this.
- You have to go down to catch it. - He's right.
How did he catch that?
(It should have popped.)
He thought it would pop,
- but Jae Seok caught it. - He's impressive.
- Who's next? - Next.
Go, So Min. So Min will catch it.
- So Min? - She can't catch it.
I don't think she can.
- Absorb the impact. - You have to sit down.
Hug the water balloon.
Here I go.
Don't be scared.
(The water balloon goes over the bar...)
(and it free-falls.)
(It goes past her.)
Throw it nicely.
I should have thrown it closer.
So Min, you should step back and catch it.
Why don't the two of you play?
- Let's play. - Try it.
- Two of you should play. - Throw it.
We don't have time.
- We have to hurry. - We really have to hurry.
Keep going. Start.
- It was too high. - Start.
Hug it.
(Seok Jin throws it with all his might.)
- Stop it. - He's driving me up the wall.
(However)
(The water balloon pops.)
(They feel frustrated.)
Give us a water balloon.
Throw it over.
He can neither throw nor catch it.
(Seok Jin drives him up the wall.)
- It's frustrating. - I'll go again.
He can neither throw nor catch it.
- Stay back and step forward. - Throw it lightly.
That's right.
(Of course it wouldn't work this time.)
We're in trouble. This won't work.
This won't work.
(Will they be able to clear the mission?)
Try it, Haha.
Haha is good at things like this.
He's good at playing basketball.
(From Jae Seok to Haha)
(Can Haha catch the balloon when it's thrown with stability?)
All right.
(Nice catch)
Nice.
- What happened? - Haha.
What happened?
(After catching the balloon,)
(his hairstyle changed suddenly.)
- What happened? - That's your real look.
- What happened? - Suddenly...
- Wait. - What's going on today?
Are you trying a new hairstyle?
- Seriously. - This is terrible.
What just happened?
(Isn't it foul to entertain people with a funny hairstyle?)
You look like the one in "Drunken Master".
Everyone is laughing because his hairstyle changed.
- What's going on today? - What's wrong with you?
- We don't have time. - Let's hurry.
- I want to try. - Okay.
- Ji Hyo. - I don't think she can do it.
- I don't think I can. - With your body,
- you must absorb the impact. - It's not easy.
(Will they pass round 2?)
- Nice. - Here it comes.
(He throws the water balloon with stability.)
(All she has to do is catch it.)
(She catches it.)
(She's an ace after all.)
That's good. You throw it.
(Impressive)
- You throw it. - That was good.
That was amazing.
You have to throw it harder than you think.
- Move forward as you throw it. - Throwing will be hard.
(The water weight makes it hard to throw it.)
(When it comes to ace Ji Hyo,)
(she has a lot of strength to rock climb.)
(She's bold and fearless.)
(There's a reason why she's an ace.)
Here I go.
(She showed her talent in every crisis.)
(Will she show it again this time?)
Here it comes.
(Popping)
- What happened? - What?
What was that?
(The water balloon pops as soon as she throws it.)
(He's gotten wet all of a sudden.)
What was that?
(You know how strong I am.)
- What happened? - What was that?
Why don't you just splash water on me instead?
What was that?
- You're the king of destruction. - Ji Hyo.
As soon as I threw it...
- She's the king of destruction. - I was startled.
- How did it pop? - You have a nickname.
- She's the king of destruction. - I was so startled.
- She breaks everything. - How did it pop?
She's the king of destruction.
You have seven minutes left.
No.
- Catch it. - You can catch it.
(They start their seventh attempt.)
Here it is.
- Nice. - She caught it.
(From Seok Jin to So Min is a success.)
- She caught it. - She did it.
(They have a good feeling about it.)
- She caught it. - So Min should throw it now.
(Is it up to me now?)
Wait.
Throw it carefully.
(It's time for So Min to throw it.)
(It's not easy to throw it.)
- It won't go up. - Can you do this?
- This. - Use both hands.
- Throw it like this. - Use both hands.
- That's right. - Throw it up all the way.
- You got it. - She did it.
- That's right. - Okay.
(She throws the balloon with two hands.)
(He catches it.)
(From So Min to Jae Seok is a success.)
(I did it.)
- It keeps bulging out. - It's bulging out.
It keeps coming out.
- So Min passed. - Okay.
We can make it.
Let's win. We don't have much time.
(I'll throw it well this time, Kwang Soo.)
(He catches it with stability.)
Nice.
(From Jae Seok to Kwang Soo is a success.)
- Is it Ji Hyo's turn to catch? - Yes.
(Please catch it, Ji Hyo.)
Everyone is ready.
(The balloon is thrown over.)
(Did she catch it?)
Catch it.
She caught it.
(She definitely caught it.)
This counts.
It's alive.
She's the king of destruction.
- She really is. - Wait.
- Look at this. - She's the king of destruction.
The balloon wasn't tied properly.
It's not the balloon's fault.
It was like an elephant that was peeing.
- It was like a peeing elephant. - Be quiet.
- I was startled. - I saw it too.
It was weak at the end.
We don't have time.
Start right away.
Do it just like before.
- Catch it, So Min. - Me?
(They make their eighth attempt.)
(From Seok Jin to So Min)
(Will they succeed?)
He got it.
She got it.
(She catches it.)
(From Seok Jin to So Min is a success.)
She's good at catching now.
- Hurry. - She's good.
- Do it slowly. - With two hands.
- She got it. - Okay.
- He caught it. - Who's next?
(They throw and catch successfully.)
- Who's next? - This is intense.
You can take your time.
Take your time.
That's right.
- It's Ji Hyo's turn. - That's right.
- Come on, Ji Hyo. - You can catch it.
- That's right. - Throw it carefully.
(Here comes Ji Hyo, the king of destruction, again.)
(They don't have much time left.)
- The balloon becomes fragile. - Okay.
(Unlike an ace,)
(Ji Hyo destroyed all the missions.)
(Will she clear her name, the king of destruction?)
(Will she come back to being an ace?)
Okay.
(Nice catch)
(From Kwang Soo to Ji Hyo is a success.)
- Change it. - We need to change it.
- Ji Hyo. - We need to change it.
Change the balloon, Ji Hyo.
You can't change it.
(Changing the balloon is foul.)
We can't change it? That's the one.
You can't change it.
(A warning has been issued.)
(They try to change it in secret.)
You can't change it.
- This is the one. - We can't?
(They work great as a team at times like this.)
- All right. - This is fine.
Jae Seok, bring that back.
Okay.
He's strict, you know.
He's strict.
(He's watching.)
I'll throw it lightly.
- Move forward. - You have three minutes.
(They don't have enough time to make another attempt.)
(The balloon is thrown.)
Hey.
(However)
(The water balloon gets caught on the pull-up bar.)
(If they fail, they have to perform a high-level dance.)
(Will they fail the mission?)
(He catches it.)
It might pop.
(He recognized that its path was short.)
(Haha moves forward and catches the balloon.)
(From Ji Hyo to Haha is a success.)
We got it.
- Start. - It almost popped.
Let's save it.
- We don't have time. - Let's save it.
Please.
(He throws it carefully.)
Okay.
Is it over once Se Chan catches and throws it?
Yes.
- Let's go, Se Chan. - It must hurt.
Don't throw it too high.
- I know. - Throw it lightly.
Lightly.
(He tosses it as safely as possible.)
- Yes. - He got it.
(From Jong Kook to Se Chan is a success.)
- Please, Seok Jin. - It's the last one.
Clap for him.
- Is it over once I catch it? - It's the last one.
- We win if you succeed. - This is the last one.
It's over if you fail.
(Everything depends on him.)
(He has never succeeded.)
(He never threw it over the bar.)
(He never caught it.)
(He's the biggest failure.)
(He's determined to succeed this time.)
It's over if you fail.
(Only 1 minute remains.)
Please.
I want to make it.
(They might avoid performing a high-level dance.)
Put your arms forward...
before it comes.
(There's no other attempt.)
You got this.
(If he doesn't catch the water balloon,)
(4 types of group dances prepared by the staff are waiting for them.)
(To avoid this,)
(they've been trying so hard for 5 hours.)
(However, if they lose the race, they'll perform one of the dances.)
(In order to avoid performing difficult dance,)
(they must accomplish their mission no matter what.)
(Will they be able to pull this off?)
(No way! He got it!)
We got it!
(With 1 minute left, Seok Jin catches the balloon from Se Chan.)
(The members win the race by accomplishing 3 missions.)
- We did it! - We did it.
We did it.
- They're about to die. - Look at their faces.
- My gosh. - Look at your faces.
We did it. We pulled it off.
- We did it. - Poor staff.
We won't do those dances.
- I won't. - I wasn't going to do that either.
- We did it. - That was awesome.
- Never. - This was doable.
- Iron Min looks very disappointed. - Yes.
I bet he wanted us to perform one of those dances.
- We have no choice now. - We won the race.
It was bound to happen. Our teamwork is perfect.
And we got better in the meantime.
We improved. We definitely improved.
And Cheol Min forgot about that part.
- That's right. - Of course.
But rules are rules.
We want to give a great concert to the fans though.
- We want to do a cool concert too. - Right.
We'll discuss this among ourselves.
We'll come up with a group choreography.
- Let's come up with a cool one. - Let's think about this.
Okay. I want you to discuss the group dance...
and tell us during the opening segment next week.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Great. That's neat. - I got it.
- We got it. - Okay.
(Which dance will they choose?)
(To my grandchildren)
(Their grandparents whom they miss are waiting at home.)
(These 8 grandchildren finally visit their grandparents' house.)
(Grandma, we're here!)
(They welcome their grandchildren with overwhelming joy to see them.)
(Hip grandparents are here!)
(Kook Soon, the youngest, 8th grader)
(They're spending a happy time with their grandchildren.)
(As they babied their grandchildren, the kids don't have any manners.)
(However,)
(some people don't belong to the family.)
(Instantly, these family members have become strangers.)
(They must survive among the fake family members.)
(Some try to deceive others, and others try to avoid deception.)
(What's the secret that will give you the goosebumps?)
(Episode 2: 9 Years of Running Man, We're Supposed to Be a Family!)