- Hi. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello. Hi, hi.
- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
- What are you doing? - Hello.
(Jae Seok approaches Kwang Soo who's saying hello.)
(He arrests Kwang Soo all of a sudden.)
- It's you, isn't it? - What?
- You're the spy. - Do we have a spy today?
Jae Seok, they didn't give us a mission yet.
- Not yet? - Not yet.
They usually give out the missions to the spies at this cafe.
- You're right. - You know?
That's the cafe.
Hold on, Jae Seok. Why did you come out of the cafe alone?
(Why did you come out of the cafe alone?)
I used the restroom in there.
- Hold him. - Hold him.
(I got you, spy!)
(The table has turned.)
Why did you come out of the cafe alone?
Hey. Hey.
Hey, you. Your punches are pretty strong.
- Right. - You know?
- My punches are strong. - They have quite the kick.
Hey, Haha.
(Haha is the fourth one to arrive.)
- Happy birthday - Happy birthday
- I got goosebumps. - Happy birthday
(Happy birthday, Haha!)
(The day of the shooting, August 20, was Haha's birthday.)
(Congratulations on turning 40.)
Come to the center.
(The atmosphere is heating up as they wish him happy birthday.)
Stand in the center.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday. - Where did you come from?
- Happy birthday. - Everyone came all of a sudden.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
Do you want only your left shoulder to hurt?
- Do you want your shoulder to hurt? - It's already red.
- It's already red. - I should put on sunscreen here.
Did you apply sunscreen there?
- Hey. - I'm going to.
It's been so long since I saw a BCG vaccine mark.
Hey.
(It's nice to see you again.)
- I didn't mean anything bad. - Stop it.
- My mother has it too. - Kids don't get that anymore.
Depending on the BCG vaccine mark, we can figure out...
- when you were born. - Right.
That's true.
It's like having a barcode.
People who were born in 1981 would have this.
(This mark proves that you are in your 40s.)
- That's so bright. - It's so bright.
- It's bright. - Look at Jong Kook's outfit.
- You dressed up today. - He did.
- This isn't dressing up. - You're dressing up these days.
- This? - You're wearing that?
- Hey. - Hey.
You've changed a bit now.
- Me? - Your outfit, I mean.
- Hey, this is... - He matched the colors even.
This just means that my stylist has been working.
- Hey, you. - She matched the colors.
Jong Kook won't be in a car accident at least.
He won't be in a car accident.
- He's safe. - Right.
You punk.
(Some outfits of the members became the talk of the town.)
We'll evaluate our airport outfits for the Jakarta fan-meet?
Hey, our outfits don't grab attention.
No, we have a star among us.
By the way,
- Jong Kook has a nickname. - What is it?
Kim Nipple.
- That wasn't my intention. - Why do you...
- Why are you showing that photo? - Seriously.
- No one looks at that. - Nipple Kook.
(Nipple Kook is the nickname.)
By the way, Seok Jin's outfit...
His outfit...
- Give him a round of applause. - Seriously.
- I agree. - That took a lot of courage.
Can we even count it as an outfit?
(His front-yard outfit requires a lot of courage.)
Let me say one thing about his outfit.
- The worst outfit at the airport. - That's true.
(One-liner evaluation)
- That's true. - That's so true.
- I can guarantee it. - I agree.
Listen. It includes the outfits from Incheon Airport too.
Counting all the outfits at the airport,
his outfit was the worst.
Even the fans in Jakarta...
- were disappointed at your pants. - Right.
Why? They were neat.
I wore them because it was approved.
(Another fan-meet is just around the corner now.)
Everyone.
- The fan-meet is only a week away. - Yes.
We've prepared Running T-Shirts...
which we'll give out at the fan-meet as presents.
- I can't wait. - Let's take a look.
- I designed the shirt. - Jae Seok designed it.
It's pretty.
This looks nice.
I don't see my face.
- It's nice. - I can't see my face.
(Her face disappears into the background.)
- It has to show. - Hey, Haha is right here.
- He really does look like Ant-Man. - Where?
- He's right here. - Where is he?
- That's so small. - Is that really Haha?
- You guys are too mean. - Kwang Soo is on the blade.
- Hey. - Hey.
But people can still see it.
(He's given up.)
Hey, this looks great.
- That's us. - That's where the bottom goes.
- What's that? - That's where the bottom goes.
Our mouth has to show at least.
- That was the penalty. - That's where the bottom goes.
- Se Chan looks handsome there. - This is nice.
- People won't know it's you. - This is great.
Goodness, unbelievable.
This is too mean. You can't see my mouth.
Kids will love it.
- It's nice. It's great. - Kids will.
- We have one more T-shirt. - What is it?
I get the feeling it will be cool. I get that feeling for some reason.
- What's that? - What's that?
- It's cool. - That looks cool.
- What's that? - What is that?
- You look cool. - Hey, you.
- Why are we doing this here? - Hey.
- Why are we showing that here? - What is it?
- "Haha"? - I see.
- This will help. - Why are we suddenly doing this?
Seriously. Where did you get this?
- All the employees... - Darn it.
- from Quan Entertainment... - Listen.
sent us an email and made this very special request.
It's because...
Z-Kiri wasn't the first group Haha was in.
- Listen. - How did you get this?
- Why did you hide that from me? - Let me explain.
- I'm so heartbroken. - He debuted as a solo artist.
- I'm so sad. - He was a solo artist.
So this is Haha?
- This is driving me crazy. - Let me explain.
Seriously. I can't believe this.
"Haha's music stirs up a corner of people's heart,"
"shakes up people's soul,"
"and makes people tremble."
- What is this? - What is this, Haha?
- Did you write that? - Did you write it?
- Did you write that yourself? - Let me keep it.
- How old were you then? - I want to keep it.
- I was overly emotional. - Well done.
"I want to return to the pure root of hip-hop music."
(The ultimate cringing line)
(I want to return to the pure root of hip-hop music.)
(Screaming)
What are you talking about?
This is making me cringe!
- That was too much. - My gosh.
This is so embarrassing.
- What was that? - This is so interesting.
- You're worse than me. - It's so embarrassing.
(And she's the Crazy Poet.)
- You'd better edit this out. - That was something else.
- All right. We'll listen to... - Darn it.
- the title track, "The Gang". - Hey!
- Hey! - Play the music.
(When his debut song is about to play,)
(he explodes.)
We can listen to it?
Hey, don't play it. I'm serious. I'm sorry.
Darn it!
- Hey. I'm sorry. - Is that your voice?
Darn it! Where are you?
(The music starts.)
Hey, where is he?
Where's the audio engineer?
(These precious lyrics show the sentiment of a teenager.)
(Haha wrote this when he was in his teens.)
- Where's the audio engineer? - There are lyrics.
This is nice.
Hey, what should I do?
Hey! Where is he?
Where's the audio engineer?
Hey! Darn it. Hey.
Don't laugh.
Cover your ears. Cover them.
It's like playing "Of Course".
(Exploding with rage)
- Stop playing it. Stop it! - What kind of music is this?
(The lyrics for "The Gang")
Stop!
Please!
(Dashing away)
- Stop playing. - I got goosebumps.
Seriously. Turn it off! I'm begging you!
"Hip-hop music is all about rap."
(This is from 19-year-old Haha.)
"I will bravely put myself out..."
- "in the world." - Yes.
"I can't make or do music without my love for hip-hop."
"The rhythm of hip-hop is coming to me."
(They get the goosebumps.)
The rhythm is coming to him.
- He was such a snob. - What was he talking about?
"The rhythm is coming to me. Yes."
Did it come to you? So did you get to see it?
- I didn't get to see it. - Really?
You switched to reggae because you couldn't see it?
I didn't know that's how Haha felt about music.
All right.
How am I supposed to film the show in this mood?
Just keep your mouth shut and go home today.
Even your shirt says, "Unfortunately" in English.
- You're right. - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
- "Unfortunately". - "Unfortunately".
- "Unfortunately". - That's what it means?
(With Haha who dreamed of flowing with hip-hop rhythms,)
(the race will begin now.)
As you can see from the set next to you,
it will be a couples' race. There will be six couples in all.
- It's a couples' race. - It's a couples' race.
- It's been a while since we had it. - Right.
Four female guests who will be...
your partners along with Ji Hyo and So Min...
are waiting in the back now.
(4 female guests will be revealed shortly.)
- in the back now. - Is that so?
Before we bring them in, you'll use a special method...
- to choose your partners. - How?
Bring in the table.
"Special"?
- What's that? - We'll blindly pick something.
- It's luck of the draw. - My gosh.
Their faces?
- Their faces? I see. - They stamped their faces.
- Like the makeup. - They already stamped their faces.
We'll have to choose from this.
(How will we choose our partners with these cushions?)
Hello, welcome to Running Man.
Today, six couples will be competing in the couples' race.
There are no male guests today.
Yes, I'm so excited.
So everyone will clearly stamp your face...
on the cushions in front of you.
(The male members will choose the partner through the cushions.)
(First up is So Min.)
Goodness.
So Min, that was too much.
(Look! This is how we do things on Running Man.)
So Min.
Gosh. What is that?
Her face disappeared.
That was so tough.
(They completed the stamping with the help of Ji Hyo and So Min.)
Mine looks terrible. Only my nose and lips are crooked.
You will choose the cushion you like...
and stand behind the cushion.
If there are more than one person behind a cushion,
the female member will choose.
If the female guest likes the male guest, they'll partner up.
The members who are rejected will be on the waitlist.
- Hey, that one is really thin. - Hey.
- They all have my nose. - By the way...
Hold on. This is a face of a woman?
Are you sure?
Aren't they all Dharma?
By the way, the one with a clear stamp like this...
- wants to stand out on the show. - That's right.
- This imprint is strong too. - The ones with deep marks...
- want to be funny. - They must be comediennes.
This person stamped it so hard that her nose got crooked.
Didn't this person apply the lipstick afterward?
- The lips are too red. - Didn't she?
That's a strong color.
- It is. It's strong. - The lighter ones are better.
- She stamped her lips too. - Wait.
Ji Hyo is wearing red lipstick today.
Let's avoid this one.
- You're right. - Ji Hyo and So Min's are here too.
- We'll know by the lip color. - This one is nice.
Did this person even try?
- As for this person... - I have no idea.
- This is so scary. - What is that?
- It's so scary. - Her face looks like a Hahoe mask.
She looks just like a Hahoe mask.
Hey, isn't this obvious...
Isn't it obvious that this is Na Rae's face?
- I'm 100 percent sure. - Right.
I'm not sure about this.
(She has the same facial features with Na Rae.)
I bet that's So Min's cushion.
This one has to be So Min's.
Look. This one has a wide face.
I really can't tell who they are by the marks.
I really have no idea.
How can we choose from these?
- Let's take turns to pick. - Number six?
- I'll take number 1. - You'll take number 1.
- The makeup... - I'll go next.
- Why did you choose this one? - Because...
- she's wearing light makeup. - Because of the light makeup?
- Light makeup. - That's Ji Hyo's.
Come on out, number four.
(Haha chooses number 4, the ambitious entertainer.)
I'll choose number five.
I'll go with number three.
(Seok Jin chooses Dharma's lookalike.)
- I'll go with number 6. - Number 6?
Yes, I was going to choose this one from the get-go.
I'll choose the one I'm mostly likely to win.
I'll go with number six.
(I'll choose the one I'm mostly likely to win.)
(He chooses the same one as Se Chan.)
There he goes again.
Let's do this. Seriously.
Hey, they... Do you know which one is yours?
- Yes, we know. - We stamped our faces earlier.
- Really? - You do?
All right. We'll start from number one then.
- Okay. - Number one.
Number one, come on out.
Who's number one? Who is it?
Her makeup is light. She's wearing light makeup.
Come on out, number one.
- That's cute. - Who is she?
- She has very small feet. - She's short.
(Who is the 1st guest that exudes the presence of a cute girl?)
- It's her. - It was Sunny.
- It's been so long, Sunny. - Hey, Sunny.
(She's our trustworthy leading vocalist in Girls' Generation.)
(This witty and chatty energizer is a hit on variety shows.)
(Sunny, the queen of cute acts that wins over people right away)
(The 1st guest is Sunny, the Energizer.)
- Sunny. - Sunny.
- My gosh. - It's been so long, Sunny.
How long has it been?
- Who picked number one? - Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - It's me.
- Hi. - It's you.
- Soon Gyu, it's been a while. - It truly has been.
- I'm Sunny. - No, you're Soon Gyu.
- I'm Sunny. - Step back.
- We're filming right now. - Sunny, you can refuse.
- Hello. - It doesn't have to be Jong Kook.
- Sunny, you can refuse. - Hello.
- Why would I refuse? - What?
(Why would I refuse him?)
- I'm just telling you. - Why would I refuse?
Why would you say that?
- She would've refused you. - "Why would I refuse?"
They were a team back then.
All right, let's reveal the second lady.
No one picked her.
- Number two. - No one picked her?
- No one picked her? - No one.
- Her face was... - She looked like Jigsaw.
- Please come on out. - I hope one of them steps up.
Maybe it's Ji Hyo.
(Is number 2 with the red lips Ji Hyo?)
It's Ye Won!
(It's Kim Ye Won, the beautiful, acting queen.)
- My goodness. - Ye Won, is this you?
Yes.
(She's the charming girl from "Sunny".)
(She has a beautiful face and amazing acting skills.)
(Number 2 is Kim Ye Won, the newly rising actress.)
(This face is you?)
My gosh.
- Hello. - She plays that bad girl in that...
- Can we switch? - No.
- We can't? - Is it too late?
- Ye Won, please stand there. - Okay.
All right.
- How could no one pick me? - Next up.
Excuse me. So Min and Ji Hyo should go in there.
Should we?
We shall.
- Did Seok Jin choose number three? - Yes.
Please come on out.
(Who is Seok Jin's number 3 who looks like Dharma?)
Who could it be?
Who is that?
No, it's a guest.
It's a guest.
(It's Song Ji Hyo, the sister of Running Man.)
(He tosses the cushion.)
Did you see what he just did?
- I'm sorry about that. - I'm sorry.
- We couldn't react well. - By the way,
- Ji Hyo could refuse him. - You're too harsh.
I'm sorry. It was a force of habit.
- I'm really excited. - She could refuse him.
- It was a force of habit. - She could.
Don't refuse him!
If you refuse, you'll get tossed around.
(The matching won't end anytime soon.)
- You'll have to take him. - It won't end.
- It really won't end. - Please pick.
You should embrace him.
- You're definitely... - It looks like his nose.
- It's me. - I didn't know it was her.
- I had no idea either. - It doesn't look like her.
Next is number four.
I picked number four.
Okay, which number is it?
- Number four. - Okay.
Come on out.
She must like to act funny.
She's like a comedienne.
(Who could this funny lady be?)
- Goodness! - SUNMI!
(She's the rising solo queen, SUNMI.)
(She's known for her uniqueness and amazing performances.)
(Every single music of hers is on the charts.)
(She conquered variety shows with her surprising charms.)
(Everyone fell in love with her charms.)
(SUNMI is number 4.)
(He's happy to see her.)
We're a team again.
- My gosh. - We're a team again?
- No way. - No way.
- We're a team. - We're done for.
It's So Min.
I'm so happy to see you.
My gosh.
SUNMI. You can refuse him.
- You can refuse him! - SUNMI.
Who's left?
There's Jae Seok and Se Chan.
- And me. - And Kwang Soo.
I'll refuse.
Really?
Okay!
You were so happy to see her.
- What's wrong with him today? - It's his birthday.
- It's his birthday today. - Seriously?
- I'm so sorry! - It's his birthday.
It's okay. Just think of it as your gift to him.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
- It's okay. - He must be hurt.
They even hugged each other.
Next is me.
- Both 5 and 6 will appear together. - Number 5.
- Together? - Yes.
- One of them is So Min. - You're right.
- Please. - One.
(1 of the 2 is So Min's face.)
(Could Jae Seok's pick be her?)
(Or could Kwang Soo and Se Chan's pick be her?)
Two.
(The rest of the day depends on this.)
Three.
(Please let the guest be number 6.)
Who is it?
So Min.
- No. - Hello.
It's Ye Won.
(She's the smiley announcer who looks like...)
(she'd only bring good news.)
(With her friendliness and way of emceeing,)
(she's conquered educational and variety programs.)
(Today, she'll be doing field work.)
- Right. - She's an announcer.
Ye Won.
- It's been a long time. - I'm so happy to see you.
- It's been a long time. - It has been.
(And another lady walks in amidst the indifference.)
(Hello)
Are you number six?
Their numbers are important.
- We don't know who picked what. - All right.
1 of them is 5, and the other one is 6.
- All right. - Okay.
- Whose is it? - Ye Won is...
number five.
(Jae Seok picked Ye Won.)
- So Min is number 6. - Ye Won is number 5.
Doesn't only one of us survive?
I was popular.
(Se Chan kicks cushion number 6.)
(He's in a hurry.)
I was popular.
- My cushion was so popular. - Again!
- One of us needs to... - I'll switch to number two.
Hey.
- So Min can pick one of them. - They'll be fighting for her.
- So Min, please pick. - This feels great.
I feel so great. Two people picked my cushion.
I was so startled to see both of you pick it.
- All right. - One of us has to be a couple?
Of course.
Where do you think you're going?
I'd like you to sing a song.
(Criteria for becoming her partner: Singing ability)
- I'd like a love song. - A love song?
- A love song? - Yes.
- Please sing one measure. - Do it.
Hurry up.
(I love you)
(The only thing I can say)
(Halfhearted)
He's singing so halfheartedly.
- It's too halfhearted. - It's a love song.
Hurry up.
(Singing)
(My love)
(He doesn't finish singing.)
So Min.
She might pick the one...
- who's not putting in much effort. - I gave my all.
She might do that.
(My love for you)
(They do their best.)
(She's happy to see them fight.)
All right.
So Min, please pick.
I'd like you to do rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Do we need to win or lose?
- If you win, you become partners. - You need to win.
You need to win.
- I'll pick the winner. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(It's a draw.)
What was that?
(It's neck and neck.)
Are you trying to win?
You are, right?
- You are, right? - Yes.
- I can't do this. - Again.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(It's a draw once again.)
(They're betting everything on this.)
This feels great.
If they make a draw once again, maybe they should all be a team.
- I'll give you 10 dollars. - Rock-paper...
- I'll give you 100 dollars. - Rock...
(They try to fix the match by offering money.)
Rock...
- My gosh. - What's wrong?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins.)
- Yes! - Yes!
(He will be So Min's partner.)
(He was happy at first...)
(and then realized the prize.)
(I've won.)
- By the way, - They're meant to be.
So Min got her way.
- They're meant to be. - She likes Se Chan.
- Everything went her way. - You've won me.
- You've won me. - She said I've won her.
"You've won me."
Hold on. Jae Seok hasn't been chosen yet.
- Ye Won needs to pick him. - Right.
- Ye Won. - You can refuse him.
Don't fool yourself that all announcers like you.
Okay.
Ye Won, don't worry.
I'm very nonchalant, so don't worry.
Hurry up.
- Someone else wants me too. - Who?
Who wants you?
- You better watch your mouth. - Hey.
- Are you going somewhere? - Never mind.
- There's someone you want. - No, it's not that.
I didn't want to burden her.
I'd like to meet the other members.
- Okay! - Okay!
(She makes her decision.)
Hey, go away!
Go away!
- Okay! - You acted so arrogantly.
Okay. Okay.
- Hey. - He's blushing!
Okay! Number five! Fine.
Those who have been rejected, gather here.
You can choose those who already have partners too.
Then the men will make the choice.
You can pick them too?
The men will make the choice.
- It's not over. - Really?
I still have a chance.
Then let's start with Ye Won.
(They begin with Ye Won who wasn't picked at all.)
- I'd like... - Pick someone...
you're comfortable with.
I'd like to pick Kwang Soo with whom I've worked with.
Yes!
(She chooses him because they've worked together before.)
If this is the case...
- Did you just accept her? - If this is the case...
Can I refuse?
Can I?
If I can refuse, then I will.
Really?
(It's a turn of events.)
- No way. - Kwang Soo.
- Did you refuse? - What?
What is this?
(She's the first guest to be rejected by him.)
- I mean... - Let's talk.
It's not like that.
We're just really close, that's all.
(He doesn't know what to do.)
Ye Won, this is a dog-eat-dog show.
I'm sorry.
Next up is SUNMI.
I pick...
(Whom will she pick?)
Kwang Soo.
(She also picks him.)
He's so popular.
- He's so popular. - Why did you pick him?
(SUNMI is nervous.)
- Kwang Soo. - She picked him.
- 1, 2, 3. - Ye Won is glaring at him.
I'd like to refuse.
Why are you playing hard to get?
(Now, he's refused SUNMI's offer as well.)
You have your eyes set on Jang Ye Won, don't you?
Hey, watch what you say.
- You could end up with So Min. - Wake up!
They'd become so awkward if they met like this.
Ye Won.
This is hard.
Ye Won. 1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo was straightforward,)
(but Jae Seok and Haha had no chance to appeal.)
(Who will Ye Won choose?)
I'll make an honest choice. I choose Jong Kook.
- What does that make us? - Seriously?
What about us then?
(Me?)
Seriously?
- Kwang Soo, you can go home now. - The losers!
What about us then?
- Jong Kook... - Yes.
- Me? - He's quite popular too.
You have to choose between her and Sunny.
It's her or Sunny.
Can you tell us why you chose Jong Kook?
I've never met him before, so I'm curious.
Is it because you saw me for the first time?
Unbelievable. We haven't met either.
Do you know what's funny?
Unbelievable.
(Is that your reason for choosing him?)
- We haven't met. - Don't say it like that.
- Gosh. - You haven't met me either.
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
We haven't met, you know.
No way. Is he making a fuss over this?
- Ye Won, how could you? - You only saw me on TV.
I know. We haven't met either.
Jong Kook, make up your mind.
What? Well, Sunny...
(So why did Sunny choose Jong Kook?)
You're my dream guy.
Her dream guy!
(You're my dream guy.)
- Just like that? - That's out of the blue.
We've known each other for a while, so when did that happen?
How could I have suddenly become your dream guy?
Okay. Even though she might've not meant it,
I choose Sunny.
- Okay. - I choose Sunny.
(I should've said something better.)
- Gosh. - So we're back to square one.
He stuck with his original partner.
All options are open!
- Right. - The market is open.
Let's go. We start with Kim Ye Won again.
I choose Jae Seok.
Okay!
- I choose Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(I'm sorry about last time.)
Then...
Haha, be my partner.
(She's the only one left.)
- What's there to think about? - Please?
- There's nothing to think about. - Please.
Beg some more.
Haha, please.
She dropped to her knees!
- Okay, you can get up now. - Okay!
(Ye Won and Haha become the final couple.)
Okay.
(The couples: Jae Seok and Ye Won, Sunny and Jong Kook,)
(Haha and Ye Won, Se Chan and So Min,)
(Kwang Soo and SUNMI, Seok Jin and Ji Hyo)
The one happiest with her partner is So Min.
(Se Chan isn't my type.)
She keeps mimicking Sunny.
"You're my dream guy."
(Just a while ago)
Stop it already.
(It's too cheesy.)
It's what Sunny said.
"You're my dream guy."
- Is that so? - Yes.
(So Min learned a bad thing from Sunny.)
- Really? - "You're my dream guy."
She keeps on mimicking Sunny.
You'll only confuse Se Chan, so cut it out.
Why are you angry about it though?
(Is he jealous?)
- Why are you angry? - What was that?
- That's so weird. - Know your place!
The timing was so off.
Why would you get angry about it?
I'm worried about Se Chan.
- Me? - I don't want him to get hurt.
Since it's hot outside, we'll keep the interview short.
First, we'll start with SUNMI.
- Hello. - A new song must be out.
Yes, that's right.
Tell us about that new song then.
Actually, I released a song...
that directly aims at "Apgujeong Nallari" by Jae Seok.
- It's called "LALALAY". - "LALALAY"?
Really?
I'd love to hear the song.
Then can you show us how the song goes?
It'll be good.
(They look forward to the master performer.)
(Hey!)
(They react to the shocking punch.)
Amazing.
(The artist is back with a richer vibe.)
Look at her playing with her hair.
This is awesome.
(Then she slows down into a thrust!)
You'll scrape your knees.
You'll get burned by the asphalt.
(The feeble men of the show worry about her getting hurt.)
(She completes "LALALAY" in one piece.)
This will be a hit.
That was awesome!
Did you see that killer move?
SUNMI, that was amazing.
It's another big hit.
Her songs never get old.
Above everything else, this song made the biggest impact.
- Nothing's better in the heat. - That's right.
Also, she's here to promote the song anyway.
- Her goal has been met. - She's not just here for that.
All right then. Next, we have an artist...
who's the senior among most girl groups.
She's like Kyun Mi Ri of the K-pop industry.
(To put it simply...)
(The actor who's been in the spotlight for a long time.)
Don't you agree?
She's like King Taejo of the K-pop industry.
Please welcome Sunny!
(Sunny also known as Soon Gyu)
It's Sunny!
I'm not just saying this, but Sunny's always the same.
I concur.
- Exactly. - Thank you.
She hasn't changed since she debuted.
- You're the same. - Really?
- Right? - That's not true.
What's the secret to your self-maintenance?
- I sleep a lot. - I see.
When I get stressed...
So you drink.
You're just like Ji Hyo.
She sleeps a lot too.
- I rest when I'm stressed. - I like staying at home.
They're not at all the same...
because Ji Hyo's not the cute type.
(Unlike Sunny...)
- Meanwhile, Sunny is super cute. - Exactly.
I'm cute too, you know.
You're my dream guy.
You're my dream guy!
- Jong Kook hates it. - You're my dream guy.
My heart almost stopped.
You're my dream guy!
Ji Hyo, try this.
- My heart almost stopped. - I'm a troublemaker!
(Jong Kook!)
(I was wrong to say that.)
I'm a troublemaker.
That was good, Ji Hyo.
- She's gotten better. - How amazing is her acting?
She was relentless.
- Ji Hyo... - She forced herself to do it.
That was relentless of her.
Good job, Ji Hyo.
Why on earth does she like Jong Kook?
I've known her for over 10 years now.
- Unbelievable. - Now she says I'm her dream guy.
There's a script which girl group members can follow.
- What kind of script? - How to avoid questions about men.
Really?
Ask if she has a boyfriend.
Sunny, are you seeing someone?
My fans are my boyfriends.
See?
(My fans are my boyfriends.)
- What did I tell you? - Still?
She answered before he finished his question.
They have scripts.
Are they provided by SM Entertainment?
- Are they? - A new one is released annually.
Ji Hyo, do you have a boyfriend?
I...
will soon have one.
What are you saying?
He's my dream guy!
(Here's my boyfriend.)
- What... - What's wrong with you?
- My dream guy. - Seriously?
I'm a troublemaker!
Gosh, what is that?
(Her cuteness brings chills to people's spines.)
She's acting weird today.
What's wrong with her?
Is she drunk?
I'm a troublemaker!
She must've practiced her dancing too much.
I'm bored, so why don't you two try dating?
Why should we date because you're bored?
About two weeks.
It's not possible since we're a family.
This is supposed to be fun, you know.
Next up, we have Kim Ye Won.
We were introduced to Ye Won...
through her charismatic performance in "Sunny".
So how do you know Kwang Soo?
There was a drama series...
I played a guest role in.
- I played his girlfriend. - Right.
- His girlfriend? - That's right.
It must've been brief, but was anything memorable?
(Without hesitating)
Not really.
- But... - Okay!
So who is Kwang Soo to you?
Someone tall.
(Kwang Soo is just someone who's tall.)
- Someone tall. - That's a good one.
- Nice. - This is good.
The interview flows without any hitches.
Nice.
Anyway, I hear that Ye Won...
majored in dancing.
- So... - Really?
So instead of an interview,
we'll watch the performance she has prepared...
for us today.
- A performance? - Even though it's nothing grand...
(Just how good of a dancer is she?)
The music is playing.
It'll only take us a second to assess her.
(My gosh)
Her lines are incredible.
It's so cool.
She really did study dancing.
(Her lines put an end to any doubts they had.)
Her lines prove she trained.
Did she learn Korean dancing?
It's been a while since she quit though.
(She's this good even though she quit a decade ago.)
Did she learn Korean dancing?
(Here come the turns.)
(She spins.)
Look at her spin!
Even on this asphalt...
You look so pretty!
(She manages to land 7 consecutive spins.)
(She then goes the other way while spinning.)
She's adorable.
(She got greedy with her spins...)
(and ended up stumbling.)
That was for real.
(She even showed that she's human too.)
Let's give her a round of applause.
(Still, she managed to prove that she learned to dance.)
We then also have another Ye Won with us.
Please welcome Jang Ye Won.
Do you remember the Flinging Competition...
we had on this show?
She hosted the event for us, remember?
- It was fun. - It's been quite a while.
You're right.
You said back then that you like Kwang Soo.
- That's right. - It was in Bundang.
She said she liked Kwang Soo.
You said you liked Kwang Soo.
Did I?
(Did I?)
- Of course. - That's what you said.
Did I really say that?
- I remember it clearly. - Is that so?
You said you liked him.
It was such a long time ago.
Anyway, we thank Ye Won for being here today.
So now that you've partnered up, I'll explain today's race.
You must unlock the secret to the prophecy...
that contains a request...
forwarded to the deity of light and deity of darkness.
You are humans who serve the deity of light.
Among you are the deity of light, the deity of darkness,
and the prophet.
That sounds complicated.
The deity of light, the deity of darkness, and the prophet.
Let me show you what the prophet left behind.
Sunny's good at these kinds of mysteries.
Can't we keep races like this to once a month?
Maybe you're the deity of light.
I just saw the word "apocalypse."
(From the beginning of time...)
"From the beginning of time, a strong power of darkness..."
"forewarned us of an apocalypse of the human world."
(Narrating)
(Seok Jin is reading the text solemnly when...)
(Jae Seok blocks Seok Jin's view.)
I was reading that.
Well...
I was reading that!
I was getting a close-up shot.
Actually, I was getting one myself.
(It was my close-up shot.)
(Seok Jin has been failing to win a close-up shot for 9 years.)
"The deity of darkness has been tormenting innocent people..."
"and disturbing the world by colluding with evil powers."
(The deity of darkness will become stronger and stronger.)
(However, if you don't give up on light, the world will be saved.)
To find and eliminate the deity of light,
the deity of darkness is disguised as a human.
The deity of light is disguised as a human too...
to eliminate the deity of darkness.
If you help the deity of light eliminate the deity of darkness...
before the deity of light is eliminated,
the deity of light and humans win.
If the deity of darkness eliminates the deity of light first,
the deity of darkness wins alone and receives a prize.
After each mission, the winning team receives a hint.
But if the prophet gets eliminated, hints will stop being distributed.
(Once the prophet gets eliminated, hints will stop being distributed.)
Therefore, it is important for humans...
- to find the prophet. - We have to protect the prophet.
There is a prophet?
There are is a prophet, a deity of darkness, and a deity of light.
After you change into uniforms,
- we'll start the race. - Okay!
(Will the humans manage to drive out the deity of darkness?)
(They start on a mission to get the first hint.)
Here we go.
The first mission that can give you a hint is called...
Telepathy Music Cue.
(Telepathy Music Cue)
Yes!
- "Music Cue"? - In this mission,
men and women will take turns.
When the song plays,
- you have to guess its title. - Okay!
In the first round, women will say the answers.
The male partners have to push the buzzer...
to give their female partners a chance to answer.
The female partner...
chooses a time position, and the song will play...
for a second from that position.
She has to say the correct artist name and song title.
If her answer turns out to be correct,
- she will dance to the music. - Dance time!
- Sunny is a great dancer. - I am.
But if someone dances better than the person who said the answer,
- the point will go to that person. - Okay!
- Isn't it unfair to Ye Won? - What do you mean?
(Are we going to dance?)
Her specialty is current affairs.
Can't we do a common knowledge quiz instead?
I might be worse at that.
- Seoul National University Quiz... - No.
Didn't you do a knowledge test to get the job?
I did, but that was a long time ago.
(She doesn't have so much new knowledge.)
The men and women's scores will be added up,
and the top two teams will receive a hint.
The team in first place will receive a hint about the prophet...
and a hint about a deity of their choice.
The team in second place will only receive...
a hint about a deity of their choice.
- That's nice. - Ye Won might be the prophet.
That's right.
Her name sounds like "prophet".
- But we have 2 Ye Wons. - We have 2.
They are both...
- Us two. - What?
- The prophet. - Their names...
- There are two Ye Won's. - sound like "prophet".
(Could one of the two Ye Won's be the prophet?)
Your reaction was so awkward.
Sunny just reacted very awkwardly.
Could Sunny be the deity of light?
- That was awkward. - Do you have a role?
- Like the sun? - The sun.
Kwang means "light" too.
No. In his name, it means "crazy".
Does it mean "crazy"?
(In his name, it means "crazy".)
- It means "light". - It means "crazy".
It means "light", not "crazy".
Who would want their child's name to mean "crazy"?
(Who would want their child's name to mean "crazy"?)
That's why I was surprised.
- Are you mocking my grandpa? - I was shocked.
It means "crazy" and "excellent".
(Kwang Soo is excellently crazy.)
Male members, please step up.
- Okay. - You're the buzzers.
(The men will push the buzzer, and the women will say the answer.)
Ye Won...
was a radio DJ until recently.
But I don't know many new songs.
- You don't know what? - I don't know new songs.
You should.
- Okay. - Okay?
(We can't wait to see their teamwork.)
- Okay! - Okay!
All right. I'll play the song for a second...
- around 1 minute in. - Around 1 minute in.
It'll play for a second.
Start...
(Do a good job!)
(What song will play?)
the music.
What?
(It literally played for a second.)
That's too short.
- It's a girl group. - All right.
To push the buzzer, the male members have to...
What are we doing?
rip off a name tag.
(Rip off a name tag.)
Gosh!
(What happened?)
Okay!
Rip off a name tag.
(The name tag is ripped off.)
(Se Chan rips off Kwang Soo's name tag right away.)
Okay!
I expected it.
Kwang Soo had his back to me.
You stupid.
So Min.
You were amazing, but I don't know this song.
You do. It's a girl group.
- So Min. - So Min,
- choose a time position. - Can I?
Choose something before or after the previous one.
Around two minutes in.
- Can't I tell her the answer? - You can't.
I'll play it for a second around two minutes in.
Play the music.
(The song will play for a second around 2 minutes in.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E466 Running Man
"The Deity of Light, The Deity of Darkness & The Prophet"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
- I have no idea. - How can we know this?
It literally played for a second.
It's a song by Girls' Generation.
(It's a song by Girls' Generation.)
It's my song?
(Puzzled)
"Into the New World".
That's wrong.
(Wrong)
(The men have to do a buzzer mission again.)
All right.
For this buzzer...
(The next buzzer mission is...)
Rip off a name tag.
(The next mission is ripping off a name tag again.)
(Jae Seok grabs Haha's name tag.)
(Jae Seok is faster than anyone.)
Yes!
(Jae Seok rips off a name tag before anyone else.)
(I did it first!)
Jae Seok.
The people next to me are too strong.
He punched me!
(He punched me!)
I didn't!
He punched me!
I didn't do that!
Jong Kook goes too far.
(He frightens me.)
(Way to go!)
Ye Won.
Choose a time position.
One second in.
- No. That's not a good idea. - 50 seconds in?
- We have to hear the voice. - 50 seconds in?
- It's over. - One second in.
- 50 seconds in. - 1 second in.
- It's 1 second in. - 50 seconds in.
- 50 seconds in. - I'll play it 1 second in.
I'll play it for a second one second in.
Play the music.
(Obvious)
(You know what it is, right?)
You know what it is, right?
No! You can't tell her!
You can't tell her!
Hurry up!
Rip it off!
Ye Won. What's your answer?
Isn't this an old song?
It's been...
Ye Won!
- Countdown! - Five.
Four.
Ye Won!
- Three. - Lee Hyo Lee?
What?
"10 Minutes" by Lee Hyo Lee.
- No. - Is it wrong?
(Seok Jin thinks it's wrong.)
(Is it really "10 Minutes" by Lee Hyo Lee?)
(Jae Seok and Ye Won get it right.)
(Ye Won did it!)
- What did you do? - I knew it too.
(It was a good call to play the song 1 second in.)
(The intro gave it away.)
("10 Minutes" by Lee Hyo Lee, with its unique intro,)
(was a national hit 16 years ago.)
(It was an easy one for Ye Won,)
(who knows mostly old songs.)
It was a good call to play it one second in.
- Do I need to dance? - Yes, to "10 Minutes".
Just dance.
- Don't worry. - I know the dance.
(You can steal the point by dancing better.)
(SUNMI joins.)
(Ye Won and SUNMI dance together.)
SUNMI, I'm sorry!
You're better than me.
- What is SUNMI doing? - SUNMI!
What is she doing?
Ye Won knows the dance too.
- She knows it. - This is correct.
(The girls who grew up watching Hyo Lee cover her dance.)
(Even the last part is perfect.)
SUNMI is so brutal.
- She's brutal. - She's really brutal.
Ye Won!
I knew the dance.
Sunny, why didn't you dance?
I don't know it.
- You don't? - I don't.
- Do better next time. - Okay!
- Jae Seok and Ye Won win one point. - Yes!
(They win 1 point because Ye Won danced as well as SUNMI.)
This time, the women will do a buzzer mission.
The men will say the answer. The women will compete.
Trust me.
So Min, I know every song.
(Okay. Let me try.)
SUNMI, get ready to rip off a name tag.
- Here we go. - You might rip off a name tag.
Ji Hyo is really good.
You shouldn't have stood next to her.
Good.
The buzzer mission is...
ripping off a name tag.
(It's ripping off a name tag again.)
(Who will get the chance?)
(Sunny rips off a name tag.)
(It took her only 1 second.)
- She ripped it off! - Okay!
(It's so easy to rip off Ye Won's name tag.)
Okay! Good job!
What's with you two?
Haha.
The people next to me are too scary.
(The people next to me are too scary.)
- They're too scary. - Ye Won...
Ye Won is so funny.
She feels so competitive.
(She feels more competitive than anyone else.)
But in the end, her name tag gets ripped off first.
She's so bad at games.
She can't play any games.
But she's so enthusiastic.
What should we do?
Should we play it one second in too?
- Let's hear the beginning. - They won't get their first one.
We'll play it one second in too.
One second in.
We might hear, "Summer is here!"
- Right. - You never know.
Then you can't be wrong.
I hope it's a song with a super long intro.
I'll play it for a second one second in.
Start the music.
(Obvious)
(I got it.)
- I know this one! - SUNMI!
- SUNMI! - I know it!
I know it!
(Only Jong Kook can say the answer.)
Be quiet.
- Countdown! - I know the answer.
It's a song by Brown Eyed Girls.
"Abracadabra".
("Abracadabra" by Brown Eyed Girls)
(Is it correct?)
It's correct.
Okay!
It has to be played one second in.
It's definitely one second in.
(It was a good strategy.)
(The intro is hard to miss.)
("Abracadabra", a hit from 10 years ago, has a catchy beat.)
(The Arrogant Dance swept the country.)
(The song starts with an unforgettable intro.)
(Dance time follows.)
- She doesn't disappoint. - Seriously.
- She doesn't disappoint. - I know.
(Her dance is perfect.)
- She is an idol singer. - She is good.
She is an idol singer.
(Her Arrogant Dance is unrivaled.)
- She is good. She is good. - That's great.
(We have to do something.)
- There we go. - Come on.
- There we go. - Who dances like that?
(The two sexy dancers)
Who dances like that?
They are good.
- What is that? - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - This isn't a part of the dance.
Look at So Min!
(Upset)
(The scene-stealer appears.)
(What is that?)
What are you doing?
(Sexy)
Go back to your spot.
What are you doing?
- You aren't sexy. - What are you doing?
- You aren't sexy. - Does your neck hurt?
Go back to your spot.
She is pretending to be sexy.
- What is her problem? - Go back to your spot.
Why does she...
Why does she keep tousling her hair?
She is the worst.
I get everything else,
but why does So Min keep tousling her hair?
She also put her hand on her neck and bit her lips.
(Seeing her bite her lips was worse.)
Why does she keep doing that?
- Why does she keep doing that? - I did it to look sexy.
- For goodness' sake. - She pretended to be sexy.
For goodness' sake.
I approve of Sunny's dance. The team gets a point.
She is an idol singer.
- You know, - She is the best idol singer.
I forgot about it.
She is good. Everyone can dance well.
This time, you need to use your brain.
It's the women's turn.
- I am in trouble. - Brain.
Who is the brainy one?
This is your last chance.
- It's the women's buzzer mission. - Ye Won, let's do this.
This time, the buzzer mission is the random three-line poem.
(The random three-line poem)
Your poem needs to make sense.
I am sorry,
but can't you give us a mission that requires knowledge, not wits?
Let's go.
Let's start with So Min.
I am nervous.
Get ready. Set, go.
(Topic: Cat)
Don't tell on me. Okay, Se Chan?
Meow!
(Don't tell on me. Okay, Se Chan? Meow!)
- What was that? - Nice!
- Why? - Why?
- Nice! Why? - Why?
"Don't tell on me. Okay, Se Chan? Meow!"
Why did she act cute for no reason?
- It made no sense. - Why do you say that?
- It's Ye Won's turn. - Why? Why was that unacceptable?
That was totally unacceptable.
(Ye Won goes next.)
Get ready.
Set, go.
(Topic: Jee Seok Jin)
He is past it.
Seok Jin is already past it.
I am serious.
(I am serious.)
- What does that even mean? - It works.
It works.
- Whatever it is, he is past it. - You should have explained further.
- What does it mean? - It makes sense, but...
- In any case, he is past it. - Are you a doctor?
- It doesn't matter. - What does it mean?
It doesn't matter.
- Seok Jin must be annoyed. - It feels strange.
Good job.
Get ready.
Ji Hyo, let's go.
Say whatever comes to your mind.
- It just needs to make sense. - It just needs to make sense.
- It just needs to make sense. - Let's go.
Get ready. Set, go.
(Topic: Slang)
Hey! Dude! Hey!
(It's like a scene from a famous movie.)
What was that?
- What? - What was that?
- It works. - It makes sense!
- Hey! Dude! - Hey!
She is funny.
- Today, - She is witty.
Ji Hyo is witty.
Hey! Hey!
- Ye Won is extremely nervous. - Ye Won.
The competition rate for the anchor audition...
was 5,000 to 1, right?
- It was 3,800 to 2. - 3,800 to 2.
That's what she overcame to become an anchor.
She is impressive.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- In 1, 2, - Focus. Focus.
three.
It's a squid. How disgusting! My goodness!
(She created perfect sentences about squid.)
(That was incredible!)
I didn't expect that.
- I didn't expect that. - I can't help but approve.
Although it wasn't funny, it made sense.
- Ye Won is the winner. - She is good at this.
- It was so clean. - It was nice.
Now, pick the time.
- What? - Was that the mission?
- Was that the mission? - That's right.
- Come on! - That was the mission.
The winner gets to pick the time.
(Everyone forgot that this was just a buzzer mission.)
Ye Won, pick the time.
I pick...
- 2 seconds. - 2 seconds.
1 second from 2 seconds in. Play the music.
(It's a crucial hint.)
- Let me answer! - You can't answer.
- Me! - That was crucial.
Red Velvet's "Red Flavor".
(I know the answer.)
(It's correct.)
("Red Flavor" starts with the title of the song.)
(We got it right!)
It's a good idea to pick the beginning.
So Min, I know all the songs.
I know all the songs. Just give me a chance to answer.
Hold on. I will give you a chance.
This buzzer mission is a bit unusual.
(What's the buzzer mission for the female members?)
Steal a shoe from a male member who isn't your partner.
(Steal a shoe from a male member who isn't your partner.)
Hurry up.
(Complete chaos)
(She is having a lonely fight.)
(Come here!)
(I will run that way.)
(Ji Hyo follows...)
(and switches her target to Jae Seok.)
(They aim for a shoe each.)
Come on.
Give it to me!
(Taking off)
I got it!
(Sunny succeeded to steal Kwang Soo's shoe.)
It's over.
Please stop these women.
For goodness' sake.
My goodness.
Please stop Ye Won and Ji Hyo.
They didn't let go even when the mission was over.
(Ye Won tries hard but fails most of the times.)
Sunny is really good at this.
- Sunny is so enthusiastic. - The others didn't stand a chance.
She is so strong.
Ye Won, do something!
- I tried hard! - 3 or 4 seconds?
3 or 4 seconds?
- Let's go. - 3 or 4 seconds? 3 seconds?
- Okay. 3 seconds, please. - 1 second from 3 seconds in.
All right.
Music, cue.
(This time, they hear a breathing sound.)
(A breathing sound?)
Hey.
- You know this one, right? - I know this one!
I know this one. Get me this chance.
- I know this one. - Okay.
- I know this one. - In 5, 4...
"Coming-of-Age Ceremony" by Park Ji Yoon.
(It's "Coming-of-Age Ceremony" by Park Ji Yoon.)
He is correct.
If you dance well, you could steal the answer.
Okay. Okay.
- What was the dance? - So Min, do something.
Participate if you know the dance.
("Coming-of-Age Ceremony" plays.)
That's it, So Min. Dance!
That's perfect.
Participate if you know the dance.
("Coming-of-Age Ceremony" plays.)
That's it, So Min. Dance!
- That's perfect. - Good job!
(It's the last chance to steal a point.)
(I won't let anyone take my point.)
They are good.
(Everyone enters the stage.)
(The stage is full.)
(She is cheerful all by herself.)
- My goodness. - No, no.
Jump in. Jump in.
Ye Won, what are you doing?
- Hurry up and jump in. - There you go.
- There you go. - Come on.
- What should I do? - Do this.
(I don't know what I am doing.)
So Min, go back to your spot.
SUNMI, dance over there.
Dance over there.
Dance in front of the camera.
So Min, go back to your spot.
(The dancing queen got a hold of a camera.)
So Min. So Min.
So Min, go back to your spot.
(Everyone tries hard...)
(to show a sexy dance.)
Gosh, So Min is so funny.
Ye Won, you are doing great.
(It's a complete mess.)
All right, Ye Won.
(I am no longer So Min.)
(Creaking)
So Min!
(Next to the dancing zombie)
- You are doing great. - You are doing great.
You are doing great.
Ji Hyo, go back to your spot.
(I close my eyes now)
- Go back to your spot. - Go back to your spot.
(The last shot is mine.)
Go back to your spot.
Good job.
You did a good job.
- You did a good job. - No one looked at me.
No one was exceptionally good.
They were about the same level.
- They were about the same level. - So Min grabbed her neck.
- She got the last shot. - Come on.
So Min was imitating a zombie.
(Was she infected with the sexy virus?)
Jang Ye Won.
Jang Ye Won was like a thug.
She danced like a middle-aged man.
She danced very differently.
Kim Ye Won did the entire dance routine.
I knew the dance routine.
- SUNMI danced at the end... - No one was exceptionally good.
because there was no space. The cameraman...
Ouch! Why did you step on my foot?
(Stepping)
(Ouch! Why did you step on my foot?)
- Why? - What?
- What? - I didn't do anything.
- Who stepped on my foot? - I didn't do anything.
Who stepped on your foot?
Everyone...
except for two people danced well.
(He didn't give any names.)
Seriously, the two of them were the worst.
There should be a mission for Jang Ye Won!
Jang Ye Won is expectant.
Since everyone was about the same level,
- Sunny will get a point. - Okay!
(In the end, Sunny gets a point!)
Sunny.
Sunny is too good.
- Sunny is good. - She is good at games.
She is so good.
- You can't ignore her experience. - Seriously.
You can't ignore her experience.
With this, Team Jong Kook and Sunny takes...
- first place. - Okay!
Jong Kook and Sunny,
please come forward.
- Okay. - Sunny is really good.
Sunny is either a lucky one or a member with a role.
- It's 1 of the 2. - That's not true.
- I only played the game diligently. - You will get...
a hint of the prophet for free.
Thank you.
One of them could be the prophet.
This is...
What is this?
(Which hint did they receive on the prophet?)
(Prophet)
(The prophet isn't in his or her 50s.)
What is this?
- The first hint is like this. - What is this?
I guess it's broad.
All right.
(The hint isn't enough to narrow down the candidates.)
You will now receive a hint...
on either the deity of light or the deity of darkness.
If your choices are the same,
you will get a hint on the deity of darkness.
If your choices are different, you will get a hint...
on the deity of light.
If one of them is the deity of darkness,
- their choices will be different. - That's right.
If she is the deity of darkness,
she would want a hint on the deity of light.
That would be too obvious.
They might have no choice but to choose the deity of darkness.
But this is the first hint.
I will choose what you want.
(What they choose could be a hint in and of itself.)
You played the game diligently. Choose what you want.
- Really? - Yes.
Light or darkness? In 1, 2, 3.
- Darkness. - Darkness.
(They will get a hint on the deity of darkness.)
It's strange. You usually choose in secret.
Today, we had to reveal our choices.
It's strange.
(Jong Kook and Sunny check the hint while everyone is watching.)
(The deity of darkness debuted over 10 years ago.)
(Deity of darkness)
(The hint eliminates Jang Ye Won.)
I see.
This helps.
Is the hint broad or not?
(Is the hint broad or not?)
If you want to know, place first.
My goodness.
(If you want to know, place first.)
That's right. I was going to say the same thing.
All right.
Good job, Sunny.
The team that placed second, please come forward.
- Darkness. - Darkness.
Since your choices are the same,
you will get a hint on the deity of darkness.
(Haha and Ye Won get a hint on the deity of darkness.)
I don't understand why they are getting a hint as well.
(Jang Ye Won isn't the deity of darkness.)
- I guess the hint is telling. - Okay.
Okay.
You are hungry, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
You will split into two vehicles and move to the restaurant.
Two vehicles?
It must be first-come, first-served.
Six people or three couples can fit into each vehicle.
- Okay. - The vehicles will give a hint...
on either the deity of light or the deity of darkness.
(A hint on either the deity of light or the deity of darkness)
Thus, board the vehicle of your choice.
Now, let's go.
- Okay. - SUNMI, hurry up.
- Which vehicle should we choose? - Let's go.
Which vehicle should we choose? Ye Won, come here.
- The deity of darkness. - Jae Seok!
Ye Won, hurry up. The deity of darkness.
Jae Seok!
(Most members want a hint on the deity of darkness.)
- SUNMI! - So Min!
We did it. We did it.
- Hurry up. - So Min.
Hurry up.
- Ji Hyo. - My goodness.
Hurry up, Ji Hyo.
- So Min, come here. - Hurry up, Ji Hyo.
(Only one more team can board the vehicle.)
- Ji Hyo. - There is no seat belt.
Hurry up.
- There is no seat belt. - Jae Seok.
How did we come here in second?
- What is going on? - The deity of light.
The vehicle for a hint on the deity of darkness is full.
- My goodness. - It's full.
You are happy, right?
Happy?
- I know you are happy. - That's not true.
- Those on the other vehicle... - They are suspicious.
- are suspicious. - The deity of darkness is there.
Why didn't they try to come to this vehicle?
There are three teams in each vehicle, right?
(Is the deity of darkness...)
(in the vehicle for a hint on the deity of light?)
The deity of darkness is there.
One team in the front row should get off.
I got here the fastest.
While Seok Jin got here the fastest...
Ji Hyo got here the last.
- Ji Hyo got here the last. - But...
You should decide among yourselves.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Rock-paper-scissors! Rock-paper-scissors!
(Se Chan wins!)
Okay! You are out.
(One member remains.)
- He won. - I won.
- Only one member won. - That's right.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(So Min wins!)
- Okay! - Let's go.
(He admits defeat now.)
Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- My goodness. - Let's go.
- Seok Jin is cool. - He is cool.
I thought you were good at rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo move to the other vehicle.)
I knew these members would get on this vehicle.
Seriously.
(The teams)
(The vehicle for a hint on the deity of darkness)
(The vehicle for a hint on the deity of light)
I think the deity of darkness is...
among us.
- Be quiet. - It's not me.
It's Sunny.
- It's not me. - The deity of darkness is among us.
I am certain the deity of darkness is among us.
I am 100 percent sure...
since this is the vehicle for a hint on the deity of light.
Is this the vehicle for a hint on the deity of darkness?
(What?)
- The deity of light. - Really?
- The deity of light. - The deity of light?
- What is up with you? - She is eccentric.
- But Haha wanted... - I wanted to choose...
the other vehicle, but we were too late.
- She isn't interested in deducting. - That's right.
It looks like you achieved your goal.
- I am exhausted. - What's your goal?
- The top searched keyword? - No!
You achieved that goal.
You made the top searched keyword.
(Real-time Keyword Search Ranking)
(It's her mission to become the most searched keyword.)
- That's not right. - Now,
you will have a simple mission for a chance to achieve a hint.
If all three couples succeed,
you will get a hint on the deity of darkness.
- Really? - All right.
We need to join forces.
You will get caught if you do something strange.
Do you understand? If one of you is the deity of darkness...
- He or she will mess up on purpose. - That's right.
Don't make it so obvious.
One of us could be the deity of darkness.
The mission is...
- Speech Balloon 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. - Speech balloon?
The couple will take turns after listening to the question.
If they answer each question in a 5, 4, 3, 2, 1-word answer...
one after another,
it's a success.
So Min and Se Chan, why don't you go first?
Okay. We will go first.
Get ready. Set, go.
What is your partner's biggest charm?
The big and protruding mouth.
(She give a five-word answer.)
Which nickname do you want to give to your partner?
(Which nickname do you want to give to your partner?)
Female Han Min Kwan.
(Female Han Min Kwan?)
- Female Han Min Kwan. - What do you ask of your partner?
(What do you ask of your partner?)
(What could be her answer?)
Your honest feelings.
- Your honest feelings. - You answered too late.
(So Min, what did you say?)
- What? - "Your honest feelings"?
- Was that... - Three words.
- "Your honest feelings"! - Was that a confession?
- No! - Three words.
"Your honest feelings" is a three-word answer.
"Your honest feelings".
May I get off?
- I mean... - Hey.
Since my answer was "Female Han Min Kwan",
I feel so uncomfortable.
Why are you smiling from ear to ear?
- I mean... - When these moments are repeated...
When these moments are repeated, you begin to think about them.
(The repeated moments brought on this romantic answer.)
- Don't be so happy about it. - Okay, okay.
- My goodness. - Don't be so happy about it.
- I will give you another chance. - Okay.
- That was hilarious. - Let's begin.
What would you say if Se Chan asks you out?
I would definitely say yes.
What would you say if So Min asks you out?
(What would you say if So Min asks you out?)
I would love that.
What?
(You would love that?)
What's your number one treasure?
Yang Se Chan!
(Yang Se Chan!)
(You are my treasure, Se Chan.)
What do you want to achieve this year?
(What do you want to achieve this year?)
True love.
(Of course, it is.)
How would you call your lover?
Chu.
(Chu)
(Se Chan loves it.)
(Let us love each other.)
I am getting off. Please stop the van.
The two of you should get off together.
This is mine.
- We succeeded! - This seat belt is mine.
This seat belt is mine.
- I got goosebumps. - We succeeded,
but it was too...
They even got their seat belts mixed up.
I can't believe it.
It was the best verbal exchange.
Ronaldo and Messi are on the same team.
The last part was the best.
(They succeeded with the power of love.)
Get ready. Set, go.
What did you do last night?
I slept tight and pooped.
(He gives a five-word answer.)
What do you do when you are bored?
I have a meal.
(She gives a four-word answer.)
What do you do when you are in a good mood?
I dance alone.
Which famous person do you admire?
Hwang Hee.
Which movie do you recommend?
(Which movie do you recommend?)
"Mulberry".
("Mulberry")
(While it's a correct answer...)
It's... It's a one-word answer.
- A one-word answer. - That's right. You succeeded.
Okay. Ye Won, we need to succeed.
- Okay. - Make sure you succeed.
- We need to do a good job. - Let's go.
Let's begin.
What is in your fridge at home?
(What is in your fridge at home?)
Clear broth from chicken soup.
What is in your fridge at home?
Some home-cooked side dishes.
What do you want to take to a deserted island?
- My cell phone. - What's your nickname?
Foolish girl.
(She gives a two-word answer.)
What was your childhood dream?
(My childhood dream?)
Poop.
(Poop)
- Yes! - We did it!
We did it! It works!
- "Poop". - It's true.
- Okay. - He was asked this question.
- My answer was "Poop" then too. - That's right.
I'm being consistent.
What was your childhood dream?
(He's been saying that his dream was to be poop.)
He's right.
- Yes! - Okay!
The deity of darkness isn't one of us.
- We're good. - Good job.
You succeeded,
so I'll give you a hint.
You can share it with each other.
You can also decide...
who'll keep this hint.
Should we look first then do rock-paper-scissors?
- Yes. - Let's look first.
- We have to look first. - I'll give it to you.
(A hint on the deity of darkness is shared with everybody.)
Open it there.
Okay. Look.
"The deity of darkness was not born in the Year of the Horse."
"Jee Seok Jin and Jang Ye Won are excluded."
(The deity of darkness was not born in the Year of the Horse.)
- So it's not Ye Won. - Year of the Horse is...
They're 12 years apart.
That's right. That's a new fact.
That's a new fact.
No, they're more than 12 years apart.
(What? Why is there a picture?)
Seok Jin and I are 20 years apart.
Let's decide who's going to keep the hint.
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors?
(They'll decide with rock-paper-scissors.)
- There's something on the back. - There is?
- We have to win. - There's something on the back?
Just do rock-paper-scissors.
- You're so slow. - Hold on.
- Give it to me. - We have to share it.
- It's nothing. - Give it to me for a moment.
- Give it to me. - Everybody,
- calm down. - Give it to me for a moment.
Hey, you're so...
- So Min. - Yes.
Give it to me for a moment.
- Let's see it together first. - Hey.
- Let's see first. - What is it?
(She gets the hint card taken away.)
- Let me see it too. - "Black swan"?
(What's this?)
(There's a picture on the back.)
(Black swan)
- There's something in the picture. - There's something.
We have to keep this then.
That's right.
This is not a black swan.
That's true.
Is this not a black swan?
It's not.
(How is this swan a black swan?)
What's a black swan?
(It's English.)
(What does it mean?)
- I'm asking because I don't know. - Hey.
Just show me then.
Se Chan.
It says "black swan".
It means a swan that's black,
but this is not black.
- This is just a swan. - A swan.
What does this mean?
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Go, Se Chan.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo is out.)
Things are working out today.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok wins.)
- I knew it. - We got it.
(Jae Seok and Ye Won will keep the hint.)
- What's this? - Why did you...
(What does the picture mean?)
Let's look.
This is a hint about the deity of light.
"The deity of light is not in their 20s."
(The deity of light is not in their 20s.)
(The deity of light is not in their 20s. Exclude SUNMI.)
Is SUNMI the only one in her 20s?
(SUNMI is not the deity of light.)
That excludes SUNMI.
- She's the only one excluded. - How old are you?
"The deity of light is not in their 20s."
Did you take the hint?
Of course.
Did you take it?
- Yes. - Of course.
Don't show it to them.
Cover it.
It's not me.
- I'm serious. - It can't be anybody else.
This is my first time meeting Ye Won,
but it feels like I've known her for five years.
- It's like I knew her for 10 years. - Right?
- That's how she behaves. - I feel comfortable.
- That's nice. - She has a great personality.
I approve.
I think you 2 should try dating for like 2 months.
(You two look good together.)
- What is your type of man? - I like...
men who focus on the family.
- That's him 100 percent. Approved. - That's him.
(He only cares about family.)
That's really him.
I just got goosebumps. That hasn't happened in a while.
I really like men...
who focus on family more than work.
That's 100 percent him. And then?
And men who like children.
What?
Stop acting.
- Who doesn't like children? - Stop acting.
Who doesn't like children?
- No, many people don't. - I didn't really like children.
He likes children so much that people say he may have one.
Really?
(He likes children so much that people say he may have one.)
That's how much he likes children. There's a rumor.
- That's tough. - I have a child in America.
- That's tough. - People say I have children.
- Is this the right place? - Yes, it is.
(The deity of light team arrives at the next mission location.)
Do you have the hint?
Right, I left it on the bus.
- Hurry. - Hold on. You can't do that.
Whoever finds it first gets to keep it.
- "You can't do that." - Run, Se Chan.
That's what Jae Seok said.
I think you took it.
(Kwang Soo is a key suspect.)
- No. - Be honest.
I think he took it.
Search him. Let me check.
(They start searching Kwang Soo.)
- I have it. - Right? You have it.
(Kwang Soo has the hint?)
He actually took it.
(He has the hint!)
We'll pretend we don't know.
(How did Kwang Soo take the hint from Jae Seok?)
I don't really...
(Jae Seok put it in the seat in front of him.)
(He forgot that he left it there and got up.)
(Kwang Soo didn't miss the chance.)
(He quickly stole the hint.)
(That's how Kwang Soo took it.)
Where is it?
Somebody took it.
(He tries looking for it, but it's gone already.)
- Keep it. - Jae Seok is coming.
You have to share it at the end.
I will.
- Is it gone? - It's gone.
- No way. - Does Ye Won have it?
She said she doesn't.
(He looks around.)
(He makes eye contact with the key suspect.)
Give it to me, Kwang Soo.
What are you talking about?
- I swear it's not me. - Let's see.
Where did you leave it?
Where did you take it from?
Why would you ask that?
- I swear it's not me. - Hand it over.
You were the last one to leave.
I understand why you're suspecting me.
I'm not just suspecting you. Just hand it over.
I really don't have it.
Can you lift your shirt?
Lift what? Go ahead.
Let's take his pants off.
(Let's do that.)
- Kwang Soo. - That's possible.
- I'm an adult. - You never know.
- Go to the bathroom with him. - You can't do that.
- Take his pants off. - He would do that.
- He would definitely do that. - Please sit down.
We'll start the mission.
- Goodness. - This is...
- You didn't see it at all, right? - Where did it go?
What is that?
During this mission, you can win both a hint...
and meal vouchers.
- Let's eat. - Please.
It's called Inner Peace Traffic Light.
- "Inner Peace"? - "Inner Peace Traffic Light"?
- You have to resist. - Each couple...
will take turns.
One person from each couple will put on a headband...
that changes colors according to your pulse and heat reading.
- Is there such a thing? - That's interesting.
Within 30 seconds,
other couples can ask you questions.
If you endure, you win.
If the red light comes on, you lose.
- We can cool ourselves? - Sorry?
You can cool yourselves with a water spray.
- As long as you don't get hot. - I see.
- All right. - This is pretty accurate.
- We tested it. - Really?
- Are you sure? - It's quite accurate.
The couple that maintains inner peace for the longest time...
without the red light coming on...
gets meal vouchers...
and hints about the deity of light and the prophet.
- This is intense. - We have to win.
- What about 2nd place? - 2nd place couple gets vouchers.
- Let's get second place at least. - Last place gets...
nothing but seaweed and rice.
I'm not good at maintaining inner peace.
(As soon as the green light comes on, you can ask questions.)
I'm nervous.
It rises when it heats up.
Questions.
(They start asking questions.)
I love you, Se Chan.
(She tries to make So Min jealous.)
(She maintains inner peace.)
(She can't.)
- What? - Don't! Go down!
- What? - Spray water on her.
- Go down! - What was that?
So Min.
(Calm down, So Min.)
It's okay now. It's falling.
- We have to ask questions. - Ask.
- Se Chan, go out with me. - It came down.
(She tries to make So Min jealous again.)
(This is SUNMI's 2nd attack.)
- Go out with me. - It came down.
(She caves in.)
It's SUNMI. What's wrong with you?
(SUNMI kept on confessing.)
Good.
I understand.
(So Min's feelings for Se Chan got revealed.)
That was incredible.
Doesn't it go up because your temperature rises?
That's right. It senses changes.
(Spraying)
- What are you doing? - Let's cool you down first.
- We haven't even started. - Stop it.
(This is her revenge for losing inner peace over Se Chan.)
We didn't even start.
- Try to make me flustered. - Okay.
(Calibration complete. They start asking questions.)
- It's good. - Are you still dating...
that stewardess you mentioned on TV in the past?
- Sorry? - A while ago...
in Paju, you said you were dating a stewardess.
- No, not at all. - No, Se Chan.
- No? - I don't know her number.
- Se Chan. - It's rising.
(He gets shaken by the question.)
- "I don't know her number." - I don't.
Do you really like So Min?
(Do you really like So Min?)
(They may become a couple. How does Se Chan react?)
(He calms down all of a sudden.)
(Se Chan's feelings get revealed at Jae Seok's sharp question.)
It's going down.
Hey.
(Why is it dropping?)
It's going down.
- It's going up. - It went up.
(It went down momentarily and is rising back up.)
- It's going up. - Hey.
- I have no feelings... - You really like her, right?
- for So Min. - It's rising more.
- I have no feelings for her. - So Min.
(He lies about it.)
(So Min's strategy fails.)
- I have no feelings for her. - I think he really likes her.
It keeps on rising. It's over.
(He fails to maintain inner peace.)
This happens.
- What happened? - It's over.
Did it go down when you talked about So Min?
- This is accurate. - As soon as I talked about her.
It dropped when I talked about So Min.
It came down and went straight back up.
That's interesting.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo and SUNMI are next.)
- It's ready. - It is.
(Calibration complete. They start asking questions.)
Are you and Sun Bin doing well?
(It's his girlfriend.)
(He drinks green tea to calm down.)
It went straight up.
(What's going on?)
(It shoots up abruptly.)
No. No!
- Why? - You're so bad.
(They asked one question, and it's over.)
Is something going on between you two? What's wrong?
No! Why didn't you spray water on me?
- It didn't even take three seconds. - It's over.
- It went up to here. - How high was it?
- Up to the top! - No way.
It reached the ventilator. I'm serious.
That's how high it was.
- It shot up. - I was going to drink this.
- SUNMI. - That was incredible.
This gadget is funny.
Right?
(SUNMI is next.)
- Are you ready? - Ask questions.
Does Kwang Soo look like a proboscis monkey?
(Randomly?)
- No. - No?
What do you mean?
- Goodness. - What was that?
- You said I didn't look like one. - Inner peace.
(As soon as she sees his face...)
- You said I didn't look like one. - It's over.
(One after another, the 2 couples both fail.)
(Kwang Soo and SUNMI both lose it with Jae Seok's question.)
Jae Seok is great at asking questions.
- That was a great question. - I wasn't even thinking.
I'm human. Do I look like a monkey?
- It's over. - It only takes one question.
(Jae Seok and Ye Won are next.)
(They're waiting for the device to reset.)
He's not pretty, right?
- You're really ugly right now. - You're really ugly.
- Are you sad right now? - You look like an alien.
- Why are you so depressed? - Is he sad?
- You know you look like an alien. - Does he always look sad?
Start.
Give Ji Ho to me.
(His love for his son boils over.)
All of a sudden?
(He fails to maintain inner peace.)
That was abrupt.
(He's determined not to give away his son.)
- That was really abrupt. - Hold on.
- Why did it go up? - That surprised me.
- Why did it go up? - Why did you start shaking...
- when she mentioned Ji Ho? - Why did it go up?
(His heart bounces when he thinks about his son.)
What was that?
That was so random.
- Kwang Hee. - That was so random.
Everybody failed, so let's go again.
- Goodness. - This always goes up.
- Let's go! - I'm hungry.
Here are the rules.
- Is it just us? - Yes.
It's just us.
Why?
(She goes to the end.)
(Ye Won is next to Jong Kook now.)
(Nice, Ji Hyo.)
You can get both hints and meal vouchers in this mission.
- This mission is... - Okay.
(They finally notice.)
(Clicking)
- Excuse me. - I'm sorry.
(He takes a picture of Jong Kook and Ye Won.)
Focus on work.
- I'll cut it out. - That wasn't original.
- Work. - Okay.
This mission is called Inner Peace Traffic Light.
This is my specialty.
- When you blush? - Inner peace.
What?
You know me. I don't really get mad.
You get mad.
My heart rate is steady.
- I don't change. - Mine doesn't go up.
- You too? - My heart rate.
Should we start first?
- Should we? - Okay.
- Good. - That's good.
- That looks nice on you. - It's going up. It's at two spaces.
You should keep it.
- You're making fun of me. - It's so funny.
They're making fun of us.
- Does this work? - You're blushing already.
- Seok Jin. - I don't get excited.
- He doesn't get angry. - Start asking questions.
(They start asking questions.)
Did your wife find out about your emergency fund?
We're cool about it now.
- Did you tell her? - I gave it to her.
- Really? - Yes.
- Did you have a lot of money? - Sorry?
Did you have a lot?
- Sorry? - Did you have a lot?
- Emergency fund? - Yes.
It kills you to think about it.
(He fails to maintain inner peace.)
(He caves in because of the emergency fund.)
It shot right up.
- He can't control himself. - I didn't do anything.
You should have sprayed him earlier.
It shot right up from green to red,
- so I didn't see it. - Did it?
It started going up when you said you gave it to her.
It was Sunny's fault.
(He's dizzy.)
I didn't give her all of it.
He didn't give her everything.
I told her it was everything and didn't give all of it.
That's pretty accurate.
- That was so funny. - Is it accurate?
- Really? - That was so funny.
Let's take turns asking questions.
- What should I ask Haha? Hold on. - For Haha...
I was mad from the beginning today.
Take deep breaths.
Hey.
- It worked. - Start asking questions.
(They start asking questions.)
- Start. - Haha,
you know the album you released in OJ Project?
The album.
- It's okay, Haha. - Do you want to release it again?
- It may go up on the chart. - It's okay, Haha.
It's okay, Haha.
- You should try it. - It's okay, Haha.
(Spraying)
(He calms down after Ye Won sprays water.)
It went down.
It worked because she sprayed water.
(What?)
Oh, dear.
(He fails to maintain inner peace as soon as he finishes talking.)
Is this even possible?
Does this even work? Is this doable?
(Is it possible to maintain inner peace?)
- We're starting. - Okay.
(Jong Kook is the real master of maintaining inner peace.)
- Good luck. - I'm known for steady heart rate.
- I'll start. - Start asking questions.
Jong Kook, would you watch a movie with Ye Won if she asks?
And have dinner together?
That's not difficult.
That's right.
He's so powerful.
Did you fall in love with Ye Won at first sight?
(This is the 2nd attack.)
I don't fall in love at first sight.
(He gets swayed.)
- Jong Kook, focus. - Jong Kook.
- Hurry. - Jong Kook, look at me.
Jong Kook, look at me.
(Jong Kook, look at me.)
(Glancing)
Do you like me?
(Ye Won makes a shy confession. How does Jong Kook react?)
Oh, dear.
(It drops abruptly.)
What?
(Jong Kook's heart freezes.)
- Don't laugh. - It dropped.
- Why did it drop? - Don't laugh.
What was that?
- Haha. - What was that?
Is it done?
(Jong Kook manages to maintain inner peace.)
- Why did it go down? - You should have stayed out.
- That shouldn't happen. - How did this...
What happened?
- What's wrong, Jong Kook? - I challenged myself.
- I challenged myself. - Jong Kook, that was mean.
I seriously challenged myself.
Kwang Soo and SUNMI win first place.
Let's do a final round to decide the losers.
(We're in 1st place!)
(So Min goes first.)
What if you confess your love to Se Chan,
and Se Chan turns you down?
Then it's too bad.
Why do you like Se Chan?
(Her heart rate rises.)
Why do you like him?
His gums? Or...
- It's not his gums. - It's not.
(She doesn't like me because of my gums.)
- I shouldn't have said that. - It's not his gums.
If Se Chan...
- Okay. - Two.
So Min, good defense.
(It's Se Chan's turn next.)
That stewardess we were talking about.
(It's the stewardess all the way.)
I'm sorry.
(He can't maintain inner peace.)
(He's knocked down every time the word "stewardess" comes up.)
What's wrong with you?
What? What was I saying?
- Is it over? - Yes.
It shot right up.
- I didn't even finish. - Get back.
You have to sit down.
Ye Won says she doesn't get swayed by others.
(A moment ago...)
(She was not swayed by any question.)
(Will she succeed again?)
(They're forming a plan.)
Why am I getting nervous?
Say a math formula you know.
- A math formula? - Yes.
(Her heart races.)
Say a math formula.
It's over! Nice!
- You shouldn't have done that. - Why?
- She's real. - Okay.
I said I liked math on radios.
- I know. - You got caught.
- What now? - Get back.
One more time. Something else.
Tell us three charms you have.
(3 charms are simple.)
- Be honest. - Be honest.
- Go. - Are you confident about your face?
- Already? - Think about it.
- No. - Think.
- Charms. - Go down.
- Go down. - Just think about your charms.
(He doesn't understand.)
Don't you have any charms?
- Why is he mad? - Jae Seok.
Why did you get mad? We were talking about your charms.
- Hey, were you making fun of me? - No.
- We were just curious. - Just say your charms.
- Just say, "eyes, nose, and mouth". - Do you want to fight?
Why do you want to fight?
Goodness.
(The sad alien got mad while thinking about his charms.)
Good job, So Min. We're second place. Let's eat.
Se Chan and So Min take second place.
If you fail,
- Haha and Ye Won win. - Okay.
- Okay. - Are you calm?
- I'll press it. - Go.
(Can he maintain inner peace this time as well?)
- It's on. Go. - It won't be fun.
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
- I got hurt. - Don't get hurt.
- I'm serious. - Why?
- You're really mean. - No.
- You didn't choose me. - It was for fun.
(It rises all of a sudden.)
- You're mean. - What do you think about Ye Won?
It's going up.
Don't do it. No.
- Jong Kook. - Hurry.
What do you think about Ye Won? How is she as a partner?
- Think about the ocean. - She's great.
No, it's red!
What can you do for her?
(He fails to maintain inner peace.)
(They kept on attacking with questions about her.)
(Jong Kook caved in!)
We did it!
- This is weird. - We did it.
Why? Because your feelings were revealed?
(Teasing is fun.)
He likes her
Does your heart pound?
Does this flutter?
Does it pound?
Change my partner.
- Hold on. - Oh, gosh.
- I'm curious. - I tried my best.
- I'm loyal. - Goodness.
The winning couple for Inner Peace Traffic Light is...
Haha and Ye Won.
(Haha and Ye Won are winners of Inner Peace Traffic Light.)
You two get hints about the prophet...
- and the deity of light. - The prophet hint is good.
What's the hint on the deity of light?
- I'm hungry. - Let's eat.
Okay.
(Will they get ideas about the three identities?)
What's this?
(People with the same name are not the prophet.)
(This excludes Kim Ye Won, Jang Ye Won)
(Kwang Soo and SUNMI received the same hint.)
(Neither Kim Ye Won nor Jang Ye Won is the prophet.)
This one is on the deity of light.
- Really? - There's more?
Why are there so many?
(The youngest Running Man member, Se Chan, is not the deity of light.)
Share it.
They're giving lots of hints.
(They check the hint on the deity of light again.)
This is weird.
SUNMI, you'll share it with us, right?
There's no reason not to.
- This is weird. - You have to share it.
I don't think we should.
Okay.
Check if there's a picture. Can they hold on to that one too?
Hold on. Can we check the back?
You can do whatever you want.
It's one of us.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - If you don't share it with us...
- Share the hint with us. - What?
Is there something else?
(This time, there's a different photo.)
(Blue Ocean in the Middle of the Afternoon)
Hold on to it.
Do we need to share this with others?
- Listen. - He'll tell us.
We can't share the hint right now.
- We can't share it now. - But...
- It's someone... - Yes.
- It's someone among us. - There's an odd part in the hint.
- Really? - Yes.
Okay.
(A secret is hidden in the photo.)
(Is that related to the deity of darkness?)
(The race starts. They must find and eliminate the deity of darkness.)
(Suspicious behaviors are slowly unraveled.)
(They give suspicious answers about their whereabouts.)
(I have nothing to hide, you know.)
(In the end, they must search the building thoroughly...)
(and find the decisive hint about the deity.)
(At that moment, she finds the hint.)
(And she's discrediting it.)
(Light versus darkness, which one will be the final victor?)
(And the D-Day has come.)
I'd like to thank everyone who has come...
(For fans who have supported the show for 9 years,)
(the members set out on a long journey of 100 days.)
(Their goal was to hold a fan-meet in Korea which was unprecedented.)
(They made the merchandise, wrote the theme song,)
(practiced the group dance, and worked with other singers.)
(They have spent all this time for this day.)
(It's the promise the members made...)
(for the love their fans gave them for the past 9 years...)
(to make sure they return the favor to the fans.)
- Yes! - Yes!
(It's the first race the members will have with the fans.)
(The splendid fan-meet begins.)
(Running Man's Fan-Meet: 9 Years of Running Man)