There aren't that many
big studios like this nowadays.
This place is nice.
- This place is like...
- This is a nice place.
Wait, this studio is Jong Kook's?
- What?
- Your outfit today...
What's up with your outfit today?
I heard that today's episode
will be quite emotional.
(I heard that today's episode
will be quite emotional.)
- You know what?
- What are you talking about?
- His outfit isn't touching at all.
- What are you saying?
- I mean...
- I can see his nipples from here.
- No way. I'm facing forward.
- Hey!
- I'm facing forward.
- Jong Kook.
My eyes keep looking down.
I know that I'll see them from here,
but I can't stop looking at them.
- I can see your pelvis through it.
- No.
Gosh, Korea isn't there yet, right?
(What's wrong
with a sleeveless shirt?)
(Jong Kook exposes his side
too early in the times.)
- We have a long way to go.
- Hey.
Now, we just need
to give you the gong.
- Is he the Gong Man?
- Gong Man?
(He will follow in
Mickey Kwang Soo's footstep.)
Do you want to be a gong today?
That's the songwriter, Jung Joon Il.
- Gong Man?
- Do you want to be a gong today?
That's the songwriter, Jung Joon Il.
(He's here.)
- Hello.
- We're meeting at last.
- My gosh.
- This way, please.
- Come this way.
- That's the keyboard.
- My gosh.
(Looking modest)
- This is amazing.
- I can see that you're shy.
- He's very shy.
- He's shy around people.
(Right now, he seems very shy.)
(But this singer-songwriter
established his own style...)
(with "Hug Me",
"Confession", and "To You".)
(He wrote "Good for You"
and "First Snow" for "Goblin".)
(He's a beloved musician
with popular songs.)
(And he will write the theme song
for Running Man.)
I write songs...
and sing those songs.
I'm Jung Joon Il.
This is the songwriter,
Jung Joon Il.
(They feel reassured
as Joon Il joins them.)
- Stay by my side
- We're lucky to meet...
a famous musician like him.
So far, he's only been on...
"Yu Huiyeol’s Sketchbook".
He's only been on that show.
Is this your first variety show?
Yes.
(His throat is dry.
Clearing his throat)
- Your throat is too dry.
- Give him a glass of water.
I can tell that you're shy.
(He wets his throat and gets ready.)
When the staff asked you
to join us for this project,
- you were in New York.
- Yes.
- Really?
- I was there for less than a month.
You're living a great life.
He must speak English well.
Usually, people who speak English
stay there for a month or so.
- No, that's not true.
- You don't speak English?
- He must've been in Koreatown.
- Koreatown.
Well, if he stayed there...
- You'd be fine on the 32nd street.
- He's an expert.
- They have Caffe Bene and all.
- Right.
(That's a Korean cafe.)
- He's the US expert.
- "Caffe Bene"?
- Right.
- Exactly.
He's the US expert.
- You're keeping your manners.
- What do you mean?
- You're covering your sides.
- What?
It's because...
when I'm talking about something,
they'll put up a close-up shot
of me.
- You're well-mannered.
- Of course.
I like that side about him.
- He's polite for a muscular guy.
- Of course.
- "He's polite for a muscular guy."
- He is.
- He's well-mannered.
- Muscular Gentleman.
- So you got our call in New York.
- Yes.
Did you say yes without
giving it some thought first?
Yes, I'm a fan of the show.
(Joon Il is a big fan
of Running Man.)
- Do you find our show...
- He's calm.
entertaining?
Do you laugh
while watching the show?
Yes.
(Trailing off)
(They've never heard anyone
say yes this unenthusiastically.)
We're so childish.
(Laughing)
- Jong Kook.
- What are you saying?
- What?
- Okay.
- We're not that childish.
- Look at them.
Look at them. Look.
(It's too embarrassing to show
these kids' sense of humor.)
(We must adjust the show
to a G-rated show.)
(An outdated gesture)
(Unexpectedly,
this is right up his alley.)
Goodness.
- He's liking it.
- He's liking it a lot.
He likes this kind of stuff.
Joon Il is liking this.
(Coughing)
(He chokes up for the 2nd time.)
He's dying.
- Are you all right?
- He's dying.
(He's dying from laughing too hard.)
- This feels great.
- In old movies,
- songwriters die like this.
- He's dying.
(He really must be our fan.)
He wants to divide up the parts.
He'd like to know
everyone's vocal range.
My throat isn't ready
in the morning. Goodness.
Which song should we sing?
- Let's go with "I Miss You".
- "I Miss You".
Kim Bum Soo's song?
Should I lower the key?
- No, I'll sing in the original key.
- We must sing in the original key.
- We don't lower keys.
- Right.
- We don't roll like that.
- That's our weakness.
- We don't lower the key.
- We...
- We'll go with the original key.
- We never lower the key.
- Shall we start?
- Ji Hyo will start.
You'll start now, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is known
to be a bad singer.)
(Her pitch is unstable
from the start.)
Don't laugh.
(Her pitch shakes
like a swaying tree.)
(Staring)
(Chuckling)
Song Ji Hyo is out.
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
(Ji Hyo might be eliminated
from singing the theme song.)
Hey, why do you keep laughing?
How can I sing when you're laughing
right in front of me?
- Don't make her feel insecure.
- Hey.
- Don't do that.
- Anyway,
you're on the show
to make people laugh.
- Wait, no.
- So it's all good now.
- It's okay.
- Are you doing that on purpose?
- Next up is...
- This is...
Actually, this is
Kwang Soo's favorite song.
- He always sings this song.
- This is...
- Kwang Soo's song.
- He sang it at a fan-meet too.
- Really?
- Yes.
1, 2, 3.
(The memories)
(When I was madly in love)
He can reach the high notes.
(He's pretty good.)
(I won't use our love
as an excuse anymore)
- He's pretty good.
- He's...
He's good.
(Unexpectedly, he can pull off
those high notes pretty well.)
That was nice.
Your pitch was stable.
He seems satisfied.
(Even Joon Il is clapping for him.)
His singing method is known as...
the Eunuch Method.
- What's that?
- That's how they sing.
I can't stop you
Your Majesty.
Come on.
- Jae Suk.
- What are you talking about?
- Your Majesty.
- What?
- I didn't sing like that.
- You did.
- "Your Majesty"?
- I sounded like him.
- Why would you say that?
- That's the Eunuch Method.
- He's the loyal eunuch.
- Right. He's loyal.
- Why am I a loyal eunuch?
- You are one.
This is funny. It's so funny.
I'll sing this time.
Jae Suk.
- He's a hidden master.
- Right.
I'll follow your lead.
- No, I'll follow your lead.
- I see.
- Don't follow my lead.
- Who will follow whose lead?
What if both of them can't lead?
At this rate, no one can lead.
- Why not?
- You must lead at least.
- Someone has to lead.
- I can follow his lead.
- Okay, okay. I'll take the lead.
- Follow my lead.
- Okay.
- Here I go.
- They are giving it a go.
- The
- Hold on.
(Singing the first note)
- Hey.
- You're not singing a trot song.
(No one can keep up
with this master.)
- This song doesn't suit me.
- Are you singing "Chang"?
This song doesn't suit me.
He changed the notes.
- The song doesn't suit me.
- He changed the notes.
I'll start.
(He gives it another try.)
- He sang with a technique.
- He has a good vibe.
I shouldn't
(I'm not done yet.
I must sing the whole song.)
This is an important part.
(I miss you)
(Like crazy)
(He's in his own world.)
What's wrong?
Are you having sleep paralysis?
(Are you all right?)
- Hey!
- Wake up. Are you all right?
I was...
- I had to wake him up.
- How...
How could you say that?
Come on, I was reaching the climax.
He wasn't that bad.
All right. I ought to show you
how a singer sings.
(He's talking big again.)
(He already finds it funny.)
(The memories)
(He adjust the notes himself.)
He can't reach the high notes.
He can't.
He started off high.
(He's about to pass out
from laughing.)
Is that right?
Great.
(This time, he sings
the high notes nicely.)
(As an excuse)
(He only mouths the parts
with high notes that he can't hit.)
(The singer with 1 released album
can sing it however he wants.)
He's definitely in control.
(The singer with 1 released album
can sing it however he wants.)
He's different.
- He's playing hard-to-get with us.
- Great.
How was it?
You were playing with the tempo.
That's an old style of singing.
(That's his evaluation in one line.)
Didn't I tell you?
I told you he has an old style.
(Oldboy Suk Jin)
His style is so outdated.
I was going to bring that up.
- Se Chan.
- Okay.
- He's a good singer.
- My gosh.
But he sings songs
in an annoying manner.
- He sounds like an annoying guy.
- That's true.
- He does sing like an annoying guy.
- That's right.
What's the first note?
- The
- That's wrong.
That's the wrong note. It's wrong.
- It's wrong.
- It's totally off.
- You were totally off.
- The memories
(He barely manages
to get the first note right.)
- Okay, I'm ready.
- You're ready.
You're relaxed.
(The memories)
See? He's so annoying.
Look at his eyes. His eyes.
(His annoying gaze
is bothering them.)
- He's so annoying.
- I told you he gets annoying.
Seriously.
He sings like that all the time.
(That's how he looks at a karaoke.)
(Although he's annoying,
his high notes are perfect.)
- Gosh.
- He sang all of the high notes.
He sang all the high notes easily.
(Se Chan's "I Miss You" is better
with your eyes closed.)
- Your voice is going to get hoarse.
- He sang all of the high notes.
- My gosh.
- It was pretty intense.
- Now...
- It's Jong Kook.
- He'll sing the female version.
- No, no.
He can't sing in the same key.
I will raise the key by one.
"I will raise the key by one."
This song is already high pitched.
- This song has high notes.
- He sounds so cool.
The memories
when I was madly in love
He's at ease.
(Jong Kook hits the high notes
without a problem.)
I'm looking for you
I won't use our love
as an excuse anymore
I can't keep you any longer
(He reveals his sweet voice
that he locked up in his muscles.)
He's singing this so easily.
(It's time to please our ears
with Jong Kook's mellow singing.)
From the depth of my heart
I miss you
So much
(Screaming)
(Haha lifts his arm.)
(His armpit is in danger.)
Don't do that!
He's the best singer among us!
You reassure us.
He even raised the key.
- It's still too early.
- Right, he did.
- He sang so easily.
- It's still too early.
We're not that bad, right?
You're all... You're...
You're...
(You're...)
- We're what?
- Were we bad?
(They can't believe it.)
- You're...
- Were we bad?
It was great.
(He forces himself
to compliment them.)
I'm glad that
we all like each other.
He likes us.
- And we like him too.
Right, it's great.
The reason why we're here
to see him is because...
of our lyrics.
- Right.
- We had to write lyrics.
- We played the game.
- You're right.
(During the theme song race,)
(they decided to give each other
nicknames.)
(Suk Jin called Ji Hyo Song Van.)
(Her nickname was Song Van.)
(Mouth Like Mount Baekdu)
(This was So Min's nickname
for Jae Suk.)
(Their nicknames were made
out of endearment.)
(Members' Nicknames)
I received your nicknames
through email.
- How were they?
(How were they?)
I thought about dropping out.
(He thought about dropping out.)
I do understand.
- Me too.
It's difficult to use
those nicknames.
- Right, it is.
- I understand.
I haven't written the lyrics yet,
so let me listen to you first.
Could we listen to the chorus first?
I actually made the music...
- beforehand.
- Did you?
- Really?
- Yes.
- I'm curious.
- Let's hear it.
I'm curious.
(The theme song will now
be revealed.)
(This is Running Man's first
theme song...)
(in 9 years.)
(What kind of song will it be?)
- I like it already.
- It reminds me of "Aladdin".
- It sounds adventurous.
- It sounds like Disneyland.
- You're right.
- It sounds adventurous.
(The intro sounds like
a parade that will unfold...)
(the story of Running Man
since the past 9 years.)
- I love this.
- Crazy Poet.
(Crazy Poet)
(Really Foolish)
(Jee Stream is flowing)
(This is how their nicknames
will be added to the song.)
(Be as Tall as 3m)
(Give Me Some Money)
(They become excited.)
(The melody makes them dance.)
I'd like you to rap here.
- Haha?
- Yes.
Okay.
For this part, either Ji Hyo
or So Min could sing.
- What?
- Have you heard Ji Hyo sing?
She can't sing.
- Come on.
- I don't think he knows.
Have you heard her sing?
(I got it.)
This is nice.
(As the song progresses,
they like it even more.)
(Humming)
I bet Suk Jin will cry here.
(Crying)
- I bet he will.
- Prepare your handkerchieves.
So this is how it ends.
(They plan to show
the 9-year journey.)
(They get up...)
(and applaud.)
Bravo!
(This will be
their first theme song.)
- Hooray.
- Jong Kook, let's say hooray.
Let's say hooray.
- Hooray!
- Grab my hand and say hooray.
Stop it.
Let's try it once.
- Just once.
- Come on.
You're right.
This is too unnatural.
- Let's do it.
- It's too unnatural.
- Show it to Joon Il.
- That was good.
- It felt cozy and warm.
- It was cheerful.
By the way, it was really nice.
How was it, Ji Hyo?
The song made me feel calm.
- Right.
- I felt peace.
There she goes lying again.
(She didn't mean it.)
(The members know
if she means something or not.)
- What do you mean?
- Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, think again.
Okay.
She acknowledged it.
- That was quick.
- She quickly acknowledged it.
- I did.
- I think highly of her.
As for the pitch,
we could work with this.
Do you have any ideas
about the lyrics?
Or do you have anything to say
to each other?
Like rolling paper?
(He doesn't understand.)
- No, it's teasing paper.
- Teasing paper?
So that's not it.
We can write whatever we want.
- Rolling paper...
- Write with emotions.
I got some great lyrics here.
What is it?
"Just like how we didn't know
we'd meet,"
"we'll never know when we'll part."
(How does he feel?)
"But for today, let's stay fresh."
- Come on.
- How was it?
- You had me at the start.
Isn't it good, Ji Hyo?
It's amazing.
- The first part was nice.
- It was great.
- It's like a diaper commercial.
- Right?
Jee Stream could appear
while wearing a diaper.
(He's fit to shoot this commercial.)
This is great.
No matter how exhausting,
struggling, and hard it was...
- we were always...
- "I rested."
(Suk Jin rested.)
(Suk Jin only thinks
about himself.)
"We were strong together,
but I was never with you."
(Haha mimics him.)
"Everyone screamed and shouted,"
"but I lip-synced."
(Jae Suk mimics him.)
What do you say?
- Isn't it nice?
- It is.
Are we writing these lyrics for him?
Is that it?
(Subtitle: "Receiver, Suk Jin")
Was there anything
you were curious about?
Perhaps, our keywords.
For me, I was curious
about your beginnings.
- Our beginnings?
- I want to know how you felt...
back then.
- That's perfect.
- Our beginnings?
"Suk Jin told me..."
(What did he say?)
"that Haha..."
(Suk Jin Told me that Haha...)
"and Jong Kook were bullying him."
(Haha and Jong Kook were
bullying him.)
(The 45-year-old remembers the days
when he was bullied.)
- This was in the beginning.
- You're right.
He told me this through the phone.
"That's why I told the producer
three times..."
"that I wanted to quit."
Good.
(Thankfully, no one quit,
and Running Man is still here.)
- This is...
- I love the melody.
It sounds like Broadway.
- It sounds like an amusement park.
- You're right.
(He likes it.)
(Once we finish filming today)
Write it down, please.
- Write it down.
- He looked pitiful.
- Even if we break up,
- This song isn't...
- Let's meet
- just for you.
- Don't lie.
- Let's meet
He wants to meet
even if we break up.
(Until Kwang Soo's son
gets enlisted in the army)
(I want to live)
Hey, I'm still young.
I wonder if he'll still be alive.
- Hey.
- He wonders.
- This isn't working.
- Don't die!
"Until Kwang Soo's son
gets enlisted in the army."
"Until So Min's daughter
gets married."
- That's nice.
- "Until"?
Yes, until.
"I'll be watching them from above."
(I'll be watching them from above.)
(Startled)
(Do you want to die?)
- Don't write such lyrics.
- I almost had a heart attack.
Don't write such lyrics.
(I'm just kidding.)
(Now, they focus
and write the lyrics.)
(They reminisce the past 9 years
they've spent together.)
I'm done.
(Time's up.)
This is difficult.
Look at Haha's.
"Being together makes
anyone stronger."
"But we've never been together."
(But we've never been together.)
"They said to go alone if you wanted
to go faster..."
"and to go together if you wanted
to last a long time."
"So we hurried."
(His lyrics are demotivating.)
It's fun.
It is.
- I like it.
- Haha is worried...
that it'll be too emotional.
- Right?
- If we give a twist at the end,
it'll be hilarious and fun.
This isn't how I truly feel, though.
This kind of vibe is good.
This is Se Chan's.
"Our relationship has lasted
for such a long time..."
"unlike the beginning."
"We all had different occupations
and personalities."
"While we chatted in our uniforms,
we heard the word,"
- "'out'."
(We heard the word, "out".)
I don't think
you should hand this in.
(His lyrics are rejected.)
I have no idea how to write this.
It's so low class.
(Jae Suk gives him
a piece of advice.)
- It's low class?
- It's too low class.
- Did my lyrics fall short?
- Yes, it did.
You can't hand this in.
Let's gather the lyrics
and hand them over to him.
Okay.
I doubt you'll be able to use
much of these.
- This is embarrassing.
- It is.
I guess we all felt the same.
Do you have anything to say?
Well... Like what?
(Like what?)
Then we'll end it here.
(He likes how natural Joon Il is.)
- I'm liking this.
- Right.
That was nice and short.
It's very natural.
Thank you!
How great.
(What kind of theme song
will be created?)
(A few days later,
the members gathered together.)
- Hello.
Ji Hyo, will you be rapping?
What will happen?
- Yes, she'll rap.
- It'll be awesome.
And we wrote...
- about the members.
- Is that so?
She always says her dance moves
and singing will be awesome.
(It's a habit of hers.)
- It will be awesome.
Another characteristic
of her performance is that...
she may look halfhearted,
- but she's actually doing her best.
- You're right.
- I'm really doing my best.
- Please don't misunderstand her.
She may be dancing like this,
but she's sweating buckets.
She just looks like that.
I hope
no one will misunderstand her.
(It may look like
she's dancing halfheartedly,)
(But she's sweating a lot.)
- Right.
- She always gives her best.
Why are you wearing a hat?
(He suddenly asks
a random question.)
- What about you?
- You're wearing one too.
Are you worried about your forehead?
Your hair takes up 70 percent
of your beauty.
- Don't listen to him.
- I'm serious. It's 70 percent.
You're hilarious.
I've waited for this moment.
(His role model
never disappoints him.)
- Take it off.
- What percent of your hair remains?
- What percent of your hair?
- Me?
About 25 percent.
(He's honest.)
He needs recharging.
I'm barely...
- You're barely holding up.
- I thought it was the worst.
Anyway, we've accepted applications
for our fan-meet since yesterday.
- Oh, really?
- We announced it on TV yesterday.
It's passed 40,000 views so far.
(It reached 170,000 views
on August 4.)
Our stage might be
too small to invite our fans.
No, our event might be
too awful to invite our fans.
We have to prepare so many things
within a short period of time.
- I know.
- Right, it's a bit...
But we're doing our best
like idol singers.
We want to do a good job.
Of course.
(What?)
- Yes.
- Oh, gosh.
- I know.
- It's said Jae Suk is busy...
looking after his second daughter
these days.
That was such an awkward way
of asking a question.
Don't ask him if you don't want to.
- Suk Jin...
- Hey, if my question wasn't enough,
they can use subtitles
to make up for it.
He's a radio show host, by the way.
- Right.
- I hear you enjoy...
looking after your second daughter
these days.
- Oh, dear.
- Goodness,
- rumors say so.
- That's too...
Your second daughter...
Na Eun is...
- She recently started rolling over.
- How old is she?
Her first birthday
is coming up soon.
Isn't that around the time you know
who she resembles?
There are different opinions.
Some people say she looks like me.
Others say she looks like my wife.
Your mood might change
from joy to sorrow.
It changes.
(Your mood might change
from joy to sorrow.)
You might cry and smile.
- What?
- Why?
What's wrong with her resembling me?
It's like going back and forth
between a hot bath and a cold bath.
- What's wrong with that?
- Between a hot and cold bath.
"No, no!"
But she's...
- so adorable.
- She's pretty.
- She might be so pretty.
- I bet.
- I know.
- She's adorable.
Suk Jin appeared
on "Mom's Diary"...
and analyzed
why Jong Kook isn't getting married.
I told them, "It's not that
he can't get married."
"It's that he doesn't want to."
Then they were relieved.
They were like, "Is that true?"
Jong Kook doesn't go on blind dates
even if we offer to set him up.
- It's uncomfortable.
- He doesn't go on blind dates.
Blind dates are uncomfortable.
He has to open up a little more.
- I have an idea.
- But he doesn't.
This time...
(Twisting)
- Stop it.
- No, it's a good idea.
(Booing)
I've never hit on a woman before.
Hey, I'm curious.
Did you ask your wife out?
- Of course.
- Really?
- How?
- How did you pick her up?
- I'm curious.
- Hey.
What do you mean, pick her up?
She's your friend's wife.
- I mean, aren't you curious?
- What do you mean,
- pick her up?
- How does Jae Suk pick up girls?
- Tell us how you did it.
- There's nothing special.
- I said, "Let's have a cup of tea."
- Really?
(How old-fashioned.)
"Let's have a cup of tea."
I'm 100 percent sure his lips were
like this when he said that.
His face must've been pale
out of nervousness.
- Because he was nervous.
- You know him so well.
- "Let's have a meal."
- Goodness.
- Because he was nervous.
It's so funny to think
he flirted with her.
- "Let's dine together."
- It makes me curious.
I must say...
I went out with her on my own,
but it wasn't the case for him.
- It's like I gave him his life.
- Right.
You were his Cupid.
I was his life consultant.
Right.
My life too. Be my life consultant.
- So Min.
- My life.
- Call Se Chan.
- What...
I'm working on it in secret,
so wait just a little.
- In secret?
- He'll be yours soon.
You guys keep setting us up,
so it's become awkward for us...
- It's become awkward?
- to even have a drink.
- I...
- Usually, she was playful to me,
but now she isn't.
- People talk in whispers too.
- We happen...
to avoid talking to each other.
He answers my calls
in a cold way too.
Hey, why would you do that?
- Do you do it on purpose?
- No.
- I'm being careful.
- He keeps minding it.
- Se Chan.
- The way I see it,
- he flirts with her too.
- Exactly.
- What?
- He acts like he's indifferent,
- but he leaves room for romance.
- Right, he's a player.
- I know.
- This is absurd.
- Is he good to her?
- He goes,
- "So Min, you're pretty today."
- Right.
- What a jerk.
- He touches her hair.
The heavens never take
everything away from you.
(The heavens didn't take
everything away from him.)
- They leave at least something.
- What are you talking about?
- I mean...
- What do you mean...
- the heavens are fair?
- They leave something.
- There are those talents.
- I know.
- What's my talent then?
- So don't be shy.
- Everyone has their strength.
- Right.
As you can see, the weather seems
like it's going to rain.
- The weather forecast said so.
- So today,
we're going to film indoors...
- for you.
- Great.
- That's good.
- Thank you.
Do you remember when I asked you...
- about the food you craved?
- Yes.
- The dishes are ready inside.
- Really?
I mentioned rib eye.
- I said clam kalguksu.
- Pyongyang naengmyeon.
Everything you mentioned
is prepared inside.
- Really?
- I ordered pork ribs too.
You'll be filming indoors
at ease today.
Let's go in first.
- Just like this?
- Nice.
- What's gotten into them?
- It's nice.
- What?
- It's strange.
How grateful.
Let's go.
There is a lot of food.
(There are so many dishes
prepared on the table.)
It's no joke.
Ji Hyo,
look at that dried yellow corvina.
That's mine.
- There's patbingsu.
- That must be for dessert.
This is awesome.
I want to eat my clam kalguksu
so much.
- Do we just start eating?
- No.
- We can't eat it?
- What...
You ordered these dishes,
so why can't we eat them?
- Wait, that's...
- This is crazy.
- What's that?
- Hey, that's...
- I think we have to pay for it.
- What?
- Our credit cards are here.
- What...
What is this?
(They're personal credit cards
of the members.)
- This is my credit card.
- Wait.
What is going on?
- What are they going to do with...
- I mean...
- Please have a seat, guys.
- What is going on?
Is this how you make a profit?
Let me remind you...
of the dishes
which you ordered yesterday.
Jae Suk ordered
Pyongyang naengmyeon...
- and bulgogi.
- Right.
Ji Hyo ordered Pyongyang naengmyeon,
dried yellow corvina,
and green tea rice.
- Suk Jin ordered rib eye.
- Right.
Haha ordered clam kalguksu
and pork ribs.
Se Chan ordered sausage stew.
- Jong Kook ordered naengmyeon.
- Right.
Kwang Soo ordered bean guksu,
big dumplings,
patbingsu, and iced Americano.
You ordered so much.
- What's your problem?
- You even ordered dessert.
I don't know about anything else,
but patbingsu was a nice choice.
- Right?
- Good job.
- So Min ordered chicken porridge.
- Right.
That's nice.
Gosh, I hate it the most.
What? Your jokes aren't even better
than the taste of chicken porridge.
(Chicken porridge isn't
as horrible as his jokes.)
What do you mean you hate it?
His nickname is Porridge Face too.
He doesn't like things
that resemble him.
Today, you just have to enjoy...
eating the dishes for a long time.
- So why won't you let us eat?
- For a long time?
Today's race is called
Why Can't You Eat Race,
and things won't be easy
for you to eat in this race.
- Goodness.
- I guess...
- this is going to be painful.
- This is too...
Your food will be taken away
exactly in three hours.
- In three hours?
- We're filming the episode...
- only for three hours today.
- Really?
- It's nice.
Only if you clear a mission,
you'll get to pay for your food...
and enjoy it within the given time.
We have to pay for it
with our money?
- There are two ways to eat.
- What are they?
The first method is to draw cards.
The first-place winner
will get to draw cards.
It will either have, "I Eat for 10
Seconds with Someone Else's Card",
10 seconds?
"I Eat for 10 Seconds with My Card",
"Someone Else Eats for 10 Seconds
with My Card",
- What?
- or "Dud".
The winner will draw
1 of these 4 cards...
and proceed according
to what the card says.
For your information, we took your
credit cards from your managers.
(Members credit card)
Here's the second method.
If you clear a special mission,
you and the person of your choice...
may eat for three minutes
with the staff's credit card.
This is what you want.
(They get to eat for 3 minutes.)
- Three minutes?
- That's nice.
This one is nice.
I can even finish eating dessert
within that time.
The special mission
will be informed...
to members who choose to do it.
I've got to do it no matter what.
If you fail to eat anything
within the time limit,
you'll be faced with a penalty.
If all of you succeed in eating,
the one with the shortest eating
time will be given the penalty.
What is the penalty?
- That will be revealed later.
- Just the thought of it...
All right, let's start
with the first mission.
- Okay.
- All right.
For the first mission,
you will play...
Dice Four Game individually.
- That gives everyone a chance.
- It's fair.
You will throw five dice at once
taking turns.
Per each number of 4 rolled,
1 second will be added...
to your penalty time
that starts from one second.
Here's what the penalty is about.
If none of your dice shows a four,
you'll have your sideburn pulled
as much as your penalty time.
The person next to you
will pull your sideburn.
If you hold out without screaming,
you may counterattack.
If you scream, you'll be eliminated.
You're safe if you roll a four,
and you get penalized if you don't.
That's right.
Okay. Should we start
from Haha then?
- Sounds good.
- Okay.
- Do it.
I better roll some fours.
- I'll roll then.
- Are you up first?
- Yes.
- If you don't roll any fours,
your sideburn will get pulled
for a second.
- That's the minimum penalty time.
- Okay.
- So there must be a four.
- Right.
You better roll that number.
- Please.
- There might be at least one.
(How will the first player do it?)
- Throw it so you get a four.
- There's none.
There's a four.
(He has rolled a 4.)
(Haha rolls a 4 and adds
1 second to the penalty time.)
That's a second
to the penalty time.
- It's two seconds now.
- That was close.
This is hard.
You might not get any fours.
- It's harder than I thought.
- There may not be any.
- It's 2 seconds now.
- Right, 2 seconds.
I wish it was just a second.
- There's none.
- I got a four.
- That's fortunate.
- He got a four.
- Just to roll a four is hard.
- It's hard.
- It's not easy.
- Why is it so nerve-racking?
- Goodness.
- Ji Hyo.
So whoever doesn't roll a four
will suffer the whole penalty.
- Right.
- Only a four is being rolled.
It's at three seconds so far.
(Thud)
Ji Hyo failed.
(Ji Hyo will have to get penalized
if she fails to roll a 4.)
- I got a four.
- Goodness.
- She got a four.
- There are 2 of them.
- I got two of them.
- There are 2.
It's five seconds now.
Why did you have to roll 2 of them?
It's going to be horrible
if you don't roll a four.
So it's better to do it first.
Our seats...
(Will Jong Kook roll any 4s?)
- There's got to be at least one.
- Our seats...
- He didn't get any.
- There's none.
- There.
- He rolled one.
- There it is.
How fortunate.
It's hard to roll even one.
I guarantee you.
Three of us will get the penalty.
No, it won't be me.
- 1 of us 3.
- Not me.
I'm 100 percent sure of it.
- Okay.
- I wish it isn't me.
It's gone up to six seconds now.
Who rolled two of them?
- Ji Hyo.
- Kiss this.
(He asks Ji Hyo
to give it her lucky kiss.)
Come on.
- That's...
- Good.
(They can't believe
what they just heard.)
- What are you doing?
- I was so surprised.
I only heard him say to kiss him.
Gosh, that was...
I mean here.
- I was so shocked.
- I mean a good luck kiss.
Give me a kiss
(The accumulate penalty time is
6 seconds.)
I really want to pass.
- There's no four.
- Please.
There's no four.
(Why did he even get
a good luck kiss?)
- There's no 4.
- No 4s.
- Whose turn is it?
- There's no four.
- Six seconds.
- This is crazy.
Jong Kook will pull
Suk Jin's sideburn, right?
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
Is it?
Suk Jin's sideburn will be pulled
for six seconds.
If he can take it,
he can counterattack.
But Suk Jin has no sideburns.
I shaved them off.
- He doesn't have sideburns.
- He doesn't.
Jong Kook might be able
to create them by pulling them out.
(Jong Kook might be able
to create them by pulling them out.)
Jong Kook.
You could pull his ears.
Ears? That'd be...
- I don't have much hair there.
- There's not much, but I got it.
You have six seconds.
I'll say "start".
- Can I start?
- Wait.
Hasn't he started yet?
It hurts. Start right now!
- I haven't started yet.
- You haven't?
I'm not pulling it yet.
- Just holding it hurts.
- I'm just holding it.
- Gosh.
- There's not much hair.
- Hold on.
- Ready.
- He can't scream? Hold on.
- And...
start.
(Scary)
(What?)
- Two.
- He's taking it.
(He's taking it.)
(He can't.)
(Screaming)
(We knew it.)
- It's impossible.
- That was crazy.
- He failed after three seconds.
- There wasn't much hair.
- Okay, good.
Suk Jin, you're out.
Go over there.
- Am I out?
- Yes.
- Please move over.
- You're out.
Please give me another chance.
What are you talking about?
- You don't get another chance.
- What are you doing?
- I didn't know I'd be out.
- "Give me another chance."
I want to take revenge.
- He's being ridiculous.
- I want to take revenge.
Move over.
(Hold on.)
- Do I move up to his seat then?
- Yes, please.
- Okay.
Move up.
- Really?
- Move up.
- It's okay if I get a four.
- I didn't know...
What's the penalty time
if he gets no four?
It's 1 second.
We start over from 1 second.
One second is not bad.
It's better to fail early.
- I don't think he'll get a four.
- Gently.
This will be...
(What did Kwang Soo get?)
- There's no 4.
- There's no 4?
- No 4s.
(He's unlucky as usual.)
- That's incredible.
- No 4s.
- 1 second.
- It's 1 second.
- I just have to last 1 second.
It's one second.
(Jong Kook pulls
Kwang Soo's sideburn too.)
Let's see.
- Oh, my.
- Look at that.
- He has so much hair.
- Make him scream right away.
My goodness. Hold on.
Gosh.
Ready.
Hold on.
(The atmosphere is tense.)
(I'll clench my teeth
and fight this.)
Start.
(Screaming)
(Shortly after Kwang Soo
covers his mouth,)
(he screams.)
(What was that?)
(Pulling)
(Kwang Soo is eliminated
right away.)
You're out. Move.
Move. Move, Kwang Soo.
Did I pull his hair out?
Your fingers didn't slip.
You pulled out my hair.
It made a huge sound.
Move.
(Kwang Soo is eliminated too.)
You couldn't take it
for just one second?
It's just impossible.
There's a reason
why some people always lose.
It's only for one second.
How could we get no four?
- The penalty time is one second.
- Okay.
- I'm sure I'll get at least one.
- That was too gentle.
There's no four.
(What did Jae Suk get?)
- There's no 4.
No fours!
- No fours!
- This is so interesting.
I can't believe it.
(Jae Suk gets no 4 either.)
This is incredible.
- Is this a rest area or something?
- No four.
- A meeting point.
- Is this a famous restaurant?
- Why is everyone stopping by?
- Just a second.
Let me...
- Let me prepare myself.
- All right.
(Sighing)
Can you take off your glasses?
They're in the way.
Hold on. I just have to last
one second, right?
Because of Kwang Soo,
my fingers are smeared with oil.
My pain won't go away.
Should I see a doctor?
I still feel a lingering pain here.
It's like a virus.
(While symptoms are being reported,
Jong Kook treats his third client.)
- Is here okay?
- It already hurts.
(He only has his fingers on him,
but it hurts.)
Is that okay?
Wait. Hold on.
- Aren't you pulling it?
- No.
- Ready.
- Wait.
Ready. Start.
Gosh.
(As soon as Jong Kook starts,)
(Jae Suk falls to the floor.)
(That could have been me.)
Did you see that?
It's impossible not to scream.
- It's impossible.
- Hey!
- He didn't go easy on us.
What?
- It hurts too much!
- So what?
How could just those three fail?
- Team Crocodiles.
- It's incredible.
- Okay.
So Min, if you fail,
your hair will be pulled too.
She's a girl, but we're...
very close now.
Didn't my skin get torn off?
It probably did.
- No way.
- Why...
- I'm worried.
I have to get a four.
- You're no exception.
- The thing is...
- She's one of us.
She'll get no four.
(With the others saying unlucky
words, So Min throws the dice.)
- She's one of us.
She'll get no four. See?
There is a four.
(She is saved by a 4.)
(I'm safe.)
- The penalty time is 2 seconds now.
- 2 seconds.
I'm so relieved.
I must have broken a bone here.
(I must have broken a bone here.)
(I must have broken
my sideburn bones.)
- Your sideburn bones?
- There's no such thing.
That's the only way
to explain this amount of pain.
- Are you talking about these bones?
- There are no bones there.
- I must have broken them.
Here we go.
(Despite the broken sideburn bones,
the game continues.)
(The penalty time is 2 seconds.
What will Haha get?)
- Please get fours.
- Please fail.
Please fail.
- It's a 6.
- There's no 4.
(No 4s)
- No 4s.
- 2 seconds.
So Min will pull his sideburn
for two seconds.
- Me?
- You're lucky. It's So Min.
So Min, show him what you've got.
Haha keeps whispering to me,
"Go easy on me."
- Pull it hard.
- You shouldn't.
- Do like Jong Kook did.
- Right.
A lot of my hair has
already fallen out.
All right.
1, 2, 3.
1, 2...
(Time's up.)
(Pulling)
(Two seconds passed
without Haha screaming.)
- Haha gets to counterattack.
- So Min!
I mean...
- Can he counterattack?
- The thing is...
Haha kept moving.
So this is how So Min joins us.
That's right.
She joins us in the end.
This is how So Min joins us.
She's joining us now.
- Now I understand.
- Look at this.
- Did your hair get pulled out?
- So much got pulled out.
It won't grow back either.
Since Haha didn't scream, he gets
to counterattack for two seconds.
If So Min doesn't scream either,
can she attack again?
No. The game will start over.
It'll start over.
- Ready.
- No grabbing.
- Grab where?
- My neck.
You escaped earlier.
That's your problem.
This is my first time pulling on
someone's sideburn.
So Min's mom becomes very worried
when she watches this show.
- Does she laugh at these things?
- She doesn't worry about this.
She's worried about me
getting involved with Suk Jin.
(She's worried about me
getting involved with Suk Jin.)
That's dangerous.
Do you want to be penalized
instead of her?
Suk Jin...
- "Penalized me instead of her."
- Okay.
That's dangerous.
- How long?
- Two seconds.
(Haha gets to attack So Min
for 2 seconds.)
Gosh.
Start.
Fail.
(Screaming)
(As soon as the attack started,)
(So Min screamed.)
Just forget that
you shouldn't scream.
So Min, come here.
Why did I scream?
I don't understand.
(Haha survives, and So Min is out.
The game restarts from Se Chan.)
But even if you survive to the end,
you'll have to beat Jong Kook.
- Exactly.
- Who knows?
- He got a 4.
He got a 4.
Okay. I got one.
(Okay. I got one.)
(The penalty time is 2 seconds.
It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
(What will Ji Hyo get?)
I think she'll get fours.
- No.
- There's no 4.
- No 4s.
(Ji Hyo gets no 4.)
(Gosh)
It's 2 seconds.
You just have to last 2 seconds.
- Who pulls her sideburn?
- Se Chan.
Is it my turn?
Se Chan is strong.
- But Ji Hyo is strong too.
- Two seconds.
Her hair will get pulled out.
Start.
- 1, 2...
- She's putting up with it.
- Three...
- Look at her face.
(Angry)
- She's taking it.
- Look at her face.
Wasn't that longer than two seconds?
- Ji Hyo's jaw was trembling.
- Her jaw was trembling.
Why are you trying so hard?
You'll have to go through me anyway.
(Why are you trying so hard?)
(You'll have to go
through me anyway.)
That's right.
It's Jong Kook in the end.
- Counterattack.
1, 2, 3.
Gosh, that hurts.
(Pulling)
(What is this?)
(I accidentally
pulled out his hair.)
You're not supposed
to pull the hair out.
You're supposed to just pull.
It was like she was waxing his hair.
You're incredible, Ji Hyo.
She pulled my hair out.
I didn't mean to pull it out.
- Jong Kook will win anyway.
- Is it my turn?
But Ji Hyo has a chance
because she's Ji Hyo.
No. Jong Kook...
- No 4s.
- There is a four.
- There is.
(Jong Kook gets 1.)
I got one in the end.
You're incredible.
Keep accumulating the time.
I got one in the end.
I hope the penalty time will
go up to 12 seconds or something.
- I hope the time will go up.
- There's a 4.
There is.
(The penalty time is 3 seconds.
What will Ji Hyo get?)
- I hope she'll get three.
- She got it.
- She got two.
(Ji Hyo gets 2.)
She got two.
- The penalty time is...
- Five seconds.
(The penalty time is 5 seconds.
It's Jong Kook's turn again.)
Here we go.
Okay!
- He got it.
- Again?
- He got two.
- Unbelievable.
- 7 seconds.
- The time is getting longer.
- This is getting fun.
It's going up.
I hope it gets even longer.
That's the fun part.
Seven seconds wouldn't be easy
even for Jong Kook.
(Extremely nervous,
Haha throws the dice.)
He rolled the dice.
(What will be the result?)
- Did he get it?
- He got it.
- I got it.
- My goodness.
- He got 2.
- The time is at nine seconds.
- This is crazy.
- It will reach 12 seconds.
- Seriously.
It will end this round.
People get four so easily.
Why didn't we get a single four?
- It's fascinating.
- I am so annoyed.
Why did I get eliminated
even though I got a four?
(Will Ji Hyo join the members
who always get the penalty?)
I am really bad at playing games.
- She got it.
- It's another four.
(Ji Hyo adds another 4
to the record.)
She got one.
The time is at 10 seconds.
I am doomed.
No one can hold out for that long.
Not even Jong Kook can hold out
for that long.
(What will be Jong Kook's result?)
If the pulling drags on...
- He got it.
- It's another four.
(Jong Kook adds another 4
to the record.)
- I can't believe it.
- The time is at 11 seconds.
My prediction will come true.
They will get 12 seconds.
I am doomed.
It's a matter of where
the bomb goes off.
It's like "Family Arcade".
(The accumulated time
is 11 seconds.)
It's about time
he doesn't get a four.
(Haha rolls the dice.)
(What will be the result?)
Is there four?
- There is a four.
- I got it.
I got it.
My goodness.
12 seconds.
(The accumulated time is
12 seconds.)
Someone's hair will get waxed.
This is incredible.
(What will be Ji Hyo's result?)
Ji Hyo will get it.
- Didn't she get it?
- She didn't get it.
(There is no 4.)
(How did this happen?)
- She didn't get it.
- It's Ji Hyo.
- 12 seconds.
- Ji Hyo.
- It's really 12 seconds.
My prediction came true.
It's impossible to hold out
for 12 seconds.
Ji Hyo can do it.
She will scream.
- Here I go.
- Say "Start" when you go.
Start.
1, 2.
(Ouch!)
She made a noise.
(I think it's going to hurt.)
(Ouch!)
She is wise.
(She shouted right away.)
I am sorry. I pulled a hair out.
- Okay.
- This is a meaningless fight.
- Don't say that. You might win.
- You never know.
You might win.
Jong Kook will win in the end.
My mind is at ease
now that Ji Hyo is out.
(The accumulated time is 6 seconds.)
(What will be Haha's result?)
- He got it.
- Did he get it?
- He got it again.
- I got it.
(Haha got a 4.)
(Okay, I got one.)
- What's the time?
- Seven seconds.
Okay.
The accumulated time
keeps getting longer.
Jong Kook is so relaxed.
- He didn't get it.
- What?
(There is no four.)
- Didn't I get a four?
- No, you didn't.
- Okay.
- This is your last chance.
If you don't eliminate him now,
you will lose.
This round will decide the victor.
If you don't eliminate him now,
you will lose.
Seven seconds.
Go ahead.
I am not joking when I say this.
I am sorry for being boring,
but I can't feel pain.
Come on.
(Haha is already annoyed.)
- Seven seconds.
- What am I supposed to do?
He is bluffing, right?
- It makes no sense.
- Everyone can feel pain.
Seven seconds.
You are out if you make a noise.
I will start the timer
when you say "Start".
(Between Haha and Jong Kook,
who will be the winner?)
Start.
(Pulling)
(He pulls as hard as he can.)
(My name is Jong Kook
and I don't feel pain.)
Doesn't it hurt?
- Really?
- How does that not hurt?
- Smack him.
- Really?
This is crazy.
- What was that?
- Did you pull hard?
- This is crazy.
- What was that?
Did you pull hard?
- Yes.
- It didn't feel like it.
I pulled hard.
- I pulled hard.
- Really? It didn't feel like it.
Haha's muscles were bulging.
All right. Come here.
Hurry up and sit down.
(Come here. Hurry up and sit down.)
(Scared)
- Sit down. How many seconds?
- He will die either way.
This is a game...
for Kim Jong Kook.
He can withstand pain.
I have a suggestion.
Why don't we name Haha the victor
if he holds out?
- Sure.
- Let's do that.
- Don't pull this part.
- Haha will win...
if he holds out for seven seconds.
- He won't be able to hold out.
- Of course not.
Haha is terrible
at withstanding pain.
- Don't do that.
- I got it.
- That hurts. Hold on.
(He is struggling already.)
It hurts just grabbing on to it.
That hurts. That hurts.
I am in pain.
- Can I start?
- Start.
(Pulling)
He is holding out!
Start.
(Scary)
He is taking it!
- He is taking it.
- My goodness.
Start.
(Screaming)
(He surrendered in 3 seconds.)
That was pathetic.
- That was pathetic.
That was seriously pathetic.
Twisting your body was
a good strategy,
but Jong Kook set it straight
right away.
I know.
It was like a UFC fight.
Jong Kook grabbed him.
I told you that my bones hurt.
This game is so annoying.
Okay.
- This, Jong Kook won.
- Okay.
Jong Kook, you need to make
a choice.
Will you choose a Mystery Card...
or a special mission?
(He needs to make a choice
that will help him eat.)
I'll go with the Mystery Card.
(He chooses the Mystery Card.)
We don't know which card
he will get.
(He will eat and pay
as the card instructs.)
I'll go with the Mystery Card.
He lost hair too.
Why didn't it hurt?
(Why didn't it hurt?)
- It really didn't hurt.
- Why didn't it hurt?
He said he doesn't feel pain.
His facial expression didn't change.
I want to see Jong Kook
hunched over in pain...
on my way to the restroom.
(Four cards are shown to Jong Kook.)
- There are four cards.
- Okay.
There are
I Eat for 10 Seconds with My Card,
I Eat for 10 Seconds
with Someone Else's Card,
Someone Else Eats for 10 Seconds
with My Card, and Dud.
- Those are the four cards.
- Okay.
I hope he gets Someone Else Eats
for 10 Seconds with My Card.
(The worst options are Dud...)
(or Someone Else Eats for 10 Seconds
with My Card.)
Okay.
1, 2, 3.
(Jong Kook received a benefit
for withstanding the hair-pulling.)
(What will be
the result of the benefit?)
1, 2, 3.
(Which card did Jong Kook choose?)
Someone Else Eats for 10 Seconds
with My Card.
(My goodness.)
(Yes!)
It's a party!
(That serves Jong Kook right.)
- I didn't think it would happen.
- Play some music.
(I am so happy.)
It's no wonder
I didn't want to pick a card.
I had my eyes...
on one card,
but you mixed the cards.
I was like...
Then who will eat?
Jong Kook will choose one member...
(Does Jong Kook get to choose
the member who will eat?)
Jong Kook will choose one member...
- to eat for 10 seconds.
- I see.
Do I get to choose?
Jong Kook, I won't eat much.
- I will eat what you choose.
I want to eat
what I ordered, patbingsu.
- I want dried yellow corvina.
- Dried yellow corvina.
I didn't have a single meal
since I was busy watching my kids.
(I didn't have a single meal
since I was busy watching my kids.)
I think I can eat anything.
Gosh, I am dizzy.
Then you should rest.
(Is that so?)
(Jong Kook is considerate.)
- It's okay.
- You should rest.
You should rest.
- All right.
- In that case...
(Jong Kook made a decision.)
(One member will eat and become
less likely to receive a penalty.)
- Haha.
- Thank you.
(Haha is struggling to raise
his third child.)
(Haha finally gets to have a meal.)
- Thank you.
- He suffered the last hair-pulling.
You are quite fair.
This is driving me crazy.
What are you going to eat?
I will eat Pyongyang naengmyeon.
Okay.
- Thank you for the food.
- Okay.
Eat a lot.
- It's about 10 dollars, right?
- Yes.
That's right.
- My goodness.
- This is an eating show.
It must be cold.
It's the perfect dish for this hour.
You only need 10 seconds
to finish that.
Get ready. Set, go.
(The 10 seconds start.)
(My goodness.)
That sounds amazing.
You should drink the soup as well.
It's not tasty
if you eat that way.
Drink the soup.
Drink the soup as well.
- There you go.
- Eat a piece of meat.
(The referees run over.)
He has noodles in his mouth.
What is going on?
You can only eat for 10 seconds.
- What is going on?
- It's "Pirates of the Caribbean".
It's "Pirates of the Caribbean".
- Davy Jones.
The noodles are going in.
(He slurps up the noodles.)
Was it tasty? Was it cold?
Was it cold?
I need to eat.
Let's go.
That was tasty.
For the next mission,
we will play Don't Make a Sound,
which is a game
you are familiar with.
Don't Make a Sound?
The member who makes
the least amount of sound wins.
If you make a sound,
you will be dragged
behind the folding screen...
and receive a penalty makeup
before you come back.
- We have to hold in laughter.
- That's right.
The game will go on for 15 minutes.
- Okay.
- I laugh too much.
I can't hold in laughter.
Get ready. Set, go.
(The mission
of the 15-minute silence starts.)
(They glance over at each other.)
(I will look up funny photos.)
(What is he doing?)
(The war begins
in less than 10 seconds.)
(Kwang Soo suppresses his laughter
and attacks with his long legs.)
(I don't care who wins.)
(Laughing)
(Jae Suk becomes the 1st one
to go to the makeup room.)
(That was close.)
- Jae Suk is out.
- I mean...
(Kwang Soo gets knocked out
in 0.1 seconds.)
Kwang Soo, please go on in as well.
(Kwang Soo and Jae Suk
go into the makeup room.)
Kwang Soo, why did you...
Who was it?
It didn't tickle. It hurt.
For goodness' sake.
(The two troublemakers
are out momentarily.)
(They came to the makeup room
faster than they expected.)
(Meanwhile, Haha shows something.)
Stop it. Stop it.
(It's So Min as Yondu.)
(It's highly likely that she will be
the Character of 2019.)
(She holds in her laughter.)
(The war of memes begin.)
(It's a synthesized photo
of Ji Hyo and Se Chan.)
(Jong Kook averts his eyes.)
(Laughing)
(What did So Min see?)
(Walking)
(The two members
from the netherworld...)
(appear with a dark aura.)
(Chic and confident)
(Gosh, I can't laugh!)
(Walking is enough
to make their presence known.)
Jae Suk's makeup is manageable,
but Kwang Soo's makeup isn't.
Is he Yondu? Is he Yondu?
So Min.
(Serious)
(Kwang Soo's looks are perfect
for this kind of a game.)
(Pinching)
(This is interesting.)
(He is as calm as ever.)
(Are you done?)
(Kwang Soo helps.)
(Se Chan is out.)
Se Chan.
(The collaboration
between strength and funny looks)
Okay. Okay.
(Laughing)
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo couldn't stand
his bare face in the morning.)
(He gets sent back
to the makeup room.)
Jong Kook is too strong.
What made you laugh?
(Laughing)
Make me look as funny as him.
Make me look the same.
(Laughing)
(A sexy man, Suk Jin appears.)
(When Suk Jin appears
with an upturned nose,)
(Ji Hyo falters.)
(Everyone wants a photo.)
(He is pretending to be cool.)
(Laughing)
Suk Jin.
(He is out
thanks to his own photo.)
I can't believe them.
(He briefly enjoys the fresh air...)
(before he reunites with his friends
back in the makeup room.)
Why are you here?
Jong Kook will win again.
Why isn't Jong Kook here?
Jong Kook has to make a sound.
- Let's join forces.
- Seriously. Let's work together.
Let's take Jong Kook down.
Okay.
(Jong Kook, look at this photo
of Suk Jin in his 20s.)
(He doesn't budge.)
(Kicking)
(Come on and laugh.)
(Did you just kick me?)
(Reaching)
(Falling down)
(Ouch.)
(She falls down on her own.)
(She really is in pain.)
(I didn't even touch her!)
My knee.
(The victory is Jong Kook's
once again.)
As for Jong Kook...
What do you want to do?
(Jong Kook said
he can't hold in laughter.)
(At that moment,)
(the man with 1,000 faces appear.)
(Lee Kwang Soo, the prince of Asia)
(Jong Kook suppresses laughter.)
(His gaze is intense.)
(Why are you taking a photo of me?)
(Not even Kwang Soo's face
can make Jong Kook laugh.)
(Jong Kook, look here.)
(Laughing)
(On Se Chan's big belly...)
(is a man's face.)
(Is that a cup of coffee?)
(Drinking)
(Jong Kook withstands
the attacks...)
(from Se Chan and Kwang Soo.)
I really can't do this.
Se Chan's belly is drinking.
(So Min is out, not Jong Kook.)
(Laughing)
(Why are you laughing?)
(Instead of making Jong Kook laugh,)
(they make each other laugh.)
Isn't this funny?
(Relaxed)
(He should laugh by now.)
(Jong Kook!)
(Mini-So Min appears.)
(Jong Kook finally faces a crisis.)
(Do you have to go this far?)
(Mini-So Min makes an effort.)
(Strange laughter is heard.)
(Laughing in a weird way)
(This is driving me crazy.)
What is he doing?
(Shouting)
(Jae Suk's touch
makes Kwang Soo come to his senses.)
Kwang Soo.
Jong Kook is the only one...
What are you doing?
(He hates it.)
Did she have to go that far?
What is wrong with her?
(I really want to make him laugh.)
(Thinking)
(Whispering)
(A knife)
What? What?
Ji Hyo told me to take out a knife.
(Did you hear that?)
(How will you make Jong Kook laugh
with that?)
She asked me for a knife.
(Didn't you laugh?)
(A human weapon quietly appears.)
What is that?
(His target is Jong Kook.)
(Stifling her laughter)
(Since Ji Hyo is about to laugh,)
(he changes his target.)
How scary!
(She was caught off guard.)
(Dancing)
(The outdated dance moves...)
(makes Jong Kook turn frigid.)
How do I make Jong Kook laugh?
- Just you wait, Jong Kook.
- How do I make Jong Kook laugh?
Jong Kook almost laughed,
but he caught himself at the end.
(I hope there is something
to laugh about.)
(I am coming through.)
(I can hold back my laughter.)
(Haha, bring me water.)
(They prepared a skit.)
(What?)
(Chuckling)
(Jong Kook finally laughed.)
For goodness' sake.
(Without a straw,)
(Haha pours water
on Se Chan's belly.)
What are you doing?
What is this?
(Thanks to Se Chan,
Jong Kook goes to the makeup room.)
What are you doing?
(What?)
(Standing)
(Laughing)
My goodness.
(The laughing machine
is malfunctioning again.)
Gosh, I am sorry.
(He pays attention to the details.)
My goodness.
(Everyone except for Kwang Soo
goes to the makeup room.)
For goodness' sake.
Hey!
(Beanpole!)
(The two great figures...)
(finally meet.)
(The tension is growing...)
(between the two lookers.)
(Neck-and-neck)
(Who will be the winner
between them?)
(Shouting)
(Jae Suk loses.)
(I am the looker of this area.)
(Thanks to Haha's kick of justice,
Jae Suk is out.)
The game will end in five minutes.
(Let's hold out for 5 minutes!)
(He gets something.)
(Haha brings something.)
(Is that a straw?)
It's the one that was in
Se Chan's belly button.
(The straw gets recycled
in an unexpected way.)
(Shocked)
Are you serious?
(It's the same straw.)
(When the secret
behind the straw gets revealed,)
(Jong Kook enters.)
(He has no thoughts.)
(I have a good idea.)
(He gets up...)
(and delivers the straw.)
(What is he doing?)
It's the one that was in
Se Chan's belly button.
It went into Se Chan's belly button.
(The secret behind the salty taste
gets revealed.)
(Haha bursts out laughing.)
Three minutes remain.
(With 3 minutes remaining,)
(Jong Kook is leading
because he made a noise once.)
There is only one thing
that can make Jong Kook laugh.
What is it?
(They prepare a secret weapon.)
(Meanwhile, So Min...)
(attacks with Mini-So Min
for the 3rd time.)
(It's saying something.)
(Stop it, So Min!)
(While So Min buys time
with Mini-So Min,)
(the secret weapon gets ready.)
All right.
(What? This face is...)
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo did a similar makeup
1 year ago in the UK.)
(But he showed up
after the game ended.)
(Blue Monster)
(Why is the game over?)
(He couldn't make full use
of his special attack.)
(Blue Monster will finally complete
his mission today.)
(Whistling)
Time's up.
Is it over?
(His eyes go wide.)
(Is it over?)
- Is it over again?
- It's over.
(Today as well,)
(Kwang Soo couldn't make full use
of his special attack.)
You only had a minute left.
You should have blown...
the whistle earlier.
(Furious)
- He was almost done too.
- But...
(Mission 2 is over before
Kwang Soo becomes an Avatar.)
The winner of
Don't Make a Sound is...
Jong Kook who laughed only once.
(Kim Jong Kook wins.)
Is it Jong Kook again?
I had my mind open.
I'll pick another card.
- Pick another card.
- Okay.
- Get a dud.
- Someone else eating looks good.
- Is there a dud?
- There is.
Goodness.
(Last time, Jong Kook's pick
only benefited the others.)
I also want dried yellow corvina.
(Which card did he pick this time?)
- Which one is it?
- I hope he'll get to eat.
(Which card did Jong Kook pick?)
It's a dud.
(Darn it, it's a dud.)
(Dud)
(It's a dud this time.)
- That's great.
- Nice.
(He wins nothing.)
We have a chance.
It'll be a party.
Why am I so unlucky today?
(Jong Kook is very unlucky today.)
I'm not lucky at all.
We're defending ourselves well.
(Haha is in first place
without doing anything.)
- Give us a worthwhile game to play.
- That's right.
Next mission is called
I'm King of Common Sense Too.
Jae Suk has good common sense.
Is it common sense?
I'm doomed.
This is for me.
It'll be a team competition.
To decide the order. All the members
except for the first will go...
wear headphones playing music.
After looking at the word
given by the staff,
you will be given 10 seconds...
to explain it
to the member beside you.
The team to correctly guess
the most wins.
- This sounds good.
- I see.
(They need to understand
the given word.)
We have to express ourselves well.
I hope I get on a good team.
You're doomed if I'm on your team.
It's over if you, Ji Hyo,
and Haha are on the same team.
Haha?
(Haha, Se Chan, and Ji Hyo)
We must avoid those three.
All right.
(They determine the teams
by picking spoons.)
- I want to be on your team.
- Here you go.
I want to be on your team.
Let's start with So Min.
1, 2.
- Red.
(So Min, Kwang Soo, Jong Kook,
and Haha)
(They're on the same team.)
- Mine is blue.
- Blue.
Okay.
- Can you be excited?
- Hey.
- Can you please be excited?
- How is this possible?
She and I don't know anything.
Our team isn't bad.
- Wait a minute.
- It isn't bad.
- We're expressive.
- It'll be worth to play.
We'll be fine if we get good words.
- Both teams are similar.
- I think you're right.
We aren't similar.
We have two who don't know anything.
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Ji Hyo,
and Se Chan start first.)
(I'm King of Common Sense Too)
(She can't hear anything at all.)
Shall I go? Get ready.
(The first question starts.)
Start.
(Roll-Over)
(What's this?
He's never seen it before.)
You can do it.
(Deferring payment...)
(or renegotiating terms
of an agreement)
It's a famous game.
It starts with an L.
- Yes, I know.
- You know it, right?
- However the game ended.
- It ended?
It has three syllables.
It's when the game ends.
(He wants to explain
that the game is over.)
Out.
- Explain to the next person.
- Out.
(Why is it out?)
- Didn't I explain it enough?
- I don't know.
(They already smell failure.)
It's a type of a game.
It's a game that's popular
these days.
Do you know Faker?
It's a game that Faker plays.
The first word is that game.
The last word is when the game ends.
It's the last two words.
(Faker? The last two words?)
"Game out"?
(When did I say "out"?)
(Faker, the last two words)
It's a game that Faker plays.
However,
the first word is excluded.
(She fails to deliver it.)
When did I say that?
(She delivers a wrong message.)
- When did I say that?
- Did he say that?
Who said such a thing?
Is there a ghost here?
Does Faker play a game called
"League of Legends"?
The first word disappeared.
It's the last word.
(What disappeared?)
"Disappear"?
When did it disappear?
Legend.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
(Wasn't that right?)
- What disappeared?
- That was right.
- It is "League of Legends".
- Hey.
- It was "roll".
- That's right.
What's the answer?
"Roll-Over".
(They fail their first attempt.)
Here we go again.
Get ready, set, go.
(Southwest Effect)
(The effect of an increase
in customers as prices fall)
- It's easy to explain.
- It's a type of effect.
In American rap,
they say east or west.
They say things like that.
It's rap, but is it also an effect?
He didn't have to say it in English.
- Right.
- I know.
- There's a neighborhood in the US.
- Yes.
- It's in the south.
- Harlem? South?
It's a southern neighborhood effect.
- Southern...
- Neighborhood effect.
- Southern neighborhood.
- It's in the southern direction.
It's rap from a foreign country.
It's an effect of
southern neighborhood rapping.
(What do you mean?)
It's not rap
from a southern neighborhood.
You can't keep talking.
(An effect of
southern neighborhood rapping?)
- Jae Suk.
- What?
It's a person who raps
in a southern neighborhood.
There's an effect.
(An effect of a person?)
(They get farther away
from the answer.)
- Ji Hyo gets scarier.
- A person?
- There's no person.
- Hey!
- Do you have a hearing problem?
- No.
- Listen.
- What's wrong with her hearing?
- How can I believe you?
- There's an effect...
- of a person who raps in the south.
- South.
(Jae Suk gets "south" correctly.)
South rap.
Effect.
(South rap effect is wrong.)
I answered based on what she said.
There's an effect
of rapping in the south.
It's southwest effect.
This is absurd.
Can we change the order?
- Let's change. It's hard.
- How could you...
- Goodness.
- Jae Suk.
Here we go. 1, 2, 3.
(Galapagos Syndrome)
(A globally available product
sold only in its local country)
This is so difficult.
(It also refers to
something isolated...)
(due to a lack of communication
with outside countries.)
- This is what it is.
- Yes?
- It's becoming alone and lonely.
- "Alone and lonely"?
- There's an island.
- An island?
(He's the first
to explain properly.)
- Its name is 5 syllables.
- 5-syllable name of an island.
- Is it becoming alone and lonely?
- Yes.
Jae Suk must know what it means.
It gets separated from the outside
and becomes an island.
- It becomes lonely.
- A lonely island?
It's in isolation due to
the separation from the outside.
- "Separation from the outside".
- It's that type of syndrome.
It's an island.
(Galapagos Syndrome)
It's where lonely people go.
(They aren't going anywhere.)
Lonely people...
That's not right.
Five... What I mean is...
There are five.
It's where lonely people go.
The name of this island has
five syllables.
(It's far from the answer.)
- It's an island.
- Okay.
- It's where lonely people gather.
It's where lonely people
communicate.
(It's infuriating.)
- It has five syllables.
- Goodness.
Five syllables?
- It's five syllables.
- It's a syndrome.
- Is it five syllables?
- Yes.
It's an island for lonely people?
Lonely island syndrome.
(Lonely island syndrome is wrong.)
(We're doomed in this round.)
This is too hard.
I told you it's difficult.
- Next team.
- What comes after "super"?
What's a word for a new person?
- Super...
- Super rookie?
- Right. It's three syllables.
- Rookie?
Rookie-ism?
(They're off to a good start.)
What comes after super?
It means a new person.
- Man.
- No.
(It's obviously Superman.)
You ran out of time.
Yawn? Four syllables?
Thunder.
You can talk.
(He's acting silly
when he's allowed to talk.)
- How many syllables, you jerk?
- How many syllables?
Not the front but...
- The back.
- Okay.
It's a total of six syllables.
Not the front but...
- Not the front but...
- The back.
Isn't it Children's Back Syndrome?
Is it right?
(Children's Back Syndrome
is correct.)
(They get
the last question correct.)
- Okay.
- We got it.
I was worried because
you said "back".
As a result, Team Jong Kook won.
- Among the team members,
- We won.
- we'll pick the winner.
- We won but...
- Even though we won,
- we have to keep playing.
- Will we choose a winner?
It's so funny that we won.
We're starving.
It's driving me nuts.
- Can we play rock-paper-scissors?
- It doesn't matter.
Who will be the winner?
I didn't win
rock-paper-scissors at all today.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jong Kook and So Min win.)
Please.
- Please.
- Jong Kook will win again.
- So Min will lose.
- Please.
I always lose in the second round.
- So Min will definitely lose.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min wins a chance to eat.)
I was going to play scissors.
(He's disappointed.)
(So Min wins a chance to eat.)
So Min...
may either pick a card
or clear a special mission.
- So Min, clear a special mission.
- I'll take a special mission.
Okay.
Special mission, So Min.
- You can do it.
- It's a mission.
- I'll take a special mission.
- So Min.
Go outside for your special mission.
Here I go.
(What kind of
special mission awaits her?)
What is it?
(She goes outside
for her special mission.)
"Take a bottle of water
from the stand in front of you."
"You win if you reach the mark
without the attendant noticing."
Take a bottle of water
and reach within this red line.
If the attendant touches
or catches you, you fail.
How can I take it
without her noticing?
(So Min and the stand)
(The stand is far away.)
How am I going to take it
without her noticing?
(She fails if she gets caught
before the finish line.)
I should have picked a card.
(She must run this distance
without getting caught.)
- Hello.
I picked this mushroom
on my way here,
but what this place?
This is a store.
(She checks where the water is.)
Can I buy something?
Yes, you can buy anything.
What would you like?
- Can you give me some water?
- Okay.
(The attendant hands her the water
without being suspicious.)
- Water and...
- Okay.
(She obtains a bottle of water.)
soda.
May I get the one on the left?
(She sees her opportunity.)
(When the worker turns around,)
Corn chips or something like that.
(She runs away.)
(She just needs
to reach the finish line.)
(She sees So Min running away.)
(Catch that thief.)
(The attendant chases after So Min
at a frightening speed.)
(She gets closer to So Min.)
Goodness.
(She throws away the water bottle.)
(So Min doesn't get far,)
(and gets touched.)
She's so fast.
(So Min's special mission...)
(is a fail.)
I want to eat too.
I usually run 100m in 21 seconds.
I don't think I ever ran
this fast in my life.
(However, she wasn't fast enough
to clear the mission.)
She's very fast.
(She touched So Min very quickly.)
(Who is this worker?)
(Athlete Choi Soo In)
(Gold medalist of an international
track and field competition)
(She's a rising star
in middle-distance running.)
("Choi Soo In,
A Double Gold Medalist")
("The Future of
Korea's Track and Field")
(To clear the mission, one must
defeat Athlete Choi Soo In.)
(It's an extreme mission.)
(Will anyone clear
this special mission?)
- So Min is back.
- So Min is here.
- Where?
- Did you succeed?
Of course not.
I shouldn't have been greedy.
- Did you fail?
- She failed.
Why are you panting?
There's a reason.
(If you're curious, go outside.)
I'm exhausted.
(What kind of mission is it?)
I'm so tired.
Is everyone hungry?
- Yes.
Here's your last mission.
It's called Spinning King of Chairs.
- I can't do it.
- It'll be dizzy.
I can't do things
that make me dizzy.
- It's a team competition.
- Team?
It'll be 4 on 4.
One person
from each team will play...
with their eyes covered.
When the spinning chair stops,
you succeed if you hit
the opponent with a squeaker hammer.
- What?
- It sounds difficult.
The team members will be important.
We need to get on a good team.
All right.
- So Min.
- Mine is...
- Blue.
- Red.
(Teams are determined.)
The teams are decided.
One from each team will come out.
Let's start.
(Suk Jin is on defense,
and Kwang Soo is on offense.)
- Can you do it, Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
- What?
- Wait.
- You get dizzy.
- Which direction is it?
That's right.
- He senses the direction.
- Okay.
That's good.
- Shall we start from here?
- Spin him.
- Let's start from here.
- That sounds good.
How about here?
- Kwang Soo.
- This is great.
- Okay.
- Spin his chair.
- Are you having fun?
- Wait.
You have to spin it.
- Here we go.
- Spin it now.
Start.
(They spin his chair.)
He got it.
(His sense of direction is ruined
because he was interrupted.)
(He's pointing
in the opposite direction.)
(I think this is where Suk Jin is.)
(It's completely wrong.)
(He has lost his sense
of direction.)
(They distract him
so that he feels movement.)
If I concentrate,
I'll hear something.
(Snapping)
(Jae Suk does something
confuse him.)
(Don't be fooled, Kwang Soo.)
If the sound is coming
from over here,
that means the cameras
aren't on this side.
(He uses all five senses.)
There's no way that
he turned his back on the cameras.
Cameras are on this side.
(He's exactly right.)
(Kwang Soo figured out
the direction.)
(All he has to do is
hit him with the squeaky hammer.)
(Stop it, Jae Suk.)
(It's okay. Trust me.)
(Will Kwang Soo hit Suk Jin?)
What?
(Swinging)
(His ridiculous swing misses.)
Didn't you say that
the cameras are on this side?
- Fool, you said cameras were here.
- You were right. What's wrong?
I don't understand.
- I don't understand it at all.
- It's hard to know.
All right.
You said that the cameras are on
this side, but you swung this way.
- They were on this side.
- This is...
- a fool's game.
- He said cameras were here.
So I thought he'd swing that way.
I thought he'd hit me too.
- Who's next?
- Okay.
- We'll give you tips.
(Jong Kook spins Ji Hyo's chair.)
(It's a powerful spin.)
(Nice one, Jong Kook.)
I spun so many times.
(Ji Hyo became the spinning top
from "Inception".)
Wait, I'm nauseous.
(Nice, Jong Kook.)
(The chair finally stops
after 20 turns.)
Wait.
(She must have lost
her sense of direction.)
(I hope that she finds
(She uses all her five senses.)
I can't hear anything.
(Pulling)
(Suk Jin cheats.)
(You can't cheat.)
I feel like someone is here.
(His body freezes except his eyes.)
I think someone is here.
If someone is here...
(He moves only his lips.)
Right?
(Moving slowly)
(Yes, that's exactly right.)
Kwang Soo must be...
(No...)
here.
What?
He got hit.
(She hit Kwang Soo.)
- He got hit.
He got hit.
He got hit on his shoulder.
Ji Hyo.
(How did she hit him?)
That's impressive.
Okay.
- As a result,
- We won.
Jae Suk, Haha, Suk Jin,
and Ji Hyo wins.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo, they win.)
We have to pick the winner
from the four of you.
The one who picks the dud will be
the winner.
- The dud?
- Is that the winner?
- The one with the dud wins.
- Dud means you won.
1, 2, 3.
(Who will pick the dud and win?)
Dud!
- 1, 2, 3.
- Dud!
(Haha picks the dud.)
Dud!
(Haha gets to choose
a special mission or pick a card.)
Haha, will you pick a card...
or do a special mission?
- Pick the mission.
- You should pick the mission.
You should do it.
I choose the special mission.
If you clear the mission, you
and a person of your choice may...
- eat for 3 minutes.
- 3 minutes?
- That's amazing.
- That's amazing, Haha.
- Good luck.
- Is it for three minutes?
Three minutes is a lot.
- That's great.
- I'm starving.
Do it.
Haha, please go
outside the building.
- Me?
- Thank you.
- Haha, I love you.
- Okay.
Don't forget that
you sprayed water on me.
Okay.
What's the special mission?
(What's the special mission?)
"Go to the stand in front of you."
"Take a bottle of water.
You win if you reach the mark."
I have to steal it right?
Okay.
Who's the attendant?
Here I go.
How should I do it?
(He heads to the store.)
- Hello.
(Getting a water bottle
is the priority.)
What do you sell?
- I sell almost everything.
- "Almost everything"?
First of all,
give me everything from
the first and second shelves.
- Everything?
- Yes.
(Athlete Choi Soo In)
(Her identity is revealed.)
(Shocked)
(Does he have to run...)
(across this wide field
faster than a gold medalist?)
(How can I win this?)
How much is it per item?
A bag of chips is two dollars.
A drink is a dollar.
That one.
May I get that and...
(He runs.)
(As soon as she turns around,
Haha starts.)
(He increases the distance
successfully.)
(His opponent is a gold medalist.)
(She's right after Haha.)
Where is it?
(He sees the finish line.)
(Did Haha win
and clear the mission?)
- He's back.
- What's wrong with him?
- Did you finish the mission?
- I think so.
Is the mission easy enough?
- I think he failed.
- Did you clear it?
I think he cleared it.
I bet it was hard.
Haha's mission was...
(What's the result of
Haha's mission?)
(Athlete Choi Soo In gets closer
to him.)
Why is she so fast?
(With just one step ahead,)
(Haha gets to the finish line.)
(Choi Soo In couldn't catch Haha.)
Haha, you've cleared the mission.
Why is she so fast?
Did she win a gold medal?
(I almost caught him.)
Was she this close to me?
(He almost got caught.)
(Haha's plan was perfect.)
(He started as soon as
her weight moved behind.)
(The start is important
for short-distance runs.)
She's so fast.
(The finish line was close enough
to reduce the distance apart.)
- Haha's mission was a success.
- That's right!
- What was it?
What did you do?
He cleared the special mission.
- With one more person,
- I bet it was hard.
he may eat for three minutes.
Three minutes? That's amazing.
- Haha.
- If it was long distance...
Haha.
Haha, please pick one person.
- Haha.
- I will never forget it.
- I'll eat only a little.
- Haha.
- Okay.
Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is impressive.
Thank you.
Haha.
He ate last time thanks to me.
He eats again.
You have three minutes.
The count will start now.
Try some dried yellow corvina.
There's a lot to eat.
(Ji Hyo starts to eat
dried yellow corvina first.)
Ji Hyo, you should eat
dried yellow corvina with rice.
- I couldn't wait.
- Try some.
(It's more delicious
with just us two.)
- It looks delicious.
- What is that?
They chose only delicious food.
It's so long.
Is it his second time eating?
He's such a selfish jerk.
(They're jealous.)
- We have to make him regret.
- Five,
4, 3,
2, 1.
- Time's up.
- Please come out.
(I still have room for dessert.)
Goodness.
(Their mealtime is over.)
As promised, three hours are up.
Except for Haha and Ji Hyo,
no one ate.
We have to pick one person
to be penalized.
- Is it 1 person?
- 1 person?
There are six of you.
I can't believe we couldn't eat.
Among six cards,
we put an X on one card.
I'm very unlucky
at picking cards today.
- Jong Kook is unlucky today.
- I'm serious.
- It's not my day.
- Let it be Jong Kook.
I'll shuffle the cards
and give them to you.
I'll tell you
what the penalty is first.
It's the one So Min did before.
When we're having guests,
you'll dress up as someone else
for the opening segment.
If So Min gets it,
we'll do that twice.
Here we go.
- Who will pick it first?
- You should pick for me.
Earlier, I chose number four...
All right. Let's pick one.
- I'm having the worst luck today.
- I don't know anymore.
- I'll take the leftover.
- I chose mine.
Yes, just take the leftover card.
I'm having the worst luck.
I should wait and see.
It's a hassle dressing up
in the opening segment.
- And it's burdening too.
- All right.
We'll go one at a time.
- Se Chan. I hope it's you.
- Se Chan will go first.
- Let it be you, so this is over.
- I hope it's him.
- The X mark.
- It's the X mark.
(Se Chan passes.)
Okay!
- 1 of these 2 should have it.
- I hope it's him.
- It has to be him.
- It's between you two.
- It's you!
- Let it be you.
(Please!)
(Jae Suk passes too.)
- Let it be you.
- Jae Suk is happy.
It's got to be you.
- How many do we have left? Please.
- Let it be you.
- There are four left.
- Please, let it be Suk Jin.
- Then it's a 25 percent chance.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(4 members remain.
The probability is 25 percent.)
(Suk Jin gets the penalty.)
(Come on.)
Oh, no.
We're good.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
All right.
There were two cards left
at the end, and Suk Jin chose that.
(It's total luck of the draw.
There were two cards remaining.)
(Suk Jin chose the card first.)
(And Jong Kook took the last card.)
Suk Jin will carry out the penalty.
We're done with today's mission.
- Okay.
- Okay!
(With what disguise
will Suk Jin make us laugh?)
(Those who don't belong
to this world showed up.)
My goodness!
(Hades is spiteful after
being exiled into the underworld.)
(Hades came back to this world
to catch Zeus and Poseidon.)
(The traces of Hades
are seen all over the place.)
(And these 4 mysterious individuals
are joining too.)
(In order to send back Hades
who is pretending to be a human,)
(they must reveal his identity
with hints and eliminate Hades.)
(Who is Hades,
hiding among the members?)
(Run away now!)
(The War of the Deities:
Hades' Revenge)