It's summer now.
- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
Looking at the set-up here today,
- I noticed we have a keyboard here. - Right.
- I already know what this is for. - What's all this?
- Finally. - And we're on the lawn too.
- We've been waiting for this. - It's the joint performance.
- It's time! - This is nice.
- I'm so excited. - My gosh.
- I'm so nervous. - This is going to be fun.
Nice.
- We have so many sitting cushions. - Seriously, I'm so excited.
- There are a lot. - How many artists are there?
- We have a lot. - There are a lot of seats.
Will I be able to see them in person?
By the way, this is nice.
- It's Pandora's box. - It's fancy.
Se Chan, seriously.
- Your outfit looks so lame. - What?
(We're having guests today, and you look so lame.)
Should I buy you a belt?
I dressed up to the nines.
- He has a string around him. - What's that?
- Should I tie it for you? - Why would you do that for me?
Hey, are you two here to film a historical drama?
(Hey, are you two here to film a historical drama?)
Me? Don't clump me with him. My outfit looks fine.
- He dressed like a womanizer. - Like a womanizer.
- No, that's not me. - He's a womanizer.
- A womanizer. - You look like a womanizer.
- He's the good-looking one. - Right.
(The Good-Looking Womanizer)
- He's the good-looking one. - Right. He's the good-looking one.
- That's your role. - He's the good-looking one?
- And you're the smooth talker. - Smooth talker.
You'll choose your artists through the Teamwork Race today.
- Yes. - Teamwork Race?
Four teams of musicians are waiting now.
Two Running Man's members will pair up with a team of musicians...
and perform together on stage.
I want to sing a ballad song this time.
- Me too. - A very soulful one.
- Can you pull it off? - Yes.
- I'll sing like Green Area. - I want a female singer.
Green Area?
- Jong Kook... - I want a soulful ballad song too.
(He's a real ballad singer.)
Do you want to pair up with me?
- No, no. - That's boring.
- Not with you. - That will be boring.
Wasn't that really disappointing? He said, "not with you".
- Why not? - I'd be disappointed.
Why not, JK? You're afraid we won't stand out?
- Double Ha. Don't be like that. - "Double Ha"?
My gosh.
You'll listen to a snippet of a trot song the artists will sing...
without any instrumental music.
- Without instrumental music? - Trot songs?
And they will choose two members who will ask them questions.
- They'll answer only 2 questions. - 2 questions?
- Two questions? - Once we hear their voices,
- we'll recognize the singers. - They have unique voices.
- We'll know right away. - Right.
Why don't you listen to their singing first?
- Okay, let's listen to them first. - Trot songs?
- We'll start with number one. - They'll sing without the music.
I'll know once I listen to them.
All right. The artists behind door number one.
Please sing a trot song without the music.
(Looking forward to it)
Please sing.
My goodness, my goodness, don't be like that
It's a female singer.
- Her voice is husky. - It's a female singer.
Isn't that Jin Young?
No, it's not Jin Young.
- She has a husky voice. - Right. It's Jin Young.
Don't laugh
Her voice is really nice though.
- I can tell she's a good singer. - She's trying to deceive us.
- She's a good singer to begin with. - Her voice is really husky.
- She was relaxed when she sang. - I can't guess who that is.
- That was done on purpose. - Right.
She didn't use her vocal power at all. Number one didn't.
- That was confusing. - Right.
- Who is she? - Her pitch was perfect.
We'll listen to the musician behind door number two now.
(The 2nd artist sings a trot song without any music.)
Please sing it.
(He sings with power.)
My love toward you
- Hold on, please stop. - What?
- That singer was... - Wasn't that Myung Soo?
- You know what? - I think he's a comedian.
Regardless of one's singing ability,
I can tell this person is very ambitious.
(The 2nd artist is overly ambitious.)
- Is it too much? - Is that so?
- He sang powerfully. - I should talk to him.
He wants to stand out.
In my opinion, I think he has a hidden agenda...
other than the joint performance.
- I should stay far away from him. - Right.
- Right. - We must put him in his place.
What do you mean?
- I must put him where he belongs? - You'll do that?
- I ought to do that. - Hey.
Do you even have enough power to do that?
- I don't. - Can you even pull that off?
- You look like a village foreman. - Right.
- You're a village foreman. - My gosh.
What do you think about the second artist's voice?
I think he might be a viewer.
- I thought... - Right.
- I don't think he's a singer. - Right.
- He's not a singer. - We should listen to the third one.
- You think he's not a singer? - Here's why. When he sang...
- He's not a professional singer. - No, I don't think he is.
- He does sound too enthusiastic. - You think so?
In my opinion, he could be a comedian who released an album.
- Is that Sae Ho? - Sae Ho?
No, no.
I know him very well. Sae Ho can't even sing like that.
- Right, he can't help others. - Exactly. He's not that good.
- But he missed a few notes. - Exactly.
- He could've done that on purpose. - That's right.
- Think about all the possibilities. - That sounded natural.
He might play an instrument.
- He might not be a singer. - Right.
It's the third artist's turn.
(The 3rd artist will sing a trot song without music.)
As we clink our glasses, we say,
"Cheers, cheers, cheers"
As we clink our glasses, we say, "cheers, cheers, cheers"
(His singing confuses them.)
- Is he another viewer? - Hold on.
- Hold on. Please stop singing. - But I can't give you
- My heart - That's enough. Thank you.
- Here's what I think. - Wait.
- I can't be in love - Stop! Stop singing!
- Stop it! - That's enough.
All alone
- Stop singing. - Stop it.
Is he also looking for a chance to be famous?
- I mean... - Stop it.
(His ambition is endless like his singing.)
As for this guy,
- he's very ambitious too. - He's overly motivated.
- I'm sorry to interrupt. - Right.
Can I ask him to sing an octave higher?
- Do you want that? - Yes, an octave higher.
- Excuse me, door number three. - His singing was too stable.
- Please sing with an octave higher. - An octave higher?
How can he sing at an octave higher?
(He warms up his vocal cords first.)
As we clink our glasses, we say, "cheers, cheers, cheers"
(Perfect)
That sounded different.
(My gosh, he can pull that off?)
Hey, isn't that Kim Chang Ryul?
Isn't that Kim Chang Ryul?
The guy from DJ DOC?
(He sings like Kim Chang Ryul too.)
That's enough.
- He sounds like a singer now. - Hey, this is...
- He's a singer. - Yes, he's a singer.
- But he's not a ballad singer. - Right.
- Perhaps, he sings rock. - Yes.
We've listened to the third artist now.
Artist behind door number four, please sing for us.
(The 4th artist will sing a trot song without music.)
- My gosh. - Goodness.
(They're surprised as soon as she sings.)
- That's Jin Young. - Wait, hold on.
- No, it's not Jin Young's voice. - She sounds like a trot singer.
- A senior trot singer must be here. - Hey, she's from "Miss Trot".
She's good.
She's really good.
(Exceptional singing skills are evident in her voice and style.)
- That's enough. - Isn't she...
- Hong Ja from "Miss Trot"? - That's enough.
- She might've been on "Miss Trot". - She's from "Miss Trot".
- It's Hong Ja. - Was her name Ga In?
- No, her voice is husky. - Hong Ja?
Hong Ja has a thin voice.
- Or it might be Mi Ae. - Hong Ja?
No, she's a real trot singer.
By the way, she's good.
What did you think?
(What does he think after listening to all of them?)
I don't want to pair up with the second one.
(I don't care about anything else. I just don't want the 2nd artist.)
(That's so true.)
- That was blunt. - The second artist...
Does everyone not want the second artist?
Usually, when people sing that part...
Hold on. It's Ji Hyo's turn to talk. Wait for yours.
(Hold on. It's Ji Hyo's turn to talk. Wait for yours.)
- Womanizer, let's stay out of it. - Womanizer, you must wait.
- What? Goodness. - Don't interrupt.
- Wait, Womanizer. - I'll never wear...
- shirts like this. - Here's why.
- Hold on. - I didn't feel good when I wore it.
- I'm so relieved. - Please wait for your turn.
It's Ji Hyo's turn.
- She's been waiting for her turn. - Yes.
- I'm sorry. - Let her go first.
- It's my turn. - I'm sorry.
Ji Hyo, tell us what you think.
He has a lilting voice.
(He has a lilting voice.)
I want you to listen to him before you talk.
- Ji Hyo, focus on the show. - He didn't have a lilting voice.
- He didn't have a lilting voice. - Right.
What about you, Womanizer?
- "Womanizer." - Can you answer on a motorcycle?
If you flip the word, it becomes Weasel.
In my opinion...
I mean, compared to other singers,
he tried too much to show us everything.
- He showed off too much? - Yes.
- What about you, So Min? - Let me make a food analogy.
We've had bland food that wasn't seasoned well.
- But as for the fourth singer, - That's a great analogy.
- she was nicely seasoned. - Nicely seasoned.
It's like grandma's cooking.
- In a nutshell, - Grandma's cooking?
- she's a good restaurant. - Totally.
What about the second artist?
In my opinion, the second artist is...
If I were to compare it to beef radish soup...
In my opinion, he needs advice from Mr. Baek Jong Won.
(In my opinion, he needs advice from Mr. Baek Jong Won.)
- He must join "Alley Restaurants". - Yes, he must join that show.
- He must join "Alley Restaurants". - Yes, he must.
Right. He needs Mr. Baek.
But we could tell that 1st, 2nd, and 4th artists were...
good at singing.
- But the 2nd artist... - The 1st artist is a great singer.
- Right. I see. - She didn't use her vocal cords.
Now, we'll ask two questions to each artist.
- Okay. - What should I ask?
Does any of you have questions for the first artist?
- Isn't the year of debut important? - That's important.
- Ask that. - The year when they debuted.
- Artist number one. - We'll know their experience.
- Artist number one. - Yes.
- My gosh. - Her voice is altered.
- It's a woman. - Yes, it's a woman.
In what year did you make your debut?
I debuted during the 2000s.
- The 2000s? - The 2000s?
- Singers from the 2000s... - She's been around for a while.
If she debuted in the early 2000s, she's been singing for 15 years.
She won't give us a number.
Can we ask what kind of genre she sings?
We can ask one more question. Go ahead, Ji Hyo.
Well, your...
- Ask her. - Genre.
- Well, your... Ask her. - Genre.
You ask her about her genre.
- She's weird. - Hold on.
Am I your parrot?
Womanizer, ask her.
She called you Womanizer.
- Ask her. - Ask her now.
May I ask what kind of genre you sing?
I sing various genres.
- Various genres? - You can't answer it like that.
- That's ambiguous. - Pick one.
- The most confident genre. - The one you sing more frequently.
- The genre you focus on. - Right.
Well, RnB and ballads?
- RnB and ballads? - Okay.
- Okay. - Artist number one.
- That's it. We asked two questions. - It's over.
- We can only ask two questions. - Stop it. Hold back your question.
- Hold it back. - All right.
RnB and ballads?
Who is she? RnB and ballads?
- Question the second artist now. - Does he want to be famous?
- Are you a singer? - That's what I want to know.
- Are you a singer? - Do you want to be famous?
Well, I...
- He's not a singer. - Hold on.
- No. He's obviously a comedian. - What was that?
I'm not a comedian.
You're not a comedian?
We can ask one more question.
- Let's ask him this. - Genre.
Let's ask whose voice among ours will complement his voice the best.
- Okay. - Yes.
- Whose... - It'll be hard to know that.
I will only accept questions about music.
(He sounds firm.)
- It has to be about music. - Ask him about genre.
- It must be about music. - He's one arrogant guy!
I don't know who he is,
- but he sure is arrogant. - He refused to answer our question.
- Ask him about the genre. - Okay. Ask him about the genre.
What's your genre?
RnB, hip-hop, indie music,
and everything else.
- Hip-hop? - He's a hip-hop artist.
- RnB. - He must be a hip-hop artist.
- RnB? - Their voices sound different.
- There are 2 people? - Are there 2 people?
- 2 people? Are there 2 people? - There are 2 people?
- There's more than one musician? - Are they a pair?
I know who they are!
- Aren't they Dynamic Duo? - No, no.
- The guys from "Show Me the Money". - Who?
- Dok2 and The Quiett. - No, not them.
- You know those famous guys? - All right.
- Nafla and Loopy? - No, not them.
Seok Jin, why did you twist my arm?
(What's wrong with this guy?)
- I didn't do anything wrong. - That's not how you play this.
- Why did he twist my arm? - Why does he use force?
- You're not supposed to do that. - I just remembered them.
What made you twist my arm?
- Why did you do that? - I just remembered them.
- Don't do that when you're happy. - I was so happy.
We can't ask the second artists...
- any more questions. - We can't?
What's their name?
(Who are these artists that focus on hip-hop?)
Ask the third artist your questions. Only two of us will ask.
Can you ask him if he's a backup vocalist?
- Is he a main vocalist? - You ask him.
Are you a main vocalist?
- Of course, he is. - We'll find out if he's in a group.
- Yes. - He's the main vocalist.
- He's the main vocalist. - He's in a group then.
We don't know if he's in a group or not.
Even if he's a solo artist,
- he can still be a main vocalist. - He'd be a main vocalist.
Hey.
How could you waste a question like that?
You wasted a question.
- I'm sorry. - Discuss it before you ask.
- Ask him if he's in a group. - If...
- If you're in a group... - Ask them about the genre.
Ask him about the genre.
If you are in a group, how many of you are single?
(She's pondering.)
- You're unbelievable. - What would you ask him that?
- What are you doing? - I mean...
I was just curious.
- You're unbelievable, So Min. - If you're in a group,
- how many of you are single? - He's laughing.
I'd also like to answer questions about music.
- Okay. In that case, - Ask him about the genre.
have you been ranked first place on music shows? How many times?
- On music shows. - That's important.
I usually perform at shows.
(If he performs at shows...)
- He's an indie singer. - An indie band!
- I prefer indie bands. - They're an indie band.
- Okay. All right. - That's cool.
- We can't ask questions now. - It's over?
- Only the last artist remains now. - The fourth artist.
Should we ask her about her age?
- Sure. Let's ask her about her age. - Yes.
Artist number four, how old are you?
I'm old enough.
(I'm old enough.)
Hey, she had a bit of an accent.
She had an accent.
- She's definitely older than us. - She's old enough.
- She is older than us. - First of all...
- First off, - Her tone...
- she sounds experienced. - She sounds like a mom.
- "I'm old enough." - "I'm old enough." Her accent...
- Okay. One more question. - That's what my grandma says.
- When did you debut? - In the 70s.
- I was active in the 2000s. - It's the 2000s.
- The 2000s. - She was active in the 2000s?
- It could be Jin Young. - She must've been a late bloomer.
In a way, her voice sounds...
- It sounds familiar. - It does, doesn't it?
We finished asking our official questions.
I bet you're curious about the artists behind the doors now.
- I'm dying to know right now. - Will they come out right away?
- We'll end it here for this week. - What?
(I know it's disappointing, but we'll end it here.)
- What? - What was that?
(We'll end it here for this week without bringing in the guests.)
- What was that? - We'll end it here?
- What are you doing? - I'm dying to know.
- I'm so curious. - Tell us.
We must end it when people get curious.
- It's not a commercial break? - Right. It's over.
Is there a baseball game after the show?
- No, there isn't. - No?
- Something else might air next. - What do we end it here?
- Will something else air next? - That was short.
We could have talked over the phone then.
- You can sit over there. - Do we sit there?
- Okay. - Before we bring in the artists,
you'll pair up to form a team for today's mission.
- Okay. - We'll form a team first?
Two members will form a team with an artist.
You can line up in front of the artist of your choice.
If you catch the ball the artist throws,
you'll form a team together.
If you can't catch it, you won't be in that team.
As for the first team,
- we'll start with the first artist. - I think she's a good singer.
(She's a hidden master who concealed her outstanding skills.)
(RnB and ballads were her main focus.)
- 1, 2, 3. - She's good.
- She's an excellent singer. - She writes good ballad songs.
I'll go for the first artist.
- I'm going to try out too. - I was about to go too. Hey.
I was going to try out too,
but those members are like losers.
The members who are trying out are like losers.
Losers?
- How could you say that? - I was going to try out too.
- We're not losers. - How...
Jee Stream, Grasshopper, Womanizer. What's wrong with us?
(I won't join them.)
- Okay. I'll go for it. - I have no choice.
- I must be with her. - Let's go.
- Why is he joining us? - Why are you here?
The competition is fierce.
My gosh, the first artist is so popular.
I knew it. Singers must have pleasant voices.
I think you, me, and the first would make a perfect team.
- Our voices are... - They fit.
- Our voices are... - If that happens,
you'll have to dress up as Groot.
- Why? - No.
- We'll be a duet. - Right.
He can be one of our backup dancers.
Right.
(Due to his height, he'll serve as a great background.)
- That'll be your fate. - Let's find out.
I've never done a duet with a female singer.
Has he never?
Seriously?
- You're right. - Yes. I've never done it.
You can introduce yourselves one by one.
Hello.
I'm Jee Seok Jin, a singer who has made one album.
I have quite some knowledge in music.
I'll consider you as my senior and serve you well.
I'm number one, Jee Seok Jin, the well-versed singer.
- That was boring. - It was.
(They almost fell asleep.)
I was being honest.
I'll show you my singing skills.
(Se Chan decides to sing.)
(A thousand years)
(Se Chan doesn't seem too promising either.)
- Goodness. - He won't pass.
He'll fail.
(Nevertheless, he continues.)
That sounds terrible.
I can reach very high notes.
I'm number two.
- You won't pass. - As for me,
I'll be standing far away.
- The farthest? - Yes.
I'll stand to the right of you.
Okay. Where are you, Jong Kook?
- I'm here. I'm the farthest. - She's already made her choice.
I'm the farthest.
You can throw it now!
Here it goes.
(The ball passes Seok Jin and Se Chan.)
(It's flying towards Jong Kook.)
(I caught it!)
(Kwang Soo catches it.)
(He intervenes.)
(Snatching)
Okay!
(Wait for me! I'll be with you!)
Hey.
Goodness.
Do you know who caught the ball?
Jong Kook?
No, it was Kwang Soo.
I see.
(Does she hate me that much?)
(You deserve that.)
- She's disappointed. - I'm...
Seok Jin. I'm the closest to you!
Where are you, Jong Kook?
- I'm the closest to you! - Hold on.
(She has her eyes set on only one person.)
- Hold on. - Excuse me.
She wants to partner up with Jong Kook.
She's already made her choice.
- Please throw it. - We'll catch it.
Okay.
(Jong Kook catches it.)
Okay. I got it.
Goodness.
Hey, Kwang Soo looks unhappy.
- Not at all. - He'll be a backup dancer.
Not at all.
- You're an outsider. - No, I'm fine.
This is exactly how I predicted it.
- Let us meet... - I'm anticipating.
the first artist.
Will her partners come out too?
Who is it? I'm dying to find out!
- Me too. - Romantic Punch and Womanizer.
- "Romantic Punch"? - They'll be a team.
Romantic Punch and Womanizer.
Please come on out.
(Everyone is anticipating.)
Who is it?
(Who is the 1st artist?)
- It's Gummy! - It's Gummy!
(1st artist, Gummy)
(She's the best ballad singer in this country...)
(with her unique and mellow voice.)
("Gummy, the Queen of Soundtracks")
("Gummy Receives 2016 Asia Artist Awards")
(She is the queen of soundtracks...)
(and also the queen of duets.)
(Her charms will mesmerize you forever.)
- It's Gummy! - It's Gummy!
(It's the mighty Gummy.)
(They're surprised.)
It was you.
Hey.
Goodness, this is amazing.
- It's amazing. - It is.
- Hello. - Hi, Gummy.
I had no idea.
I'm looking forward to Jong Kook and Gummy's duet performance.
But she's way too good.
I am looking forward too.
I'm really looking forward to them performing.
- Me too. - They look good together.
- Their voices match. - Hey.
He said it's a collaboration between a spider and a mosquito.
(He tattletales on Se Chan.)
(It's a harmony of insects.)
- Don't say that. - I didn't say that.
- No, no. - What did you just say?
Hey, come here.
I can kill you with some insect repellent.
This is a nice match.
There is a spider, a mosquito, and a long-headed grasshopper.
- He's a swallow. - He's a water strider.
(Kwang Soo is pretty much invisible.)
Gummy.
The first artist was Gummy.
You should've given us a heads-up.
I know.
We will do the interviews later.
- Okay. - Please sit down.
- Sit down. - Number one was for ballad songs.
I really look forward to Jong Kook and Gummy.
Me too.
(They're a fantastic duo.)
That's enough!
(Kwang Soo is useless.)
I really look forward to their performance.
But these teams aren't fixed.
- Right. - Right.
- It's not fixed. - No, it's not.
Now, let's move on to the second artist.
(They move onto the 2nd door.)
(They were criticized for their oddly-familiar voices.)
(Everyone thought they were amateur singers.)
(But they claimed to specialize in RnB and hip-hop.)
(Who are they?)
This is the second room.
Come on out.
- Many of you are going. - It's the easiest.
- I know. - I want to partner up with them.
Hello, I enjoy hip-hop and RnB.
I can do many different genres.
Who's your favorite hip-hop, RnB artist?
(They want to know how well she knows the genres.)
I like Drunken Tiger.
(Drunken Tiger debuted in 1999.)
- That was a terrible answer. - They're very old.
- So Min doesn't know much... - Hey.
- She's old-school. - about these genres.
I think it's over. Come in.
I like Free Style!
(Laughing)
- Free Style? I see. - We use it for Cyworld.
We'd set their song as our background music.
Right, it was "Y".
All right.
I want to perform with you.
I am confident I can do well.
Okay, well, I don't have much to tell you.
(They're flustered.)
Can we move on?
- Why aren't you asking me anything? - Step back.
I bet they watched her singing on YouTube.
- Did you? - I think they did.
(She gives up.)
No wonder they don't want to team up with her.
- I think they watched it. - I think so.
It can't be helped then.
Hello, I'm Yang Se Chan.
Hello.
- What? - They like you.
(They're hospitable towards him.)
It seems like you want to become famous.
I can help you with that.
Help yourself.
(He acts arrogantly.)
(Haha gives him a reality check.)
I'll help you.
- Okay, go stand. - Hey.
- I'm Haha. - I'll be behind Haha.
We want Se Chan.
- Where is he? - They want Se Chan.
They want me?
They really like him.
- They really do. - They like me.
- Se Chan, please come close. - Why him?
Okay, I did.
(I'm here!)
- What? - Where did it go?
(What?)
(Why did they throw it so far away?)
(Haha reaches the ball first.)
- Nice! - Haha caught the ball.
Where should I stand? It's me, Se Chan!
It's over.
- What? - You may return.
- It's over? - Se Chan, go sit down.
Hey! You have a ball left!
- He's mad. - He is.
- He's mad. - You have a ball!
- Who are you guys? - I'm upset too!
- Who are you? - All right.
- I'm going to catch it. - Do you know...
where Haha is?
- He caught it. - He caught it.
- He did? - Yes.
Okay. That was a bad throw.
Okay.
- Who are they? - They're toying with them.
I'm not doing this either!
They're toying with us.
- He already caught one. - I'm so curious about them.
They know how to toy with us.
They must've been emcees before.
- Is that MC Ding Dong? - It could be.
MC Ding Dong?
- Goodness. - Ji Hyo!
(The ball is thrown.)
(Ji Hyo catches the ball.)
- She caught it. - Go sit down.
How could they throw it while we were talking?
That's fine. That's up to them.
- How could they? - They were faking it.
Let's see who they are.
Come on out.
- Who are they? I'm curious. - Who are they?
It's Code Kunst!
(The second artists are Nucksal and Code Kunst.)
(Nucksal went from an underground rapper...)
(to a leader of hip-hop music.)
("His Rapping Skills Are Commendable")
("Nucksal Is Known for His Crazy Raps")
(Code Kunst is the master of producing hip-hop music.)
(All hip-hop artists admire him.)
("Genius Producer with over 400 Beats")
("He Is the New Number One Composer")
(The two unique artists have come out together.)
They're Code Kunst and Nucksal!
(This is an even more monumental moment because...)
(Nucksal is known to look like Ji Hyo.)
Nucksal is here!
Seriously!
(Nucksal feels like a family member.)
It's so nice to meet you. I'm a big fan.
He really came out!
- He really did. - They look exactly alike.
- He really came! - They look alike.
(How much do they look alike, you ask?)
They look similar.
Goodness. I wanted to see him.
My gosh.
(She can't help looking at him.)
- They look alike. - Nucksal.
Do we really look alike?
You guys do look alike.
- I can't tell the difference. - We look alike.
I really wanted to see you.
He's become quite popular in the hip-hop scene.
He's so good with words.
He's like the Yu Jae Seok of hip-hop.
No wonder. They were so good at talking.
Goodness.
- This is amazing. - Nucksal is finally here.
I really wanted to see you.
Nucksal is witnessing the 40-year-old him.
- This is great. - It is.
It's wonderful.
- This is incredible. - Goodness.
- Right. - This is amazing.
Where should I go?
Perhaps, it because of her outfit.
But Gummy looks like the owner of this mansion.
(She looks like the owner.)
- She looks successful. - Right.
She looks like a successful realtor...
- in LA. - I know.
What's important is that these teams are not fixed.
- Really? - Yes. Because...
I'm not talking about anyone in particular,
but we won't succeed like this.
What?
Why were you pointing at me?
- I wasn't. - He wasn't talking about you.
- We're a set. - Okay.
- He didn't mention your name. - I mean...
- They won't be whole without me. - Right.
This just won't work.
I'm just saying some corrections are needed.
All right.
- Now... - I'm aiming for the fourth artist.
Let's move onto the third room.
Here we go.
(The 3rd artist is...)
(He seemed to enjoy making others laugh.)
(His singing voice sounded stable.)
(He also said he did concerts.)
(Is he in an indie band?)
(Who is the 3rd artist?)
- Okay. - Third artist.
- We should go. - Should we?
- For now... - So many are going.
Everyone's going.
Hello, I'm Jeon So Min. I'll do my best!
(He shouts loudly.)
Are you a freshman in college?
What are you doing?
Please pick me!
What is she doing?
Okay. Next, please.
Next, next.
(The freshman is rejected.)
Get out.
- Next. - Hello, this is Yang Se Chan.
I've finally come to my senses.
When you sang for the first artist,
your high pitch was memorable. We value that a lot.
(His high-pitch singing was memorable to him.)
Really?
(Singing)
(He tries to win some points.)
He likes it.
(So Min sings as well.)
(What is that?)
(They try to win his favor.)
So Min, come here.
Come here.
(They're happy that they didn't choose them.)
Hello, I'm Yu Jae Seok.
- What was that? - What?
- He's good at high-pitched singing. - She's getting right in this.
I'm a big fan. Can I listen to your high-pitched singing?
Here you go.
(Se Chan pinches him.)
(Se Chan gets the highest pitched sound out of him.)
- Was that nice? - That was wonderful.
- Really? - Yes. It was commendable.
All right. Please throw the ball.
Hold on.
The fourth artist has something to say.
Hi. I'm the last one.
Does that mean I don't have a choice?
- She's right. - Right.
They should go simultaneously.
- Right. - I'm disappointed.
She's so experienced.
She's right.
(The 4th artist seems to know well.)
(She had an experienced, sorrowful voice.)
(She sounded like a very experienced singer.)
(However, she debuted quite late.)
(Who is the 4th artist?)
Does the fourth artist have anyone she likes in particular?
As long as it's not Seok Jin, I'm fine.
Then we can exclude him.
- How dare she? - She doesn't want you.
I'm going to catch her ball.
You just wait! I'm coming for you!
- Please throw your balls. - That's hilarious.
Where is Se Chan?
I'm in front of the fourth door.
Stay there. I'll throw it towards you.
- Okay. - Third artist.
Please throw your ball.
- Please catch it. - All right.
(Murmuring)
So Min, what are you doing?
(The ball goes to So Min.)
Why did you talk to me?
(Haha distracted him.)
Why did he interrupt me?
A player doesn't look at the audience when they're noisy.
He's one funny guy.
- Why did you act that way? - Come on.
- He should have something. - I know.
I really like So Min.
- What? - I really like So Min.
- Thank you. - Fourth artist.
Where is Se Chan?
Seok Jin is far back.
- Okay. - Se Chan is...
right in front of you.
Seok Jin is the farthest.
- Get ready. - I'm right in front of you.
Get ready.
(They're planning to create the oldest duo.)
Go.
(Se Chan is in front.)
Seok Jin is in the back.
(Seok Jin takes the ball.)
Now, you'll take turns throwing your balls again.
- Third artist. - Here I go.
Okay.
(The 3rd artist is teamed up with So Min and Jae Seok.)
What is this?
All right. Let's meet them.
Third artist, please come on out.
It's SORAN.
(Third artist, SORAN)
(SORAN is a four-member band that has performed...)
(in many music festivals.)
("SORAN Has Amazing and Lovely Lyrics")
("SORAN Steals the Hearts of Women")
(They're a competent band that sings songs of comfort.)
(Hello, we're SORAN.)
Hello, Young Bae.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - It's SORAN.
It's SORAN.
"I Study You".
- You must like them. - Totally.
Didn't you go on stage with So Min before?
- Yes. - A long time ago.
- Right? Goodness. - It was during a festival.
We still have our fourth artist, so please sit over there.
Fourth artist.
She seems like a very experienced trot singer.
- She's like a teacher. - Yes.
Please come on out.
(Who is the 4th artist who will team up with Se Chan and Seok Jin?)
(It's Apink.)
It's Apink.
(Fourth artist, Apink)
(They debuted 8 years ago.)
(Every album that they've released had at least one hit song.)
("Apink Has Become More Mature and Skilled")
("Apink Members Are Both Beautiful and Talented")
(They appeared on the show often and always attracted high ratings.)
(They agreed to come out once again.)
(All the members have come out.)
- It's Apink! - It's Apink!
- They all came! - You should've told us it was you!
- Goodness! - I had no idea.
- Hey, you should've told us! - I had no idea.
- Come on! - What is this?
What is this?
They wanted to be as far away as possible from Seok Jin.
Oh, no.
- Seok Jin thought... - Goodness.
- you were his senior. - It was worth it.
I thought you were older than me.
Don't worry because...
- these teams aren't fixed. - No, they're not.
- That's a relief. - Let's sit down.
Why would you tell us not to worry when no one was worried?
Don't worry. These teams aren't fixed.
(Current Couples: Team Gummy, Team Nucksal and Code Kunst,)
(Team SORAN, Team Apink)
For our fan-meet,
we've called the best musicians...
of this country.
Please give a round of applause.
(Welcome)
I've said this numerous times,
- but these teams aren't fixed. - Right.
I won't say whom I'm talking about.
But some of you are not wanted by your teammates.
But then again, it may differ per team.
But for me, I look forward...
- to Gummy and Jong Kook. - Me too.
This is my personal opinion.
I think she's the best female singer.
- Right. - Me too.
Gummy's real name is Park Ji Yeon.
- It's interesting. - Why are you saying my real name?
I think it's a nice name.
It is. But if you're going with Gummy,
- Jong Kook needs to be Mosquito. - Hold on.
- Hold on. - Gummy and Mosquito.
I'm serious. You have to.
- How could you say that? - Mosquito.
It'll be Mosquito, Gummy, and Water Strider.
They're all insects.
- You should do that. - I like it.
If it's with her, I can deal with that.
- I think it's nice. - Of course.
(You can call me Mosquito.)
Gummy, isn't this your first appearance on our show?
- Yes. - Yes.
You can see who's filmed outdoor variety shows...
- by their outfits. - Right.
Am I not prepared?
Apink has a lot of experience in such shows.
They're prepared for today. On the other hand,
I'm the most concerned about Code Kunst.
- He's burning up. - He is...
- He's sweating. - He looks...
- He's sweating a lot. - He looks like a newbie.
- Why are your shoulders so big? - He's burning up.
(He's melting.)
If you put a magnifying glass over his body, he'll burn up.
- His lips are dehydrated. - A magnifying glass?
You'll see a haze.
Code Kunst is dressed the worst right now.
But SORAN is also in serious trouble.
- Look at them. - It's fall for them.
They're wearing vests, cardigans, and knits.
- Why are they wearing knits? - They're wearing black pants too.
It's so hot.
Seok Jin has been on this show...
for a very long time, so why is he wearing a knit?
This isn't a knit. This is a sweater.
- Right. - This is...
- Just ignore him. - like our team uniform.
I don't want my arms to get tanned.
- They're getting tanned. - He's going through puberty.
He's sensitive, so please be careful.
(He's a 54-year-old going through puberty.)
First off, let me introduce Gummy.
On February 7, 2003, she released her 1st album...
with her song "Like Them".
- She debuted 17 years ago. - I'm so embarrassed.
Applaud for her.
It's very rare to stay in the entertainment business...
for that long without causing any problems.
- Right. - You know that, right?
- I've been around for too long. - I debuted 24 years ago.
Please applaud for him.
You'd expect him to get in trouble.
- Seriously. - He's right.
But he's still holding on.
- 27 years. - What?
- He debuted 27 years ago. - Please applaud for him.
- His time is running out. - What?
- He has three more years left. - His time is running out.
- It'll be 30 years soon. - Right.
- He debuted 29 years ago. - Your time is running out.
Please applaud for me.
- He debuted 29 years ago. - Please applaud for me.
He's my senior.
He debuted before I was born.
These days, there are many issues in our industry.
But she's been doing great for 17 years now.
- Right. - It's amazing how much love...
she still gets with her voice.
Ji Yeon, please say a word.
- About being scandal-free? - Yes.
(What?)
Right.
This is an important question.
It is.
I've been realizing my fame more recently.
I've been doing many concerts,
and it's evident that my fans are growing.
It makes me want to sing until the day I die.
- Please do that for us. - Please do.
- Seriously. - I hold concerts too.
- I always say something at the end. - What?
That I'll be scandal-free and sing for a long time.
The paparazzi have given up on him.
(No one thinks he'll cause any trouble.)
- That's right. - Yes.
Ji Yeon, as I have said earlier,
I'd like to congratulate you.
You got married.
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
I'm not the type to interrogate her...
- on her marriage life. - Right.
- I'm not like that. - I hate those kinds of people.
- How's your marriage life? - We're not like that.
(How is her married life?)
- You ended up asking her. - It's just one question.
I can ask one question.
One question is all right. How is your marriage life?
- My marriage life? - Yes.
I'll just say that I recommend marriage to everyone.
- Really? - Yes.
- That's a rare thing to say. - Jong Kook is single.
Can you explain to him why you recommend it?
You have someone with whom you can freely talk...
about your worries.
- They will always be on your side. - Right.
They will forever be your companion.
What do you not like about Cho Jung Seok?
(Seok Jin suddenly asks a question.)
What was that? You're such a mood wrecker.
- Tell us three things. - You're the worst.
- Tell us three things. - You're just terrible.
- Tell us. - Don't make her uncomfortable.
We don't ask that question even on "Happy Together".
- My goodness. - Not even on talk shows.
If you ask that question on a talk show these days,
- you'd be booed. - Of course.
- Ji Yeon. - Yes?
"Running Man" has been going on for many years,
but we've never done this kind of collaboration.
We're very curious.
Is there any member you want to team up with?
He's right next to me.
(Do you mean us?)
But...
you pointed to the right first and then to the left.
- Is that important? - All right.
- We're number 1 and number 2. - Okay.
(Let's watch what Gummy did again.)
(Her right hand is telling the truth...)
(while her left hand is just being polite.)
- That's right. - That's so funny.
Number 1 and number 2.
She's so nice.
Why do you want to team up with Jong Kook?
When we did a show where artists collaborated,
I wanted to sing with him, but I didn't get a chance.
Also, Haha and I have been talking about...
collaborating for a long time.
Your partner is Kwang Soo.
Your teammate is Kwang Soo.
She picked me.
- Are you her manager? - No.
Are you here to shoot "Omniscient Interfering View"?
No.
- "Omniscient Interfering View". - Send him to that show.
All right. Shouldn't we see Ji Yeon's performance?
(Shouldn't we see Gummy's performance?)
- It's such an honor. - It really is an honor.
Finally.
It's an honor.
- I can't believe I get to see this. - I love you!
This song isn't really when the sun is out.
- I'm sorry. - We'll love it!
Thank you.
- We'll love it! - I can cry.
(Gummy shows off her charms before the collaboration.)
- This song. - I love it.
(One of Gummy's many hit songs)
("You Are My Everything")
(The audience is already falling in love.)
It was you
From the start
You were the one
Who would come to me
Even with just one encounter
My eyes spoke
I hope
This isn't something
That just passes by
Like the wind
(Gummy's soft voice makes you forget the heat.)
(Her voice from the in-ears sounds even better.)
(With 17 years of experience, she is the star of stars.)
You are my everything
Our fate pours down like the rain
(I can't believe she is on our team.)
Inside
My stopped heart
There is only one love
You are my everything
- Oh, my. - That was amazing.
Gummy!
(Her song was honey to the ears.)
Can I switch to Gummy's team?
- That was amazing. - Please sing one more song!
- Encore! - Encore!
Can you sing one more song? That was incredible.
I didn't expect you to ask for an encore.
Let me sing one more song then.
I'll sing "Childish Adult".
("Childish Adult" by Gummy)
- Please sing with me. - Are you going to dance?
(The audience is already excited.)
(Get ready to have fun.)
(Here we go.)
(Soulful)
(This is so fun.)
She's amazing.
(Look at So Min.)
(Dancing)
(She's trying to look sexy.)
(The soul groove begins.)
(This is what a groove means.)
(Dancing)
She's amazing.
- This is so classy. - She's fantastic.
("Running Man" has never been this classy.)
Make some noise!
(Gummy is the best.)
(The audience explodes with excitement.)
(Everyone copies Gummy's dance.)
Nice!
(Like this?)
(She finishes up with a fantastic vibrato.)
Thank you.
(Standing ovation)
This dance is so attractive.
That was amazing.
Everyone, give a big hand to Ji Yeon!
(The RnB queen gave a superb performance.)
(Praise Gummy!)
That was so classy.
- So classy. - I loved the dance.
She didn't move her hips too much.
- What are you doing? - Just a little bit.
Like this.
I loved it.
You shouldn't move your hips too much.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
It's burning.
Seriously...
- It smells like burning pork belly. - Yes. It does.
There's a burning smell.
- The leather is burning. - What are you wearing underneath?
- Can't you take the jacket off? - Okay.
- You can take it off. - Take it off.
This is the first time I've left home since spring.
(This is the first time I've left home since spring.)
You haven't left home?
(Code Kunst, been home for three months)
- Since spring? - Look at the color of his skin.
We rarely go outside.
- You don't go outside a lot? - No.
Unless we have a performance...
- And you perform in the evening. - Exactly.
In the hip-hop scene,
these two became a phenomenon.
They're writing history right now.
(They are talented hip-hop artists.)
Please introduce yourselves.
Hello. I'm Code Kunst of AOMG.
Also,
on hip-hop audition shows, he is the most sought-after...
mentor right now.
- He has so many hit songs. - He's so popular.
But Nucksal is just as popular as Code Kunst.
As you all know, "Cut Cut Cut"...
How would you describe the relationship between you two?
We met when we had almost no money.
We were 27 and making music without earning much money.
Since then, we've been working together.
You two have been best friends, right?
- I guess? - Are you best friends?
I overheard their conversation.
They're nothing more than business partners.
(They're nothing more than business partners.)
- Really? - Yes.
- Friends can do business too. - Of course.
We just have a different style of friendship.
- A "different style of friendship". - Keeping a beautiful distance.
You're close to Nucksal too, but who are you closest to?
- Woo Won Jae. - Won Jae.
- What about you, Nucksal? - I'm closest to Code Kunst.
What about you, Nucksal?
(He didn't think for a second.)
(It's a one-way friendship.)
You must feel hurt.
- It's a bit... - I...
It can happen.
- He can be closest to someone else. - They're so funny.
Do you have a nickname, Code Kunst?
- You look a bit like Kwang Soo. - Really?
- He looks a bit like Kwang Soo. - A little.
How did you feel when you heard that?
My mom often says I look like Kwang Soo.
- Your mom? - Your mom?
His mom must like you.
Did your mom feel proud?
I felt...
a bit offended at that time.
(I felt a bit offended.)
(Mom, how could you say that?)
His mom...
Does he have to be that honest?
But my mom told me that I shouldn't feel offended.
She made that clear to me.
- She corrected me. - His mom said that.
Why would he say that in such an angry voice?
It's just the way he speaks.
- Code Kunst is very polite. - All right.
I'll ask you the same question I asked Ji Yeon earlier.
Which member do you not want on your team?
To be honest,
- I don't want So Min on my team. - Why not?
On Running Man,
she's often clumsy.
She's incredibly clumsy.
Look at her right now.
(Awkward)
Look how awkward her gestures are.
That's... Look.
(Clumsy)
- This... - I know what it is.
Her upper body and lower body are out of sync.
I know what you mean.
- She wants to enjoy hip-hop music, - Exactly.
- but she can't express it well. - Actually,
I'm sorry to say this, but Ji Hyo will drive you crazy.
(Be prepared.)
- When you see Ji Hyo later... - She's the worst.
- She's terrible. - Show them.
No!
(Stiff)
Stop!
(I wish I didn't see that.)
- No! - Stop!
Every single joint moves on its own.
- But she doesn't have to move. - It might be a good thing.
- It might be a good thing. - What do you mean?
She asked if his name was Code Concert.
(She asked if his name was Code Concert.)
She thought his name was Code Concert.
It's not Code Concert.
(So Min didn't even know his name.)
(When they just started interviewing Code Kunst...)
(Code Concert?)
(What's his name?)
(It's Code Kunst.)
(I thought it was Code Concert.)
(Kunst, not Concert.)
- She thought it was Concert. - It's not Code Concert.
I'm relieved she didn't say, "Code Consent".
- It's not Code Concert. - She could have said, "Consent".
- I'm sorry. - Most people know his name.
She thought it was Code Concert.
Now let's see Code Kunst and Nucksal's performance!
(Code Kunst and Nucksal's hip-hop stage)
(Excited)
I love hip-hop.
I wanted to see it in real life.
This is not good.
(Code Kunst plays the keyboard.)
He's playing the keyboard.
Let's hear Code Kunst...
play the keyboard for a moment.
- Amazing. - It's a live performance!
(Full of swag)
He looks different.
He looks totally different.
(How will the nation's best hip-hop artists perform?)
This is so cool.
("Perfume" by Code Kunst, featuring Nucksal)
(They become soulful.)
(Nucksal's vibe lives up to his reputation.)
(This is fun.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E458 Running Man
"A Collaboration with Artists - Teamwork Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(This is crazy.)
I can hear the lyrics clearly.
(I can hear the lyrics clearly.)
(The song Code Kunst produced meets Nucksal's flow.)
(The performance captivates the audience in no time.)
(Good vibe, good performance)
(This is what Code Kunst and Nucksal can do.)
I could hear the lyrics clearly.
It was nice.
- It was an honor. - They are cool.
- They are cool. - I wish I could hear "One over N".
(Even the layman in hip-hop gives them a thumbs up.)
The next guests are...
Apink and SORAN.
(The popular girl group, Apink and the indie band, SORAN)
Let's start with SORAN.
SORAN.
Young Bae, you have starred in many TV shows...
and radio shows.
However, it's rare to have the entire band on the show.
- It's the first time. - Please, say hello.
I am the vocalist of SORAN, Ko Young Bae.
I am the bassist, Seo Myun Ho.
I am the guitarist, Lee Tae Wook.
I am the drummer, Pyeon Yu Il.
Pyeon Yu Il.
(The members of SORAN, welcome.)
Yul Il, I don't know how this will sound,
but...
you are quite ordinary.
(You are quite ordinary.)
Seriously.
You look like a man...
I would pass by on the street.
- That's right. - You seem ordinary...
and relaxed.
- There is a celebrity I resemble. - Who would that be?
He is very famous these days.
- And who's that? - It's Ryu Hyun Jin.
- Ryu Hyun Jin. - He is right.
(The Korean monster, Ryu Hyun Jin)
- I see the resemblance. - I see the resemblance.
- I see it. - That's right.
I see it.
I am sorry, but did you prepare that comment?
Your answer was unrelated to my question.
- Seriously. - I said you look ordinary,
- but you brought up Ryu Hyun Jin. - I said what came to my mind.
I see.
Ryu Hyun Jin is too extraordinary.
I heard that you have met So Min before.
- That's right. - I once worked as a festival lady.
That's when...
- Young Bae helped me. - Really?
She sang a duet with me on the stage.
- I sang a duet. - Really?
(In 2014, SORAN performed with So Min at a music festival.)
(Young Bae stayed by So Min's side since she wasn't used to the stage.)
(She kept her eyes on Young Bae and depended on him.)
(Thank you, Young Bae.)
How was your performance with So Min?
So Min has many bad habits...
as a vocalist.
What bad habits?
That's good. That's what we need to hear.
We need to know these things before we take the stage.
I thought he would compliment her.
Most people would compliment her in this situation.
(Did So Min do that badly?)
She tries to show off despite the lack of skills.
You are spot on.
(She tries to show off despite the lack of skills.)
- You know what I mean, right? - You are spot on.
You are spot on. You saw her move her hands, right?
Although she doesn't have any skills,
- she tries to feel the music. - That's right.
Her performance gets ahead of her.
- She prepares many comments. - Comments.
How did you feel about Young Bae back in the days?
Young Bae was known...
as Lee Byung Hun of Hongdae.
He resembles Lee Byung Hun a lot.
- Excuse me? - He resembles Lee Byung Hun a lot.
(Hold on.)
- I am serious. - I thought he was Pyo In Bong.
- I am serious. - Come on.
(I thought he was Pyo In Bong.)
- Haha. - Come on.
Watch your words.
We are meeting for the first time.
Stop it. Stop it.
We could form Tin Tin Five.
- No! - Tin Tin Five.
(They could use this opportunity to form Tin Tin Five.)
(Look forward to the 2019 version of Tin Tin Five.)
Nucksal could be Kim Kyung Shik.
We want to ask SORAN...
the same question we asked other teams.
Is there a member you want to work with?
As for me,
I want to work with Ji Hyo.
- Why do you want to work with her? - Why?
You haven't heard her sing.
- That's right. - I can sing well.
(Why did you pick Ji Hyo?)
- Think about it. - I can sing well.
Stop it.
I have watched her.
- You will be surprised. - I think...
Ji Hyo's tone of voice...
is very charming.
She has a baritone voice.
Ji Hyo, please sing a bit.
- Keep it short. - That's right. Go ahead.
- What should I sing? - It can be anything.
Sing one you're confident at.
- It can be anything. - Sing one you're confident at.
I loved you too much
(My goodness.)
Why did you sigh?
- What do you think, Yu Il? - Why did you sigh?
I will play the drums to her beat.
- I can do it. - My goodness.
He is kind.
- He is nice. - He sighed so loudly when I sang.
Seok Jin, what is your problem?
She made the atmosphere depressing in this heat.
(She made the atmosphere depressing in this heat.)
(For goodness' sake.)
I loved you too much
She should have sung that way.
I watched TV
(She shouldn't have stretched the note.)
Let's give SORAN a round of applause.
(It's time for SORAN's performance.)
Let's go SORAN.
(Everyone is excited.)
You guys are awesome.
Give them a round of applause.
SORAN!
(How will SORAN's performance be?)
("Don't Lose Weight" by SORAN)
(The melodious sound fills the area.)
(1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4.)
(The atmosphere turns 180 degrees.)
Let's go.
Running Man, make some noise!
(Screaming)
(She can't contain herself.)
(I was like that)
Then I met So Min
(I am embarrassed.)
(He added my name to the lyrics.)
(She shows him a heart.)
(Gosh, what is she doing?)
(What an eyesore!)
(I am sorry.)
(SORAN captivates women's hearts and sings love to the ears.)
(They have the unique vocal and harmonious band sound.)
(Anything is good with SORAN.)
(I love it!)
(Look at her.)
(The bass, guitar, drum, and vocal)
(The ensemble is uniquely SORAN.)
(SORAN never disappoints.)
- Thank you. - Give them a round of applause.
- They are the best. - Thank you.
The band, SORAN...
and girlfriend of one of the members,
So Min.
(Good work.)
- She made a heart. - Seriously.
That was too much.
- They are so cool. - They are so cool.
It was great to check out...
their performance outside on a hot day.
- Seriously. - They heated up the atmosphere.
Like I said before, recruiting the four teams...
- takes a lot of money. - That's right.
Do you have money?
Do you think I don't have money?
- What? - "Do you think I don't have money?"
- Do I look like a beggar? - I just mean...
you should be thankful...
- for the performances. - I know.
- It's an honor. - It's hard to recruit all of them.
- I know. I know. - Seriously.
Please give SORAN a round of applause.
(SORAN's performance with a full band sound ends.)
It's time for Apink.
(The girl group with 8 years of experiences, Apink)
Apink!
They visited Running Man as a group six months ago.
- That's right. - They are part of the family.
- That's right. - Eun Ji, you sang earlier, right?
- Yes. - I was so startled.
- Thank you. - I imagined...
a singer in her 50s.
- A seasoned singer. - I wanted you to imagine me...
- as Kim Yon Ja. - You sounded like her.
- Really? - Yes.
- Thank you. - Eun Ji is an incredible singer.
How long has it been since Apink debuted?
It has been eight years.
They are a long-running group.
Give them a round of applause.
All right.
- You know the Seven Year Jinx. - Yes.
Apink overcame it.
- It's quite a feat. - That's right.
There are people who think they are the best...
and want to work alone.
- That's right. - You left that way in two months.
- What? - It's true.
- It's true. - Yes.
- Who did that? - Seok Jin was in my agency.
Then he left in three months.
I did calculations and learned that I was losing too much money.
(I did calculations and learned that I was losing too much money.)
(He did calculations and decided to leave.)
- That's why I left. - For goodness' sake.
It's funny because it suits him.
- That's hilarious. - I respect him.
It's funny that the agency let him go without any regrets.
He became known as a troublemaker in the industry.
He really is a troublemaker.
Yes, he is a troublemaker.
Son Na Eun of Apink.
Na Eun, you filmed a commercial with Jong Kook.
- It's often on TV. - I see it very often.
- Yes. - It's about a diet.
Don't you keep in touch with Jong Kook?
- We text from time to time. - Yes.
He said he is going to LA.
"He said he is going to LA."
He loves LA.
People always see Jong Kook in LA.
A gym or LA.
A friend of mine went to LA on a trip.
He called me and asked,
"Does Jong Kook have a girlfriend in LA?"
- Really? - I asked, "Why?"
He said, "Everyone here says Jong Kook visits too often."
- "He must have a girlfriend here." - It must be...
because his daughter is having a summer break.
(Haha corrects the rumor.)
She is going to a summer school.
- That's right. - Because of you,
so many people think the rumor is true.
Cho Rong heard the rumor.
Really? Did you hear the rumor?
- Really? - I heard you have a child.
- What? - A child?
(Carefree)
Me? In LA?
Cho Rong's carefree words...
entered my ears so clearly.
- My goodness. - Seriously.
I am starting to have doubts since I heard it so often.
Maybe he really has a child.
We can't let them go without a performance.
That's right.
Apink!
(Let's see the powerful and pure Apink's performance.)
- They have so many hit songs. - That's right.
My goodness.
(Their most popular song livens up the atmosphere.)
(The uncle fans yell the chants.)
(When Apink members show the refreshing dance moves,)
(the uncle fans show dirty dance moves.)
(The members turn the shoot into an Apink concert.)
(Powerful)
(Pure)
(Fresh)
(Cheerful)
(The performance of "Luv" ends.)
What?
- Here comes another song. - Gosh, don't do this.
Don't do this.
("I'm So Sick" by Apink)
"I'm So Sick".
(Jae Seok shows off his good cheer.)
(The medley of Apink songs makes everyone excited.)
(Jae Seok is captivated.)
(Call me!)
(No!)
(The girl group with 8 years of experiences makes them chant.)
(The stage becomes heated up.)
Code Kunst took off his jacket.
(He took off his jacket.)
You put your hands together.
- It's my first time to see them. - Really?
He is in awe.
(There is no exit from the fairy-like group's charms.)
(The original fairy-like group, Apink)
(Everyone stands up.)
- Come, come. - They have many hit songs.
Please give Apink another round of applause.
- Apink is the best. - Everyone.
- I knew it. - Apink finally made...
Code Kunst wear an outfit that suits the weather.
Congratulations, Code Kunst!
(We did it.)
Code Kunst looks happy.
The sun and summer failed,
- but Apink succeeded. - Seriously.
He didn't stand up once before.
Then he suddenly took off his jacket and stood up.
He watched with his hands put together.
Ji Yeon, I am sorry.
- Why? - We blocked you...
too much.
Jong Kook's shoulders hit her a few times.
I wanted to watch Apink's performance,
- but I couldn't see anything. - I am sorry.
(When the atmosphere heated up earlier)
(I want to watch the performance.)
I am sorry.
- We went too crazy. - It's okay.
- "We went too crazy." - Seriously.
Give them a round of applause.
- It was really nice. - It was so much fun.
Since it's hot, I will hurry up and give you the rules.
Today, you will choose your partner for collaboration...
through Part Five of Nine Years of Running Man,
- Teamwork Race. - Okay.
Do you like your partners?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Yes. - Some of you...
might not like your partners.
The race consists of three rounds of team competitions.
The teams will be set at the end of the last mission.
- The partners can change now. - I see.
If you don't like your partners,
you can weed them out through the missions.
"Weed them out"?
Kwang Soo will be weeded out.
He uses such mean words.
- "Weed them out"? - How could you say that?
The 1st and 2nd place winners of the mission will be given...
special cards for changing the team members.
There are Change One and Change Both cards.
If all members submit the same card, the team will stay the same.
If a member submits a different card,
the team will be changed in accordance with that card.
Let's get the race started after you change.
(Who will be the final collaboration partner?)
It's a paradise. It's a paradise.
- It really is a paradise. - It's so cool.
I can finally breathe.
(They relax indoors after struggling under the sun.)
(Turning around)
(She suppresses her laughter.)
We are the only ones who look like middle-aged men.
(We are the only ones who look like middle-aged men.)
(It's especially true since they are wearing a uniform.)
We are neither fresh nor trendy.
- I am talking about our looks. - Yet we are on the front row.
We are the only ones who look like middle-aged men.
(They have friendliness.)
The first row is a disaster.
(The first mission starts with the friendly SORAN.)
You can weed out the team members you don't like...
and recruit team members you like...
- through this opportunity. - This is nerve-wracking.
Stop talking about weeding people out.
This is the first mission,
a relay in three parts, Do You Trust Me?
- Do You Trust Me? - Do You Trust Me?
(Do You Trust Me?)
- It's about trust. - That's right.
Okay. Let's go.
Three representatives from each team can participate.
In the set time of three minutes,
the team members must finish the relay.
The first player must sing...
two songs in a row like playing the word chain...
using the first word that is given by the production crew.
That's too hard.
We have to play word chain using songs.
Let's say "Sun" is the given word.
Sun sets at Soyang River
Eh, eh, eh, 2NE1
- That's how you play. - It's beyond our intelligence.
It's too hard.
This is what the second member will do.
The first player finished up with "2NE1".
Kung Kung Ta, One piece, Kung Kung Ta, Switzerland,
Kung Kung Ta, Stockings, Do three words in a row.
- That's so hard. - What does that mean?
(He doesn't understand the rules.)
You play word chain alone.
This is what the third player will do.
The last round ended with "Stockings", right?
Then name three movies with "King" in the title.
(That's what the 3rd player needs to do.)
(Name 3 movie titles that contain the last word of Round 2.)
- "Kingsman", "Kingdom". - This is really hard.
If the third player fails,
you go back to the first player.
This is so hard.
Apink. Apink.
Who knows a lot of movies?
I will do it.
I will do it with two members of Apink.
(He makes a decision alone.)
Then Ha Young and...
Did you hear Seok Jin? "I will do it."
"I will do it with two members of Apink."
Seok Jin, I am upset.
Seok Jin.
I am nervous.
Let's go. Ha Young, don't be down.
- I was thinking. - Don't think.
Get ready.
(I don't think.)
Let's see how they do it.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Get ready. Set, go.
(The given word is "This")
(This is the moment, this is the day)
(When I call my mom)
She is good.
(My heart hurts so much)
(The most precious)
"Han".
(It's time for "Kung Kung Ta".)
(Seok Jin needs to come up with 3 words for word chain.)
Hannibal, Kung Kung Ta, Foot odor, Kung Kung Ta
Saetaeryeong
"Ryeong".
- "Ryeong". - "Ryeong".
(In 10 seconds, she needs to name 3 movies titles...)
- "Young" works as well. - "Ryeong".
(which contain either "Ryeong" or "Young".)
"Dead Friend 1, 2, and 3".
"Dead Friend One".
(Ha Young begins.)
- "0.0MHz". - "0.0MHz".
(Ha Young goes over the set time.)
"Ryeong" was a good one.
- Keep going. - Go again.
- Ha Young won't do. - I want to try it.
Okay.
- "Ki". - You can go second.
I will go third.
(When the train moves through the darkness)
There you go.
(And crosses over Milky Way)
(Sunlight falls at the space station.)
(Edelweiss, edelweiss)
- "S". - "S".
(They need to list 3 words in word chain.)
Switzerland, Kung Kung Ta
Sri Lanka, Kung Kung Ta
- No! - Cho Rong! It's three syllables.
(She fails since her chosen word went over three syllables.)
- Cho Rong. - Three syllables.
Three syllables, don't you remember?
- What? - Keep going.
"Look". "Look".
- Didn't you know? - "Look".
Look at me, look at me
Look at me
So
- So - Sotseokung, Sotseokung
Sotseokung, Sotseokung
If you win, can you change a team member?
- Seok Jin is working very hard. - Seok Jin is working very hard.
My love who left said that he will return
- Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta
- Yogurt, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta
- "Re" - Re...
Rare car, Kung Kung Ta
(Rare car?)
(She fails Kung Kung Ta.)
She should've come up with an easy one.
There's ready-mix concrete.
She's so obstinate.
- Eun Ji did a good job. - Good job.
I can't seem to think here.
I can't think.
Even if you can't think,
Cho Rong was so careless.
How can she say "rare car"?
She follows the flow of her consciousness.
For my team,
So Min will play.
- Yu Il knows many movies. - Yu Il.
- Yu Il will play. - He knows lots of movies.
(Yu Il, a fan of movies, joins.)
Here's Yu Il who is very ordinary.
He's the ordinary himself.
In general,
after spending time with SORAN,
I noticed that they're quiet.
(They're quiet.)
(They aren't noisy at all.)
They don't talk.
If I don't ask questions...
None of them talk if I don't ask them questions.
(We never heard their voice.)
Let's start.
- Get ready. - You got this.
Start.
I'll give you everything
Hey, everyone
That was good.
(Next is Kung Kung Ta.)
Children, perilla oil.
Hum, hum, hum.
("Hum, hum, hum"?)
(Is she humming?)
Let me do it again.
What's "hum, hum, hum"?
She's the problem.
She's the problem now.
- She isn't working hard. - She's the problem.
Why is she changing places?
Don't get it right.
(So Min decides to name movie titles.)
"La".
The fragrance of lilacs
A train runs through the darkness
- "Go". - Through the darkness
(It's time to play Kung Kung Ta with "go".)
That's good.
- Ko Young Bae. - Kung Kung Ta
- Bae Cheol Soo - Kung Kung Ta
- Swimming pool - Kung Kung Ta
It's "jang".
(Last is Naming Movie Titles.)
"Jang" is easy.
(She must name 3 movie titles with "jang" in them.)
The third player has to name three movie titles.
(What movie titles are there with "jang" in them?)
"Mother-in-law".
("Mother-in-law")
(What?)
- Come on, So Min. - "Mosquito Net".
Wait.
- "Mosquito Net". - Come on, So Min.
No, wait.
There's nothing with "jang" in it.
There is "The General's Son".
The time is up.
(Team SORAN fails.)
I'm not sure if this is a good thing.
I'm not sure.
- Let's go. - Okay.
It'll be easy.
This team is small.
It'll be a good team if you kick out one member.
(He speaks vaguely.)
We won't change members, will we?
- Of course not. - Really?
"We won't change members, will we"?
He asked if they'll change members.
We definitely won't change.
- Let's start. - Okay.
- Okay. - Get ready.
- We can do it. - Set.
- Go. - "Bo"?
"Bo"?
- Like purple color - That's right.
She's good. She sings right away.
It approached me lightly
At this moment
She's good.
(He has to say three words starting with "gan".)
- "Gan". - "Gan"?
Flag stop, Kung Kung Ta
Post horse...
What? Why is it so difficult?
- Post horse... - Stagecoach.
- Can we play again? - Yeoksam-dong.
- Yeoksam-dong. - Yeoksam-dong.
- Don't you want to play? - Knotweeds.
There's Yeoksam-dong.
- That was... - Let's go again.
- No. - You aren't working hard.
("Ga")
- Are you really leaving? - They almost made it.
Singing, singing, mambo
- She can sing anything. - Gummy is very good.
- Boiler - Kung Kung Ta
- Russia - Kung Kung Ta
(They might succeed.)
- Mister - Kung Kung Ta
- "Ssi". - Kwang Soo.
"The Surrogate Woman".
- "The Surrogate Woman"? - "The Surrogate Woman".
(Mumbling)
(Kang Soo Yeon won Best Actress at the Venice Film Festival...)
(for her role in this movie.)
- "The Surrogate Woman". - "The Surrogate Woman".
- "The Man from Nowhere". - "The Man from Nowhere".
"The Handmaiden".
- "The Handmaiden". - "The Hand"...
- "The Handmaiden". - "The Handmaiden".
(They succeed.)
We got it.
(Team Gummy clears the mission.)
There was "The Handmaiden".
Who said "The Handmaiden"?
- Why, Ha Young? - Ha Young.
- Why did you tell them? - I wanted to swap.
- I thought we could swap. - To swap?
- To swap? - That's smart.
I thought that they'd swap with us.
They got it.
It's the only team that was successful.
(Team Gummy wins a chance to swap team members.)
They won a chance to get rid of a member whom they dislike.
(They won a chance to get rid of a member whom they dislike.)
(Does he have to talk in a mean way?)
To determine the second place, you'll play Kung Kung Ta.
- Okay. - After repeating "Kung Kung Ta",
name a food item for the last word.
The last word should be a food item.
Do you understand?
You can't repeat any words.
- You win after playing two rounds. - Okay.
Do we name food items?
Nucksal and Code Kunst.
- Ji Hyo should play. - Come on, guys.
1, 2, 3, 4.
- Kungs, Kungs, Kungs - Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
- Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
- Raccoon, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta
- Handcart, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta
Car service center, Kung Kung Ta
Udon sold at terminals.
No.
(Udon sold at terminals?)
Why not?
That doesn't work.
Udon at terminals is the best.
Isn't it correct?
It cannot be accepted.
You're done.
Code Kunst has never done it before.
We haven't either.
(Look at my team first.)
We've never played this before either.
- We've never done it before. - Haha is angry.
Apink members, please come out.
(We understand you.)
Se Chan will play this.
(Team Apink gives a try.)
- Let's go. - We can do it.
Let's drive him out.
(Let's drive him out.)
Let's get it right and drive him out.
Let's take out the old stone.
(Is he talking about me?)
(The old stone)
Push him out.
(They're talking about me.)
Get ready.
- Here we go. - Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
- Kungs, Kungs, Kungs - Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
- Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
(The given syllable is "si".)
Inquisitive...
(A four-syllable word?)
"Si"?
(Where did "inquisitive" come from?)
- What's wrong with him? - Hey.
What starts with "si"?
- Spinach. - Time difference.
- Change places with Na Eun. - Change.
I'm sorry.
Did you see that? Who's better?
- Let's go, Se Chan. - I can do it.
(There's only one goal.)
(His feelings get hurt again.)
(Hang in there, Seok Jin.)
I did better than him.
Do it slowly.
Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta
Let's start.
- Kungs, Kungs, Kungs - Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
(Do it very slowly.)
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
("Seo")
Western food.
What are you doing?
(Are they playing that slowly?)
Epicurism.
Clorox container.
(She has to name a food item that starts with "tong".)
(What will be Nam Joo's response?)
Tong rice.
(Tong rice)
(What's that?)
What is that?
(What's wrong with her?)
It exists.
It's rice in a container.
There's rice in bamboo.
Rice in bamboo exists,
but there's no "Tong Rice".
- It can say anything at this rate. - Right?
They're good.
Myun Ho and Tae Wook are next.
As you can see,
they look like new hires.
(We introduce you to the new hires.)
(Welcome, new hires at Running Man in 2019)
(It looks like an orientation for new hires.)
It's their orientation.
I thought they were three referees.
They don't look like musicians at all.
Please say something.
Say something.
These three don't...
jeer at you.
Neither do they cheer for the team.
Three of you.
You should change places.
Wait. Myun Ho should sit there.
(They're changing their seats.)
(They're moving fast.)
The way that they change seats is quite systematic too.
Did you change seats?
Wait, did you change seats?
- It doesn't seem like it. - It looks the same.
Did you change?
Did they change seats?
Did you?
Wait, they didn't change.
Jae Seok is in the same place.
We changed our seats.
- We changed our seats. - Did you?
Myun Ho changed his seat.
(They really changed seats.)
It's because...
we look quite ordinary.
We look familiar.
- They did change. - We did.
Here we go. Start.
- Kungs, Kungs, Kungs - Kungs, Kungs, Kungs
- Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
Minnow.
Handcart.
- Car repair shop. - That's right.
(Minnow, handcart, car repair shop)
Turkish ice cream.
- They have one more round. - Im Chang Jung.
Im Chang Jung.
Jeongbalsan.
San...
(San...)
(Fail)
You should have said it.
- Foot of a mountain. - That was close.
We almost had it. Come back in.
- You could have said... - Did you see them?
They don't complain.
They come back right away.
(Good job, new hires.)
What should we do?
Let's get started.
- What are you doing? - They're strategizing too much.
- What are you doing? - Code Kunst.
I'm explaining to them.
I asked them what they will say if I end with "teo".
He said, "Haha, there's market gukbap."
(He said, "There's market gukbap.")
"Market gukbap"?
That's how we are.
We can't help it.
It's okay.
It should start with "teo".
They should know the rules by now.
- Let's go. - Is Code Kunst the last?
You can do it.
You'll be amazed.
He said that he'll amaze us.
Okay, we look forward to it.
- It'll be amazing how I end it. - Okay.
Let's believe him.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(Will Code Kunst end it with a grand finale?)
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
Sunrise.
- Okay. - Lee Myun Soo.
- Okay. - Soo...
(Lee Myun Soo is wrong.)
("Lee Myun Soo"?)
- It's Lim Yeon Soo. - It's Lim.
(It's Lim, not Lee.)
- Is it Lim Yeon Soo? - He's not educated either.
- Go easy on him. - He always does that.
He doesn't know.
- Do it twice. - Why am I so nervous?
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
("Ma")
- Magma. - Kung Kung Ta
Magma, Kung Kung Ta
You can't repeat words.
(They said that no words can be repeated.)
He doesn't know the rules yet.
I won't play with you.
(I won't play with you.)
Code Kunst practiced a lot.
(He couldn't say a word.)
What are you doing?
- He doesn't know the rules. - What are you doing, Nucksal?
- I was ready to end it well. - Go back in.
Go back in for now.
- Let's start. - Start.
(Kung Kung Ta Ri, Kungs Kungs?)
(What kind of tempo is this?)
What did you just say?
What's "Kung Kung Ta Ri, Kungs"?
(She's never heard of such a tempo.)
Ha Young, smile a little.
(She's so serious.)
We have to win.
(He's the reason why Team Apink must win.)
Ha Young looks so serious.
(They start Kung Kung Ta again.)
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
Happiness house.
What?
(What?)
(What kind of house?)
(What's wrong with me today?)
"Happiness"?
(That's terrible.)
Come back in.
- Come back in. I'm sorry, Ha Young. - Give me one more chance.
- One more chance. - Go back in. I'm sorry.
- Give me one more chance. - We don't have time.
You succeed if you finish one round.
(Team Nucksal and Code Kunst give it a try.)
(The syllable is "Ma".)
Majang-dong.
Dongjak Station.
Station employee.
(Fail)
- Mother. - Kung Kung Ta
- Handcart. - Kung Kung Ta
- Carnival. - Kung Kung Ta
Foot smell.
(Fail)
Okay.
I'll work hard and stay on Team Apink.
Here we go.
- Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
Seaweed soup.
Soup bowl.
Balsamic.
(Seaweed soup, soup bowl, balsamic)
Seek weed soup.
(Fail)
(What is "seek weed soup"?)
(Poor Team Apink.)
How many mistakes is she making?
(Can we please win?)
- She wants to keep me on the team. - We'll give you one more chance.
- You got one more chance. - Thank you.
- All right, we can do it. - We can do it.
- We can do it. - Start with Kungs, Kungs.
(They concentrate and try again.)
- Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta - Kung Kung Ta, Kung Kung Ta
- Name a food item at the end - Name a food item at the end
First lady.
Insa-dong.
(First lady, Insa-dong)
Dongchimi.
(If she makes it, they place second.)
(Will they win this time?)
Seaweed soup.
(Seaweed soup)
(They succeed.)
(They finally did it.)
- You shouldn't be happy. - No, they won't.
They won't betray us.
- That was great. - We worked hard.
The winning team, please come out.
- You did a good job. - Do we come out?
(It's time to swap members.)
We were so close.
Take your time to discuss and show us your card.
We'll announce now.
Do we not swap if we give the same card?
If you give the same card, there won't be any changes.
(If the cards are the same, the teams remain the same.)
It will depend on the minority card.
The one with the minority card gets to decide.
- Will you keep the same team? - Yes.
- Do you promise? - I don't want to swap with anyone.
- Me neither. What about you? - Me neither.
I want us to become the perfect team.
I'm worried.
- I promise. There's no one. - Me neither.
- It's this one. - Okay.
- Okay. - This one.
You saw it, right? Don't be confused.
We can't get mixed up.
- All right. - All right.
1, 2.
(Will they show the same card as they promised?)
Three.
(Both Jong Kook and Kwang Soo pick Change Both card.)
(What did Gummy choose?)
- Are we the same? - All three have the same card.
Okay.
(All three of them picked Change Both card.)
I was so startled.
What?
(What's wrong with him?)
Is this the wrong one?
You startled me.
I thought that you changed it.
(I was worried that you changed your card.)
Did you pick this?
Did you pick this card?
- I see. - I would've been disappointed.
(Team Gummy remains unchanged.)
I thought you picked the white one.
They have many obstacles to overcome.
Team in second place, please come out.
Let's not discuss and think instead.
If you think carefully...
If I think carefully, I can stay on the same team.
- It's possible. - How do I dance to...
Apink's songs?
(Behind Seok Jin who was getting ahead of himself)
We're discussing without him.
Join us.
What are you doing?
It just happened that way.
(He's very disappointed.)
As we were discussing,
it just happened.
Don't discuss. Just do it.
I'll pick just any card.
Leave it up to luck. Pick whichever card.
- "Pick whichever card"? - That's interesting.
We're ready.
(Which side will luck be on?)
1, 2.
(Will Seok Jin rest or will Apink send him away?)
Three.
(What's the result?)
(1 Change Both and 2 Change One)
Both of them picked the same.
(Team Apink will change both.)
(It's a big twist.)
(Am I being swapped too?)
In this case, Seok Jin and Se Chan will...
join a different team.
- In this case... - You should stay with Apink.
Can't I change it?
Both of you will be swapped.
- Both of you have to leave. - Both of you have to leave.
- Seok Jin has to leave. - I have to leave?
- You have to. - Why did I pick this card?
(Why did I pick this card?)
(I thought I wouldn't be swapped.)
You should explain better.
The final result is the minority card.
I don't want to join this team.
If I stand among them,
I might become ordinary too. I can't join them.
(He's afraid of becoming ordinary.)
If I join their team,
no one will recognize me. I want to avoid that team.
- You join this team. - Stop it.
(Se Chan is perfect for the team.)
- Stop it, Seok Jin. - Join this team.
You won't find me if I join them.
- Join this team. - Seok Jin.
Whom do you choose?
Either me or So Min has to join your team.
So Min is a woman.
- Okay. - Jae Seok should join.
Me? Okay.
(Se Chan joins Team SORAN.)
(Jae Seok joins Team Apink.)
(Jae Seok is joining us.)
I'm glad that I'm leaving before they grew on me.
Look how polite they are.
Since I'm leaving, they came to walk me out.
- Goodness. - They're saying hello.
They came out to see him.
Se Chan is a good fit.
Take off your cap.
Goodness.
Who's who?
- Who's who? - Who's who?
Here you go.
Code Kunst is looking away...
and ignoring Seok Jin the most.
- Hey. - He's looking away.
Come out, Haha.
(He picks Haha.)
I'll join this team.
I'll join the hip-hop team.
(Here comes MC Seok Jin.)
(Welcome, Haha.)
No.
Don't leave. I'll join you again.
- Stay there temporarily. - Haha, stay there temporarily.
Seriously.
Our team members are the best.
No way.
Apink members look so happy.
(What will be the final teams?)
We're leaving.
(Joint race isn't over yet.)
(They fight to join members that they want.)
(Wavering bodies and teamwork)
(Four teams are in confusion.)
(I'll fall in the water.)
(Some team members don't know the rules.)
(It's good to play without knowing the rules.)
(Those who try to defend their team no matter what...)
(fight with those who try to leave the team.)
(What will be the final teams?)
(My Partner is Faraway on Running Man)