(The Year of the Golden Pig)
(It unfolds at a traditional house where the tradition is evident.)
- Soon, it will be... - Yes?
- the Lunar New Year. - That's right.
- We must offer our greetings. - Yes.
It's 2019, the Year of the Golden Pig.
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
(Why are they bowing down all of a sudden?)
- Hold on. - Give us a heads-up.
- Goodness, come on. Seriously. - Okay.
- Happy New Year. - He caught us off guard.
- This is at last... - Come on.
- Seok Jin's year. He's 54. - Right.
- It's started. - 54. Bring in happiness and luck.
(Acting silly)
He's in a good mood today.
- I think he'll get tired easily. - Hey, this was nothing.
I think he'll get tired easily.
- He's already tired. - He's tired.
Right now, Haha caught a cold.
- Right. Goodness. Poor him. - He's not in good health.
- It's my fault. I wasn't careful. - Really?
I was really worried as soon as I got here.
That's why Jong Kook is standing far from him.
- That's not it. - Usually...
(Is it because he might catch it too?)
- That's not it. - Usually, he's right next to Haha.
When Haha came into the room this morning,
he went, "Poor you. You caught a cold."
- "Are you okay?" - No, no.
When I said we should work hard, he just gently tapped my fist.
- That disappointed me. - He doesn't want to catch a cold.
It's been a while since we wore these traditional clothes.
- It really has been a while. - That's right.
It's been a while since I saw you in the traditional dress.
- It's been a while. - Yes.
Did you two fight? Why aren't you standing together?
(Did you two fight? Why aren't you standing together?)
(Standing far)
- They're cooling off on purpose. - From Jong Kook.
- This is done on purpose? - They must take it slow.
She's Jong Kook's first love interest on our show,
- Jong Kook is her second. - That's right.
That's not a bad thing. It's not.
- Ji Hyo... - Jong Kook.
Jong Kook was on our show even before that happened.
Ji Hyo has to be a bit careful. She needs to be careful.
Her previous love interest...
- got married. - Yes, that's right.
It's all neat. It is.
- But we must congratulate. - This is amazing.
We should definitely congratulate them.
Listen. Say that you pair up with a lady.
Are you nice to them or not?
- I'm nice to them. - I must obviously take care of her.
Whenever I do something,
- you go all like this. - You act tough, but you're gentle.
(You're so coy.)
(Everything ends with Jong Kook and Ji Hyo's love interest.)
Love is power. Love is power.
- Hold her hand! - Hold her hand!
- Hold her hand! - He'll hit you.
- He's a loving giraffe. - You won't hold hands?
- I'll keep an eye on you. - Come on, Kwang Soo.
- He wants everyone to be in love. - He's so interested in love.
Today's special is for the Lunar New Year.
Four special guests have come to our show.
- Really? - Who are they?
Are they coming out?
What's going on? Look.
I can't believe this.
- My goodness. - It's been a while.
- She's pretty. - Goodness.
- What's going on? - Goodness.
Il Woo. A Ra.
- My gosh, she's pretty! - I can't believe this.
- Kwon Yul and Park Hoon are here. - Unbelievable.
- This is like a painting. - Goodness.
I am that lowly prince.
(It's life story of Yeongjo, )
(a son of a lowly maid becoming the king.)
(The drama, "Haechi" will premier on February 11.)
- Hello. - Hi.
- A Ra. Long time no see. - Goodness.
- Have you been well? - Hello, A Ra.
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
- Long time no see. - Happy New Year.
- Hello. - Happy New Year.
They look great in traditional outfits.
- They look great in these outfits. - They look really nice.
- They look great in these. - Exactly.
- I agree. I agree. - The upper garment looks pretty.
I would like the four of you to say hello to our viewers.
- Hello. - Okay.
- I haven't been here for a while. - It's been a while.
(The queen of beauty, Go A Ra)
Give it back!
(Behind her beautiful looks, she has unexpected charms.)
(This beautiful lady ruled the show with all of her hidden talents.)
A Ra has been in the entertainment industry for 17 years.
- 17 years? - It's been so long.
- You're surprised too. - I didn't know either.
- You've had many roles so far. - Right.
Is there a role you'd like to try out?
- I want to do one with romance. - Romance.
Your roles have never been in love?
- You've never had those roles? - You've done it before.
- Really? - You had a lot of those roles.
- You had a lot of those roles. - I want passionate romance.
I see.
(That's a great genre.)
- Like having a lot of kiss scenes? - Passionate romance.
What about passionate romance?
I'm Zo In Sung's fan.
(That came out of nowhere.)
- Why is she saying that now here? - What's going on?
(She's revealing her support all of a sudden.)
- You're his fan? - I would like to do the project...
- with him. - With In Sung?
- I would love to do it with him. - By the way,
from Il Woo's point of view,
even if you disguise as a man in the drama,
- he would've been offended. - I mean...
- The romance... - Really.
Even before the drama airs, you showed your support for In Sung.
(And as for the passionate romance...)
Actually, an actress from our show is in passionate romance now.
- It's Jong Kook and Ji Hyo. - It's happening now.
No, no. Not at all. It's not true.
- It's Jong Kook and Ji Hyo. - This is completely not true.
They started talking about this only since yesterday.
It's not true?
- Isn't this romantic comedy? - Kwang Soo...
Il Woo, please say hello to our viewers.
- It's been so long, Il Woo. - How long has it been?
Right. After I got discharged from the military,
Running Man is my first variety show.
- Nice to see you. - That's great.
(He has a 100 percent accuracy in winning over women's hearts.)
Put it in. Put it in there.
(With his fierce competitiveness, he won all of the games as well.)
- Great. - That's it.
(His competitiveness was evident in Dubai too.)
(This manly guy takes it to the end when he starts something.)
Hello, I'm Jung Il Woo.
Congratulations on your discharge.
All right. Tell us how you think. Is this your first time...
- working with A Ra? - Yes, that's right.
After working with her, what kind of actress do you think she is?
- A Ra? - Describe her in three words.
Go ahead.
- Go A Ra is... - Go A Ra is?
- A Ra is... - A Ra is?
- Your time is up. - Okay.
Is this it?
(Is this it?)
- All right. - Fine.
There are a lot he could've said. "Cute, pretty, and kind".
Is this it?
(Sorry, I couldn't think of anything.)
Describe Il Woo from your point of view in three-syllable words.
- 1, 2, 3. - He's good-looking.
He's good-looking?
(To her, he's good-looking.)
- Three. - He's good-looking.
(Yes, you are my love interest in the drama.)
What about In Sung?
I love you.
(Her love for him doesn't falter.)
That was perfect. It worked perfectly.
- "I love you." - That had three syllables. Perfect.
- It was perfect. - It was perfect.
All of a sudden, I feel like crying.
Look at his face. Hey.
- Look at his face. - Right now...
- This is passionate romance. - That was perfect.
You star in a lot of historical dramas.
Yes, this is my fourth one.
- This genre suits you well. - I agree.
What are charms of the historical dramas unlike modern-day dramas?
We wear traditional clothes instead of modern-day clothes.
And these clothes are comfortable.
- They are comfortable? Really? - You wear traditional clothes.
In winter, I can layer up a lot of clothes.
I can wear about seven long johns underneath.
If so, why are you wearing dressy shoes? You're the only one.
(If so, why are you wearing dressy shoes? You're the only one.)
- You were trying to look cool. - Hey.
- Was it because it's uncomfortable? - Hey.
Hey, he's trying to look cool.
- I mean, listen. - Hey.
No, he didn't wear them to look cool.
- Will you make him cry today? - No.
- I wondered if it's uncomfortable. - He's already having a hard time.
- I thought he meant something else. - He's trying to look cool.
- Because of A Ra... - Everyone else wore the same shoes.
That style is from the late era of Joseon Dynasty.
- We're wearing traditional ones. - No, it's like...
- His is from the late era. - He looks like a butcher.
His outfit is from the late era of Joseon Dynasty.
- I'm about to lose it. - What's wrong with him?
Il Woo just said that he's about to lose it.
- He's attacked. - He's lost it.
- He's attacked at full force. - Yes, he was.
We'll stop interviewing Il Woo.
- Will we stop here? - Yes, we will.
We will stop interviewing Il Woo for the time being.
We'll leave him in this state?
- Next guest is Kwon Yul. - Kwon Yul.
- He looks so cool. - He's the general.
(Good-looking guy with many charms, Kwon Yul)
(With his prince-like look, he releases all of his manly sides.)
(He was all over the place when he was on our show 3 years ago.)
(His unexpected charms threw the members into a frenzy.)
- Nice to see you. I'm Kwon Yul. - Nice to see you.
- Kwon Yul. His name is so cool. - He's so cool.
He has a name of a general.
Has it been three years for you too since the last time?
(He's clapping all of a sudden by himself.)
Gosh, what is this?
(He's unpredictable.)
Tell you what.
- I read this about Yul. - Okay.
He has gone viral with his sweet voice...
- and great singing skills. - Really?
Then could you sing us a song?
That was sudden.
- Let's hear you sing. - My gosh.
He has a low-pitched voice.
(If you want me to sing, I'll sing.)
I'll sing Yoo Jae Ha's song.
- Great. - Goodness.
I love his songs.
- "Myself Reflected in My Heart". - "Myself Reflected in My Heart".
I love that song.
(It's as if he prepared to sing.)
(Pieces of dreams I cannot hold onto)
- He has a great voice. - His voice sounds great.
They disappear one by one
(Getting into the song by himself)
I keep getting lost without an end
(Puzzled)
(Everyone starts singing.)
(Everyone is getting into the rhythm. This looks like...)
It's "Challenge 1000 Songs" ' Lunar New Year Special.
(Reply "Challenge 1000 Songs")
- Yes, it's really nice. - The unfinished part
(It's nice and all, )
(but until when will he sing?)
(He finishes the song after enjoying it alone.)
He's great.
- Actually, he has a great voice. - He has a great voice.
He has such a great voice.
- His voice is pleasing to hear. - That's right.
What did you say?
Be honest. You weren't sure earlier.
- You didn't look impressed. - This is what you did.
This is what Kwang Soo did, facing me.
(Holding down his laughter)
- That's what you did. - You tilted your head.
It's not that. No.
(Tilting his head)
(I can't tell if he's good or not for sure.)
You tilted your head.
- It's not that. He's very good, - You did that.
but I must've had high expectations.
- If you're singing for everyone... - That's right.
- I thought he'd be an opera singer. - I get what you mean.
- I thought he'd sing like this. - Be quiet.
- It didn't reach my expectations. - Be quiet.
- That's right. - Be quiet.
(Kwang Soo had high expectations, and he was overly sentimental.)
When I was singing it, I wasn't sure either.
(Tilting his head)
I've never seen someone sing as long as he did.
- People usually sing the hook. - Seriously.
- He sang from the start. - He said he'd sing only one line.
- He sang the whole verse. - He sang the first verse.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes, the song healed me.
(I'm healed after listening to his singing.)
(His medicinal voice can cure colds.)
This is his first time on Running Man.
- Park Hoon. - Yes.
- Please say hello. - Okay.
Hello. I...
Nice to meet you. I am...
here to promote the SBS drama, "Haechi".
- You can't be shy on variety shows. - Is that so?
(Coaching how to be on variety shows)
- He's shy. - You have to be louder.
- That's all right. - My heart is about to explode.
(The most charismatic actor, Park Hoon)
(He's the formula for successful dramas such as...)
("Descendants of the Sun" and "Memories of the Alhambra".)
(His charismatic acting performance has no boundaries.)
Hello, I'm Actor Park Hoon.
Park Hoon.
- He has a cool name. - He has a great voice.
It was one of those names I wanted when I was young.
- Hoon. - Hoon.
- Kim Hoon. - Hoon.
His name has just one syllable.
I really like names like his.
- That's why your nickname is Hyuk. - You have a nickname, Hyuk.
- I'm Hyuk. Hoon. - He's also known as Hyuk.
- I like names like yours. - That's right.
- I love your name. - Me too. Hoon.
I heard that Hoon's role in the drama...
is a beggar.
- I'm a beggar. - A beggar?
If I were to put it in a playful way,
I'm the king of the streets.
It's a story how everyone becomes kings in their places.
To borrow today's terms, I would be an influential blogger.
(To borrow today's terms, I would be an influential blogger.)
- That's right. - That was amazing.
- He shapes the public opinion. - I get it.
- Back in the days, - He's right.
- he would circulate stories. - That's it.
He is right.
That's my role.
(This newbie on variety shows is witty.)
- Hoon has such a likable face. - I agree.
- In what ways? - What?
He has kind eyes.
- I've seen you before. - Where?
(I've seen you before.)
- It has started. - Here we go again.
- Someone saw Seok Jin again. - He can't remember again.
- Really? - Yes.
- When? Where did you see him? - I saw him once.
- This is my first time seeing him. - Where was that?
We probably ran into one another.
- No, no. - When did we meet?
- I was on your radio show once. - My goodness.
(I was on your radio show once.)
- My goodness. - It's his radio show again?
- You were on my radio show? - Yes.
It's his radio show again?
I got the goosebumps.
- This is fascinating. - He was on the show with Jong Hyuk.
- That explains. I know you. - Right.
You're a musical actor.
No, no. I'm a theater actor.
(That's incorrect!)
You're a musical actor.
No, no. I'm a theater actor.
(We're looking for his memories which has disappeared.)
- He keeps getting it wrong. - A theater actor.
(He is the victim of Seok Jin's bad memories.)
He's very famous theater actor.
He keeps getting it wrong.
- He keeps forgetting. - This never ends.
- You gave me your number too. - He gave you his number?
- Really? - You said I should call you up.
- I... - I called you after we finished.
I only give out my number to people I really like.
I gave it out only to a handful of people.
That doesn't matter. He doesn't remember.
- Are you from Jeongseon? - Yes.
- My goodness. - He's also from Jeongseon.
(Nice to meet you, my fellow hometown friend.)
That must have been why he gave you his number.
You're also from Jeongseon.
You talked about it on the radio show.
(He stubbornly exposes Seok Jin for the 2nd time.)
(Everything that happened today had happened that day.)
We already talked about it.
- You were born in Yeongwol, right? - This is unbelievable.
You were born in Yeongwol.
After listening to everything,
I can tell why he got Seok Jin's number.
- They were from the same place. - Right.
It was because he was from Jeongseon.
- But he thought... - We talked about it on the show.
- he had never seen Hoon before. - He didn't recognize Hoon.
He kept saying how he had kinds eyes.
He said that Hoon had kind eyes. This is unbelievable.
It was my first time meeting such a big celebrity like him.
- What's going on lately? - He's another Seok Jin's fan.
- Listen. - Remember Dong Hwi?
- He was my fan too. - Seok Jin has a lot of male fans...
- from the entertainment industry. - He's a celebrity of celebrities.
- We've met too, Jae Seok. - Hey.
(Another scandalous remark)
(This newbie keeps on exposing people.)
He even met Jae Seok?
- No one remembers him. - My goodness.
I usually remember people.
- Jae Seok and I... - When did we meet?
It was when Jung Jun Ha was on a musical.
I was in the musical with him.
- I see. You were in the play. - Yes.
You were in the play.
After meeting him that day,
- he left a strong impression on me. - Why?
- Why? - Did he do something good again?
- A lot of people came for Jun Ha. - That's right.
We were all nervous because we heard that he was here.
We were waiting for Jae Seok,
but he didn't come.
We were wondering what was taking him long.
When I went out of the room,
he was saying hello to every single staff member.
He went all the way to the back and said he enjoyed the show.
He's being nosy. What would he do that?
Why would he say hello to the staff of someone else's show?
That's being nosy.
Why would he say hi to the staff of a show he wasn't on?
You should have met up with the actors.
Goodness.
- I can't understand him. - He's nervous about...
- good stories about Jae Seok. - Goodness, Hoon.
You were in the show with Jun Ha.
I remember that now.
Great. We finished interviewing Hoon now.
- Hoon. - Yes?
Since you were in a musical, could you sing us a song?
- From the musical? - Yes.
Assessing from the aura he's exuding,
- I think he has a powerful voice. - I agree.
Please sing us a snippet.
(How will his 1st song on his 1st variety show sound?)
(Clearing his throat)
Thank you
Father
I'm sorry.
(Shouting out for the priest in the middle of a variety show)
- I'm sorry. - He's asking for the priest.
- That was too religious, right? - That was religious.
What was that? Was that a hymn?
- I got shy when I was singing it. - A hymn?
- Was that a hymn? - Which song is that?
- I'm sorry. When I was singing it, - Excuse me.
- it was too religious. I shouldn't. - He asked for the priest.
- My goodness. - I'll sing a different song.
When I was singing the song,
- the song didn't suit the location. - You can sing religious songs.
- Father as for the priest? - Yes, exactly.
- When I was singing it, - Could you...
- I startled myself. - sing a song we know?
I shouldn't have sung this song.
- Let's try again. - Okay.
(He tries to sing again.)
(From the musical, "All the Brothers were Valiant")
("Crying")
He's good.
(They're impressed.)
I'll stop here.
(He sings a short and powerful snippet.)
- I can't sing it anymore. - He's very good.
This is how people usually sing when we ask.
They sing a short snippet.
No one sings the whole verse like he did.
I've never heard of a song without a pause.
Please give a round of applause to these four guests.
That was great.
- I can't wait for their drama. - They're fun.
Today,
- it's the Lunar New Year Special. - Okay.
You can only win when you find the true king...
and when the king sits on the throne.
The race is called Will You Be the King or Nobody?
(Will You Be the King or Nobody?)
The candidates who can be the king are...
Seok Jin, So Min, and Il Woo because last names all start with J.
Hello.
(Preliminary meeting before filming)
All three of you...
are candidates to become the king as your last names start with J.
One of you is the real king.
And the two of you are only pretenders.
We'll choose the real king by a random draw.
You will choose 1 of the 3 royal seals.
You will stamp the seal,
and if it says, "king", you will be the king.
If it says, "nobody", then you will be pretenders.
(Pretenders)
(They start the draw to select the king.)
Wouldn't the older-looking one be the real one?
I will go with this one.
(The identity of the king has been chosen randomly.)
Please! Please.
Let me be the king.
(Which one of them will be the real king?)
Today's race is a team match, and the three of you will...
form your own teams.
The king with the most number of civilians will take the throne.
And if the real king takes the throne,
the king's team will win the race.
The king and the civilians will win a prize.
If the pretender takes the throne, it will be the pretender's victory.
The rest of you will face the penalty.
Before we begin today's race, you will divide into teams.
The maximum number of people...
in each team is four including the king.
You can choose the king you want to follow.
We'll be choosing the team.
I like that we get to choose our team.
Everyone, line up.
You have to pick the right line.
Seok Jin, definitely.
Welcome, Haha.
Why is it only girls behind Il Woo?
Why did so many choose Seok Jin?
This is not a popularity contest.
There was no one here.
- There was no one. - This is not a popularity contest.
Is this a popularity contest?
So Min, you're a king. Come here.
(I want to be Il Woo's civilian.)
- You're a king. - I don't want to be.
I don't want to be a king.
Look at that. Do you know why they all chose Seok Jin?
It's because he looks easy.
There will be a coup.
The king looks so easy.
- That's why... - It's affecting me.
It's bothering me.
To help the kings to decide, this is who has the face...
of a traitor.
"The face of a traitor"?
- I know already. - Okay.
But we already know.
- Kwang Soo. - We already know.
No. There is nothing wrong with my face.
- Who is it? - It's the most likely one.
Isn't it Kwang Soo?
- I don't look like a traitor. - It must be Kwang Soo.
The person who has the face of a traitor.
Kim Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
- Jong Kook! - It gave me goosebumps.
(The result surprises everyone.)
- Me? - Unbelievable.
- It gave me goosebumps. - Me?
"His high cheekbones and strong jaw indicate..."
"that he cannot stand dirty work."
(Jong Kook's face analysis)
"He is highly likely to stage a coup."
- Oh, my. - "The more you try to oppress him,"
"the more determined he will be..."
- That's right. - "to overcome it."
- That's right. - He rebels.
Kim Jong Kook, how impertinent of you.
Go away!
- Me? - He has the face of a traitor.
(Seok Jin decides to kick Jong Kook out.)
I have to get rid of him in the beginning.
He doesn't sound like a king at all.
Go away right now!
"Me?"
How dare you speak to the king that way?
You're not my king.
(He speaks his mind.)
- You're not even my king. - It's a coup.
You're others' king.
- I don't care about you. - "Others' king".
- That king is over now. - He is over.
His whole country is over.
What's that?
(What is the first step to finding the real king?)
What's that? It's my face.
The first step towards finding the real king,
King Son Byung Ho.
- What's that? - "Fold a finger."
(It's a game of folding fingers.)
The three teams and the staff...
will take turns in asking questions.
If any member's answer is "yes",
the team has to put down the picture of the king.
The winning team will receive...
a hint, a treason right, and a recruitment right.
All three?
That's generous.
We need more people, right?
- That's how we win. - We need to recruit more people.
We should ask a question first.
- That'd be better. - We should go first.
- Can we recruit a king too? - No.
(The civilian doesn't understand the rules yet.)
Don't say that.
- Can you go wash your face? - I'm your only king.
- Do you want to go wash your face? - I'm your king.
Go wash your face.
He seems to want to leave.
You can leave if you want.
Go ahead.
(Seok Jin's team will go first.)
- That one? - Yes.
Is that one good? Are you sure?
Of course.
(What is Seok Jin's team's first question?)
- It will kill everyone. - Okay.
- Then... - Okay.
- Let's go with that one. - Let's do that.
"While shooting a drama or something,"
"my heart has never fluttered..."
"because of a colleague."
Even if you don't like that person, your heart can flutter.
If your heart has ever fluttered... It's happened to me.
My heart flutters every day.
(Yul's heart flutters every day.)
Yul's heart flutters every day.
It's happened to me.
- I think this one will just pass. - Don't fold your finger.
No one will fold their fingers.
If your heart has never fluttered, fold your finger.
1, 2, 3.
(Will any of the pictures be put down?)
No one has folded their fingers? It's happened to everyone?
Everyone? It's happened to everyone.
My heart fluttered because of my wife.
I met my wife during a show.
You performed together?
For the first time...
- Your heart fluttered? - You felt something.
I thought, "Is this not just a show?"
(They met as an actor and an actress.)
(Park Hoon and Park Min Jung share their lives now.)
She is very beautiful.
- She is? - She is really beautiful.
I'm jealous.
(That's when my heart fluttered the most.)
That's amazing.
For you, it was your wife.
For Seok Jin, it was Yang Jung A.
You told me your heart fluttered.
Why...
(Seok Jin's heart fluttered because of Jung A?)
(What are you talking about?)
It's not like that.
Since then, you've been talking about "Flaming Youth".
(Haha is setting Seok Jin up.)
(Seok Jin will not be able to go home tonight.)
It's not like that. When my wife appeared on this show,
she was wearing bridal makeup.
(She made my heart flutter.)
It's Seok Jin's wife.
- Really? - Hi.
- She is beautiful. - She is gorgeous.
My heart skipped a beat. I was so excited.
You're lying.
(You're lying!)
- After the shooting, - Your attack was so clumsy.
he said his wife made him so uncomfortable.
I had no idea she was coming.
Suddenly...
Yul, what about you?
I shot "Let's Eat"...
with Seo Hyun Jin.
(The lovely actress, Seo Hyun Jin, made my heart flutter.)
I love her.
She made the viewers' hearts flutter too.
- We agree. - Everyone's heart fluttered.
She drives everyone crazy.
Right. She's so attractive.
Her charms make everyone's heart flutter.
So Min, what about you?
Well, most recently,
Kim Ji Suk made my heart flutter.
Doesn't Lee Sang Yeob appear too?
He didn't make your heart flutter?
He and I are a family.
(Sang Yeob and I are a family.)
In addition to Ji Suk, Gong Myoung as well.
- Myoung. - Gong Myoung.
(So Min approached Gong Myoung with her acrostic poem.)
(His puppy-like charm stole So Min's heart.)
- Gong Myoung... - When he appeared,
- she was completely... - She kept talking about him.
(Myoung, how are you doing?)
She's shy.
Ji Suk or Gong Myoung?
(Choose one.)
Well, Ji Suk or Gong Myoung?
1, 2...
They're completely different. Myoung is like a puppy,
and Ji Suk is sexy.
Ji Suk or Gong Myoung?
(Everyone is with her in this important choice.)
When will this air?
February 3.
Gong Myoung.
(Then I choose Gong Myoung.)
(Our drama will be over by then.)
Your drama will be over, right?
(That's a reasonable choice.)
- Gong Myoung. - Suddenly...
What about you?
- For me... - You didn't fold your finger.
Na Kyung Eun, of course.
(Manly)
How did it happen?
No one knew about it.
- We called her Ma Bong Chun. - We did.
You didn't know it was Kyung Eun?
- No. - We didn't.
How did you find out alone?
Because I loved her.
(Passionate Romance Warning)
- That's so cool. - "Because I loved her."
- That's so cool. - How manly.
(It makes everyone's heart flutter.)
"Because I loved her."
- "Because I loved her." - Because I loved her.
He's so manly.
Because I loved her.
What about you, Il Woo?
For me, it was A Ra.
I knew it.
(The interrogation begins.)
When did it start?
When we started shooting this drama.
Before, she was just a friend,
but she is a girl now?
If you didn't mean it that way, you have to fold your finger.
(A friend? A girl?)
Are there different ways?
(He wants to protect his king.)
Why are you picking a fight?
We're both civilians.
If he meant it that way, they'd be married by now.
You're helping him?
(Ji Hyo is suspected to trying to help Jong Kook.)
She's helping him.
She brought up marriage.
(You want it to show?)
I mean...
We're a team.
- I mean, your heart flutters... - You two... All right.
- Ji Hyo. - I'm curious.
Doesn't your heart flutter these days?
Be honest. You didn't fold your finger.
Ji Hyo's heart must have fluttered many times.
Did your heart flutter more when Gary was here?
- That... - Who is Gary?
(She has moved on completely.)
(Their supporters are excited.)
- Okay. - Hold your hands!
Gary has left.
Why would I have feelings left for him?
- Hold your hands! - Hold your hands!
- Okay, good. - A girl's heart...
Okay, good.
So everyone proved it.
Everyone proved it.
- Is it our turn now? - Yes.
We should...
What kind of question will we be able to escape from?
(What will So Min's team ask?)
- We're ready. - We're confident.
It'll definitely work.
- Here we go. - Okay.
If you have a girlfriend, fold your finger.
(If you have a girlfriend, fold your finger.)
(Girlfriend?)
"If you have a girlfriend"?
- What about a wife? - It doesn't count.
- Not if you're married. - "If you have a girlfriend"?
Call her and break up with her.
Right now.
(That doesn't count.)
Call her and break up with her.
You can meet her after this.
(After thinking for a moment, )
(he put down the picture.)
He's so cool.
(The romantic giraffe is back.)
- He's a man. - He's a man.
He's so cool.
I couldn't escape.
It was a trap.
- Okay. - Okay.
- They were going for us. - We did a good job.
We're done. Let's move on.
- Ask that one. - I will.
Relax.
(We already have a question ready.)
If you're married, for your finger.
(If you're married, for your finger.)
This is not okay.
Why is it different from the previous one?
Okay. Put it down.
I'm sorry. I'm married.
- It's a good thing. - Okay.
It's a good thing that you're married.
I'm married. Put it down.
(So Min and Seok Jin's teams have put down 1 each.)
- This is annoying. - They have only one left.
They picked the right target.
If they put down one more,
- they'll be out, right? - Yes.
- It's the staff's turn now. - The staff's turn.
Sing into the karaoke machine.
All teams except the winning team will put down one.
(All teams except the winning team will put down one.)
- Guys, we have Yul. - Me?
We have Yul.
- Yul. - We have Hoon.
- Right. - Seriously.
Park Hoon. We have him.
I got a high score in a karaoke bar recently.
We have Jong Kook.
Okay. Let's do this!
- If you sing a dance song, - Let's do this.
you'll definitely get a high score.
- What should we sing? - Something fun.
- Something fun would be nice. - Let's take off our jackets.
- Turn around one by one. - How do we do it?
- Like this. - How?
(Team King Seok Jin goes first. The intro starts.)
We have to sing something like that too.
(The intro of "To You" by Infinite Track excites everyone.)
Turn around.
(The variety show newbie, Park Hoon)
(Haha with a cold)
(The weak king, Seok Jin)
(The romantic civilian, Kwang Soo)
Oh, my.
(They show off amazing teamwork.)
They picked a good song.
- The color of Yonsei University. - Let's go!
They're wearing the color of Yonsei University.
Please send a lot of love to SBS's "Haechi".
Arms around shoulders.
So Min.
(Perfect teamwork)
Let's go!
(He sings with a holy voice.)
(With stable vocals and systematic moves, they start out nicely.)
(What?)
(They get too excited and forget about competition.)
(Civilian Hoon leads, )
(and the whole kingdom follows.)
- What other songs are there? - What should we sing?
(Even if I lose...)
(everything...)
(I have loved)
Jump!
(While Team King Seok Jin sings, )
(they jump in again.)
(The dancers intrude.)
(Way to go!)
(Explosive high notes)
Together!
(He has a cold.)
They won't get a high score.
(We won't?)
(Then we'll gather around the microphone.)
(We can feel the high score.)
They won't get a high score.
- They won't. - They won't.
- They won't get a high score. - They won't.
(They finished the song with great teamwork.)
One person should have sung. Please.
(What's their score?)
(They only have 1 left. They have to win.)
It's 93. It's high.
(It's not bad.)
- The machine is generous. - It's high.
- It's generous with scores. - Okay.
We have to win. Otherwise, we're out.
- Let's go! Yul, let's go. - Let's go!
Where is it?
- Let's do this! - We danced so hard.
"As I Told You"?
(This song is strong.)
- "As I Told You". - This song...
("As I Told You" by Kim Sung Jae)
(Here come the dancers.)
(The pop dance expert, So Min)
Rotate. Rotate around Yul.
(The whole-verse singer, Yul)
(Nervous)
A Ra, what fun songs are there?
"Wrongful Encounter" or...
(Limp)
(Turning)
What's that?
(It looks weird, but he is a good dancer.)
(It's funny and cool at the same time.)
Good!
(I don't want them to get a high score.)
(It's time to sing!)
(He starts singing at the top of his lungs.)
(This is fun.)
(Korean songs are the best.)
(Another day gone, )
(and I am still...)
(here)
(Excited)
(All the civilians team up.)
(They make even their opponents have fun.)
(His steps are fancier than his singing skills.)
It's so flashy.
His steps...
(So Min's signature moves)
(You did a good job, Your Majesty.)
Sideways.
(Will they get a high score?)
(Yul seems to have danced a lot in the old days.)
(Immersed)
(Worried)
(Here it comes.)
(Yul's turning dance)
(They're still deciding which song to sing.)
(He sings the last line...)
(at the top of his lungs.)
(The passionate performance is over.)
Please.
(If their score is higher than 93, Team King Seok Jin will be out.)
(Their score is 94, which is only 1 point higher.)
(Team King Seok Jin is out.)
We beat one team.
- Good job. - Good job.
- Yul. - Yul.
- Good job. - It was nice.
- A Ra. - It was amazing.
(It's Team King Il Woo's turn.)
- Good job. - Crying Nut?
("Speed Up, Losers" by Crying Nut)
- Right? - It usually gives you a high score.
It's very fun.
- It'll be amazing. - It's a fun song.
(It starts out calm.)
(Jong Kook warms up his voice.)
(Let's go.)
(Shut it!)
(It's time to scream.)
(It's getting more and more fun.)
- It's getting fun. - Here we go.
It's time.
Let's go.
(Let's speed up towards a high score.)
(Running)
What is he doing?
(Even a member of the losing team is having fun.)
(It's a mess.)
(But it doesn't affect the singing and dancing.)
What are you doing?
(What are you all doing there?)
(Splash)
What are you doing?
(They do their best to the end.)
(Despite all the disturbance...)
Is it over?
(They managed to finish the song.)
(If their score is higher than 94, Team King Il Woo will win.)
- Oh, my. - We win!
(Team King Il Woo has to put down 1.)
We won with "As I Told You"!
- "As I Told You". - What's our score?
- Team King Seok Jin... - 83.
Hoon picked the song.
(Complaining)
Hoon...
(You had fun.)
- It's 2 to 2. - It's 2 to 2.
- We have a chance. - All right.
- Okay. - It's our turn to attack.
Okay.
Kim Jong Kook, fold your finger.
(Straightforward)
This is...
Fold your finger.
- Should we... - Let's go with facts.
Those wearing glasses, fold your fingers.
(They fight back with facts.)
(Jae Seok takes off his glasses.)
You should have taken them off before the question.
You have such deep marks.
What are those lines?
Be quiet. Okay.
- Put one down. - Okay.
It's the staff's turn to ask a question.
- Okay. - Okay.
- This will determine the result. - Be fair.
The losers of a ddakji game will fold their fingers.
Okay. Jae Seok.
(The losers of a ddakji game will fold their fingers.)
It's time for Yu Hyuk to step up.
- Yu Hyuk. - Yu Hyuk. We trust you.
Both teams have good players.
(I'm good at it too.)
Will they take turns?
You have to beat all members. Okay.
Hit the center.
So Min, hit the center.
It's not easy.
Hit the center.
Don't use too much force.
(So Min attacks first.)
(It's powerful.)
(A Ra's ddakji is flipped halfway. She might lose.)
Good.
(It didn't flip.)
- Okay. - Hit the center.
- The center? - Just hit it.
(It's A Ra's turn to attack.)
Stay calm.
(Her ddakji hits So Min's.)
(Will So Min's flip?)
(It flipped.)
- A Ra. - Okay!
(I'm the ddakji queen.)
- She is strong. - Good job.
- A Ra. - Good job.
- I knew it. - Good job.
- Yul. - Yes.
- It flipped. - A Ra knows how to do it.
- Yul will flip it at once. - What?
Yul will flip it at once.
(He hits the floor.)
What was that?
What did you do?
You surprised me.
Am I seeing things?
Next time, I'll flip it.
- I'm all set now. - Right?
(A Ra feels confident.)
She'll flip it.
(She attacks.)
(Yul's ddakji is lifted.)
- It's okay. You did well. - That was close.
- A Ra knows how to do it. - That was close.
Yul, are you all set?
- I am. - Be careful. It's dangerous.
Be careful. You might get hurt.
(Will he be able to flip the ddakji this time?)
- Yul... - He is athletic.
(He flipped the ddakji perfectly.)
- Nice! - Yul.
- Good job. - Once he is set...
- Good job. - It's 1 to 1.
Which one is ours? This one?
Move it to the center. Hold on.
(It has to be here.)
(Jong Kook kindly moves Ji Hyo's ddakji.)
Jong Kook, show her how you do it.
She's good. I'm not doing it because of you.
(I won't fall for it.)
(Exposed)
You'll tease me, right?
You'll start it again. I'm not doing it.
- I won't do it. - Jong Kook is bothered.
- He is bothered. - I'm not doing it.
Just hit it.
(Ji Hyo tries.)
- Good job. - She is all set now.
- Good job. - Good job.
- I'll flip it. - You should.
(You have to flip it.)
(He gets ready...)
(and hits the ddakji.)
Okay!
(He flips it this time too.)
- Nice! - Kwon Yul's power.
- Good job! - Yes!
- Okay. - Il Woo, are you good at it?
- You should be better than me. - I never tried it.
- Never? - No.
That's great.
- Let's go. - Just hit it.
(King Il Woo comes out to stop So Min's kingdom from winning.)
Jong Kook is playing too.
(How skilled is King Il Woo?)
- He's never done it. - He never has.
(The way he plays is obviously awkward.)
How could you hold ddakji like this? He grabbed it like this.
He's quite strong.
All right.
(Yul does it without hesitating.)
(Bam)
(It's 1 shot, 1 kill.)
(He eliminates 3 people instantly.)
- Yul is good. - All right.
- Yul is very good. - Just defeat Jong Kook.
(Only Jong Kook remains.)
(Is it time for me to take action?)
(His strength is enough to break the ground.)
(He's an authentic strong player who never fails to turn ddakji.)
(Will it be the strong player?)
(Will it be up-and-coming player?)
Let's go.
(There's no place to back down.)
Wait.
(Thud)
- Didn't he throw it? - That was strong.
(There's no practice.)
- Ji Hyo, encourage him. - It doesn't hit accurately.
(Thud)
(Victory of Il Woo's team depends on Jong Kook.)
(Will Jong Kook stop them from winning ddakji?)
(It didn't flip.)
That's unfortunate.
(One is happy, and the other is sad.)
- We still have a chance. - Come on, Yul.
If you succeed, we win.
- Right. - Yul, let's go.
(Without hesitation, )
(he throws his ddakji.)
(Will So Min's team win? Or will Il Woo's team get a chance?)
(He flips it again.)
(Il Woo conquers it all by himself.)
Is it over? Did Jong Kook lose?
(King of ddakji, Yul does a splendid job.)
He's very good.
- I got a hold of it. - Okay.
- Okay. - What happened?
(Didn't I tell you? I got a hold of it.)
The winner of this mission is...
Team King So Min.
- Our teamwork was great. - Pardon?
The king of the winning team is...
given a treason right, a hint,
- and a recruitment right. - To the king?
- Is it only the king? - I bet she's fake.
Keep it hidden. Let's look at it together.
(What hint does King So Min receive?)
"As his jaw is hard,"
"the real king is responsible, but he has more desire than luck."
Isn't it me?
(Is So Min the real king?)
(Which one of them is the real king?)
Who shall we recruit?
They're increasing. We should win games no matter what.
- Who is someone... - Easy to order around?
easy to order around?
- Someone who is... - Who do you recommend?
(Who's someone easy to order around?)
(The one who's standing)
- In that case... - King So Min.
- Please make the decision. - Okay.
I pick Kwang Soo.
(It's Lee Kwang Soo.)
(He's easy to order around.)
Give me the hint.
I knew that he'd be picked.
It couldn't be helped.
That's how he is.
(He changes his nationality without regrets.)
- That's him. - You'll be the youngest.
- You'll be the youngest. - Thank you.
You'll be the youngest.
- You're the youngest. - Since you're the youngest,
- He's the youngest. - be good to us.
- They should like you. - Yes, sir.
How about the treason right?
- Who wants it? - The king may...
give out the treason right.
- Who do you trust the most? - Right.
He flipped most ddakji.
He's most accomplished.
(She gives Yul a treason right.)
- Thank you very much. - You're welcome.
That's the right thing to do.
Can you share the hint with me?
We'll decide after we discuss.
(Are they acting territorial?)
- What do you mean? - You don't get...
citizenship automatically.
- That will be later. - You aren't a citizen yet.
We need to review your identity first.
What about my ID?
- You're wearing blue. - Your color is different.
Let's move to the next mission.
(Current team status)
(Yul has a treason right.)
(After a new citizen is invited to So Min's kingdom...)
Gosh, what's this?
(King So Min finds a menu.)
Do we earn it?
That's right.
(Various dishes are written.)
By the way,
I don't know if I can say this.
Both the king...
and one of your people are sick.
There can be sick people.
One of your people feels awkward.
He doesn't feel awkward at all.
We're having so much fun.
(He gets very close to him.)
(What was that?)
What?
- What are you doing? - We got close.
Hoon and I have known each other for a while.
He made a physical contact.
(King Seok Jin's physical contact)
Wait.
Our slave shouldn't use a sitting mat.
Move.
(It's already sad that he's a slave.)
(His sitting mat is taken.)
- Why? - Give it to me.
Why did you join their team?
Don't I look like a mercenary?
- No. - I'm not a slave.
- Watch it. - Watch it.
You should have sat in between two kingdoms.
You'll start an epidemic.
(It's a dangerous zone for an epidemic.)
That's why you're sitting there.
This is your next mission.
It's called Royal Table Coins.
(Royal Table Coins)
Each team will push a lid that you see in front of you.
You obtain a dish, and that will be your lunch menu.
- It's difficult. - It's very difficult.
There are no bad side dishes.
All members will play.
The team with the highest score wins.
Determine the order of play. The order is very important.
- It could bounce off. - Let me think.
- It's like curling. - This is important.
- The last team. - How about this way?
Let's play a simple team game...
and determine the order.
Is there any game you play, A Ra?
- No. - There isn't?
Is there a game you're good at, Hoon?
(What about Hoon?)
How about Initial Consonant Game?
- Initial Consonant Game? - That sounds good.
(They agree on Initial Consonant Game.)
Let's play in teams.
- That sounds good. - Initial Consonant Game?
Let's play that.
If it's K and S, each person plays.
- Then everyone takes a turn. - Right.
People who don't answer get eliminated.
As soon as someone is eliminated, the consonant changes.
- Okay. - That's right.
Start.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
(N and M)
Tree.
Tear.
Aged mother.
(They start off well.)
Cold noodles.
I knew this would happen.
(N and M?)
(Let me think.)
(Ji Hyo from Team King Il Woo is eliminated.)
Ji Hyo is terrible at games.
That was expected.
- A Ra starts with new consonants. - Start with A Ra.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
(S and K)
Apple.
(She starts one beat later.)
- Effort. - The beat is off.
It's offbeat.
Thought.
Success.
Resident director.
Ginger.
Towel.
"Ginger" was strange.
- What's wrong with that? - A moment ago...
(Wasn't it strange a moment ago?)
What's the problem?
I thought "ginger" was repeated.
- No, it was "thought". - "Thought" and "ginger".
Oh, I see.
(Oh, I see.)
- You just ruined my turn. - Wait.
(What do you mean by that?)
- What? - How could you?
- We have to complain. - What's wrong with you?
I'll apologize.
Apologizing isn't enough.
My hearing isn't good.
Your hearing?
(Your hearing?)
(How could you?)
(That's what he says.)
Wait.
A Ra and Il Woo.
(Play with the right beat.)
"Ginger". Stay with the beat.
- Don't say "ginger". - Okay.
Does Seok Jin start?
- A Ra goes first. - No, it's your turn.
- Mine? - Yes.
We'll do it faster. 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
(J and O)
Tuning.
Chang Ung.
Father-in-law.
Acupressure.
Jang Hwang?
(She was busy with the beat and coming up with a word.)
- What? - J and O are difficult.
J and O are difficult.
Here we go. We start with Il Woo.
- Start. - It's difficult.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
Freight vehicle.
(He ignores the beat.)
- Can't you follow the beat? - Keep the beat.
Keep the beat. It goes like this.
(Clap twice and say the word.)
Start.
(They restart the game starting with Il Woo.)
Freight vehicle.
(He ignores the beat again.)
- No. - Hey.
Freight vehicle.
(I can't hold it anymore.)
There's a beat.
- Clap, clap, freight vehicle. - Okay.
Is he bad with beats?
- Let's hurry. Get ready. - Did he do it...
- on purpose? - I got it.
- Start. - Initial Consonant Game
(I'll do it right this time.)
Freight vehicle.
Black tea.
Black pepper.
Plant.
Form.
Hapcheon.
Red vinegar.
Haechi.
Iris.
(It's my turn.)
Wasn't it me?
He's eliminated.
(I'm the only one on my team.)
It's because Jong Kook doesn't want to sit next to me.
I'm disappointed in him.
He's been covering his face.
I thought that he wasn't there.
It's confusing who's eliminated.
Those who are eliminated should interlock their fingers.
(He brings up interlocking fingers again.)
(She agrees.)
All right.
- Who's next? - Haha.
Start.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
Radish.
Radish?
He's eliminated.
- What? - Radish.
It's one word.
- The pronunciation isn't long. - It's just radish.
Let's start with Il Woo.
Do it on the beat. If you don't, you're eliminated.
Start.
(They play again starting with Il Woo.)
Soo...
He's eliminated.
(He hesitates.)
(He wants to cry.)
- The red team is eliminated. - This is good.
I'm nervous.
- It's us and the blue team. Start. - Eliminate two more.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
Lion.
Dictionary.
Circumstance.
Award certificate.
Unnecessary comment.
(Our team is so good.)
Exhausted.
Master.
I was eliminated.
(It's not my turn.)
Was it my turn?
(He fell in the black hole of the eliminated.)
He's out.
- You're out. - You are.
Move back.
Only two of us remain.
- The two of you. - Okay, this is good.
We need to defeat two people.
- Let's go. - We're the top.
This is great.
Here we go.
Do I start?
Start.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
Memory.
Gong?
(Gong?)
(K and O)
(How about gong?)
There's "common use".
- Pledge. - Sharing.
This game is quite difficult.
- Here we go. - You're out, right?
Yes, I'm eliminated.
- Start. Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
Byung. Gosh.
(He sighs.)
- Come on. - It couldn't be helped.
This is too harsh.
It's 2 to 2. Let's go.
Okay, do it.
- Do it. - Okay.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
Cucumber.
"Eung Eung".
("Eung Eung"?)
- What? - There's a song.
- "Eung Eung". - It's by Apink.
There's "Eung Eung" by Apink.
- It was released. - Okay.
We approve of it. Start.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
"Eung Eung".
Milk.
Cucumber.
- He already said it. - When?
(King So Min is eliminated.)
- When did you say it? - I said cucumber.
I said it the first time.
(Tables are turned.)
Only one remains.
Okay, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo starts. - Start.
- Kwang Soo starts. - Hey.
- You have to win, Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- Start. - Kwang Soo.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
(Consonants given are H and H.)
(What will Kwang Soo's answer be for H and H?)
- Start. - Kwang Soo.
- Initial Consonant Game - Initial Consonant Game
(Consonants given are H and H.)
(What will Kwang Soo's answer be for H and H?)
Hong hong.
(He laughs.)
It's H and H.
(He fails in front of H and H.)
Seok Jin and Hoon win.
Hoon is doing well today.
- He's very good. - Hoon is good.
- Please determine the order. - We should go last.
- Am I deciding the order? - Yes.
(He forgot momentarily.)
(He just remembers.)
Decide the order.
- Order? - Do we get one point?
That team is our biggest enemy.
- They should go first. - Goodness.
(Team King So Min goes first.)
- We're second. - Okay.
This is good.
Decide the order of your players.
Are we white?
One of us can't play since there are four.
- All right. - How shall we do it?
- Who wants to go first? - By the way...
By the way, we didn't discuss at all.
- Will the four of you grab a piece? - Stay still.
What? I'm a team member too.
You aren't yet.
- Wait. - Wait.
"Wait"?
Let's have Yul go first.
- This is ours. - All right.
- Good luck. - Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
- Braised short ribs. - Or spicy stir-fried pork.
Can you place it where they want?
- Of course. - Stir-fried sausage sounds good.
- Sausage? - Stir-fried sausage.
- I'll go for sausage. - Throw it between sausage...
- Eggs are good too. - Eggs.
(Will Yul meet his teammates' expectation?)
Say start.
Start.
(Yul from Team King So Min starts.)
(Flicking)
(He throws it toward sausage.)
Goodness.
(It goes out.)
(It falls off the table.)
That was great.
- I'm sorry. - How did you do that?
(I'm sorry?)
It should have gone to the middle.
(He just laughs.)
He was so confident.
Next team.
- It's us. - Is it us?
- This could be good strategically. - We're in trouble.
Send it to the side.
We can push theirs off.
- Start. - You can do it.
Il Woo is quite bad at games.
- He's actually sloppy. - He couldn't follow the beat.
- Are you a bad dancer? - He has no sense of beat.
(Will he succeed despite being bothered?)
(Flicking)
That was good. We scored 10 points.
Is it zero?
(Soy sauce is 0 point.)
It's zero point.
He got soy sauce.
That's hilarious.
We have zero points.
This isn't safe.
- Let's go. - Let's go, Haha.
He has a cold.
Go for spicy stir-fried pork. It's the safest.
(Flicking)
(It goes out.)
Why are you so strong? Aren't you sick?
(My goodness)
It's difficult.
(It's Team King So Min's turn again.)
- Se Chan. - Show us, Se Chan.
Se Chan.
Let's do it.
I'm really good at this game.
(He mumbles to himself.)
(Be quiet.)
Be quiet.
(He's trying to concentrate.)
We didn't call you for this.
(He gets sad.)
(What?)
(It stops at stir-fried sausage.)
- Stir-fried sausage. - 1 point.
(This is amazing.)
This isn't bad.
That was amazing. Good job.
(Their piece could be pushed away. They must stay focused.)
- A Ra. - Let's go.
(Next is A Ra from Team King Il Woo.)
- Start. - I know
I know
(It pushes Il Woo's piece to rolled omelet.)
Soy sauce?
It landed on rolled omelet.
(Hers pushes Il Woo's piece to rolled omelet.)
- It landed on rolled omelet. - It's on rolled omelet.
- It's on rolled omelet. - A Ra.
- You pushed it. - She pushed it on purpose.
Next is Hoon.
(Hoon from Team King Seok Jin starts.)
- Hoon. - You can push the other piece.
That's not a bad tactic.
Soup or spicy stir-fried pork sounds good.
Soup or spicy stir-fried pork?
(Okay, he got it.)
(I'll give it a try.)
(His fingers used to handle knives.)
(Flicking)
(It lands on soy sauce.)
(It's far from spicy stir-fried pork.)
(It doesn't even go near soup.)
- No, it's soy sauce. - Soy sauce?
- My goodness. - It's soy sauce.
We should do it from here.
Is this it? I know how it feels now.
Why did you do that?
- Go, So Min. - Someone has to play.
- So Min. - We need to score.
It should go this way.
It might land on stir-fried sausage if you don't do it well.
Push it this way. Be careful on this side.
Do you have to put your bottom so close?
(Moving about)
(His bottom bothers him.)
- Listen. - Sit down.
My goodness.
Start.
I hope it doesn't fall off.
(For now, )
(she throws it.)
(It passes between the pieces in the front.)
(It lands on braised short ribs.)
(Is it really braised short ribs?)
(King So Min does it.)
Yes!
(They admit her success.)
She's our king.
So Min, So Min.
- So Min. - So Min.
She's our king after all.
- She did it. - That was amazing.
So Min is the real king.
Hit braised short ribs.
If she pushes off our piece, that would be incredible.
(Flicking)
Vegetable wraps are good too.
It's zero points. That's good.
Here's a pretender.
(He eliminates Ji Hyo's piece.)
What?
Did we lose vegetable wraps?
- Kwang Soo. - What?
(Is he giving the last chance to Kwang Soo?)
Don't lose our braised short ribs.
What if Kwang Soo pushes off our stir-fried sausage?
- Kwang Soo. - He might hit it.
- What if he creates a mess? - What mess?
Don't create any mess.
Can you do it? This time...
- Go for spicy stir-fried pork. - Let's go for that.
- How about something else? - Soup is good too.
- Get rolled omelet. - Right.
Okay? Don't be greedy.
We don't expect you to get something like ribs, okay?
We'll kick you out if you fail.
Here's Kwang Soo.
(But that's not how people think.)
I think he's looking at braised short ribs.
Don't. No.
- Don't go for it. - Seriously don't.
Leave it.
(Will Kwang Soo take the safe route?)
(Flicking)
(Is he going to blow the chance away?)
What?
(He didn't even reach "soy sauce".)
What did you just do?
- Are you a spy? - Kwang Soo.
Move.
- Is this why we accepted you? - I got too nervous.
- It's nothing. - "Move".
- "Move". - He blew it.
What should I do?
("Rolled omelet" and "soy sauce" are taken.)
You have to flick it far.
You can do it.
- Start. - Good luck.
(Flicking)
(It goes far.)
- Okay! - That was too strong.
(He went out.)
That was too strong. That went straight out.
Do you want to go? You go.
- Hoon. - He's...
- athletic. - Hoon,
(Listen to me.)
come in the middle and hit this.
- You can land on short ribs. - Should I do that?
Yes, come in the middle.
That would be insane.
- Come in the middle. - Stir-fried sausage is in the way.
- It's right here. - Hit it.
(This is their last chance. Can he do it?)
(He went in the middle!)
(If he keeps on going...)
(He hit So Min's piece!)
(If So Min's piece falls off, the game will turn around.)
(It stops on the edge.)
You did it!
(How is this possible?)
- We did it! - Oh, my.
(They almost did it!)
(Hoon played as Seok Jin instructed.)
- He did it. - He almost took her out.
- We did it! - Oh, my.
Oh, my. Hoon.
You did it.
(He didn't take her out but he landed on short ribs.)
He was saved because of me.
That's right. He was saved because of So Min.
If it weren't for hers, it would have gone out.
This is unbelievable.
The winner is Team King So Min.
- King! She's our king. - I'm the king.
I'm the king.
A fake king dominates the world.
(That was so close!)
What's the hint?
(She obtains a hint, treason right, and recruitment right.)
You get too many things.
The hint is too good.
(They took another hint.)
Read it out loud.
(What is the hint about their king?)
"The real king lacks honor..."
He lacks it.
(Hold on.)
(The hint states...)
("The real king lacks honor but he has a developed nose...)
(which represents wealth, so he hesitates between wealth and fame.")
Hold on.
(He has a developed nose?)
Il Woo, can you look at us?
(Who has...)
Is it him?
(Who has the king's nose?)
- Do you agree? - Come. I'll explain.
- Hold on. - I'll explain.
The nation is being shaken.
(The nation is being shaken.)
- It's being shaken. - It's being shaken by the roots.
- My goodness. - It's starting to shake.
This one is good.
- This one is... - I'm curious.
I'm curious.
(What will happen to the three kings?)
(Team King So Min recruits Hoon.)
Can you not figure it out?
Our hint was too confusing.
- That was. - I know.
- Was it confusing? - The hint...
We were certain after the 1st hint. We're not sure about the 2nd one.
- How was it? - The 2nd hint...
How was the hint?
- It confused us. - It confused me.
What's it about?
- I convinced them. - We can't say.
- They won't say. - I'm certain.
(There's one nation that looks especially weak.)
- Excuse me. - Our kingdom is falling apart.
Are you guys the class president and the vice-president?
(Are you guys the class president and the vice-president?)
We're a kingdom.
I thought you were accepting money...
- at a wedding. - We're a kingdom.
What's wrong with this nation?
- There's an old man and just me. - My goodness.
This is the last mission...
where you can switch the members and check the identity...
of the real king.
This is the last mission.
It's The King's Tears.
"The King's Tears".
- What's this? - "The King's Tears".
I want to cry.
If one of the kings gets the answer,
they have to remove a stick from a member's cap...
and if the water falls, they can recruit that member.
- If the water falls? - It has to fall.
- I get what it is. - The water has to fall.
If a civilian gets the answer,
they can pick two kings...
and find out if the real king is one of them.
You're going to tell them?
(The civilian can pick two kings and find out who they are.)
- You're going to tell them? - Really?
Whether the king is there or not?
- Great. - That's good.
When So Min heard that, she laughed really hard.
(Hold on.)
I was happy. I'm the king.
I'm the king, Jong Kook. I'm certain.
- We'll know right away. - That's great.
However, the member can only be switched...
only the king removes the stick...
and the water falls on them.
- This is difficult. - We have to do well.
Their civilians are getting ready to escape.
(Why is that?)
What are you talking about?
Don't be mistaken.
They're just not telling us.
- They're getting ready to escape. - What are you talking about?
- This is So Min's demise. - I think I'm right.
What do you mean?
I think it'll be her demise at the end.
I'll serve you until the end.
Bring the table in.
(There are 5 sticks on the cap.)
Do we put them on?
(They need to remove the number of sticks as designated.)
Put it on.
I'm worried about this.
The theme of today's quiz is "king".
- "King". All right. - Okay.
Haha, let's build our kingdom. This won't do.
Here's the first question.
- There are two sticks involved. - Good.
You pick two sticks.
"Who is referred to..."
"as the King of Song?"
- "The King of Song". - "The King of Song"?
One, Franz Peter Schubert.
Two, Ludwig van Beethoven.
Three, Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart.
Four, Antonio Vivaldi.
- Answer. - Four.
Antonio Vivaldi.
Answer.
Four, Wolfgang Amadeus Vivaldi.
- What? - What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
- No? - What was that?
- Answer. One, - Wasn't I right?
Wolfgang Tereus...
(Incorrect)
It's hard to memorize.
We have to memorize it.
Answer! One,
Franz Peteru Schubert.
Can you say it again?
Answer!
(That was close.)
Answer.
- Frunch? - What?
He said "brunch".
- Answer! - Answer!
- Answer. - Ji Hyo.
Frenz?
Answer!
(It's King So Min's turn.)
One, Franz Peter Schubert.
(She pronounces it accurately.)
(She got the name right, but is it 1?)
(Who is referred to as the King of Song?)
We tried everything.
(She's correct.)
(He was an Austrian composer known for "Trout Quintet".)
I know he's the King of Song. Goodness.
- This is the day. - Let's grow...
- You're indeed the King. - Let's grow the kingdom, everybody.
I can't bow.
King, you should save a civilian from there.
There's only one here. Go there.
- Yes? - Take two sticks out.
Kwang Soo, this is your job.
- Take two out. - Why would you take my civilian?
- You're usually unlucky. - Okay.
Take one out. You're unlucky.
It's too lonely here.
Take one out.
Please.
Please work.
(What will happen to Civilian Haha?)
(He removes the first stick.)
Please.
(Please don't let water come out.)
- It didn't come out. - It's coming out.
(Dripping)
- It's coming out. - It came out.
- Yes! - I knew it.
(Welcome to Team King So Min.)
It's freedom!
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, Haha enters Team King So Min.)
- This kingdom is done. - What's going on?
The real king is alive.
You're on your own.
Isn't that nation done?
- I know. It is. - This is driving me nuts.
(Team King So Min has 6 civilians now.)
My nation is prosperous.
- I can't even take over. - We're in trouble.
Here's the second question.
- Second question. - This is not difficult.
There are two sticks assigned to this question too.
"Which actor didn't play..."
"the role of a king?"
- I watch many dramas, - All right.
so I know for sure.
One, Han Seok Kyu from "Deep Rooted Tree".
(Which actor didn't play the role of a king?)
Two, Jung Tae Woo from "Ladies of the Palace".
- What? - Three,
Yoo Dong Kun from "Daejoyoung".
Four, Ji Jin Hee from "The Great Seer".
- Answer. - Answer.
(It's King Il Woo's turn.)
Four, Ji Jin Hee from "The Great Seer".
Answer!
(His eyes shake.)
Yoo Dong Kun from "Daejoyoung".
- What number? - Three.
(Which actor didn't play the role of a king?)
All right!
(Choi Su Jong played the king in "Daejoyoung".)
We're killing it today.
Oh, well.
I get to..
find out who the king is.
I can pick two.
That's right. That's the hint you get.
Please check.
Try Seok Jin.
(Which two kings does he want to know about?)
- Do I pick two? - Yes, go ahead.
(King Seok Jin insists he's the one.)
(King So Min has the most number of civilians.)
(King Il Woo is keeping quiet and looking for his chance.)
Seok Jin and Il Woo.
(Is one of them the real king?)
(The real king is...)
- Only Jae Seok gets to know. - One of them...
is the real king.
(The real king is either Seok Jin or Il Woo.)
(Really?)
Really?
- He's shocked. - Really?
He's shocked.
- There is? - Yes.
(If the real king is either Seok Jin or Il Woo, )
(So Min isn't the king.)
(Who's the real king then?)
- Why? - He's shocked.
(Why is he so shocked?)
If you want to switch to another team,
you can take two sticks out from another member's cap.
Jae Seok, come here.
I'm the real king.
(The real one usually stays quiet.)
- Goodness. - Jae Seok.
Your decision is very important right now.
But he has the treason right.
This doesn't mean anything to him.
- He can use it at the end. - He has treason right.
Should I go here?
(Then!)
(He picks King Seok Jin who looks easy.)
- It could be me, right? - Well.
If the water falls, then it'll be funny.
Two?
- Please fall. - You might not switch.
Hey.
Hold on to my head.
(The first stick is a fail.)
- Should I hold on to your head? - Your head?
- I'm sorry. - What do you mean?
- Hold on the helmet. - No, hold on to this.
You can hold on to it.
- That's true. - Right.
If no water comes out, then nothing changes.
- Nothing changes. - There's no water.
(The second stick is a fail too.)
You're usually good at this.
Nothing came out.
Jae Seok, you looked sad.
No way.
But...
(He's speechless.)
(Other civilians don't know what's going on.)
(They don't have the hint.)
I have no idea.
- Here we go. - Okay.
This is a short-answer question.
There are three sticks assigned to it.
I have to get this right.
- "In five seconds," - Oh, dear.
"name five movie titles that has "king" in them."
Answer.
"The King's Tears", "King and the Clown", "King's Lady",
Joey Wong's "A Chinese Ghost Story"...
Isn't it "Tears of the Dragon"?
(He only got "King and the Clown" right.)
Does Joey Wong count?
(What has "king" in it?)
Answer!
(It's Yul's turn.)
"King and the Clown", "The Foul King",
"Queen of Walking",
"King Arthur",
and "I am the King".
(Time over)
- Answer! - Answer.
(It's about who takes it first now.)
"I am the King", "The Foul King",
"Queen of Walking", "The King of Jokgu",
and "The King".
(He's correct!)
"Queen of Walking"?
- Is there "Queen of Walking"? - There is.
- There's a movie. - There's "Queen of Walking".
- Shim Eun Kyung is in it. - Right.
- Can I ask? - Go ahead.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo got the question right, so he gets to ask who the king is.)
Seok Jin...
and Il Woo.
(The pretender is anxious.)
One of them is the real king.
(The real king is either Seok Jin or Il Woo.)
(It's not So Min?)
He looks shocked.
(He reacts the same way as Jae Seok.)
Kwang Soo. You look shocked.
- Kwang Soo. - I was shocked too.
- He's shocked. - He's really shocked.
I was shocked too.
He's really shocked.
(It's either Seok Jin or Il Woo.)
(Kwang Soo's reasoning)
I knew it!
(The second hint stated that he has a developed nose.)
(Jae Seok picked Seok Jin as well.)
(That means...)
Really?
(Kwang Soo predicts the real king is...)
- Can I pick three? - Yes.
I pick Seok Jin!
(Seok Jin has a huge nose.)
(Will Seok Jin be the king...)
(as Kwang Soo predicted?)
(King Seok Jin has 3 sticks left.)
(Jae Seok removed 2.)
(He's so happy that he's flooded in tears.)
(He has a civilian.)
Do I get to escape?
(Kwang Soo heads to Team King Seok Jin.)
Kwang Soo escaped.
Goodness.
Come here.
(The civilians without any hints are confused.)
Everybody,
do you understand the flow now?
I'll save poor Civilian Kwang Soo.
- No. - Listen.
(There's no refusal.)
Civilians of Team King So Min,
bring Kwang Soo back.
(It's the king's will.)
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
I don't know.
It might be So Min.
I'm not 100 percent sure.
- Make sure we bring him back. - Okay.
Here's the fourth question.
There are three sticks assigned to this as well.
This is a multiple question.
"What do you call a man..."
"who gains social status by marrying into a family of high status?"
A man?
One, Love Nobleman.
That's not it.
Two, Skirt Nobleman.
(They have to get a hint.)
Three, Government Post Nobleman.
Four, Outside Nobleman.
- Answer! - Answer!
(Se Chan tries for the first time.)
- Se Chan. - One, Love Nobleman.
Answer.
Two, Skirt Nobleman.
She's the king!
(Love Nobleman is the male head of the household.)
(Government Post Nobleman is a government official.)
Bring Kwang Soo back!
Hold on. Think about it.
Think about it.
Think about it carefully.
I...
This is so funny.
He comes right back.
Why are you doing this to me?
Come this way.
If no water comes out,
- I get to stay. - Right.
Jae Seok,
- please use your bad luck. - Yes.
- Please help me with your bad luck. - I have one civilian.
- This is my expertise. - Three.
- One. - You brat.
- One. - Our king treated you...
with kindness.
How dare you run away?
(He removes the first stick to bring Kwang Soo back.)
(There are 3 sticks to be removed.)
- You brat! - That was okay.
One.
(Gushing)
You brat!
(He only took one out.)
Welcome.
(Welcome back.)
- Come back! - The king treated you so nicely.
- Come. - I'm sorry!
(He gets dragged to Team King So Min.)
I'll never do that again!
This is driving me nuts.
(King Seok Jin was happy for a moment because he had a civilian.)
Gather.
(He's alone again.)
This is driving me nuts.
This is a short-answer question.
There are three sticks assigned.
I need to get this right.
"In five seconds..."
- This is difficult. - It's so hard.
"name five actors..."
"who played a king."
- Answer! - Answer!
Choi Min Sik, Han Seok Kyu,
Cho Joong Hoon...
Was it Park Joong Hoon?
- Answer! - Answer!
(It's Haha's turn.)
- Jung Tae Woo, Choi Su Jong, - Hong Suk Chun.
Yeo Jin Goo, Hong Suk Chun...
(Se Chan interferes.)
(Goodness)
(He's successful.)
Answer!
Han Seok Kyu, Song Joong Ki,
- Lee Kwang Soo, Lee Sang Yun, - Hong Suk Chun.
and Hong Suk Chun. Hey!
(He interferes again.)
(They can't overcome it.)
Answer.
Jung Il Woo, Lee Kwang Soo, Song Joong Ki,
Choi Su Jong, and Yeo Jin Goo.
(Jung Il Woo, Lee Kwang Soo, Song Joong Ki, )
(Choi Su Jong, and Yeo Jin Goo)
Haha. I almost had it.
I'm sad.
I would know for sure if I have another chance.
Is the king either...
Seok Jin or Il Woo?
One of them is the real king.
(One of them is the real king.)
I see. I knew it.
What is it?
(Is this why they were shocked?)
- Okay. - Haha.
Do you understand why I'm being quiet?
This is interesting.
- What is it? - I'm so curious.
(Is King Il Woo making a move?)
Do I pick?
Yes, pick three.
(He can pick 3 sticks. Who will he choose?)
They're all looking at Seok Jin.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo picked King Seok Jin...)
(after seeing the second hint.)
There must be a hint.
(King Il Woo finally broke silence.)
(Where will Haha go?)
Go. Come on.
- Seok Jin? - Go.
It's him.
I knew it. Three.
Come out.
(He removes the first stick.)
What if it doesn't come out?
(He removes the second stick.)
I did it.
(With King Seok Jin's tears, Haha returns to the team.)
Haha went back.
- Okay. - Okay.
Move over, Kwang Soo.
I'm so curious. I have no idea.
- You have to get this right. - I know.
- This one's easy. - Okay.
There are three sticks assigned as well.
"In the Joseon Dynasty period, one of the state examinations..."
You can get this right. You've written them.
I did?
I took it three times.
You've taken the state examination.
Right, he took three pairs of straw shoes and went to Hanyang.
Hanyang.
You've taken the state examination.
I studied with Yi Mong Ryong.
(How old is he then?)
"In the Joseon Dynasty period,"
"one of the state examinations was Hwanggamje."
"Hwanggamje"?
"It was held to commemorate the event..."
"where people put this fruit at the king's feet."
What is this fruit?
- Answer. - Answer.
"Hwanggam" is "Yellow persimmon", so it must be a tangerine.
It's a multiple-choice question. What's the number?
(It's a multiple-choice question.)
Three, Tangerine.
- What's the number? - Three, Tangerine.
(Incorrect)
Answer! One, Tangerine.
(He steals the answer.)
(No way.)
- Please say it again. - One, Tangerine.
Is it tangerine?
It's tangerine.
What do I do now? Do I ask for a hint?
Do I ask for a hint first?
Okay.
That's good.
Is either Jung Il Woo or Jeon So Min...
a king?
(Three questions revealed that So Min is a fake king.)
Is either Jung Il Woo or Jeon So Min a king?
(If the answer is yes, Il Woo is the real king.)
(If the answer is no, Seok Jin is the real king.)
Neither of them...
is a king.
(Neither of them is a king.)
(The real king is...)
(Seok Jin.)
Do I pick one out of three?
(Only one is the real king's royal seal.)
Okay.
It will either say "King" or "Nobody", right?
(The royal seal Seok Jin chose...)
(belonged to the real king.)
My time has come.
(I can't believe I am the real king.)
(He suddenly becomes majestic.)
Okay.
Jee Seok Jin.
(He goes to remove the real king's sticks.)
Okay. Jee Seok Jin.
(He removes 3 sticks at the same time.)
Okay.
(Jong Kook enters King Seok Jin's kingdom.)
I am saved.
Il Woo, do you have an excuse?
I don't want to die.
This kingdom is poor,
but the king is real.
It's just a poor kingdom.
Now you know the truth.
Here comes the last question.
I will get it right and leave.
The person who gets this question right will survive.
(The real king's civilians can sit still.)
This question is worth three sticks.
"In 'The Annals of the Joseon Dynasty'..."
"are records of a bird oil."
"It was a precious gift to the king from Pyeongan Province..."
"which was effective in treating skin diseases..."
"and various ailments."
"What is this bird?"
One, Flamingo.
Two, Pelican.
- What? - Did pelicans exist back then?
Three, Albatross.
Answer! One, Flamingo.
- Answer! - Answer!
(Haha gives it a try.)
(Will Haha get the answer right?)
Two, Pelican.
- Really? - I am right.
- Is he right? - I know I am right.
- Really? - All right!
(Pelican is the answer.)
You shouldn't have gotten it right. Now, you have to switch places.
- You have to switch places. - You have to switch places.
(He has to switch places with a civilian of another kingdom.)
(He is buffering.)
Haha, switch places with me!
- Switch places with me! - You have to switch places.
I don't mind the spilling water.
I want to wet my face with water.
- You have to switch places. - I want to get hit with water.
You should aim to pull out three sticks...
and have no water come out.
That's right. That's your only chance.
- Haha. - Haha.
Pick A Ra.
(She looks the saddest.)
- I will pick... - A Ra.
- Please. - A Ra, come to the paradise.
- I want to live. - Pull out three sticks.
- I want to live. - Three sticks.
- All right. - Three sticks.
- In 1, 2, 3. - Haha doesn't want water to spill.
(He removes the first stick.)
(A Ra needs the water to spill in order to escape.)
(Haha doesn't want water to spill.)
(Pouring out)
It only took one try.
I want to be hit with water. No, I want to be hit with water.
I want to be hit with water.
- Go, A Ra. Congratulations. - Il Woo.
Welcome.
Il Woo.
(Thus, the descendants said "Haha" whenever they were incredulous.)
- This is driving me crazy. - Let's now go...
to the platform of judgment.
(Current team status)
(Jae Seok and Yul have the treason rights.)
You are jealous, right?
Will You Be the King or Nobody?
Before the final judgment,
King So Min's Kingdom has five civilians,
which is the highest number.
We will now have the last treason time.
There is the treason time.
(Use treason time to choose one king to stand on the platform.)
Jae Seok and Yul have the treason right.
Move to the team you think has...
the real king.
Jae Seok, go first.
In one...
(What is Jae Seok's choice?)
My king.
(There is only one answer.)
(Seok Jin is the real king.)
Come here.
- You did it. - All right.
- All right. - He is wise.
- He is wise. - I will use my treason right.
Yul.
- I will use it. - We will win if he comes to us.
2, 3.
- My king. - Come here.
(Welcome to King Seok Jin's kingdom.)
- My king. - General Kwon Yul.
My king!
- My king! - General Kwon Yul.
The most number of civilians...
chose Seok Jin as the king.
- Please go up to the throne. - Okay.
- My king. - Follow me.
Let's hear a few words from our guests first.
It was nice to open 2019 with Running Man.
I had a fun time.
I received the energy of the king.
Happy New Year.
Please send a lot of love to "Haechi".
Thank you.
Will I be the king?
(Will I be the king?)
I was out of my mind!
(Two kingdoms that served pretenders are hit with a water bomb.)
My goodness.
(Splashing)
(Happy New Year.)
I am the king!
(We will work hard in the Year of the Golden Pig.)
(Roulette chose Jong Kook and Ji Hyo as the winning couple.)
(However, their partnership didn't last forever.)
(Monopoly)
(They have a showdown for the prize money.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo go against each other.)
(For the first time in the history of Running Man, )
(the two best members will compete against each other.)
(Champion versus Ace)
(A legendary match begins to monopolize the prize money.)
(No one backs down in this neck-and-neck match.)
(Champion versus Ace)
(Between the Ace and Champion, )
(who will be the final winner of the legendary match?)
(Ace versus Champion)