- Hello. - Hi.
Hi.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hi. - Hello. Good morning, everyone.
- Hello. - "Good morning, everyone."
Kwang Soo.
You were generalizing it for everyone.
- What? - "Generalizing".
- You're overgeneralizing it. - Yes.
- It can be a good morning for you. - It's a good morning for you.
but it might not be the case for others.
- That's right. He's right. - I want you to think about...
a neutral greeting for other people.
How am I supposed to respond?
- It's morning. - Mind your own business.
Besides, I watched the episode that...
- aired yesterday. - Okay, okay.
We were just using the restroom briefly.
I had no idea they would talk about prostate on a variety show.
(A prostate conversation made it to the show.)
(2 weeks ago, Jae Seok and Seok Jin went to the restroom.)
(When you get old, your prostate can be a problem.)
(Because Jong Kook was nosy, they talked about urology.)
That aired?
- Yes, that aired. - Listen.
- I was so surprised. - Really? It aired?
- My goodness, this is... - I was shocked when I heard it.
- It's all right. - It's not that.
- We can talk about prostate on TV. - Listen.
- It's a medical term. - Prostate...
- That's a medical term. - It's a medical term.
- I know that it's a medical term, - It's a medical term.
but Myung Soo talked about it once on TV for the first time.
- That's right. - This is what he said back then.
He said he could donate two meters of his prostate for me.
- After that... Yes. - Two meters?
You must start taking care of it at the age of 12.
Gosh, the prostate...
- We do learn about this at school. - That's right.
- Right. - We learn at school.
By the way, do you remember the slush fund?
- Yes. - Did your wife say anything?
(Viewers were curious about what happened after his mission.)
(Seok Jin did the Collateral Mission on everyone's behalf.)
(He had to give his wife the passcode...)
(to his slush fund account and show her the statement.)
(After giving it a lot of thought,)
(he decided not to try the mission.)
(He suspiciously gave up on the mission as if he had a slush fund.)
When she watched that part, she laughed out loud.
- She just laughed? - And she asked me a question.
She asked me if I really had a slush fund.
- So what did you say? - You did this again.
- I said, "Of course, I don't." - Seok Jin went like this.
(This is neither yes nor no.)
When I told her that, the corner of my mouth was shaking a little.
I could feel it shake a little, and my wife didn't see it.
- Now, she'd know. - She would know now.
- Right. She'll know now. - Seok Jin, say no now.
Actually, I even saw the balance of his secret account.
- Really? - My gosh.
- Hey. - You even saw his balance?
- Really? - I didn't see it on purpose.
- I bet he bragged about it. - Seok Jin.
It's the one I accidentally saw, right?
Exactly. How did you see it standing up? Your eyes must be good.
I was just standing there, and you were like this.
- So I saw it. - Right.
Since his eyes are bad, he increases the brightness on his phone.
Everyone can see it.
- Stop it. - Hey, Jong Kook.
- What did I do? - When he unlocks his phone,
he says. "3, 2, 5, and 6".
- That's what old men do. - Hey, punk. You're lying!
Don't old men do that?
- Hey. - That dachshund.
I'll get you a necklace strap for your phone.
- That's enough. - Necklace strap for phones?
- Dachshund, you stop it too. - A present for an old parent.
That dachshund.
- During the same mission, Haha... - That's right.
- I saw this one too. - Haha.
- I went to the restaurant. - He posted the photo.
- You did it? - He did post the photo.
- Yes. I made good on my promise. - Good job.
- That was so cool. - He really went.
But that restaurant was really busy.
- I was really nervous inside. - In your selfie,
it looked similar to your restaurant.
- "Your restaurant"? - Oh, I misspoke.
(It's a shocking comment from his business partner, Mr. Kim.)
There's a rift between them.
- That's also your restaurant too. - They're fighting.
This must disappoint him a lot.
Are you embarrassed that you own a barbecue restaurant?
- Are you that embarrassed? - No, no.
Calling it "your restaurant" was so shocking.
It's not that. I'm just used to calling it that.
- Right. Why didn't I tell you this? - What?
- You went on a trip... - Yes, yes.
- with In Sung and D.O. - That must've been a lot of work.
- Good work. - Great work.
What do you mean?
- I was on a trip for pleasure. - You were their butler.
Kwang Soo went on the trip too, but the article...
- only mentioned In Sung and D.O. - What are you saying?
- No, no. - But Kwang Soo,
you were carrying a lot compared to other guys.
What are you saying?
You were carrying a lot.
- I packed a lot of stuff. - Was that all yours?
- It was all mine. - It was all yours?
What did you do in Japan? Did you put on a show?
What show?
My goodness, you made a lot of money,
- but you're still stingy. - There he goes again.
(Did you go there to make more money?)
- Stop talking about money. - There he goes again.
He's talking about money again.
- That's not why I went. - This is Round Two.
I'm not that materialistic.
Did you do the Gundam Show this time?
(Was that the follow-up after the Bumblebee Show?)
I bet he asked for 50 cents.
(You're unbelievable.)
I drive an imported car.
(I'm not poor.)
(He brags about his car which makes him look cheaper.)
- He drives an imported car. - Listen.
I get it. You need more money for the gas.
- Kwang Soo's car... - To pay for the gas,
- you need more money. - I'm greedy over money.
- This is driving me crazy. - I'm so sick of it.
All right. You know that your fan-meet is coming up soon.
- Yes. - We have only two months left.
- We only have two months left? - Will we have enough time?
- We didn't even start. - The dance...
You're going to give out free merchandise...
to the fans who will be at the fan-meet.
- There's merchandise? - We'll have merchandise too?
- Is that so? - That's so interesting.
- This will be a gift, right? - That's right.
Since it's a project with our program's title,
we're going to make 3,000 shirts with our title on it.
- 3,000 shirts? - That many?
If we're making 3,000 shirts...
- Will we have 3,000 fans? - How many fans will come?
Will 3,000 fans come?
We'll prepare a space big enough...
- for 2,500 to 3,000 fans. - My goodness.
- Really? - That's a lot.
- It must be a huge place. - We're having that many fans?
- But that's too many. - That's a lot.
Today, we'll decide on a design for the Running Shirts.
We'll have to come up with a design?
It's Part Three of our project. It's Let's Make Merchandise Race.
Okay.
You will come up with your own design for the shirt.
We'll make 3,000 Running Shirts...
- with the design of the winner. - Really?
- I already have a design in mind. - What is it?
I'll go with the Avengers' theme.
And we'll put on the disguises again?
- He will be Groot. - There you have it.
(Kwang Soo will be Groot.)
- There you have it. - That's great.
Jong Kook will be the Hulk.
- Yes, there's the Hulk. - Jong Kook will be the Hulk.
Jong Kook is the Hulk.
And So Min will be...
Doctor Strange.
- Why? - Hey, he's a guy.
She shaves her chin too.
- She does? - She has a beard.
- She has a beard. - She shaves it.
Haha is Ant-Man.
- Ant-Man. He's the Ant-Man. - Okay.
(We found someone for Ant-Man.)
(He's the perfect guy for the role. No questions asked.)
- You're Ant-Man. - Why am I Ant-Man?
- He's the original Ant-Man. - Ant-Man.
- Why am I Ant-Man all of a sudden. - Ant-Man.
- You're Ant-Man. - That's perfect for you.
For your character, you don't even have to get smaller.
- Anyway... - You don't have to.
That's right.
We already call you Ant-Man...
when you're not here.
You can be Ant-Man.
(They already found out Ant-Man's identity.)
Before we start today's race, we'll give you 30 minutes...
- to draw your own designs. - That's great.
- I'm already done with mine. - You'll take turns...
- to present your designs. - I already have mine.
(This is the Running T-Shirt.)
These are the shirts for our merchandise.
Hey, these are basketball jerseys.
(They can draw their own design in the middle.)
- What should I draw? - I don't know what to draw.
Are there other characters except for the Avengers?
I need someone for Seok Jin.
- Yondu is the best one I have. - I think Yondu will be funny.
Jae Seok, I want to be Captain Marvel.
Captain Marvel?
I haven't watched "The Avengers" yet.
(Feeling left out)
("Kwang Soo's 'Inseparable Bros' Competes Against 'The Avengers'")
- I can't follow the conversation. - Oh, right.
- Make Ji Hyo Gamora. - Right.
Gosh, Black Widow is so pretty.
I guess you all liked that movie.
I guess it was that fun to watch.
(Clenching his teeth)
- I know that it was a fun movie. - Hey, Haha even cried.
Haha cried even.
You should draw one for your movie, "Inseparable Bros".
Yes, you should do that. What do you think?
That's lamer.
Why don't you put the can in your chest?
- Why would I do that? - People can drop 10-cent coins.
(You like money.)
He's all about money.
I'm all for having a new character,
- but this is not that cool. - Go with Greedy Millipede.
- Greedy Millipede? Seriously? - My gosh, Greedy Millipede.
- That's a great one. - Listen.
Make everything about insects.
Insects?
(What have I done wrong?)
That's right. That one is cool.
I won't add perspective to my drawing for now.
- Hold on. What is it? - Is that...
- What is that? - What is that?
This is Captain America.
- That's Captain America? - Yes.
(It's a simplified version of it.)
Isn't that Anpanman?
- This is Captain America. - That's totally Anpanman.
He'd be placed last...
- even among elementary school kids. - That's so true.
I would believe it someone says that Ji Ho drew this.
Ji Ho is better than me.
This is Captain America.
I want to go with Sherlock Holmes.
- Sherlock Holmes? - Yes.
- You'll be Sherlock Holmes? - Yes.
Why?
What?
It's a project I couldn't complete.
I see. What kind of project was it?
- There he goes again. - I'm sure you know, punk.
- Seok Jin... - I'm sure...
- you know what I mean. - He's getting mad now.
Why do you ask when you know what it is?
You're annoying me.
(Why do you ask when you know what it is? You're annoying me.)
- He's angry now. - Why are you getting mad?
- You just got mad, right? - Seok Jin is mad.
- He got angry. - This is nothing to be mad about.
- He's mad. - I'm not mad.
- Are you sure? - He asked me when he knew. I got...
I almost got angry.
(I got... I almost got angry.)
- You're not angry? - I'm glad you're not angry.
(I'll tease him again later.)
You're good. Jong Kook, you're good at drawing Jigsaw.
It really looks like Jigsaw.
You'll present in five minutes.
(His drawing is high quality when it doesn't have to be.)
I'm ready. I'm done with mine.
- I'm done. - Take turns to present now.
- Okay. - Shall we start?
Mine is very simple.
- Is it scary? - Let me see.
- All right. - What's that?
- Mine is very simple. - Everyone is bald.
2019, 9 Years of Running Man.
I thought about people who wore undershirts.
Let me tell you who it is.
There's this guy, the Beast in "Kung Fu Hustle".
- That's right. - I know who it is.
(The Beast from "Kung Fu Hustle")
- I know him. - We'll dress up like him.
- That guy from the movie? - That's right.
Everyone will be dressed up as the Beast.
- That's cute. This is fun. - And I'll wear a suit...
like Stephen Chow.
I'll stand in the front while looking cool. Behind me,
- That sounds fun. - you'll wear the undershirts.
You'll be running to the fans in slow motion like this.
- Okay, I got what you mean. - I got it.
- Mine is simple. - Great, great.
- I'll make mine simple. - This is funny.
Should I go next?
In my drawing, Sherlock Holmes...
is looking for culprits with his sharp eyes.
He has profound detective skills and is very observant.
Around Sherlock Holmes,
- there are many... - Why are your arms uneven?
- Which ones? - Sherlock's arms.
I guess he's right-handed.
- Is he Wreck-It Ralph? - No.
- Is it Wreck-It Ralph? - No, it's not.
No, my drawing is just off.
Please be understanding.
Sherlock Holmes...
- I want to do... - There are... Let me finish.
- just one thing. Can I do it? - What is it?
(Booing)
Hey!
(The audience disapproves of his lengthy and boring storyline.)
I'm...
I only introduced my character. You can't disapprove of it yet.
If I had eggs, I would've thrown them at you.
- I would've done that. - I only introduced my character.
How could you do that?
What's the character on the far left?
- This one? - Yes.
This is a dachshund.
- What? - It's a dachshund.
(He was inspired by Haha for this dachshund character.)
Is that from "Cabbage Guru and Radish Guru"?
Isn't that Xuanzang?
(His drawing flusters even him.)
- It's a dachshund. - A dachshund.
- Please be understanding. - I thought that it was you.
And this one is a chicken.
Lee Kwang Soo.
- I'm a chicken? - You'll be dressed up as a chicken.
He'll hold an umbrella like the light card.
- A chicken will do that? - A chicken.
How are they related?
It's just my imagination.
- You're not that imaginative. - It's just my imagination.
- You have a poor imagination. - Yes, you're terrible.
Your imagination is lacking.
What do you mean?
- Why doesn't he hold a can? - No, no.
(Since it's Kwang Soo, why doesn't he hold a can?)
Why does Haha keep bringing up the can?
- That's not a bad idea. - Why does he keep bringing that up?
Why do you keep mentioning the can and 50 cents?
Hold on. That's a great idea.
Kwang Soo will hold a can instead of an umbrella.
- By the way, overall... - Okay.
I'm sorry to say this during your presentation.
But your design doesn't come together as a whole.
It's all over the place.
- Mine isn't related at all. - Why not?
- They are culprits from everywhere. - Why?
- It's just my idea. - The viewers have to relate to it.
It doesn't matter if we can relate to it or not.
(His tactic of using the viewers makes a compelling case.)
Let's keep your idea for now.
Come on. How could you do this to me?
- Did you hear him? - "How could you..."
What do you mean by that?
(What happened to his confidence?)
And I'll be Sharp Sherlock Holmes.
Everyone...
(Yawning)
(Hitting)
That really hurts.
(Seok Jin was never violent.)
(He attacks Haha with his paper.)
- He really hit Haha. - He really hit Haha.
He really hit Haha.
- He's really angry. - He really hit Haha.
I'm sorry. I was going to hit your face with this.
I'm sorry.
- He really got mad. - I'll be...
I will be really sharp.
- It will be obvious... - He did get angry, right?
- Definitely. - A sharp detective...
I'm not angry.
(He's not angry yet.)
Why would I be angry at this hour?
All right. I will be...
You can never get angry.
- I will be... - I've known him for 20 years.
I've never seen him get mad.
That jerk.
(He gives up.)
- That was... - Didn't he say that before?
I told you, didn't I?
I told you that he curses at me when he gets mad.
- That's what he said before. - Yes.
My gosh, I'm so livid.
I wasn't angry.
- I have a temper. - He cursed at me. He wasn't mad.
(He's not angry yet. He only cursed to show they're friendly.)
- Okay. I'll stop here. - That's it.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Make it simple. - Look at his drawing.
("The Avengers: Captain Yumerica")
You can tell from my drawing that...
- Which one is me? - there's Captain Yumerica.
- "Yumerica"? - "Yumerica"?
It's just an old man.
- Isn't that Anpanman? - Is that necessary?
These are the characters that fit...
- our characters. - That's true.
Who's that man in a hanbok?
(Who is this?)
(He looks charismatic with an eye patch on.)
This is...
Gung Ye.
Gung Ye?
This is Gung Ye.
(Why is he there?)
- It's a bit... - Why is he there?
(What does he have to do with this?)
- Why is Gung Ye there? - I was going to draw Nick Fury.
- But I wanted something... - Right.
more humorous in this.
- He's detailed. - Right.
As you all know,
we need to help Seok Jin become a bit more famous.
I know...
(Jae Seok wants to make him into a bigger star.)
I know it doesn't fit my theme, but I chose Gung Ye.
Why me, though?
I know.
- He's similar to Nick Fury. - I don't want to read minds.
And this is Yondu.
It'll be So Min.
Yondu. He controls his arrow.
- He's cool. - Yondu.
- He comes even cooler. - I believe...
So Min will be able to play him well.
- Is he completely blue? - Yes.
He is.
- He's blue. - I see.
This is a collaboration between the Avengers and Gung Ye.
I strongly recommend this.
("Avengers: Om Mani Padme Hum")
(This is Ant-Man.)
He draws well.
For mine, I will be standing in the middle.
I will be holding a rod, and there will be a Jigsaw family.
(A Jigsaw family?)
("The Tiger Who Subdues Jigsaws")
Jong Kook, it doesn't look...
- like you. - It's me.
What's the rod for?
- What? - What's the rod for?
I need to hit them.
- The Jigsaws. - I see.
This is the Jigsaw family.
- This is Jae Seok. - He draws well.
- This is Jae Seok. - You're good.
And this is So Min.
- Really? - She has short hair.
This is Kwang Soo. He's bald.
I see.
- You have some hair on the side. - Okay.
- Can you make me completely bald? - No.
- No? - We need that bit of hair.
- We need it. - He's a tall one.
This is Ji Hyo.
- Haha has reggae hair. - I see.
- He's reggae Jigsaw. - Reggae.
- This is... - That one's riding a bicycle.
Seok Jin.
- This is Seok Jin. - What?
I forgot Se Chan.
Where am I?
- Wait. Where's me? - Hold on.
I forgot about you.
(He feels betrayed.)
- It's scary. - Tell him that he's the bicycle.
Se Chan, you're the bicycle.
- That's me? - Yes.
- That's me? - You're the bicycle.
- I'm the bicycle? - Yes.
- Your teeth protrude. - Right.
He's the bicycle. And here's Seok Jin.
He's riding me?
I like this. It looks cool.
I think that will be nice.
- All right. - For my design,
- I'll be surrounded... - What is that?
by the staff members.
- Are we the staff? - Are you...
- Are you the star? - Yes, I am.
I'll have my legs crossed in this drawing.
Jae Seok is my makeup artist.
- That's good. - Me?
- Okay. - This is his back.
- That's his back? - Is my face not shown?
Yes, it's his back.
Seok Jin is my manager.
This will be it.
(He's considerate.)
It's his eye.
- That's it? - And his nose.
- That's it? - Yes, this much.
(His nose is too big.)
- 30 percent of his face is shown. - He's still in it.
Where's Haha?
He's here. He's Ant-Man.
- All of a sudden? - Suddenly?
(He's pretty much a dot.)
Okay.
I really love that character.
- It suits him. - So...
Give me a sketchbook. Let me draw something in a hurry.
- No. - I can't stand this.
He's a dot.
- Okay. - He'll be small.
("A Day of a Prince")
I was inspired by Kwang Soo's drawing.
We will be standing in a line in the order of our age.
- We will be facing the rear. - And then?
And this much of my face will be seen.
What I want to portray is...
that everyone...
can be like us.
- Our faces? - When we wear it?
Yes.
I was inspired to draw this.
That's creative.
By the way, it shouldn't have been that difficult...
to line the feet when you were drawing this.
(The line is ascending.)
- It's rising. - Their feet became smaller.
Is Haha the smallest?
- I see. - Why me?
(Ji Hyo is a true believer of realism.)
- It just happened to be so. - He's Ant-Man, you see.
You're right.
- It'll be simple. - It is.
- Who's next? - Go, So Min.
Yours is colorful.
Yes, it is.
- What is that? - This is...
- What is that? - Tinky-Winky?
This is...
("The Seven Colors of Running Man")
This is like how when you go to the clubs,
there are clothes that glow in the dark.
They have purple lights at karaoke.
Yes, I want to do that to you guys.
I want them to wear tights or get painted in these colors.
Body painting?
- This is crazy. - I always say this,
- but we can't let her do this. - I know.
- We can't allow her to do that. - I'll stop her at all costs.
- She can't do that. - I will stop her.
- That's risky. - Body painting?
It will be pitch-dark.
I will receive the spotlight.
You will surround me in rainbow colors...
with body paint or tights.
Since navy is similar to blue,
Kwang Soo will just wear black tights.
(Kwang Soo will wear black tights.)
(Kwang Soo)
Hold on. If I'm wearing black in the dark,
I will be invisible.
You can say that.
- You'll be... - There's no black glow-in-the-dark.
Right. Just consider yourself a part of the background.
I'm not sure about this.
Okay.
Isn't it pretty?
("The Seven Colors of Running Man", Annoyingness,)
Mine is cute so that...
- you will all like it. - What?
- It is adorable. - This was my original drawing.
It's cute.
But after seeing your drawings, I got a bit upset.
- Why? - I was nothing but a dot.
- No, you're Ant-Man. - You're Ant-Man.
- Come on. - So...
- this is my new drawing. - What is it?
(What could it be?)
("I Sometimes Shed Tears")
In this drawing,
I will be the only one looking good in the center.
Do you remember those photoshopped photos...
of you all with Se Chan?
I will use those photoshopped faces.
- No. - I will use them.
Your original faces won't be in this.
- It's the worst. - "I don't care who it is."
The order doesn't matter to me.
- That's terrible. - However,
Kwang Soo won't even have a photoshopped picture.
- It will just be his neck. - That's my body?
(It will just be his neck.)
(He can't believe it.)
- Why is he doing this? - This is too much.
In case you guys don't like this,
I drew myself only.
- It's... - You don't look like that.
- We've been in this for 10 years. - Why are you crying?
We've received so much love...
- for the past 10 years. - You're the only one in it?
Since I'm so thankful,
I'll pose with teary eyes and a smile.
- Like this. - That's disgusting.
- Like this. - That's terrible.
(Dear fans, I'm always grateful for you.)
Ma'am!
What do bring up my mom suddenly?
(Is that Haha's mother?)
- That's Haha's mom! - How is it?
- That's Haha's mom! - I'll have teary eyes.
- You know what this is, right? - I do know.
- I'll be emotional. - I get it.
- And... - What's behind you?
you will all be dots.
You're just several of these countless dots.
- So we don't come out? - I'm the only one visible.
It'll be 1 of these 2.
We're all dots.
He's the only one in his drawings.
("I Sometimes Shed Tears")
(The Running T-Shirts will be chosen by the winner.)
Today will be part three of Nine Years of Running Man,
Burdensome Race.
2 individuals will make a team. There will be 4 teams in total.
Okay.
The team with the most R Money wins.
Among the 2 members, only 1 will be the final winner.
Two teams with the lowest rank will be penalized.
There's a penalty?
- What is it? - What's the penalty?
This is the back side of the merchandise.
(On the back side of the Running T-Shirt,)
(the losers will be drawn on the bottom.)
The losers will be drawn on the bottom part.
They will be crushed by the bottom.
If you sit, the two members won't be seen.
Oh, no.
- It's the worst. - Only two?
That must feel terrible.
Goodness.
The mission fund is crucial.
You will be given either 30 dollars...
or the chance to throw a die.
You will be given the amount shown on the die.
If you get a 6, you'll be given 60 dollars.
If you don't want to throw it,
- you'll be given 30 dollars. - All right.
We will throw it.
However, if you get a three,
- you won't be getting any. - What?
(Getting a 3 means you won't receive any money.)
- We should avoid that. - We should.
- We should avoid getting it. - Yes.
- We shouldn't get it. - And one too.
We can get 10 or 20 dollars.
- Right. - Let's do it.
Who'll throw a die first?
I will.
All right. Sorry, we're booked.
(Someone else has booked to throw the die already.)
What?
- Here. - Is it for me? Thank you.
It was booked.
- The die was booked? - Yes.
(He can't reserve on the spot.)
Se Chan, what will you choose?
I will throw the die.
- We need to risk it. - Yes.
- There's 4, 5, and 6. - Right.
- Let's go! - Let's go.
(Se Chan opts for the die instead of 30 dollars.)
- Let's see. - Please. It's a high number!
(He just needs to avoid getting a 3 or lower.)
(Getting a 6 will be the best.)
If you get a three, you won't be getting any.
(He will receive no money.)
(The die rolls and lands on 3.)
You're getting no money!
(They show different emotions.)
- He gets nothing! - Nice shot!
- Nice shot! - It's possible to get a three.
- Nice shot. - Yes!
He failed!
I got a three?
I shouldn't team up with him.
I doubt another three would come out after that round.
The possibility is extremely low.
It won't come out.
That's impossible.
- He should get 3 or 1. - 1 is good too.
(He slams the die.)
- What? - That was cool.
(Give me a 6!)
(He's my role model.)
(Will his powerful slamming reap fruits?)
Six!
(He gets a 6!)
- Do it again. - Six!
- Do it again. - That doesn't count.
- You can't slam it. - Why again?
- You can't do that. - You should've thrown it.
- What game is he playing? - You slammed it.
- You shouldn't do that. - It's just my style.
- You shouldn't do that. - You should throw it.
- It looked cool. - Seok Jin.
Young fans will watch this and mimic you.
- That's right. - It's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
- They could injure their faces. - It's too aggressive.
- Why isn't this allowed? - It's too aggressive.
My child gets scolded for throwing things too.
This is rolling.
- What you did was slamming. - Gosh.
It's because...
- I got a six. - Give him a round of applause.
(They applaud him for not getting mad.)
Let's laugh it off!
- Smile! - Move on!
- Laugh it off. - Laugh it off.
- Laugh it off. - Okay, okay.
- I'll throw it. - Okay.
- What was that? - This is my style.
- It's your style? - Yes.
(Will he get a 6?)
- 1! - 1! This is acceptable.
(He gets a 1.)
(Hold on.)
- This is fun. - It is.
That was cute.
The kids will mimic me again.
- They will mimic me. - Let them!
- That was cute. - Laugh it off.
Seok Jin will get 10 dollars.
How could you allow this and not the other one?
(Seok Jin gets 10 dollars.)
Are you throwing it?
I'm throwing it, of course.
3. 3. It's a 3.
1. 1. 3. 3.
(What will it be?)
3. 3.
- 3. - 60 dollars!
(Jae Seok gets 60 dollars.)
(I thought I was unlucky.)
- The die hit something. - 60 dollars.
- He got a six. - I know.
Hold on. Who said it was your turn?
(Haha picks on him.)
- No one. - You're right.
(No one chose him to go next.)
- Wait. - No one.
- No one said you could go next. - I volunteered.
- Listen. - I wanted to go next.
- There's an order to this. - Give it to me.
- I really wanted to go next. - I wanted to do it from the start.
- Me too. - Get it from him!
- Get it! - No.
- This doesn't count. - This doesn't.
(They take away the 60 dollars.)
Why did you go first?
- This doesn't count. - Who wants to go next?
They stole the money from me!
- Who wants to go next? - Hey!
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's go this way. - Hold on.
- We should do that. - Ji Hyo.
- Haha. - I'm flabbergasted.
- Okay. - Yes.
- Okay. - I'm very thankful...
that Jong Kook didn't get involved.
You know I don't like unnatural things.
(He's firm in his preference.)
I don't care if he gets 60 dollars.
- Here we go. - Okay.
3. 3. What was that? 3.
- He rolled it. - It's a three.
(He's surprised by this new tactic.)
It's a three.
Okay!
(Haha gets a 5.)
- Okay! - You shouldn't have rolled it.
- You shouldn't have rolled it. - You should've tossed it.
You shouldn't have rolled it.
Didn't you learn anything from what Seok Jin did?
- Gosh. - I'm not supposed...
- to roll a die? - You should toss it.
Isn't the phrase, "roll a die"?
You should toss it.
My gosh.
Be thankful you're not eliminated.
It's "toss a die"?
Who rolls a die? You toss it.
(He's flabbergasted.)
I thought you didn't like anything unnatural?
- Listen. - No, no.
- That's what he said. - This is right
- You don't roll a die. - You do roll...
- a die. Fine. - You toss a die.
- I'll go again later. - You toss it.
- Who's next? - Do I toss it like this?
- Yes. - Upwards, right?
Don't toss it too high.
- Yes. That was perfect. - That's good.
Please make it be a 3.
- It's a three. - No, no.
This is a three.
- No, no. Please no. - It's rolling for so long.
- This is a three. - What?
- What? - When will it stop?
(What is the number?)
(After rolling for a long time, it stops at a 1.)
(Why did it have to be a 1?)
Gosh, that was nerve-racking.
It's not a big difference with mine.
Be serious this time.
I'll go next.
Toss the die!
I'll toss it. Here I go!
(He tosses it like he's supposed to.)
(Will he be able to get a 6 like he did before?)
(He gets a 1.)
(Everyone is happy.)
I no longer feel lonely!
- Nice. - It could've been better...
to just ask for 30 dollars.
You're right.
- 30 dollars is better. - I know.
- Here. - Me?
- Toss the die! - Toss the die!
(Toss it, don't roll it.)
(Knowing that she's lucky, she decides to do it.)
It rolls a lot.
(Will her luckiness work its charm this time as well?)
(No way!)
(What did she get?)
- 1, please. - 1!
(Ji Hyo also gets a 1.)
- Everyone's getting a 1. - I know.
What's going on? How is this possible?
- Okay. - It's either 1 or 0.
(Se Chan is the only one without any money.)
But you see, it's about time for a 4, 5, or 6.
- Right. - It's about time.
We've had five 1s so far.
- Right? - Just throw it.
- Throw it. - If he opts for receiving...
three dollars, then he's really greedy...
- about money. - Okay.
- Let's go. - I'm not greedy about money.
- Okay, okay. - I'm going to toss it.
Just toss it so you won't look like a Greedy Millipede.
That's not why, but I'll toss it.
- I'm tossing it. - You should.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Good. He's really tossing it.
I should be getting a four.
It's too low.
(The Greedy Millipede...)
(makes a timid toss.)
I'm not alone. I'm not alone.
Okay!
(He gets a 3.)
- Okay! - Okay!
Okay, Jae Seok!
- That's amazing. - I'm not alone.
I'm not alone.
It's just like him to get that. It's fascinating.
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- He got a three. - How is this possible?
Everyone else will get a 4, 5, or 6.
- Okay! - This is unbelievable.
Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
- I'd like 30 dollars. - What?
(He doesn't hesitate.)
- What is this? - He didn't toss it?
- What are you doing? - What is this?
Okay!
What is this?
(Haha suddenly barges in.)
- Hey, Haha. - I'd like 30 dollars too.
(You can't do that.)
- What are you doing? - You can't do that.
- You already tossed it once. - You can't do that.
- You already did it. - You did it.
- You did it once. - Why can't I get 30 dollars?
- You already did it. - You did it once.
They can't do this to Jong Kook, so they're doing this to me!
- You can't do that. - You've already done it once.
Is there such a rule?
You already tossed it once.
- Jong Kook didn't start at all. - I didn't start, but you did.
I thought you hated anything unnatural.
This isn't unnatural.
- Is there such a rule? - I didn't toss the die at all.
- But you did. - So is there a rule?
- Of course. - Okay.
Sit down.
Okay.
- Toss the die! - Toss the die!
- Can he use just one hand? - Of course.
[VIU Ver] SBS E454 Running Man
"Let's Make Merchandise Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(He gets a 1.)
Darn it!
(He throws a fit.)
(How could I get a 1?)
- This is so irritating. - Wait.
(Jong Kook is happy with this natural outcome.)
- I'm so vexed. - Just laugh it off.
- At least you got a 1. - I feel irritated.
You at least got 10 dollars.
- You should be grateful. - All right.
Now, we will start the race. Like I said,
- it's two members per team. - Okay.
- You will pick out spoons. - Your teammate is important.
Two members will become a team.
- We should team up with Jong Kook. - We should.
- We should. - Okay.
- We have to team up with him. - Okay, it's Jong Kook.
You and I have to split up.
- We need to split up. - Or we're doomed.
All right, Seok Jin.
- It's matching colors, right? - Yes.
It's the same color. All right.
(Jong Kook picks out his spoon.)
- Okay. - I'm done.
Let's start with Seok Jin.
(Members with the same color will become a team.)
- Red. - Red.
(Seok Jin's spoon is red.)
- Jong Kook. - I hope it's not red.
- Is it red? - It is.
(Jong Kook's spoon is red.)
What?
(Jong Kook is teamed up with Seok Jin.)
- Oh, no. - We're a team!
Seriously.
We needed him.
- He was our last hope. - This is driving me crazy.
But still...
What color is yours?
(Ji Hyo's spoon is...)
- Blue. - Blue. Let's go this way.
- This is important. - Don't pick blue.
- All right. - 1, 2, 3.
- It's green. - It's green?
- Kwang Soo shouldn't pick green. - So Min.
- They have no money. - Okay, show us.
- 1, 2, 3. - What is it?
- It's yellow. - Hold on.
- Then what about you? - Those two are...
- No! Not Kwang Soo! - No!
- Goodness. - Oh, no.
This will be fun.
All right. Let's see.
1, 2, 3.
(Will he successfully avoid Se Chan who has no money?)
(Haha's spoon is...)
- Green. All right. - Okay!
Okay! 10 dollars! Okay!
Ant-Man!
- Now... - Thank you so much.
- Ji Hyo hasn't been teamed up yet. - Neither did So Min.
- Ji Hyo and So Min. - I just...
I just need to avoid zero dollars.
I really want to team up with Jae Seok.
Me too.
- Jae Seok. - I want to team up with him.
- Please. - Step back. One.
- Kwang Soo, no. - Please, Jae Seok.
1, 2, 3.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo's spoons are...)
(blue and yellow, respectively.)
- Ji Hyo. Three. - What is this?
(She's relieved that it's not Kwang Soo.)
(I can't believe I'm partnered up with the Greedy Millipede.)
Goodness, this is it.
You got 10 dollars, So Min.
- Okay. - We have 40 dollars.
I know we have 40 dollars, but let's be clear.
30 dollars is mine.
- Hey, we're a team. - You know that, right?
- I have 30, and you have 10. - We're a team.
It's 20 dollars and 40 dollars.
It's a 10-dollar difference.
Shouldn't you help us out a little?
- This is too little. - We have 10 dollars in total.
Then you should've made a wiser decision.
(They have nothing to say.)
- He's right. - He's totally right.
Take one each.
- "Team's Land Price"? - "Team's Land Price"?
- "Team's Land Price"? - What is this?
(What could this be?)
For today's Burdensome Race, you need to pick...
- the right land to win. - Really?
Your decision is what counts.
Each team is given two pieces of land each...
of 10, 20, and 30 dollars.
You can freely place the 7 gold bars and 2 duds...
on that board.
After every round,
the winning team can see two of the opposing team's.
The second place team can open one of them.
If you pay the price and purchase their land,
you will acquire their gold bars.
However, if you choose a dud,
you will have to hand over one of your gold bars to them.
(They need to pay them.)
- We should allocate them well. - It is of the utmost importance...
- where you put them. - You're right.
1 gold bar is worth 50 dollars.
- 50 dollars? - The value is high.
After the final mission, the team with the most R Money will win.
All teams will get 2 of each, 1 gold bar for 1 person.
- That's great. - We have money.
That is money.
- No, wait up. - What?
- We're on the same team. - I know that.
Come on!
(He explodes.)
I'm sick of this. Wait.
- We're on the same team! - I know that, so let me hold them.
It's exhausting to be on a team with So Min.
- You can have one each. - You can have one each.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors. Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Okay.
What?
You have to spend your energy somewhere else other than games...
when you play with So Min.
He took it without even asking me.
Stop it! I was talking to myself.
(Jae Seok explodes too.)
Come on now.
Each team can discuss now,
- and place them cautiously. - Okay.
This is crazy.
Where should I put them?
So we have to anticipate where they will ask us to open,
and put duds in there.
You choose.
- First, 20 dollars. - 20 dollars.
(She places 1 gold bar on the 20-dollar land.)
This is where they won't open.
- What if we... - Or...
why don't we put 2 duds on the 30-dollar land?
They won't expect us to put both of them on here.
- Right. - Right?
But putting them in one place is dangerous.
You are a risk-taker.
- Let's put them in one place. - No.
Ji Hyo, let's put them together.
- You already know... - It's dangerous.
how good it feels when they pick an empty one.
- Don't you? - It's too dangerous.
- Let's do it. - Jae Seok.
- How about we put all of them here? - No.
I was afraid you might do that.
- I feel suffocated now. - No.
- It gives me stress... - No.
- just thinking about these. - No.
No, Jae Seok. Just hold on.
Ji Hyo, listen to me.
(They relocate the gold bars and duds...)
(thanks to Ji Hyo's rationality.)
It'll be hit or miss.
- How about one for each? - How about...
No.
Why don't we divide them by 6 and 1 gold bars?
6 and 1? Okay.
But don't you think it's risky?
5 and 2 sounds safer.
That sounds safer?
(It's not that safe.)
It's safer than 6 and 1.
So 6 and 1.
- 1 for number 2? - 1 for number 2.
(They put six gold bars in one place.)
And then what?
- How about number 4? - 20 dollars in number 4?
(They're thinking about where to put the rest 6.)
- How about here? - Good.
Isn't this too dangerous?
(It is a bit risky.)
Should we put just five of them?
- Should we put all of them here? - Yes. Let's do it.
(Kwang Soo is more of a risk-taker.)
If a team chooses that, they'll win.
What should we do?
Take them apart.
(Let's take them apart.)
We were being hasty. I'm sorry.
(His timidness surpassed his character of risk-taker.)
I don't know anymore.
You choose yourself.
Are they reflected on that car?
Something is reflected on it.
(You can barely see them.)
Right.
(Why are they watching at us right now?)
Wait.
(They cover with their bodies after noticing.)
Are you allowed to peek through the reflection?
- I wasn't trying to peek, - Isn't that cheating?
it just showed up on me.
Jae Seok.
Ji Hyo's eyes are so clear...
that we can see yours through the reflection in her eyes.
She likes it.
So Min.
Your skin is so transparent that yours is reflecting on it.
No.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
I can't see anything because your eyes seem muddy.
(I can't see anything because your eyes seem muddy.)
(Suppressing anger)
How about this?
I'll shake my hand up and down and you say, "Stop!"
What do you think?
Because when you're confused...
- Okay, I won't look. - Yes, don't look.
That's a simple strategy.
Say, "Stop."
(It's a manual system.)
- Stop. - Haha.
That's awesome. Let's put one here.
Yes.
I like it because it's simple.
Let's put ourselves in their shoes.
Let's say we choose another team's number.
Shouldn't we put a dud in the 10-dollar land?
If they open a dud with 10 dollars,
they have to give us a gold bar.
- Okay, let's do that. - Yes.
Because 10 dollars...
- is nothing. - It's nothing.
There's no pressure in choosing it.
Good.
Where should we put this dud?
How about the 20 dollar-land?
I think the 30-dollar land is the better choice.
Right.
If they pay 30 dollars, they have a better chance...
- of choosing number 6. - Right. Number 6.
- They would choose number 6. - Yes, number 6.
If they...
(He dropped a gold bar sticker while he was talking.)
Are you going to keep dropping these gold bars?
(Stop being so clumsy.)
- Hey. - What?
Hold on to them.
You're younger than me, why am I doing all the work?
I'm holding these.
- Why am I... - Hold on to it.
(He's very docile.)
- We're good. - We're good.
(It feels like it should be the other way around.)
Placement is finished.
Okay.
- We just don't have to be the last. - Right.
We just have to avoid being drawn on the bottom part.
I watched you before,
and you were doing everything Jong Kook told you to.
- That's not true. - He suggested some ideas.
Seok Jin looked like a parrot on Jong Kook's shoulder.
- That's not true. - You were just copying him.
- He's like a little brother to me. - You were talking a lot.
I was leading this team.
I'm planning to.
(We'll see, Seok Jin.)
I'll let him lead our team,
- and hold him responsible later. - Sure.
- That's better. - That sounds scary.
- That sounds scarier. - It's better that way.
- All teams can set off now. - Let's go.
- Should we sit by teams? - Yes, we should.
(Let's go start the mission.)
Can I ask you something?
Did anyone put everything in one place?
- Anyone? - You can't do it that way.
- I would never do that. - Who would do that?
- You did, didn't you? - Right. You put them in one place.
- Okay. - They took the bait.
I think...
Kwang Soo and So Min put everything in one place.
No, because our goal...
- was to avoid being the last. - That was our goal.
I think they put everything in number one.
(Coughing)
(The moment he mentioned number 1,)
(she started coughing.)
- Wait. - Why are you coughing?
- This is bad timing. - I'm not...
- What's going on? - It's nothing.
Why are you coughing now?
- It's either number 1 or 2. - Right.
They're flustered.
(Did they really put the gold bars in one place?)
It's just a slight cold.
Ji Hyo's face is actually smaller than So Min's.
(He suddenly talks about the fact about their faces.)
(And So Min tries to make her face look smaller.)
So Min is sitting closer to you.
Right. That would be the reason.
Seok Jin, your face looks way smaller than Kwang Soo's.
I do have a small face.
It's the size of an idol star.
Is your face as small as an idol star's?
- The style of an idol star? - No, an idol's look.
I have an idol's look.
Looks like you'll be dead soon.
(He puts an end to Seok Jin's absurd remarks.)
Jong Kook!
Hey!
I'm really going to hurt you soon.
He has a sad look.
- Looks like he'll be dead someday. - That sounds better.
How does that sound better?
- Still, he omitted "soon". - Seok Jin.
- Come on. - Hey, you brat.
How does that sound better?
You couldn't say anything to Jong Kook,
- and you're blaming me? - Why are you blaming him?
- You punk. - He's upset at Jong Kook.
What did I do?
(You little...)
He has anger issues.
- It's just me. - He has anger issues.
- Seok Jin. - You two are going to...
He's flustered.
You two are going to have juniors one day.
You have to be strict when you have to.
I wasn't able to do that.
- You have to when needed. - Who would you...
scold in order if you could?
In the future.
He's number one.
- Jae Seok? - Jae Seok?
- Then he's number two. - Jong Kook?
Yes, he should be next.
(Jong Kook is staring at Seok Jin.)
- And... - Look me in the eye and tell me.
(Don't be so frightened.)
I saw that his pupils were trembling.
(I can't even be in a staring contest against him.)
It looked like Jong Kook was sitting over here.
That was a genuine reaction.
I feel sorry for him.
What song are we going to choose for the couple's performance?
- The disco dance? - No.
(Jae Seok and Haha have to put on a couple performance.)
Is any kind of music okay?
And we can either just sing or dance, right?
- Are we allowed to... - Why don't you two do that?
get a song composed by a songwriter?
- That'd be great. - Right.
That's going to be awesome.
- Do you want me to write you one? - You?
- I'll write you one. - Why don't you write some checks?
(Don't write a song, write a check.)
- Please. - Hey,
I'll write you a song.
He said, "Write a check."
- I apologize. - I'll write you a song.
I already have a few songs I wrote.
- You wrote songs? - Yes.
(Did I mishear?)
- Why would you write songs? - Because...
I thought I'd need them someday.
They're melodies that came into my head at 2am.
But you go to bed early.
- You go to bed early. - You go to bed at 10pm.
Sometimes I wake up at that time.
So I wrote them.
- To go to the bathroom? - Yes.
Pee goes squirt, squirt Pee goes squirt, squirt
(Pee goes squirt, squirt Pee goes squirt, squirt)
(It's a song he wrote when he was going to the bathroom at 2am.)
I have to pee
Fart goes poop, poop Fart goes poop, poop
You're old enough not to say "Pee goes squirt, squirt."
Pee goes squirt, squirt
My prostate, stay healthy
(Stay healthy, Jae Seok's prostate.)
Stay healthy all the way
(The song was written to wish men's prostates to stay healthy.)
- That was... - "My prostate, stay healthy."
That was the best one among all the songs you wrote.
Soft and dry
- Let's be soft and dry today - Let's be soft and dry today
Let's be soft and dry today
(He was expressing his wish of not getting wet.)
It's really addictive.
- Let's be soft and dry today - Let's be soft and dry today
I struggled with that song for two months.
I kept singing it in my head.
- It should be banned for SAT. - Right.
I'll come up with a melody with those lyrics.
It's going to be an EDM song.
Like this.
How does an EDM song sound?
(What was EDM?)
That's not...
It sounds like ajaeng or a small gong.
Right?
(This is what EDM sounds like.)
That's it.
Soft and dry
(He gets into the old rhythm.)
(He has no idea what EDM is.)
- That's samulnori. - That's not how you do it.
It sounds like samulnori.
(It's an incomplete fusion of samulnori and EDM.)
(I should help him listen to EDM songs.)
That was hilarious.
All my melodies in my head are still from the 90s.
We've arrived.
- What is that? - There's something here.
There's the bouncy thing.
- Is that a trampoline? - Yes, it's a trampoline.
(What will their missions be this time?)
It's higher than I thought.
It looks like egg yolks.
It's a trampoline.
Isn't it called...
What's that in the middle?
It looks like egg yolks!
(The balloons look like they're about to burst...)
(and there is a mat underneath.)
(What in the world is it for?)
I don't think we're supposed to get on it.
- No? - No.
I think it has to do with the water.
I really have no idea.
I just sang the "Soft and Dry Song" on the way here.
- It's suites the song. - The weather is dry.
- Soft and dry - Soft and dry
- Let's be soft and dry today - Let's be soft and dry today
(Soft and dry, Let's be soft and dry today)
(They all sing the song since it might be their last chance.)
The first mission, which can get you both the gold bars and meal tickets,
will be Save Me.
(The mission to get the gold bars and meal tickets, Save Me.)
- Ji Hyo, we can... - Let's at least get some food.
- Exactly. - We need to eat.
Two teams will be playing at a time.
One person from each team will lie face down...
under the trampoline that has water balloons on top...
and the other person will have to solve the quiz within the time.
You may escape from under the trampoline...
only if your teammate gets the answer.
If the balloon hasn't popped yet, even when the opposite team...
gets the answer right, you can still try and answer.
It's a quiz, Haha. We're doomed.
- We're doomed! - I'm sorry.
We're doomed.
What do we do?
We can do it.
- What did he say, Ji Hyo? - Okay.
What?
This is driving me crazy.
What did he say, Ji Hyo?
I couldn't hear him.
- Could you repeat that? - How long haven't you heard him?
I think they are completely doomed.
They're doomed. You know how she is, right?
I don't think she ever understands the mission.
She just goes with the flow!
Do I have to understand? I can still play without understanding it.
- Exactly! - Wake up!
So the top two teams will get meal tickets,
and the top team gets two tickets to reveal other teams' territories,
- while the runner-up gets one. - Let's at least place second.
We need to get at least second place.
- This is... - We need to be at least second.
Third and fourth place will only get rice and dried laver.
- That's it? - Come on.
Whoever is going under, please lie face down.
(First Round, Kwang Soo and So Min versus Jae Seok and Ji Hyo)
Get it right.
- You have to get it right. - So Min, you're trusting Kwang Soo?
- You have to get it right. - She's trusting Kwang Soo on this.
Let's go, Kwang Soo! You can do this.
Show them what you've got, Kwang Soo!
The first one is about songs.
Songs? That sounds great.
- Let's go! - Hey!
- Ji Hyo! You can do this, right? - We can do it!
- Let's show them. We won't lose. - Okay.
Who will go first? Please play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(Ji Hyo goes first!)
I'm bad at being quick.
We will begin.
Name five song titles...
that contain breaking up with a lover.
(Five song titles that contain breaking up with a lover.)
Within five seconds. Begin!
- "Goodbye", - 5, 4,
"Say Goodbye", "Don't Say Goodbye"...
What are you doing? What was that?
(You're making me worried.)
- What is she... - What was that?
"Love Equation". "Saying Goodbye Is Sad"...
"Good"...
- There's "Star" by GB9. - "Farewell Taxi"
"Farewell Trip", "Love Equation",
"Farewell Taxi"...
- "Farewell Bus". - "Fare"...
Ji Hyo!
"Farewell Trip", "Farewell Taxi",
"If There was Practice in Farewells".
"If There was Practice in"...
In farewells! "If There was Practice in Farewells".
"Farewell", "Farewell Taxi", "Farewell Bus"...
No, not bus.
("Farewell Bus"? She failed.)
(She was doing well,)
(but she suddenly said "Farewell Bus".)
Let's take the bus!
- Ji Hyo! - 10 seconds!
"Farewell", "Farewell Taxi",
"If There was Practice in Farewells".
- "If You Need Practice"? - Five.
(His 5 seconds are up. We're doomed.)
- 4, 3, - "Farewell", "Farewell Taxi",
"Farewell Trip", "Love Equation"...
(Time is up.)
(Pop!)
(The water pours down after 100 seconds.)
(Watch out for heavy rain.)
What is this?
- It's a flood! - What's this?
That much?
(Did they have to go this far?)
What's this?
You're pouring this much?
This is...
(Miserable)
You look like you committed high treason.
(She kneels down like a criminal.)
You look like Ae Bong.
(Aren't you Ae Bong?)
She looks like me, doesn't she?
She looks like me now.
The water is...
It's unbelievable.
It keeps pouring down.
I know.
- There's so much water. - It doesn't come down together.
This is...
Let's put in less water now.
(Now I know what you're trying to do to us, so put in less water please.)
- Who are you talking to? - Put in less water please.
- What are you saying? - I mean...
- What are you doing? - Let's put in less water now.
This is hard.
Five seconds is hard.
- Let's move on. - Okay.
- Let's do this. - Let's go!
- We can do this. - Please play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(They play rock-paper-scissors to see who gets to go first.)
(So Min won and Jae Seok lost.)
I lost.
We will begin.
Tell me 5 great people in history who have 4-syllable names. Begin!
(5 great people in history who have 4-syllable names.)
5, 4,
- Je Gal Gong Myeong. - 3,
Sister Ryu Gwan Sun.
Sejong the Great, Park Hyeok Geo Se,
Je Gal Gong Myeong...
(5 seconds is up.)
- This is hard. - This is hard.
So Min, try to come up with foreigners.
(It's So Min's turn, but a while ago...)
(Say foreign people, So Min!)
(Hellen Keller!)
(Okay, Hellen Keller.)
I need one more!
Helen Keller, Park Hyeok Geo Se,
Je Gal Gong Myeong, Dokgo Young Jae?
(Dokgo Young Jae is a great person in history?)
What? Wait!
- "Dokgo Young Jae"? - "Dokgo Young Jae".
- Je Gal Gong Myeong, - Namgoong Ok Boon.
Namgoong Ok Boon.
Stop that.
Stop saying things from behind me.
Hellen Keller, Je Gal Gong Myeong,
Park Hyeok Geo Se...
Brother Jong Kook.
"Brother Jong Kook"?
(Brother Jong Kook is a great person in history?)
Sejong the Great, Park Hyeok Geo Se...
Sejong the Great, Park Hyeok Geo Se, Hellen Keller,
Je Gal Gong Myeong...
Hwangwoo Seul Hye.
Hellen Keller, Je Gal Gong Myeong,
- Sunwoo Jae Duk. - Sejong the Great.
Hellen Keller, Je Gal Gong Myeong, Sejong the Great,
Park Hyeok Geo Se, Pasteur.
But isn't Park Hyeok Geo Se a mythical character?
(Is Park Hyeok Geo Se a great person in history?)
- He's a great person in history. - And...
- No, he's not! - He is.
Okay!
- Jae Seok! - Hurry!
- Hurry, So Min! - Jae Seok!
That was amazing!
Hurry, So Min!
Say the five people!
Sejong the Great, Je Gal Gong Myeong,
- Park Hyeok Geo Se, Pasteur, - Dokgo Young Jae.
(She has 6 seconds left, and she has one more to go!)
(The last answer is .... )
Hurry, So Min!
Say the five people!
Sejong the Great, Je Gal Gong Myeong,
- Park Hyeok Geo Se, Pasteur, - Dokgo Young Jae.
Dokgo Young Jae.
(Dokgo Young Jae?)
Just keep going, So Min!
Hellen Keller, Je Gal Gong Myeong,
Pasteur, Sejong the Great,
Je Gal Gong Myeong...
I'm sorry.
(The water pours down after 100 seconds.)
(I'll make those who sabotaged her pay for this!)
That's a nice facial expression.
(Let's watch it one more time.)
(It's so easy to make people laugh with your face, isn't it?)
(She is sorry, but it's funny.)
- That's a nice facial expression. - Okay!
- That's a great expression. - It's good.
I'm sorry.
Jae Seok already said all five! Why couldn't you...
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo move up to the finals!)
We will continue on with the next team.
Don't worry, Jong Kook!
I'm already worried.
Don't worry.
- We will begin. - Let's go, the king of quiz!
Let's go!
Please play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(Seok Jin wins.)
Okay.
- We will begin now. - Okay.
Give me five movie titles that have numbers in them...
in five seconds.
"Nine", "Se7en",
"666"...
(5 seconds is up.)
- "Miracle on 1st Street". - "666".
There's no such thing as "666".
"Nine", "Se7en", "666",
"Miracle on 1st Street", and "21".
("Nine", "Se7en", "666", "Miracle on 1st Street", and "21".)
(Will all his answers be correct?)
- Where they play Black Jack. "21". - That's right.
- It's a Hollywood movie. - Does it...
Really?
Haha!
(The posters of the movies he mentioned.)
- You're so great! - Amazing!
"Nine"! Wait! I'm sorry.
Isn't it "Miracle on 7th Street"?
It's not "Miracle on 1st Street".
- No, it's 1st. - It's correct.
- It exists. - The three of you...
- It's 1st Street. - Say it!
It's right.
"Nine", "Seven"...
"Seven", "11th Street"...
"11th Street"?
(The movie title is "11th Street"?)
- Are you going shopping? - "11th Street"?
Let's go shopping!
"11th Street"?
What are you saying?
- "Nine", "The Sixth Sense", - Ten!
The convenience store's name.
(Haha tries to sabotage Seok Jin.)
Twenty what?
Be quiet.
- "Nine", "The Sixth Sense", - Ten!
(5 seconds is up.)
- "666". - "Nine", "The Sixth Sense",
"Seven"!
You forgot "Seven"!
- Begin! - The Korean War movie.
"Nine", "The Secret of the Korean War"...
"The Secret of the Korean War"?
- I'm sorry, wait. - Go!
- 5, 4, - "Nine", "Sixth Sense",
- 3, 2, - "666",
("Nine", "Sixth Sense", "666")
- 1. - "61..."
- "61"? - "11th Street" is still on my mind.
(Bursting)
(I knew it.)
I was saved!
He is the king of quiz!
- Haha is good. - The married...
- king of quiz! - The king of quiz!
I am sorry, Jong Kook.
Seok Jin had no intention of getting this question right.
That's not true.
(Seok Jin had no intention of getting this question right.)
(That's not true.)
That's not true.
That was a barbed comment.
- I had no expectations. - That's not true.
- I had no expectations. - It's not like that.
Jong Kook, you are very angry.
- I had no expectations. - Seriously.
I will also answer the question in a relaxed way.
Jong Kook, you are the only one I can depend on.
You need to win for us to make it to the final match.
Let's do this in a relaxed way.
- Let's begin. - Seok Jin, go under the trampoline.
Okay.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors and Se Chan wins.)
- Let's begin. - Okay.
In five seconds,
name five movie titles with a region.
(Movie titles...)
(with a region?)
- A region? - Se Chan, you will lose.
- 4, 3, - You will lose.
- 2, 1. - A region?
- "The Power of Kangwon Province". - That's a good one.
"Gwangju..."
(5 seconds are up.)
"Milyang".
"Milyang", "Gokseong"...
"Leaving Las Vegas".
"The Memories of Las Vegas".
- "The Memories of Las Vegas"? - It's "Leaving Las Vegas".
(Jong Kook, it's "Leaving Las Vegas".)
"Leaving Las Vegas".
"Milyang" and "Gokseong".
What are you doing?
(Why aren't you answering?)
- "Milyang" and "Gokseong". - My goodness.
"Leaving Las Vegas".
Jong Kook has no intention of answering the question.
Hey, hey.
"Silmido", "The Power of Kangwon Province",
"Gokseong", "Milyang", and "Leaving Las Vegas".
(In 5 seconds, name 5 movie titles with a region.)
- Okay. - Okay.
- Haha. - Hey.
(Good job, Se Chan.)
(Running)
- Jong Kook won't answer. - No, he won't.
- Hey. - Two,
- one. - What are you doing?
"Milyang", "Gokseong", "Leaving Las Vegas",
and "The Power of Kangwon Province".
If you are so good at the quiz, why did you do that earlier?
(If you are so good at the quiz, why did you do that earlier?)
(His conscience is pricked.)
(Seok Jin got what he deserved.)
- 10, - Hurry up.
- 9, 8. - The time is ticking.
- "The Power of Kangwon Province". - "The Power of Kangwon Province",
- "Milyang", "Gokseong", - "Milyang".
- and "Leaving Las Vegas". - "Leaving Las Vegas".
- That's right. - "Gokseong".
He couldn't think of another one.
He just needed one more.
(It's time over and he gets drenched in water.)
- My goodness. - Why didn't his face get any water?
(What? Why is his face fine?)
Why didn't his face get any water?
Why is his face dry?
Hurry up and put your face under the water.
Why didn't your face get drenched?
It's not my fault the water fell this way!
(It's not my fault the water fell this way!)
Your face should have gotten drenched.
The water fell this way!
You should have moved.
Listen. It's not my fault the water fell this way.
That wasn't funny at all.
Don't be ridiculous. I don't care if it was funny or not.
(Try to be funny.)
My entire body is wet. Don't be ridiculous.
Your face should have gotten wet.
It's not my fault. I lied down next to Haha,
but the water fell to my butt.
He is sullen. He is sullen.
- He is sullen. - Is he a child?
- Seok Jin is annoyed. - He is sullen.
Seok Jin is sullen.
- Why are you picking on me? - That wasn't funny at all.
- Why didn't they move the balloons? - Your face should have gotten wet.
No one cares your butt got wet.
The balloons were at the wrong place!
I'm not talking about that.
(It's not my fault.)
He is angry.
Seok Jin is sullen.
- For goodness' sake. - The balloons were far back.
The 3rd and 4th place have been decided.
- Okay. - Okay.
It's time for the final match.
- Let's do this. - We can do it.
This is the final match to decide the 1st and 2nd place.
The 1st place gets 2 tickets to reveal other teams' land.
It's really important to place first.
Jae Seok, let's go.
- All right. - Please.
The king of knowledge, let's go.
- Let's begin. - Let's go.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors...)
(and Haha wins.)
Gosh, I won.
No! Just don't answer it.
You can go first.
In five seconds,
(In five seconds...)
name 5 Korean movies with the 2-character title.
Korean movies?
(In 5 seconds, name 5 Korean movies with the 2-character title.)
- Five. - "Bloody Tie".
"Bloody Tie".
(5 seconds are up.)
"Bloody Tie", "The Unjust".
"The Unjust", "Bloody Tie", "Public Enemy", 1, 2.
(1, 2.)
"The Unjust", "Violent Prosecutor",
"Public Enemy", 1, 2.
Come on! Don't do that!
- "Madame Aema". - "Madame Aema".
"Madame Aema".
What? It works.
"Bloody Tie", "Madame Aema".
- "Madame Cow". - And...
Hold on. "Madame Cow", "Madame Aema", "Madame Cherry".
(He names all the sexy movies.)
- Hey, hey. - What?
(Don't do that, you punk.)
- What? - Those movies exist.
- 3, 2, - "Bloody Tie".
- one. - "Ideology..."
- "Red Hood". - "Red Fox".
My goodness.
Gosh, it's cold!
(Both teams failed to score, so they get drenched in water.)
(They get completely drenched.)
It's like a waterfall.
This is too hard.
There are so many Hong Kong movies which fit the condition.
"Bloody Tie", "The Unjust", and "Mamma Mia!"
"Mamma Mia!" isn't a Korean movie.
- We needed to name Korean movies. - Isn't "Mamma Mia!" a Korean movie?
What kind of question was that?
- Go under the trampoline. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Haha is completely dry.
Help me this once.
- Fine. - How will that help us?
If they place 1st, they can check 2 pieces of land.
That's right.
Promise us you won't check our land.
- Okay. - Promise us.
- We won't do it. - Then we will help you.
- We will do our best. - I trust you to keep your promise.
I will keep my promise.
Se Chan, let's stay dry.
Haha, I will try to be the king of quiz.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors and Ji Hyo wins.)
- Let's go. - Haha, we are going to lose.
Good luck. We will help you.
- Let's begin. - I don't know.
I don't know how the match between them will go.
(They are neck-and-neck.)
- I don't know. - The fight of a dragon and a tiger.
The fight of a dragon and a tiger.
I wouldn't know where to bet my money.
Preparing for the next game would be the wisest move.
That really would be the wisest move.
Ji Hyo, let's go.
- Okay. - Come on.
I can do it.
- I can do it. - You can do it.
In five seconds,
name five movie titles with a color.
Go.
"Red" and "Blue". "Red" and "Blue".
There are "Red" and "Blue".
- "Blue Door". - "Red" and "Blue".
- "Blue Door". - And...
"Anne of Green Cape".
"Anne of Green Cape"?
(Ji Hyo, now is your chance.)
"Red", "Blue", "Anne of Green Cape"...
- "Blue Valentine". - "Blue Valentine".
(Gosh, it isn't "Anne of Green Cape".)
"Black", "Red", "Blue",
- "Yellow"... - My goodness.
For goodness' sake.
"Blue Valentine", "Black".
"Black".
"Blue Valentine", "Anne of Green Gables",
"Blue", "Red", and "Black".
(In 5 seconds, name 5 movie titles with a color.)
(Ji Hyo succeeds first.)
How did this happen? How did this happen?
Ji Hyo did it.
Hurry up. Hurry up. Copy her answer.
"Anne of Green Gables",
"Blue", "Black", "Red"...
- Ji Hyo. - What was the last one?
I am sorry, Haha.
(I should have known.)
(The loser gets drenched in water.)
- It's a familiar look on Haha. - You must feel cool.
Haha's face turns that way when he gets drenched in water.
(The screenshots of all past videos look the same.)
The screenshots of all past videos would look the same.
Haha, I am sorry.
Thus, Team Jae Seok and Ji Hyo places first.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
- The second place isn't half bad. - Thank you.
So Min, I won't forget your help.
It's time to pick the land.
(It's time for the 1st and 2nd place to pick the land.)
I envy the first place.
Why don't you go first?
- Shall we do that? - Yes.
- All right. - Haha.
Let's go with that team.
(In that case...)
- That team? - Yes.
You shouldn't attack us.
If you attack us,
we will get back no matter what!
I bet they put two duds in one place...
unlike the others.
- We didn't do that. - We didn't do that.
(Did Kwang Soo and So Min put the duds in one slot?)
(When they distributed gold bars earlier,)
(they went all in.)
(They agreed to put nearly all gold bars in one slot.)
This is driving me crazy because they are risk-takers.
We won't stay still. We will retaliate.
- Let's go with number 6. - Number 6?
Shall we go with number six?
- Go ahead. - Go ahead.
- Shall we go with number one? - Go ahead.
- Number two? - Go ahead.
- How about number three? - Go ahead.
- How about number four? - Go ahead.
Okay. Let's go with number one. Her eyes shifted.
- Number one. - Are you sure?
Yes.
- Shall we go with number 5? - 5.
- Go ahead. - Four.
- Number 5. - Number 5.
Give them 30 dollars.
- Okay. - Give them 30 dollars.
Kwang Soo is happy.
Kwang Soo is happy. He can't wait to reveal it.
Let me reveal it right now.
It must be number one.
I got the money.
- Reveal number 5. In 1, 2, 3. - I will reveal it.
(If there are gold bars, Haha and Se Chan will beat them.)
(If there is a dud, they must give a gold bar to Kwang Soo and So Min.)
(What will be the result?)
(Haha and Se Chan get a dud.)
- A dud. - A dud.
(It's a dud.)
- It's a dud! - Give us a gold bar!
(Kwang Soo is the most excited.)
- Give them a gold bar. - My goodness.
(Although they placed 2nd, they lost money and a gold bar.)
- It's a dud. - What happens now?
- What? - Do we take this?
- We take this money and a gold bar. - Really?
That means we get 80 dollars.
(Kwang Soo and So Min get 30 dollars and 1 gold bar.)
- That's incredible. Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- Now, we will reveal two slots. - Yes.
You shouldn't pick us.
- We helped you. - We tried our best...
to help you.
I am certain they put all gold bars in one slot.
I recommend number one.
Ji Hyo thanked us.
- That's right. She did that. - Ji Hyo thanked us.
That's right. We are very thankful.
(The two teams had a deal before the game.)
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo could place 1st thanks to their help.)
(You can trust me.)
Remember what happened 10 minutes ago.
- They lost a dud. - They lost a dud.
Even if we pick the slot with the other dud,
we have another chance to pick the slot with gold bars.
- That's right. - Ji Hyo.
The slot could be empty.
- That's right. - Yes. The slot could be empty.
But you still won't be a bum.
(But you still won't be a bum.)
"You still won't be a bum."
- "You still won't be a bum." - What?
- Use polite words. - Polite words.
You should've said, "You won't lose."
I can't think of a word.
What's another way of saying "You still won't be a bum."?
"You won't lose."
"You won't waste it."
(Haha knows it.)
Don't look them in the eye and take it off.
- You're paying for it. - It makes no sense.
If we don't do this, you'll help someone else.
- Number one. - Will we...
- Number one. - Us?
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo pick number 1.)
- 10 dollars. - You have to pay 10 dollars.
- Us? - Do you mean us, Ji Hyo?
- Seriously? - I didn't expect...
Is Ji Hyo really doing this?
- Okay, okay. - Go.
Are you serious about ours?
- Ji Hyo. - We have no choice.
- Go, Ji Hyo. It's okay to get dud. - We will...
Go. 1, 2, 3.
(What's on land number 1?)
- It's empty. - There's nothing.
- There's nothing. - There's nothing.
They put them together.
Pick number two.
- Stop it! - Stop it.
- Why? - Why are you bothering us?
Why is it only us?
- We don't have any power. - Change your mind.
We're in the last place anyway.
- We have no possibility. - Give us a chance.
It's only 10 dollars.
They definitely have a gold bar.
It's number two.
- We'll take revenge. - Please.
- If you take it off... - Jae Seok.
(If that's what you think...)
- I pick number two. - Okay.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo pick number 2.)
- Us? - That's enough.
Stop picking us.
I'll give you one last chance.
- Listen. - Number two.
- Number two? - Yes.
Take it off.
1, 2, 3.
(What's on land number 2?)
(They get one gold bar.)
- There it is. - There's one gold bar.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo win 1 gold bar.)
We got one.
Do they only have one?
- They put them together somewhere. - I wanted to get 20 dollars.
Their number 5, 6 are dud.
Let's win next time no matter what.
How?
- Let's go eat. - Okay.
- We can't even eat. - I know.
(They go to have a meal.)
(Each Team's Current Assets)
It looks so delicious.
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you for the meal.
Thank you so much for the meal.
(He makes a wrap and takes a big bite.)
- It's delicious. - It's good.
- It's delicious here. - It smells good.
(Two teams that didn't clear the mission...)
(get rice and dried laver only.)
I'm hungry.
Can't we eat that?
It looks so delicious.
Thank you for the meal.
The soup looks good.
Kwang Soo, a wrap for five dollars.
(Kwang Soo, a wrap for five dollars.)
- Five dollars? - Yes.
- For how many? - It's too expensive.
How about 2 for 5 dollars?
One wrap each.
What? Thank you.
(While Se Chan tries to make money with meat,)
I want some too.
(Jae Seok gives them some meat.)
Thank you.
Shouldn't you make them pay?
We need to apologize to them.
(They're given two pieces of meat for free.)
(Stealthily)
(He takes it in one bite.)
(He's an old hyena who steals the youngest members' food.)
(He's unbelievable.)
I'm not kidding.
I want to put my hand in his mouth,
but I'm afraid that I'll pull out his tooth.
(I'm afraid that I'll pull out his tooth.)
- Be careful. - Hey.
- Seok Jin should be careful. - Hey.
(Her words hurt him.)
When I had a dog,
he lost his teeth.
When I touched them, they felt like artificial teeth.
They're hard.
For two dollars.
- What? - A big piece for two dollars.
This big one, Seok Jin.
- How much? - It's five dollars.
It was 5 dollars, but now it's 3 dollars.
- It's only for now. - You have to take this chance.
Give me one more.
I'll pay five dollars.
- 2 for 5 dollars. - Okay, okay.
Seok Jin.
Why are you making all the deals?
2 big pieces for 5 dollars? Okay.
Seok Jin, it's not okay.
It's my money.
(He announces his financial independence.)
- Hey. - You just said it was your money.
You said that it was your money.
- Five dollars. It's mine. - Okay.
- 5 dollars? - 5 dollars.
- We'll add it. - We got five dollars.
(Just then...)
(Kwang Soo takes meat away from Seok Jin.)
(He steals Seok Jin's meat for stealing his meat.)
He took it.
We got his money.
Spit it out.
Seok Jin lost.
- You should'be been careful. - It's really good.
You should have handed to me.
I did.
- I gave it to you. - It's so delicious.
You should have come near me.
Thanks to you, I had meat that he dropped.
Did you eat some?
It's so delicious.
(While they were fighting over the meat,)
(Seok Jin dropped a piece of meat.)
(She picks up meat that falls from the sky.)
(She eats it.)
(She gains unexpected meat.)
- Where's the other half of my meat? - It's delicious.
- I ate it. - It's delicious.
(He can't say anything because he stole hers.)
It's delicious.
It's very delicious.
- It's very good. - I know.
(He lost 5 dollars.)
This is two dollars, Seok Jin.
Do you want to pay 10 dollars with other things?
I need to keep a few dollars,
or Jong Kook will scold me.
(If I spend all the money, Jong Kook will scold me.)
10 dollars are yours, anyway.
- Do you want it for 10 dollars? - Show me a 3-dollar one.
- Okay. - How much is it for three dollars?
We're sharing the food,
you can't decide to give that much on your own.
Make it a wrap.
It's a lot.
It looks good.
- Kwang Soo. - Add some rice.
Kwang Soo seems to be experiencing the farm hardship period.
He keeps eating rice while looking over there.
(Kwang Soo is experiencing the farm hardship period.)
- He's looking over there. - I'm okay.
He's looking over there.
I'll put this on top.
How much is it?
- This is a bargain sale. - How much is it?
- It's 2.5 dollars. - How about 2 dollars?
No, it should be 2.5 dollars.
Why additional 50 cents?
- It's 3 dollars. - 3 dollars.
- How about 2 dollars? - 2 dollars?
- Is there four pieces? - Hurry up.
Deduct two dollars from my money.
- It's too expensive. - Two dollars.
- How much is it? - Two dollars.
Don't you need permission from Jong Kook?
It's my money.
- It's his money. - It's okay.
Do you keep your money separately?
We decided to keep it separately.
We do.
Can you give me a wrap?
I mean doenjang.
Doenjang is four dollars.
(You're a pushover.)
- Hey. - It's not good without doenjang.
I'm serious.
That's nonsense.
- Doenjang makes a huge difference. - It's important.
- Seok Jin, the taste is different. - It has no taste without doenjang.
Doenjang is good by itself.
That's true.
How about one dollar?
I'll buy it for a dollar.
- A dollar? - Are you a regular customer?
- Yes. - I'll give it for 1.5 dollars.
- How about 1 dollar? - I need to keep two dollars.
- You get one dip. - Okay.
- Okay. - For a dollar.
It's so cheap.
- It'll be salty. - Did you dip it?
- Salt isn't good for your health. - He took a lot.
Can we get more doenjang please?
(Can we get more doenjang please?)
(Goodness)
I could have asked for more doenjang like him.
(Gosh)
Hey, hey!
(Kwang Soo steals Seok Jin's meat again for the second time.)
(She picks up Seok Jin's meat again.)
(Stealing becomes fun.)
(Kwang Soo steals Seok Jin's meat consecutively.)
(The elderly wails.)
Hey.
He's very upset.
(Onlookers are having fun.)
I got some meat again.
- I never imagined he'd do it again. - It's great how you drop it.
What? Did I drop some?
- Yes, I ate it. - It's delicious.
I never imagined he'd do it again.
- It's delicious. - I'm full.
I'm full too. I finished the meat.
- Thank you, Seok Jin. - Thank you.
(Thank you for the food, Seok Jin.)
He yields to others.
- He's a great man. - He really is.
How about a big wrap for two dollars?
(He's obsessed.)
- That sounds good. - A big wrap for two dollars.
(He makes a wrap for 2 dollars.)
- This is upsetting. - I put doenjang in it.
- Seok Jin, it's 2 dollars. - 2 dollars?
- Two dollars. Did you add meat? - Yes.
- If not, don't take it. - Okay.
- Let me see the meat. - Here's the meat.
Should I keep my two dollars, Jong Kook?
Don't ask me. It's your life.
(He rejects.)
(The teammates become unfriendly as Seok Jin bought wraps.)
- He is sullen. - I know.
Jong Kook's mind has already turned away.
Since I feel bad for you, I'll add this.
- 2 dollars? - 2 dollars?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- Deal! - Okay.
You still have a gold bar.
We have a gold bar that costs 50 dollars.
(Sudden attack)
(The thief makes a sudden attack.)
(Slapping)
(Seok Jin slaps Kwang Soo with a wrap.)
(Seok Jin explodes by slapping him with a wrap.)
(Eating)
Don't eat it. It's fish cake.
(Kwang Soo, it's fish cake.)
(He gets a fish cake wrap after getting slapped.)
Kwang Soo got ugly when he stole and ate it.
(He feels bitter.)
I never saw a lettuce slap.
I thought I was watching a morning soap opera.
(A water slap)
(A kimchi slap)
(A wrap slap)
How are you eating it?
(He's a rising star in soap operas.)
Look at the rice on his face.
(They finish a battle of revenge.)
Most of us are...
sitting with teammates.
However, Seok Jin insisted on sitting this seat.
(Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Jae Seok, and Ji Hyo sit separately...)
(as Seok Jin insists on his seat.)
Can you film this?
- He gets in my space. - He's a mess.
Scoot over.
It's such a mess today because of Seok Jin.
I don't want to lose to this team. They can't work as a team.
We're sitting separately because of Seok Jin.
Why don't you two exchange seats?
Don't you know?
This has been my seat. I lean to the right.
Why? Why is it your seat?
Tell us now.
Say it to the viewers. Why is it your seat?
- "Say it to the viewers". - Say it.
The viewers don't care whether I sit here or there.
- Why is it your seat? - Why are you obsessed?
- Tell us. - I feel suffocated.
Why do you have to sit here?
I notice that Seok Jin is...
arguing with four people.
(Seok Jin is arguing with 4 people.)
This is funny.
- He's arguing with four. - I just want to sit here.
What if I want to sit here? I want to.
Then take it first.
(He's being childish.)
That's childish.
It's so childish.
- Can I sit if I take it first? - Yes.
Okay.
Take it first.
This is why after the shoot,
- He becomes tired. - Seok Jin is very tired.
When I go home after the shoot,
I get annoyed with my wife over nothing.
That's because I get upset from the shoot and tired.
- You shouldn't do that. - Jong Kook is right.
You should give her a hug and cry.
It's because he gets very stressed out.
When she asks me twice if I have eaten, I get annoyed.
- Then, I go, "I ate." - He's mean.
"I said that I ate."
He causes family discord.
Then, my wife says, "Why are you annoyed?"
And I have to say, "I'm sorry."
(He apologizes immediately.)
That's because of work.
- Seok Jin is stressed out. - I'm sorry that...
I got stressed out from work.
For the first time, I want to help him.
I wanted to sympathize with him.
You could just say, "Let me sit here."
Then we'd say,
"Go ahead. You can sit here."
That's not it.
- You can take this seat first... - Ask each of us kindly.
Ask all the members.
Say, "I like to sit by myself."
- "Let me sit here." - I'm the eldest.
You have a lot of chances to sit here.
(You guys are still young.)
Don't say that.
(The youngsters feel bad for him being weak and vulnerable.)
What's wrong with you?
- Did you abandon your pride? - What's wrong?
If possible...
(The whole group gets sad.)
Ji Hyo.
I'm getting tears in my eyes.
Tears, my foot.
(He changes completely.)
(Why are you being mean to Ji Hyo?)
What's wrong with you?
- Why are you being mean to Ji Hyo? - Why?
Why are you being so mean to her?
- Just go home if you keep this up. - When you're at home,
- do you act like that? - Why are you being mean to Ji Hyo?
- Don't take it out on me. - She didn't do anything wrong.
You were faking it.
Don't do that to Ji Hyo.
- I got emotional. - It makes no sense...
- that you would cry for me. - Seriously.
That was so fake.
Saying that you're getting tears was going overboard.
(They arrive at the second mission spot.)
- Weren't we here before? - Right.
That's right.
We have to win no matter what.
We have to win.
- No matter what. - Otherwise...
We have to.
Something is waiting for us.
I think a variety of missions awaits us.
(Running Man, the variety show.)
(They stop Let's Make Merchandise Race for a while.)
(A week later, at a dance studio in Gangnam)
Isn't this place...
- It's a famous place. - I saw it often online.
- This place? - Is this the place?
Is this place famous?
People watch from the outside.
(This is the spot in a famous dance video.)
People were cheering.
People were dancing in here.
- Is that so? - Is this the place?
There was also a teacher.
It's a famous place.
All the people who teach us how to dance...
are the top instructors in Korea.
That's right.
They're also famous internationally.
- They must be. - J Black.
That's right.
There was also MMARY.
- They're the best. - Right.
Teaching us is probably a challenge for them.
Some instructors couldn't finish teaching us.
(Some instructors couldn't finish teaching us.)
I won't specify who, but some of them left...
without finishing their lesson.
It's an obstacle they must overcome.
- Won't you tell who they are? - I won't.
Even the top instructors...
They ignored me...
a few times.
- Are you good? - They left.
(Are you good?)
He didn't say who it was.
- Does he dance well? - Why are you getting angry?
To be honest, Jae Seok is...
- part of our group. - That's nonsense.
- That's right. - He's one of us.
I approve of him.
I approve of Jae Seok.
(I agree.)
- You can even do the insider dance. - Yes.
I can do many dances.
- Can you do the hipster dance? - 1, 2, 3, 4.
Look. He's very good.
(His feet movement is fancy.)
He can do it.
(An audience member interrupts.)
Come on, Seok Jin.
(What is this all of a sudden?)
(People freeze.)
- Come back in. - "Fire"?
He gave me the creeps.
When he started dancing, that creeped me out.
Wait, Seok Jin.
(BTS Old Men's Group Dinner Show)
- Isn't he a zombie? - Zombie?
Ji Hyo said you looked like a zombie.
Isn't he a zombie?
It's scary.
It's nice that he can move like this.
Goodness.
Regarding the group choreography,
- we defeated the staff. - Yes.
Let's go.
(In the competition against the staff,)
(Running Man members won dramatically.)
(Instead of the difficult choreography,)
(Running Man can prepare choreography that they want.)
(They want fun dance...)
(with a fast beat like Celeb Five's performance.)
(Please make a fun dance for us.)
Just like what you asked,
we asked the instructor to create a dance like Celeb Five's.
- Okay. - Did she?
The instructor choreographed dance to the music.
Is it done?
We'll invite the instructor now.
She's a globally popular dancer.
Here is Instructor Lia Kim.
We meet her in person.
Lia Kim.
Hello.
(She's the chief choreographer at 1Million Dance Studio.)
(She's good at popping.)
(She's a good dancer.)
(She dances all genres.)
(Her social network subscribers are over 12 million.)
(Globally popular choreographer)
She's choreographed dances all over the world.
I'll introduce her briefly.
Some people might not know.
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
Don't look at me suspiciously.
(He's full of distrust.)
Why do you suspect me when I said she's popular in many countries?
I don't know her well.
- I know that she's very famous. - I don't know...
- I heard that she's famous. - People line up for her.
- Not anyone can learn from her. - To learn from her,
you must line up.
She's famous for slapping her students if you don't dance well.
(I don't slap.)
Do you think that I'm a fool?
She does it while dancing.
In the middle of dancing.
She dances...
popping, modern dance, hip hop, locking, and classical dance.
She's one of the few dancers of all genres in Korea.
- She can do all. - Respect.
Let me tell about her achievements. This will catch your attention.
- "Gashina" by SUNMI. - "Gashina"?
"TT" and "Like OOH-AHH" by TWICE.
Did she create this?
"Very Very Very" by I.O.I.
- Very, very, very - You know this song, right?
"Fox" by BoA,
and "I Feel You" by Wonder Girls.
She created dances for many songs.
Will Running Man be part of her work experience?
That's right.
That's the best work experience.
It's the best.
Teaching us could be her first crisis in her career.
It could be her first crisis in her career.
(She's worried.)
You must overcome it...
- That's right. - to enter a whole new level.
She prepared a choreography...
- that fits your level. - That's good.
Those wearing white t-shirts in the video will be you guys.
What kind of dance is it?
- Let's see. - It looks amazing.
- White t-shirts. - The white t-shirts will be us.
It looks amazing.
(The formation looks cool from the beginning.)
The start isn't bad.
- What? - What is that?
Will we do that?
(They starts to feel...)
It's too difficult.
I don't think we can pull that off.
What should we do?
- This is... - No.
We can't do this.
I like the beat.
(The beat gets faster, and they start to dance in perfect sync.)
We can't do it.
(How can we do this?)
- How can we do it? - How?
- How can we do it? - We can't.
(They follow the faster beats.)
(Movements become powerful as the beat gets faster.)
Isn't this a choreography for a competition?
Is it for an international competition?
It's appropriate for competitions.
Those in white are us.
I know. That's us.
- What's that? - What's that?
(The rhythm changes.)
That was instant.
(Movements keep changing.)
- It's interesting. Goodness. - No way.
- I can't get up like that. - How?
- It looks amazing though. - We can't do it.
It does look amazing.
I want to do like Celeb Five.
This is not Celeb Five's dances.
My joints already hurt.
(Their joints hurt already.)
(Is it over?)
It's not over.
- Is there more? - There's more.
There is.
- No way. - It should be over.
- Is there more? - This is Ji Hyo's part.
(The beat becomes lighter.)
There are two. What?
(They work together.)
Do we have to do that?
So Min and Kwang Soo can do it.
Did you see them getting in formation without looking?
This is exciting.
It looks cool though.
- It looks amazing. - It's awesome.
Add some of these.
Let's keep that one.
- Kwang Soo can do it. - We can add this.
We can add this one.
- This is like a circus. - It is indeed.
The dance is well choreographed.
Seriously.
(Isn't this fun?)
Lia, this is...
(Speechless)
How can do we that?
- How can we pull that off? - They're just...
- They're just showing it to us. - Do you think so?
- There's no way. - They're just showing it to us.
They're just showing it to us.
(Group dance for the fan-meet)
- By the way... - It looks amazing though.
- Seriously, - There's no way.
- it does look cool. - It does.
It is an art.
Yes, indeed.
- If we could dance well, - It looks amazing.
- we'd love to do it. - That'd be good.
- That'd be very good. - But...
- we can't. - We can't do it.
I adjusted the level to Celeb Five's dances.
- I made it look like their style. - They're good dancers.
(Is it that level?)
(Isn't it more difficult?)
Celeb Five members dance well.
That's right.
Celeb Five's dances are very difficult.
- Right. - Even to me,
- They dance so well. - it's very fast.
- There are many movements. - They're good dancers.
Aren't you asking too much from us?
We have two months left.
We have two months.
I didn't add any movements that require technique.
You can do it by memorizing, but the movements are quick.
They're quick, but you can do the movements by memorizing them.
- Those came later seemed difficult. - I know.
If we can do it, it'll be a miracle.
(Will the members be able to pull off the group dance?)
(Next week)
(Eight members challenge themselves to create a miracle.)
(However, they keep making errors.)
(Repeated practice awaits them.)
(What? Look at that! They're starting to dance in sync.)
(Everyone can do it. My gosh!)
(Will the members have a miracle?)
(And...)
(the filming for the Running Shirts starts at last.)
(The makeup that shocks everyone will be revealed.)
(4th Episode for 9 Years of Running Man: There Was a Miracle)