Hello.
- I haven't been here for a while. - Hello.
Did you guys watch "AM Plaza" today?
Yes, I did.
(Yu San Seul, also known as Yu Jae Seok, was on "Am Plaza".)
- San Seul was on the show. - My goodness.
- By the way, Jae Seok... - Yu San Seul.
and Yu San Seul were both trending online.
- They were on the trending list. - Okay.
Hey, Yu San Seul was ranked higher.
You know what? I can't forget what Seok Jin said to me...
- when I got here. - What did he say?
- What did he say? - What?
(What was the first thing he said before the filming?)
"I'm jealous."
(I'm jealous.)
(He's jealous of San Seul's success.)
- Seok Jin is totally jealous. - My gosh.
- I was very jealous. - You're really honest, by the way.
- To be honest, - Seok Jin is jealous...
- of me and So Min. - My gosh.
- Why is he jealous of So Min? - Goodness.
So Min is going viral because of her armpit incident.
("As So Min's Armpits Sweat, the TV Ratings Soar")
- He's very jealous. - So Min...
Seeing Jae Seok establish a new career as San Seul...
- makes me jealous. - Many are jealous of you...
because you live the life of a bachelor.
Many are jealous of you...
(Some people are jealous of Seok Jin...)
(who's in a crisis.)
- Some are jealous of you. - "The life of a bachelor"?
- No. - A lot of dads...
- are jealous of you. - I live the life of a married man.
A lot of people are jealous of you.
- That's funny. He's hiding it. - That's not true.
But his wife lives like she's single too.
(Is his wife in a crisis too?)
She's having fun like a single lady.
- She lives like a single lady. - That's so cool.
- Hey, Ji Hyo is in a new drama. - Right. I read the article.
Yes, I read the article.
- "Did We Really Love?" - Who's your love interest?
- Three men like your character. - That's right.
- There are 4 guys that like me. - There are 4?
We're close with the director.
- Who's the director? - It's Seok Yoon.
- Kim Seok Yoon. - He's the director?
- He's the CP. He's the head. - I ought to give him a call.
(I ought to give him a call.)
- You're trying to do everything. - Hey.
- That doesn't work nowadays. - I can't believe this.
- I was on his show before. - What are you saying?
- I was on one of his shows too. - Really?
He's doing well, directing dramas and movies.
- My gosh, he's the CP? - He can't betray us like this.
- What do you mean? - He did variety shows.
He was the first one who gave me the costume head for a grasshopper.
Really?
- Really? He's your savior. - So in other words,
- when no one hired me for shows, - Right.
- he hired me as the director. - Kim Seok Yoon.
He told me to come to the sixth floor, so I went.
- He put the costume on his desk. - He's your hero.
"If you want to be on variety shows,"
"you must wear this."
(It was the moment that brought a big change to Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok got a nickname, Grasshopper.)
(A cornerstone that helped him become the nationally beloved host)
"If you want it, put it on. If you don't want it,"
- "you can leave." - Seok Yoon...
When I was active with my song "One Man",
- he told me to be an actor. - My gosh.
And I never heard from him again.
(It's already been 15 years.)
Seok Yoon will give you a call.
Whenever I saw him, he told me to be an actor.
He's one of many people who helped me...
- get where I am now. - That's true.
- He works with Ji Hyo a lot. - He'll work with Ji Hyo.
Is there anything for Seok Jin?
All right. Today,
- There's no news about Seok Jin? - last week...
(There's no news about Seok Jin.)
- Nothing for Seok Jin? - I'm sure you can find something.
- Anything about his bachelor life? - Bachelor life?
Did he go on another trip?
Seok Jin is wearing long johns today.
What about Kwang Soo? Anything for him?
Well,
I've been filming in Incheon lately.
What? For what?
It's been over six months since I started filming "Sinkhole".
- It's a film about a disaster. - You know what?
He's filming with Cha Seung Won.
- You're awful. - Gosh, you know what?
I stop following it after "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks."
- Hey, there will be another one. - He always talks about that.
- "One-Eyed Jacks." - "One-Eyed Jacks."
- There's another one. - "One-Eyed Jacks."
I thought he was filming that.
Cha In Pyo... No, that's the wrong name.
- Isn't that with Cha Seung Won? - Right.
- You'd better be nice to Seung Won. - Okay.
Seriously. Be nice to him.
- Is that all? - Yes.
That's it.
All right. We'll settle that he'll be nice to Seung Won.
- I'll be nice. - Be nice to him.
We've prepared today's episode to repent...
for doubting and framing one other...
for the past weeks and unite as one.
- Unite as one? - Unite?
It's Everyone Must Pass: Along with Distrust Race.
(Everyone Must Pass: Along with Distrust Race.)
- We're good at that. - We need to come together.
We're good at uniting as one.
You will try out for four missions where everyone must pass.
Whenever you successfully complete each mission,
you'll be provided with delicious winter snacks.
- Fish-shaped bun. - Fish-shaped bun, hotteok,
- fishcake. - Fishcake.
- I'm craving ramyeon... - Egg bun.
- or snacks more than fancy meals. - They are more delicious.
We have prepared unique winter snacks today.
If you fail, one more member will have to face the penalty.
One more member?
Members who have to carry out the penalty...
will do the Yondu makeup and sell 100 fish-shaped buns.
(With this makeup on,)
(we must sell 100 fish-shaped buns?)
- We have to wear makeup? - Sell 100 with the makeup on?
- I really don't want to do that. - My gosh.
- We can't let our guard down. - I really don't want to do that.
We will give you each 10 candies.
The number of remaining candies will determine who'll face the penalty.
The member with the most candies will win the race.
The winning member will win a prize and be exempted from the penalty.
- We can get chosen for the penalty. - Yes.
The members with the least candies will face out the penalty.
For example,
if you fail 3 missions as a team, 3 of you will face the penalty.
Two members with the least candies will face the penalty.
And as for the last member to face the penalty,
the 2 members will discuss and select 1 more member.
Is there a scenario where we won't face the penalty?
If you complete all of the missions, you won't have to.
- Right. We can complete them. - All of them?
- We should complete the missions. - We really have to.
- You'd better bring your A-game. - Okay.
- Shall we start? - I'll give you the candy pouch.
- Everyone should pass. - All of us will pass.
- No one should face the penalty. - Let's do our best.
- We must complete all the missions. - Right.
We must complete all four missions.
- But that will be hard. - My gosh.
Don't steal candies to win the race, Kwang Soo.
I won't do that.
- To get exempted from... - Why are you eating that?
Why are you eating that?
- What do you mean? - That's our money.
That means you lost one.
- They'll give me one more. - We don't have any left.
(We don't have any left.)
Stop lying. Give me one.
- You can't eat that. - Are you serious?
All right. He lost one. That's it.
Seok Jin only has nine to start with.
He will face the penalty for sure.
- Can I spit it out? - No.
- I can put it back nicely. - It's over. That's it.
I can see your future in about six hours.
- I know for sure who it will be. - Mr. Yondu.
(Be Yondu, Seok Jin)
I won't be Yondu.
We'll get going for your first mission.
Am I really starting with nine candies?
Of course.
- What's this now? - What is it?
I'm really good at this kind of game.
(What kind of mission awaits the members?)
(There are partitions, a scoreboard, and soccer balls.)
(What is their first mission?)
It's the fish-shaped bun which I love.
What's that huge fish-shaped bun?
(It impresses them right away.)
That's the fish-shaped bun?
The first winter snack...
- is a huge fish-shaped bun. - That's the fish-shaped bun.
- This is amazing. - Some parts taste like pizza.
Pizza?
This is crazy.
- The huge fish-shaped bun... - I want pizza.
is at stake on the first mission.
Everyone Must Get the Right Answer: Striker the King of Quiz.
- It's a quiz. - A quiz?
- We're doomed. - Come on.
You'll kick a ball to the scoreboard that consists of...
different categories ranging from 10 to 40 points.
You'll solve a question from the category your ball lands.
Everyone will get to kick once. So within a total of eight attempts,
if you gather 100 points, you have completed your mission.
We need 100 points?
If we complete four missions, you can't change your words.
If we complete all four missions, you should do the Yondu makeup.
Come on. They can't do that.
- You should do it. - They can't do that.
You can...
They are already working hard trying to edit our videos.
- Jae Seok is scolding him. - Hey.
- He's getting scolded verbally. - Whose side are you on?
- I feel bad for our staff. - They must bet something for us...
- to feel motivated. - They stayed up all night...
and now, they have to do the makeup?
- They ought to do that. - We don't do that in this era.
Let's bet something.
- Okay? - Seok Jin.
Se Chan,
- What? - Ji Hyo, and I have to solve them.
- My gosh. - You need to be understanding.
But the worst one among them is Ji Hyo.
(But the worst one among them is Ji Hyo.)
- If I'm being really honest. - That's true.
- She's not faking it at all. - She's the hidden player.
But we weren't able to air the quiz clips for Ji Hyo.
(That's true.)
Sister Fish.
He called you Sister Fish.
- I like fish - You are Sister Fish, aren't you?
- I'm not your sister. - Ms. Fish.
- Sister Fish and Madame Gurie. - I think...
Clueless Ji Hyo is better.
- That's nice. It's cute. - Clueless Ji Hyo.
- How witty. That was so witty. - You're indeed better than us.
You can say Clueless Ji Hyo.
How about...
Informative Ji Hyo.
(What is that?)
Informative Ji Hyo?
- Seok Jin fails! - Fails!
(Seok Jin fails!)
(It's so fun teasing Seok Jin.)
(The guys are having fun.)
Strangely, I'm so happy when you tease me like this.
(Clasping his hands tightly)
Keep talking about me.
I liked it when you said I failed.
You're getting attention from us.
- I guess I'm an attention-seeker. - You can get started now.
Of course, you cannot discuss when solving the quizzes.
Well, that won't help anyway.
- I don't want English words. - Hold on.
Are you saying that you can get everything right except for English?
I want People.
I can solve quizzes about People and Music.
You can tell us...
- before you start. - We'll start.
All of you must kick it at least once.
- Really? - You have eight chances.
- I'll go first. - Really?
Seok Jin will go first.
- I'll start! - Start.
(On which category...)
(and how many points will Seok Jin's ball land?)
- That's 20 points, right? - English Words.
English Words for 20 points. Please sit.
We're in trouble. How will we solve this one?
I'm doomed. I don't know anything.
- I'll just write down what I know. - All right.
(Their 1st question is on English Words for 20 points.)
Here's your question.
This question about English Words will earn you 20 points.
We'll get 20 points.
- It won't be that hard. - It's not that hard.
If you all write down the correct answer, you'll get the points.
Write down...
all the colors...
you would get when you mix red and blue together...
in English.
- How would we do know that? - I don't know that.
I'm color blind.
What do we get when we mix red and blue? Do we get black?
I know the color, but I don't know that in English.
- What's the color? - Can I tell you?
- It's purple. - Is it purple?
No, it's green.
It's green?
Isn't it purple? It's green?
No, it's purple.
I'm in trouble. I can't even spell blue.
Hold on. Blue...
Blue is blue.
I can't... I can't spell red in English. This is awful.
- Hey, come on. - Wait, the letter in the middle...
Are you serious?
Wait, this is...
(Why did he write down R, D, and B on the board?)
My gosh, I'm confused about the words.
The last word has five letters, right?
- There are six. - What? Why?
(He's shocked.)
(There are 6 letters?)
There are six.
Wait. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
- That's not right. - There are six letters.
- That can't be. Hold on. - There are six letters.
- There are six letters? - Purple.
We'll let you discuss up to here.
- This can't be right. Wait. - Purple.
- It's purple? - Yes.
You know that in English, right?
Can't we go with green?
Let's go with green.
There are three colors. One.
- Let's get this one right. - Two.
You can't cheat. 1, 2.
Wait.
- Three. Show me your boards. - I'm not sure.
(Did everyone get it right?)
(The answer is red, blue, and purple.)
- This has to be correct. - I think my answer is right.
- I think this is right. - A long time ago,
I wrote that on the card.
I guess we all have the right answers.
Did everyone get it right?
(Haha gets it right.)
(Jae Seok also gets it right.)
- I guess so. Look at his face. - We all get it right.
(Did Se Chan and Ji Hyo get the question right?)
We all got it right.
They look nervous.
- I don't know. - What? What did you write down?
Why are you laughing?
Hey, everyone is laughing at Se Chan.
Why are you laughing at Se Chan?
- That means Se Chan got it wrong. - Which one got it wrong?
All right.
Red is spelled R-E-D.
- I got it right. - Okay.
- Blue is spelled B-L-U-E. - Yes.
Darn it.
Who just said, "darn it"?
Purple is spelled P-U-R-P-L-E.
- Yes! I got it right. - Okay!
(He's happy that he got the last one right.)
I spelled "purple" correctly!
(Since 4 of them got the question wrong, they fail the 1st round.)
You got them all right.
- I got them right! - What did you write down?
- I got them right too. - My answer was correct!
- Seok Jin. - I misspelled it.
You said there were six letters, Seok Jin.
How could you get it wrong?
I made a mistake. Why did I mess this up?
- What did you write? Let me see. - I'm sorry.
- I was in a hurry. - Let me see.
What is "bulru"?
- He really didn't know. - "Bulru".
Hey, "bulru..."
I got "purple" wrong.
Hey, aren't I smart?
- Let's compliment each other. - I got it right as well.
We shouldn't pick any that are related to English.
We should pick anything but that.
You've failed the first round.
It was worth 20 points.
- Gosh. - I can't believe I got it right.
(Will they be able to accumulate 100 points in 7 tries?)
Then...
(Tell them that I got this right.)
- Hey, I get it, so go. - Compliment me.
Don't gloat over this.
- P-U-R-P-L-E. - Did you get it?
- I did. - Goodness.
Dream!
Your dad isn't stupid!
(Jealous)
I can speak English!
(Dream, are you watching?)
Dream, I got it right!
- How awesome. - You're awesome.
The category is Music, and it's worth 30 points.
Okay, let's get this one right.
You're going to hear a familiar song.
Listen carefully to the lyrics...
and write the answer to the given question.
- Okay. - I like this.
Isn't this so fun?
It sure is. We should've picked this one.
Here's the music. Please play.
What is this?
(Which song is this?)
Isn't this Outsider?
What? You're right.
(Something feels ominous.)
- Is it related to English? - Be quiet!
(Haha suspects the staff.)
(So Min jots down the lyrics.)
(Everyone is focused.)
(What...)
(is he saying?)
[VIU Ver] SBS E479 Running Man
"Everyone Must Pass: Along with Distrust Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Jae Seok looks dazed.)
(The song ends.)
Why does he rap so fast?
- He's amazing. - He sure is.
Here's your question.
What does the protagonist dream about?
- He mentioned that? - It was in the beginning.
I only heard about him wiping something.
This is too hard.
This song is... Gosh, it can't be helped.
We'll have to dress up as Yondu.
His delivery is awful.
(All of them are lost.)
I'll play it once again.
- What was the question again? - Hey.
Did you hear him?
"What was the question again?"
- What was it? - His dream.
- The protagonist's dream? - The protagonist's dream.
- Let's go. - Be quiet and focus.
- Be quiet. - This is your last chance.
All right. Play the music.
(He does his best to listen.)
(They focus all their attention on the lyrics.)
(Concentrating)
(What did the protagonist dream of every night?)
(They focus on the lyrics.)
- When did he mention that? - When did it come out?
It was in the beginning.
I have no idea.
Is this dream...
- like his hope? - Be quiet.
- We don't have time to chat. - Stop irritating me.
By dream, do you mean what he hopes for?
Or is it literal?
He talked about what he dreamed about every night.
I'm so lost.
We just need to write one word, right?
(They jot down their answers.)
As an individual who has experience in rapping...
You sang a trot.
You were a trot singer.
- It has nothing to do with you. - Hey!
I know I'm singing trot these days, but I used to rap back then.
Gosh, he's so successful.
(What's wrong with him?)
Come on. You're a good singer.
- Right. - You suit trot music.
Right? Should I begin my new career?
Yes, you should.
Your stage name should be Mr. Boring.
(Mr. Boring is the upcoming trot singer.)
All right. Three...
I have no idea.
2, 1. Let's see your answers.
- We can't win this one. - I couldn't get anything.
It's impossible for us to all get it right.
How can we all get it right?
What if we all get one word right?
Let's look at your answers one by one.
- Let's do that. - Let's start with Se Chan.
I heard "I picture myself having ramyeon with you."
- What? - This is what I heard.
- He said that? - He did?
(He mimics.)
Really?
I picture myself having ramyeon with you
- Really? - That's what I heard.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
Did you write down all the lyrics?
No. Mine is...
"Every night when he's asleep, a woman comes..."
"and wipes away his tears."
- "There are arrows, he prays..." - "There are arrows, he prays..."
"and is heartbroken. So what?"
So what dream did he have?
Maybe that's her dream.
This is what the woman did in his dreams.
- She did that? - Yes, she did.
You actually heard it.
I wrote, "They meet again."
What is that?
That's all you wrote?
They'll meet again.
I wrote that he wants her to return.
- That's it. He wishes for that. - That's right.
- They're going to meet again. - Yes.
Haha?
I wiped your tears as you cried after getting hit by the arrow
(I wiped your tears as you cried after getting hit by the arrow)
- Why do you sound so cheeky? - I wiped your tears as you cried
After getting hit by the arrow
Hold on. What about you?
I dreamt of her wiping away my tears
But she was hit with an arrow
- That's... - So Min?
- Did you write a poem? - "The woman..."
- Did she get hit by an arrow? - "The woman whom he loved..."
"appeared in his dreams, and he watched her leave."
"She cried, and he tried to wipe the tears, but she refused."
It's similar to Ji Hyo's.
The answer is in there.
- Really? - Really?
(They can't believe it.)
The answer is...
(Which one of them...)
(understood the lyrics?)
- Kwang Soo has the right answer. - Okay!
(Kwang Soo gets it right.)
- What? Let me see? - Really?
- I wrote that but erased it. - I'm not stupid!
What is it?
He dreamt of her wiping away his tears.
I dreamt of her wiping away my tears
(Let's see the footage.)
(I dream of your wiping away my tears in my dreams)
- Then I got it right as well. - Look.
But you wrote about an arrow.
That was just for fun.
All right, you got it right then.
Okay!
Raise your board! Kwang Soo isn't stupid...
and neither am I, Dream.
(He happily repeats his answer.)
(He happily repeats his answer as well.)
(They are incorrigible.)
Where are you?
(He suddenly starts singing.)
What was that?
Were you singing a folk song?
- Was that a folk song? - It was Outsider's song.
- Come on. - Are you sure?
(Since he's a trot singer,)
(he reinterprets the song in his style.)
My gosh.
- This is difficult. - It is.
It's too hard.
All right. Ji Hyo, you can kick this time.
- Yes, you do it. - Pick People.
She's surprisingly good at things like this.
- Start. - Go.
- People. - Don't pick English Words.
- No. - That's 20 points.
(What?)
That's 20 points.
- It's 20 points. - Right? See?
- That's it. - She got People for 20 points.
(Surprisingly,)
(she scored a bullseye.)
- It's 20 points. - People for 20 points.
- Right. - Okay.
It's obviously 20 points.
If we don't get it right this time,
- It's over. - we'll lose for sure.
We must get this right.
This is unexpected.
Haha and Kwang Soo are in the lead.
I know.
We're the top two players.
In my head,
I'm thinking about how Haha is a good match for me.
I think we should sit far away from each other...
for those who don't know the answers.
So that we can help them?
- I keep thinking of him as a rival. - Come on.
You guys got the right answer by coincidence.
(They're the brainiacs of this week.)
Let's do this. We need to get this right.
I'm going to show you three photos of celebrities...
- when they were young. - Okay.
You need to guess the right celebrities.
We need to get all of them right.
I'm good at this.
I'm known for being sharp-eyed.
- 1, 2... - We need to get all three?
I can't see.
(You can guess as well.)
- Can we take a closer look? - I can't see.
- They're all different? - I can't see.
- I know this one! - Me too.
(1st and 2nd photos are easy to recognize.)
I recognize the one in the middle.
- Don't you recognize her? - First one is easy too.
Right? But I don't recognize the last photo.
Who is this? I'm stuck on the last one as well.
I recognize them two.
- Dimples? - It's on the tip of my tongue.
Hold on a minute. Don't we...
- Who is she? - What?
Don't we...
(Who is she?)
Are you allowed to do that?
- Is he allowed to do that? - No.
- What's wrong? - I recognize her.
- What? Wait. - She's old.
- Isn't she from Gugudan? - Can we do this?
- It's not her. - No?
- This photo looks quite old. - Who is this?
- This can't be Se Jeong. - It's an old photo.
- I thought it was her. - The bricks say it's the 80s.
- She looks like a rich kid. - Look.
The background looks like one from the early 90s.
- Look at her clothes. - So...
I think she was born...
- Which celebrity has dimples? - around the mid to late 80s.
She's around my age.
- Jae Seok! - He got it.
- Hey, you shouldn't tell us. - He got it.
- I won't. - Who is it?
- You should tell us. - Then why did you ask?
- Why would you ask him then? - Why would you?
- You shouldn't tell us. - You shouldn't.
Okay. Oh, this is team play.
- Let me think. - Dimples?
- She's a singer. - Right?
- I'm right, aren't I? - It's a singer?
Is she a singer? Give us that.
- She's an actress. - I thought it was Kang Min Kyung.
No.
- I thought it was her. - Me too, but we're wrong.
(Ji Hyo and Haha both exclaim at the same time.)
- I knew it! - I got it!
New Zealand!
- Yes, you're right! - New Zealand!
- Hey, hey. - What was that?
- New Zealand! - No, it's Switzerland!
- Switzerland? - Switzerland!
Switzerland?
Okay, we're done here.
- Okay, okay. - Yes.
I got it.
- "I'm strong." - Yes, that's it.
- That's it. - I know it.
(Could she be...)
(Kang Han Na?)
I know it.
- "I'm strong." - Be quiet!
You shouldn't tell the others!
I have no idea.
(1st, 2nd, 3rd)
(These girls all look so pretty and cute.)
One,
two,
- three. - We got this.
- We got this. - It's unanimous.
- We got it. - Yes, we did.
(Is Kim Yu Na, Lee Young Ae, and Kang Han Na correct?)
- You've all succeeded. - Okay!
You've all succeeded.
(They may have broken all the rules,)
(but they've gained a victory.)
- Okay. - It was Han Na.
- Yes. - This was her when she was little.
- How adorable. - I can see it in her smile.
Yu Na...
- She was already famous back then. - haven't changed.
- She was already famous. - Young Ae looks so beautiful.
Gosh, look at Lee Young Ae. She was absolutely beautiful.
I wonder why she isn't actively working anymore.
- What? - She recently filmed a movie.
- What? - It was recently released.
My apologies.
I just felt so bad, that's all.
Why don't you know this when you're always on the Internet?
He only reads the stock page.
I can't believe this was Han Na.
- Well, we secured 20 points. - Nice.
Okay!
All we need to get right are 2 40-point questions.
All we have is 20 points?
Shall we try another one?
- Yes, one more. - Another one?
- Let's double the score. - Right.
Let's do this.
Here you go.
- The photos are too old. - Goodness.
- This is HyunA. - Of course.
- HyunA. - That's right.
- Son Ye Jin! - Son Ye Jin?
- Are you sure? - He's right.
This boy is extremely handsome.
- Ji Chang Wook! - No.
- It's Lee Hong Gi. - Won Bin.
Isn't it Won Bin?
The nose and lips seem familiar.
- It's Won Bin. - Isn't it Jung Woo Sung?
- No, he's not like this. - No.
He might not be so handsome now.
Some people get uglier as they grow up.
I was handsome as a boy too.
Don't be absurd. We saw your photo.
- Right, I forgot. - We saw your photo.
(He quickly gives up.)
- You were just the adorable type. - Right.
- I'm completely clueless. - You have five seconds.
You got Son Ye Jin and HyunA right.
- Right? - Isn't it Jung Woo Sung?
Yes, Jung Woo Sung.
- Let's go with Jung Woo Sung. - Do it!
In 1, 2, 3.
- Jung Woo Sung. - Jung Woo Sung.
(The members think it's Jung Woo Sung.)
Did we get it right?
(Is this Jung Woo Sung?)
It's Hwang Jung Min.
- No way! - It's Hwang Jung Min.
(They're all baffled.)
- You're lying. - Remember what I said?
- Really? - What happened to him?
- Unbelievable. - The mouth is the same.
Is it really him?
- Jung Min... - The face is still there.
He's not this pretty now.
We invited him on Introducing My Ugly Friends Festival.
Doesn't it seem like he's provoking us?
That brings your total to 40 points.
- He was handsome. - My gosh.
We would've never guessed that.
It's impossible to guess right.
(So the 20-point question in the People category is over.)
Next up is the 30-point question in the People category.
Here's the 30-point question in the People category.
Please write down...
eight different movies that this person was in.
- Well... - If you write down...
the same movie more than twice, or one the actor wasn't in,
or the wrong title, you fail.
We can't write down the same movie twice?
- No. - Even among us?
- I'll write the most famous one. - Me too.
The celebrity this time is...
Lee Byung Hun.
(Actor Lee Byung Hun)
- What about TV series? - Are TV series allowed?
No, please stick to movies.
Okay, no one will know this one.
Don't write down the one from an elevated height.
("Bungee Jumping Of Their Own")
- What? - I was going to write that!
No way.
It's what I was going to write down.
I'm suddenly confused by the movies he was in.
I'll write down a foreign film.
I'm sticking to a recent release.
I'm going to rotate my wrist.
Isn't this close to cheating?
- Why? - I'm going to Thailand.
I'm writing down something completely off the radar.
I can't believe I even thought of this.
You must write down the correct title.
The correct... Wait, the full title?
- In one... - I'm writing just the title.
2, 3.
All right.
- Goodness. - Shall we begin with me?
"The Harmonium In My Memory".
- "Good, Bad, Weird". - "Good, Bad, Weird".
- It's different from mine. - "Bungee Jumping Of Their Own".
- Nice. - "Terminator".
(Jong Kook has been cleared.)
"Joint Security Area".
- "Master". - "Inside Men".
(All 7 of them wrote down different movies.)
(They will win 30 points if So Min wrote a different one too.)
- "Monster". - Was he in that movie?
- He was. - Right?
- It's an omnibus film. - "Monster".
There is a movie of that title but...
- An omnibus... Why? - Why?
(What?)
It's "Three, Monster."
What?
(The correct title is "Three, Monster.")
(Because of So Min, they fail to earn more points.)
Also, it's "The Good, The Bad, The Weird,"
not "Good, Bad, Weird."
- Is it "Three, Monster"? - We call it that for short.
If that's the rule, then you should explain it again.
This is wrong.
Ji Hyo has a hard time understanding these things.
She didn't quite understand the rules.
We all shorten the title.
He wasn't in "Monster" anyway.
- "Monster" is incorrect. - "Three, Monster".
- Do we have a spy among us? - But...
- So Min... - Are you a spy?
What's wrong with you?
- Was this on purpose? - Do you want to dress up as Yondu?
No, of course not. I don't want that at all.
- Out of all the options... - But I...
- What else is there? - "Bungee..."
There is also "INSEPARABLE BROS."
(The movie stars Kwang Soo and Shin Ha Kyun.)
- Don't you agree? - That's what I said.
That's the movie I wrote down.
Right.
- Now, you're upsetting me. - Gosh.
When was Lee Byung Hun in that film?
- I... - Are you trying to make me angry?
- No, I... - Are you provoking me?
That's not it.
"Keys to the Heart".
So Min, what's wrong with you?
That was so close.
This is your last chance.
- Let's score some points. - We almost got it right.
We'll now refrain from giving each other hints.
You're the one who mentioned jumping from somewhere high.
That wasn't much of a hint.
All I did was rotate my wrist.
Here we go then.
Jeon Do Yeon.
- I know one. - Don't do it.
Don't write the one with the harmonium.
That's mine!
(He shamelessly calls dibs again.)
- That's mine! - Hold on.
- I'm going to write that one. - What's wrong with you?
- Stop it! - Don't write it down.
- Just don't. - If so,
then it's the end of happiness.
Hold on a second.
- Okay, I won't write that one down. - Don't do it.
I'm sorry.
- That... - I'm sorry.
- That's what I was going to write. - Well, don't.
What else is there?
Three...
Someone else probably wrote this down.
- Two... - Gosh.
- One. Hold them up. - Just a second.
I enjoyed this movie.
Let's not blame anyone.
Let's take a look.
"A Promise".
- "Birthday". - "Birthday".
"The Harmonium Inside My Memory".
- "A Promise". - "A Promise".
(Se Chan and Jong Kook wrote down the same movie.)
- "Secret Sunshine". - "Happy End".
- "The Contact". - Unbelievable.
"The Contact" and "Happy End".
There are two entries for "A Promise"...
and it's "The Harmonium In My Memory."
Did you write "inside" instead?
I wrote down the correct title minutes ago.
Is it "in" or "inside"?
Isn't it "inside"?
Right, of course.
- Yes, "inside." - Right, instead of "in."
(Yes, "inside" sounds better.)
I wrote down the correct title minutes ago.
He tends to watch movies that have slightly different titles.
- Jae Seok... - You mean adult films?
Those with slightly different titles.
- Is this a rated R movie? - Of course not.
Where inside is this harmonium?
Tell us about this adult film.
For instance... Let me see.
Like "Hairy Something"?
A title that's slightly different.
"Aroused" instead of "Yonggary"?
There's also "Swiri for a Moment."
"Swiri for a Moment"?
(He bursts out laughing.)
- That one exists. - It exists.
- I remember seeing that title. - Me too.
My friend's family used to own a DVD rental shop.
- "Swiri for a Moment"? - It was famous in our school.
- "Aroused". - "Swiri for a Moment".
- Well, you failed this round. - It's difficult.
I can't believe we couldn't grasp this chance.
Well, you currently have 40 points.
Give us one worth 60 points.
- 60 points? - We won't conspire.
Just one single question.
- Just one? - Yes.
Okay, I'll give you one more.
This is worth 60 points.
- It was worth 40 points. - Okay.
- You'll give us 60 points? - Let's go up to the front.
- Okay, let's go this. - I will show you a person.
- Write down his full name. - His full name?
He must be a foreigner.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Many sigh upon seeing who it is.)
- No way. - Gosh.
We're doomed. I have no idea.
I know who it is, but I don't know his full name.
I know him too, but not his full name.
I'm suddenly confused.
(Even the smart Jae Seok seems confused.)
(Vladimir Putin, President of Russia)
You know the two syllables, right?
- Yes. - Of course.
- He's the President of Russia. - Right.
I only know those two syllables.
- Same here. - Me too.
(Even Ji Hyo seems to know Putin.)
Is it Bush?
(Bush is the only President she knows with a two-syllables name.)
- Who is it? - Putin.
- Putin. - Putin?
Who's that?
(I haven't heard of him before.)
- Russia... - Tell us the last syllable.
I don't know his full name.
Can we at least know the first syllable?
- The first one. - Just the first one.
His first name is of five Korean syllables.
- Five? - Tell us the first one.
Then you'll be able to guess it.
- We won't. - I doubt it.
- I'm sure of it. - Some don't even know...
his last name.
- Exactly. - Somebody doesn't even know that.
Then I'll tell you the last letter of his first name.
It's probably a P or a T.
It ends with an R.
Really? I thought it ended with an S.
My answer ends with an S.
I don't have a clue.
I have to get this right in order to elevate my status on this show.
This one's too hard.
Hold up your answers.
(They show their answers one by one.)
(Remibonjar Putin)
What?
(Why are they laughing?)
Just so you know, I answered it in all seriousness.
I wrote down anything that made sense.
I'll go first.
I wrote Remibonjar Putin.
Remibonjar Putin.
There's an MMA fighter named Remy Bonjasky.
I get why he got them mixed up.
Let me now see Ji Hyo's answer.
- Is she kidding me? - I think it's right.
Really? Are you serious?
No way.
(Did she write down Vladimir Putin?)
- I take that back. - Ji Hyo got it right?
- What did she write? - I only saw the last syllable.
She wrote down Parrrrrr Putin.
Parrrrrr Putin.
- Jong Kook... - I have no idea.
- Mir Putin. - It was something-mir.
Seok Jin wrote Sultanvarrr Putin.
- Haha wrote Emelessor Putin. - Emelessor.
Emelessor Putin.
Emelessor...
- Wasn't it good? - Kwang Soo... It's a good one.
Bessamor Putin.
(Proud)
Bessamor.
Emelessor.
(Omegador Putin)
Omegador Putin.
- It sounds like a supplement. - Bessamor.
- Omega? - Omegador.
- It suddenly came to me. - Sultanvarrr Putin.
Emelessor.
It's Vladimir Putin.
- I think this is it. - Is it?
The answer is Vladimir Putin.
- That's right. - Yes, this.
I only could think of "mir."
- We went to Vladivostok, remember? - It was too difficult.
I couldn't have guessed it.
I'm sure that some didn't even know Putin.
I didn't.
So you failed the first round.
One will at least receive the penalty today.
One?
It shouldn't be either Haha or me.
- I did a good job on the quiz. - However,
do you see the booth in the back?
Even though you guys failed the mission,
you can still win candies.
The staff will say a certain range of numbers.
Each of you will go to the booth...
and hand in as many candies as you want in private.
If the total number of candies handed in...
happens to be in the given range,
you'll win double the number of candies you handed in.
We get more candies?
However, if the number is outside the range,
you'll lose the candies you handed in.
We've done something similar before.
- Right. - Yes.
We have to hand in more than a certain amount.
- But if some people don't... - But if some people don't,
it's annoying.
Here's the range.
The first range is...
between 19 and 29.
That's a lot.
- Hand in 19... - That's a lot.
to 29 candies.
To hand in 19 candies in total...
There are eight of us.
3 times 7 equals 21. 3 times 8 equals 24.
This is the first round. There's no reason not to hand in anything.
- We just have to hand in 3 each. - Yes, 3 each.
- If you don't, you're stupid. - All right. Let's do that.
Don't say Kwang Soo is stupid.
(Don't call him stupid.)
- One by one... - He can.
He's obviously joking.
You can go to the booth one by one in private.
- It'd be safer to hand in four. - That'd be safer.
That'd be safer.
- It won't exceed the number either. - Exactly.
Let's start.
Let me go first.
(Jong Kook hands in 4 as promised.)
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
I'm handing in four.
- Can I go next? - Okay.
(Se Chan somehow looks excited.)
Guys, you have to hand in the minimum amount.
I'm handing in four.
(Instead of being greedy, Se Chan kept his word.)
You don't even have to think.
What?
- I saw it. - What?
- You didn't hand in anything. - I did.
- I did. - You didn't?
- I did. - You should.
- I did. - I saw it.
I handed them in.
(Everyone is done.)
Let me announce the number of candies handed in.
- How many? - It has to be over 19.
(If the number is between 19 and 29, they can win more candies.)
You handed in 16 candies. You failed.
I can't believe you guys.
- You can't do this. - Unbelievable.
Why are you smiling?
- You guys! - Who...
Gosh, it's annoying!
I can't believe it.
(How many candies did each member hand in?)
I'm handing in one.
(So Min handed in only one to avoid ending up at the bottom.)
(Seok Jin handed in 3.)
I'm holding candies in my hand.
(After the confident announcement,)
(these three handed in zero candies.)
(Haha, Jae Seok, and Kwang Soo loses no candies.)
The four of us got fooled again.
- You didn't hand in anything. - I did.
- You didn't. Neither did Haha. - I did.
I can swear I did.
- I handed in so many. - Guys.
We're the ones who handed them in.
- I think four people did. - The first ones did.
- Four people did. - You handed in 10,
- and I handed in six. - I handed them in too.
I wanted more candies.
- If we get penalized, - This is shocking.
we'll choose one of those guys.
- Not me! - Why me?
(They all pretend to be innocent.)
- I'm innocent. - Why would you say that?
- We'll choose one of you guys. - I handed them in.
- I'm innocent. - I can't believe this.
That's just your prejudice. I handed them in.
I handed them in.
I really did.
I saw that you did not hand in anything.
- Me? - Yes.
- I did. - Gosh.
I'm disappointed in you.
You don't know yet.
- Let's eat in the second round. - Let's go.
Let's go.
Whatever, the war is on.
(With some people frustrated, they move on to Round 2.)
We'll be penalized.
I'll be penalized.
- Is everyone here? - Yes.
You came last, punk.
Watch your language.
You're younger than me anyway.
- You debuted later than me. - You debuted later than Jae Seok.
When will you stop saying that?
- It doesn't matter anymore. - What do you mean?
It doesn't matter. I'm older than you.
You're older than me?
- Did I just sound like a fossil? - You did.
- Totally. - Completely.
Even my mom thinks you're an old fossil.
(Even my mom thinks you're an old fossil.)
(Even someone his age agrees.)
While watching TV,
she said, "Mr. Jee definitely is an old fossil."
- "Mr. Jee". - That's good.
You should debut as a trot singer called Fossil.
- That's a good idea. - Fossil Jee.
- That's right. - Fossil Jee.
I'm not a fossil
- That's not it. - That's not it.
I'm a fossil, so what?
(I'm a fossil, so what?)
I'm a fossil wannabe
A fossil wannabe?
What's that?
- Seok Jin. - The title is, "In My Time".
- In my time - "In the Old Days".
In the old days
- You should do a series. - That sounds good.
Everyone calls me an old fossil
Even an old fossil can love
Even though I'm married
I'm on my own
(Catchy)
- Old people would love it. - Of course.
(The fossil anthem is complete.)
This mission can give you lunch and ice cream hotteoks.
The second mission is called...
- Food My Way. - "Food My Way"?
Ice cream hotteoks?
There are 8 dishes that cost between 50 cents...
and 15 dollars.
You'll choose one dish in private.
Ramyeon sounds nice.
If the dishes you chose cost less than 30 dollars in total,
- you all pass... - "Less than 30 dollars"?
and can eat what you chose.
If the dishes you chose cost 30 to 50 dollars in total,
you don't pass,
but you can still eat what you chose.
- Oh, my. This is tricky. - But if the dishes cost...
more than 50 dollars in total, you fail the mission...
- and get only rice and soy sauce. - To be honest,
I'm not even considering a filling course meal...
- or soy sauce marinated crab. - Me neither.
- Me neither. - I'll go for tteokbokki.
If we give up on soy sauce marinated crab and a course meal,
we can succeed.
- I'm craving tteokbokki. - Can I have a cola?
Just get rice and soup and be satisfied.
(He suddenly sounds like a fossil.)
Why do you say that?
Jong Kook, don't be so strict.
Jong Kook is a half-fossil.
(Jong Kook is a half-fossil.)
(Kim Jong Kook, a fossil in progress)
- Right. - He's halfway there.
That tone of yours.
- So Min. - Yes?
Let me ask you something.
Including yourself,
who's the worst old fossil here?
- Hey, Mr. Old Fossil. - You.
(Hey, Mr. Old Fossil.)
You.
What were you expecting?
- Jae Seok. - Did you think you weren't?
Jae Seok, look at this.
All of you here from Haha to Jong Kook are old fossils.
(The Old Fossil Belt is from Haha to Jong Kook.)
(Shocked)
Haha, you're one too.
- You're one too. - You're one too.
You little punks!
You little punks.
(Old fossils lose their temper easily.)
- You! - See?
Haha sounds totally like an old fossil when he's drunk.
He is.
He brags so much.
You should stop that.
- And he talks about his past a lot. - Why would you do that?
He never stopped talking.
Stop your nonsense!
I'm serious.
(Haha pretends to be angry.)
You're an old fossil too.
We're all old fossils
Let me say something that totally sounds like an old fossil.
Stop shooting.
(Stop shooting.)
Are you going to air all of this?
- Are you going to air all of this? - Stop shooting.
That's what an old fossil sounds like.
- We've got enough. Stop shooting. - Stop shooting.
If I'm going to be an old fossil anyway, I want to be a cool one.
- I want to be a cool old fossil - I want to be a cool old fossil
Put those cameras away.
I said, stop shooting! Put those cameras away!
You'll go into the restaurant one by one.
- Haha, go first. - Should I go first?
Make the right choice.
- I'll have ramyeon. - Okay.
What's that?
Oh, my.
We get to eat this if we succeed?
Oh, my gosh.
Ice cream hotteoks? They look amazing.
Seed hotteoks with ice cream?
My mouth is watering.
We have to succeed to eat this, right?
See you in a bit.
Their pork cutlets are delicious.
(In the restaurant, Haha is welcomed by...)
Look at that pork cutlet. Oh, my.
(A feast is prepared.)
(A filling course meal)
(Plump, soy sauce marinated crab)
(Crispy pork cutlets)
(The chosen dishes have to cost less than 30 dollars in total.)
(Now that he's seen the food...)
Gosh, what do I do?
What do I do with this food?
This...
I've been craving pork cutlets all day.
My mouth is watering.
I wouldn't dare to choose a filling course meal,
but pork cutlets might be okay.
Choose 1 dish on the count of 3. 1, 2, 3.
(Can Haha resist the pork cutlet?)
A pork cutlet meal.
(He chooses a 7-dollar pork cutlet meal.)
I'll have that.
(The pork cutlet makes Haha betray his team members.)
That looks fantastic.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Gosh, seeing all this food...
is driving me crazy.
I love this dish.
That pork cutlet looks delicious.
(Will Ji Hyo give in to the pork cutlet too?)
I want the pork cutlet so much.
I choose ramyeon.
(Ramyeon costs 2 dollars.)
(Jae Seok is frustrated too.)
I love ramyeon, but this pork cutlet looks...
I'll choose one of these two.
(My team's victory or my satisfaction,)
(that's the question.)
I choose this.
(Kwang Soo, Se Chan, Jong Kook, and So Min make up their minds.)
This is insane.
If we're going to fail anyway,
should I at least eat?
This is driving me crazy.
(He can't resist the 10-dollar crab.)
It looks so fresh.
Should I just eat this and not look at the bulletin board?
(I've made up my mind.)
(Seok Jin chooses the 10-dollar soy sauce marinated crab.)
For my team...
- Did you make the right choice? - Did you not betray us, right?
Let me announce the result of the second mission, Food My Way.
It can't go over 50 dollars.
If it does, I won't just sit back.
- I'll find the culprit. - It can't.
I want the hotteoks.
I'll tell you who chose which dish.
Haha chose...
a seven-dollar pork cutlet meal.
(Haha chose a 7-dollar pork cutlet meal.)
I knew it.
I told you that I will pick pork cutlet.
I knew Haha would do that.
Didn't you say you will pick ramyeon?
I told you that I will pick pork cutlet.
- Okay? - Let's hope...
- no one else picked pork cutlet. - Okay.
- I told you. - It will be over...
if someone else picked pork cutlet.
The menu Ji Hyo picked is...
- ramyeon that costs two dollars. - Good job.
I really wanted pork cutlet,
- but I picked ramyeon instead. - Okay.
- Jae Seok said he wants ramyeon. - Ramyeon.
- It has to be ramyeon. - He wouldn't have betrayed us.
It has to be ramyeon.
It has to be ramyeon no matter what.
Jae Seok picked ramyeon.
- Yes! - Jae Seok.
(When he picked the menu...)
Ramyeon.
My goodness.
- You are cool. - Did you see that, Ji Hyo?
(It's a heartwarming moment.)
- Did you see that? - Jae Seok.
Did you see that, Ji Hyo?
- It's Kwang Soo's turn. - If you didn't pick ramyeon...
I will end you if you didn't pick ramyeon.
Ramyeon.
(Kwang Soo picked ramyeon that costs 2 dollars.)
- Yes! - He's so cool.
I picked ramyeon. I picked ramyeon.
- What is up with you? - I picked ramyeon.
We will win if the rest of you picked ramyeon.
(The total cost could be under 30 dollars at this rate.)
- Se Chan picked... - Se Chan, you...
(Se Chan's choice)
ramyeon.
Ramyeon.
- We did it. We will succeed. - We did it.
- We did it. - We will succeed no matter what.
- Three people remain. - This is how it should be.
This is beautiful.
- This is beautiful. - Seok Jin is turning pale.
- No, no. - Seok Jin picked...
I will end Seok Jin if he picked a course meal.
(Jae Seok has no idea.)
Soy sauce marinated crab?
A 10-dollar soy sauce marinated crab.
(Seok Jin chose a 10-dollar soy sauce marinated crab.)
What is his problem?
(It ruins the heartwarming moment of unity.)
(The total cost is 25 dollars.)
Are you serious?
Jong Kook chose...
(Jong Kook and So Min remain.)
a three-dollar tteokbokki.
We did it.
(From the vehicle, he said he will have tteokbokki.)
I choose this.
(He picked tteokbokki without wavering.)
(The total cost is 28 dollars.)
What did So Min choose?
What did you choose?
So Min's menu will decide...
- You will be shocked. - What did you choose?
It's up to So Min's decision.
- So Min. - You will be shocked.
Praise me.
- So Min chose... - You will be shocked.
You will be in tears.
(What did So Min choose?)
A 50-cent boiled egg.
(Praise So Min.)
If I choose tteokbokki, it will go over by a dollar.
Then I have to choose a boiled egg.
To gain the team members' trust,
I will choose a boiled egg.
(The icon of trust and sacrifice, So Min)
We would have failed, had you chosen ramyeon.
- So Min! So Min! - Seriously.
So Min! I can't believe it.
This is the best.
- I... - So Min, are you on a diet?
We should celebrate without Seok Jin.
- Hey. - Seriously.
(He has soy sauce marinated crab, but he has no comradeship.)
In any case,
I chose something that is just right since I know you guys.
Thank goodness So Min is on a diet...
for her new drama.
- This is incredible. - Exempt me from the Yondu makeup.
- You deserve that. - My goodness.
It seems like Seok Jin will wear...
- the Yondu makeup. - He took another step towards it.
Yondu.
Thus, you will get the menu you ordered.
(They will get lunch and ice cream hotteoks.)
- We succeeded in the mission. - You will get ice cream hotteoks.
This is a good day.
I will have tteokbokki, fritters, and hotteok.
The pork cutlet looks amazing.
It looks delicious.
(The menu shows self-love!)
(Eating)
Is it good?
Here is water.
(This pork cutlet tastes amazing!)
(Jae Seok eats ramyeon.)
Please remember that you are having lunch...
- because I chose a boiled egg. - That's right.
Ice cream hotteoks are here.
(Ice cream hotteoks are here.)
Are these the ice cream hotteok?
There is ice cream inside a hotteok.
(It looks delicious.)
It's delicious.
- It's delicious. - Right?
It tastes like a waffle.
It's really tasty.
Since you succeeded in the mission,
you will play Candy Dilemma, a game that can get you more candies.
Write down a number from 1 to 10 in secret...
and turn it in.
Excluding the overlapping numbers,
the person who wrote down the highest number...
will get the same number of candies.
You need to get the highest number that doesn't overlap.
The highest number no one else chose.
This is insane.
What should I do?
A lot of people will choose the two-digit number, right?
Seven would be a good choice.
Seven, my foot. Stop playing tricks.
Don't trust anything that comes out...
of that treacherous mouth.
- Seriously. - That treacherous mouth...
- "That treacherous mouth"? - Stop playing tricks.
I ate ramyeon!
Don't live that way.
What are you talking about? I ate ramyeon.
I wrote down a number with confidence.
- Me too. - I will turn it in.
We can't choose 10 now. Jae Seok chose 10.
(Who will get candies?)
Maybe no one chose 10.
- I will turn it in. - I will turn it in.
Come on. You can trust me.
- Put it in. - So Min, give it to me.
Why can't you trust me? Why are you putting your guards up?
I was afraid you would see it.
Why would I see it?
He will trust you when he loves you.
Don't you love me yet?
- Don't be ridiculous. - When will you love me?
Give me some time.
So Min.
- I will announce the result. - Okay.
(The result of Candy Dilemma)
People who chose 10...
I guess many people chose 10.
How many people chose 10?
Se Chan, Jae Seok, and Ji Hyo.
(Se Chan, Jae Seok, and Ji Hyo are out.)
Three people are out.
Then there is a member who wrote down the lowest number.
So Min wrote down four.
(So Min is out.)
I don't think So Min will be able to eat.
One person wrote seven.
It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo chose 7!)
(He is a strong candidate.)
Among the remaining three members,
eight was written down...
(If all 3 of them wrote down the same number, Kwang Soo wins.)
by Haha and Seok Jin.
(Haha and Seok Jin are out!)
- Did I win? - Jong Kook wrote down nine.
- Did I win with 9? - Jong Kook wrote down 9.
That means Kwang Soo failed.
Did he fail?
- What? - Good job.
(Disappointed)
I changed the number from 8 to 9 at the last minute.
- You will get nine candies. - Are you serious?
- You could share them. - I won't do that. Give them to me.
(I won't do that. Give them to me.)
(He is greedy for candies.)
- Please give me one. - No, no.
I will give one to Ji Hyo.
- Jong Kook. - Why?
- Why would you do that? - Why?
I handed in a lot of candies too.
I will give one to Ji Hyo and Haha.
- I need candies too. - What about me?
Please give me one.
What about me, Jong Kook?
Don't speak nonsense. Be quiet.
(Why are you so mean to me?)
I chose ramyeon.
I used seven candies as I promised!
Sit down.
I mean...
- Thank you. - Please give me one.
- I used seven candies. - Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, give me one.
(Haha gets 1 candy!)
(Thank goodness I didn't get caught.)
Thank you.
I spent four candies before.
- For now... - Please give me one.
Let's do this.
- I might end up placing last. - No.
So Min, you hurt my feelings.
You chose to sit next to Se Chan instead of me.
It's not like that.
I want to check some photos with him.
I doubt that.
- Just now? - She never leaves Se Chan's side.
It's not like that.
You are just a nice man...
while Se Chan is the man she loves.
Se Chan is the man she loves.
- Let me see it. - It's a nice photo.
It looks like a photo they took at an airport...
on their way to honeymoon.
I didn't know I was smiling like that.
They look like newlyweds.
It looks like a photo they took at an airport.
- "You're My Sunshine!" - "You're My Sunshine!"
I didn't know I was smiling like that.
(They sing the OST of "You're My Sunshine!")
Se Chan!
- She's mimicking Jeon Do Yeon. - Se Chan!
I learned that tone from Se Chan.
Se Chan!
I am exhausted, So Min.
Se Chan said he is exhausted with a smile on his face.
"I am exhausted."
What was that?
(When did I do that?)
(He looked so cheerful.)
- Stop it. Stop it. - "I am exhausted."
(Ji Hyo bursts out laughing.)
I haven't heard that kind of laughter from Ji Hyo in a while.
Ji Hyo.
That was an honest laugh.
- I burst out laughing. - That's right.
Ji Hyo.
I burst out laughing.
Gosh, I love this kind of snack.
(They arrive at the location of the third mission.)
- I love this kind of snack. - What is this?
I love this kind of snack.
- It's a healthy snack. - It contains fruits.
It's a healthy snack.
(There are fruits inside chewy rice cake.)
(Sweet and refreshing fruit rice cake)
I want the one with strawberries.
- I want the one with strawberries. - Me too.
I love this kind of snack.
Something funny happened...
in the vehicle.
Mi Yeon, the writer,
stumbled when the vehicle came to a sudden halt.
Seok Jin spoke like a senior university student.
"Mi Yeon, don't hurt yourself."
(My goodness.)
(Stumbling)
(He almost hurt himself.)
"Don't hurt yourself."
(Flailing)
He almost hurt himself badly.
He almost fell off the vehicle.
He could have just said,
"Mi Yeon, are you okay? Be careful."
"Mi Yeon, don't hurt yourself."
(He embarrassed himself.)
The third mission in which you could win...
fruit rice cakes is...
Categories, Answer Me.
- Categories, Answer Me. - Categories, Answer Me.
(What could it be?)
When I give you a category,
everyone must say a fitting answer that doesn't overlap...
in eight seconds in order to succeed.
(Everyone must say a fitting answer that doesn't overlap in 8 seconds.)
Jae Seok isn't good at games.
I am good at this kind of game.
We just need to succeed once, right?
There will be three rounds. 8 members must answer in 8 seconds.
- Let's go. - Each member has a second.
Let's go. Categories, Answer Me.
Set, go.
Movies with aliens in them.
..., go.
"Alien".
"Armageddon".
- Six, - "Aliens".
- five, - "Independence Day".
- four, - "Men in Black".
- "Mars Attacks!". - "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial".
- One. - "Men in Black II".
(They fail Round 1.)
There are no aliens in "Armageddon."
Who said "Armageddon"?
(They all turn their heads.)
- There are no aliens in it. - Why did you do that one?
They just go to Mars in "Armageddon." They go abroad.
(They just go to Mars in "Armageddon." They go abroad.)
(They go abroad?)
- They go abroad? - No, I mean...
What are you talking about?
Bruce Willis stars in it.
- They leave to protect Earth. - They're in space.
They prevent an asteroid from colliding into Earth.
- I know. - A comet.
There might be aliens in "Armageddon" if you look carefully.
- No, there aren't. - No?
There was a movie where Kwang Soo was a fish. Is that also an alien?
It's a fish person. How's that an alien?
(It's a fish person!)
- What is it then? - It's not an alien.
- It's a mutant. - On "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks,"
- aren't you an alien? - Why am I an alien?
(He's enraged.)
- Because of your butt. - Your butt was too droopy.
Your butt.
You had no butt.
I was not an alien.
My character was called Cho Kka Chi.
(It sounds like he's cursing.)
- No? - My bad.
I see.
Dooly's grandfather is in my related search.
(He's known for having a flat butt.)
- Seriously? - Yes.
Haha said he looked like Dooly's grandfather.
This is an easy question. You have three chances left.
- Good luck. Keep it going. - Let's do this.
- Let's do it this time. - Let's go.
Should I go to the end?
- I think that's better. - Should we do that?
Let's do that. Move over.
- I'll stay in the middle. - Okay.
- This is good. - You're going to be in the middle?
Leave the easy ones.
- The peaks are too high here. - Stop pretending like you're good.
(This is the Himalayas of quizzes. Nobody can reach the top.)
I'm the leader here.
- Why me? - I'll be quick.
Let's do this.
Should we start? What should we do?
- Yes, start with Jae Seok. - Okay.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
- Good luck! - Good luck!
- Let's go. - Give us slightly easier ones.
Let's go. Categories, Answer Me, start.
Words with ssang giyeok in them. Eight,
- Flowers. - seven,
- six... - Dud.
- Old fossil. - Tin.
- 4, 3... - Peeled tangerine.
- Three, - Peeled tangerine.
- two... - Tangerine. Honey.
What was that?
What was that about?
Haha.
- I did it. - What was that?
- Are you out of your mind? - I did it.
What was that about?
Did you see four of them standing up at once?
They all stood up to kill one person.
That startled me.
(As soon as the bell rang,)
(all 4 of them stood at once.)
(He was intimidated.)
I don't even remember.
I don't remember. What did I say?
- There are so many words. - What did I say?
- What was that? - What did I say?
- Tangerine? Was that it? - What was that?
- There's honey water. - Cockle.
Let's keep going.
Be quick.
We have to speak fast.
I answer as soon as Chul Min asks me.
I answer right away. It's back and forth.
- There goes the emperor of ad-lib. - Move. Start.
Here we go.
Categories, Answer Me, start.
Korean people in history. Eight...
- Shin Saimdang. - Sejong the Great.
- Yi Sun Shin. - Jang Bo Go.
- Yul Gok. - Four...
- Toi Gye Yi Hwang. - Gang Gam Chan.
Two...
- What? - What did you do?
- Sejong the Great! - Jae Seok!
Four people took mine!
- Four people took mine! - Think!
I was going to do Yi Sun Shin then I thought of Toi Gye Yi Hwang.
Then what was I supposed to do?
- You can't do this to me. - There were more.
The last person is important. It's hard.
- It's hard. I know. - You get stuck.
This is your last chance. Where do you want to start?
Please give us an easy one.
- This side. - That side is better.
Let's go.
Categories, Answer Me, start.
Foreign musicians. Eight,
(What did you say?)
- What did you say? - seven...
- Hurry up. Anybody. - He didn't understand. Start over.
- Sorry. - Foreign musicians.
- Start with him. - 8, 7...
- Me too. - He's a musician.
- 6, 5, - Beethoven.
- Beethoven. - four,
- Mozart. - three...
(Beethoven, Mozart...)
- Ji Hyo has got nothing. - Goodness.
(They run out of time in the last round.)
Ji Hyo.
- For a moment... - Chopin.
- Bach. - Handel and Bach.
Sonata.
(Confidently)
What was that?
Sonata?
Somebody's going to say Beyer.
- What? - Are you serious?
(Something tells me I'm wrong.)
I was thinking of Michael Jackson.
It's foreign musician, so doesn't Michael Jackson work?
- I panicked. - You can do him.
I thought I had to say a hard one.
It's not hard. Beethoven is not hard, you punk!
(Beethoven is not hard, you punk!)
(He's furious.)
Fine.
- I know. - You need to understand.
- Thug. - One last chance.
If one person gives up their candy, then I'll give you another chance.
- Give up yours. - Who should it be?
- Seriously. - Jae Seok.
You answered 1 in 7 seconds.
- Let's place Race of Wits. - Haha.
- Okay, Race of Wits. - Race of Wits.
More games.
There are too many games within games.
Let's try one more time.
- I'll be sitting until the end. - Start.
- I'm serious. - One.
Two.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 6.
(7, 8.)
(What did he say?)
That was a clean loss, Seok Jin.
They have great teamwork.
- My goodness. - This is back and forth.
(It's him again.)
7, 8.
Running Man members have great teamwork.
- I don't have too many left. - 7, 8.
Categories, Answer Me, start.
Mixed-gender bands. 8, 7,
6, 5,
- COOL. - four,
- three, - Time out.
- two... - Pause.
You timed out at five seconds.
- Time out. - Just do whatever.
- Just do whatever. - You have to start off.
- Every second matters. - Again.
We timed out at five seconds.
- I did COOL, right? - He took three seconds.
- You can finish in 5 seconds. - Go fast.
Let's go.
- Ready, - I'm going to do COOL.
- set, go. - Got it.
- COOL. - Roo'Ra.
- Space A. - I was going to do...
- What? - Goodness.
- What? - 2, 1.
I was going to do Space A.
- I told you to do Roo'Ra. - I said I was going to do it.
I was thinking of Space A the whole time.
This is what I told him. What was it?
UP, COOL, Roo'Ra, Space A.
That's what we were going to do.
- Space A. - Hold on.
You failed Categories, Answer Me.
(They fail Categories, Answer Me.)
There are still chances to earn more candies.
If you're within the range, we'll double your candies.
I'm in last place.
Here's the range for the number of candies.
19 to 29.
(Range: 19 to 29 candies)
It's unchanged.
Please hand in the candies one at a time.
We can go over.
That's my concern.
Se Chan didn't give up any earlier.
He didn't.
I did hand in some. I really did.
- Are you going to hand in 6? - I'll give up everything I have. 6.
Go, Se Chan.
I'll hand in five.
- That's a lot. - I'll hand in three.
(He's careful.)
Six.
(He gives up everything he has.)
(Their candies get doubled if they fall within the range.)
Did you do it? Six?
- Are you sure? - You handed in six?
This is giving me a headache. I'm going to hand in 11.
- What? - I'm going to hand in 11.
- Really? We're going to go over. - You don't have too many left.
- I don't think we'll go over. - We will.
I'm going to do three. Ji Hyo gave up some too.
This is going to go over.
It won't, Haha. It won't go over.
How many did you give up?
I can't tell you, but I gave a lot.
Hold on.
I just got goosebumps.
Didn't Haha say he gave up his candies earlier?
He did.
- Right? - Yes.
- So you gave him some. - So I gave him one.
That's true.
Why do you have 11 then?
(Why do you have 11 then?)
- That's not true. - Hey.
- I said too much. - Attention.
- Are you serious? - I have it.
I got goosebumps.
- Did he betray you? - Jong Kook.
- He didn't give up any earlier. - He didn't.
It was me.
What are you talking about? It was me.
I swear it was me.
Jong Kook, you trust Haha too much.
He more than betrayed you.
This is mind-blowing.
He said he was going to hand in 11. He couldn't have 11.
He took mine.
Trust me.
- My gosh. - This is insane.
- I got goosebumps. - It'll soon be over.
- Unbelievable. - I do it.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn.)
We won't go over this time.
(He's serious.)
Jong Kook handed in three.
(The result might change depending on what Kwang Soo does.)
I'm not good at this kind of stuff.
Don't hand in any, Kwang Soo.
- Don't hand in any. - Just live like you always have.
Don't hand in any candies.
(What will be Kwang Soo's choice?)
Kwang Soo.
You won't hand in any candies.
- You need to avoid placing last. - Seriously.
(0 candies)
(Did he hand in candies?)
- Stop it. - Come here.
(Everyone handed in candies!)
(What is the total number of candies?)
All right. I will give you the number.
- Okay. Did we go over? - I am curious.
The range is between 19 and 29.
The number of candies you handed in is...
(If the number is within the range,)
(everyone will get twice the candies they handed in.)
- 28. - We did it.
(The number is within the range.)
Is it within the range?
- What does it mean? - It's within the range.
- Will everyone eat? - We are safe.
Will everyone eat?
(Everyone gets twice the candies they handed in.)
(So Min gets 6, Ji Ho gets 8,)
(Haha gets 8,)
(Jong Kook gets 6,)
(Seok Jin gets 10, Jae Seok gets 6,)
(and Se Chan gets 12.)
(The current number of candies)
(Kwang Soo places last with 10 candies.)
I got goosebumps.
I would like to remind you that...
only those of you who handed in candies...
- will get twice... - Did someone not hand in candies?
- the amount. - Someone didn't hand in candies.
I thought a lot about whether I should hand in one more.
Everyone looks happy, but Kwang Soo looks sad.
(He can't hide his sadness.)
- Look at Kwang Soo's face. - Are you okay?
I am set now.
- I am rich now. - Is that so?
Sure.
We will move on to the last round.
(With Kwang Soo feeling sad, they move on to the last round.)
- Honey butter sweet potato. - What is that?
(Honey butter sweet potatoes await them.)
- Gosh, they look delicious. - What are these?
(Sweet honey and soft butter inside sweet potatoes)
Sweet potatoes.
- They smell amazing. - Sweet potatoes, butter, and honey.
- So Min. - Don't put your nose in them.
(Did she put her nose in them?)
They smell so nice.
My nose didn't touch them.
It's okay even if it did. We are a family.
He is generous.
Jong Kook, do you like So Min?
(Do you like So Min?)
Sometimes...
(Does he like me as well?)
(He feels sad for some reason.)
I feel uncomfortable.
Jong Kook, do you like me?
(She shows off her charms.)
- Come on. - You need a beating...
to come to your senses.
(Scared)
It's time for the final mission to acquire the upgraded version...
of a famous winter snack, honey butter sweet potatoes.
- The final mission. - Sweet potatoes.
Don't Cross the Line.
- Don't Cross the Line? - What is that?
(What is that?)
It's what you see at the beach.
- You throw a coin. - You win prizes that way.
I know this game.
Each member will throw an R coin on a panel with squares...
ranging from 50 cents to 10 dollars.
If the total amount in 2 rounds is 25 dollars or greater,
the mission is a success.
The R coin needs to land within the boundary.
If it lands on the line, you fail to win money.
The lines are quite thick.
There aren't many 10-dollar squares.
You can hit and push each other's coin.
We will get started when you say, "Here I go."
- I will go first. Here I go. - Let's go.
(Jong Kook goes first!)
This is hard. It will be hard to get the 10-dollar squares.
(The 10-dollar squares are smaller.)
(Jong Kook lowers his body...)
(and throws the coin.)
There you go.
(The coin slides.)
- Two dollars. - Okay.
(He wins 2 dollars right away!)
We are off to a good start.
We are...
- What? - We are off to a good start.
We are off to a good start, are we?
Good job.
I will hold your hand. Lean forward.
It will be fine as long as your feet stay in.
- Okay. There you go. - There you go.
- Let's go a bit further. - A bit further.
This is cool. We look really cool right now.
(Are you sure about that?)
(Approaching)
Pull. I will lean forward.
- This is good. - Pull harder.
Hey, So Min is watching.
(Knowing that So Min is watching makes him falter.)
(What is up with him?)
Do I look okay?
Seriously.
So Min's facial expression is so oily.
(I will cheer for Se Chan.)
(Their position is set!)
You look like a hero right now.
Let me go a bit further.
(He carefully throws the coin like a hero!)
So Min is watching.
(Se Chan has So Min's support.)
(What will be the result?)
(The coin lands on a 10-dollar square!)
(He succeeded to acquire 10 dollars.)
(Everyone is excited.)
(The total becomes 12 dollars in 2 turns.)
Let's do this.
We won't get this kind of chance again.
- You looked so cool. - Really?
- That was amazing. - I would like to remind you that...
the member in last place won't get a chance...
to win more candies if this mission ends successfully.
You won't get a chance to hand in candies.
Let me explain. If this mission ends successfully,
we won't get to bet our candies.
- The rankings will stay the same. - We won't hand in candies.
The rankings will stay the same.
We still need to succeed in this mission.
What is it, Kwang Soo?
- But... - It's worrisome even if we succeed.
The person in last place should be careful.
Okay.
Just be careful not to hit the coin on the 10-dollar square.
(Kwang Soo made up his mind to do something evil.)
(It's Haha's turn.)
(Throwing)
(50 cents)
(I could have gotten 10 dollars.)
At least we got 50 cents.
- It suits you. - 50 cents suit you.
No coins are on the lines.
Everyone did a good job.
- No coins are on the lines. - Everyone did a good job.
We have 12.50 dollars.
Hold on. Kwang Soo is practicing to hit the coins.
That's not true.
(Earlier)
(His eyes are on the coin on the 10-dollar square.)
(He wants to hit the coin.)
That's not true.
I was trying out new methods.
(He becomes wary of Kwang Soo.)
Let's see what Kwang Soo does.
Ji Hyo.
(Kwang Soo gives her a lift.)
Make sure your feet stay behind.
- Make sure your feet stay behind. - This is a good idea.
You can do it. It looks promising.
- This is a good form. - This is a good idea.
Make sure your feet stay behind. I will hold your feet.
This is the best. She will get 10 dollars for sure.
There you go.
- Ji Hyo. - Throw lightly.
(Ji Hyo is ready.)
Ji Hyo, get 10 dollars.
(She just needs to throw the coin lightly.)
(Will the airplane method succeed?)
(Lifting)
(Kwang Soo lifts Ji Hyo up.)
(He did it as Ji Hyo threw the coin.)
(What will be the result of his action?)
- Do it lightly. - Come on.
That was close.
(She could have gotten 3 dollars.)
Her aim was nice.
(She didn't add more money.)
(My goodness.)
- Her aim was nice. - What?
Why did you kick?
(Why did you kick in the end?)
(He got caught.)
(Did he kick?)
Three dollars.
Go for a three-dollar square.
Stop worrying and throw.
(Throwing)
(It lands on a line.)
(The total is still 12.50 dollars.)
- I missed. - It's on a line.
- This is hard. - 1 dollar or 1.50 dollars.
(Jae Seok throws.)
- Gosh, I missed. - Did you miss?
(Jae Seok fails.)
(Thank goodness.)
So Min.
- That's good. - There you go.
I wish it had gone a bit further.
- I was close. - She really looked like a frog.
(They have 12.50 dollars left to go.)
- I haven't gone yet. - Do you want me to lift you up?
Yes.
- Do you? - Yes.
- Wait. He might do something weird. - No, I won't.
Haha.
- Haha. - He can get...
- He can get the 10-dollar square. - Haha.
(The squares are really close to Kwang Soo.)
(With 10 candies, Kwang Soo is likely to receive a penalty.)
(If the mission ends successfully, he won't get to move up the ranks.)
(The coin on the 10-dollar square is the biggest obstacle.)
(I need to hit that coin on the 10-dollar square.)
(Dropping)
(He drops the coin.)
Hey! Hold on. He dropped it.
He dropped it.
(Nerves make him lose his grip.)
(I need to hit that coin!)
He is acting strange.
- He is acting strange, right? - No, no.
Why did you aim for this square?
(Throwing)
(Let me hit that coin.)
(I hope this mission fails.)
(The 1st round ends with a total of 12.50 dollars.)
- See? - He is acting strange.
(JI Hyo, Jong Kook, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo won 2.50 dollars.)
(It's So Min's turn.)
I am sorry, but would you help her with her form?
(Would you help your girlfriend with her form?)
I don't think she knows what she is doing.
Hold my hand.
- Hold my hand. - Okay.
(The two married men are excited for their sake.)
Hold my hand.
(Romantic)
Hold my hand well, you little...
(Hold my hand well, you little...)
(Her words are as wild as her love.)
- Se Chan won't let go. - No, I won't.
Let me support your weight. There you go.
- There you go. - The power of love!
(Throwing)
The power of love!
(She got 1.50 dollars.)
- 1.50 dollars. - 1.50 dollars. Good job.
(They need to get 8.50 dollars.)
- Why are you sweating so much? - It's hot in here.
- It's over if we get 10 dollars. - It's over if we get 10 dollars.
- How many of us haven't gone yet? - I haven't gone yet.
- Haha. - I really hope we succeed.
You never know what will happen in a variety show.
Why don't you sit down more?
(His tone isn't polite.)
(Despite being 10 years younger, Jong Kook uses a casual tone.)
- Why should I do that? - You are standing up too much.
It's okay. Just throw the coin.
- Gosh, that won't do. - 1.50 dollars.
It's okay.
We are closer to our goal.
- It's time to get 10 dollars. - 10 dollars.
Haha, let's do this.
Throw it.
(They succeed if Haha's coin lands on a 10-dollar square.)
(Will Haha be able to finish the mission?)
(He throws the coin!)
(Haha throws the coin...)
(and it rolls towards the 10-dollar square!)
(Will it land on a 10-dollar square?)
(It touches the line of a one-dollar square.)
(Haha fails to get money.)
- I thought he got it. - Me too.
- He passed by it. - That was close.
He touched the line.
- This is hard. - It's all on you.
You're an expert at these kinds of things.
You can do it. You will be a hero.
You always pull through in difficult circumstances.
(It's all up to Jae Seok!)
(As soon as he inserted, the pirate popped out.)
(He turns a crisis into an opportunity.)
(Whenever he threw darts,)
(he always hit the bullseye.)
(Jae Seok shines during the most difficult time.)
(Will he carry the team this time as well?)
Should I get closer?
Kwang Soo's plane is not bad.
- His airplane? - It's not bad.
You know, right? He's on the opposite side.
You don't know what he's going to do.
I won't let go.
(Trust me, Jae Seok.)
(Raising)
Hold on. You just raised me with your feet.
No, no.
(You just raised me with your feet.)
He raised his feet?
I was getting in the right position.
(Don't be mistaken.)
- Are you sure? - I was getting in position.
(He trusts Kwang Soo once more and leans his body.)
Go for 10 dollars.
(They make a plane,)
(and he tosses.)
(He tossed it.)
(They need 7 more dollars. If he gets 10, then they win.)
(If he fails, the mission is over. They won't have sweet potatoes.)
(What is the result?)
(The coin rolls toward 10 dollars.)
(Will miracles come true?)
(Cheering)
Wait.
(He landed on 10 dollars.)
(It touched the line though.)
It didn't touch the line.
- It did. - It didn't.
(They are 7 dollars short.)
- That was so close. - That was close.
- That was so close. - That really was.
You failed this round.
(Don't Cross the Line is a fail.)
(Kwang Soo is relieved.)
(Candy Booth reopens for Kwang Soo to turn the game around.)
I almost had 10 dollars.
That was really close.
It was 1mm.
The range this time is...
(Range: 17 to 27)
17 to 27.
- 27? - It's less.
(Within range: win double, Outside of range: lose all)
They adjusted it.
If we bet 3 each, then it's 24.
The person who thinks they're in last place...
- will hand in everything. - Right.
That's how they can turn this around.
To stop that, we can't just bet less.
- We either bet nothing... - Or go over.
or go over.
We have to predict how many they have.
- Se Chan first. - Should I start?
(Se Chan goes first.)
I feel like I'm in first place.
(He has 18 candies in total.)
(Thinking)
(Current Number of Candies)
I'm not going to bet any.
- You're not going to bet? - Yes.
I'm betting none.
I have to win first place.
All right.
(He wants the penalty exemption, so he bets 0.)
Will we go over?
Will that happen?
This is complicated.
- Right? - I don't even know.
(Ji Hyo has 15 candies in total.)
I'll bet two.
(She bets 2.)
Is this the right choice?
I'll leave it up to fate. I'll keep 10,
and bet five.
I'll bet some.
(Jong Kook hands in 2 out of 19.)
Good work.
I won't bet too low or too high.
(Jae Seok hands in 3 out of 15.)
(Haha hands in 7 out of 19.)
(Current number of candies: 19)
I'll go.
(Seok Jin hands in 0 out of 15.)
(7 members made their bets.)
This is giving me a headache.
(Kwang Soo goes last.)
(Spilling)
Wait. This is giving me a headache.
I have 10. That's unchanged.
- 17 to 27? - Yes.
Let's say everybody bet 2 to 3 each.
16 to 27.
(If he bets 9, then they go over.)
I have to bet seven for sure. But if we go over...
(What will happen if we go over?)
Let me think about that scenario.
If we go over, I'm still last place.
(He realizes it quickly.)
I have to do this.
I have to get within the range.
So, what's the maximum I can bet?
(He has to get within the range, and win double.)
Wait. Three to start.
If I do all 10, then we'll go over.
(If I do all 10, then we'll go over.)
Did they bet or not?
(It depends on how many candies the members bet.)
Hold on.
I'm going to bet seven for sure.
(He bets 7.)
What should I do with these three?
This is driving me insane.
Should I bet just one more?
- Let me bet 1 more. That's 8. - Okay.
Never mind. We might go over by one.
We were within the range by one earlier.
Should I bet one more or not?
If they bet three each... No.
There's no way they would do that. One more.
I bet one more.
At eight, I will stop.
(Current number: 27)
- I bet 8. - Okay, I got 8.
(Pausing)
(If he bets one more, they go over.)
(He will be in last place.)
I will stop.
(He makes up his mind for the 3rd time)
(Stopping)
3 times 7 is 21.
Let me bet one more. This is the last time.
One more.
(Hesitating)
I hate this.
I don't want to be Yondu and sell fish-shaped buns.
I'm going crazy.
(He doesn't want the penalty. How many did he bet in the end?)
- He's back. - Is he back?
(Kwang Soo returns after betting his candies.)
- Why are you running back? - He has none left.
He went all-in.
He's all-in. I don't hear anything rustling.
No, I didn't.
Let's see how this ends.
The result is shocking.
(The total amount is shocking)
Really?
Kwang Soo must have won.
(Did Kwang Soo turn the game around?)
Oh, dear.
17 to 27 was the range.
The number of candies submitted is...
(Each person made their bets without telling each other.)
(If they fall within the range, they win double what they bet.)
(If they're out of the range, they lose what they bet.)
(Is the total between 17 to 27?)
28.
- Fail. - We went over.
(That's the total submitted.)
Fail. You failed by one.
(A moment earlier)
(I don't want to be Yondu and sell fish-shaped buns.)
(He was afraid of the penalty.)
(Gosh)
(He ate a candy because it made him suffer.)
- I'll hand it in. That's 9. - You ate 1.
(He bet 9 in total.)
Nine. You have none left.
Yes, nine. I'll bet all.
(He made the wrong decision.)
(The total is 28, so they go over by 1.)
You failed by one.
- Should I announce first place? - Yes.
(We know who's in last place.)
The person in first place is...
(1st place will be exempted from the penalty.)
It was very close.
Se Chan wins with 18.
(Se Chan is 1st place.)
Come on!
- He didn't bet any. - Come on!
I didn't.
(He didn't bet any.)
(Se Chan is exempted from the penalty.)
He didn't bet any?
I'm first place.
Se Chan was in last place after the 1st round with 6.
Right. Really?
- You were the one who bet. - I bet four.
- He won. - I went all-in in the second round.
I knew it.
- Jong Kook. - I knew you would win.
- That punk. - We knew it.
(That punk.)
I can't believe I'm doing business with this guy.
- You're exempted from the penalty. - Exempted.
(2nd place gets announced next.)
Jong Kook is in 2nd place with 17.
(Jong Kook is in 2nd place.)
- By 1. - I bet 2.
Seok Jin is in 3rd place with 15.
Next is Ji Hyo with 13.
Haha and Jae Seok were tied...
- They tied? - at 12.
Then what? So Min and Kwang Soo?
And So Min is in 7th place with 10.
The person in last place is Kwang Soo.
Penalties will be given to...
Kwang Soo and So Min.
(They have to dress up as Yondu and sell fish-shaped buns.)
They can pick one person to go with them.
- Se Chan, you are exempt. - Yes.
Let's talk.
(They get to pick 1 person to join them.)
(Please, not me.)
Let's talk. Who do you want to pick?
(Kwang Soo says a name.)
- One person will join them. - Why?
- This is cruel. - Why?
We'll pick.
(They get to pick one person...)
(to join them and sell fish-shaped buns together.)
(Fish-shaped buns taste great in the cold weather.)
(To express their gratitude to their fans,)
(they'll be selling fish-shaped buns in the middle of the street.)
(Who are the lucky 3 up for the job?)
(Younger son Kwang Yondu)
(He's an expert in playing mutants.)
(Adorable daughter Jeon Yondu)
(You can't beat the original.)
(Who's the last member joining them?)
(Oldest son Kook Yondu)
(They called out members who were exempt.)
(They left one at a time.)
(Jong Kook and Haha were left behind.)
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook was the last person.)
(Haha was exempt.)
- Bye. - Bye.
Bye.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, you two.
(Jong Kook got the penalty.)
Goodness. Let's go.
(Jong Kook tried to stop Kwang Soo from messing up.)
(The Yondu trio is formed.)
(He's bitter.)
Please come over.
(They'll be expressing gratitude for all the support they got.)
- There are 70 made. - Okay.
One person can make 30 more.
- Two of you can hand them out. - Okay.
(She starts making ones filled with red beans.)
(Daughter Jeon Yondu is in charge.)
- Hello. - If you would like...
some fish-shaped buns, come on over.
We'll give fish-shaped buns out for free.
We'll give them out for free.
It's good.
We're not weirdos.
Don't retreat.
- I'm Jong Kook. He's Kwang Soo. - Right.
- Hello. - Hi.
(They have their first customers.)
- I washed my hands. - Give them two each.
I'll give you a red bean and a choux cream.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Bye. All right.
- The 2 of you... - We'd like 6.
- We should give out two each. - Yes.
Right. You were pretty shocked, weren't you?
- Bye. - All of these...
- Kwang Soo. - Take a photo with me.
A photo? Sure.
(Their fish-shaped buns are delicious.)
- Should we put them in the cups? - Okay. In the paper cups?
- Let's give them out in the cups. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
You're done with your penalty.
Thank you.
She's Yondu.
- All right. - Okay.
We're Yondu Siblings.
I knew that things were going too well today.
(I'm sorry for choosing you.)
I never get that lucky, you know.
I eventually had to do the penalty.
(Clenching his teeth)
Well, this is just getting started.
It's really funny to see them fight with the makeup.
This is hilarious.
Talking to each other with the makeup...
makes me feel like I'm watching a musical.
("Yondu: Ill-Fated Relationship Reboot")
(An investment class which is more fun than a musical is held.)
(To take the class,)
(Lee Hee Jin and Kang Han Na have come.)
(Yoo Byung Jae and YooA are attending the class too.)
(1st class: How to make good investments)
(They will make investments in different fields every time.)
(They must carefully decide on whom to make investments.)
(2nd class: How to get investments)
(To get investments, one must be bold.)
(They must get investments with their unyielding bold acts.)
(And luck)
(Some people are lucky.)
(And some are not.)
(The members face a shocking result when they are learning?)
No way. All-in?
(Everyone looks out for themselves in the world of investors.)
(Which one is the top investor who made wise investments?)
(Run to You: Project to Attract Investments)