(Running Man has been airing for 9 years without a break.)
(So many of the fans have supported the members of Running Man.)
(We have prepared this special episode to repay their support.)
(The very first fan-meet in Korea, Running Man's Fan-Meet)
(Opening song by all 8 members)
(The first performance was a grand opening of the fan-meet.)
(The opening song by the members was about gratitude for the fans.)
(And there are more performances to come.)
(It's time to show off their charms.)
(The members of Running Man will perform separately.)
(Apink, Nucksal and Code Kunst, SORAN, and Gummy)
(Joint performances with the best lineup of musicians)
(Group choreography)
(And the highlight of the fan-meet, the group choreography)
(Theme song, "I Like You")
(The show's first theme song will make the grand finale!)
(The fan-meet of Running Man starts now.)
(They went on a long journey of 100 days in preparing it.)
(The fan-meet begins at last.)
(Utterly nervous)
(However...)
- "a spy among you." - Come on!
(There is a spy among you today.)
(One of them is a spy?)
(We asked the spy to be the most passionate today.)
(The audience already knows who the spy is.)
(There are hints?)
you finish your performance,
(When the members finish their performance,)
(if the shout from the audience is over 120dB, they get a hint.)
(Why are you doing this?)
With your expectations...
(After learning about the mission, they finish the opening segment.)
(The race...)
(starts!)
(It's time for the members' individual performances.)
You're so handsome, Se Chan!
(Which member will start off the performance?)
(Getting splashed)
(Haha)
(The shortest villain who never hesitates)
(He throws things,)
(hits people,)
(and runs!)
(He even disregards BTS as if they're nothing.)
(What kind of performance will Haha show the fans?)
(Exploding with anticipation)
We have to give it our all today.
Since this is going to air on TV, make sure you give it your all.
Just like the old times. Give it your all.
Let's give it our 100 percent.
(Utterly nervous)
Get them hyped up to the max.
Don't let them rest for a second.
(He can't conceal the nervousness although he's a veteran performer.)
We can go out now.
Go out now.
(Haha will perform first.)
(What kind of performance will he show the fans?)
("Dang Diggi Bang" by RGP: Haha, Skull, and M.Tyson)
(Even their appearance...)
(is enough to get them excited.)
(Don't I look pretty cool?)
- Get up! - Okay.
It's "Dang Diggi Bang".
"Dang Diggi Bang".
(Dancing timidly)
- Get up! - Okay.
(The reggae master, Skull, starts off the song like a pro.)
(It's Haha's turn now!)
(Rapping furiously)
(Haha's furious rapping makes the audience go wild!)
(If it goes over 120dB, they will get a hint.)
(Haha proves himself to be a singer.)
(Raise them up above your heads)
(I feel like V in BTS)
- Put your hands up and clap! - Clap now!
Raise them higher!
- Keep going! - Let's go.
(The heat of the performance reaches the green room.)
(Feeling excited)
(His nervous face is gone,)
(and he makes the audience join like a pro.)
(His secret weapon, his jump)
(Thanks to his wild jumps, it goes over 115dB.)
(His confidence explodes along with the thundering shouts.)
(It's like a revival meeting for Haha.)
Since this is what he used to, he seems relaxed.
The beach woman
(The green room is busy for the next performance.)
With her
(Utterly nervous)
(Even though the audience is going wild with Haha,)
(the other members keep on practicing.)
Louder!
(The next members are ever so nervous.)
(Haha is more passionate than his usual self. Is he the spy?)
(Say, "Oh, yes!")
(Oh, yes!)
(Yes!)
One more time. Scream, everyone!
(Haha and Skull's performance was wild to the end.)
Scream, everyone!
(The audience went wild.)
(Did it go over 120dB?)
(Haha, you're the best!)
(Haha's performance lingers even with these talented musicians.)
Stang, digi, digi, ding, dang, digi, bang, bang
Digi, digi, dang, digi, dang, digi, bang
Hello, we're a new group.
- I'm Skull of RGP. - I'm Haha.
- Yes! - Yes!
Yes!
All right. We'll bring in the next performer to the stage.
(They are disappointed.)
Running Man's...
(The kind audience cares about the performer's feeling.)
(He has never experienced such support from anywhere.)
(He's enjoying it to the fullest thanks to the kind audience.)
(Thank you for the support. From The Gang)
- You'll see me again. - But...
- You'll see me again. - there are more great performances.
These two worked really hard.
My role model.
(Haha's role model?)
The big brother of Running Man, Seok Jin.
Although she's about to turn 40, she's still adorable.
It's the joint performance by Ji Hyo and Seok Jin.
- Go! - Yes!
(Full of expectations)
(Haha heads to the backstage after his performance.)
- Well done. - Good job.
- Haha. That way. - Well done.
I have so much to do right now.
Hurry. I have to pick one?
Is that the hint?
Yes. The decibels of your audience was...
(It must go over 120dB for him to get a hint.)
Scream, everyone!
(The audience went wild.)
(How high did the decibels go up?)
(Let's reach 120dB!)
The audience's cheer for your performance reached 123dB.
You successfully obtained a hint.
There are 3 hints. Choose 1.
(Haha gets a hint.)
Who on earth is the spy?
(Who on earth is the spy?)
"The spy suits Friday, but doesn't suit Sunday."
(The spy suits Friday, but doesn't suit Sunday.)
"The spy suits Friday,"
"but not Sunday"?
(He still needs more information. Who is the spy?)
Okay. I'll think about it.
(The audience is still hyped up after Haha's performance.)
I'm slightly nervous, you know?
Aren't you nervous?
I'm a bit nervous.
(Even the veteran entertainers can't conceal their nervousness.)
Should I wear sunglasses?
No?
Don't get wet
I'll go home nice and dry today
(Jee Seok Jin)
(As the oldest member of Running Man,)
(he always gets splashed first to set a good example.)
(Squeaking)
(Seok Jin is indeed the first-tier entertainer.)
(He doesn't spare his body to make people laugh.)
- That's me. - My gosh. Bo Mi.
- Start the race. - The race has started.
(He's the official starter of the race.)
(We'll look forward to it today.)
Madam Gurie.
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Get lost.)
(She looks pretty even when she curses.)
(The strong lady everyone recognizes and legend of girl crush)
(Regardless of the location, she's always brave and daring.)
It's higher than you thought?
(She's an incredibly pretty all-around member.)
(She's amazing.)
She's amazing. Seriously.
(Ace of Running Man, Song Ji Hyo!)
Why did you choose this?
- I mean... - It's so hard.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo got together for the performance.)
- You... - Hear me out, Seok Jin.
She chose it. She did.
- My gosh. - She chose it.
- She chose it. - Listen.
Both of us have to sing the song alone.
- Right. - But we have so much to do though.
- So we can perform as a pair. - My gosh.
I chose this song...
because I wanted to get the audience excited.
- You... - You just woke up, didn't you?
- You said you were okay with it. - You just woke up, right?
Yes.
I only put on the sunscreen.
You said you were okay with the song.
But you have to do a really good job with the song.
(What's the song they chose?)
(Sexy song, "Don't Give It to Me" by Loco and Hwasa)
(Chatting among themselves)
(They will sing "Don't Give It to Me"?)
This is such a hard song.
Don't you agree, M.Tyson?
Isn't it really hard to sing like Hwasa?
It's a very difficult song.
It's very difficult.
What are we going to do?
Shouldn't she sound like she's in pain when she's singing it?
- Yes. - In pain?
Pretend you're sick.
- You must get into the song. - You know?
- You really must get into the song. - Exactly.
(An advanced acting skill to convey the fling is needed.)
I'm sorry
(Sounding in pain)
You must be in pain like this.
(What is that? I guess he's really in pain.)
- You're trying to cut me out - I don't want to hear it.
- You have to sing it like this. - Why don't you switch the roles?
- Why don't you switch the roles? - Do you want to switch the roles?
- I'm Ko Sa. - Ko Sa.
- "Ko Sa". - "Ko Sa"?
- Sleeping Co. - Sleeping Co.
It's not bad. Ko Sa and Sleeping Co.
I(t's not bad. Ko Sa and Sleeping Co.)
- It's nice. - Ko Sa and Sleeping Co.
(He loves his own joke.)
(Ko Sa and Sleeping Co start recording the song!)
(Ji Hyo's singing suddenly comes into their minds.)
(The memory of loving you like crazy)
(Did someone ride a horse here?)
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
(She's known to be an awful actor.)
(Ji Hyo carefully gets into the rhythms.)
It's dangerous
I'm on the edge when I barely managed to stop myself
(Her sexy vibrato pulls off Hwasa's sexy intro part.)
(Is this a new discovery of her talent?)
(Everyone is surprised.)
She's better than I thought.
(He's surprised.)
(The weakling, Seok Jin's rap)
(The ace member, Ji Hyo's singing)
(Unexpectedly, they make a nice pair.)
(How will their performance pan out?)
("Don't Give It to Me" by Seok Jin and Ji Hyo)
(A bottle of wine and glasses are set up on the stage.)
(A man and a woman are having a fling.)
(Ji Hyo exudes a voluptuous beauty.)
(And he's looking at Ji Hyo.)
(Seok Jin, his first time having a fling)
(He dressed up to the nines.)
(It's dangerous.)
(I'm on the edge when I barely managed to stop myself.)
(The number hikes up thanks to Ji Hyo's sexy looks.)
(Ji Hyo is pretty today as always.)
(Her first line captivates him.)
(The tension and mood are elevated.)
(Look at me.)
(She's close to bursting into laughter.)
(What's wrong with him?)
(She warns him.)
(Don't step over the boundary.)
(Don't give me.)
(Don't give me alcohol.)
(If I get drunk, I might make a move on you.)
(He's mesmerized.)
(He tries to stay calm.)
She doesn't look awkward at all...
when she's all dolled up.
- Right. - It suits her.
- She's acting. - Right.
She's good.
- Seok Jin... - Don't sway to the beat.
He did this.
(Squirming)
He's the type...
who'd go home alone at 4am.
(He gets ready to sing.)
(What is this?)
(Surprisingly, he does well.)
He's good.
(He continues to rap well.)
(But he brings up too much emotion.)
He's good at rapping, but his gestures are too old-school.
(Despite his old-school gestures, they don't look bad together.)
(They're getting in the mood.)
(What is this alcohol?)
(What is that?)
(They get in the mood.)
(Cheers)
(They make the crowd cheer.)
(The decibels rise.)
(It was a surprising harmony...)
(between the 50-year-old Seok Jin and the horrible singer, Ji Hyo.)
(2019 version of "Don't Give It to Me"...)
(by the sexy Ji Hyo and the confident Seok Jin)
Thank you!
(The audience is elated by this unexpected duet.)
(Great work!)
They're good.
That was amazing.
You see...
We prepared so much for this, but we were so anxious back there.
I'm not sure if we did a good job.
(You did well.)
It was so nerve-racking.
- It really was. - Yes.
Isn't Ji Hyo so beautiful?
- Yes! - Yes!
Isn't he so good-looking?
Doesn't he look like Loco?
(They hesitate.)
- What? Is that a no? - That's a no.
- I'm Koco. - He's Koco.
The next performance...
will be given by the youngest members.
They're the youngest.
Our three babies have prepared a song...
that you will definitely love.
Let's give it up for them!
(Please welcome them with applause!)
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo finish everything without any mistakes.)
- Good work. - You did well.
You were terrific.
- Seok Jin. - You were excellent.
(They compliment each other and go backstage.)
I was so nervous.
It was really nerve-racking.
(Now, they'll find out.)
- Your hint. - What hint?
- Did we... - Did we surpass it?
- Did we? Seok Jin! - Okay, okay!
(What was the highest decibels they got?)
(It's 120dB.)
Please pick 1 of the 3 hints.
Do we each pick one?
(Which hints will they receive?)
This one? I pick the one you previously chose.
(The spy likes cafes but not restaurants.)
(The spy likes cafes but not restaurants?)
Shouldn't you give us pens and paper?
I think we need to use reasoning.
(Who are these hints pointing at?)
(The spy suits Friday, but doesn't suit Sunday.)
(The spy likes cafes but not restaurants.)
(This time, it's the 3 youngest members' stage.)
(The prince appears.)
(The audience cheers for him.)
(Running Man in-depth exploration)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(Everything he picks is a dud.)
(Everything he chooses is a dud.)
(Kwang Soo's mother)
(Everything that he touches...)
(turns into a dud.)
(Kwang Soo is always the one who receives the penalties.)
(Everyone is shocked at the penalties.)
What is that?
(Laughing)
(It's an extreme-level penalty.)
(And it's an extreme-level face.)
(Is Kwang Soo a junior comedian?)
(He's so ugly.)
(I can't do it!)
(I just can't!)
(It's hard to say no...)
(to this charming man.)
(She's another person subjected to in-depth exploration.)
(Jeon So Min)
(Everyone cheers for her.)
(So Min's parents)
(Let's dig into So Min.)
(She's known to be crazy.)
(She has committed some unprecedented humiliation.)
(In order to induce laughter,)
(at times,)
(she even shows some skin.)
(She's known to sacrifice herself.)
(She sacrifices herself to do what's right.)
(I can't do this show anymore.)
(She's the epitome of someone who's selfless.)
(Mom, take out the deposit.)
(Those in the green room burst into laughter.)
(BS)
(Yang Se Chan)
(This is the last, youngest member.)
(The audience is hyper.)
(Let's dig into Se Chan this time.)
(He's a comedian to the bone.)
(Having a runny nose is nothing.)
(He's the number 1 lowly singer.)
(The true comedian is finally here.)
(He's known for his wits and for being reckless.)
(He always induces laughter.)
You're out.
(23 days before the fan-meet.)
Will Kwang Soo sing Lee Jae Hoon's parts?
- Yes, he's the main vocalist. - Yes.
I'll sing Kim Sung Su's parts.
She'll sing Yu Ri's parts.
Yesterday,
we filmed a horror special.
We overworked our throats.
- Our throats are sore. - We screamed so much.
(They're not in their best conditions.)
It's not like you have to sing well anyway.
(He tells the truth.)
- What do you mean? - What do you mean?
You said you trusted us.
It's only an event.
- It'll work out. - Right.
- He'll help out. - Yes, he will.
- All right. - Thank you in advance.
(Kwang Soo begins recording first.)
(I struggled just as much as you did.)
You have absolutely no emotions.
(He tells the truth once more.)
What are "emotions"?
(English isn't Kwang Soo's specialty.)
He's talking about your feelings.
I got it.
- All right, I got it. - You lack strength.
Do you want to continue or take a rest?
How... How... How about... How about I take a break?
- Come out. - Okay.
Go on.
- Kwang Soo, sit down. - You did well.
You truly live up to your name.
- You said your throat was sore. - You sang well.
Your voice wasn't hoarse at all.
Your voice was great, but your skin looks terrible.
- You look really dry. - Seriously.
Hold on. I'm the only one who got my makeup done,
but my skin looks bad?
(Hold on. I'm the only one who got my makeup done,)
(but my skin looks bad?)
(Even the Prince of Asia is getting old.)
What is that?
Is that a speaker?
(What is he curious about?)
(It's a machine used to treat your skin.)
What is that?
How could that be a speaker?
- Is it light? It looks like so. - Yes.
What is that?
(He looks dignified.)
Is this right?
- I can hear something. - What?
- What is that? - I can see your face.
I can see your face.
- You can see me? - I can see your mouth too.
Is this working?
- Yes, I think so. - Yes.
- Is it off? - It's off.
Wouldn't it be too blinding...
if the light doesn't turn off?
No, you need the UV rays to have better skin.
Infrared rays.
(They're not UV rays.)
- Right, that. - Infrared rays.
- They shouldn't be UV rays. - You're right.
- Wake up. - Okay.
- I'll focus. - You must concentrate.
(This mask company could go bankrupt thanks to you!)
What?
(Please focus, Se Chan.)
(Fascinated)
I think it's...
- It's pink. - It's pink.
- What is that? - It must be something else.
Isn't this for clubbing?
(After taking a rest,)
(Kwang Soo continues recording.)
(This time, he puts in his emotions.)
(Meanwhile, Se Chan puts in too much emotion.)
(His blood vessels are visible.)
(So Min finishes recording as well.)
(They practice the choreography.)
(They do their best to bring out the vibes from 1997.)
That's good.
(They hope they can give COOL a rebirth.)
We're going to make a parody.
They're going to be exactly the same.
I'm going to have the same hairstyle too.
Her hairstyle used to be trendy back then.
Sung Su wore a fedora.
Kwang Soo would look hilarious.
(How will their "Woman on the Beach" look?)
("Woman on the Beach" by Kwang Soo, So Min, and Se Chan)
(Only the dancers are seen on stage.)
They're coming out from behind.
(The real oldies begin.)
(Hey, it's summer!)
(Screaming)
(So Min's father)
(They start off with raised energy.)
(Welcome to 1997.)
(COOL has been reborn.)
They're dressed just like what COOL used to dress.
I thought they cut of the sleeves the prisoner outfits.
(Laughing)
She's adorable.
(She's adorable.)
(The lead vocalist enters.)
What are the clothes?
He looks like Rain.
(Cool Kwang Soo)
(Its familiar melody...)
(quickly brings all generations together.)
(Let's hurry off!)
(The decibels rise as they reach the hook.)
(The youngest of Running Man, go, go!)
(Kwang Soo is the leader of the three,)
(and So Min and Se Chan...)
(join him for an adorable retro performance.)
(The overly emotional Se Chan is up.)
(Screaming)
(Back and forth)
(Perfect chemistry)
(They're all in love with the two.)
Make some noise!
(Screaming)
(Se Chan's plan worked and they're at 125dB.)
During practice, Se Chan kept asking...
when he should add that.
- He really likes doing that. - Exactly.
Make some noise!
(The chant he prepared elevates the tension and mood.)
(We'll forever be in love with our fans.)
(We promise.)
(Retro So Min, Lead vocalist Kwang Soo, Cheerleader Se Chan)
(The three of them show off perfect harmony.)
(Thanks to them, we went on a trip down memory lane.)
(We're back to present time again.)
(Great job!)
(Even the recording artists agree.)
It was perfect.
(You guys are the best.)
- Gosh, I'm so embarrassed. - Hello, everyone.
- It's good to see you. - Hi.
(The get a grip on themselves and greet the audience.)
Let us properly say hello.
Hello, I'm Kwang Soo.
Hi, I'm So Min.
Hi, I'm Se Chan. In 2, 3.
We're GHOUL!
(Not COOL but GHOUL)
Right.
Not COOL but GHOUL.
- It's GHOUL. - That's right.
From what I heard, this is supposed to air...
- in September. - In the fall.
- But... - We sang a summer song.
- A summer song. - We said it so loudly too.
- I know. - We didn't know...
- it'll air in the fall. - It's still hot outside for us.
We admit our wrongdoing...
and promise that we'll never make this mistake again.
We're very sorry.
Did you have fun?
- Yes. - Yes.
Because of all the cheers and chants,
I had a blast on stage as well.
Me too.
(Have some more then.)
- Thank you. - It's been insane.
- Good. - So we should introduce who's next.
- Right. - That's right.
I see that a few things have been set up.
- Four chairs. - Those indicate...
a grand performance.
Right, but less than four people are performing next from what I know.
I know it as just one person.
One person?
Could it be him?
Running Man's Sparta-Kook.
The man with the muscles. It's his turn.
- That's right. - Small chested.
"Small," did you say?
(Watch it, Kwang Soo.)
- He can be petty. - Oh, I get it.
That's why it's small?
- He can be petty, that's all. - I know him as the opposite.
So Min always takes the joke as far as she can.
- So let's introduce him up here. - Sure.
Please put it together for Kim Jong Kook.
(Here is the muscular but petty Kim Jong Kook.)
Thank you!
(They applaud even when they're leaving the stage.)
- I... - You were great.
Was I any good?
Did we do well?
- We were amazing. - Kwang Soo, So Min, Se Chan,
you reached 125dB,
- which earns you a hint. - It was 125dB.
- Nice. - We did really well.
I asked them to scream during the song.
Please choose 1 out of the 3.
- Kwang Soo, go ahead. - You choose.
(They treat him as the leader at times like this.)
You're our leader.
- Leader Lee. - Well...
How about this?
- This one? - The choice is yours.
(Which hint did they choose?)
- "The spy..." - "The spy..."
"can be with balls",
"but not dice".
What does this mean?
A ball is round while dice is a square.
Could it be the Running Ball?
It can be with balls,
- but not dice. - Not dice.
- This... - It's too difficult.
The hints are tricky today.
Do we keep this for now?
- We need another one. - What do the numbers add up to?
From 6 to 1, I mean.
Well... 6 plus 5 plus 4 plus 3 plus 2 plus 1.
Don't you think that's a bit too complicated for us?
(Don't you think that's a bit too complicated for us?)
That isn't the answer anyway.
- Let's go for now. - Sure, let's go.
(They aren't any closer to identifying the spy.)
It can be with balls but not dice.
Want to see some tears?
(Who's taking the stage after GHOUL?)
(It's the man who can do anything.)
Want to see some tears?
(Kim Jong Kook)
(It's not like I can mince you instead.)
(I could boil you guys, you know.)
(A half-hearted joke...)
(never feels like a joke with Jong Kook.)
Behind you.
(His history of victories had no hitches.)
(Not even a player in the Major League could stop him.)
(Who are we? We're Running Man!)
(The man who only knows victories was challenged though.)
(His opponent was the gold-medalist Yun Sung Bin.)
- He couldn't possibly win. - Yun Sung Bin's fast.
- That's impossible. - Get set...
On your marks.
(He challenges the gold-medalist to a 10m sprint.)
(Will he keep his winning streak?)
(A national team athlete versus Kim Jong Kook)
(Tensions are high.)
(A close match)
- What? - That was fast.
(Who won?)
(Neck and neck)
(Jong Kook won!)
(Gosh...)
How is that possible?
(It's absurd, but he still won.)
(Jong Kook even beat the gold-medalist.)
Good job.
(He's really good.)
(He makes us forget that he's a singer sometimes.)
(The famous soundtrack from the movie "Aladdin")
("Speechless" featuring Princess Jasmine)
(It's the song that was covered by female singers with high pitches.)
(During the dry run)
(They film Jong Kook as he sings.)
(He fully prepares for the stage by checking sound and movement.)
(What spin will he give to the song?)
("Speechless" by Kim Jong Kook)
[VIU Ver] SBS E468 Running Man
"Running Man's Fan-Meet 2019"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(They scream the moment he starts singing.)
(He captivates the ladies' hearts.)
(He mesmerizes the audience with his sweet voice.)
(I am a singer.)
(Jong Kook's voice is brought to us on top of string instruments.)
("Speechless" by Jong Kook couldn't be any better.)
(Dazzling)
(We had forgotten for a second...)
(that he's a recording artist.)
(Jong Kook doesn't disappoint.)
(His performance is nearing its climax.)
(High notes explode.)
(Their ears are blessed.)
(He's incredible.)
(His beautiful voice is a treat to the ear.)
(This special performance cannot be enjoyed anywhere else.)
Thank you.
("Speechless" performed by Jong Kook)
He's on another level.
He's amazing.
(Impressed)
How can such a beautiful voice come out of that muscular body?
His vocal cords must be squeezed by all his muscles.
His key is so high.
- Right? - It's a key for women.
Hello, I'm Kim Jong Kook.
Well...
(Thanks for the beautiful song.)
Your cheering was so loud...
that I couldn't even hear the music well.
Thank you so much.
Running Man has...
many young fans.
That's why I sang a song from a movie loved by many people.
Did you like it?
- Yes! - I see.
I was so nervous.
Thank you.
(Be my boyfriend.)
This was...
the last individual performance...
we prepared.
The next performance...
is actually a penalty.
Jae Seok and Haha...
prepared an amazing performance.
Are you excited?
- Yes! - Yes!
Please enjoy.
See you in a bit.
(The performance starts shorty. Stay tuned.)
(I'm still nervous.)
Be careful.
- Be careful. - Let's do it here.
Here?
Jong Kook.
See how much you've got.
The audience's cheering exceeded 120dB.
- You won a hint. - It did?
(He met the goal of 120dB.)
(The audience's cheering...)
(the loudest at the climax of the song.)
(I did it.)
All right.
(What hint has he chosen?)
I picked the one that dropped.
"The spy likes cafes..."
"but not restaurants."
What?
(The hints are confusing. Who is the spy?)
All right.
(The audience is still filled with emotions after Jong Kook's ballad.)
(Jae Seok appears.)
(Jae Seok appears on the screen with the theme song.)
(The audience is excited.)
(Yu Jae Seok)
(His dance moves are hard to watch.)
(He always does his best to be frivolous.)
(And no one beats him when it comes to ugliness.)
(His looks stir up the waiting room.)
I love him.
(He creates fun scenes with just one touch.)
(By both luck and effort,)
(he's become the number one entertainer.)
Cameras, come!
Cameras, come with us!
(You don't want to miss a second. He is the best of the best.)
(It's supposed to be a duet performance.)
(Why is there only Jae Seok?)
(Jae Seok's video is over.)
(Just then)
(We'll decide which members will do a duet performance.)
(The race will determine which 2 members...)
(will prepare a performance by themselves.)
(No one wants to be chosen.)
(Haha is chosen for the duet performance.)
(And)
(Jae Seok is chosen as Haha's partner.)
(Yes! It's Jae Seok!)
(This is how...)
(Super-X's performance was decided.)
(Duet performance by Super-X composed of Haha and Jae Seok)
(The audience is excited to see the two sexy men's performance.)
(The two sexy men are worried.)
- Hi. - Oh, my.
(Three months ago, Super-X met a songwriter.)
- Hello. - Hi.
He's the best songwriter.
Haha chose him.
(Songwriter Lim Kwang Wook)
I'm the main producer of the songwriter group,
Devine Channel. My name is Lim Kwang Wook.
- Kwang Kook? - Lim Kwang Wook.
- Kwang Wook? - Yes.
Let me tell you how amazing he is.
His songwriting is...
world-class.
In Korea, he writes songs for idol groups...
I'm sure...
he is very famous.
That must be why you contacted him.
But it'd be easiest if you tell me...
- what songs he wrote. - Of course.
- Exactly. - I'm curious.
First of all,
"Fire" by BTS.
("Fire" by BTS)
I wrote it...
together with my colleagues.
Stand up and greet him properly.
Hit songs make us stand up.
(Excuse my rudeness.)
(Jae Seok automatically bows.)
- I had no idea. - I'm so proud of him.
You should have told me...
"Fire"?
- Did you... - So this is how it works.
- What else? - And...
(If you need more information...)
I wrote many songs for EXO.
Stand up.
(He wrote songs for EXO?)
Shake hands.
Who else? EXO?
For EXO,
I wrote, "Tender Love",
"Baby, Don't Cry", "El Dorado", and so on.
We should go see him.
Let's do that.
My goodness.
- He's incredible. - He is.
(And I contacted him.)
You know Haha, right?
How do you know each other?
First of all,
we don't know what to do ourselves.
We're completely lost.
The thing is, there aren't many male duos these days.
You're right.
- We used to have so many. - Deux.
- Ryang Hyun Ryang Ha. - These days,
the market is dominated by idol groups.
It's hard to find male duos anymore.
We can't find...
any examples we can give you.
(To find out their preferences, they listen to some songs.)
This sounds so trendy.
This is...
(The electronic beat is a bit too trendy for them.)
(Haha pretends to be enjoying the beat.)
It's so annoying when he does this.
- It doesn't even suit him. - Gosh. This...
To imagine I'd perform this with Jae Seok...
This is not okay. Kwang Wook.
This is too high-quality for us.
All your music is so cool.
If we perform this...
(If we perform this...)
If we do this...
It'd be so annoying.
It'd be terrible.
(It'd be clumsy and comical.)
(They keep listening to more music.)
To be honest...
(They're afraid the music is too trendy.)
I love the music, but...
I'll be honest.
I'm not sure if we can pull this off.
- Is it too difficult? - It's too difficult for us.
You stopped grooving to the rhythm after a while too.
I'll put it simply.
We're very close anyway.
Do you have any disco music?
(They're old-fashioned.)
(Is that what you wanted?)
Hey.
You shouldn't say that.
I recently wrote...
- some old-school music. - That sounds amazing.
(Now he knows what they want.)
- It's getting popular again. - The previous songs...
are too high-quality for us.
(What old-school song will the duo perform?)
The main...
- Hi. - Hi.
I'm sorry, Kwang Wook.
We were just penalized.
We should have taken a shower before coming here.
- The thing is... - How have you been?
- We didn't have much time. - Right.
So we just came straight here.
(They're recording the song today.)
This song...
- It's the best. - This song...
I'm not sure if we can pull it off. I'm sorry.
I believe you can.
(I trust you.)
As soon as I played it, I got goosebumps.
It's fantastic.
The song is too good for us.
It's too high-quality.
In my opinion,
we should sing this in an obnoxious way.
In an obnoxious way?
(In an obnoxious way?)
I think we should.
Focus on delivering the feeling.
- Okay. Let's listen to it. - Okay.
I can't sing high notes these days.
- It's not good. - First of all...
(The song sounds amazing even from the very beginning.)
(Guide vocal)
(This is the first time the fans hear this song.)
(They like it.)
(The addictive intro is followed...)
(by singing.)
When the fun rhythm starts flowing out
A thrill passes through my body
(The song doesn't only satisfy Generation X.)
(All generations think it's a great song.)
I like this song.
(Hands above your head)
(Why does he sound so hoarse?)
- This part is... - We have to lower the key.
(He can't hit the high notes.)
Excuse me.
- We have to lower the key. - Right.
You can't hit the high notes at all.
I told you as soon as we got this song.
(We were going to do ballads.)
(Haha starts recording first.)
(Sing loudly after me.)
I'm sorry.
I can only do this three times.
(Haha's warning him.)
My neck feels sore.
(There are only 3 chances to record the high notes.)
(He keeps on trying the high part.)
(His voice is not in a good condition,)
(so he's not satisfied.)
Let's warm up your voice.
- Okay. - Try the beginning.
(Let's go, Jae Seok.)
(His voice sounds stable.)
(He's good.)
(Is he rapping all of a sudden?)
(He transforms from the main vocalist to a rapper.)
This part feels rushed.
- It's difficult to pronounce. - I agree.
Can we change this?
(That was random.)
(He tries to negotiate with the songwriter.)
Shake until you get tired
How's this? We can omit "wildly".
(He didn't hear Jae Seok.)
(He tries again with the original lyrics.)
I'll try again.
(He's not confident.)
Shake wildly
- You have to emphasize that part. - Shake wildly
Shake wildly until you get tired
This is hard.
Shake wildly
(This is the next high part.)
(Easily)
- Let's go one more time. - Okay.
(We don't know each other.)
This is...
(He was confident in the beginning,)
(but he makes more mistakes as the parts get complicated.)
It's easy like a midsummer night's dream
(He's having a hard time.)
(Will Jae Seok be okay?)
(His condition doesn't improve.)
This part is hard.
I'll just use my voice,
and if it doesn't work, I'll give up.
(Will Jae Seok and Haha be okay?)
(The members are practicing the group dance.)
I can't do this.
Five, six, shake it, shake it.
(It's break time after a run-through.)
That was awesome.
(Jae Seok is practicing the couple performance.)
(He practices while everybody else takes a break.)
Do you know what time we're doing it with Apink?
I think it's 5:30pm.
One...
(They go over the dance moves together.)
(Watch the giraffe in the back.)
(The older members are working hard,)
(so he can't just watch.)
(Fluttering)
(I did my best.)
(They practice after the others leave.)
(They lean the microphone stands...)
(at the same time.)
(Their movements are not the same.)
(They didn't bring the stand back at the same time.)
Let's try again.
Listen to the first part.
Memorize the song.
(Memorize the movements with the song.)
I'm getting confused.
(Jae Seok tries by himself.)
- 1, 2? - Yes.
(He tries the 2nd time.)
- 1, 2. - You were too fast.
(He tries the 3rd time with the producer.)
(He's accurate.)
(Jae Seok misses it the 3rd time.)
Count for him in the back.
He needs it.
I focus on hearing the song too much.
(Will Super-X be fine during the actual performance?)
(Good luck, Jae Seok!)
(Dress rehearsal, the day before the concert)
(Jae Seok is trying out the moves.)
- This is too close. - Is it too close?
(He expresses his opinion.)
Jae Seok.
You look more excited here than when you are with me and SORAN.
- What? - You look more excited here.
Right.
(He doesn't deny it.)
He agreed.
I'm a guest in that group,
- and here, - He's the main vocalist.
I'm the main vocalist.
This is my main group.
(This is actually my main group.)
- Main group. - Jae Seok.
(He makes the distinction clearly.)
(The rehearsal starts.)
(This is the part that gave them trouble.)
(He's a beat too fast.)
(It's perfect this time.)
(They're an exact copy of each other.)
(This song is fun.)
(The rehearsal is over.)
- One more time? - Awesome.
(He's passionate as the main vocalist.)
(They practice again for a better performance.)
It's such a great song.
It's really good.
If you're ready, let's get started.
Stand by.
(They are passionate about the song. How will Super-X's performance be?)
(The performance begins.)
(Jae Seok and Haha are nervous as they wait.)
(They're very nervous,)
(and the fans cheer for them.)
("Hollywood" by Super-X)
(They're very nervous,)
(and the fans cheer for them.)
("Hollywood" by Super-X)
(They lean at the same time.)
(They touch their chests, and straighten the microphone stands.)
(They point their toes.)
(That was perfect teamwork.)
(That was amazing!)
- Haha's so good. - He's good.
That outfits suit them perfectly.
(Their colorful outfits suit their Generation X vibe.)
(We're...)
(the Super-X generation.)
(The cheer almost reaches 110dB.)
This is really good.
(This song is really good.)
(She copies the wiper movement.)
(This is...)
(the old sexy.)
(You somehow fall for these middle-aged men.)
(Now it's the footwork part.)
(They tap dance to the beat.)
(They show off their controlled footwork,)
(and turn away nonchalantly.)
(Let's go!)
(They move forward.)
(Raise the volume)
(The decibels rise above 110.)
(Here's the chorus.)
(This is so much fun.)
(They show off their old dance moves.)
(The super duo excites the fans.)
(However, the audience's cheer hasn't surpassed 120dB.)
(He hits high notes.)
(And then,)
(he moves his hips.)
- Make some noise! - Let's go!
(This is the real climax.)
(They summon the Generation X dance moves.)
(The decibels rise again at the climax.)
(They surpassed 120dB.)
(This is awesome.)
(This is getting heated.)
(Jae Seok and Haha are excited, and the mood is cheerful.)
Five, six.
(They pause.)
(They both move their hips.)
(The atmosphere peaks with the double body waves.)
(That's old sexy.)
Is this how they dance?
(The fans are in love with Super-X already.)
("Hollywood" reflected the Generation X vibe.)
Super-X.
That was nice.
That was very nice.
The dance moves they showed at the end were modern.
They did this.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I am sorry for pretending to be sexy.
We are Super-X.
That's right. Super-X.
We resist the existing regulations.
We are the X-generation.
It's time to wrap up Part One.
That's right. Three months of work is passing by so quickly.
- I know. - I feel disappointed...
and sentimental at the same time.
All right. When this episode airs, I won't be home.
(When this episode airs, I won't be home.)
(He is too embarrassed to watch the performances.)
- I already made appointments. - I see.
All right. For Running Man's fan-meet,
- we invited guest singers. - That's right.
- Who are they? - Part One will be wrapped up...
by the artists who are the most popular these days.
Please give them a round of applause.
(Which guest singers ran over for Running Man's fan-meet?)
(Running Man's Fan-Meet: Nine Years of Running Man)
Who are they?
(The couple performance they worked hard on is over.)
We did a good job.
- Jae Seok and Haha, - What is this?
the cheer for your performance reached 121dB.
You succeeded to acquire a hint.
- Please choose a hint. - All right.
(Which hint did Jae Seok and Haha pick?)
(The spy likes cafes but not restaurants.)
"The spy likes cafes..." What is this?
I know who the spy is. Okay.
What is it?
(Did Haha figure out who the spy is?)
What does this mean?
- Okay. - Cafes?
I know who the spy is.
Let's find the spy.
Yes.
- Everyone received a hint, right? - That's right.
Shall we share the hints?
But the hints...
- I will tell you mine. - What is it?
(It's rare for Seok Jin to share his hint so readily.)
"Monday..."
("Monday...")
Gosh, I forgot.
Seok Jin.
What was it?
- Didn't you receive the same hint? - What was it?
I received the same hint, right?
- What was it? - I became suspicious of him now...
- since he said something different. - I forgot.
- "The spy suits Friday..." - Seok Jin.
This is a fan-meet. This isn't the right time...
to seek attention.
- "The spy doesn't suit Sunday." - What?
"The spy likes Friday, but doesn't like Monday."
Doesn't that apply to everyone?
- That's right. - Everyone likes Friday.
- Seriously. - I will share another hint.
"The spy likes cafes, but not restaurants."
- Did you receive that hint? - Yes.
What was the hint we received?
What was it?
"The spy suits balls, but not dice."
What?
I have no idea who the spy is.
(As the deductions continue, the guest singers enter the stage.)
(This is incredible.)
(The surprise guest singers are ITZY.)
(I can't believe ITZY is here.)
("Dalla Dalla" by ITZY)
(Speechless)
(Running Man's fan-meet has a variety of performances.)
(I am so excited.)
(I am different.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(The members and artists finally come together.)
All right.
- Good job. - Hello.
- I bet you were really lonely. - I was so bored.
You were bored, right?
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan changed into the stage costumes.)
- Ji Hyo. - You look cool.
How was my rap?
It was amazing.
(I will show you one more time.)
- It was okay, right? - It was amazing.
- It was a live performance. - We screamed.
- Really? - We were so surprised.
I practiced so hard.
You did a good job.
It was great.
I am so embarrassed. It's driving me crazy.
Se Chan, you did a great job.
- You are too kind. Let's sit down. - You did a great job.
Let's sit down.
I didn't get to watch the beginning.
How did you channel Hwasa?
Ji Hyo, you were so pretty.
Seriously.
We became a fan.
- Don't be like that. - Seriously.
- My goodness. - You are so cool.
They tease relentlessly.
Stop it already.
Stop teasing her.
- Stop it. - Don't be like that.
Didn't Ji Hyo and Seok Jin make a mistake?
- We made many small mistakes. - Like what?
He suddenly poured real alcohol.
- That's right. - I was so surprised.
I poured wine. I didn't do that during rehearsal.
(Seok Jin did something that was unplanned.)
(Pouring)
(It was an ad-lib that came from the good mood.)
Running Man is for those who are 12 years old and older.
It was grape juice.
(Don't be mistaken.)
- Really? - It was grape juice, not wine.
I want to talk to that man in the middle.
- Yes? - Do you practice martial arts?
Yes. Hello.
That's not how you do a kick.
- Really? Did I do it wrong? - Yes.
Maybe he was copying "The Gang".
- "The Gang". - Maybe he was copying "The Gang".
(Were you copying me?)
- "The Gang". - Why would I copy that?
It looked as if you were holding something.
In the performance of a COOL's song,
Kwang Soo wore a vest.
He did it to show off his muscles.
I didn't show off. Lee Jae Hoon of COOL...
Then why did you get tanned?
- There were no muscles to show off. - What?
- I didn't show off. - What were you showing off?
I didn't show off.
Why did you do push-ups in the waiting room?
- Did he do push-ups? - I didn't do push-ups!
- I did it since I was nervous. - You were determined to show off.
- Seriously. - I was nervous.
- Did you do push-ups? - He was pumping up his muscles.
- Yes. - My goodness.
- I will be honest. - I hope you succeed.
(I will be honest.)
I did do push-ups. But next to me...
(I will reveal everything.)
So Min did push-ups too.
(Kwang Soo drags So Min down with him.)
- Why did you do push-ups? - Who?
So Min did push-ups too.
- I can explain. - Did So Min do push-ups?
The neckline of my outfit was a bit low,
- so I wanted to pump up my muscles. - So Min...
- isn't used to such outfits. - For two days,
So Min didn't have a proper meal.
- She might collapse on the stage. - I am hungry.
So Min pumped up her muscles.
I wore a prisoner's uniform for the opening.
I was so embarrassed.
I forgot about it at first because of the audience's cheer.
Everyone in the audience knows the color of your underwear now.
My goodness.
You could see the color, right?
That's right.
The audience cheered so loudly...
- that I forgot for a second. - Upon seeing the underwear,
a lot of people became disappointed.
(Haha keeps going.)
(Dear fans, I am sorry for disappointing you.)
Haha. My goodness.
- Jae Seok. - What?
- Didn't you hear the sound? - What sound?
(I am disappointed.)
For goodness' sake.
- Didn't you hear the sound? - What are you talking about?
All of us heard it.
- For goodness' sake. - The moment they saw it,
they were like...
The three of you should react.
(He takes out his anger on other people.)
(They get yelled at for no reason.)
From the back, it looks like...
SORAN is at a wedding.
Seriously. It looks like they are waiting...
for the wedding to end so that they can eat.
You are an employee at the wedding hall.
- That's right. - I have seen such employees.
- Me too. - He shows people to their seats.
- An employee for the event. - Yes.
They are the guests at the wedding.
So Min is a guest...
who dressed up more than the bride.
She is here for the after-party.
I am determined to meet my future husband here.
That's right. You dressed up excessively.
By the way, the hints are too difficult.
Yes, they are. They are like riddles.
- There is a spy. Did you hear? - Yes.
- Who is the spy? - Isn't it you?
Which member is working the hardest?
That member is the spy.
Seok Jin didn't work hard, did he?
He keeps rapping by himself.
This is hard. All of us are working hard.
Apink thinks the member...
who is working the hardest is Haha.
- I see. - My goodness.
- They think Haha could be the spy. - I am not the spy.
- I am 100 percent sure. - I was the spy...
for the last two weeks. I am not the spy.
It must be someone who suits a circle.
Maybe "Balls" represent the Korean letter, ieung.
Then the spy's name would have ieung,
but not mieum.
Ieung looks like a circle and mieum looks like a square.
(Do "Balls" represent ieung and "Dice" represent mieum?)
- I think you are right! - Everyone's name has ieung...
- except for yours. - My name doesn't have it.
- My name doesn't have it. - You are the only one.
Jee Seok Jin doesn't have ieung.
Everyone else's name has it.
- Everyone else's name has it. - How about So Min?
- Haha. - Jong Kook's name has it.
(Is the hint about the spy's name?)
- We are ITZY. - ITZY.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Part 1 came to an end!)
- Let's go! - Apink!
- Apink, let's go! - You can do it!
Apink, let's go!
- Kwang Soo. - Good luck.
- Good luck. - Do a good job.
(The joint performances...)
(with Apink, Nucksal, Code Kunst, SORAN, and Gummy.)
(What kind of joint performances will we see?)
(Pink Nose Light, Hyo Chan Park,)
(Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok, and F-Killer)
It will be fun.
Please standby.
I think I will forget the dance.
- Don't do that. - I am so nervous.
This is driving me crazy.
Why are you nervous? Do you get nervous when you act?
I haven't performed on a stage.
I feel like it will be over if I make a mistake.
(The pressure comes from knowing he only has one chance.)
How fascinating!
To be honest, I could puke right now.
I am serious.
I am holding it back.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo are on standby on the stage.)
(Screaming)
There they are.
(Other artists watch with anticipation.)
It's Apink!
Will I be able to wear that kind of pink before I die?
There they are.
(These men are wearing pink outfits, which is Code Kunst's dream.)
(Their hearts are about to burst.)
(Apink watches them worriedly.)
(What kind of performance did they prepare?)
(Apink)
(Jee Seok Jin)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(Pink Nose Light)
- Hello. - Hello.
This is the kind of song we would never have received.
Are you satisfied with the song?
Do you think it's good?
- I did my best. - Right? It's really nice.
- I hope we can pull this off. - I know.
You might become disappointed today.
- We'll do out best. - You might become disappointed.
Nang only gives compliments.
- Really? - He does that even if you are bad.
- Really? - Yes.
I have low expectations.
I take what I can in a short amount of time.
Nang.
Did you compliment us in the past to take what you could?
I didn't mean that.
I complimented you in the past because you did a good job.
- I am glad we met a good man. - Seriously.
I want to ask you...
not to give up on us.
I will make it work.
If the notes become mushy...
"Mushy"?
(His tongue gets twisted already.)
(You'll tune our recording with the computer, right?)
He is the repair shop of the music industry.
(Don't worry because Nang is a veteran composer.)
- Should we decide on a team name? - That's right.
- The others already made theirs. - That's right.
What should we use?
Since our last names are Lee and Jee,
we go by LeeJee Brothers.
Then we could be Pink LeeJee.
(Then we could be Pink LeeJee.)
- Pink LeeJee. - Pink LeeJee.
It's cute.
Pink Nosebleed.
- Pink Nosebleed? - Pink Nosebleed?
- Why? - We want people to get nosebleeds.
You are "Pink", he is "Nose", and I am "Bleed"?
You don't want that name.
(If not Pink LeeJee or Pink Nosebleed...)
I think Pink Nose Light would be good.
- Pink Nose Light. - Pink Nose Light.
- "Kwang" means "Light". - Pink Nose Light.
- Pink Nose Light. - It's a good one.
- Pink Nose Light is cute. - It's a good one.
- We are Pink Nose Light. - Pink Nose Light.
(They decided on Pink Nose Light.)
- Shall we listen to the song? - Yes.
(It's time to listen to the song.)
(We gonna party, I like that.)
(We gonna party.)
(I like that.)
It suits him.
(He is pretty good.)
It sounds like he is singing the guide track.
(Seok Jin's throat is in good condition.)
(Good cheer)
Nang, let's record the song now.
(Humming)
The bridge.
It's your part.
(Gather around! Right now!)
(That's incredible.)
(Yeah!)
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo are good.)
That part was funny.
(The enthusiastic response gives them confidence.)
- The song is really nice. - I know.
It's refreshing.
- You are good. - Until the sun rises
- Eun Ji, warm up your throat first. - Okay.
She will warm up her throat.
(The main vocalist of Apink, Eun Ji warms up her throat.)
(When the sun sets.)
(When the stars rise.)
(Baby, baby, right here.)
(Impressed)
- My goodness. - Her voice suits the song.
- Her voice suits the song. - Gosh, it's so nice.
- He always does that. - That's right.
- That's his style. - Nang.
(Nang's compliment makes Eun Ji embarrassed.)
- It was okay, right? - It was really nice.
(Baby, baby, right here)
- That's good. We are set. - Are we set?
That's good.
(Eun Ji's recording goes without a hitch.)
- It's nice. - Okay.
It's nice, but...
He says "It's nice" first.
That's how he starts off.
It seemed like he was angry.
"It's nice, but..."
(There are many emotions within "It's nice.")
It's not like that.
Good!
(It means he really likes it.)
Gosh, it's nice.
(It means he likes it so much that he is going crazy.)
- Nang. - That's his style.
I am gaining confidence.
I know.
- Seeing Nang gives me confidence. - I know.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
I feel nervous in here.
- Please sing comfortably. - Good luck.
All right.
It's Seok Jin's turn.
I can't wait.
(He pulled off the intro perfectly a moment ago.)
(We gonna party.)
(That...)
(He missed the beat.)
My goodness.
Let's start over.
(They burst out laughing.)
It's nice. It's nice.
It's very nice.
He will lose his confidence.
- It's nice. - When that happens,
his back becomes hunched.
He will soon sing like this.
(He did a good job earlier.)
I am nervous.
- Good luck. - Please sing comfortably.
(With Apink's support, his 2nd attempt begins.)
(I like that.)
I am less nervous now.
(He suddenly becomes arrogant.)
Your vocalization became freer.
(How about this?)
(That's incredible!)
That's incredible.
Thank you.
I don't know if we are complimenting him...
or making fun of him.
- Are we complimenting him? - Yes.
- Let's warm up your throat first. - Okay.
(Until today becomes tomorrow morning)
(My goodness!)
(They cheer loudly.)
- It wasn't half bad. - Bravo.
He is happy. He is happy.
(Look at Kwang Soo.)
He is happy.
Stop it!
Let's stop it.
If we tease him too much, he will catch on.
It's nice.
- It's nice, right? - Yes.
(Pink Nose Light sings "Party" together.)
(The song that will welcome the refreshing breeze of fall...)
(will be revealed soon.)
(Pink Nose Light practices dance 3 weeks before the fan-meet.)
(Jo Ah Ra, Choreographer of "Party")
(A dance battle between Kwang Soo and Seok Jin...)
(is a key point of the dance routine.)
(Na Eun, Eun Ji, Bo Mi, and Kwang Soo...)
(versus Ha Young, Nam Joo, Cho Rong, and Seok Jin)
(When the two of them have a fight,)
(Bo Mi does a silly dance...)
(and wraps up the situation.)
Here is the important thing.
You shouldn't dance to the beat.
Don't dance to the beat.
Dance however you want.
It will be better that way.
(Bo Mi's offbeat and silly dance begins.)
(Laughing)
(How about this dance?)
(The vending machine of silly dances...)
(begins to work.)
(Bo Mi showed a new dance at every practice.)
(Which dance will she show on stage?)
Shall we begin?
Pink Nose Light, good luck. Let's go.
Kwang Soo.
When you sing "This honest feeling",
- you move to the back. - Yes.
The camera will zoom in on you then,
- so please look to the front. - Okay.
Music, start.
(The rehearsal that serves as the final practice begins.)
(They do relatively well until Kwang Soo's solo part.)
(He just needs to fall back as he looks to the front.)
(He bumps into Bo Mi.)
(He lifts up Bo Mi to hide his embarrassment.)
(This is a disaster.)
(The final practice ends that way.)
- Good work, everyone. - Are you okay?
(You fell down.)
(The last rehearsal ended on a shaky note.)
(In that nervousness,)
(these two men prepare for the performance.)
("Party" by Pink Nose Light)
(The refreshing intro improves...)
(the two men's musical-like performance.)
They are so cool.
It's like a youthful drama.
- "Tree Blooming with Love". - "Grease".
(The female leads of the youthful drama enter.)
I need to stand up.
- I can't see very well. - Me neither.
(The two uncle fans watch reverently.)
(Na Eun's performance heats up the atmosphere.)
(It's Seok Jin's solo part.)
(Seok Jin will forget about his age today.)
For Seok Jin,
this is like "Dad's Challenge".
(My son, are you watching?)
(Gather around! Right now!)
(They burst out laughing.)
What was this?
(He is proud.)
(She keeps her eyes on the camera.)
She is so relaxed.
How does she look at the camera with such ease?
(It's time for Kwang Soo's problematic part.)
(Will he take a risk for a closeup shot...)
(or stick to safety even if it's cowardly?)
(He looks at the back.)
(He took the cowardly route and looked at the back.)
(The sun goes to the sea.)
(The stars go to the sky.)
(Bo Mi flies.)
(Kwang Soo lifts her up as powerfully as he can.)
(Bo Mi's jump excites the audience.)
(It's for Kwang Soo and Seok Jin to get sexy.)
(Dancing)
(Men cheer even louder.)
(It's time for the climax, the dance battle.)
(Check out my Mosquito Dance!)
(Stop it!)
(She is the queen.)
(Bo Mi's silly dance wraps up the situation.)
- Oh, Bo Mi. - She is cute.
Bo Mi.
(She is so cute.)
(Bo Mi.)
(We gonna party, I like that.)
(Put everything down and party.)
(I like that.)
(Thanks to Apink's lead, they look like a cute coed group.)
They're cute.
(They clap along with the bubbly and cute song.)
Kwang Soo.
(This is the 1st collaboration performance of the night,)
(so Pink Nose Light members practiced hard for 3 months.)
(That was Pink Nose Light.)
(That was a perfect performance to start Part Two of the fan-meet.)
(The audience loves it.)
Thank you.
- We should have gone first. - Let's go.
They were so good.
Thank you very much.
- Are you all right, Kwang Soo? - I am.
- Are you okay? - I'm okay.
Please give him a round of applause.
Thank you.
(His parents are proud.)
We practiced so much, but I made a mistake.
I was so nervous.
I was supposed to do this,
but I did this.
(He did a hula dance.)
This dance...
Everybody, we are...
- Pink - Nose Light
Excuse us.
(He gives up fast.)
(Pink Nose Light is better at performing than singing.)
(It's all right.)
We tried our best not to hurt Apink's reputation.
I don't know if we did okay.
I'm worried.
How were the past three months?
I was the oldest in this group...
for the past eight years,
but I got rid of that title for the first time...
in eight years,
- so I was very happy. - It's difficult...
- to have somebody this old. - Right.
- Right? - Yes.
When I found out...
that we were on the same team,
I was ready to dance with Seok Jin on my back.
Because of me,
you were far from the oldest.
- You were far from it. - Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Let's introduce the next team.
I heard Se Chan is into hip hop now.
- Hip hop? - Yes.
(MC Se Chan is ready.)
The next collaboration team is...
Ji Hyo, Se Chan, Nucksal,
(Ji Hyo, Se Chan, Nucksal...)
and...
Code Kunst.
I heard that...
somebody incredible is coming.
There's a hidden card.
There's a hidden card again?
You can look forward to it.
Everybody,
are you ready to have fun?
- Yes! - Yes!
Make some noise!
(Seok Jin emcees the old way.)
That concludes Pink Nose Light's performance.
- Cho Rong, do you want to end? - Okay.
Let's say goodbye.
That was...
- Pink - Nose Light
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
There's so much excitement out there.
This is no joke.
- Great work, everybody. - Great work.
Are you all right?
Did you vomit on stage?
Drink some water.
Everybody, let's check the hint.
(It's time to check the decibels to earn the hint on the spy.)
(What were their highest decibels?)
The cheer from the audience reached 126dB.
The cheer from the audience...
reached 126dB.
- so you've earned the hint. - Okay.
(The highest decibels came from this part.)
(Thanks to Bo Mi's dance, they scored 126.8dB.)
- Okay. - Please choose 1 out of 3.
This is the hint. It's a hint about the spy.
(The spy buys coffee sometimes.)
What's this?
- What is it? - Let me see.
- They buy coffee. - Does anybody own a coffee shop?
- No. - Great work.
- They buy coffee. - They do.
Did nobody pay for coffee?
I don't think we did.
Wait.
So Min paid for coffee today.
Did she?
- It was her first time paying. - Really?
(So Min paid for coffee today.)
(She usually don't get coffee.)
(Who is the spy?)
(This is the second collaboration performance.)
(Nucksal and Code Kunst appear,)
(and the audience's expectations rise.)
(They look relaxed.)
(They dominate the stage...)
(with their bright auras.)
Nucksal.
He looks cool.
Are you ready to have fun?
(They're ready to have fun.)
(They're professionals who have been in competitions.)
(He's a rookie who is not relaxed at all.)
(They're really nervous.)
(The video plays before the performance.)
(How was this performance made?)
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Yang Se Chan)
(Hyo Chan Park)
- What are we going to do? - I think the important thing is...
to discuss the lyrics you and Ji Hyo wrote.
That's the most important part.
- We need a theme. - That's what we'll talk about.
Like you mentioned last time,
is this going to feel like a night club...
or something else? I wrote my lyrics to feel like that.
Let's hear it first.
- Here? - Yes.
- I'm so embarrassed. - Come on.
You can read to the beat.
This is a night club,
and everybody is having fun together.
You can read.
"Raise the volume and excitement".
"Soak your body with sweat".
"Those who are tired from studying, tired from looking for jobs",
"and those who are stressed and losing confidence".
"Spray the perfume, add the insoles",
"and use every penny you have to have fun. Let's go".
(and use every penny you have to have fun. Let's go.)
(It's fun to squander.)
- "Use every penny you have." - You have to.
- "Use every penny you have." - Let's go
- This is nice. - That's the feel.
"You don't know how to run, so you are suffocated".
"I'll provide the solution. I'm Baek Jong Won".
(I'll provide the solution. I'm Baek Jong Won.)
- "Baek Jong Won"? - That's the last part.
He rhymed it.
(This is MC Se Chan's newly discovered hip hop DNA.)
That's what I wrote.
- Then Ji Hyo. - Well,
mine's too dark.
That's good. That's better.
- That's better. - That is.
- Read it. - Please read it.
This is mine.
"When I started Running Man at 30, it was a hot day in July".
"I didn't know anything. I just ran, searched, and rolled".
"I am 39 now. It's a hot day in July again".
- "A grave"? - Hey.
(She said "hot" not "grave".)
Why would she go to a grave after nine years?
- Why would you do that to me? - Hot.
- You said it was dark. - Hot.
- That sounded scary. - I thought she said "grave'.
"I spent my 30s and one-third of my life on Running Man".
"Every moment and memory".
"Running Man is a part of everything".
That's nice.
"Kids go from kindergarten to high school".
"They smile and come say hi to me".
"I learn about myself".
"And I learn about you".
"And I learn about us".
"And we protect and lead each other".
You really like "and", Ji Hyo.
- You really do. - I didn't know how to end it.
- You don't have to. - It's nice.
That's why you have us.
They're writing something.
They wrote something. Are you done?
(Look at this.)
- Why? - What did he write?
- Did he write "grave"? - He said you failed.
We failed?
(Code Kunst said you failed.)
- At the end, - We failed.
I wrote, "We're in trouble".
Both of us.
(If this was an audition, they would have been eliminated.)
Okay.
What's our team name?
- The team name is important. - Right.
It's nice to combine our names.
I kind of wanted to do...
- Ji Hyo and Friends. - "Ji Hyo and Friends"?
No, we're not friends. We're much younger. What do you mean?
Ji Hyo and...
(Ms. 40 is mad.)
- You're not much younger. - Ji Hyo,
- the team name is important. - You're not much younger.
The team name is important.
You're the oldest.
- Hyo Chan. - I'm right.
- Ji Hyo and... - Hyo Chan Park.
- Hyo Chan. - Hyo Chan.
- Se Chan. - Hyo Chan Park.
- Hyo Chan Park? - That's good.
- One word each from their names? - Yes.
Are we a park?
- We are. - Yes, it's nice.
We let people play.
(We let people play.)
(Goodness)
(That's amazing.)
- That's awesome. I respect you! - I knew it.
(They respect Code Kunst.)
You are a park.
This is nice.
- Let's listen to it on the phone. - Okay.
(They listen to the melody of the song they'll be performing.)
So we'll take this song,
then you rap, I rap,
and she raps.
Do we just tell the story?
- I have a basic idea... - Are we going to work on that?
about the composition.
First of all, Ji Hyo...
(This is the first composition.)
will be the center.
- The center? - That's the chorus.
- You're moving her to the back. - No, I'm not.
(You're moving her to the back.)
You're unsure about letting her sing in the beginning,
- so you're moving her to the back. - She's not in the beginning.
I want to make her entrance impactful.
Are you saying that after you heard my lyrics?
- That's not what I meant. - Okay.
Being the center is even better.
That's the chorus part. The chorus is important.
Can she do it by herself?
So this is the second suggestion.
If I leave it up to Ji Hyo,
she might feel too pressured.
If you're not a vocalist,
- it's tough. - Right.
Can we give that part...
to somebody else?
- Somebody else? - Yes.
Like a vocalist?
So this is the idea.
In hip hop,
there's a featuring culture.
The songs can be diverse.
(For featuring,)
(how's that team?)
- Really? - What do you think?
(Can we ask them?)
(Who is them?)
- They're too huge. - The audience doesn't need us then.
(The audience doesn't need us then.)
It'll be more fun if they do it without us.
- It'll become a big party. - Is that right?
- That's not it. - They don't need us.
They won't come out in the beginning.
It'll be just us to start.
If the song is three minutes long,
we'll do 2 minutes and 30 seconds of it.
They just want us to be funny.
And that person will do the grand finale.
- You just want us to be funny. - That's not true.
- I'm so disappointed in you guys. - No.
- All of us will do it together. - All of us.
The appearance itself will improve the performance.
Right.
(Next week)
(A special guest joins the joint performance.)
(When Ji Hyo and Se Chan's performance is wild enough,)
(this guest has come to make them go wilder.)
(Burning excitement)
(The band and the members put on playful performances.)
(And they put on performances, full of emotions too.)
(Their sharp group choreography will be revealed.)
(And this song will be the grand finale.)
(It will be remembered in a corner of their heart for a long time.)
(And it's time to arrest the spy at last.)
(Many accounts of the spy will be reported.)
Is it Se Chan?
(Members who seemed unusual will be pointed out.)
I really wasn't sure.
(Will they be able to finish the fan-meet successfully?)
(Nine Years of Running Man: The Grand Finale)