(Autumn is the perfect season to film along with fall foliage.)
- Hello. - Hi.
(Se Chan and So Min arrived earlier than usual.)
That was natural, right?
(But they spotted something.)
- What's that? - I have no idea.
- What is that? - What is it?
I don't know. Look at this.
- Who's going to wear this? - Is that centaur?
I don't know. What is this?
- This is the worst. - Who is this for?
(These four colorful outfits wait for their owners.)
(2 weeks ago, they arrested the bio-terrorist, Jae Seok.)
(Except for Haha and Jong Kook, everyone will face the penalty.)
(However, Haha and Jong Kook can save two people from the penalty.)
(The first survivor is Kwang Soo.)
(The second survivor is Seok Jin.)
(The rest of them will face the penalty during the opening.)
This is the worst.
Which one is yours?
So Min will wear a Minion's outfit.
- Minions? - That's cute.
- They gave you a cute one. - It's cute.
Is that for me?
- Is that yours? - Is that for me?
You're the octopus villain from "Little Mermaid".
Ursula.
I don't know who she is.
I'm just curious. When he wears that,
does he just wear this without anything on the bottom?
(Does he just wear this without anything on the bottom?)
Hey, you want me to wear this with just my underpants on?
What is that? No way. That's ridiculous.
That's a nice outfit. I think it will be funny.
Let's change.
Once you change into your outfit, we'll start your makeup.
I think we're meeting so often these days.
I went to the amusement park a while ago.
(What?)
(My gosh, Se Chan.)
My gosh, Se Chan.
I don't know. This is...
(It's obvious that 8 tentacles were made at the last minute.)
- Hey. - You didn't put any effort into it.
It's really tight on the bottom.
Strangely, it resembles Se Chan.
It does?
I can't wait to see it.
(What? That's...)
You're going to use glue?
(You're going to use glue on my eyebrows?)
- What? Glue on your face? - I've done a lot of makeup,
but using glue is the first.
(The glue is new to this veteran.)
So Min, you get the penalty every single time.
I don't know. I guess I'm fated to face the penalty.
Promise me. When I get married, delete all of these clips.
No, they should play the clips at your wedding.
You know that they play a video at weddings, right?
The video before the weddings.
They have to play this.
What's that?
What did they put on your face? Are those bruises?
(What did they put on your face? Did you get bruises?)
I look like a patient. A sick patient.
- He's sick of it. - You're an expert, right?
I'm sorry to have doubted you.
We just got started. But people always doubt in the beginning.
- Hi, Ji Hyo. - You're here.
- Ji Hyo. - Which year were you born?
Year of Rooster.
- You're a chicken then. - You're a chicken.
(Ji Hyo will be the Angry Bird.)
You can wear it every day. You're always angry.
- Hello. - My gosh.
- My gosh. - Jae Seok.
Jae Seok, you can come later. There's nothing for you to do.
I was surprised for a second. I thought you had makeup on.
Jae Seok, did you get your makeup done for the penalty?
So Min, check if he got the special makeup done.
- Jae Seok. - Jae Seok, you need...
- to dress up for your penalty. - What is it?
You'll be a llama.
You're a llama, so you'll be called Yuma today.
Since he'll look like a llama, people might feed him straws.
Make sure you eat that. Okay?
(The highest budget spent on a costume)
- Shall I put on the wig? - Se Chan, you look so cool.
You look great.
- Don't I look like a musical actor? - Yes.
You guys look like a couple from a theater troupe.
(You guys look like a couple from a theater troupe.)
Honey. Thank you.
- She's starting the skit again. - Honey.
Honey, are you an octopus today?
(He can't get into the role.)
- What's that? - My hair.
- What? You had hair? - Yes.
Look at them. They're having fun together.
(They're having fun together .)
(A forced love interest for the airtime)
My goodness. You look like a couple.
Honey. Get on.
Give back my body.
Do you think we're doing a show today?
This is a penalty.
So Min. It looks like you're happy with your character today.
- Me? Do the Yondu makeup. - Yes.
Everything after that is nice.
(Afterward, she's happy with anything.)
But isn't that wig for the grass?
(His witch disguise is going nowhere.)
Se Chan looks nice.
I do resemble my mother.
- Hey. - I just realized it. I'm serious.
(What did your mother do to you to deserve that?)
My gosh. Jae Seok.
- I look like Hong Hyun Hee. Look. - You do look like her.
(He also resembles Hong Hyun Hee?)
- My goodness. - So Min, look at me.
"Sir."
Se Chan, Jae Seok looks like...
the kangaroo at the zoo.
(The kangaroo who seemed to be troubled in Episode 470)
Look at him. He looks just like the kangaroo.
Look. Jae Seok.
(Laughing)
- Look at him. - My goodness.
You can't laugh while doing my makeup.
He looks like that kangaroo.
- I mean... - Seriously.
You look like that kangaroo. You resemble a lot of things.
- You're done. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Well done.
(How will the llama look?)
(Bursting into laughter)
Everyone, give him a standing ovation.
You look perfect.
(Yuma is born.)
Actually, he looked more like a llama without the makeup.
(You can't deny the resemblance.)
The llama is eating.
(The llama is eating.)
(As llamas eat everything, they eat grass, straws, and chocolate chips.)
- I need to shake it for llamas. - The llama is eating.
They like it when I shake it like this. All right.
Go ahead.
(You brats.)
Llama, there you go.
But So Min's makeup could've been better.
Jae Seok, we have to give her a yellow card. This can't be right.
But the hair...
I mean, if she's going to be on the show,
- Gosh. - it should be shocking like yours.
You're making a lot of noise while you eat.
(That's bothering me.)
My goodness, Mr. Llama. You're eating too loud. Gosh.
You're chewing it over and over again.
Give us the mission.
(It's time to listen to their mission.)
- Today... - Don't you dare.
(She's caught, trying to get on the llama's back.)
Don't even think about it. Okay?
Before you start your race,
you will carry out a simple mission.
You must run away from the other members...
in this park for 30 minutes starting now.
(They must be on the run for 30 minutes.)
(Stay away from the members for 30 minutes.)
How could I get away from them in this costume?
How can I run in this?
This is good for you. You'll be running on fours.
- You'll be much faster. It's good. - Hey, you have eight tentacles.
(Here's an 8-wheeler!)
- You have eight tentacles. - Right.
- And you can fly around. - I can fly around.
If you look at your costume,
there are six spots such as the front, back, arms, and legs...
- to put your name tags on. - Right.
Among these 6 spots, you can choose 1 spot...
to secretly hide a sticker for a chance card.
- A chance card? - Okay.
There is a total of six members...
including two guests who will chase after you.
The chasers can only take off two name tags per each member.
If they get a name tag where you hid your chance card,
the chaser will take the chance card.
If you manage to protect the card until your time is up,
you will get the chance card.
That's nice.
You will attach your own chance card in secret.
Okay.
(Where will they put it?)
- The weather is great today. - Yes.
As you can see, there are only four of you.
Before we meet the rest of the members,
let me bring in two guests who will join you today.
- The guests are coming here? - They are coming here.
Guests, come on out.
All right. Come on out.
- Over there. - They are coming.
(Are they two ladies...)
(with a spring in their steps?)
Hey, Hyun Hee.
(Hong Hyun Hee, the comedienne and Park Ji Hyun, the actress)
Hyun Hee.
Hello.
(The marriage ambassador, Hong Hyun Hee)
(This comedienne is ruling the industry with her husband.)
(She has a wide range of roles with her delicate performances.)
(She was in a historical drama as well as a horror movie.)
(This rising actress made the movie look realistic with her acting.)
Hello.
(Feeling super excited)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Hello.
By the way, where is Jae Seok?
- He has something to do. - Why did you ask that right away?
- Why did you ask that right away? - He'll be here.
Well, he's the symbol of this show.
- "Symbol"? - Yes.
- That's true, but today... - That's so outdated.
You're trying to get into his clique in an outdated manner.
(Trying to get into Jae Seok's clique)
We don't do that anymore.
- I mean... - We don't do that.
I don't know who's leading. I don't know who I should look at.
You can look at anyone.
- We work for the viewers. - You can look at the camera.
By the way, you married such a nice guy.
- Thank you. - I like your show.
They make a great couple.
- They make a great couple. - And they are so fun to watch.
- Besides, he's younger than her. - By four years.
After getting married, I've been working...
10 years' worth of work in just 1 year.
- I actually got to save up. - Congratulations.
I bet you made a lot of money.
Our first wedding anniversary is this October.
- Give me a round of applause. - Really?
(Our first wedding anniversary is this October.)
(Give me a round of applause.)
She told us to give her a round of applause.
- I heard that when I was in Turbo. - Right.
- Right. - Now that Jae Seok isn't here...
The hosts would say, "Give a round of applause."
(Jae Seok is missed in many ways.)
Here's what's interesting.
Ji Hyun didn't get to say a word at all.
Actually, we don't have a lot of information.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm a new actress. My name is Park Ji Hyun.
(I'm a new actress. My name is Park Ji Hyun.)
Why is she joining us today?
What? What do you mean why?
- What do you mean why? - No, hear me out.
- Then, why are you here? - Hear me out.
Why are you joining us today?
I was wondering if she was here to promote something.
- Like a drama. - You should've asked smoothly.
Today's theme is the popular comedienne and popular actress.
- I see. You're popular. - That's the theme.
- You're popular. - Not at all.
Before we start the race,
you'll do a preliminary mission for the chance card.
- A chance card? - We'll just do it?
(There's a chance card?)
You decided on the members to face the penalty two weeks ago.
Those four members have put on a costume and makeup...
and are on the run in the park.
- Gosh. - On the run?
My fur is shedding. This is awful.
- Right? It's shedding a lot. - My goodness.
Starting now, you will...
It's going to be hard to hide too.
- Start... - You can't hide.
- the race. - My gosh. It's too early for this.
- You'll start the mission now. - Great.
Where are they?
Start the race.
- Let's split. - Let's split.
Jong Kook, we only have 30 minutes.
My goodness, hold on. How can I find them?
I hate running the most.
What kind of costume did they put on?
(So Min the Minion is on the run with her hair fluttering.)
My shoes are too heavy.
I picked the wrong shoes.
(I'm going to get angry!)
Move.
I hear something from there.
(Barking)
No, I'm a human.
I'm a human.
My dog doesn't bark at people.
Wait.
The dog doesn't bark at people.
I'm a human.
I can't run in this costume.
(The 4-wheeler is broken.)
(He hides in the woods.)
(Looking docile)
My gosh, this is too white.
If I roam around, I'll get caught no matter what.
(His costume is quite visible. What will happen to the llama?)
(Meanwhile, Hyun Hee who hates running...)
Where are they?
I don't think I need to...
run from the beginning.
(Hello.)
(My gosh, it's Hyun Hee!)
(Feeling hyper)
(It sounds like a conversation among animals.)
Do you have gimbap?
(That was her agenda.)
(We have gimbap!)
Gimbap.
(Depending on the presence of gimbap, her reactions vary.)
(What? I see a lot of people.)
Who is it?
Who's there?
That's Hyun Hee. Darn it.
What's she doing?
She doesn't want to get the chance chard.
Do you have gimbap?
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo the Angry Bird is running in the woods.)
(Jong Kook finds her red costume.)
Hey, she's right there.
(Jong Kook fiercely chases after her.)
(And Ji Hyo toddles away while getting mad.)
She's right there.
She's a parrot.
(Jong Kook is coming from the left, and Haha from the right)
Just come here.
(What should I do?)
- Come here. - I'm so angry!
I got it.
- Are you the Angry Bird? - She's the Angry Bird.
I'm so angry.
- Right here. - Haha got one.
Really?
(He finds the chance card on his first try.)
- Okay. I got the chance card. - Really?
(Ji Hyo is out, and Haha gets a chance card.)
Chance card!
(Haha is on a roll. His next target is So Min the Minion.)
- Come on. - Okay.
Are you serious?
Come on.
(He also steals So Min's chance card.)
I got the chance card.
Se Chan!
(Se Chan is spotted by Hyun Hee who was looking for gimbap.)
I don't know the rules.
(She gets a chance card.)
Teach me.
(As Se Chan is out, only the llama remains.)
I can't find Jae Seok.
(Everyone is getting eliminated, but Jae Seok is seen nowhere.)
Where is he?
(Kwang Soo is passing by the llama's hideout.)
Where is he hiding?
It's Kwang Soo.
Se Chan.
(It turns to be the best spot to hide.)
(It's the perfect blind spot. Haha zealously looks for Jae Seok.)
(It's the perfect blind spot.)
Seriously.
I'm a professional.
My gosh, look at this.
Wandering around will not help at all.
(Wandering around doesn't help in the jungle.)
(Only 1 minute remains.)
(Surprised)
(Kwang Soo found something all of a sudden.)
(He goes after the llama's tail.)
(Dashing away)
(The giraffe spotted the llama's movement.)
(And everyone gathers around.)
- Over there. - He's over there.
It's Jae Seok.
(The 4-wheeler is too slow.)
I got you.
(The llama is caught right before time is up.)
- I was so surprised. - He got me first.
I was really surprised.
- are you a llama? - Yes.
- Seriously. - You're a llama?
- I thought he was a real llama. - He looks like a real llama.
I was doing a pretty good job at hiding.
- He looks like a real llama. - I was so surprised.
- This is amazing. - I get to take off two, right?
I'll do it.
(I'll take the one from here.)
Here I go.
(There's no chance card.)
- I got scared for a second. - You got one more chance.
You were scared for a second?
(What?)
(If he got scared when I chose his left leg,)
(does that mean the chance card is on his right leg?)
No, it's not here.
It's not here. It cannot be here.
(10 seconds before time is up)
It has to be here!
(Will Kwang Soo take it? Or can Jae Seok keep it safe?)
(What will happen to the chance card?)
(Sighing)
The race is over.
(No one was able to steal Jae Seok's chance card.)
My goodness.
You can't find the chance card?
(Where is Jae Seok's chance card?)
Jae Seok, there's a spot on the stomach.
- Where? - There's a spot on the belly.
- I should put it on the belly. - There's a spot on the belly.
Lucky you.
Jae Seok is so lucky.
(He hides the chance card where it can't be easily reached.)
- Where is it? - It's on my belly.
- It's on my belly. - Goodness.
We have guests today.
Hyun Hee and Ji Hyun are joining today.
- Hello. - Hi.
You weren't here earlier. I looked for you as soon as I got here.
- I wasn't here? - Right.
(Feeling excited again)
She's hyper.
Weren't you in "Gonjiam", Ji Hyun?
- Yes, that's right. - I knew it.
- Right. - "Gonjiam".
Right. Why didn't you tell us that?
- That was the scariest movie. - Earlier...
- The movie was really scary. - Thank you.
How do you feel being on our show for the first time? I'm curious.
It's my first variety show ever.
- I'm so nervous. - This is your first variety show?
I was on "One Night Two Days" briefly. It was really brief.
- You were on that show? - "One Night Two Days"?
(What are they picking up after asking her a question?)
- Very briefly. - What are you doing?
What are you doing?
You asked her a question.
- You asked her a question. - What are you doing?
It kept fluttering away. My apologies, Ji Hyun.
- It's all right. - You should shave.
- I'm sorry. - I thought it was a foxtail.
- You should shave. - I'm sorry.
- I thought it was a foxtail. - By the way,
is Se Chan older than you, Hyun Hee?
No, I debuted before her, but I'm younger than her.
- You're like Jae Seok and Seok Jin. - You're just like us.
- You're just like them. - You're similar to us.
But she always treats me with respect like a senior comedian.
- She's always respectful. - Yes, I am.
- Seok Jin isn't like that. - You should learn from her.
- You should learn from her. - Why don't you do the same?
What are you talking about?
You need to be respectful toward Jae Seok.
- I have to do that to him? - Yes.
I mean this when I say it.
- I should teach him a lesson. - You should.
(He sounds serious.)
I plan to teach him...
- and So Min a lesson. - Yes.
- You should. - Seriously.
- I need to be harsh on So Min. - You ought to do that.
- You should. - I need to be harsh on her.
- Look at her disguise. - This isn't right.
For a comedienne, this isn't acceptable.
(For a comedienne, this isn't acceptable.)
- Comedienne? - Comedienne?
- It's not acceptable. - It's weak, isn't it?
Today,
to celebrate autumn which is full of delicacies,
you will visit good restaurants with the guests...
and taste delicacies of the autumn ingredients.
- You came on the right day. - You came on the right day.
Usually, it's really hard to be on our show.
- This is great. - You picked the right day to come.
(A restaurant mission to celebrate autumn with full of delicacies)
Of course, the number of members who can eat...
and the mission will change for each restaurant.
And only the winning members can eat the food.
(Only the winning members can have the meal.)
As for the chance cards you acquired earlier,
if you don't have a chance to eat the meal,
you will be given a chance to have one bite of your choice.
- 1 bite? - 1 bite?
Right now, Haha has...
two chance cards.
Hyun Hee stole one from Se Chan.
And Jae Seok was able to keep his chance card.
- Okay! - He did?
Later, Haha, you can give one of your cards to someone else.
Or you can use both of the cards.
I'll use them.
I don't know the definition of "give".
Is that so?
Same here.
However, today's race is called...
Let's Eat with Greedy Pigs.
- "Let's Eat"? - There are greedy pigs.
- There are greedy pigs. - Among you,
there are two greedy pigs.
- Two again? - My goodness. What is this?
Today, it has to be Kwang Soo.
- Why me? Why? - It has to be Kwang Soo.
- It has to be you, Kwang Soo. - It must be you.
- Why are your ears red? - It's about time...
- that he got a role. - But Kwang Soo...
- looked different from yesterday. - Right. He smiled earlier.
- Seok Jin wants us to pick on him. - I applied a bit here.
(This doubt-seeker is praying with his hands clasped.)
- It's not him. - It's not?
Don't do it? Okay.
(Don't give him attention.)
I think it has to be Kwang Soo.
- Shouldn't we pick on him once? - It's either Kwang Soo...
Let me tell you why it can't be him.
He doesn't eat much to be a greedy pig.
- That's true. - Right.
- And he doesn't enjoy the food. - Right, he doesn't.
All right.
There's a hidden mission for the greedy pigs.
- I'll reveal the hidden mission. - What?
(You'll reveal the hidden mission?)
- What's the mission? - The greedy pigs...
must not eat any food today.
- But you have a chance to eat. - They have to keep losing.
- If they eat anything, - Should I make them have a bite?
Those who get to eat...
will know how many greedy pigs are in that group.
(The staff will reveal the number of greedy pigs.)
They're giving us a lot of intel today.
- I know. - The greedy pigs can't eat?
- How is that possible? - They'll get caught right away.
After trying three fall special dishes,
you'll get to vote.
If you fail to catch both greedy pigs, they'll win.
They'll get to pick two members who'll be penalized.
Today's penalty is that after the filming,
you will hand wash cars.
- Goodness. - Oh, no.
No way.
All right, please change, and then, we'll begin.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- I'm ravenous. - Me too.
Ji Hyun looks a bit tense today.
Did you not sleep well last night?
- It's her first variety show. - You didn't, right?
You have trouble sleeping before shooting your first variety show.
You couldn't sleep well last night either, right?
(You look unwell.)
I slept very well.
(He's in his best condition.)
It doesn't look like so.
- Your skin looks bad. - He's been doing this for 25 years,
but he still gets nervous.
Ji Hyun, what is your impression of Seok Jin?
Tell us.
Don't I look better in real life?
Don't I?
(What is her impression of him?)
You're not wearing any makeup, are you?
- No, I am. - He's wearing thick makeup.
It took him three hours.
- It's very thick. - It took him three hours.
We waited for him to shoot the opening scene.
- You don't look too well. - He's wearing makeup.
- It was dark when I put makeup on. - He wears a lot of makeup.
What do you think about his personality?
I think you're smart.
- Right. - That's not it.
- He majored in economics. - Right.
- No, it was business. - Oh, right.
You didn't take the SAT, right?
No.
He took the state examination.
- He took the state examination? - That's right.
He went to primary school.
I walked to Hanyang.
(He plays along.)
He failed the first time around because his rice paper got ripped.
It was too drenched in ink.
(He was nervous, and his handwriting was too thick.)
- Gosh, Seok Jin. - He's an intangible cultural asset.
I know.
Ji Hyun, are you good at drinking?
No, I'm not.
- Really? - It must be tough.
What do you do for fun?
- I like gaming. - What?
What game?
I play League of Legends and PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds.
- Really? - She's a game mania.
Legendary Battlegrounds?
(Legendary Battlegrounds?)
(He mixes the two names.)
Is that a Chinese idiom?
(Are the battlegrounds legendary?)
- What was that? - He's serious.
It's League of Legends.
- And PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds. - Come on.
What's wrong with him?
- What did you think it was? - His face is red.
- It's League of Legends. - League of Legends.
- League of Legends. - League of Legends?
What is Jason doing today?
He has a radio show.
We appeared on the show together,
but he was given a permanent position.
Before they got married,
they went on a trip abroad for a very long time.
- How long? - We went to Spain.
- Before they got married? - Yes.
Why did you go for so long?
We got married after six months of dating.
- My schedule wasn't that busy, - Trips are a must.
so we went to Spain for two weeks.
But we rarely went outside.
We were getting to know each other.
(Was it a field trip?)
- That's a lie, right? - Right?
- You're lying, right? - No.
Right?
- Lucky them. - Right?
We didn't get to see the Baroque buildings.
We were busy getting to know each other.
- So... - She must have a lethal charm.
- She does. - She does.
- She's very charming. - Indeed.
- She's fun. - She is.
- I thought I'd be living alone, - Being fun is the best.
but this happened. You never know when it comes to life.
- Soulmates do exist. - Yes.
When did you feel that...
he was the one?
- So Min. - It's my time!
- I've been waiting. - Do you have a boyfriend?
- No. - That's why she asked, right?
- No, she's single. - Really?
She does have a slight interest in Se Chan.
- But it's not reciprocated. - Jae Seok, come on.
- Seriously? - You're in big trouble.
- Don't be ridiculous. - I think you do have feelings.
- So... - Then I wouldn't be doing this.
You may not have any feelings for him,
but your parents like you guys.
So you could just think,
- "I wonder how it'd be." - Just imagining it?
I can only do that if he gives me a hint.
- He doesn't show me anything. - Look at you.
- But... - But since he acts that way...
He's more charming. I'll tell you why.
(She finds that more charming.)
- He makes you go crazy. - He's...
- That's not it. - I get it.
He doesn't step over the line. That's why he's more charming.
- He is charming. - He'll be a good, loyal husband.
He'll never cross the line with other women.
That's why Park Na Rae likes him. He knows when to refuse.
He says no if it's a no.
That's a must.
- He doesn't play the field. - Why didn't you say no to me?
What do you mean?
Tell her right now that you're not interested.
I'm not.
Forget it. I'm not interested in him either.
You can't say that. You never know.
Next thing you know, you're married.
Go Eun said no to me at first.
Se Chan said he saw So Min get wasted a couple of times.
(There's a reason why he said no.)
That's not it.
- He saw you. - You're so cute.
- You're so cute. - She said I'm cute.
- So Min can be cute. - Right.
- You're so cute. - She's full of charms.
(They arrive at the first destination.)
I'd love to have some octopus.
Look at this.
It's samhap.
- Look at this. - It's samhap.
- Goodness. - I'm craving this.
- It's samhap. - There's pork.
- It's octopus soup. - There's kimchi too.
I'm really craving this.
This is insane.
- Sit down. - Okay.
Why are you sitting next to me? I thought you didn't like me.
(They argue once again.)
- You can sit over there. - I thought you didn't like me.
- Why are you sitting next to me? - Go over there or just sit.
- I just sat wherever. - They'll grow on each other.
- They're arguing. - Ji Hyo was like that once.
You're right.
Are you doing well?
"Are you doing well?"
- How are you doing? - He's doing fine.
- Are you doing well? - I'm watching and cheering for you.
This first fall delicacy...
is a treasure from the sea...
and is good for rejuvenation and your eyes.
It's a parboiled octopus set.
(Kicking)
It's octopus.
(What is that?)
- He's in good condition. - He is.
You're quite hyper today.
- Right? - You're hyper today.
That must be good.
Before doing the mission, we will play a game of wits...
to determine how many people can eat.
- We need to do that. - Game of wits?
We all need to eat.
For example, if I say 2 and 2 people stand up,
only two people will eat.
Let's say it's four.
If no one calls out 5 in 5 seconds,
then only four people can eat.
It's best to call out the highest number possible.
All right, everyone.
I'm going to call out one, so do remember that.
- I'll call out 2. - I'll call out 3.
- I'll call out four. - We need the highest number.
- I already said what I'll call out. - Everyone.
- The greedy pigs are listening. - Okay.
(The greedy pigs heard their plan.)
- They don't want to eat. - They'll interrupt us.
- Right. - They'll make us fail.
- One. - They shouldn't eat.
They'll definitely call out one.
(Listen to me.)
- Be careful. - Seok Jin.
- What? - Why isn't anyone listening to him?
- We keep ignoring him. - Come on.
Ji Hyun, you even ignored him.
It's okay.
I'm right next to him, but I keep ignoring him.
I keep focusing on her.
I heard you.
- Here we go. - I'll keep that in mind.
Ready.
Set. Go.
One.
(Jae Seok calls out right away.)
(Everyone is looking at each other.)
- 2. - 2.
You both said it.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyun say 2 at the same time.)
You both said two at the same it.
- Who was it other than Kwang Soo? - Goodness.
- Did Kwang Soo say it? - What's wrong with you?
(Everyone's suspicious of him.)
Ji Hyun also stood up.
What's the matter with you?
- You don't want two people to eat? - It's obvious.
Did you not like it?
She's a rookie. I knew she'd call out two.
You could've yielded to her.
- Why would I? - Why did you stand up?
At least three people should eat.
You should've yielded to her.
Five people should eat.
- You're a greedy pig. - He's right.
Let me say one thing.
Before we heard about the rules,
Ji Hyun was spotted somewhere all alone.
That's because she didn't want to find any chance cards.
- That's not true. - What do you mean?
(She had no interest in the chance cards.)
(Is she a greedy pig?)
What do you mean?
Look at her.
She's a rookie.
- You... - Just go home, already.
You're a tall pig.
- You're a tall pig. - That's true.
(But I'm not a greedy pig.)
- Why would you suspect her? - Only two people can eat.
Let's do a practice round.
Okay. I finally got how to do it.
Or we can change the rules and just pick out a random number.
- I'm going to call out 1. - I'll call out 2.
- I'll call out three. - I'm serious.
- I'll call out 2. - I'll call out 4.
I told you guys in advance.
Get ready.
Set. Go.
- 1. - 1.
(They both said 1.)
- My gosh. - This is for certain.
I told everyone that I'd call out one.
Hey, it's you, isn't it?
- It's you, right? - Hold on.
- It's you. - It's you.
- I said one before. - I repeated myself, right?
- My gosh. - I heard you.
- I said one before. - You're a greedy pig.
I called out one before.
(Actually,)
(Jae Seok did call out 1.)
I called out one before.
That's why.
- We're on the same team. - Why would you call out one again?
Gosh, Jae Seok.
- This is infuriating. - Jae Seok messed it up.
- He said it out loud. - It's him.
- Hold on. - Look.
Kwang Soo looks too happy.
- Hold on. Kwang Soo. - He's too happy.
- Why are you smiling so much? - Kwang Soo.
- Do you have good news? - You're grinning.
(Me?)
- Why are you grinning? - They're driving me insane.
- Why are you grinning? - Come on.
- You're... - He's hilarious.
- Then should I be crying? - That's not what I mean.
This isn't a good situation.
Doesn't he look strange?
You should feel bad.
- You should feel bad. - My goodness.
You should be regretting.
I'm not smiling because I'm happy.
- You should be flustered. - The situation is just funny.
It wasn't that funny.
He kept doing this.
- He keeps... - That's not right.
snickering.
- That's not right. - You should know better.
I know.
There are 2 1's and 2 2's.
- Who will pick? - Should Ji Hyo pick?
Ji Hyun can.
(He makes a suggestion, but Jae Seok ignores him.)
All right, then.
Did no one hear what...
- Seok Jin said? - I know, right?
- I pretended... - Everyone ignored him.
- like I didn't say anything. - He said it loud and clear.
His voice is like background music.
Please pick the right one.
Let's see what you've got.
Go, Chuncheon's daughter.
(Which one did she pick?)
What is it?
(They especially focus on Kwang Soo.)
- What? - I bet it's one.
(It's a 1)
- Sit. - Just sit down.
(I'm sorry.)
Actually, it won't be her.
(He's an expert at taking it back.)
- Hold on. - Didn't you hear what I said?
I mentioned that Seok Jin suggested Ji Hyo first.
Ji Hyo, go ahead.
Be confidence.
"Confidence"?
Isn't it "confident"?
(Is that a new type of pep talk?)
- With style. - Be confidence itself.
How is it that he rarely makes sense?
He doesn't even know simple grammar.
- Okay, I'll choose. - Just choose one.
(Which number did Ji Hyo choose?)
(They're keeping an eye on Kwang Soo.)
(Is he trying to maintain a poker face?)
- Two. - All right!
(2 people!)
- That's decent. - She's definitely better.
- Two is better. - Definitely.
Two...
What are you so happy about?
It's better than one, right?
- Gosh. - The greedy pigs must be happy.
Exactly.
- It's easy to hide who they are. - I know.
This next mission is to decide who'll eat the food.
It's called Conceal Your Lips.
Lips?
You will relay a word that fits the category...
to the person next to you.
No same words can be repeated,
and you must hide your lips so that we can't see it.
The category is food.
Food?
(The number 1 suspect Kwang Soo starts things off.)
Carbonara tteokbokki.
(Carbonara tteokbokki.)
(Not laughing is essential since that's also another condition.)
Bukchang-dong silken tofu.
They all have good pronunciation.
(Gosh...)
Yes, I heard it too.
(LA short ribs)
LA short ribs.
(I can't believe she didn't laugh.)
Grandma's boiled pork.
(Grandma's boiled pork)
(Her jaws bounce up and down.)
(She just put it out there and mentioned the brand.)
What was that?
(We can't laugh...)
(Her teeth are showing.)
(So Min's teeth are showing.)
So Min's out.
(So Min's out.)
What? Why?
Isn't it just the next person who can't laugh?
I thought the rule only applied to the next person.
- Seriously? - I didn't know.
- I'm... - She's out.
- I... - Are you one of the greedy pigs?
I thought it was just the next person...
- who had to keep a poker face. - Anyway, you're out.
- So Min, you're out. - I didn't know.
- Your teeth showed. - Really?
Anyway, we'll keep going starting with Ji Hyo.
The category is food just like before.
Gosh.
(I need to keep a poker face.)
Busan's soup and rice.
(Busan's soup and rice)
(Se Chan calms himself down mentally.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E475 Running Man
"Let's Eat with Greedy Pigs Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Shark fin soup.
(Shark fin soup)
Sinsa-dong marinated crabs.
(Bring it on.)
Pistachio and almonds.
(Pistachio and almonds)
What on earth was that? What did he say?
"Pistachio and almonds."
(Hyun Hee's out.)
Hyun Hee, you're out.
(Ji Hyun's next.)
Haeundae short ribs.
(Haeundae short ribs)
(Seok Jin stays strong and withstands her attack.)
- She's good. - She's just saying the brand.
Let's go the other way around.
We're going that way now.
You'll be saying it to her.
Is it my turn then?
Go.
Sindang-dong tteokbokki.
(He yells just so that he could make her laugh.)
Is it my turn?
(What type of food will the master name this time?)
She's really good at this.
Im Chang Jung Corner Jokbal.
(Im Chang Jung Corner Jokbal)
(He bursts out laughing.)
(She nearly gets them all.)
Im Chang Jung Corner Jokbal.
I didn't expect that.
No way.
She knows a lot of brand names.
No one can beat her.
It was like listening to an old lady from the Netherlands.
(Park Ji Hyun can play an old lady from the Netherlands.)
- No kidding. - She was like an old lady.
My gosh.
Her lips reached the back of her throat.
Who knew she'd be this funny?
(Others couldn't keep their laughter in.)
(Haha is out.)
(Ji Hyo is out.)
(Kwang Soo is out.)
(Only 4 remain.)
- Only two more to go. - Right.
Go ahead.
Ji Hyun's hilarious.
She looks like a different person with her lips tucked in.
I can't help but picture her face.
Isn't she great at this?
(We're reminded of the old lady from the Netherlands.)
(He does his best.)
(What is he saying?)
- What? - What was that?
What did he say?
Coal grilled pork?
Dongdu River budae stew.
- What? - Just tell us what it is.
What was that?
- Dongdu River budae stew. - You're out.
- Why? - You're out.
Why? Dongdu River budae stew.
- You're out. - Couldn't you hear it?
- Ji Hyun's next. - You won't withstand this.
You can't. She's an expert at this.
Here comes the old lady from the Netherlands.
It's over if he laughs.
(He gets himself ready.)
Shake Shack burger.
(Shake Shack burger)
(They all stand up laughing.)
(Laughing out loud)
This... I mean...
Are you kidding me?
- Do it again. - Gosh.
Ji Hyun, say it once again.
Jong Kook, look at her.
Shake Shack burger.
(She's a force to be reckoned with.)
(She was able to take down Jong Kook too.)
How can you not laugh at that?
She's too wicked.
- You became an old lady. - How is this possible?
It was like watching a horror movie.
So the two that'll be eating the dish...
are Ji Hyun and Se Chan.
(Ji Hyun and Se Chan are able to eat.)
- Nice. - Those with chance cards,
will you activate them?
- Must we decide right now? - Yes.
Hyun Hee and Haha.
What's the dish?
Out of the dishes you saw, it'll be the octopus ramyeon.
Just the octopus ramyeon? Can we have a whole bowl?
- Just one bite. - With our chopsticks?
Just one bite?
I'll wait for the next dish.
I'll use mine.
Haha, Ji Hyun, Se Chan.
I'll let you know if there are greedy pigs.
(Is there a greedy pig among the 3?)
There are...
no greedy pigs.
- See? - You get it now, right?
(There are no greedy pigs.)
- I knew it. - We lost a chance.
Everyone knows I'm not a greedy pig.
- That's right. - I can eat in peace now.
- None of us are a greedy pig then. - Okay.
- Never. - That's right.
- The suspect pool has shrunk. - A lot, actually.
Right.
How nice.
- Unbelievable. - One should eat the whole octopus.
My gosh.
It looks so good.
I'll enjoy some too then.
(This is the taste!)
- Haha needs to stack them up. - Is that allowed?
Gosh, the chance card is actually good.
Look.
(A symphony of octopus and boiled pork)
Gosh, what is he doing?
- Look. - That looks delicious.
Can I taste some and spit it out before I swallow?
- What? - It doesn't count as eating.
This is hard to tolerate.
We should've done a better job in the first game.
- Why ruin a perfectly good chance? - It was difficult.
- Exactly. - Must you put it that way though?
It wasn't on purpose.
- Why ruin... - Is the llama from the woods back?
Didn't he have his name tag on his belly?
That's right.
(After their meal...)
I hope we'll be offered a meat dish next.
I'm full.
We have to win the number game first.
I know.
- We could all eat. - Yes, and then...
we can see who doesn't eat.
Whoever they are got lucky this time.
- There are 10 of us. - Congratulations.
Greedy pig, you got lucky.
Unbelievable.
We can safely rule out those three though.
- Right. - It's hard not to eat, right?
- Right. - Exactly.
Ji Hyun, you seem to like food.
Yes, I do.
Exactly.
- That's always nice. - I think she eats well.
She likes eating.
Foodies who don't gain weight always seem charming.
Right.
- You see... - I easily gain weight though.
- What? - I easily gain weight though.
(She groaned from deep within.)
What...
Don't you hate soulless responses like that?
- I know. - Can't they just be honest?
- Just say you're being careful. - Don't you?
I want to hear them say...
that they don't eat after 6 p.m. and work out every day.
I used to weigh 78kg.
- What? - Really?
- So you went on a diet? - She worked hard.
That's close to my weight.
When was that? In high school?
- When I was 20. - 20 years old?
Yes, right after high school.
- So you lost the weight. - How did you do it?
I ate less and worked out.
- You should see Hyun Hee's... - No wonder she has a small face.
See her wedding photos.
- I lost 10kg for my wedding. - Really?
She lost the weight and I couldn't recognize her.
- Really? - That was me at 59kg.
You should look up the photo.
I love female comedians though. They're so charming.
- Right. - They're funny.
My in-laws love me because I bring laughter.
That's right.
Father, join me!
(Let's get it!)
(Father, laugh with me!)
- Do you really do that? - Yes, to my father-in-law.
He loves how I lighten up the atmosphere.
- He wants to live laughing. - 15 years.
- 15 years? - I'll take care of it.
- What? My life? - Yes.
- Okay? - What's the plan then?
- "Same Life, Unlike Dreams"? - Then "The Return of Superman".
- "The Return of Superman"? - "Taste of Wife".
And then "Son-in-law".
Then I'll let you be on "Burning Youth".
She said she'll let you go.
You've got to be kidding me.
She'll let me go.
We must be here.
It must be western cuisine. Are we having wine?
- Look. - This place is fancy.
I already smell something delicious.
- What? - What's this?
The next dish is pasta made with blue crabs.
Blue crabs are good for the skin and at preventing dementia.
This we must have!
- Seok Jin, let's eat this. - I want to.
- It prevents Alzheimer's. - Right.
Please sit down.
(They're about to sit down and start the mission.)
(So Min sits next to Se Chan.)
- You... - Hey.
- You sat next to me. - I didn't.
Why do you always sit next to each other?
- I mean... - She...
She sat next to me.
I sat here first, and she came and sat next to me.
(What are they bickering about it this time?)
(On the way here...)
- Why did you hold my hand? - What?
(Se Chan holds So Min's hand.)
Why did you hold my hand?
(There they go again.)
Why do you keep holding So Min's hand?
He put his hand on mine and stayed that way.
I was surprised, so I pulled my hand away.
- I had no idea. - Be careful.
- You didn't feel my fingers? - No.
You can't sit next to me anymore.
- Not during the mission either. - Fine.
You two sit next to each other all the time.
- This is my seat. - This is my seat too.
What's going on between them?
This time, four people can eat.
Let's decide who can eat by playing a game.
- Call My Name. - Call My Name?
Do you remember the game where you guessed the person?
We'll play that game.
(You have to guess the name on your head by asking questions.)
(He wears oversized clothes.)
(Oversized clothes?)
- Let me answer. Dracula. - Correct.
(You have to ask the right questions and think fast.)
I'm not even a greedy pig. I don't want to mess up.
Let's sit down.
If Kwang Soo is our player, we shouldn't expect to eat.
I'll do my best.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Let's eat. - Sure.
- Let's eat, Kwang Soo! - Okay!
- It'll be a tight game. - It will be.
It's not going to be easy.
Give them to me. Should I hand them out randomly?
That's easy.
(Kwang Soo gets Baek Jong Won.)
(Jong Kook gets Santa Claus.)
(Surprised)
(Ji Hyo gets...)
(Kwak Cheol Yong.)
(He was a scene-stealer in "Tazza".)
(Many of Kwak Cheol Yong's lines in the movie have become famous.)
- Let's go. - That's too easy.
- Let's do this! - I'll get it right!
Let's go!
What's my gender?
It's...
- not clear. - Really?
You can't say that.
Why is it not clear?
What?
- Why is it not clear? - You can't lie.
- You can't lie. - Fine. You're a man.
- Hey, hit him. - You're a man.
Was it unclear because you've never seen him naked?
(Was it unclear because you've never seen him naked?)
Hey.
- What? - How...
I'm just saying.
What's with him?
He destroyed my innocence.
Am I a man or a woman?
- You're a man. - You're a man.
Jong Kook is straightforward.
- Of course. You shouldn't lie. - He gives an answer right away.
Am I rich?
(That's a good question.)
I've never seen his bank books, so I have no idea.
(I've never seen his bank books.)
- What are you talking about? - It's true.
We can't know that.
- We can't know that. - We can't.
That's...
(Jong Kook avoids answering the clever question.)
What's...
my occupation?
(Impressed)
- It's hard to say. - In my opinion,
- I think he is... - Just give me one.
- a volunteer worker. - Well said.
(A volunteer worker)
(Santa Claus does volunteer work for children.)
Well said.
He donates a lot too.
He donates?
(He donates presents around the end of the year.)
- That makes sense. - That's hard.
It's true.
What's my occupation then?
(A "gambler" would be too direct.)
You're a romantic.
(You're a romantic.)
A romantic?
His occupation is a romantic?
(He has a real occupation though.)
- A romantic... - He is a romantic.
I know what you mean.
I know why you said that.
You're a CEO.
That's right. You're a CEO.
Does he have a construction company?
- Construction? - Are you sure?
I think it's finance.
(He's a gambler.)
- He's in finance. - Let me give you a bigger hint.
He started his business at an early age.
(He started his business at an early age.)
That's right. That's actually right!
- That's right. - He started at an early age.
That's right.
("I joined the gang at 17.")
(After starting at 17, he climbed up to the top.)
That's right.
(Good shot, Kwang Soo.)
That hint was too crucial.
- I just gave you a big hint. - It was too big.
It really was a big hint.
I'm on Ji Hyo's team, but I admit it.
- You admit it, right? - I have to.
Let me ask you a question.
Have I been on any variety shows?
(Santa Claus on variety shows?)
- Yes. - I've seen it.
Me too.
A volunteer worker appears on variety shows?
(He often does.)
I've seen it many times.
Really?
- It's a big hint. - Let me answer.
(A male volunteer worker who appears on variety shows?)
(Will Jong Kook get it right?)
Sean.
- It's a big hint. - Let me answer. Sean.
(Sean is a volunteer worker who appears on variety shows.)
Let me give you a big hint.
The beneficiaries of his donations aren't decided.
- They aren't decided? - No.
They're not decided beforehand.
- I disagree. - The scope is pretty big.
- I don't think so. - Give me another answer.
I disagree.
The beneficiaries are decided.
- They are. - There is a specific group.
- There is a specific age group. - A specific age group.
- A specific age group? - No.
- You shouldn't say that. - No.
That's not okay.
- Hit So Min once. - An age group?
I still get it sometimes.
Let me answer.
(Did he get it?)
Santa Claus.
(Correct)
- It's your fault. - She said an "age group".
Haha gave it away.
- He's still a child. - Haha gave it away.
- He said it... - Is it my fault?
"I still get it sometimes" gave it away.
Why couldn't you be more careful?
We should have been on Jong Kook's team.
I'll get it right.
I have to.
Does he have any famous quote?
(Does he have any famous quote?)
A quote?
I think there are many.
Say something.
Try to sound like him.
That'd be too easy.
Say something.
A quote?
(This might put everything to an end.)
This is...
If I said anything else,
it'd be against the rules, so I'll just say it.
(Which line will Kwang Soo say?)
Double...
(Double...)
(We win!)
That's too easy.
Hey, that's too easy.
(Ji Hyo remembers.)
- Oh, no! - Say the answer, Ji Hyo!
Did you get it?
Say the answer, Ji Hyo!
(Was my hint too easy?)
(As soon as Ji Hyo heard, "double",)
(she got up.)
(Will Ji Hyo say, "Kwak Cheol Yong"?)
I don't remember his name!
(I don't remember his name!)
(Celebrating)
What?
(They can't believe it.)
What is this?
- "I'm a romantic." - She doesn't remember his name.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
I go double!
(I go double!)
(Here's a quote.)
Sit down.
(Annoyed)
(I guess we'll win.)
(This is not good.)
This is the worst possible situation.
- This is crazy. - Ask one last question.
- She knows his face. - Ask for a quote.
What's my famous quote?
You have many famous quotes. "I go double."
"Has Mapo Bridge collapsed?"
"I'm a romantic."
(The quotes don't help Ji Hyo remember his name.)
What's my famous quote?
(What's Baek Jong Won's famous quote?)
(Well...)
That's enough.
You've done enough. You can stop.
- She should stop? - She should stop here?
Kwang Soo said, "I go double", and Ji Hyo should stop here?
- This should be enough. - I agree.
- "Well..." - Stop.
She crossed her arms.
Ask a question.
This person...
(She needs to remember his name, Kwak Cheol Yong.)
Give me a hint...
about his last name.
The actor's name is Kim Eung Soo.
(He makes it clear that it's Kwak Cheol Yong.)
(He even says the actor's name.)
(Kwang Soo says everything except the character's name.)
And what you have on your head is the character's name.
(He gives an additional hint.)
(Why can't you still remember the name, Kwak Cheol Yong?)
She still doesn't remember.
- This is... - He's really popular these days.
I know he's popular.
This is driving me crazy.
Both of you failed. The correct answers are...
(Both Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo failed to win a point.)
Baek Jong Won and Kwak Cheol Yong.
(Baek Jong Won and Kwak Cheol Yong)
It was Baek Jong Won.
Only Team White won a point.
- Let's move on to Round Two. - Okay!
This is going well.
(Who will play Round 2?)
My opponents are not easy.
- We narrow down the answers, right? - Yes.
- Like 20 Questions. - Exactly.
We'll narrow down the answers like when playing 20 questions.
Close your eyes.
(Who are the people they have to guess?)
(Hyun Hee gets Michael Jackson.)
(Ji Hyun gets Gummy.)
- Goodness. - That's not good.
Poor Se Chan.
(Who is the person that Se Chan have to guess?)
(Se Chan gets Gautama Buddha.)
(What is it?)
- Se Chan, look at me. - Why?
Look at me.
Why?
(Why? What is it?)
Let me ask a question first.
Is this a word I know?
(Is this a word I know?)
(He checks the difficulty of the answer.)
Is this a word I know? What do you think?
(Is this a word I know? What do you think?)
It would be difficult not to know.
It would be difficult not to know?
I think you would get confused.
I would get confused? It must be an advanced word.
It must be an advanced word. Okay.
- It could be an advanced word. - I see.
It could be an advanced word.
Am I a person?
This is a game where you guess the person.
(The producer steps in.)
(Embarrassed)
What was that?
(Hyun Hee, let's concentrate.)
That was a lousy question.
She surprised me.
- All right. - Am I a foreigner?
Yes.
- Am I a foreigner? - Yes.
That's one question. You are done.
Am I Korean?
- My goodness. - It's hard.
- Is it hard? - It's hard.
It's really hard.
As far as I know, you have several nationalities.
I have several nationalities? Several citizenships?
Several nationalities?
Isn't this person genderless?
How could I be genderless?
- He has a gender. - He has a gender.
- Of course. - Really?
Do the two of you know who this person is?
(Do the two of you know who this person is?)
Gosh, give me...
a different person.
I might be the one who knows.
You are an influencer.
- What is that? - Isn't that right?
- That's right. - What's "Influenza"? "Influenza".
(Whispering)
He said "Influencer", not "Influenza".
(He said "Influencer", not "Influenza".)
(For goodness' sake!)
- He is so stupid. - I didn't hear him.
("Influencer" is a word that is too advanced for Se Chan.)
I have babies, right?
Babies?
(Michael Jackson has children.)
- I have children, right? - Yes.
You have children.
- Okay. - Do you know the answer?
- Hyun Hee must have an idea. - Do you have an idea?
You can blurt out the answer.
It's okay if you get it wrong.
Sam Hammington?
(Is the answer Sam Hammington?)
(Everyone bursts out laughing.)
Sam Hammington!
(Sam Hammington is the epitome of a foreigner with children.)
I didn't expect that one.
Sam Hammington.
- Sam Hammington! - I didn't expect that one.
I will ask a sharp question.
I passed away, right?
(Did I pass away?)
(Sighing)
- I don't know what to say. - It's hard to answer.
It's hard to answer.
- It's hard to answer. - Listen.
If no one knows, why did I even get this person?
If no one knows...
- It's hard to say. - I can't help but be cautious.
Let me tell you this. My mom says you are in her heart.
What?
Let me answer.
(He receives a crucial hint!)
(Will Se Chan be able to get it right?)
A deity.
No?
(Se Chan is close to the answer.)
You are going in the right direction.
That's good.
(Hitting)
You hit hard.
All right. All right.
Give me one of my important works.
(Give me one of my important works.)
Okay.
(Hyun Hee asked a sharp question.)
One of your important works?
Yes.
- That person has... - Where does my face appear?
music videos.
(That person has music videos.)
- Music videos? - What?
(Se Chan unintentionally gave a crucial hint.)
What was it called?
The foreign award ceremony.
Let me answer. Michael Jackson.
(Michael Jackson)
Yes!
How did you know?
(Hyun Hee of Team Blue places 1st in Round 2.)
- How did you know? - How did you know?
- You told her too many things! - I did?
I did?
How did you know?
- He isn't that stupid. - You're right.
Seriously.
One side of his brain is developed, but...
The other side collapsed.
(I pity him.)
For goodness' sake.
"The other side collapsed"?
(One side is okay.)
One side is okay.
Se Chan,
I will let you know that you are close.
Keep going in the direction of the last answer.
He can get it right.
I bet he knows the answer.
What kind of garments do I wear?
Is "Garment" the right word?
- "Clothing". - "Clothing".
"Clothing".
That's the collapsed side.
(That's the collapsed side.)
(He showed his collapsed side with a wrong word choice.)
Don't be so full of yourself.
- Seriously. - It's just one side.
- It's just one side. - For goodness' sake.
- I understood you. - You understood me, right?
- I understood you. - You did, right? Thank you.
Tell me.
Overall, you wear one color.
She is right.
He wears one color.
I think I know.
- Hurry up and say it. - Hurry up.
Let me answer.
(Who wears one color?)
(Will Se Chan get it right?)
Monk Won Hyo!
Monk Won Hyo! No?
(Monk Won Hyo!)
(He isn't entirely wrong, but...)
Thank goodness he didn't say "Wonhyo Bridge".
(Monk Won Hyo!)
I can't believe Se Chan.
This is like Se Chan's segment.
- Keep going in that direction. - Am I not Monk Won Hyo?
- It's okay. - This is bad.
This is bad.
- I don't know the answer. - No, no!
- Don't give up. - Don't be like that.
- Monk Won Hyo. - You...
- Keep going in that direction. - You...
Se Chan, it's time to get it right. You are nearly there.
If Monk Won Hyo isn't the answer,
I have one option left. But this is...
I can't wait to hear it.
Do you have one option left? I can't wait to hear it.
- Give that answer. - Go ahead.
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
Bodydharma.
(He said "Bodydharma", not "Bodhidharma".)
(Bodydharma!)
It's "Bodhidharma"!
(He showed his flaws through a series of lousy answers.)
- It's "Bodhidharma"! - Bodhidharma.
Bodhidharma.
Is it incorrect?
"Bodydharma".
- Come on, Se Chan. - Bodhidharma.
- Go ahead. - Come on, Se Chan.
Is it incorrect? What's the answer?
Which age group am I in?
- Hold on. - My age.
You are in your 40s.
- What? - What?
- What? - Is that right?
You can get scolded later.
(You can get scolded later.)
(Se Chan, I am not in my 40s.)
- Hold on. - It's okay.
- It's okay. - Oh, you are in your late 30s.
Big Sister, I am sorry.
I thought she was in her 40s.
- Hey. - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Is she in her late 30s?
- "Big Sister"? - I thought she was in her 40s.
- "Big Sister"? - Make sure...
you apologize to her later.
- My goodness. - It was a crucial hint.
(Se Chan revealed a crucial hint!)
Se Chan, you are close.
Make a U-turn.
When I said "deity" earlier,
- people reacted. - That's right.
Then I should go in that direction.
That's right!
(That's right!)
I like the cross, right?
(I like the cross, right?)
(Don't say something so controversial.)
Are you talking to yourself? Is that a question?
He is talking to himself. Say so, you jerk!
(Say so, you jerk!)
I am frustrated too, you jerk!
(I am frustrated too, you jerk!)
(He clenches his fists.)
Who am I? I am dying over here.
Stop attacking me when you are on my team.
(Se Chan's anger makes everyone else laugh.)
(Laughing)
They said one side of my brain collapsed.
(The older members collapse because of Se Chan.)
(The collapsed side is making this round interesting.)
You have nothing to do with the cross.
Really? Okay.
You can do this.
- It must be a hard one. - No, it isn't. You can do this.
Do I have a signature pose?
That wasn't a bad question.
- That was pretty sharp. - A pose.
- Crossed legs. - Crossed legs?
Let me answer. Crossed legs?
Let me answer.
(He finally gets an idea!)
(An influencer who wears one color and sits cross-legged)
Gandhi.
Is it incorrect?
(Gandhi)
(Gandhi is an influencer who sits cross-legged)
Is Gandhi incorrect?
I don't know what to do.
All the answers are similar.
(All the answers are strangely similar.)
Both of you failed. The answers are...
(Both Se Chan and Ji Hyun failed to win a point.)
Gautama Buddha and Gummy.
- Who? - Gautama Buddha.
Do you know the word?
I have heard it before.
(I have heard it before.)
(Gautama Buddha is an advanced word he has heard before.)
You have heard it before.
That's too bad. We could have done better.
You were close.
Thus, the four members of Team Blue will eat.
(The 4 members of Team Blue win the right to eat.)
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, and Hyun Hee can eat.)
Does anyone want to use the chance?
I will use it.
Now, I will tell you if there are greedy pigs in the group.
- Okay. - Tell us.
I bet Kwang Soo is a greedy pig.
- I am not a greedy pig. - I bet Kwang Soo is a greedy pig.
The number will either be 2 or 1.
The number of greedy pigs in the group is...
(How many greedy pigs are in the group?)
one.
(It's one.)
- Watch them. Someone will act. - Jae Seok.
- I am not it. - I am not it.
- You keep saying that. - It could be Hyun Hee.
It could be Kwang Soo.
- I am telling the truth. - You aren't it, are you?
- You aren't it, are you? - No.
Haha isn't a greedy pig.
- I am not it. - It's one of the two.
There is one greedy pig among them.
- I am really not it. - Ji Hyo.
It's definitely her.
Kwang Soo's ears are red.
- He said he won't eat. - I'm really not it.
I'm quite full.
- It was a good meal. - It was very delicious.
- Yes. - It looked really delicious.
It looked so delicious.
- Come on, come on - Come on, come on
Wait, who else is it other than Jong Kook and Ji Hyo?
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and So Min.
- It's 1 of them right? - It's 1 of them.
- Next are me, Kwang Soo, Jae Seok. - And Kwang Soo.
- He's a greedy pig. - Hyun Hee.
- It was a great meal. - Hyun Hee. It's one of us.
We should exclude those with a chance card.
We should exclude them.
Right, those who have a chance card aren't it.
I'll eat again at our next destination.
- Jae Seok, do you have one? - Yes, I do.
Hyun Hee, do you have a chance card?
- I do. - Does Jae Seok have one too?
- Yes. - It's either me or Kwang Soo.
- Right. - It's either me or Kwang Soo.
- It's not me, so it's him. - It must be Kwang Soo.
Isn't it both of you?
What's your hobby, Ji Hyun?
Me? It's fishing.
- Fishing? That's unexpected. - Fishing?
- Do you fish in the sea? - Yes.
- Do you follow your boyfriend? - I know.
- It seems like it. - I'm certain of it.
Have you been together for two years?
How did you know?
(How does she know that?)
- No. - She's so innocent.
- She knew for certain. - No.
- How does So Min know? - How do you know for sure?
- I can tell you that... - She's so innocent.
So Min knows a lot about dating.
When it comes to dating...
She knows a lot about love.
Regarding love, go and see So Min.
I hope that So Min gets a segment.
I got a lot of advice on dating.
- She's different. - Why did you get advice on dating?
- Stopping getting dating advice. - Hey!
(Who's giving who advice?)
- Kwang Soo. - You're with someone.
I'm her VIP client.
You have no experience in dating.
Seok Jin, you got married thanks to whom?
- That's right. - Thanks to you.
That's right.
Eating sausage stew was a mistake on the first date.
Why?
Your date doesn't like you if you eat sausage stew, right?
I had sausage stew once on my first date.
- Really? - That day,
I wanted to break ramyeon noodles, so I did.
- I still remember what he told me. - What?
He said that the ramyeon noodles that I broke looked pretty.
I always break ramyeon noodles ever since then.
I always break them.
She knows a lot about love.
Forget it.
Ji Hyun, is there something that your boyfriend said...
that's unforgettable?
- What made your heart flutter? - Or something that offended you.
An action.
We were watching a movie at a movie theater.
- We looked at each other. - You looked at each other.
He said that my eyes were like stars.
Goodness.
- Goodness. - I heard of it.
What are you talking about?
- "I go double" - I'm not finished talking.
I'll double it.
When we were watching a movie,
my boyfriend looked only at me for two hours.
(He only looked at So Min.)
He turned his head and looked at me because I was pretty.
- Isn't that scary? - It's scary.
- No. - It's scary.
- It's very scary. - He liked me so much.
Do you remember something, Ji Hyo?
You remember something, don't you? Tell us.
I heard what So Min said.
When I was watching movies with my boyfriend,
he kept touching my hand...
and kept looking at me.
I asked him if he's not watching the movie.
He said that he wanted to keep looking at me.
He wanted to keep looking at me.
(She's so affectionate.)
- I slapped him to wake him up. - Did you slap him?
- She slapped him. - Did you slap him?
- Come to your senses. - "Come to your senses"?
- It's because she was embarrassed. - Isn't it like this?
I also said something similar.
She asked me what I wanted to watch.
I said, "Watch anything. I'm going to look at you."
(He goes after what women love.)
That's not all. Sometimes I take photos of something,
and then I start taking pictures of my girlfriend.
When she tells me to stop, I say,
"I usually take pictures of pretty things."
(I usually take pictures of pretty things.)
What's that? Goodness.
- Come on. - That's too much.
- Goodness. - Don't you do it?
- That's annoying. - Don't you do it?
He's a machine that makes people's hearts flutter.
This is how it goes. Say, "Don't take my picture."
Don't take my picture, Haha.
"I usually take pictures of pretty things."
No.
(It's the same line.)
- That's not how you do it. - Haha.
- Haha, that's... - That's strange.
- That's not it. - That's the wrong tone.
That's not how it sounds.
- Say, "Don't take my picture." - That's not it.
Why do you keep taking photos of me? Stop it.
I took a photo of myself.
- It was a selfie. - It was a selfie.
- I like this too. - That was funny.
- What are you taking photos of? - Your earwax.
- Why are you taking a photo of it? - I take photos of intriguing stuff.
(I have to take photos when it's intriguing.)
- It's your earwax. - It's very intriguing.
I can't stay still when I see intriguing things.
Why is my ear intriguing?
- That's funny. - Hey.
(While they finish imitating Jong Kook...)
Where are we?
It's a Chinese restaurant.
(Last dish that awaits the members)
It's crab meat. It's a gourmet dish.
Gosh, it's tangsuyuk.
It's mala sauce.
- I really want to eat it. - It's unbelievable.
It's braised seafood and vegetables.
Braised seafood and vegetables?
- Braised seafood and vegetables. - It's sold a lot these days.
Braised seafood and vegetables.
So Min, Ji Hyo, and Jong Kook haven't eaten yet.
- Right. - One of them is a greedy pig.
It's your last chance to catch the greedy pigs.
- Have a seat, everyone. - Okay.
(Will they find the greedy pigs?)
- Shall we start? - Let's go.
- Let's do it. - Now...
- Start. - let's enjoy yourselves.
- 1. - 3.
- 2. - 3.
- 3. - 4.
- 2, 3. - 5.
- 2. - 6.
(Kwang Soo and Hyun Hee say 6 at the same time.)
(They got caught at 6.)
We went far.
- Kwang Soo. - We got to six.
- It's six. - That was amazing.
- We went far. - Here's a card for six.
- Gosh. - This is good.
- It's great. - Get ready,
set, go, three.
- 1. - 2.
3, 2, 1.
Three.
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin say 3 at the same time.)
Three people.
(Kwang Soo gets caught on Round 2 as well.)
- Gosh. - Why?
Here's the last round.
Get ready, set, go.
- 1. - 1.
(Haha and So Min say 1 at the same time.)
(Why did So Min say 1?)
- Who said one? - Haha.
- So Min. - Why did you say it?
So Min is very suspicious.
- I thought... - She's very suspicious.
That's not it, Ji Hyo.
I always said one whenever we played Race of Wits.
- I always said 1 or 2. - So Min.
It's obvious that I'm the one who says it.
You never said one at all today.
The result is quite extreme. It's 1, 3, and 6.
- That's true. - Who will pick?
I'll pick.
Come back.
(Booing)
(The majority is against it.)
(He comes back.)
(He acted cute, so they let him pick.)
- That's funny. - I'll pick.
How many do you want?
- We want 6. - Pick 6.
- Six? - Doesn't he know?
Pick six.
- Here I go. - Make it clean this time.
It's six.
(He picks without hesitating.)
- Show us first. - Please.
(Will it be a card of 6 that the members wanted?)
(Disappointed)
One person.
- Isn't this... - What's wrong with this?
What's wrong with this?
Was I supposed to pick it?
- This is difficult. - We're in trouble.
Here's the mission to have one member eat.
It's Catching Water While Lying Down.
Five members will lie down in opposite directions.
Pass a tray filled with water to the next person without rising.
The team with the most water after three minutes wins.
The winning team can choose one member to eat.
Let's select the teams carefully.
- Right. - Right?
In the count of three,
show what you have. 1, 2, 3.
- Red. - Blue.
Yes, I'm not on Kwang Soo's team.
- Kwang Soo. - I'm not it.
He's a strong candidate.
- Let's make him do that. - He should play first.
- Right, he should play first. - If it reaches all the way here...
You can't make mistakes here.
- So... - Let's see how well you pass.
It's a lonely fight.
You should be the last, Haha. Do you want to pour it?
Okay.
(Haha is the last player.)
Put your shoulders together.
- Shoulders? - Shoulders.
Get ready, set...
(Get ready.)
It'll be obvious based on how he plays.
- Gosh. - It looks heavy.
(The tray is filled with water.)
It's not easy.
Hold it.
(Pouring)
Hold it. I swear that I'm not it.
- Look at him. - How is he not it?
It's not easy.
- He can't do it. - It's not easy.
- He's getting angry. - Seok Jin.
You shouldn't grab it like that.
(You shouldn't grab it like that.)
(Seok Jin slightly grabs the edge.)
Seok Jin is being suspicious.
Seok Jin is suspicious.
Grab both sides. Why are you holding one side?
Right, you have to grab both sides.
Grab both sides.
That's how it was sent.
Seok Jin is suspicious.
(Spilling)
Hurry up.
- One minute has passed. - It's cold.
Seok Jin is terrible.
How should I grab it?
- Hey, hey! - Come on.
- Hey, let it go. - Seok Jin.
Your grip isn't straight.
- What do you mean? - It isn't straight.
- See? It's not straight. - It's not straight.
You shouldn't grab it like that.
It's cold.
Two minutes have passed.
It's so cold.
We have to go faster now.
Okay, take it now.
(Seok Jin is so terrible.)
- That's right. - Both sides.
- Seok Jin. - Let it go.
You're not straight.
(He explodes.)
- Let it go, Ji Hyo. - You're not straight.
- Seok Jin isn't straight. - Let it go.
Hey, Ji Hyo is being suspicious.
- Right? - Your grip isn't straight.
(Spilling)
Seok Jin didn't grab it straight.
He spilled all of it.
No, Seok Jin isn't suspicious. He just can't do it.
- That's it. - Try it and see if you can do it.
- He can't do it. - Seok Jin is terrible.
Ji Hyo is being suspicious.
- You didn't grab it straight. - You're being strange.
- She can just let it go. - She won't let it go.
- Ji Hyo holds it. - Fine, I'll let it go.
Look at that.
(As you said, I'll let it go.)
Look at this! For goodness' sake!
(For goodness' sake!)
What was that? He went, "For goodness' sake!"
It's game over!
"For goodness' sake"?
(He is childish.)
(Seok Jin lost his temper.)
- There is no water. - You spilled it on purpose.
(3 minutes end!)
Why did you spill it on purpose?
- You have the worst teamwork. - Seok Jin, look.
- You are really suspicious. - Seok Jin, look.
- I... - You should have let it go.
- You would have spilled it all. - I was holding the tray.
I told her to let go,
but she held on to it.
Since you were holding only one side,
- I had to hold the other side. - She pulled it towards her.
- For goodness' sake. - She is it.
Everyone, Ji Hyo is it.
It just means...
- we have terrible teamwork. - Don't be ridiculous.
- I am serious. - Ji Hyo is it.
I am really not it.
(Ji Hyo is suspicious.)
I am really not it. I swear.
I swear.
Your shoulders should stay touching the floor...
even if you lift your head.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Get ready.
There you go.
Hold it. Go slow. It's okay.
- All right. - It isn't easy.
Gosh, it's cold.
(Why did it have to spill over there?)
- What is going on? - It's cold.
- It isn't easy. - Hold it.
- Okay. - We have to do this.
Gosh, it's cold.
(Spilling)
- It's cold. - Keep going.
(So Min practically waters her belly.)
So Min.
Make sure you hold it tight.
- We will win. - There you go.
Give it to me as it is. There you go.
- Is there anything to pour? - Okay.
(It's time to pour water into the bowl.)
(Jae Seok pours it onto the floor.)
- Here you go. - You should know that...
Jae Seok spilled the most amount of water.
(Kwang Soo tells on Jae Seok.)
- Jae Seok spilled everything... - Be quiet.
- on the floor. - Jae Seok!
- Trust me, Hyun Hee. - Jae Seok.
Here you go. Hold it, So Min.
- So Min is bad at this. - Hold it tight.
- I am holding it tight. - Hold it tight. Okay.
- It's cold. - There you go.
Balance the tray.
(Spilling)
So Min spills the most amount of water.
- So Min is... - She is suspicious.
I didn't spill a lot.
- Seok Jin spilled more earlier. - Okay, okay.
(There is another member who is bad at the game.)
(Jae Seok)
Okay, okay.
- This is the last one. - When the tray reaches the end,
- Jae Seok spills everything. - Be quiet.
There are so many spies.
Be quiet.
Jae Seok is acting strange too. Everyone is acting strange.
As for Jae Seok, I am clueless.
I am really not it.
- You have one minute left. - Let's calm down.
I didn't spill a single drop.
Pour it into the bowl as it is.
Look... What?
(Jae Seok spills it onto the floor.)
This makes no sense.
What's the point of transferring water?
- The last member spills everything. - It's hard to aim.
- It's hard to aim. - Jae Seok.
Hyun Hee, it's hard to aim.
Se Chan, this is the last one. Fill it to the brim.
(3 minutes end!)
- I have no idea who will win. - I have no idea.
We'll know once we compare them.
We have more water, right?
We have more water.
- We have more water. We won. - They have more water.
- Yes. - Yes.
(Jae Seok's team will choose who gets to eat!)
- We need to choose carefully. - Choose carefully.
- Choose carefully. - Who should get to eat?
Leave the two of them out.
Seok Jin. You ate, right?
Who should we exclude?
- Exclude Seok Jin. - I am not a greedy pig.
- Kwang Soo ate. - Should we stand over here?
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Jong Kook didn't eat.
Three of them didn't eat.
I am suspicious of Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo was strange. - Ji Hyo...
- Should we pick Ji Hyo? - You should be happy.
I want to eat because I am hungry,
but I hate being suspected.
I strongly recommend So Min.
Good thinking.
- You can choose me. I want to eat. - Am I the only one with a chance?
- So Min was more suspicious. - All right.
- Ji Hyo... - So Min was more suspicious.
- and the two of you should eat. - So Min was more suspicious.
Ji Hyo, Hyun Hee, and me.
- All right. - Okay.
Among the three of you,
the number...
(Among Hyun Hee, Ji Hyo, and Jae Seok,)
of greedy pigs is...
(the number of greedy pigs is...)
one.
(One)
- I knew it. - What does it mean?
Okay.
- What was the number? - Hey.
I am not it.
What was the number? One?
- It's one of them. - I have a chance.
- But Hyun Hee ate earlier. - I ate earlier.
- She ate earlier. - She ate earlier,
but there were other people.
- There were other people. - Hyun Hee, did you eat earlier?
- Who did you eat with earlier? - Me?
- Me. - Jae Seok,
- Kwang Soo, and... - Me.
Me.
- Four people ate earlier. - Yes.
- The number was 1, right? - 1.
- The number is 1 now. - It's 1.
So I am not it.
- It's one of them. - That doesn't prove your innocence.
- That doesn't prove your innocence. - Earlier, it was Kwang Soo.
- Now, it's Ji Hyo. - That's right.
No, no.
- I am not it. - Seok Jin is right.
Seok Jin is right.
Which one of you is it?
- No. - Which one of you is it?
Since I am not it, one of them is it.
- I am not it. - I am really not it.
- I am really not it. - You are it.
(Are Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo the greedy pigs?)
Gosh, hold on. This is braised seafood and vegetables.
I can't believe I am eating braised seafood and vegetables.
It smells so good.
- My goodness. - Eat that as well.
It looks delicious.
As you eat, we will distribute the ballot.
- It's so tasty. - Will we have the vote now?
- Do we pick two people? - Yes.
If two greedy pigs get the majority vote,
they will get the penalty.
If two greedy pigs don't get caught,
they will choose two members who will get the penalty.
Both greedy pigs need to be caught.
I am done.
What should I do?
(I picked you, Kwang Soo.)
My goodness.
- I am really not it. - I am done.
I am done.
Let me see.
He showed me that. I can't believe...
he wrote down my name and showed it to me.
- I am not it! Come to your senses! - All right.
He has been that way since the opening!
- All right. - I am not it. Don't be absurd.
Ji Hyo, are you it or not?
- What? - I swear I am not it.
Seriously.
You should tell me more.
There is no way I can prove myself.
She isn't even writing down any names.
I don't even have a pen, Hyun Hee.
Let me give you other possibilities.
If Ji Hyo isn't it, So Min is it.
If Kwang Soo isn't it,
- Jae Seok or Hyun Hee is it. - Jae Seok.
- No, no. - I am not it.
- There is a possibility. - Jae Seok isn't it.
Since I am not it, Kwang Soo is it.
- I have no idea. - Seok Jin.
- Are you not it? - No.
Then it's Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo.
Why do you think that?
- Kwang Soo. - It's him.
It's him. It's him.
Whose names did you write down? Tell us.
- Who did you pick? - Who did you pick?
Why didn't you write down any names?
- You didn't write down any names. - Kwang Soo.
I was under suspicion all day long!
Why didn't you write down any names?
I tried to prove my innocence all day long!
You are being suspicious.
- You left it blank since it's you. - Write down the names now.
- Who will you pick? - Who will you pick?
- I am the most curious. - I am the most curious.
Why would I show you when this is the secret ballot?
- Show us. - Let's have a good laugh.
- Write down the names. - Whom will you pick?
- You are good at deducting. - I am really not it.
You should be the first to write,
"Me".
(That's quite original.)
Why would I do that?
Why would I do that when I am not it?
- Seriously. - Listen.
You should help us by deducing with us.
Who do you think are the greedy pigs?
- Jae Seok? - Jae Seok?
- Is he writing down my name? - Who is the other one?
Ji Hyo is suspicious, right?
It's delicious.
Ji Hyo and Jae Seok can't be the greedy pigs at the same time.
- Am I wrong? - You are right.
- You are right. - If Jae Seok is it, Ji Hyo isn't.
- Then who is it? - Then it's Ji Hyo.
(He changes his mind right away.)
- You are so easily swayed. - It's not like that.
All day long, I gave reasons for why I am not it.
- You are halfway there. - You are 50 percent complete.
Go for the 100 percent.
Come to think of it, you and I ate earlier.
- Do you think it's me? - Since I am not it, you are it.
Okay! I got you, you rascal.
(Okay! I got you, you rascal.)
(He refuses to write down his name.)
- I am really not it. - "Okay! I got you, you rascal."
I am really not it.
- It can't be Seok Jin. - Seriously.
Then it's me.
Then it's either me or So Min. It's either one of us.
But it can't be Ji Hyo then.
It doesn't make sense then because the number was one earlier.
So who are the greedy pigs?
You need to decide.
You will get the answer only if you write down your name.
(This is the conclusion.)
How did this happen?
Where did the puzzle go wrong?
- You need to write down your name. - How is that the conclusion?
Why would I get the answer only if I write down my name?
You can't deduce further because you left your name out.
Seok Jin is it if I am not it, right?
That's the answer for you.
- This is hilarious. - Okay.
All right. That was hard.
For fairness, we will call out the names.
Seok Jin chose Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
- Most people did the same. - Jong Kook chose...
- Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo. - Most people did the same.
Jae Seok chose Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
So Min chose Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
It's never like that.
- It's the majority vote. - Haha chose Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
Se Chan chose Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
Hyun Hee chose Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyun chose So Min and Hyun Hee.
(It's unexpected.)
(Us?)
Ji Hyo chose So Min and Hyun Hee.
Kwang Soo chose Ji Hyo and Seok Jin.
Thus, Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo received the most number of votes.
(Are Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo the greedy pigs?)
Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo...
(Either they receive the penalty...)
(or the real greedy pigs choose two members to receive the penalty.)
They aren't greedy pigs.
- No? - They aren't greedy pigs.
(They aren't greedy pigs!)
Since you failed to catch both greedy pigs,
the greedy pigs win.
- Who are the greedy pigs? - Who are they?
- It must be So Min. - Seriously.
If you are a greedy pig,
please stand up on the count of 3. 1,
(Who are the two greedy pigs?)
Two.
(The greedy pigs are...)
Three.
(So Min and Hyun Hee.)
Are they the greedy pigs?
(Shocked)
(The night before the race, SBS Building in Mok-dong)
Tomorrow,
you will be in the race called Let's Eat with Greedy Pigs.
Greedy pigs?
The two of you are the greedy pigs.
Really?
Let me know.
(Hyun Hee avoided suspicion by obtaining the chance.)
(By making frequent mistakes, So Min avoided eating.)
(Greedy pigs avoided suspicion with completely different tactics.)
I was right.
Why didn't you believe me? Why did you keep cornering me?
Ji Hyo, you should have told us.
- I did, - Why didn't you tell us?
but you kept cornering me.
Why didn't you say that you weren't it?
You kept cornering me.
How can I say anything?
- Why didn't you insist on it? - I did insist.
- When? - Since a long time ago.
- You're joking. - Goodness.
Tell us who will be...
- penalized. - We'll tell you.
- I trust you, So Min. - Tell us one person.
We need someone tall...
- because... - That's right.
(She doesn't even hesitate.)
(He's tall.)
- Me? - It could be a dump truck.
I'm not meticulous.
He was suspected all day long.
- He was suspected all day long. - He was suspected.
He cleaned the ceiling.
- That's why... - Don't you need someone strong?
(Don't you need someone strong?)
(He's someone strong.)
It would be terrible if they stayed apart.
We want them to have a good time.
- Hold each other's hands. - Talk about things.
We pick the one who's tall and the one who's strong.
- Okay. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(We thank Hong Hyun Hee and Park Ji Hyun for being with us.)
(Located in Gangnam, Seoul)
You're penalized quite often.
It's so funny that you and I came here together.
I should have been careful from the start.
Okay, now I understand.
- Let's make up today. - Yes.
Seriously.
- Why... - When it's not, it's not.
do you keep acting that way?
Why do you live that way?
(Why do you live that way?)
What? Me?
Why do you act so suspicious?
- You know, don't you? - If I remember clearly,
I was standing still during the opening.
When I looked at you...
(He was very suspicious.)
Even at the end of the show,
when I looked at you...
People are relative.
You make me suspect you.
Did you suspect anyone other than me today?
No.
I didn't.
Get rid of any hard feelings...
- while washing the car. - That way?
All right, let's get washing.
- All your sins are disappearing. - Jong Kook.
- The water is strong. - Yes.
(They start rinsing.)
(He's looking at him carefully.)
- It's getting really clean. - Gosh.
It's amazing.
(The water must have got him.)
(Is it starting?)
(The water starts to rise.)
(Shall we start the game?)
(The car is only there as a decoration.)
(Impressed)
It's so clean.
I see why...
I see why people prefer to hand wash cars.
(They're cleaning pent-up hard feelings.)
Hey.
(Stop it.)
(Such an ending was expected.)
I see why people hand wash their cars.
- This is unbelievable. - Yes.
It feels like my body got cleaned too.
That's why people like hand car washes.
Don't ever act suspicious.
- Okay, I understand. - Promise.
(They promise a new start.)
(They start to suspect each other right away.)
(You have to suspect him first.)
(What started the suspicion?)
(It started at a peaceful animal farm.)
(Kang Han Na and Lee Gook Ju)
(Sihyeon)
(Even Hyun A could be a candidate.)
I want to measure it.
(While six pairs of animals are having a dance party)
(There's a forbidden animal that wasn't invited.)
There are two forbidden animals.
(It's a war in the wilderness.)
(Make deductions.)
(Suspect and...)
(interrogate)
(Can you trust the evidence you just saw?)
(Forbidden animals)
It's also dangerous for Jae Seok.
(Mysterious Animal Farm)