(The choreography for the group dance was revealed last week.)
(Everyone was shocked at the difficult choreography.)
(If we can do it, it'll be a miracle.)
(However, there's no giving up for these members.)
(They'll do it until they can. Their fierce training began.)
(It's Lia Kim's rescue project for these bad dancers.)
(The bad dancers will surprise you. You'll witness the "miracle" soon.)
(And to practice dancing, they've been delaying...)
(Let's Make Merchandise Race.)
(They'll manufacture Running Shirts with the winner's design.)
(Find hidden gold bars from your opponent's land.)
(It's Gold Hopscotch Race.)
(Name 5 great figures whose names have 4 syllables.)
(Last week, as they faced water bombs as their penalties,)
(everyone looked terrible.)
(And Team Jae Seok and Ji Hyo are leading the race.)
(The design of the group shirts depends on this Merchandise Race.)
(What is the next mission?)
- What is this game now? - What is it?
Is it long jump or something?
It's a pair match again.
Let's just try not to be placed last this time.
(What's the mission this time?)
You will be able to acquire gold bars with this mission.
It's called Fly Super Balloons.
You will blow the balloons yourselves...
and fly them without trying them. And the team that has the balloon...
that travels the farthest will win.
The winning team will get to open two pieces of the opponent's land.
- But it's windy. - It's windy.
It's windy. Will this work?
However, before we start the game, we'll do a simple preliminary game.
The winning team can fly the balloon after taking a step forward.
- We have to win that. - We'll let you do that.
Kwang Soo has long legs. If he takes a step forward...
- You have long legs. - We must win this. I'm serious.
The mission for this benefit is called Speech Balloon 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- "Speech balloon"? - What?
Each team will take a turn to do this mission.
I will ask you questions. And the pair will take turns...
to answer the questions in 5, 4, 3, 2, and 1 syllables...
in the order given.
- That's hard. - The winning pair will move a step.
For the 2nd ranked pair, 1 of the 2 will get the benefit.
That's how we'll grant the benefits.
You should go first.
Okay. So Min, your answer must have 5 syllables. And 4, 3, 2, 1.
- Does mine have 5 syllables? - 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- Yes. - Which one has five syllables?
- You first. - Okay.
- Here we go. - 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Get ready. Start.
What's your weakness?
I am ugly.
What's your nickname?
It's a giraffe.
What's the nickname you want to give to Kwang Soo?
Poophole.
I'm sorry.
(She names him Poophole as if it's the most natural thing to do.)
- I couldn't think of anything else. - Poophole?
I'm sorry.
- You look like Poophole. - You do look like it.
- No. I mean... - You're Poophole.
- I didn't mean it. The syllables... - He does look like it.
- Poophole was great. - She didn't say Anus.
- She said Poophole. - You two are out.
- Why... - You're out.
Why can't you speak?
Hey, we should try it. This is...
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo will go next.)
Don't think long about this kind of game. Just blurt it out.
- Watch. - "What?"
- Watch and learn. - Let's see...
- Answer it right away. - how good he's at this game.
I'll show you this is how one thinks on his feet.
- He'll give ridiculous answers. - Get ready.
Start.
What did you tell your son last night?
Go to sleep, Ji Ho.
What was your childhood nickname?
Dumb Idiot.
- That's possible. - Things to take to a desert island?
Tteokbokki.
- Why would you take that? - How could you bring that there?
(Acting brazen)
(Why would you bring tteokbokki to a desert island?)
- I... - Lighter.
- I'm going to bring it. - Bring a lighter.
- He's going to eat that there. - It has to make sense at least.
- You could've said a cellphone. - It makes no sense.
- You won't accept that again? - Why would you bring that there?
- You said no... - You could've said a cellphone.
to Im Su Yeon's fried rice.
They should do it over.
- Do-over. Start from the beginning. - It makes no sense.
Seriously. You guys are unbelievable.
- You'll start with five syllables. - Okay.
Get ready. Start.
What would you say if Se Chan asks you out?
- Should I think about it? - Really?
- Really? - You should say, "I'd be crazy."
What would you say if Ji Hyo wants to date you?
Have you gone mad?
That makes sense.
What's Jae Seok's nickname?
- Grasshopper. - There you go.
- That one was easy. - What do you do when you're happy?
(Screaming)
(Scream when you're happy.)
- That's not acceptable. - It was about your action.
- It was about your action. - Hey.
- Listen. - Say hurrah or something.
- Hold on. - Or say hooray.
- That's not acceptable. - Say hurrah.
- Why isn't that acceptable? - Hurrah.
- Or smile. - That won't work.
- It wasn't "Oh, yes". - Or jump.
- Jump. That's right. - Darn it. You're too harsh.
- That was onomatopoeia word. - Exactly.
- I don't get why it's wrong. - Get ready.
Haha will start with five syllables.
Start.
What if you don't have toilet paper in the bathroom?
I'm in trouble, man.
- What? - What did you say?
("I'm in trouble, man"?)
"I'm in trouble, man."
- That's a dialect. - "I'm in trouble, man."
- Why the dialect all of a sudden? - "I'm in trouble, man."
- That can't count. - Hey.
- That's a dialect. - You'll create regional friction.
- "I'm in trouble, man." - That can't be accepted.
"I'm in trouble, man."
(You won't allow the Hamgyong Province accent?)
- "I'm in trouble, man." - This isn't acceptable?
- No, it's not. - This is unfair. Get me a new one.
- That can't count. - That came out of the blue.
- That's not acceptable. - "I'm in trouble, dog."
This can't count either.
(This is already getting exhausting.)
- Do it over then. - No, no. You...
- Let's use standard Korean. - "I'm in trouble, son."
That came out of nowhere.
- I'll start now. - Here we go.
- Are you ready? - I'm ready, man.
Get ready.
Start. Do you have a girlfriend?
I have one now.
(He answers without hiding anything.)
Do you know who it is?
I totally know.
(I totally know.)
What will you take to a desert island?
Girl... Darn it.
(Girl... Darn it.)
(He falls into the girlfriend trap.)
- Tell her that you love her! - Move.
(What are you saying?)
- Se Chan has a girlfriend? - He has a girlfriend?
- I had no idea that he had one. - He got a girlfriend.
- Stop it. - Congratulations.
Don't get caught!
(You're listening, right?)
Hey, Se Chan is imagining it.
Congratulations on your imaginary relationship.
Imaginary relationship?
- When did it start? - That came out of nowhere.
- I got so flustered. - Who's next?
- Should we go? - Okay.
We did well earlier too.
The chemistry between them is great.
- Their chemistry is great. - I'm so curious.
Jong Kook has met his perfect partner now.
- They're also the Monday Couple. - They make a good couple.
They're Stressful Couple.
- Jong Kook, you'll start. Yes. - Five syllables?
Get ready. Start.
What's your number one treasure?
Stuffed...
toy car.
- Stuffed toy car? - That's my treasure.
(What? Jong Kook likes stuffed toy cars?)
- That's so scary. - Stuffed toy cars.
- You like stuffed toy cars? - Yes.
- That's my number one treasure. - That doesn't suit you.
- Do you hug it in your sleep too? - Of course.
- I love stuffed toy cars. - You like stuffed toy cars.
- Of course. - That's adorable.
- It doesn't have to be true, right? - He has a point.
- We'll start again. - I'll go with that.
- I'll go first. - Get ready.
Start.
Whom do you love the most?
It's Yu Su Jeong.
(His romantic line sounds calculated.)
Whom do you hate the most?
- Jee Seok Jin... - Jee Seok Jin.
(Everyone heard Seok Jin's name clearly.)
That makes sense.
Jee Seok Jin.
- Jee Seok Jin. - That works.
- Jee Seok Jin. - Let's go with that.
- It works. - Right.
- Hey, Jee Seok Jin. - It works.
- You'll be casual now, right? - This works.
- They dropped honorifics now. - That's upsetting.
- Jee Seok Jin. - It's upsetting.
We'll start from four syllables again.
- Yes, have a do-over. - Okay, let's do it again.
Get ready. Start.
What would you say to your ex-girlfriend?
Sorry for everything.
(He longingly whispers, "Sorry for everything".)
- That's sad. - Hold on.
What do you say when you confess your love?
I love you so...
You could've said, "I love you".
(Stuttering)
(He could've gone with "I love you".)
I needed three syllables.
- My gosh. - He's so frustrating.
- Come on! - Get out.
- Sorry, but get out of the seat. - Get out.
- Get out. - Get out, man.
- Seok Jin, go over there. - Get out.
- I didn't know it was three. - Go over there.
- We'll start with five syllables. - Let's try this again.
Get ready. Start.
Where would you like to go with So Min?
My...
- "My"? - "My"?
(That's the place he wants to go with So Min?)
- Is that "my house"? - It's a game.
- "My house"? - You're out.
- I can't come up with an answer. - Why can't you?
- What could I have said? - Take it easy.
- Paju Heyri. - Yes, "my apartment".
"My mom's house". There are many possible answers.
- All right. Next team. - Ji Hyo will go first.
Watch me.
There's a winning method for this game.
"There's a winning method."
Since I'm very good at improvising,
- you must play along. - Jae Seok.
- Who has to play along? - Your improvised lines are short.
Do you mean "tteokbokki"?
Mr. Tteokbokki.
- Mr. Tteokbokki. Play along what? - Listen.
- You're too uptight. - Here we go.
Get ready. Start.
What's the lie you tell the most?
What did you do yesterday?
- What was that? - What? Why did you ask a question?
(The lie he tells the most is "What did you do yesterday?")
(Why did you ask a question?)
- His improvised lines are terrible. - He's terrible at this game.
- What's up with your answers? - What's wrong with you?
- His answer was weird. - Hold on.
- Hear me out. - Are you nervous, Jae Seok?
- What's wrong with your answer? - It's not that.
- Are you nervous? - You lie about that question?
- I must have a do-over. - No.
Ji Hyo didn't get to answer one.
What are you talking about? You should start with her first.
- That was the worst answer! - Listen.
- I didn't prepare my answer. Sorry. - Exactly.
- I didn't prepare five syllables. - It's because you're nervous.
- Ji Hyo will go first. - Okay, okay.
By the way, Jae Seok is awful at this.
Hail to the king of improvisation.
- Anyway, he's bad at this. - Look at the king of improvisation.
I'm telling you.
- We're to play along to that? - Watch me.
Get ready. Start.
What will you do when you get 10 million dollars?
I'll buy a house and land.
- Okay. - What did you say...
when you proposed?
What should we do?
Come on. What was that?
(He asked, "What should we do?" when he proposed to his wife?)
- Hold on. It makes no sense. - Wait.
- That was pathetic. - Listen. Hold on.
- That was so pathetic. - "What should we do?"
How does that make sense?
- Hold on. - This makes no sense.
- What doesn't this make sense? - What was that?
No one can understand where I'm coming from?
- "What should we do?" - You can't understand it?
- "What should we do?" - It's a riddle.
It's hard to say this in four syllables.
Hey, Jae Seok.
You said you were the king. You told us to watch and learn.
Seriously.
All right. Let's do this, Jong Kook.
Let's do this. When they're not doing well,
we should win this.
I can't believe we're doing this again.
- We'll keep getting our turns. - I already gave up on it.
Hey, do your best.
Everyone, do better than this.
- Get ready. Five syllables first. - Let's go.
- Me? - Get ready.
Start.
Where do you want to go for your vacation?
It's LA.
How do you feel when you watch our show?
I'm very good.
What will you do if you get 10 million dollars?
I'll buy a car.
What do you think when you look at a mirror?
I'm handsome.
(For the first time, it's time to answer with one syllable.)
(If Jong Kook can answer with one syllable,)
(Seok Jin and Jong Kook will get the benefit.)
What did you do yesterday?
Sleep.
("What did you do yesterday?" "Sleep")
(With a neat answer, they will be ranked 1st.)
Great!
What about my high-five?
(Jong Kook skips the high-five.)
(Their playful chemistry is getting funnier.)
I'm not that happy,
but I have to act I'm happy.
Why aren't you happy?
- All right. Next time. - It's our turn.
Get ready. Start.
What's your best dish at your barbecue restaurant?
Pork belly and entrails.
What's your pet name for your girlfriend?
Can you not ask about my girlfriend?
Seriously.
(It's breaking his heart.)
- That question flusters me. - Listen.
He doesn't have a girlfriend.
Why do you make up an imaginary girlfriend?
- He's teasing me. - Listen.
How can he have a pet name when he doesn't have a girlfriend?
How can he have a pet name?
Say something like Alien.
What? Alien? Why would that be Alien?
- Why would I do that? - Just do it.
- Just go with me. - This is upsetting.
- Alien. - Whenever he asks about that...
- My gosh, this is so frustrating. - You can say "green frog".
- Who will go 1st? Here it goes. - I'll go 1st.
Get ready.
Start.
Who's your ideal type?
Handsome guys.
What's your pet name for your girlfriend?
(Hesitating)
- Answer it. - Come on.
- Answer it! - Just answer it!
(As he can't bring himself to answer it, he only mouths it.)
- Why didn't you answer that? - Is she his imaginary girlfriend?
- Why didn't you answer it? - Hey. Are you...
- bragging in front of Se Chan? - Exactly.
(Are you bragging in front of a guy with an imaginary girlfriend?)
- What was that? - You know?
- He's teasing me too. - Exactly.
He's trying so hard to come up with one...
- when he has no one. - This is driving me crazy.
Cutie Pie.
- That's a pet name. - There are other names.
What was that?
It must have four syllables.
You could've said, Giraffe's Girlfriend.
- Get out. - It's our turn.
(I'll show you.)
- Here's the king of improvisation. - Don't you worry.
- The king of improvisation. - Get ready to play along.
Listen.
If you don't accept my answer, I'll angry.
(What kind of improvised lines will the king say?)
- Jae Seok. - Get ready.
Start. What was your childhood dream job?
- It was a comedian. - Right.
- "It was a comedian." - Okay.
- He had a hard time. - That was slow.
What was your childhood nickname?
Dumb Idiot.
What lullaby do you want to sing for your son?
"I Love You".
(He's barely surviving with vague answers.)
What's your boyfriend's nickname?
Honey.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo, they have a chance to complete the game.)
(The king of improvisation must answer it with one syllable.)
(Will this team be able to succeed?)
What was your childhood dream job?
Poop!
That was true.
(Korea's favorite MC's dream job was being poop.)
- That was true. - No, no.
- Why not? - We can't count this.
- This one is true. - Come on. You can't grow up...
- to become poop. It makes no sense. - Listen.
- Come on. - We can't count this one.
- Why not? - This can't count.
- We can't accept this answer. - That was my childhood dream job!
- You could've said, "You". - We can't count that.
- "You". Right. - "Him". "Her".
I can deal with other members telling me that my answer was bad,
- but you can't do that. - Why not?
- Why not? - I don't deserve it from you.
(Lack of Quick Thinking versus Lack of Imagination)
Here we go.
- Is it me first? - This is confusing.
Ready, set, go.
You farted in the bus, right?
Yes, a bit.
When did you date for the last time?
Two days ago.
He tries so hard to lie.
What would you like to tell your wife?
I love you.
What's your girlfriend's nickname?
Earlobe.
This is right!
(Se Chan's fake girlfriend's nickname is Earlobe.)
- What's wrong with it? - This isn't right.
- Don't do this. - It doesn't make sense.
He's trying so hard.
Are her earlobes long?
- It should... - Are they?
- It should make some sense. - Her earlobes...
Her earlobes are this long.
- Earlobes. - It's a nickname.
- "Dear Earlobe". - We should acknowledge this.
- Why is it wrong? - Fine.
- What's wrong with it? - "Dear Earlobe".
We have one more.
- We're using our imaginations. - We'll go again.
We'll start with the two-syllable answer again.
(He successfully gets another chance.)
(If they win 2 more times, they'll come 2nd place.)
Who's your favorite historical figure?
Historical figure?
- Hey. - A historical figure?
(He was thinking about his girlfriend.)
(Surprised)
(It wasn't the genre he expected.)
Come on. Goodness.
(He fails to give an answer.)
- A historical figure. - Why me?
Why me?
(This was a difficult question for him.)
- It's all right. Good job. - Goodness.
You know how I am when I get flustered, right?
You know, right? Right?
Why are they so bad?
How long will we do this for?
- The sun is setting. - Let's get this over with!
- That was an easy question. - I was flustered.
- You could've said, "Haha". - Or "mother".
- Or "My something". - Right.
Are you good at this game?
(You're so talkative.)
- Sir, are you that good? - Listen.
- He's the king of improvision. - I improvise things.
- He's the king. - Is that so?
- I'm that awesome. - I see.
- Let's start. - No one approves, though.
- Ready, set, go. - Kwang Soo goes first.
Why did you go to Japan?
It was a trip.
- Don't you dare lie. - I was going to say that.
- What was that answer? - "I was In Sung's butler."
(He was In Sung's butler.)
(As In Sung's butler, Kwang Soo went to Japan.)
What do you mean? We went on a trip!
- It was a trip. - "To make money".
- What do you mean? - You're so frustrating.
We'll do the five-syllable answer again.
Ready,
set, go.
How did you feel after returning from Japan?
I felt great.
What's your favorite dish?
- Omurice. - What's...
- That's wrong. - Those were five syllables.
You should've said, "kimchi stew".
- "Omurice"? - Come on.
- Why can't you count? - "Omrice".
- "Omrice". - Get out.
- That's wrong. - It's English.
(This won't end anytime soon.)
- Ready, - He's good.
set, go.
What do you think of when you see your wife every day?
"You're so pretty."
- "You're so pretty." - "You're so pretty."
Which historical figure do you admire the most?
Sejong the Great.
(He gets the question right.)
Whom do you dislike the most?
That scumbag.
(He hates...)
(the interviewer.)
(Director Cheol Min)
No, wait.
That wasn't what I meant.
- What was that? - I'm sorry.
- Haha. - He meant it.
- How could you? - I'm sorry.
- That was so harsh. - I didn't mean it.
- You could've said a name. - I was...
trying to make it witty.
I should've just said, "Jung Cheol Min".
- We'll do it again. - Do it again.
- We'll do three syllables again. - Okay.
- Yes. - Don't get hurt.
Ready, set, go.
What do you look like the most?
Kim Go Eun.
(That's his wife's name.)
(Right, you do look alike.)
What's your nickname?
Pauper.
(He criticizes himself in order to win.)
(Will Haha succeed?)
What was your dream as a kid?
The best.
You did it!
(Haha and Se Chan succeed.)
- That was brilliant. - It worked.
How could you be so shameless when saying, "pauper"?
It's in my imagination.
- We did it. - I'm a pauper.
The last question was hard.
- "The best". - Okay.
The winning team can take one step closer...
when flying the balloons. The second team will...
That's what we're doing?
(We're still on that?)
- We're still doing that? - We are?
We're not taking each other's lands?
- We're not taking their land. - What is this?
This was the longest game we had today!
It was a preliminary game.
- It was the most exhausting. - Goodness.
- They still got an advantage. - Right.
The team with...
- the farthest balloon will win. - It's so windy.
- Do we only get one chance? - We should use the wind.
That's right.
(They need to use the wind.)
- Haha. - Me? Okay.
(Haha will go first.)
(He blows it as big as possible.)
You're good.
- You can take a step forward. - Okay.
Okay.
You should blow on it more.
It's windy.
- It is. - It's quite windy.
The wind might change the balloon's direction.
(He pretends to test the wind.)
You should do it now. The wind is blowing forward.
(Flying)
- Hey, hey! - Nice!
(Haha lets go of the balloon.)
- Nice! - It went far.
Haha.
(It's over 7m.)
(He's content.)
It bounced off my head.
(The balloon fell on So Min's head and bounced off.)
- Haha. - That went far.
(It's all thanks to So Min.)
- Good! - 7m and 40cm.
Okay! That's great.
Go, So Min.
Taking one step forward is a huge advantage.
I wish I could do that.
- It's so windy. - I think mine will go right.
- Should I let go right now? - Yes.
(She lets go while the wind is blowing forward.)
(Flying)
(After flying around aimlessly,)
(it lands on the 1m mark.)
It was so weak.
(Discouraged)
(The wind stopped blowing the moment she let go.)
- It was so weak. - Why was your balloon so weak?
- I thought it was a blowfish. - Your team did well.
- 40cm. - 42cm.
- Goodness. - Why did it go sideways? Why?
I think it'll explode.
We're not sure if blowing on it will help it fly farther.
- Step forward. - It might actually backfire.
That's good. You should lower it.
- Lower it? - Yes.
Taking a step forward is a big advantage.
Good.
(What?)
(Why is the balloon rising?)
Good.
- Good. - It hit something!
(The balloon flies up high.)
Good. That's good. Okay.
- Oh, no. - Are we still winning?
Haha, tell me.
Mine went slightly farther.
It's neck and neck.
- It's a tight match. - We should leave it there.
(Did Seok Jin beat Haha?)
- Haha's was 35cm? - No.
(Seok Jin's balloon is 5cm short.)
(Haha, with 7m and 40cm, is still in 1st place.)
- There's no wind right now. - Do it now.
(It starts off great,)
It's going so far.
(but plummets.)
(Ji Hyo's balloon went 5m and 30cm.)
5m and 30cm.
- That was far. - It was.
Do it now!
I can take one step forward, right?
(Se Chan has a chance to step forward.)
- Good luck, Earlobe! - Go, Earlobe!
(He fails to focus.)
- Come on. - Her earlobes are this long, right?
- Right. - Yes.
- It'll be... - She has Buddha's earlobes.
It'll be obvious no matter where she goes.
Let go when the wind blows.
Right now.
It's so weak.
(It flies without much strength.)
- What is that? - Goodness.
What was that?
- Let go when the wind blows. - I knew it.
(What?)
(It's flying quite fast.)
(It shoots forward.)
- It's going backwards. - It's going backwards.
It's so weak.
(Disappointed)
- The yellow ones have issues. - There's something wrong.
Our balloons are odd.
- The yellow ones are weird. - Why are they so weak?
Jae Seok's balloon is huge.
- It is. - Pop it.
Pop it, please.
Bite it with your front teeth and pop it.
Done.
The direction is what matters.
(All he needs is good wind.)
(What?)
- What? - What is that?
(What has happened?)
(To everyone's disbelief,)
(the balloon passes 10m...)
(and 15m.)
(It flies past 15m.)
(He's the master of flying balloons.)
- What was that? - Jae Seok!
How is that possible?
- You're amazing. - This is impossible.
- The wind helped. - This is absurd.
The wind blew midway.
Since he's teamed up with Ji Hyo, he's become lucky now.
I've become lucky.
- The wind blew midway. - He's lucky.
I'm pretty sure they're the winners.
Jong Kook isn't good at these games.
(Jong Kook has yet to compete.)
(Jae Seok's record is by far the highest.)
(His balloon is 16m away.)
(However, Jong Kook is competent.)
(He clenches his teeth.)
Oh, yes!
What?
(What is this?)
Yes!
(He comes 2nd to last.)
Goodness.
(We see a weak side of him.)
- He's not the type to do this. - I know.
Jong Kook looks so stressed.
- This is... - Even he failed.
Yours was weak.
- Good job, Jae Seok. - We did it.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo acquire 2 Purchase Cards)
Now, we'll start the territory game.
(Will Jae Seok and Ji Hyo acquire the gold bars?)
We'll start now.
Okay.
Should we choose 30 dollars or 20 dollars?
- It's the same. - It doesn't matter.
- Just open both. - You can just open both.
You're going to open one of Kwang Soo's anyway.
- Right. - Right.
(The target has already been decided.)
Can they open all of them?
(Kwang Soo and So Min...)
(placed 6 of their gold bars in 1 territory.)
(Jae Seok opened Kwang Soo's 1st...)
(and 2nd territories.)
(They're left with only 3 territories.)
Do you think they placed them in 20 dollars?
Gold bars? Dud?
Since they're both ours, let's open 20 dollars.
- You could open both. - It could be in 30 dollars.
- Okay, 20 dollars. - 20 dollars.
- 20 dollars? - Yes.
- There's no dud. - 20 dollars, please.
I'll give you one last chance.
- 20 dollars. - 20 dollars. Number 4.
(Just open it.)
They must've put all of them in one place.
- I'll reveal it now. - 1, 2, 3.
(If they get the 6 gold bars, they'll be winning with 8 of them.)
I'm certain there are gold bars in there.
(Will number 4 contain the bonanza?)
(They hit the jackpot.)
Jae Seok!
They're way ahead of the rest of us.
(We made the wrong choice.)
They put them all in there.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo get six more gold bars.)
If we were them, we would've spent 50 dollars right away.
They saved 30 dollars and got the gold bars.
Jae Seok!
You have one more chance.
- Right, we do. - Yes.
Okay, okay.
- We have another chance. - Please choose us.
- Just once. - Please?
- Why? - If we get a dud,
- They'll get a gold bar. - we have to give them one.
Then let's pick theirs.
- Thank you. - We might get a dud.
- I forgot where it was. - I forgot too.
- I don't remember anything. - It was done randomly,
so we have no idea.
Which one should I pick?
(Their territories have not been opened yet.)
I pick number 1 for 10 dollars.
- Number 1. - Number 1?
- Pick that one. - Number one.
- 1, 2... - Ji Hyo wants number 1.
(They have a chance to gain more gold bars.)
I'm curious.
(What's beneath the 1st territory?)
(They find 2 more gold bars.)
- Did we put gold bars here? - It was there?
What's wrong with them?
They get 100 dollars.
What's gotten into them?
- I can't believe this. - This is boring now.
- They're winning by far. - I know.
This mission is called Our Balloon Link.
This is hard.
(They win again.)
Here!
Okay!
Gosh!
Their record is 1 minute and 35 seconds.
(They may be boring, but they're strong.)
- They came first place. - Again?
- They did. - Again?
- Let's choose this one. - We don't need that one.
- Also... - Please.
(When picking out the territory,)
(they hit the jackpot once again.)
Darn it!
Jae Seok and Ji Hyo win.
(Stupefied)
Haha and Se Chan came last.
- Our faces will be on the back. - It's actually better.
- Is it? - I preferred that anyway.
- All right. - It's all thanks to Ji Hyo.
Let's see their designs.
- I don't like them. - Ji Hyo's is okay.
- Let's go with hers. - I like Ji Hyo's.
- I like her idea. - It's amazing.
The winning team is Jae Seok and Ji Hyo.
One of them will be chosen to design the Running T-Shirt...
for the fan-meet through a mission called...
100 or General.
- What is that? - What is that?
(100 or General)
(They thought it was over.)
- What does 100 mean? - What is that?
- What is that? - It's a number.
This game just won't end.
You'll flip a coin. 100 is on 1 side...
- My gosh. - 100 is on 1 side...
- and the general is on the other. - Gosh.
You made the mission sound so intense.
This is such a simple game.
- Come on. - 100 or General.
- Everything was in vain. - It really...
- was. - It was all in vain.
- I'm glad we lost. - Me too.
This is like rock-paper-scissors.
What difference is this to rock-paper-scissors?
What should we do?
Pick which side of the coin you want.
- Do you want the general? - Se Chan asked if...
it was 100 or genie.
(Se Chan asked if it's either 100 or genie.)
(When the mission was introduced,)
(he didn't recognize the word "general".)
"Genie"?
- Earlobe, what's wrong with you? - Earlobe.
- I should wake up. - It's a cute nickname.
Who picked 100?
Which one do you want?
Who's going to pick the number, and who's going to pick 100.
That's the same side.
(Make a decision.)
He said the same thing.
- What is this? General? - It's number and general.
- Hero. - General Yi Sun Sin.
General Yi Sun Sin.
It's not "hero". It's "general".
- Got it? - Okay.
- They're different. - You deserve that.
- My gosh. - It's either General Yi Sun Sin...
- Right, or 100. - or 100.
I'll choose 100.
Okay, then I'll choose the general.
- If Jae Seok wins... - Hey.
- Let it be 100. - Let the coin drop.
Please let it be 100.
- 100 is the best for us too. - If it turns out to be 100,
- I'll be amazed at her luck. - Let it be the number!
Let it be the number. It's much better.
(3,000 t-shirts' design depends on this coin.)
- Number - Number
1, 2, 3.
(The coin has been tossed.)
(If 100 comes out,)
(a design stating that anyone could become a Running Man member...)
(will be chosen.)
(If the general comes out,)
("The Avengers And Gung Ye" will be chosen.)
(Which design will get picked?)
(The day after the shooting, Sangam SBS)
Hello.
(Kwang Soo arrives at the dressing room first.)
Good morning.
(He looks anxious.)
What is it?
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello. We're starting right away.
(What is this?)
What is this? Is this my head?
Yes.
(What is this? Is this my head?)
- It's Groot's head. - Right.
(That means...)
One...
(Ji Hyo versus Jae Seok)
(The outcome of 100 or General is...)
(General Yi Sun Sin.)
(Jae Seok's design is chosen.)
(This is bad.)
No one's reacting.
To Jae Seok, the winner,
we will give him the right to design the 3,000 t-shirts...
for the fan-meet.
("The Avengers And Gung Ye")
(Kwang Soo will be dressed up as Groot.)
I can't believe everything's ready in one day.
(He wishes it didn't happen.)
This is the costume?
(It's a shiny, feces-colored rag.)
This is for Groot?
(That rag will be Groot's body.)
It even covers my fingers.
We should put makeup on him before he puts that on.
I'm sorry, but could you please not whisper?
(He's become sensitive.)
Wear it.
Okay.
(How will he look with the costume on?)
Or we can do this.
This is...
- Oh, no. - There's no hole on the bottom.
(Surprised)
There's no hole at the bottom.
(They refuse to look at him.)
It's a bit tight.
I'm fine.
But it's really skintight.
I'm sorry. It's really tight.
- What should I do? - Hurry and sit down.
- It's skintight. - Hurry up and sit down.
My feet are covered.
Hello.
(So Min, who'll be dressed as Yondu, arrives.)
(This is what Yondu does, right?)
(Thinking he's a cool character, she enters cheerfully.)
Hello.
Kwang Soo! Oh, no!
(Kwang Soo! Oh, no!)
- Welcome. - Hello.
- Hello. - He isn't Groot.
He's a trophy. Look at him.
(His golden-brown costume...)
(makes him look like a trophy.)
(It's a special trophy to celebrate their 9th anniversary.)
Hey, Yondu is cool.
Wow, you're right.
(She'll be wearing a charismatic leather jacket.)
- But... - Don't lie. You didn't even see it.
Don't lie. You didn't even see it.
(I'm very sensitive right now.)
Don't be fake with your reactions.
- It's cool. - Yondu's costume is nice.
(So Min is content.)
Is this mine?
(However, Yondu is known for his blue face.)
Kwang Soo, there's something odd.
There's silicone here.
There are a pair of scissors and tweezers.
(It looks like an operating table.)
- Is this for my head? - Yes, to make it bald.
(Yes, to make it bald.)
What is this? Kwang Soo.
This is my head.
(I think it's going to be bad for me.)
I have feces on my face.
(It's already gone bad for me.)
(Se Chan joins this chaos.)
(Laughing)
(He bursts into laughter after seeing Kwang Soo's face.)
- You look hilarious. - What are you doing?
- Why are you here already? - Se Chan.
Hi. Hi, So Min.
I saw you through the door gap,
- and you looked like a mess. - Doesn't he look like a trophy?
- Kwang Soo. - Hi, Ji Hyo.
- So Min, hi. - Ji Hyo's here.
Look at Kwang Soo.
Ji Hyo, start your makeup. Start right now.
- Se Chan, it's bad for you too. - What?
There's a lot of fur in there.
- Really? - Yes.
What's his name?
- What's his name? - Rocket?
- Rocket. - That's his name?
Yes.
(Staring)
Is this a real sword?
(Ji Hyo will transform into Gamora.)
- Move aside. I have a sword. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo gets ready.)
(Jong Kook arrives.)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hey.
Do you think I look like a raccoon?
(He looks like a delinquent.)
Jong Kook, look at this.
(I've seen this face before.)
Do I seriously look like a raccoon?
Who are you?
(Se Chan has yet to put on the raccoon mask.)
You remind me of "Journey to the West".
He's right.
(He just needs a crown to look like Sun Wukong.)
Hey, there's also Thor who has a good body.
So why do I have to be Hulk?
You're right.
Why do I have to be Hulk?
- They both have great physiques. - You're right.
Either Gamora or Hulk needs to come first.
- Go, Hulk. - Go first.
You'll take a while.
I will? Don't I have a costume?
Maybe they'll do body painting.
I just need to paint my face, right?
You little...
(I ought to hit you.)
Hold on.
(Standing up)
- Forget it. - Just wear these.
Forget it.
(He pulls his pants down.)
You can wear these.
(Flustered)
You can wear them.
No, you should wear them.
- It's okay. - Put them back on.
I just wanted to help him.
Does Yondu not have any ears?
(She looks like a shuttlecock.)
How detailed.
He must not have any ears.
(What?)
Isn't that Noh Joo Hyun?
(Let's see.)
(She looks like Noh Joo Hyun.)
You know,
Jong Kook is fit for Hulk,
I'm fit for Groot, and Se Chan is fit for Rocket.
But why are you Yondu?
(Why does he want to make you Yondu?)
- We all look similar... - Right.
- to characters. - I know what you mean.
Because of that...
- Why are you Yondu? - I don't know.
Why would Jae Seok say that?
Jae Seok actually whispered in my ears yesterday,
"You'll thank me."
"I'm making you a star."
So you're a star.
I think everyone didn't oppose to Jae Seok's decisions...
because no one knew he'd win.
- Right. - Right.
(He's surprised.)
Wait.
(Why are you making me wear that all of a sudden?)
- Wait. - What is it?
What is that?
It looks like a crown.
That doesn't even seem to belong to Groot.
Wait. This looks like...
the decorations from sushi restaurants.
(It looks like the decorations sushi restaurants give out.)
It looks better, though.
- It's over. - It's over?
Try to speak like Groot.
I mean, this is...
Aren't you the sushi chef?
(Are you the sushi chef?)
(He looks like a tanned sushi chef.)
"Welcome. Thank you for visiting".
- He's the sushi chef. - It would be less embarrassing...
if the other parts looked more like Groot.
(He looks at the mirror,)
(and feels more miserable.)
Jong Kook.
You're not Shrek, right? You're Hulk.
I look like Shrek.
(His face looks too green.)
(Just be Shrek.)
You'd never get in a car accident.
(You'd never get in a car accident.)
It's too...
He looks like Shrek.
(The winner of Let's Make Merchandise Race has entered.)
- Hi. - Hi.
Kwang Soo.
Look at Se Chan.
(He looks like the raccoon from the theme park.)
My wig...
makes me look like Jo Hye Ryun.
(His hair makes him look like Jo Hye Ryun.)
Right.
But you look better than the others.
I like the raccoon.
So Min, do you know what you are?
- Yes. - Good.
I'll make you the star of the day.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Are you attaching it by yourself?
It's just that...
- she looked too busy. - Good.
I was helping her.
These are my works of art, so please be careful.
- We will. - All right?
(Seok Jin enters and he'll be Gung Ye.)
What?
Here comes Gung Ye.
Gung Ye is here.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Laughing)
Seok Jin.
He's laughing.
- Seok Jin is enjoying it. - Hi.
Goodness.
So Min's head is so pretty.
Don't lie to her. The back of her head is so flat.
(He's insulting her with facts.)
(It's flat.)
Why did you make me Gung Ye?
The other members are all heroes.
Gung Ye could read minds. He's the father of heroes.
This is ridiculous.
Is Ant-Man coming late,
or we just can't see him?
Is he wearing his costume in here?
Watch your feet, everyone.
(Here comes Ant-Man.)
- There he is. - There's Ant-Man.
- Hello. - Ant-Man.
- Why are you late? - Hello.
I just got the call.
- You're wearing cute today. - It's pretty.
You wear so well usually,
why do you wear like that on camera?
(I get that a lot.)
I get that a lot.
- Why do you wear like that? - What are you?
I'm a raccoon.
How is that a raccoon? You look like a bum.
Or a beggar who sings on the street.
Kwang Soo.
(He's still working on his crown.)
He's Groot.
- Are you a long poop? - Did you say "poop"?
(He's shocked by his looks.)
Did you say "poop"?
- I'm a chocolate pie. - You're a chocolate pie?
I'll make you a star, Kwang Soo.
- You should thank him. - You should thank me.
(Here's another one who will become a star.)
I look so unfamiliar.
(You are a star, right?)
It's too unfamiliar.
(Tapping)
(Ant-Man with the suit enters.)
(Awing)
What are you awing for?
- You look good. - Really?
Really.
- It's so cool with the suit. - Yes.
Even your body looks better.
He's got six-pack abs.
No, they're eight-pack abs.
(He now has six-pack abs thanks to his role.)
(Meanwhile...)
What am I wearing?
(What am I wearing?)
He said, "What am I wearing?"
I look like the mascot for a sushi restaurant event.
You still have to come to my house today...
- What? - with Se Chan.
For the performance for your son?
I made a reservation at a family restaurant.
Isn't that place filled with people?
Let's go somewhere less crowded.
There will be too many people.
Why are we going there?
My son's best friend, Eun Je, it's his birthday.
You should go to more events while you're at it.
You're coming too.
(You're coming to the birthday party too.)
(I'm coming too?)
But kids don't like Gung Ye.
- They do. - They do.
Kids don't like Gung Ye.
They like what you guys are.
- Ji Hyo looks awesome. - Let me take a look.
She actually looks like one.
(She looks like the real one.)
She looks too much alike, it's almost scary.
- I'm getting chills. - It's interesting.
I do look alike.
- You do. - It's your face.
(Next to Ji Hyo's high-quality makeup is...)
(Look at that.)
Hey, Yondu.
(What?)
(Did you call my name?)
(You can do anything but smile.)
(Please don't look at us.)
(She's disappointed.)
(Excuse me.)
- You have to put on the mustache. - What?
- What? - There's a mustache?
Is there a mustache?
(Because Yondu is the blue guy with a lot of mustaches.)
(The Yondu make up is looking better as it goes on.)
- Is she getting the horn too? - Yes.
- Really? - I'll show you.
What is that?
(He's taking out something.)
(It's a fluorescent pink horn.)
Wait.
(The blue face and mustache are finished with a pink horn.)
Look.
I was wondering what that was.
I didn't know what it was.
- Sit down. - I'm going home!
No, don't.
- This is the last one. - This is the last one.
- You're almost done. - I want to go home.
- Please. - I thought this was...
a sponge for washing dishes.
- Then he put it on her head. - Then he...
placed it on her head.
(It's very tough...)
(to become a star.)
I want to go home right now.
Look at this.
(I approve of that she's a real star.)
- Stop teasing her. - I mean...
The fish roe soup guy wants us to stop.
(Laughing)
What is that laughing sound?
Is that coming from the fish roe?
Hey, green onion.
- Get away from me, green onion. - Did you call me a green onion?
I'm done.
(The makeup of her life is finished.)
Can I get a picture?
I'm just a raccoon passing by.
Can I get a picture with you?
So Min, stand in the middle.
Let's take a picture with the wood.
I'm just Gung Ye passing by.
(What will their makeups look like in the end?)
All heroes, come here.
(It's time to take the pictures for the T-shirt.)
Everyone.
Jae Seok is trying to look cool. He likes his costume.
This costume...
is a lot better with the pin on the back.
- It makes you look better. - But on the back...
- It's a mess. - It makes you look better.
Right.
- Come here, heroes. - Yes, I'm ready.
Our stylists...
have perfectly...
Ji Hyo looks like the actual character.
- Look at Ji Hyo. - She's like the actress.
Hey, Ant-Man.
Come here.
Why am I Gung Ye?
- You guys are all the avengers. - Come here, Avengers.
Come here, Avengers.
- Let's gather here. - We're Guardians of the Galaxy.
You're Guardians of the Galaxy.
Gung Ye can find another set.
(Gung Ye can find another set.)
- You should be at the Folk Village. - Go to another set.
- Go to the Folk Village. - Why am I the only one?
Why am I wearing this alone?
You guys are all the avengers and I'm Gung Ye.
Mr. Fish-roe-soup, this isn't your set.
Stop calling me fish roe soup. I'm Gung Ye.
(You have insulted Gung Ye.)
Right. He's Gung Ye.
I have to check...
the costumes starting with Groot.
Why is Groot so...
- Is that the vine? - Yes.
- It's the vine. - It's the vine?
Okay. Wait.
(And he moves on to Yondu.)
- I... - She's perfect.
(It's Captain Yumerica's masterpiece.)
She's Yondu.
- It's awesome. - Sorry.
(He's satisfied.)
- That's a sponge on her head. - She looks like a chicken.
- No, she's not. - I think...
she could be cast as Yondu's daughter in Hollywood.
- Seriously. - Seriously.
I mean...
(Do you want to get pierced with my arrow?)
- I mean... - You should work at my restaurant.
(The owner is scouting her.)
I'll put the meat on her head instead of the headpiece.
(She was cast at the barbecue place before Hollywood.)
Stay put, Ant-Man.
- Stay put, you have nothing. - Stay put.
He'll be photoshopped smaller in the photo, right?
He actually...
didn't need to put on the suit.
But thank you for your dedication.
(Sighing)
Ant-Man will...
- almost look like a dot. - He should.
So the fans can find you...
with a magnifying glass.
There's fun in that.
- With a magnifying glass. - Right.
- It'll be quite fun. - I like it.
That's why you're being a dot.
I've been complimenting the staff.
Gamora looks so real.
She looks exactly like her.
- Right. - Right.
I think you'll be in the news.
- I was so surprised. - Her face is so similar.
In "Guardians of the Galaxy", Gamora is actually...
- She's considered beautiful. - Yes.
You're perfect.
- You... - I'm the daughter of Thanos.
You two should thank me.
(You two should thank me.)
(Did we hear him right? We should thank him?)
- Are you sure? - We're all related to our roles,
but why is So Min Yondu?
Right, why did you make me Yondu?
She and Yondu have nothing in common.
- She even has a mustache. - Why?
- You're... - I love my character.
- Rocket looks very good. - It's perfect.
- You look like a raccoon. - Yes.
Jong Kook is also perfect.
I have nothing more to say about him.
- That's not even padded. - That's not even padded.
- Right. - It's his actual muscles.
I thought it was stuffed with cotton, but it's just a tight shirt.
- I love Jong Kook's costume. - Yes.
And for you, Gung Ye...
- has a mind-reading ability. - That's right.
- He can read other people's minds. - Yes.
- Who dares to sneeze? - It was a cough.
It was a cough.
Who dares to make coughing noises?
That's not how you do it.
Actually, when Seok Jin was using the toilet...
This is a true story. It really happened.
When Seok Jin was using the toilet,
he farted.
And then he said, "Who dares to make coughing noises?"
(He pretended that he didn't fart.)
It's true! Isn't it, Seok Jin?
- Yes, it is. - Anyway,
since this is going to be printed on the shirts,
please do your best to stay in character.
- All right. - Could you give us our positions?
- Sure. I'll be in the center. - Okay.
We're going to take several shots and choose the best one.
When you take the group picture,
could you make sure Haha doesn't get overlapped with the others?
You need to be isolated.
(I can't be overlapped since I'm Ant-man.)
How sad.
Can't you just take his picture separately?
- It won't matter. - He can take it on his own.
Don't be sullen.
- He can just be photoshopped in. - Since you're Ant-Man.
It'll be fun to zoom in the picture to see me.
(The 7 members stand by the middle...)
(and 1 member stays in the corner.)
Do I put my mask on or not?
You can take it on and off.
(Will my face show if I do this?)
Whether your face shows or not isn't important.
Your face won't even show.
(Whether your face shows or not isn't important.)
How sad.
Let's begin.
Act like you're actually saving the world.
(Acting like they're actually saving the world,)
We will begin the shoot.
(they begin the shoot with a serious and cool face.)
(I am saving the world.)
(Click click)
Great.
Come over here, Haha.
We'll play with you. Come here.
- How cute. - I can pretend that I'm normal now.
- Come over here. - We'll play with you.
(They take the second group picture with Ant-Man.)
(So full of confidence)
Don't act so cool!
(Gosh, don't act so cool!)
How dare you do this?
(How dare you act so cool?)
You're holding a fake shield, too!
(Hey, I'm Captain!)
I almost thought you were actually saving the world.
- How about you? - I should have won.
For the next pose,
how about if we pretend that the enemies are in front of us,
- so we're surprised? - Acting surprised?
- Don't join us, Seok Jin. - Why not?
Why can't I be surprised?
Gung Ye doesn't have to change positions so often.
- Can the rest of the heroes do it? - Okay.
(Posing)
I told you not to do it.
(Get lost, enemies!)
- He's at it again! - Don't do that.
- Why does he keep doing that? - Excuse me,
- this isn't "Shaolin Temple". - It's no fun if I stay put.
And why do you keep moving forward?
- I'm the only Asian character. - Wait a minute.
Why?
Stay over here on this side.
I won't be able to read minds here.
- Just stay there. - You can't be in front of Ant-Man.
Oh my gosh.
(You're the best, Captain Yumerica.)
- Let's huddle a bit. - Okay.
(They continue on after Captain Yumerica fixes the positions.)
- Get closer. - Just stand there...
- and stare out into the distance. - Exactly.
- That's it. How cool is that? - Like you're protecting the Earth.
Who dares to see my mind-reading?
- Now, for the individual shots. - Let's take the individual shots.
Please move over for the individual shots.
We will shoot three different poses.
Look at that confident face.
He thinks he's really Captain.
Stop acting so cool.
You seem so unfamiliar without your glasses.
He's wearing a fake costume, too.
(He's acting so cool when he's wearing a fake costume.)
- Gosh... - He's wearing a 30-dollar costume.
(That tiny ant...)
He's wearing a 30-dollar costume.
(You're not cool at all.)
(Gung Ye gets in next to take the individual photos.)
- Let's go with Hulk, next. - Great.
- Excuse us. - Come on!
- The avengers need to go first. - We should go first.
The avengers will go first.
(Hulk starts to pose...)
- He looks genuine. - Great.
You look like the real Hulk.
Amazing.
- That's it. - Could you do this...
just in case?
- What? - Oh, this.
(Are you going to put Ant-Man in my hand?)
- That's it. - Ant-Man.
We're going to put the meat on your hand.
(We're going to put the meat in your hand.)
Hey!
(Even his business partner is embarrassed.)
- Don't you dare use it for that. - Come on, let's share.
This isn't for caldron lid meat, you know!
(What a good idea!)
This isn't for caldron lid meat.
- Can you pose for that? - Don't you dare use my shield.
Let's go with Guardians of the Galaxy next.
(Gung Ye comes to the center while they are busy with the meat.)
(He gets pushed aside again for Guardians of the Galaxy.)
It is Guardians of the Galaxy's turn.
- This is driving me crazy. - Guardians of the Galaxy.
- Hey! - They need to shoot.
(Next is Rocket of the Guardians of the Galaxy.)
- He looks just like him. - He's identical.
Hey, you look better this way.
Next is Gamora.
- She looks exactly like her. - Gamora looks great.
- You're all perfect! - She looks exactly like her.
She looks exactly like her. Ji Hyo, can you do this, too?
This pose. A knife...
I told you not to do that!
Why would the Hulk and Ant-man be doing that pose?
- Come on, try it. - Hey!
- Try using a knife. - Come over here.
Cut the meat with a knife.
Could you take that for me?
What's wrong with him?
- Yondu, next. - Yondu.
The chicken.
- "Chicken? - You're a chicken.
(Cute)
(Cutie Yondu is here!)
- What kind of Yondu are you? - Don't act out of character!
You're Yondu!
- That's so terrifying. - What are you doing?
- You look so scary! - What is she doing?
Don't do that!
- Don't do that! - What is she doing, that Yondu!
- You have a beard? - What kind of Yondu are you?
She has a beard.
Next is...
- Groot. - Groot.
Okay, you're done. Get out.
- Already? - Move over.
Hey, could you point to your head...
and make a three?
(Could you point to your head and make a 3?)
- Don't do it. - What's that?
- Bamboo meat. - No, don't do it.
Bamboo meat?
- Come on, do it. - Don't.
Come on!
You can go next, Seok Jin.
- Help me. - You can do the mind-reading.
Who dares to make coughing noises?
He's so bad at it.
He's so bad at acting.
- This isn't the "Shaolin Temple"! - Seok Jin...
Seok Jin!
(Isn't this right?)
Let's go with Haha next. Ant-Man.
Ant-Man.
- He's putting on his mask. - Come on.
- Okay, great. - We didn't even need him to come.
- Someone else could have done it. - No one will know it's him.
How can you tell in the picture?
- That's enough. - Show your face, Haha.
That's enough. Move over.
Come over here, Jong Kook. Hurry.
- What are they doing? - What are you doing?
Is it for the restaurant?
- Stop that! - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Don't take the pictures...
- for personal use! - Don't take them!
- Come over here. - What are you doing?
Can you hold this up for a minute?
Don't you dare photoshop the meat on this.
Could you put your head on this?
- Put your head on it to grill. - I'll cut it up.
Okay, cut it.
Let's take it.
- What's this? - I'll start the fire, then.
(The poster for the restaurant is completed!)
(Korean Barbeque House, Captain's Caldron Lid Meat)
(Come to Haha and Jong Kook's Avengers Barbecue House.)
It's a barbecue place.
- Hey, wait. - That's enough.
- Thank you. - Good job.
- Good job, everyone. - Good job.
Good job.
(The final picture will be revealed on the day of the fan-meet.)
How are we supposed to do this?
Since Lia dances well,
she makes even the simplest moves look so cool,
- but we won't be able to do that. - No.
Why are you already sitting down and talking?
(Serious)
We were talking about how hard it will be for us.
- Since you guys are full of power. - It may be hard for the ladies.
- But we aren't. - You can do it.
(As soon as they saw the video,)
(she looked grim.)
(They all dance in unity to the beat.)
(It is a powerful dance where you can feel the dancers' strength.)
No way, we can't be doing that.
(Will they be able to do it in time?)
So Min is already...
a good dancer.
I only know how to dance at the nightclub.
(I am good at nightclub dancing.)
I don't know how to dance like that.
Show us, then. Show us that move.
- This one! - Yes, that's the one.
(I was a clubber back in the days!)
This is how we dance.
(She's good.)
Why don't you show her, Se Chan?
Like this.
(I can dance, too.)
(Pointing here and there)
Oh, you're good.
Can't we just do this?
She's laughing so hard.
I don't think she's ever laughed because of a dance.
- Hey... - Like this.
- How about this? - How about that?
- If it's anything like this, - How does that look?
- we can do it. - We can manage that.
I just had a vision...
of us dancing on stage.
(He saw what they would look like on stage.)
- Are you a superhero? - I mean...
we will be doing it,
but we won't look anything like them.
- You saw our future? - Yes.
Just for a minute
We'll have a perfect ending, though.
(They're going to make the ending right.)
But it might just be the case...
where you didn't know that you could dance...
until now.
- No way. - I mean...
(He's suddenly dropping his manners.)
since you've never tried.
- Why are you being rude to her? - Since you've never tried.
How could you talk to our teacher like that?
- I didn't mean to say that. - How could you say that?
- I was only... - How could you say that?
I was only...
You even told us to speak impolitely.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry, I was only trying to say that it's impossible for us.
Oh, is that so?
Seok Jin, why don't you show us your "Fire" dance?
Look at him.
(He is showing her his best moves.)
(Swinging around)
(He washes his face...)
(and dries off.)
2, 5, shoot! Shoot, shoot.
I'm actually not that worried anymore,
- after seeing his moves. - Really?
- My speed is... - He's quite swift.
I keep hearing his bones crack, though.
(Cracking)
(His body cannot support his passion.)
(Are you okay?)
- I kept hearing it. - That's enough, Seok Jin.
- It's all right. - You don't have to do that.
I think you pulled a muscle.
He needs to act fine if he wants her to teach him.
He's fine. They're not important bones, anyway.
It's nothing serious.
You can manage us, right?
- Sure. - We're good enough.
Yes, I think you'll do well.
There are a lot of students...
who came as terrible dancers,
but turned into great dancers after your classes, right?
Yes, of course.
Son Dam Bi was a terrible dancer.
- No way! - Dam Bi?
- She mentioned that before. - Yes.
It took Dam Bi...
a long time to learn how to dance. She struggled a lot.
She overcame with her effort.
She could be a scary teacher.
We are worried that you would be different...
- when you begin to teach us. - It's entirely possible.
- Do you get angry at your students? - I am incredibly sensitive.
- I am a perfectionist. - Really?
- This is a disaster. - So I might...
Do many students cry?
- What? - Do many students cry?
When they cry, I ignore them.
(When they cry, I ignore them.)
(The cruel world of dance)
She is cold-hearted.
- That's cold. - She is cold-hearted.
Otherwise, I tell them to go outside.
- "Would you go outside and cry?" - "You can go to the restroom."
"Go and wash your face."
She is strong.
Show us a few of your dance skills.
- Then, I'll... - Do what you do the best.
- Start with popping. - Popping?
(How good is Lia Kim, the world-class dancer?)
Let's see Lia Kim's dance skills.
(She slowly moves to the rhythm.)
(Her joints move freely.)
She is twisting her body.
She can twist her body like no other.
Doesn't she have any bones?
(She moves like mollusks.)
Her facial expression is incredible.
(Her moves are controlled...)
(to go with the beats.)
This is popping.
(The members are surprised,)
(but Lia Kim plays with the rhythm in a relaxed manner.)
- Doesn't she have any bones? - She is amazing.
Is that waacking?
Yes, it is.
(This time, it's waacking.)
(To the rhythm,)
(she moves her arms and legs.)
(Her small body exudes explosive energy.)
(Her knees slam into the floor.)
(Are your knees okay?)
This is it!
This is waacking.
That's enough.
Hip-hop dance.
(After popping and waacking)
- She is an expert. - Hip-hop dance.
- Hip-hop dance. - My goodness.
Hip-hop dance should go like this.
(Hip-hop dance is characterized by groovy moves.)
She moves fast.
(She becomes one with the music.)
(This is the class of the world-famous dancer.)
I am afraid her hips will dislocate.
(He enjoys the dance in a daze.)
(She plays with the rhythm.)
(This is like a revival meeting.)
(Lia Kim, we believe in you!)
- Lia. - My goodness.
I got goosebumps.
She is on another level.
- She did this. - She was really fast.
She moved so powerfully. Is your back okay?
She was really fast.
Where should we begin?
We can work on the formation for the intro...
later on.
Today, you will get the taste...
of the dance moves.
- Let's do that. - Let's get the taste.
- Let's get the taste. - The beat is fast.
This is how you start. Put your legs apart with a kick.
- Jump and kick like this. - Bam!
That's right. Your arms spread out.
- Bam! - Yes. Combine them. Bam! Bam!
- Bam! Bam! - Bring your limbs back.
(Bring the arms and legs to the chest.)
- I can do this. - That's right. Spread and fold.
- You can do this, right? - Yes.
I told you that you can do this.
(Carefree)
We can do this much.
We aren't that terrible.
The routine is a fast combination of these dance moves.
- This is pretty doable. - Bam. Bam.
As you put your arms down, cross the fists.
(As you put your arms down, cross the fists.)
(Concentrating)
All right. Everyone can do it.
As the right foot goes back, pull the right arm.
- Bam. - There you go.
Now, throw your arm as if you are pitching...
and move your foot to the front.
Throw.
(Throw your arm and move your foot to the front.)
You can do every move.
(She is impressed.)
Let's try it again.
- Lia. - Lia.
(This is too much.)
- Hold on. - This is too much.
Just how hopeless did you think we would be?
I looked in the mirror and everyone followed along.
She is pacifying us as if we are children.
I received the same treatment on the first day of boxing class.
They told me that I am a secret weapon.
(He becomes a secret weapon.)
They told me not to use my fist haphazardly.
When I did this, they went, "My goodness."
Trainers are like that.
- They wanted to motivate me. - Right. They do that.
- Shall we try it slowly? Let's go. - Yes.
(She breaks down the moves they have learned.)
(They learn one part at a time.)
(The members follow along.)
Shall we try it a bit faster?
- Okay. - It will become harder.
In 5, 6...
(They will connect the moves to the second part.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E455 Running Man
"Challenging Choreography"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
That was almost perfect.
- Is she making fun of us? - I am serious.
I am the ace dancer among them.
(I am the ace dancer.)
Gosh, he became confident in no time.
(He exudes confidence.)
That was almost perfect. He is the best student.
This must be why teachers compliment their students.
Shall we try it? Let's go.
(She checks each member.)
(The ace dancer, Haha goes first.)
(He does it without a problem.)
That was good.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
- No words are needed. - Thank you.
- Let's go. - She is generous with compliments.
(Bam! Bam! Bam!)
(Oh...)
(Creaking)
(She gives her first sigh.)
Shall we try it again?
(There was a hidden challenge.)
She had a realization. "Oh."
The first obstacle.
A small mountain you must climb over appeared.
(It's the first out of many obstacles.)
I can't help but move this way because I am groovy.
- Did you get it? - Really?
Lia, how many of these four beats are there?
(An unexpected question...)
(leaves Lia flustered.)
Ji Hyo, this is the beginning.
- I am curious. - There must be 400 beats.
- 400 beats? - Maybe a couple of hundreds.
When you go home today, you will sleep soundly.
She will sleep like a baby.
You have never received this kind of question, right?
"How many of these four beats are there?"
When she wakes up tomorrow, she will go,
"For goodness' sake."
I see a lot of potentials.
- Really? - Yes.
- Let's continue on. - Let's learn a bit more.
(They continue on with the next move.)
Grab the hand that comes over...
and move your shoulders. Right, left,
right, left. Move your shoulders...
four times.
Do it as you go up.
What was that?
(Move your shoulders as you go up.)
Kwang Soo and I are good at this.
- We can go down... - That's right.
and come up.
He is good.
(What do you think?)
(I am good, right?)
Kwang Soo, do this. He is good at going up.
- Go up. - There you go.
(He moves in a funny way.)
Is there a mechanism for this?
- He is good. - He is like a doll.
- He is like a robot. - He is the best at going up.
- He is the best at going up. - That was good.
Let's do it again.
(They go over what they learned.)
2 and 3.
(They follow along pretty well from part 1 to 4.)
- 5, 6, 7, and 8. - Go up, step, and spread.
(The dance moves come along.)
You can do the moves. It's so fascinating.
We can do the moves, but we don't look cool.
(His self-examination is brutally honest.)
You are right.
- That's the problem. - My goodness.
- That was honest. - Seriously.
- That was honest. - We don't look cool.
- That was honest. - He is right.
- We don't look cool. - When you do the moves,
you shouldn't push your hips back...
because you will look funny.
- I see. - For hip-hop dance,
- you should stand like this. - Lia, you are a professional.
- Seriously. - Lia.
(What's wrong?)
You pulled up the T-shirt without hesitation.
(You pulled up the T-shirt without hesitation.)
We felt a bit comfortable.
- We were behind you. - We understand, but...
(Her daring way of revealing the tip...)
(left them flustered.)
She pulled it up.
We understand, but...
I will wear those shorts the next time.
(I will wear those shorts the next time.)
- Don't do that. - No.
Don't do that, Jae Seok.
Don't do that.
I will wear those shorts.
She wanted to show us the details.
That's right. You need to learn how to use your body.
That startled us.
You are cool.
- If you do this, you look funny. - That's right.
- Do this instead. - This is...
- what we need to learn. - Swagger.
- Roll up your body. - That's what we need to do.
- Let's keep going. - We will work hard.
From here...
Move your body to the right...
and pop your shoulder once.
- So... - Gosh, that's hard.
Imagine hitting your chin with your shoulder.
Move quickly like this. Left and right.
- Left and right. - Your body...
(He hits himself twice.)
(Is it supposed to hurt this much?)
Lia, he hit his own chin.
It hurts so much.
(Isn't this what I am supposed to do?)
(She has never had students like them before.)
- I did it unconsciously. - He really hit himself.
Do it as if you're hitting.
- As if you're hitting. - "As if"?
Keep your head still.
Like this.
Move your torso.
Go back and forth.
Once on each side. Left hand, right hand.
It looks amazing when Lia does it.
You're such a good teacher.
Seriously.
- I think I can do it. - Right?
Shoulder, shoulder.
- Hand, hand. - Hand, hand. Good.
(The order is accurate.)
(It's the same dance but looks different.)
She's such a good teacher.
- It's the wrong hand movement. - What?
(Those who watch are embarrassed.)
Shall we dance to the music?
- Okay. - That sounds good.
(Can they dance to the music?)
(The atmosphere changes when the music starts.)
It looks amazing.
(Her movements are accurate with the beat.)
That's great.
(It's full of charm.)
It looks amazing.
(Is that what we learned?)
That was amazing.
Wait, Lia.
- It's faster than I thought. - It's very fast.
That was three seconds.
It's so fast.
We have to listen to the music...
- in order to figure it out. - We should relax the torso.
At first, you may be wrong. You may not keep up with the beat.
As you practice, you'll catch it.
(At that moment)
(All their moves are accurate to the beat.)
He got it all.
(Ace of dance, Haha)
- You know it all. - No, Seok Jin.
He's as good as the dancers in the video.
No, not at all.
- Dance solo, Haha. - Seriously.
You're very good at this part.
(Did you compliment me?)
Look at him.
(He can't hide it even if he tries.)
He pretends to be amazing.
Come here if you can't do it.
This is why I don't want to practice with him.
(Everyone is jealous of him.)
He's so annoying.
I want to do it. Is this it, Haha?
What's wrong with you, So Min?
So Min is a good dancer, but she has her own style.
- She's good. - They're very good.
She has her own style.
When it comes to our ace dancers,
they're Jong Kook and Haha.
Let's watch them dance first.
- Let's divide into teams. - So Min is one of them.
So Min.
(They start with the music.)
(They dance to the beat like an ace group.)
(No one misses a move.)
(They dance exactly what they learned.)
I'm sorry.
(So Min and Haha bump into each other.)
(Instead of being flustered,)
(they concentrate until the end.)
(They dance successfully to the end.)
(She's truly surprised.)
They're ace.
That was perfect.
That was amazing.
It was great.
(We did it.)
They're very good.
The rest of us should come out.
It's a mixed group.
- I feel too shy to do it. - Come this way.
- Stand here, Ji Hyo. - She's the only woman.
(We can do it, odds and ends.)
I know.
- It ended so quickly. - It's hard to look cool.
(Odds and ends also start.)
I was late.
This is bad.
(This isn't easy.)
What I'm doing is wrong.
(He's creating another choreography.)
(They're satisfied with themselves. "We danced well".)
(Total disaster)
This is what he did.
- You did that. - Don't mock us.
Don't laugh at us.
We aren't laughing at you.
(We're in trouble.)
Now,
you memorized up to this point.
- Let's go on. - Okay.
- What's next? - When you come to this position,
go up this way.
This way.
This is the position. It's the 90-degree angle.
Lift it up like an elevator all the way to your elbow.
Bend and lower it.
- Lift your left arm again. - I'm confused.
This arm will come down like an elevator.
- This comes down. - Isn't it as hard as this?
(It's very advanced.)
(The body and the mind move separately.)
It's very confusing.
- Right. - Haha.
It's like the triangle and circle.
Next,
bring them in like this.
(Swing the hands together toward the stomach.)
It's like we have a stomachache.
Do it faster.
As if we have appendicitis.
- Appendicitis. - My stomach.
Open up quickly.
- Next is here. - Here.
(Raise the left hand with the right arm stretched out.)
(Bring the left hand to the right.)
(Pull the hands toward the chest.)
(Then lower them.)
- It's difficult. - It's hard.
Clap your hands and send one hand away.
(Send one hand to the back by clapping.)
After that,
- push forward your pelvis twice. - We saw that before.
- The beat... - We're in big trouble.
Will we be able to do it later?
(They dance up to where they learned to the music.)
(Ace Jong Kook and Haha learned perfectly.)
(Is it the stomachache part?)
7, 8, 1, 2, 3, 4.
(There's an error due to a stomachache.)
I can't follow the latter part.
- I can't do it. - I'm in trouble.
I can't do it after grabbing the appendix.
As I grab the appendix, my body gets twisted.
When I got to this part,
I said, "I did it wrong."
- Gosh, I'm wrong. - That's right.
(He did well up to here.)
(As soon as he grabs the stomach,)
(I did it wrong.)
- You can do it if you memorize it. - We have to get used to this.
What if the half of us keep grabbing the appendix?
The good dancers...
do the original dance.
The rest of us hold and rest.
What are you talking about?
We'll do this part in unison.
Turn and do this twice.
(She's speechless.)
I'm sorry, Lia.
(He's quick to notice.)
She was giving you a look, Seok Jin.
That was a bad idea.
(No one can boss her around.)
I should practice it at home.
I'll keep practicing at home, Lia.
We can do it if we practice a lot.
If you memorize it, you can do it.
- You can do it with muscle memory. - It's possible.
- It is possible. - If you practice 100 times...
(She gives an extreme solution.)
- Did you say 100 times? - Did I hear you correctly?
Did she say 100?
If no one makes a mistake, do it 50 times.
- Okay. - If no one makes a mistake.
This is a boot camp.
We shouldn't say the slogan at the end, right?
If you make a mistake, practice 20 more times.
- Oh, no... 120 times? - That's good, Lia.
Let's stop, Hye Rang.
What are you doing?
(It's a privilege of a 54-year-old soldier.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
- What did you say to her? - "Hye Rang"?
Hye Rang.
- Don't call her Hye Rang. - I'm sorry, Lia.
I'm sorry. I must be out of my mind.
- He's out of his mind. - Now, get ready.
He's about to lose it.
Shall I take a look?
(They practice 50 times if they get it correct.)
(If one of them makes a mistake, they repeat 120 times.)
(Will they pass the difficult part successfully...)
(and do it 50 times?)
(Jae Seok's right foot moves one beat faster.)
(Members don't know about it.)
- No. - I got it wrong.
- We got everything right. - I got it wrong.
Get down on all fours.
Get on your knees.
(How can you be so proud?)
We should practice.
- We should. - I thought about reducing it,
but I had a change of heart.
- Okay, it'll be 120 times. - Let's go.
- How many was it originally? - Let's see.
If we cry, can we go outside?
(I can't do it 120 times.)
(He tries to haggle with his tears.)
Do I have to show tears...
to go outside?
I can't do it anymore.
- Stop it. - I can't do it anymore.
- Stop it. - Just to go out?
We are being punished now.
He asked if he can leave if he cries.
- I can stand this anymore. - Stop it.
How about no restroom break until you do it 100 times?
Do it without going to the restroom and going out.
- Okay. - Okay, we'll do it.
We have to dance while crying.
Okay.
This is how I train dancers.
- Seriously, - We'll practice.
she's so strict.
You can use the restroom after you do it 100 times.
Get ready.
- 5, 6, 7, and 8. - 5, 6, 7, 8.
- Wait. - Was I wrong?
- The right side. - What's wrong?
(They resume the training while holding back the tears.)
(When everyone moved the right foot,)
(Kwang Soo moved his left foot.)
What's the matter?
Did you move the right foot?
- What's wrong with you? - What's wrong?
- Left leg. - It's this foot.
(Move the left leg.)
Last time.
(Why is everyone giving me a hard time?)
He's crying.
- Get out. - Kwang Soo is crying.
(He finally bursts into tears.)
(Finally Kwang Soo is crying.)
- Where is he going? - Hey, come here.
- Cry here. - Come here.
- Do it while crying. - Come here.
I really can't do it.
I'll just do the wing walking instead.
I'll go to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
- Go home. - Don't tell me to go home.
Tell your mother.
(I miss Mom.)
Let's do this.
(He stops crying, and they resume training again.)
(Squirming)
(He steps backwards instead of dancing.)
(What's wrong with my legs?)
It's confusing because of him.
What's wrong?
I thought he got shot.
(Seok Jin walks backwards.)
- What's wrong with you? - I thought he got shot.
(From the movie "The Front Line")
(Shooting)
(Goodness)
- I thought he got shot. - What's wrong with you?
- It's because... - I thought he got shot.
I swung too hard.
(He got too ambitious.)
I lost my balance.
What's wrong, Seok Jin?
- Lia, my legs are shaking. - All right.
- Let's count together. - Okay.
- Then you can memorize faster. - Let's try it.
If we count together, will you reduce it by 10?
Is that possible?
(Shooting!)
(Bullets are the best punishment for students who don't listen.)
(He acts as if he got shot.)
He's the best actor for getting shot.
He's the best.
- It looked real. - He's good.
Go somewhere else for acting.
That was good.
All right.
Ready, set, go.
- 5, 6, 7, and 8. - 5, 6, 7, and 8.
Keep going. Get ready.
(Their training continues without a break.)
(No matter how exhausted they are,)
(they repeat until they do it perfectly.)
(He gulps down the water.)
(Lia is still full of energy.)
- All right. - Lia is my type. I like her.
It's 10th time.
- It's 11th time. - 11th time.
Lia.
- Count properly. - Do we keep going?
- Okay. - Get ready.
5, 6.
Lia, it's this way.
Lia.
(Lia, it's this way.)
- You need a break. - You should rest.
- Take a break, Lia. - Take a break.
- Rest. It's okay. - Have a drink.
It's okay, Lia.
- Go and wash your face. - It's okay.
Don't do it 100 times.
Take a break.
I'm tired too.
Your personality comes out now that time has passed.
Have some water.
(She finds out about herself as she teaches bad dancers.)
- Shall we start? - Okay.
This is great. Let's go.
What's so great?
- It's great to do it quickly. - Do you feel great?
Five times to the music.
We'll do it five times.
- Lia. - After five times...
This is great.
- No, this is great for me. - We'll do it five times.
- It's a great exercise. - Do it five times.
- Do it five times. - Let's do it.
- Lia is so strict. - Let's go.
- Here we go. - Let's go. This is great.
(He's very happy.)
7, 8.
(As the practice continues,)
(one person becomes happier.)
(This is exciting.)
- I'm so tired. - I'm tired.
(Everyone is getting tired except for one person.)
- I won't do it. - Let's keep going.
- Let's go. - Let's go. Okay.
Get up.
Please stop.
7, 8.
(They're dancing,)
(but their minds are off somewhere else.)
(He's making a face.)
(He's the only one smiling.)
1 and 2 and keep going.
1, 2, yes.
We got lost in the mood.
- Stop now. - Five times.
We can keep doing this.
Let's go.
- I can't do it anymore. - This is an exercise.
Have some water.
I love it.
What should I do?
(Do what?)
- Right now, - Do what?
- I'm so full of energy. - What's wrong?
Right now...
- What? - I have to do something.
- Right now. - What?
- I have to do something. - What?
- What's wrong? You're scary. - What's wrong with you?
- My heart is beating fast. - Seriously.
- My heart is beating fast. - I really hate him.
(I never met a student like him.)
I'm just starting.
Let's start again, everyone.
- One more time? - Time is precious. Let's hurry.
- Go to the gym after this. - Okay.
Here is not your gym.
I'll go after my heart rate goes up.
Let's go.
- Okay. - We have a long way to go.
- Get ready. - Okay.
Ready, set, go.
(They continue to practice over 4 hours.)
(They repeat 120 times.)
- 1 and 2. - Kwang Soo is about to faint.
- 3 and 4. - It's tiring.
Now,
I'll watch how you're doing.
Whether we do it well or not, we'll do it one last time.
- Let's leave. - I'm leaving.
You can't do that.
We'll say goodbye next time.
I'm leaving. I can't do it anymore.
How about you dance individually?
How about those who pass can leave?
- That's cruel. - That sounds good.
What's wrong with you?
You can go home if you make no mistakes.
- It's like the room escape game. - It is, indeed.
- Let's escape. - It's escaping from a room.
- How about 2 together? - 2 by 2?
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo have to dance all night.
Two of you dance together.
- Let's hurry and go. - Go home if you make no mistakes.
- Try it. - Do we dance by two?
Play the music.
They'll do well.
(Jong Kook and Haha try first.)
They're good.
They look amazing.
(They're good.)
(They get the stomachache part perfectly.)
(Jong Kook gets the last part wrong.)
- That was right. - Jong Kook almost had it.
I got the last part wrong.
- They dance well. - He got the last part wrong.
Haha can go home.
I'm jealous.
(He escapes like an ace.)
He goes home!
Would you like to try again?
- Yes. - Try it again.
Can I dance with a pair?
- How about... - Three of you dance.
With me and So Min.
Start.
(They're determined to escape.)
(He was doing well.)
(Then he misses the beat.)
(Perfect)
They passed.
- That was correct. - Okay.
Neither of them made a mistake.
Good job.
- You successfully escaped. - Success!
- 2 people. - 2? Okay.
- Start. - One.
(He looks determined.)
(He's better than we expected.)
(This is Se Chan's second try.)
(It's the difficult stomachache part.)
(He succeeds without trouble.)
I got it.
(Kwang Soo is doing well.)
(After missing a beat, he has a meltdown.)
(Fluttering)
(I won't be going home today.)
Se Chan passed.
- You're impressive. - Seriously.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo's turn)
(He dances quite well.)
He dances well.
(They don't look good, but the order is perfect.)
- That's right. - It's right.
(Suddenly there's a duck move.)
(He adds a new move.)
Wait a minute.
Seok Jin.
Didn't he do this last time?
- Why would you make a pigeon? - Didn't a pigeon fly by?
Why would you make a pigeon?
Why did you do this move?
- Something flew by. - What was that?
- Ji Hyo passed. - You passed.
You passed.
Kwang Soo, let's give it a try.
Let's do it neatly.
- Music. - I'm confused.
They're very good.
(Kwang Soo makes a mistake of stepping forward.)
He got it wrong.
(Except for one mistake, both were perfect.)
That wasn't bad.
No.
- Was it vague? - He passed.
- Did I pass? - Yes.
Did he pass?
He passed.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Seok Jin is so funny.
I can do it.
Music, start.
(Flinching)
(He's unstable from the beginning.)
Why did you do that?
(He calms himself down.)
(They start seriously.)
(They're perfect so far.)
(Losing balance)
- Wait. - What? Why?
(Someone always shoots after some time.)
- What's wrong, Seok Jin? - He got shot again.
Who shot you?
- Don't shoot him. - Hey.
- Who keeps shooting him? - Who shot him?
Don't shoot.
Did you get electrified?
That's not it.
I had to stretch out my arm.
He went backwards.
(Seok Jin blocked his way.)
I swung too hard again.
I should have controlled it.
- I tried to look cool. - Lia.
Please stop.
Seok Jin might die at this rate.
This is enough.
(He might die from exhaustion.)
- Do it well. - Try it again.
- It's the last time. - Last time.
Okay, it's the last.
Even if you move back, I'll stretch out my arm.
- No matter what, - I'm sorry.
- I'll poke you. - Okay, I'm sorry.
Okay, okay.
(Concentrating)
- Start. - Go.
It's okay so far.
You have to do this part well.
(Will he continue to dance without getting shot?)
(Seok Jin always got shot after this move.)
(Will he pass it safely?)
(He passes.)
(Lia is also impressed.)
Okay, you got it.
You did it. You did it.
I did it.
- You got it. - You made it.
Thank you.
We should recognize what deserves recognition.
- Seok Jin's impressive for his age. - Seriously.
(Infinite training changed Seok Jin.)
- That was impressive. - You made it.
I made it.
How long is the dance that we just learned?
About 17 to 18 seconds.
- We spent 5 hours for 18 seconds. - 18 seconds out of 3 minutes.
We're worried since we're still not perfect for those 18 seconds.
The latter part is less difficult than the beginning.
- Really? - The beginning is the hardest.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- Lia was with us. - That's a relief.
We could do it because we were in front of the cameras.
(They can do anything in front of the cameras.)
What if there were no cameras?
If there were no cameras,
we'd have gone home after less than an hour.
We made it because of the cameras.
- We'd like to tell the viewers. - That's right.
Lia, I really enjoyed it...
- today. - Thank you.
- See you again next time. - Thank you, Lia.
(How will their performance be at their fan-meet?)
(What if members become lyrics?)
(It's time to decide the lyrics for Running Man's title song.)
(They reflect on what members represent.)
(8 poets write modifiers.)
(They're generous with their own modifier.)
(They're strict with modifiers for other members.)
(And the patterns of creating modifiers change drastically.)
(Jae Seok, a positive word)
(It's a battle of lyrics as they exchange words of blessing.)
(And)
(Bizarre missions for lyricists)
(Who will be the final winner to decide the lyrics?)
(Lyrics Writing Race)