(Previously on Running Man)
- Please come on out. - Hello.
- It's Hyun A. - See?
It's been so long.
Today, six couples of animals will participate in today's race.
It's called the Mysterious Animal Farm Race.
There are two forbidden animals who destroyed the farm.
- Forbidden animals? - There are two...
- forbidden animals. - Two?
- Can you move a bit to the side? - All right.
- Team Bear and Team Snake. - Okay. We did it.
- We got it. - We did it.
- We'll check it together, right? - Yes. One team at a time.
What?
Hold on.
- Pig. - It's not snake then.
- Snakes... - Do tigers live in packs?
No, they don't.
- Bear. - It can't be tiger.
- It's not tiger. - It's 1 of these 3 teams.
Then, they are among these six people.
- Rabbit, pig, and fox? - It's not me.
The last mission to fish out the forbidden animals...
is Find Hidden Animals.
- What? - I guess they are hidden.
Hints about the forbidden animals are hidden all over the building.
- There are hints. - Yes.
If you find the forbidden animals and eliminate them, you'll win.
Oppositely, if the animals get all eliminated,
the forbidden animals will win.
The losing team will face a penalty.
However, if you eliminate an animal, not a forbidden animal,
both of the animals will be eliminated.
Some of us should go around in groups.
- What if one of them is it? - But it's hard to eliminate...
all of us when there are only 2...
All right. Be quiet. So...
Why do you let him treat you like this?
- It's driving me crazy. - Why do you let him?
It's driving me crazy. This is why we'll lose today.
We'll lose because I didn't speak up.
And if you are eliminated by the forbidden animals,
that area in the building will get closed off.
(An area will get closed.)
All the hints in the area will be removed,
and if you step into the area, you'll be eliminated. So be careful.
(When both their feet are in the area, they'll be eliminated.)
So if I push someone into it, that person will get eliminated?
- Yes. - My gosh.
- My gosh, that's scary. - I shouldn't even go near that.
In addition, there is a special DVD rental shop and a library...
where you can enter whenever you want.
At the DVD rental shop,
there will be several DVDs with animals.
After choosing a DVD,
you can play a scene of your choice for one minute.
- One minute? - You'll find out...
if the forbidden animals are in the scene you chose.
(They'll find out whether or not if there are forbidden animals.)
- They're giving us a lot of hints. - If you chose, the movie "Babe",
and if there are pigs in the scene you watched for a minute,
you'll either see an O or an X if it's a forbidden animal.
- Really? - We'll let you know.
With the letters? They're telling us everything.
That's great.
However, each couple gets only one chance to rent a DVD.
One chance?
And only one person can enter.
- That's hard. - I'll go in.
- Why? - What?
- I'll know for sure. - As for the library,
everyone will get one chance to enter.
If you win the mission against the mission-keeper,
you'll obtain a hint about the forbidden animals.
Before you head to your own spots, I'll give out the rental ticket.
There's only one rental ticket for one couple?
- It's for the DVDs. - Each couple gets only one?
Han Na, you should hold onto it.
- Sihyeon, you watch the DVD. - I'll hold onto it.
- Look. Everyone is yielding. - Everyone is yielding.
Everyone gave it to their partners. You're the only one who didn't.
- Give it to me. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Why won't you give it to me? Give it to me if you're not it.
Rock-paper-scissors
Okay.
- I'll hold onto it. - I don't feel safe about this.
- There's 2 out of the 6, right? - Right.
- Why didn't So Min make a guess? - Two of the animals are it.
We should suspect So Min too.
Once you go to your own spot, we'll begin the race.
Yes. Okay.
(The race begins once they go to their spot.)
- Seok Jin. - Gook Ju.
I doubt that it's you, right?
- It's not me. - I couldn't trust you that day.
It's really not me.
I'm sure it's Han Na though.
- She is, right? - She came early, you know.
What's your animal? Are you a pig?
(Blurting it out)
- No, Seok Jin. - You're...
- You're a tiger. - It's so obvious I'm a tiger.
- How could you say I'm a pig? - I'm sorry.
You're unbelievable.
It clearly says I'm a tiger. Can't you read?
- I'm sorry. - It clearly says...
- "tiger" here. Seok Jin. - I'm sorry, Gook Jin.
- You heard me roar earlier. - I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Do you know what he said to me?
It's her. I was suspecting her.
He asked if I was a pig as soon as he saw me.
- But he read my badge. - No.
I'm sorry. That's not true.
Actually, HyunA from Team Pig looks very suspicious.
It's odd that she's deceiving us.
She was acting strange earlier.
I really have a bad feeling about So Min.
I really have a bad feeling about her.
It's either Jae Seok and Han Na or Seok Jin and HyunA.
(So Min is suspecting Jae Seok, Han Na, Seok Jin, and HyunA.)
Today, Jae Seok has been awfully quiet.
Jae Seok seems suspicious today too.
My gosh, I'm not sure about HyunA either.
It's HyunA. Something about her feels off.
There's no way she really didn't understand that game.
(HyunA, the prime suspect, is suspecting Jae Seek and Han Na.)
Right?
(I found bad animals. They're probably my partner and Han Na.)
Let the race begin.
(The race to find 2 hidden, forbidden animals will begin soon.)
3, 2, 1.
Start the race.
Jae Seok.
You look lonely, Jae Seok.
Oink, oink.
(Is So Min starting psychological warfare?)
Didn't I tell you? I'm serious. You are...
Where is he going?
He didn't even turn back.
That's such a skinny pig.
(She's unbelievable.)
My goodness, you're ridiculous.
(Following only after Jae Seok)
You startled me.
Why do you keep following me?
I'm looking for Haha.
So we can go to the DVD cafe.
No, it's not a DVD cafe. I meant a DVD rental shop.
I'm sorry. That's not what I meant.
Why did they name it like that?
- So we can watch the DVD. - Is that so?
- No, we'll rent the DVD. - All of a sudden,
you caught me by surprise.
(She's looking for Haha to get the hint at the DVD rental shop.)
Haha.
HyunA and I need to go together. Where did she go?
(Engrossed in the race)
(Filming a spy movie all by herself)
(Everyone, be quiet. I'm really serious right now.)
- That's HyunA. - She's the most suspicious one...
- because... - Yes, her behaviors are suspicious.
HyunA is the most suspected member from Team Pig.
As soon as she saw me, she rushed to me from the opposite side.
You're the most suspicious one.
Come here, HyunA.
Why do you think Han Na is it? Tell me why you think it's her.
Don't try to get my name tag.
I won't do it. I'm not it.
HyunA, it's not me.
(She hides behind the door to avoid Haha.)
Hey!
HyunA!
Where did she go?
- HyunA. - It's HyunA.
HyunA, it's not me.
- She went inside. - I'm so scared.
HyunA.
- Come out and just talk. - Hey.
This isn't how you play this.
You should still film the show.
- HyunA. - Go away!
I'm not it.
- We won't rip your name tag off. - I know that you're not it.
- I know that you're not it. - Okay.
But it's Han Na.
Why? Tell me why it's her.
- Starting from the opening segment, - Okay.
she kept lying that Kwang Soo was the forbidden animal.
I wasn't lying. Kwang Soo seemed suspicious.
Actually, she's a terrible detective.
- Haha. - Everyone knows how awful she is.
Haha, you need to be careful.
You might get eliminated if you let your guard down.
Come out and talk to us. We won't rip off your name tag.
Let's just talk.
- Haha. - Listen.
See? Han Na is totally obsessing over me.
Right?
(How did the conversation get to this point?)
- I can't believe this. - Why is HyunA hiding?
HyunA, you won't really die from it. So come on out.
Kwang Soo, eliminate Han Na first!
(Speechless)
- I mean... - You're not going to die.
- Don't get into the role too much. - Let's talk once you come out.
- This isn't a movie or a drama. - I mean...
- Please. That's not it. - Why do you think it's Han Na?
- Tell me once HyunA is out. - Please Haha.
Please believe me.
HyunA, Han Na is gone.
What are you doing there? Why are you hiding there?
No, if I'm eliminated,
I won't get any airtime on the show.
Hey, we're not playing mafia. We're not it.
- Did Han Na leave? - Yes. She left.
(She unlocks the door.)
- She left. - What's happening?
- No, get up. - You don't have to go that far.
- She left. - She really left.
- Did you get her name tag? - No, we didn't.
Why didn't you remove her name tag?
There's no definite proof.
- If she's not it... - I'm 100 percent sure.
My gut tells me she is it.
I don't think you're good at these games.
This is your first time playing it.
I'm serious.
You weren't good at the game with the tray.
There's nothing to talk about with these two fools.
- In my opinion, HyunA... - HyunA.
- She's a prime suspect now. - She wasn't on my suspect list.
Same here. But she just got on my list.
(HyunA is on their suspect list.)
- Are you suspecting me now? - Yes.
You don't want to talk to me, right?
HyunA.
(Communication is cut off.)
- It's been a while, right? - Seriously.
It's been a while since someone locked the door.
It's been a while since I got goosebumps during a race.
This just brought back old memories. I'm thinking about the old days.
HyunA.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Where are you going?
Over there.
To find a hint?
(Dashing)
What is it? What?
What is it?
(Where did Kwang Soo rush to?)
As for the library,
everyone will get one chance to enter.
If you win the mission against the mission-keeper,
you will get a hint about the forbidden animals.
- Wait, this place is... Hello. - Hi.
- I'm Onda of EVERGLOW. - Hello.
- Hello. - You're in EVERGLOW too.
- You'll play a game with me today. - Okay.
You can choose a book.
This is completely random.
(This is completely random.)
Did you choose one?
I chose...
this book.
This game might be about how many people are on a page.
It's very likely that it might be that game.
"Winning" by Jack Welch.
(Kwang Soo chose a book as he wishes for a win.)
- So you can win? - Yes.
(He draws a piece of paper to pick a game.)
"Lift the book with your toes. The one that lasts longer wins."
Actually, I have the most powerful toes...
- among the members. - Really?
We played a toe-wrestling match once.
And I won.
(Thick)
(Falling)
This is too heavy for me to lift.
This is like a dumbbell.
(Dropping it again)
(Is his chance of winning getting slim?)
Hold on. I'm sorry. Wait.
- We'll start once you're ready. - Okay.
Wait.
(Getting his toes ready once again)
All right.
(At last)
In 1, 2, 3.
(The game starts.)
(It's a close match.)
Isn't this hard?
Gosh, your toes are really strong.
It hurts so much!
My toe muscles hurt like crazy!
(Why did you choose a thick book?)
I want to give up!
(In the end,)
(he didn't win at all.)
Are you all right?
(His defeat only left him in pain.)
(It hurts so much.)
My gosh, it hurts so much.
(Nice try, Rotten Toenails.)
Since you lost the match, you failed to get the hint.
- Seok Jin, let's go watch the DVD. - Yes. Let's go.
The DVD rental shop is over there.
(That's the DVD rental shop.)
- Hello. - Hi.
(There are movies about 6 animals at the DVD rental shop.)
(They can play a scene of their choice for 1 minute.)
(They'll know if there are forbidden animals in the scene they chose.)
- Rabbit? - How about this? "Rabbit".
- I like it. - Rabbit is written on it.
- "Rabbit". - Yes, let's check that one.
(They'll check So Min whom Han Na is suspecting.)
Okay. Great. Let's go.
(Only one person can enter the DVD rental shop.)
Hello.
Play the scene...
5 minutes and 10 seconds into the movie.
(The movie plays.)
(Like a movie about rabbits, a rabbit shows up on the screen.)
(Totally focused)
(She gets to play the movie only for 1 minute.)
(She's taking notes in case she misses anything.)
(Meanwhile)
Is this it?
Yes, that was it.
You'll get the result now.
(She'll find out if forbidden animals are in the scene she chose.)
(If the forbidden animals came up in the movie, she'll get an O.)
(If the forbidden animals weren't in the movie, she'll get an X.)
(Did the forbidden animals show up in the movie?)
(What is the result? Why is Han Na so surprised?)
Let's shake hands then.
You're really not it. I won't suspect you.
(Is the forbidden animal in Team Rabbit?)
It's really not me either.
Han Na.
It looks like you got a hint.
You got it, right?
(Were the forbidden animals in the movie or not?)
- This is very odd. - What is it? Tell me...
about the forbidden animals.
The screen showed me an O, so the forbidden animals...
were in the movie.
- It was an O? - Yes.
- Then, it's in Team Rabbit. - It's in Team Rabbit.
Then, between So Min and Haha...
It's either So Min or Haha. But I don't t think it's Haha.
- Okay. - Okay.
Someone in Team Rabbit is definitely it.
One of them has to be in Team Rabbit.
(They are certain of it.)
Han Na.
- Aren't you it? - Me?
(She meets other animals in front of the DVD rental shop.)
One of them is in Team Rabbit.
I just got it from the DVD.
- You saw a rabbit? - I did.
What did it say?
I watched "Peter Rabbit".
It said that the forbidden animal was in the movie.
- It's in Team Rabbit. - Team Rabbit.
I'm certain that it's either So Min or Haha.
Since we watched "Peter Rabbit", watch something else.
- Yes, we should. - Watch something else.
(Or could it be that both of them are the forbidden animals?)
- We have to eliminate them, right? - No way.
(Team Fox comes up to the 2nd floor with suspicion against Team Rabbit.)
Hey.
- Then, it must be So Min. - Hey.
- Did you check? - I figured out everything.
What is it?
(What did he figure out?)
I can tell Kwang Soo.
- Seok Jin, tell me. - I can't tell you.
- We found out something great. - I'm in Team Rabbit.
- What is it? - We should suspect Team Rabbit.
- Did you watch the DVD? - Yes, we did.
- Haha. - I'm in Team Rabbit.
I know that.
It must be So Min, right?
- You're on the suspect list. - Does it mean it's not in Team Fox?
We watched "Peter Rabbit".
I sounded like a detective again.
- Wait. Did you watch it together? - Tell us.
- I heard it from her. - That's mine.
But how could you trust her?
She's trustworthy.
Look at her face. She won't lie.
- Seriously? - I actually suspected Seok Jin,
but foxes weren't in the movie.
- Right. - But it was for the rabbits.
- What do you think, Haha? - It was for the rabbits.
- Someone from Team Rabbit? - Tell us.
- It's either you or So Min. - Tell us.
- All right. - Just share a comment.
It's either you or So Min.
(Meanwhile)
Se Chan...
(So Min is observing the other animals' whereabouts.)
(What is So Min doing?)
Everyone, remove my name tag.
- We can't. We can't do that. - Let's all get eliminated.
- We can't. We're not sure. - I think it's So Min.
All right, then. I can...
- Tell us that you're not it. - Tell us what you think.
(Tell us that you're not it if you feel wronged.)
I'll show you with my actions.
I'll go and eliminate So Min.
- Really? - Yes. You'll trust me then, right?
- Okay. - Then, catch her for me.
- Catch So Min? - Catch So Min?
- Must we help you that much? - It's not that.
- A long time ago... - You can't do it yourself?
That was so weird.
- It was. - We should eliminate him.
- Hey. - What were you talking about?
They were going to lure us in and then eliminate us.
- Do you need our help? - That's not it.
- That's ridiculous. - No.
- Is it both of you? - To be honest,
So Min is not an easy match.
(Is he a forbidden animal?)
It's definitely not me.
I'll prove it to you by eliminating her.
- All right. It's 1 of you 2. - It's either you or her.
Since it isn't me, it's her.
- Okay. - Keep him in check.
(Haha looks for So Min.)
I told them that it's not me.
Your gaze is so strange.
Let's watch a movie together.
I know you're just luring me in.
Where would I lure you to?
- At the DVD place. - Do I look like a spy?
You're going to eliminate me...
- at the DVD rental shop. - Do I look like Jong Kook to you?
What is this?
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin appear.)
- You're a bit... - It's not me.
- It's not you, right? - It's not me.
- If it's not her, it's you. - Rip hers off.
Eliminate her. It's not me.
I told him it was a rabbit, and he said to eliminate you.
- You said... - Eliminate her.
- I... - Eliminate her first.
You should do it.
Okay.
- Because... - Hold on.
- It's one of you. - It's one of you.
- I swear. - So...
- Then... - So...
- I swear. - Listen to me.
I'll do it.
I'll do it if you think it's a rabbit.
- It's either one of you. - It's not me. Darn it.
- It's not me. - It's not me.
- How dare you? - It's not me.
- Hurry, tear it off. - It is you.
- Why aren't you ripping it? - Why aren't you ripping it?
- Come on. - It's not me.
Does this look natural to you?
- It's not me. - Are you sure?
- It's not me. - It's one of you.
- It's not me. - It's not?
- No. - Then it's you, isn't it?
- No. - Then it's you.
- Eliminate her. - I swear.
- Trust me this once. It's not me. - It's her.
If it isn't you, eliminate your partner.
- Grab her arms! - It's not me.
- It's not me. - Why can't you do it?
- Are you going to do it? - It's not me.
He did it.
- It's not me. - He did it.
- Maybe she's telling the truth. - I told you it's not me.
Show me your back.
- It's not me. - It's not her.
(So Min wasn't a forbidden animal.)
- It wasn't her. - It wasn't her.
- It's not me either. - Haha.
(Does that mean he's a forbidden animal?)
(Han Na watched a rabbit movie.)
(After finishing it...)
(She said rabbits were forbidden animals.)
(According to Han Na,)
(Haha is the forbidden animal.)
It's not her.
(What is his identity?)
(Now, it's 100-percent him.)
- Haha is out. - It's a rabbit.
See? It's not me!
(Haha is eliminated as well.)
- It's not him either? - Why did you say it was us?
- Hold on. - I'll tell you who told us.
Han Na saw the DVD.
(Han Na said that there was an O for rabbits.)
(She announced it to everyone.)
(Everyone believed that rabbits were forbidden animals.)
(However, rabbits weren't forbidden animals.)
(The suspicion falls onto Han Na.)
- Who said it? - Han Na.
- Hold on. - Then she lied?
One team is gone.
(Was she a forbidden animal herself, trying to eliminate the others?)
- Han Na. - My gosh.
(They feel betrayed.)
Gosh, she's so suspicious.
(Seok Jin goes out to find her.)
(At that moment,)
(some people are tailing him.)
(They are following him.)
(Then suddenly,)
(they make a U-turn.)
(After they're gone...)
Seok Jin is out.
- I'm out? - You're out.
I'm out?
(All of a sudden?)
What did I do?
(Someone has shot his name tag.)
(He has no idea why he's out.)
Was it because I looked back?
Seok Jin is out. Seok Jin is out.
- He's out? - The forbidden animals...
have eliminated him.
The forbidden animals got him?
Seok Jin is out.
I'm so shocked.
There is a closed area.
(If any animals are eliminated by the forbidden animals,)
(that area will be closed off.)
(If both feet go inside, they're eliminated.)
(Did Han Na eliminate Seok Jin?)
(Team Rabbit, Team Fox, and Team Pig were candidates.)
(As of now, Team Pig and Han Na from Team Fox are alive.)
I'll pick pig.
(Gook Ju wants to confirm Team Pig.)
Hello.
(The 1-minute movie begins.)
(A pig appears.)
(Only a small piglet is seen.)
(The movie is over.)
There's no O or X? It's done?
(No way!)
(There aren't any forbidden animals in Team Pig?)
Gook Ju.
- What is it? - My gosh.
What is it?
The pigs aren't it.
(Shocked)
- What? - The pigs aren't it.
There was an X.
(She clearly saw it.)
Hold on.
(What is going on?)
(There are 2 forbidden animals.)
(The first hint said...)
(that the forbidden animals lived in groups.)
(They made a list of animals who lived in groups.)
(However, they didn't have proof.)
(They agreed that pigs, foxes, and rabbits lived in groups.)
(That's how these candidates were formed.)
(Seok Jin, Haha, and So Min have been eliminated.)
(If it's not Team Pig,)
(that means it's Han Na.)
(But there are two forbidden animals.)
Why?
Doesn't this mean we should suspect those...
who don't live in groups?
But think about this.
Because of that first hint,
we've only been suspecting those three teams.
- Right. Let's not do that. - But I think...
we should suspect the other teams as well.
- We should check their DVDs too. - Then I want you guys...
to watch our movie.
(Gook Ju from Team Tiger makes a suggestion.)
- Kwang Soo is suspicious. - Team Tiger?
(Kwang Soo was awfully quiet today.)
That's not true.
(They started suspecting him.)
(Even Gook Ju was suspicious of him.)
(Could Gook Ju be right?)
- That's not a bad idea. - Just trust me.
- That's not a bad idea. - I won't check.
- I won't. - You should check then.
- Tiger. - Tiger.
- Who will check? - I will.
- Enjoy. - I won't take long.
(Will they be able to narrow down the forbidden animals?)
20 minutes and 40 seconds in.
(He picks his timestamp.)
- I'll play it now. - It's playing.
(The movie begins.)
(It's a movie scene with hunters and a tiger.)
(Focused)
(A small animal is spotted in front of the tiger.)
The tiger cub is dead.
(The movie ends.)
That's it?
Please check the box.
Where is it?
(Is it an O or an X?)
O? O?
(It's an O.)
(The tiger movie showed an O.)
O?
(Does this mean either Kwang Soo or Gook Ju is a forbidden animal?)
(Shocked)
- Jae Seok. - Did you check?
- This makes no sense. - Why not?
- It's an O. - Really?
I told you! It's Kwang Soo!
Really?
- It's an O? - Yes.
(Their doubts have been confirmed.)
It's Kwang Soo.
It's him.
This is driving me crazy.
Should we just eliminate him?
Should we?
It's an O?
(Kwang Soo...)
(and Han Na are the strong candidates.)
It's definitely him.
(She's determined to eliminate him.)
Let's eliminate Kwang Soo.
It's not you, right?
- No, it's definitely not me. Wait. - Right?
(He spots Kwang Soo from afar.)
(Flinching)
(Maybe he will believe me.)
I'll eliminate him.
- What? - Grab him for me, I'll do it.
- You trust me, right? - Really?
You do, right? You grab him, and I'll rip it off.
- You'll rip it? - Yes.
(He decides to trust her.)
- Se Chan. - Yes?
- If you're right, - Go on.
it's either Kwang Soo or Gook Ju.
(He senses danger and leaves the scene.)
- Look! He's running away! - He's running.
See?
(Catch him!)
He's running.
(Sprinting)
Hey!
Come here!
(Stop right there!)
Come here! He's running away!
- Catch him! - It's not me!
- Stop there! - It's not me!
He's running away!
My gosh!
Hurry up!
(Staggering)
(She falls down.)
(It's humiliating.)
Gook Ju, come on.
Gook Ju. Gook Ju.
I'm done for.
(Jong Kook, go on without me.)
(It's too cold to lie down here.)
- I'm done for. - Gook Ju.
(She finds it funny too.)
- Are you okay? - Hey.
I must be really unfit.
- Hey. - I collapsed.
You wiped the floor...
as you fell.
(She realizes the importance of working out.)
Gook Ju.
I think it's Kwang Soo.
(They're 100-percent sure since he ran away.)
(Kwang Soo successfully runs away.)
(Did he run away because he was a forbidden animal?)
Let me explain.
Among the candidates,
I am the most suspicious of Han Na.
Many people are suspicious of her.
So we should watch her movie.
- She's a fox. - She's a fox, right?
"The Fox and the Child".
- "The Fox and the Child". - "The Fox and the Child".
(Sihyeon will be the one watching.)
I'll watch from 11 minutes and 55 seconds.
Once she comes out, I'll hear the result.
And then...
(If there's an O, Han Na is definitely a forbidden animal.)
I'll share the info with the others.
(She begins watching.)
(Of course, a fox appears.)
(Will other animals appear too?)
(Only a fox appears...)
(And her minute is up.)
Okay.
(Will it be an O or an X?)
(If it is an O,)
(then Han Na is a forbidden animal.)
(What?)
(It's an X!)
(The fox isn't a forbidden animal?)
(Flustered)
(What is going on?)
No...
We're in trouble.
- What? - No way.
- It's all right. - We're in trouble.
- What did you watch? - I got an X.
Hold on a second.
(The fox isn't the forbidden animal?)
See what I mean? I said it wasn't the rabbit.
(Why did Han Na lie about the rabbit video getting an O?)
(Han Na watched a video of a rabbit earlier.)
(What Han Na watched got an O.)
(She thought that the rabbit was the forbidden animal.)
(She told the truth.)
(Han Na didn't lie. She told the truth!)
- It's not me. - It's not her.
(Then why wasn't one of the rabbits a forbidden animal?)
(What on earth is going on?)
I said it wasn't the rabbit.
(They're all confused.)
I'm going to leave.
- Where? - Even you seem suspicious.
- What's going on? - I'm so confused.
Hear me out.
(If the fox isn't the forbidden animal,)
(then which of the nine is?)
I should watch a DVD, so where's HyunA?
Why does she keep avoiding me?
Can't I watch this by myself?
You can't.
(The couple must be present even if only one can enter.)
My partner has to be here? Where do I find her?
Jae Seok is the forbidden animal!
(HyunA's still filming another show on her own.)
Please save me.
(HyunA's solo drama)
(On high alert)
Don't breathe so loudly.
(She's too absorbed in the game.)
I should watch a DVD, so where's HyunA?
(HyunA, where are you?)
(At that moment!)
Hold on.
(Jae Seok gazes at the posters.)
(He keeps looking at them for quite a while.)
(Gazing)
(Which poster caught Jae Seok's attention?)
(DVD rental shop)
(Is he looking at me?)
(After gazing at the posters for a while...)
Where do I find HyunA?
(He leaves to look for HyunA.)
- Ji Hyo. - Gosh, you startled me.
- What were you up to? - I...
I was just looking at my phone.
Why on earth is HyunA avoiding me?
She's been running from everyone.
(She's been running from everyone.)
My gosh.
(She lets out a weird scream.)
(HyunA keeps running around screaming.)
My gosh. Where is she?
We talked about her,
and it seems like she's filming another show.
We need to watch this, so where is she?
Can you find her for me?
- I'll tell her if I see her. - Tell me if you see her.
- Let me know as well. - Sure.
(Where did she go?)
HyunA!
HyunA, you can't go there.
(He spots HyunA who's been wandering around.)
(She hides from him before asking why.)
You can talk to me from there.
HyunA.
Talk to me from up there.
This is important. We must watch this DVD...
if we want to catch the forbidden animal.
We both need to be present for this.
Why is it that...
- He's smiling. - your teeth show...
when you smile?
(Why are your teeth showing?)
What?
(HyunA finds his protruding teeth suspicious.)
Why do my teeth show when I smile?
My mouth has always been sticking out.
You've got it all wrong.
Anyway, HyunA, just join me this once.
It's how we can solve this problem.
We need to watch a DVD.
- Okay. - Come on.
Are you sure...
Of course. Would I be asking you if I was a forbidden animal?
Just join me for a second.
Hurry. Join me downstairs.
HyunA.
Good, you're here.
- HyunA, don't go anywhere. - Why?
We need to watch the DVD.
You watch it.
All right, just come over here.
- You can watch it. - Okay.
- We're both here. - Right.
I'll watch a DVD then.
(He carefully chooses the DVD he'll watch.)
What are you going to watch?
Which one should I watch?
(Choosing the right DVD is key.)
(He can only enter once, so he's contemplating.)
(Let me tell you about the DVD once again.)
(The video will play for a minute.)
(If the animal shows up, an O will light up.)
(If not, you'll see an X.)
(Which animals show up is key.)
(An O could light up because of another animal that shows up.)
I'll check the tiger.
(But that already got an O.)
- I watched that. - I need to be sure.
Just because you saw a tiger, doesn't mean that it's...
the forbidden animal.
Then what...
Since the DVD showed an O,
I'm going to check again.
If another animal...
appeared on the DVD, then it might not be the tiger.
Stay here. I'll check the DVD.
(He decides to check the tiger DVD again.)
All right.
Here's "A Tiger's Tail".
(If another animal doesn't show up,)
(then the tiger is a forbidden animal.)
(The 1-minute-video plays.)
There's a tiger.
(Highly focused)
A dog?
(A tiger appears and so does a dog.)
(Only a tiger and a dog can be seen.)
A dog isn't part of the race.
O or X, which is it?
(The video has stopped playing.)
(Now it's time for the verdict.)
(Only a tiger and a dog appeared during the minute.)
(What's the verdict?)
X?
(It's now an X!)
(In the tiger video that Se Chan watched,)
(the forbidden animal had appeared.)
(The screen now shows an X.)
(What's going on?)
Guys!
(On guard)
I just got goosebumps.
Goosebumps? Why?
All I saw were a tiger and a dog.
The screen showed an X.
(The tiger has been cleared from suspicion.)
Then it's not the tiger?
The earlier tiger video showed an O.
Hold on. I got the chills.
Is it the tiger then?
No, it means that it's not the tiger.
Then why did an O appear with the other video?
This is really important.
(He calls Se Chan to confirm it.)
Yes, Jae Seok.
Didn't you watch "The Tiger" earlier?
- Yes. - I just watched a video...
that featured a tiger and a dog. It showed an X.
An X?
That means the tiger isn't a forbidden animal.
What did you see when you watched "The Tiger"?
A lot of hunters,
a tiger,
and a baby tiger on the ground.
Hold on a second. Okay, hold on.
What? Why? Hello?
(What? Why?)
He just asked me for an answer and then hung up on me.
- He watched a tiger video, right? - Yes, but it showed an X.
Meanwhile, the video you saw showed an O.
What's going on then?
I watched "Peter Rabbit" and there was a rabbit.
What did you see?
A rabbit. Look.
I saw this rabbit in the blue vest.
He's on the tomato field and one gets crushed by a trap.
It's a rabbit.
- This got an O? - Yes.
And all you saw were rabbits?
Rabbits, tomatoes, a trap,
a tractor, and a man.
(The videos Se Chan and Han Na saw both got an O.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E477 Running Man
"Mysterious Animal Farm Race: I Can Hear Your Cries"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(DVD rental shop)
(Suspicious posters on the wall)
(Jae Seok notices something.)
- Han Na. - Yes?
(Han Na!)
It's a person.
(Out of the blue?)
A person?
But we're supposed to be animals.
A person.
(Jae Seok points to the posters.)
A person. Human. That's it.
Humans are animals too.
Check out the red letters.
Right?
(Person, Human)
- What does it mean? - They all had people in it.
It's not an animal, but a human.
- So there's a human among us? - A human!
There are two humans among us.
(Humans also live in packs too.)
Humans were the ones who killed the animals.
There are humans among us.
We must find the humans, but in what way?
- Guys. - Yes?
- Jae Seok. - We have humans among us.
- What? - Humans?
(What is he talking about?)
Humans.
- What are you saying? - Humans?
- Yes, Kwang Soo. - Humans?
Wait, humans are animals too.
- That's right. - So we're looking for a person.
Who can it be then?
That I can't tell.
Let's look around...
and search for more clues.
I will.
Wait.
Kwang Soo, come over here.
Guys, Se Chan, Gook Ju, hear me out.
I came back on my own accord.
- Kwang Soo. - I was suffering, you know.
Hear me out.
Kwang Soo.
Humans are animals too.
(He's trying to comprehend the information.)
You look like you know what he's talking about.
What are you saying?
Humans are animals too.
The forbidden animal could also be a person...
because humans are animals too.
- So in a broader meaning? - Finally.
The DVDs they watched...
- all had people in them. - Right.
That's why it showed an O which means you're not it.
I'm sorry.
(Kwang Soo lets out his anger.)
- All day long... - I'm sorry.
I've been chased all day.
Every time I looked for a hint, I was chased.
(I told you I was innocent.)
The DVD rental shop and the library are closed now.
- Jae Seok... - Where's Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo is innocent.
- Kwang Soo is innocent. - The tiger is innocent.
Ji Hyo, are you sure you're innocent?
I'm innocent.
I swear.
- I don't even have any hints. - Are you...
the forbidden one?
(Since there aren't enough hints, everyone suspects everyone.)
Are you a forbidden one?
- Are you sure you aren't? - I'm not.
Gosh.
(Jae Seok is looking for hints about humans.)
She's still here?
(Onda is still in the closed library.)
Why...
(She's sitting still.)
(Why is she still here?)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(Yiren is still at the DVD rental shop.)
Yiren is here too.
(I'm still here.)
(The announcement said the shop was closed.)
Is anyone watching a DVD right now?
No one is.
Why are you still here?
I just saw...
Onda at the library.
- And you're still here too. - Yes.
(Does she have something left to do?)
You have a name tag on your back.
(She has a name tag on her back.)
I know nothing.
- I have no idea. - Yiren...
(Why would she need a name tag?)
Hi.
Hey! What are you doing here?
Are you a member of EVERGLOW?
- Yes. - That's right.
You have a name tag.
Why do you have one?
Go upstairs.
- Why does she have a name tag? - What?
Also,
why would she not tell me who she is?
Really?
(Strangely, she's still standing...)
(at the closed shop.)
Excuse me.
(Jae Seok checks the name tag on her back.)
- May I rip it off? - Yes.
Go ahead.
(Na 2-1?)
(He finds mysterious letters on her back.)
Na 2-1?
What does this mean?
- Do you know what it means? - No.
I have no idea.
Wait.
Na 2-1?
Let me see.
The two must have the hints.
- You're still here. - Hi. Yes.
Just a second, Onda.
Hold on. What does it say?
Ga 8-1?
(Ga 8-1?)
(What do these letters on their backs mean?)
(Onda and Yiren were holding mysterious hints.)
(After seeing the letters, Jae Seok looks around.)
(He notices something on the bookshelves.)
Excuse me.
(The letters in the hints are written on the bookshelves.)
I'm sorry. Ga 8-1?
(He locates the letters from the hints.)
Ga 8-1.
(He finds a mysterious book...)
(at the location Ga 8-1.)
And then Na 2-1.
(He finds another book at the location Na 2-1.)
What's this?
(He found two books following the hints.)
I got goosebumps.
Let me see. Just a second.
(He opens the book.)
"The bear that became a woman was called Ungnyeo."
(The bear that became a woman was called Ungnyeo.)
Who's a bear?
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo are bears.)
"The bear that became a woman was called Ungnyeo."
(The bear that became a woman?)
It's Ji Hyo.
(Is the bear that became a woman Ji Hyo?)
(Jae Seok opens the other book hurriedly.)
"The sister turned into a fox"?
Who's a fox?
(The sister turned into a fox?)
(Seok Jin and Han Na are foxes.)
(Seok Jin is already eliminated.)
(That leaves Han Na.)
Han Na?
Is it Ji Hyo and Han Na?
(Are Ji Hyo and Han Na the forbidden animals, humans?)
(Is Jae Seok's guess right?)
Han Na, did you take any notes?
I did, but they're useless.
They're all useless.
(Just then)
(Ji Hyo pushes HyunA and Sihyeon into the closed area.)
HyunA and Sihyeon,
who are animals, are out.
- But my name tag is still there. - Mine too.
You stepped into the closed area, so you're out.
(When both feet of an animal get into the area, the animal is out.)
(I can't believe this.)
We promised we'd survive a long time.
(HyunA and Sihyeon got into the closed area and got eliminated.)
What do we do?
(I'm sorry, girls.)
(Han Na and Ji Hyo are the humans.)
Six pairs of animals will participate in today's race,
Mysterious Animal Farm.
You two are descendants of the forbidden animals,
who destroyed the farm decades ago.
The forbidden animals?
As you're forbidden animals,
you need to hide your identities.
Ji Hyo will pretend to be a brown bear.
- A brown bear is very strong. - A brown bear.
It can attack people.
I think it suits me.
- Han Na is an Arctic fox. - An Arctic fox?
I should have been an Arctic fox.
- You think so? - I should have been one.
To get your true identities back, you need to carry out...
hidden missions...
before the final race without getting caught.
Here's Ji Hyo's mission.
As bears are associated with paws,
she'll put a mini name tag...
on her partner's shoe.
(Ji Hyo put a name tag on Se Chan's shoe successfully.)
Han Na is an Arctic fox.
As foxes are associated with tails,
she'll kick her partner in the bottom once.
(Han Na accomplished her mission too.)
You forbidden animals...
successfully carried out your hidden mission.
Let me tell you your true identities.
The brown bear, Ji Hyo, and the Arctic fox, Han Na,
are, in fact, humans.
One of you will hand over a plastic item...
to a member to be eliminated.
When the other shoots the member's name tag...
with a water gun, that member is out.
It makes me sad.
Considering the environmental issues these days...
That's our intention.
That's the real theme.
I can't believe we'll be playing such evil roles.
(Han Na watched the DVD with her partner, Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin drank from Han Na's plastic bottle unsuspectingly.)
(Han Na informs Ji Hyo of the situation.)
I got a text from Han Na.
(Shoot Seok Jin with a water gun.)
Have you found anything?
It's confusing. It's not going well.
Where's Han Na?
(When Seok Jin's back was turned to her,)
(Ji Hyo snuck up to him...)
(and shot him with a water gun.)
(Seok Jin was eliminated without anyone knowing.)
I'm sorry, Seok Jin.
I'm sorry.
(The humans, Han Na and Ji Hyo, have been eliminating animals.)
Ji Hyo and Han Na.
I have to find them.
(Jae Seok hurries down the stairs.)
Han Na.
- Han Na. - Yes?
- Where's everybody? - Why do you ask?
(Han Na backs off.)
(Jae Seok approaches Han Na.)
What's going on?
(The moment both his feet are inside the lines, he's out.)
Do you think I'm a forbidden animal?
(Glancing)
(Han Na has almost led Jae Seok into the closed area.)
What's this?
(Jae Seok notices it and steps back.)
Han Na.
(What a shame.)
(Just then)
Ji Hyo!
(Ji Hyo appears from the back.)
(She shoots Jae Seok's name tag and disappears.)
Ji Hyo! A water gun?
Did I get him?
(Jae Seok hasn't touched a plastic item yet.)
- Was he hit? - Hey!
Hey, Jong Kook!
(Dodging)
(A plastic water bottle is thrown at him.)
Jong Kook!
What?
It's Han Na and Ji Hyo!
Who?
- Han Na and Ji Hyo? - Who?
Han Na and Ji Hyo?
Do you have any plastic items?
Over there. I'll get it.
Hey, it's Han Na and Ji Hyo. Come here.
Are you sure?
(The failed operation puts the humans in danger.)
They just tried to shoot me with a water gun.
- Really? - Yes.
- They tried to shoot you? - There must be something.
But I don't know what it is.
- You got shot. - You did.
Yes, but there must be something else.
I think they both have to do something.
(A human approaches.)
Please check if I'm shot too.
- You're not shot. What about me? - You're fine.
They both have to do something.
(A plastic bottle is thrown...)
(and hits Jae Seok.)
What?
(Han Na threw a bottle at Jae Seok.)
I think she did that because she's angry.
- She's just angry. - She hates you.
She hates you.
(Jae Seok is out.)
- Jae Seok is out. - You're out.
Guys.
Let's rip her name tag off.
(I hit him.)
They both have to do something to eliminate someone.
- Do you get it? - One by one...
We're clear. Let's go.
- Han Na! - Han Na!
(Let's go get the forbidden animals, the humans!)
- Let's finish them. - Where's Kwang Soo?
- What's going on? - Let's finish them.
Kwang Soo. Hurry up. It's Han Na.
It's Han Na and Ji Hyo. Hurry up.
Han Na.
(Ji Hyo was watching the situation.)
- Where is Kwang Soo? - Han Na.
Kwang Soo.
It's Han Na and Ji Hyo. Hurry up.
Kwang Soo, let's hurry up.
(She aims for Kwang Soo's back.)
Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo, be careful!)
Kwang Soo.
(She succeeds hitting his name tag.)
- Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo. - What?
You are out if Han Na hits you with a plastic bottle.
- A plastic bottle? - Beware of a plastic bottle.
You understood, right?
- Yes. - Beware of a plastic bottle.
Kwang Soo got hit by a water gun, so he is out.
Hold on. He didn't get hit by a water bottle.
- He got hit by a water gun. - We need to take them out.
When did you get hit by a water bottle?
Did I get hit by a water bottle?
(When did Kwang Soo come in contact with a plastic item?)
I want to share what I have. Would you take a look?
- What is it? - Take a look.
(Han Na handed over her notebook to Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo's hand touched the spiral bind of the notebook.)
Take a look.
(The spiral of the notebook was plastic.)
(I got him!)
Kwang Soo, let's go.
Am I out?
Kwang Soo, who is an animal, is out.
- I told you they were suspicious. - Ji Hyo was suspicious.
I told you they were suspicious. I told you Ji Hyo is suspicious.
What should we do?
(The forbidden animals formulate a plan.)
Let's get Jong Kook first.
- Let's do that together. - Yes.
We just need to shoot his name tag with a water gun. I will lure him.
(He already touched plastic.)
Let me see your guesses.
(Jong Kook touched the plastic spiral.)
(Jong Kook will be out once he gets hit with a water gun.)
(They will take out the others with plastic spoons.)
(Let's come from behind and win.)
Let's go.
(The forbidden animals approach the remaining survivors.)
They are here.
(Wary)
(It's the humans versus...)
(the animals.)
Be careful. I don't think that will take me out.
- It's the water gun. - It's the water gun.
(The plastic and water gun take out an animal.)
(At that moment)
Hurry up and come here.
(Jong Kook attacks Ji Hyo.)
(Ji Hyo's water gun aims at Jong Kook's name tag.)
(If Jong Kook is out, it will be 2 against 2.)
(The Strong One versus The Sniper)
(What will be the result of the final showdown?)
(If Jong Kook is out, it will be 2 against 2.)
(The Strong One versus The Sniper)
The race has ended.
(The race ends with the result shrouded in mystery.)
In today's race,
the forbidden animals who destroyed the farm...
and took out other animals...
were humans.
My goodness.
- Humans are animals too. - That's right.
I was so startled.
Plastic represents environmental pollution.
Plastic and dirty water.
- Pollution and... - The destruction of the ecosystem.
Humans kill animals.
- That's what... - During the race,
the place where the animals died became closed off.
It shows how humans encroach on animals' habitats.
(Animals lose their habitats due to mindless development.)
It's sad.
So who won today? I am curious.
I don't know the result because I was in prison.
The winner of today's race is...
(Team Humans...)
(versus Team Animals with 3 members)
(Which team won?)
Team Animals.
- Did we win? - Did we win?
(Team Animals won.)
- We won. - Really?
(We won.)
(Earlier,)
(Jong Kook grabbed Ji Hyo.)
(Running over)
Rip off her name tag. Hurry up.
(Jong Kook and Gook Ju worked together.)
(Ripping)
(Ji Hyo, who is a human, is out.)
Ji Hyo is out.
- It didn't hit your name tag. - It didn't, right?
(Jong Kook's name tag was clean.)
- It's clean. - Rip off her name tag.
(She was knocked out by Gook Ju.)
Rip off her name tag.
My goodness.
(Ripping)
It's over, Han Na.
(Han Na, the last human, is out.)
My goodness.
That's incredible.
Today, the two humans will suffer the water bomb penalty.
That's clean.
One.
- 2. - 2.
(Let's go.)
- 3. - 3.
(Pouring)
(The cold shower washes away the humans' sins.)
Look at Ji Hyo's hair.
Han Na is great.
(Dancing)
(The Animal Farm Race ends with a dance.)
Are you okay?
(One day 2 weeks later)
- Hello. - Hello.
- It has been a while. - It really has been a while.
I feel like I am back in my hometown.
It has been a while.
On SNS, you really went on a trip.
- That's right. - Seriously.
You really went on a trip.
- But... - He went to Vietnam.
he went to Vietnam.
(Last week's episode)
(So Min said Seok Jin wants to go to the Czech Republic alone.)
(I plan to go alone.)
(He must be having an affair.)
(The rumors spread.)
He really went on a trip.
(He ended up going to Vietnam!)
- But he went... - Seok Jin.
- to Vietnam. - That's right.
Who took those photos?
- You couldn't have taken them. - He went with his wife.
- I went with my wife. - I see.
- I went with my wife... - I knew it.
- in the end. - I told you...
he won't be able to travel alone.
- I thought you had her permission. - Jae Seok has foresight.
- I made that prediction. - Yes.
She asked me if I really plan to go alone.
I said, "Of course not. You can join me if you want."
Then she said, "Okay."
(He had to give up on his plan to go to the Czech Republic.)
- You couldn't turn her down. - I only asked...
to be polite. I only asked to be polite.
She bought two tickets.
Had he insisted on going alone, she would have canceled the trip.
- Seriously. - I had so much fun.
- What was so much fun? - I saw historic sites.
- What did you see? - If you were so happy,
why didn't you post photos you took with your wife?
Seriously. Why did you take the photos alone?
I thought a lot about posting our photos.
On SNS, he seems like...
a single man.
Seriously.
- Well... - You know,
- some men are like that. - That's right.
There are married men who pretend to be single.
Seok Jin, Se Chan cares a lot about you.
- What do you mean? - If you are wearing sunglasses,
- he zooms in on the photo. - Why?
He does it to check if you are with another woman.
I do it just in case. It's a scary thought.
I didn't know you went on a trip with your wife.
So I was like, "Hold on."
- I had to check. - That's right.
I joked about how he must have...
- a mistress. - That's right.
That made many people suspicious.
Many articles about that comment got released.
I was so surprised.
(Thus, "Seok Jin in Crisis" persona came to be.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- It's too much. - What?
(It's too much.)
(Jae Seok suddenly attacks him.)
- His fashion is too much. - Today,
- he dressed up too much. - It's too much.
It's too much.
She dressed up too.
On SNS, I saw how Se Chan used an app...
and got me as a celebrity lookalike.
- He posted it on SNS. - Really?
There were over 2,000 comments.
- Really? - Everyone laughed.
It was particularly upsetting...
because I used the best photo of myself.
- Then I got you. - Yes.
- I used that app too. - Who did you get?
- I haven't used that app. - I buried it in fear of backlash.
- Who did you get? - Who did you get?
(Who did he get?)
Who did you get?
I got Leonardo DiCaprio.
For goodness' sake.
(That kind of nonsense will make the Titanic take a U-turn.)
- I am serious. - Get out of my face.
I could show you.
I am serious. I could show you.
- Stop talking nonsense. - I am serious.
(I will show mine too.)
Look at this. I got...
- Beenzino. - What?
(Your celebrity lookalike is Beenzino.)
(This is ridiculous.)
You got Park Joon Hyung too.
(Here comes Park Joon Hyung.)
Hold on. You got Park Joon Hyung too.
Let me see.
- What is wrong with him? - You got Park Joon Hyung too.
What is wrong with him?
He got Park Joon Hyung too.
For goodness' sake.
Before I dive into the explanation,
let me tell you that there are guests...
on standby.
Let's bring them in.
Who are they?
(Who are the guests?)
- Who are they? - Who are they?
Gosh, it has been a while.
- Eun Su. - My goodness.
(The competitive one, Seo Eun Su and the rising star, Choi Ri)
(She can pull off a dialect.)
(Seo Eun Su is a unique actress with many charms.)
(On Running Man, she was the queen of competition.)
- My goodness. - No, no.
(Choi Ri is a newly debuted actress...)
(with incredible acting skills and cheerful charms.)
Eun Su.
It has been a while.
- Hello. - It has been a while. Hello.
- Hello. - It's her.
(Did we get female guests only?)
Actually, there are two more guests.
So Min and Ji Hyo always get disappointed...
when they are female guests only.
- So Min. - There are male guests.
- Why is it necessary? - So Min is happy.
We have these two already. Why do we need more?
- Ji Hyo. - Let's invite...
- the remaining two guests. - All right.
It's been a long time since we had new faces. I'm glad.
It's been a long time since we had male guests.
- It's Kyeong Hwan. - Look at that guy.
Jinyoung is here too.
(Heo Kyeong Hwan is a handsome comedian with a nice body.)
(He recently formed Maheun Five which is a band.)
(Jinyoung of GOT7 captured every woman's heart.)
(I don't know where to look.)
(So Min was all fidgety because of him.)
(She's blushing.)
(She's had a crush on him since then.)
- I was like doing this. - Doing this.
- Jinyoung. - Hello.
- Please welcome me too. - Hello.
Kyeong Hwan is here.
(What am I going to do?)
It's so good to see you too.
It's Jinyoung.
Kyeong Hwan is here.
Gosh, it's Jinyoung.
- Why? Do you like him? - Yes, when he came last time.
Hello, owner of a wood-fired pizza place.
- Hello. - What's wrong, So Min?
- So Min. - She's shy because of Jinyoung.
- Don't worry about her. - She really likes him.
Go to the middle.
- We have to switch spots. - She keeps on whispering,
"He's handsome."
- Stand next to him. - This is our second time meeting.
When we first met, we took a picture.
Are you on a date with Ji Hyo right now?
- No. - Why are you so close to her?
You never link arms with Ji Hyo.
Why are you linking your arms with hers?
- She's shy, so she hid behind me. - Why is she doing that?
You want to link arms with him, but you settled with her.
- Kyeong Hwan. - Kyeong Hwan.
You sound so impatient.
Are you a middle-aged man walking through the neighborhood?
Are your hands inside your pockets or not?
Were you supposed to go on the radio and came here instead?
I'm considering whether to put my hands inside my pockets or not.
You are dressed for the radio.
Let me give some brief introductions.
- I'm happy to see them. - Eun Su.
Nice to meet you.
When she came last time, she showed us the insider dance.
That's right.
- I remember. - It was the alien dance.
- This dance. - I did the alien dance.
I was waiting for it, but it got edited out.
I was pretty upset.
It got edited out?
- Why did you edit it out? - That's the producer who did it.
(My bad.)
- That time, - Gook Ju's chair dance.
- Gook Ju was too intense. - The chair sank.
Right.
(Gook Ju did the chair dance.)
(She's back on the show after 5 minutes.)
(She tried to lift her leg.)
(Swaying)
(The chair sank into the ground.)
(Gook Ju got all the attention, and Eun Su's alien dance evaporated.)
- They usually don't omit stuff. - Right?
Maybe it was really bad.
In order to redeem herself, she prepared another dance.
(It's time for Eun Su's dance to redeem herself.)
Can we see it?
- Now? - Yes, now.
- As soon as I got here. - When then?
- You have to overcome it. - I have to. I'll overcome this.
- You have to overcome it. - I'll overcome this.
Do you see this? They are going to watch you dance...
with their arms crossed.
We're the judges.
We don't clap for everybody.
We are frank.
- Be quiet. - What?
Be quiet.
- Be quiet. - I said one thing.
Kwang Soo keep your voice down.
- Eun Su. - I didn't want to be edited out,
- so I prepared extra hard. - I see.
Let's watch Eun Su. Please give her a round of applause.
All right.
- Ready? - What's this?
- What's with the corduroy shirt? - She prepared a lot.
(She takes her jacket off.)
Top and bottom.
I haven't seen a corduroy top and bottom in a while.
Eun Su looks nice in it.
She's determined.
Do you know the dance moves perfectly?
- I think she took lessons. - Yesterday,
- I went to a dance academy. - A dance academy?
- A dance academy. - I took a last-minute lesson.
(I took lessons too.)
Let's watch. Please take a few steps back.
This is our dance.
(Eun Su's new dance time to redeem for the last time.)
- I don't hear it. - Is it the same?
(Turning)
(Her gesture is provocative.)
- I like her facial expression. - She prepared this.
It looks like she took lessons.
Hold on.
(Wriggling)
(She shows off the tadpole dance with determination.)
(What is that?)
Goodness.
(The song changes.)
(She's full of energy.)
What?
- Why are you doing this? - Eun Su.
What's wrong?
(She shows a strange movement.)
- Why are you doing this? - Eun Su.
- What's wrong? - Why are you doing this?
Was this necessary?
Look.
- Is she dead? - What's wrong?
Is she dead?
- Is she dead? - Was this necessary?
What's wrong?
- She's alive. - What are you doing?
She's alive.
- Be quiet. - She shushed us.
She's a good dancer.
(She finishes off with a hot dance.)
Stop it.
- Stop it. - You're good.
You can finish, Eun Su.
(She's not done yet.)
(This is the real end.)
All right.
She's good.
She's good, but something's funny.
I've never seen anybody try so hard.
- Give her a round of applause. - Thank you.
She tried hard.
Eun Su is ambitious.
I thought she was going to be shy, but when we got close,
she shushed us. She had to focus on dancing.
I couldn't hear the music well.
- I see. - She's good.
Choi Ri, why did you copy her dance?
I got excited.
- Really? - She couldn't stay still.
(She got excited.)
Are you a good dancer?
Do you want some music?
- I... - Freestyle dance?
Freestyle?
- I prepared... - You did?
- a Korean dance. - You can do whatever.
- Try it. - Korean dance.
I'll be dancing to IU's song.
- Really? - She prepared something.
- How does this go? - You have to...
I'll do it.
- Go away. - Are you her boyfriend?
I'm not.
(Are you her boyfriend?)
(So Min pulls him back in anger.)
(Waddling back)
- He was worried... - Come here.
- I was stealing his time. - Don't do it. Come back.
You were all the way back there.
They...
- gave it to me. - I lost a camera shot.
- He told me to move. - Hey.
You never help me with anything.
- Do something then. - You never do.
- You're wrong. - So Min is...
So Min is actually not interested in you.
You know, right?
- She's just saying that. - She is.
- She's just saying that. - For Jinyoung to hear.
So that he gets jealous.
I know.
Jinyoung doesn't get jealous of anybody.
You got it.
- Choi Ri. - She's ready.
It's pretty.
I think this is better.
Really? I should go around like this.
- Did you learn Korean dance? - Yes, I majored in it.
- She majored in it. - Let's watch Choi Ri dance.
- Yes. - Her fingertips look nice.
She's serious.
She's really pretty.
(The atmosphere changes.)
(This is an elegant turn.)
She's serious.
(She's so pretty.)
She has a nice figure.
She looks cool.
(Her dance is beautiful as she's a seasoned dancer.)
(She jumps lightly...)
(and turns.)
(She finishes off gracefully.)
(They're amazed.)
(That was different from the excited version of her.)
That was the most serious dance I've seen.
- She looks different. - Look at Seok Jin.
That was so pretty.
Eun Su, did you take dance too?
- I did Korean dance too. - Really?
For a short time in high school.
I took it for two years.
- That's not a short time. - That's a very long time.
Eun Su, can I ask you to dance for us?
Can you?
I took it for two months.
- You did? - At a welfare center.
- You too? - I learned at the welfare center.
Show us.
(From the welfare center)
Hey.
- So Min. - Why?
She learned it at the welfare center.
For two months.
- At the welfare center? - She learned it for two months.
- Two months. - At the welfare center.
You should show us too then.
Everybody who took lessons should go up and dance.
It's rare for all these people to be in one place.
I'm curious what you learned at the welfare center.
There aren't that many celebrities who majored in Korean dance.
Please cue the music.
If she learned for two years,
- she must have a nice figure. - That's a long time.
That's a long time.
She's a good dancer too.
She's a good dancer.
She's a bird.
Her gaze is soft.
You need to wear a hanbok.
(She does a successful turn.)
She's good.
- You know when you watch them turn. - She's good.
She's a good dancer.
She learned to dance.
That was unplanned.
- She's lying down. - Is she lying down again?
(Collapsing)
- Don't lie down. - Eun Su, stop lying down.
Get up.
Eun Su, get up.
It's the same dance as before, but slower.
It's the same dance, but slower.
If you keep putting your face on the cold floor, your mouth will turn.
The welfare center version.
- Eun Su, it's cold. - Good job.
(She might get a facial nerve palsy. The welfare center dancer is next.)
She learned for two months.
The welfare center version.
- Do I have to look nice? - The welfare center version.
- Does she have to look nice? - You can leave your jacket on.
Hey, just do it.
- I need to show my figure. - What figure?
It's better not to show it.
- Jinyoung took her jacket. - You're not even that good.
(Oh, dear.)
Did you see her? When Jinyoung handed her the microphone.
(She tried to act cute.)
I hate this.
- Let's watch what she learned. - Gosh, So Min.
She took off her shoes too.
What's wrong with your socks?
They're kind of small for you.
Your toes are about to pop out.
- They're sharp. - So Min, are your toes bleeding?
I think they're about to bleed.
- They're sharp. - Pedicure.
- I think they're bleeding. - So Min.
- Will I remember? - So Min, are your toes bleeding?
(She shows off her see-through socks before revealing her dance.)
Two months at the welfare center.
Look at her facial expression.
- You have to look serious. - Look serious.
- Look at her figure. - Is this really Korean dance?
I can see it.
It's too unnatural.
Hey, So Min!
- Wait a minute. - Hold on.
(My goodness!)
- Hold on. - Your armpits are sweaty!
(Your armpits are sweaty!)
(Stop right there.)
(They protect So Min.)
Come out.
(So Min's sweaty armpits bring chaos.)
- So Min. - Hey!
- Hey. - What is up with you?
(So Min, put this on.)
You must have been very nervous.
What is up with you?
This is the end. This is the end.
- I thought I was seeing things. - Don't say anything.
This has to be a lie.
I mean...
- I was so startled. - So Min.
- Hey. - Your armpits...
You must have been very nervous.
Jinyoung.
She is easygoing, right?
She is unaffected.
Stop it already.
It looked as if there was dried seaweed on her armpit.
- Dried seaweed. - Stop it already.
I was like, "Did it come from gimbap?"
Seriously.
It wasn't a small piece, but a big piece for making gimbap.
Just think of it as a part of the design.
"A big piece for making gimbap"!
It was the shade.
It was just the shade on her armpits.
Okay.
- She broke out in a sweat. - I mean...
I realized how nervous So Min is today.
Her armpits showed us.
You should use deodorant.
Deodorant.
- Jinyoung brought her shoes. - Jinyoung.
He has manners.
Why did you point it out?
Why did this happen today...
when Jinyoung is here? I am going crazy.
- You took off your jacket. - Seriously.
Why did you take off your jacket? You should've kept it on.
She didn't raise her arms much.
Her sweaty armpits became obvious at this pose.
(Suppressing her anger)
- Everyone on that side saw it. - I wondered...
- if she broke out in a sweat. - The left side was relatively dry.
- My goodness. - She was nervous.
It's your first visit to the show, Choi Ri.
- Yes, it's my first visit. - Please introduce yourself.
My full name...
has 2 words instead of 3 words.
It's Choi Ri.
- Choi Ri. - Yes.
Are you from Busan?
- I am from Geochang. - Geochang.
- What a coincidence! - What do you mean?
- The guests' hometowns. - Gyeongsang Province?
Choi Ri is from Geochang. Eun Su is from Busan.
- Tongyeong. - He is from Tongyeong.
- Jinhae. - Are you from Jinhae?
Let's have a battle of three-line poems in a dialect.
(A battle of three-line poems in a dialect)
- It will be fun. - Now...
- Kyeong Hwan should show us. - Kyeong Hwan, let's go.
- You can do it, right? - Kyeong Hwan, show us.
- Does it need to be in a dialect? - Yes.
- Show us how it's done. - Okay.
- Can you make one about Se Chan? - Se Chan?
Okay, I'll do one about Se Chan.
- Is there something you prepared? - Se Chan.
- I will make one about Se Chan. - Se Chan.
The first line.
Yang Se Chan, it has been a while.
Have you been well?
- It really is a dialect. - The second line.
Did you wash your face?
Your face doesn't look so clean.
The third line.
Go and wash your face with cold water.
What was that?
You didn't wash your face, right?
Wash your face with cold water!
Kyeong Hwan, wash your face with cold water.
- Wash your face with cold water. - Wouldn't it be too cold in winter?
- He lacks wits. - He can't be perfect.
- He can't be perfect. - It was nice.
Jinyoung, it's your turn.
What should it be about?
- So Min. - So Min?
It will be hard to make one about me.
Jeon So Min.
- Gosh, she worries about him. - Use a dialect.
The last line will be hard.
(Jinyoung will make a three-line poem about So Min.)
- The first line. - So Min.
"So Min."
(He exudes manly charms.)
The second line.
Although your armpits became sweaty,
We were past that. Why did you bring that up again?
- "Your armpits became sweaty." - We could have edited it out.
The third line.
Don't be embarrassed.
(So Min, don't be embarrassed.)
(He captivated women's hearts.)
- It was good. - It was good.
It was witty.
He mixed the dialect and the standard Korean.
The three guests struggled a lot so that Jinyoung could shine.
I didn't make a three-line poem.
(He feigns ignorance.)
(He has a feeling his poem will get edited out.)
"Go and wash your face with cold water."
Among comedians,
Kyeong Hwan is known as a comedian...
- who makes comedians laugh. - You are too kind.
I haven't made the public laugh in over 10 years.
(The comedians' comedian is shy before the public.)
I am still waiting for my chance.
- He is hilarious. - That was a good response.
That's great. Kyeong Hwan's story...
Why do you keep saying that? It isn't great.
- The atmosphere isn't great. - Jae Seok.
Jae Seok, are you sure it's great?
- He has many things to cover. - I mean...
- He has many things to cover. - Listen.
- "That's great." - I meant that...
it would be great if we wrap this up here.
(That was the hidden meaning.)
If you keep going, you will get edited out.
- Throw in the white towel. - That was enough.
No, no. I will keep going until the end.
I will keep going until 8pm.
(You should have wrapped it up there.)
The next guest we will introduce is...
Jinyoung of GOT7.
Finally.
(Awed)
GOT7 made a comeback with "You Calling My Name".
Let's give him a big hand.
Jinyoung.
- Please let us check out the song. - Of course.
Jinyoung of GOT7.
The dance is incredible.
There is music.
(So Min has been waiting for Jinyoung's solo performance.)
(He stretches his ankles.)
My goodness.
Even the way he warms up is different.
- His body is light. - It's light.
His body is light.
- It's light. - He isn't like us.
He jumps so lightly.
He is sexy.
(Every dance move shows a seasoned idol singer's sexiness.)
(My goodness!)
My goodness.
(So Min claps like a seal when he grinds his hips.)
(His jaw dropped.)
I see why So Min is crazy about him.
("You Calling My Name" by GOT7)
- He is good. - I see why she is crazy about him.
I don't know...
if you saw So Min.
When Jinyoung was getting ready,
she captured every moment with her eyes.
- She did it with her eyes. - Click.
(From the moment Jinyoung stretched his body,)
(So Min saved every moment in her heart.)
(So Min's eyes worked like a shutter.)
- She captured it with her eyes. - She saved it.
She captured it with her eyes.
I haven't seen So Min react that way in a while.
I think Se Chan is wary of Jinyoung.
- Why would I do that? - Why?
- He said he can dance to the song. - Okay.
- What are you talking about? - Se Chan, let's go.
(Will he do the fan-meet dance to this song?)
You said that.
- I can't dance. - You said that.
Play the song.
Play GOT7's song.
I can't believe Se Chan will dance.
I feel bad.
He will look so sloppy.
- I feel bad. - He will look so sloppy.
(What?)
(What is he doing?)
(He copies anything that looked cool.)
(Why does it look funny when he does it?)
That's good.
He knows what looks cool.
(Se Chan responds to Jinyoung's warmup.)
(I will let go of myself.)
(Wait, the dance suits the song.)
(He is making good use of the dance he learned.)
That's hilarious.
(I want to be a part of this.)
Get out of there.
Get out.
That was hilarious.
- That was so much fun. - That was hilarious.
I couldn't help it because it's my favorite part.
- I am sorry. - How embarrassing!
(Why did you make me do this?)
- Wash your face. - I should wash my face.
That was embarrassing.
He looked cool. He looked cool.
I guess he really is wary of Jinyoung.
This is So Min's favorite situation.
- Why? - You danced for her.
You danced for her.
- Did I dance for her? - Listen.
- Se Chan danced for her. - That's right.
The situation became that way.
This is my day.
- This is my day. - Enjoy it.
All right.
So Min should get her hair dried.
- Why? - The top of her head is sweaty.
(The top of her head is sweaty.)
Her hair became limp.
The top of her head isn't the only place that is sweaty.
- My goodness. - Kwang Soo.
- My goodness. - Jinyoung...
- is fanning her head. - Don't be too nice.
- So Min. - Today...
Why did you even say you want to see Jinyoung?
For some reason, I am in a terrible condition today.
I don't know why.
It started when we talked about the welfare center.
Nothing is going my way.
What?
- What is Jung Min doing here? - He was on a radio program.
- Jung Min. - What are you doing here?
I was on a radio program.
(Park Jung Min was on his way home from a radio program.)
- Come, come. - Jung Min.
- "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks". - This is cool.
They always make fun of me about "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks"!
(Kwang Soo tells on the others.)
I am glad you are here.
They...
Jung Min.
They always make fun of me about "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
I enjoyed the movie.
- "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks". - I enjoyed the movie.
- I enjoyed it, Jung Min. - Seriously.
I really enjoyed it.
I might as well take off my pants here.
(Kwang Soo finally met an alley who starred in the same movie.)
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
- I can't believe it. - Jung Min.
Thank you. Thank you, Jung Min.
Thank you so much.
- Jung Min. - Please say good things about it.
- Thank you. - Of course.
I really enjoyed the movie.
I told everyone that the movie is fun.
Do you want to see So Min's sweaty armpits?
Stop it.
(Jung Min, do you like the water park?)
- Stop talking about her armpits. - Show him.
Stop it.
- Bye, Jung Min. - Take care.
(We thank Jung Min for dropping by despite his busy schedule.)
- He is the best. - We said hello...
- to every guest. - My goodness.
Now, let's get the race started.
Did you check out the ghost story in the preview?
- No, I didn't. - No.
(A ghost story appeared in a preview the day before the shoot.)
(Late night in the editing room of the production crew)
You don't know the ghost story of our TV station, SBS, right?
It's my first time hearing it.
You don't know about Clacking Ghost and Coughing Ghost?
No, I don't.
Listen.
A long time ago, a main producer and assistant director...
wrote a legendary proposal that guaranteed 40 percent TV ratings.
Another competing producer and a writer were envious of them.
One night, the competing producer and the writer...
eliminated them.
But the producer coughed a lot so his nickname was Coughy.
And the writer always wore heels so her nickname was Clacky.
And after they had gotten eliminated,
every night,
there were clacking and coughing sounds.
They are roaming around the building to find that proposal.
Didn't you guys twist the story too much?
Let's just go home.
Shall we? Let's go.
(Screaming)
(Coughing)
(Clacking)
(There's a ghost story surrounding the legendary project proposal.)
It's a ghost.
Today's race will be here at the TV station.
It's called "Ghost Story of a TV Station: Legendary Proposal"
You are producers and writers...
of "Dalim Man".
- We are? - Yes.
We are producers and writers?
Within the group are the main producer,
the assistant director, Coughing Ghost,
and Clacking Ghost who are ghosts from the story.
There is an assistant director?
I think I know who Coughing Ghost is.
- Who is it? - Seok Jin coughs a lot.
(He's Coughing Ghost.)
(He's 100 percent Coughing Ghost according to his symptoms.)
That's why I'm trying not to cough.
He coughs a lot.
You must eliminate Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost...
who wanted the proposal...
or if you find the proposal first,
the "Dalim Man" production crew wins.
On the other hand, if the producer gets eliminated...
or if Coughing or Clacking Ghosts find the proposal first, you lose.
The losing team gets the penalty.
(It's Coughing and Clacking Ghosts versus everybody else.)
We'll announce the team members...
for the first mission.
It's assigned.
First team is...
Jae Seok,
Seok Jin,
Se Chan,
and Eun Su.
(First team: Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Se Chan, and Eun Su)
- What's this? - This team combination...
If you just look at our faces,
Kwang Soo should have joined us.
- What are you talking about? - It's the four of us.
- No way. - Eun Su and the three of us.
Come this way.
(The teams were assigned by the production crew.)
(Second team: Jong Kook, So Min, Choi Ri, and Jinyoung)
(Third team: Kwang Soo, Haha, Ji Hyo, and Kyeong Hwan)
Jong Kook is on our team. We're the strongest.
These are the three teams.
You are the production crew of "Dalim Man".
There are Teams Producer, Writer, and New Producer...
for the first mission.
Please keep in mind the new producer is the youngest member...
and must wear a suit jacket during the mission.
Please pick your teams.
Let's play Race of Wits.
It's been a while.
If you lose, you are out.
- Get ready, - Does the winner get to decide?
set, go.
(Race of Wits starts.)
One.
Two.
Three.
- It's dangerous from 4. - 4!
(That was good timing.)
- 5. - 5.
(They were standing next to each other and lost.)
- Hey! - I was getting started.
- Goodness. - Jae Seok.
Go back.
- My gosh. - Jae Seok.
We're too old to be new producers.
Look at him.
He's...
He's the Chief Director.
He's almost the director.
I am.
The teams have been decided.
Please get changed before starting the race.
(Team Producer: Kwang Soo, Haha, Ji Hyo, and Kyeong Hwan)
(Team New Producer: Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Se Chan, and Eun Su)
(Team Writer: Jong Kook, So Min, Choi Ri, and Jinyoung)
Isn't this the entertainment headquarters?
This is the entertainment department.
This is the entertainment production department.
We're actually going to be here.
Production crew office of "Dalim Man".
- Right, we're "Dalim Man". - We are.
We're going to have a meeting.
- A reform meeting? - It's a meeting.
(2019 Reform Meeting)
What? A reform meeting?
- Is somebody getting fired? - Who's that on the bottom?
Look at that.
Seok Jin's name is on the bottom.
Why am I the only one down here?
That's what I was saying.
- We have seats. - We do?
- Writer. - New producer.
(Each person has a designated seat.)
- Writer one. - I'm a writer.
Jae Seok. We're producers.
Jae Seok, you are number one.
- Where do new producers go? - Please be quiet!
- New producers are here. - Where are we?
(It's messy.)
There are assigned seats.
New producers sit here.
Do writers all get laptops?
There are too many cords at our seats.
- You don't have laptops either. - We don't have laptops.
Goodness.
(He tries to wash away his sorrow with a beverage.)
- This is good. - You're not allowed to drink it.
(I feel better now.)
Where do I sit?
- Producer Yang. - Yes.
Get me some iced coffee.
That's an abuse of power.
- He's a new producer. - Look at that writer.
Hello!
Hello! I'm the new producer Jee Seok Jin.
(He tries to flatter his coworkers.)
I look forward to working with you.
I'm different from these guys.
I heard from somebody...
that you went through six TV stations.
- Rookie. - Yes?
You're talking like a CEO.
(How dare you?)
(He gets a warning for his bad attitude.)
He's just rude. I'll educate him.
Why don't you introduce yourself?
I'm a new producer,
but I'm not new.
Then?
In America...
I won't mention it.
He got stuck.
(He got stuck.)
- Stop it. - He got stuck.
America what?
Excuse me,
but aren't you the producer for a fitness channel?
- Writer. - He's a writer.
He's the main writer.
Is he the main writer? I see.
My qualifications include...
We didn't ask. Stop talking.
I don't think qualifications matter.
I'm new here, so I'll try my best.
New producer one tries to stand out.
(New producer one tries to stand out.)
You said you're a new producer, but isn't this an age spot?
I'm a little bit older.
Are you married?
(Are you married?)
- I am. - Why would you ask that?
Dating isn't allowed at work.
Are you married?
Yes, I am.
(He doesn't give her a chance.)
I didn't think he was married.
Writer. Are you a writer?
Yes, I am.
I've never seen such a good-looking writer...
at a TV station.
He's married.
(So Min creates a love story as soon as she gets the chance.)
With whom?
(It's Jinyoung's turn to answer.)
With a producer. I didn't marry a writer.
You didn't?
(He bursts her bubble.)
Honey.
Jinyoung.
He drew the line.
Writer.
Jinyoung.
- I'm kidding. - He married a producer.
He's like me.
Excuse me, but are you a producer?
Yes.
- Why? - What's wrong?
What show did you produce?
"Darling Man".
(He's annoyed.)
- He said "Darling Man". - "Darling Man"?
- Dalnim? Or hatnim? - Dalnim?
It says "Dalim Man" here.
(What's wrong with all of you?)
- It's "Dalim Man". - Do you produce a children's show?
No, it's an adult show.
- An adult show? - An adult show.
He's preparing a subscription adult channel now.
Not that kind of adult show.
- It's for all ages. - I see.
I heard many rumors...
about how So Min proposes no ideas.
Me? I do everything. What are you talking about?
What shows were you a part of?
There's a show called "Sweaty Armpit Park".
(She's the main writer of "Sweaty Armpit Park".)
It's the best water park in the summer.
I recruit water parks...
in the summer.
- I plan games too. - I see.
Ding-dong. Here's an announcement.
(Pretend like this is an overhead announcement.)
Hello, "Dalim Man" production crew.
Here's the first mission to test the qualifications...
of an entertainment show production crew.
It's called Straight Face TV Station.
The producers, writers, and new producers...
will conduct the 2019 fall reform meeting...
for 30 minutes.
You are the level-headed crew of an entertainment show...
so you shouldn't laugh in any circumstance.
Whenever you laugh, you will get a penalty.
At the conclusion of 30 minutes, the team who laughed the least wins.
The hint that will be given to the winning team...
of this mission is the number of ghosts.
The winning team can pick one team of their choice...
besides their own team,
and check the number of ghosts within that team.
(This is a crucial opportunity to pick out the ghosts.)
(Everybody is keeping a straight face.)
(Giggling)
Jinyoung, we didn't do anything. Why are you laughing?
He's funny already.
(He's looking at Kwang Soo.)
- Am I funny? - His face?
No.
I was listening seriously.
This is funny. The atmosphere.
When I blow the whistle, the time starts.
If you laugh even when you try to make other people laugh,
you go outside and get the penalty. You'll rejoin the meeting after.
- Are you going to cry? - I don't laugh when I'm with you.
- Are you going to cry again? - I laugh when I see other people.
- It drove me nuts. - Are you going to cry again?
Ready, set...
I'm going to attack.
Let's resist first.
Do your gums have to show?
Yes.
There's some bad news in my family.
Really?
You dressed too colorfully despite the bad news.
(You dressed too colorfully despite the bad news.)
You did.
After my wife and I...
(They're about to laugh from the start.)
(He's in danger already.)
After my wife and I came back from a trip,
I don't feel that great.
(They are about to laugh over...)
(a very normal conversation.)
The new producers look like...
new comedians.
We are not.
We're producers.
Isn't he a comedian?
Me?
Is he a former comedian?
Producer, what is our reform meeting about?
Please conduct the meeting.
The reform is...
The lobster is on the crab's side.
(That was random.)
(That was a pun.)
(Laughing)
(I have to resist.)
- I'm sorry. - The lobster is on the crab's side.
Do you want to be funny?
(What's the penalty next door?)
What's this?
(The penalty is self dress-up.)
(Running Man's make-up team has everything you need.)
(They can dress themselves up in any funny way they want.)
If I knew this was the penalty, I would've held my laughter longer.
We told you to come up with ideas.
- Yes. - Start with the newbie's ideas.
- It's a test. This can be a test. - I...
(Seok Jin is about to present his idea.)
What are you doing?
(He's all over the place.)
I like trying out my ideas first.
I see. You take initiative.
You try out your ideas first.
Yes, I try them out first.
- That's a great attitude. - I experience them first.
- Right. - That's great.
That's the attitude new producers ought to have.
I...
(Snorting)
(He's trying to continue his presentation.)
(But he caught Kwang Soo's eyes.)
(Laughing)
You're out.
(Jae Seok heads to the penalty room after looking at Kwang Soo's face.)
Jae Seok is out.
He was presenting his idea. How can he laugh on his own?
- He laughs easily. - Yes.
- Go to the room. - I thought that you were ugly...
- for a moment. - All of a sudden?
I can understand that.
- You'll go in that costume? - Yes.
I told you to come up with an idea.
- Right. - Yes.
I didn't come here to do this.
I wonder if this is why I came to star on Running Man.
My gosh. Look at you.
(A handsome beggar with a bald spot)
(His makeover is a bit sloppy as he's new to this.)
(But why is this so funny?)
(Trying hard not to laugh)
I didn't recognize him for a second when he walked in.
Ji Hyo, you're out.
(Ji Hyo ends up laughing at his sloppy makeover job.)
- I didn't laugh that much. - That was pretty quick.
I didn't know you looked handsome because of your hairstyle.
Of course. Hairstyles make men look handsome.
I didn't know you changed your hairstyle.
- No, no. - You look the same.
- Thank you. - You still look handsome.
- Why don't we continue? - All right.
- Here's a short presentation. - Sure.
- He has a lot of ideas. - That's great.
As for the water slap, the water comes out from the bottom.
But we have never done a real water "slap", per se.
- Hold on. Ideas... - So... Okay.
(Hold on. Ideas...)
(Catching everyone's eyes)
(Goodness)
(Oh, no)
(Think about sad memories.)
(Jae Seok with a high nose bridge shows up.)
(Everyone keeps quiet as he confidently...)
(enters the room.)
- I went to the restroom just now. - Okay.
(I went to the restroom just now.)
I gave this some thought.
(Crying)
(Laughing)
(Bursting into laughter)
- You are... - So Min, you're out.
(Feeling proud for some reason)
Did you discuss your ideas?
(Avoiding eye contact)
- We're still discussing them. - Go. You need to leave.
- Yes, I'm leaving. - Okay.
This is so funny. His centaur costume is so funny.
This is hilarious.
(Things are wrapping up as So Min leaves.)
All right. Let's hear it.
(Laughing)
(It makes him laugh rather late.)
Hey, don't look at me.
(Hey, don't look at me.)
(The moment your eyes meet with his, you'll face the penalty.)
Don't look at me.
(Holding his laughter)
This is so annoying.
Gosh. You look so funny.
I'm sorry. Can you turn around for a bit? Yes.
(I'm sorry. Can you turn around for a second?)
(What are you saying?)
That's funny. You want me to turn around?
- Yes. - So...
This is driving me crazy.
Okay. We should let his mistake slide as he's new.
(We should let his mistake slide as he's new.)
(Kwang Soo, don't say anything.)
Could you turn around?
- Hello. Excuse me for interrupting. - Hey.
(Excuse me for interrupting.)
I'll just change the light bulb.
- You need to change the light bulb? - Yes.
All of a sudden? We're in the middle of a meeting.
The light bulbs are fine. But you're going to change them?
(Jong Kook starts crying to avoid laughing.)
- We should watch him. - We ought to.
(The moment you watch it, you cannot stop laughing.)
(A strong aura of his skit tell them...)
(it will be impossible not to laugh at his skit.)
(The staff members are in a big crisis.)
(Will they be able to watch his skit without laughing?)
(A parade of funny skits you will want to watch)
(A fancy outing for the staff will be held.)
(An awful body roll)
(Phenomenal dance)
(Infinite cute acts)
(They were laughing without any worries.)
(A dangerous night at the TV station deepens.)
(Terrible water slaps)
(Deepening suspicions)
(The Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost are coming.)
(Put the legendary proposal in the safe without their knowing.)
(And there's one thing they cannot forget.)
(The Coughing Ghost and Clacking Ghost appear at midnight.)
(1st rule: Do not trust anyone.)
(2nd rule: Find the legendary proposal.)
(Those who are a step too late...)
(and those who are rushing.)
(You startled me.)
I'm sorry.
(Ghost Story of a TV Station: Legendary Proposal)