- Hello. - Hi.
2019 New Year Project,
- Level Up Race. - Yes.
- Congratulations on your winning. - Yes.
Who will it be?
(At the random roulette to reach the highest level from last race...)
(Kim Jong Kook and Song Ji Hyo)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo were chosen.)
(The winners must decide if they'll use SBS' corporate card,)
(their reward, together or not.)
On the cards...
(The time to decide has come at last.)
"Alone" and "together" are written.
- If both of you choose "together", - Yes.
each of you will get to spend half of the credit limit.
If both of you choose to spend it alone,
you will go through a match, and only the winner...
will get to spend the money on his or her own.
- Only one of us will get it? - Yes.
However, if one of you chooses to spend it together...
and the other chooses to spend it alone,
only the one who chose to spend it alone will get the reward.
Goodness.
(The one who chose to spend it alone will get the reward.)
Okay. I got it.
- Well... Okay. - Think very carefully.
(But Jong Kook, do you remember?)
I will think carefully about it.
(We were so happy then.)
Then we will check the cards now.
(Yes, Ji Hyo. We won because we were together.)
1, 2...
(What will happen to them and the prize money?)
Three.
Here.
(Jong Kook chooses to spend the money alone.)
(Ji Hyo also chooses to spend it alone.)
"Alone"?
- What did you choose? - "Alone".
You also chose to spend it alone.
- Hey, I couldn't let you take it. - You chose the same card.
- I was thinking the same. - By the way,
I thought that if I chose this "together" card,
I knew that it wouldn't work well for us.
We need to take a break.
If we decide to spend the money together,
- it would turn out weird. - I got it.
- I thought I should get rid of it. - I got it.
- I'll spend it alone. - Same here.
Since both of you chose to spend it alone,
after going through a match, only one of you will...
- get the entire prize money alone. - Great.
If you were to get the entire prize money alone,
is there anything you'd like to do?
I've been telling you about this for a long time now.
I think...
I have to go to LA.
(The City of Angels everyone dreams of going, LA)
It's my second hometown which I love very much.
I would like to go there.
Even if we film for 24 hours,
I would welcome it as long as it's in LA.
I would be so happy even if we film for 24 hours.
I want to go to LA.
(His dream and career align.)
(How much does he love LA?)
I also want to...
- experience LA he's talking about. - Why would you go there?
(I want to go to LA too!)
Why would you go to LA?
You've been there many times, but this would be my first time.
You've never been to LA?
- No, I'd like to know about LA. - Really?
I want to experience the city too.
I want to go to LA too!
Goodness, this is weird.
(A few days later)
- Hello. - My goodness.
- Gosh. - Hello.
What's all this?
- Hello. - Gosh, look at this.
Hey, let's sit here.
- What's this? - It smells so good.
Everyone, what you're seeing now...
is a family meal from the South of the US.
I was really hungry.
Everyone, this is a meal...
for the winners of Level Up Race.
(Congratulations on your winning once again.)
- Eat a lot. - Are you buying?
Thank you for the food.
(It's my treat.)
- This is delicious. - Hey, it's good.
This is delicious.
(The exotic flavors fill their mouths.)
(It feels as if they are in the US at the moment.)
- It's good. - It's so good.
I guess I like the food from the South.
(It's perfect for the members.)
This is great.
Did you see what Seok Jin posted on his social media recently?
- What did he upload? - He took a photo with Cha Eun Woo.
- Eun Woo from his radio show? - Yes.
Why did you post that photo? There were other members too.
Should you only mention Eun Woo in the post?
It's not that. I just wrote that,
"Out of all places, I stood next to the handsome guy, Eun Woo."
- That's what I wrote. - I see.
By the way, there's the ugliest guy next to a handsome guy.
- Why am I the ugliest? - Yes, you are.
- The comments are blowing up. - Why?
They wrote that I must have looked great in my young days.
(Why is he suddenly feeling proud of his looks?)
- Really? - No way. We have your photo.
They wrote that they didn't know how small my face was before.
Here it is.
(Providing Seok Jin's photo)
(Given how old it is, the photo shows vivid colors.)
- I can only see his nose. - Hey.
- He was in his 20s. - Where did you get this photo?
- Seok Jin was in his 20s. - I don't even have that photo.
- He was one of a kind. - This is Seok Jin in his 20s.
- What's wrong with you? - He actually looks younger now.
- Doesn't he look better now? - You look younger now.
- Exactly. - He aged very nicely.
Today, we will determine...
the final winner of Level Up Race. It's the Ace versus the Champion.
It's the Ace versus the Champion. It's called La La Land Race.
La La Land?
(La La Land Race will determine the final winner.)
After the match between them,
we will cover all the expenses that will incur...
- during the winner's trip. - Yes!
Really?
As for the rest of the members,
you will listen to Ji Hyo and Jong Kook's trip itineraries to LA.
Pick the team leader with the trip that's more attractive to you.
We'll get to choose.
- We'll choose them? - Yes.
- You'll play games together today. - Okay.
The team leader of the winning team...
can go to LA with only one teammate...
of his or her choosing.
Then it would be just the 2 of them, right? Just the 2 of them?
- Just the two of them? - My gosh.
It will be just the two of them?
- If we were to go as a group... - What about three?
Seriously? Isn't this obvious?
No matter who wins, they can pick each other.
(It's bound to be Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
(This is a conspiracy of cornering them together.)
This is a complete fraud!
- Then... - A fraud.
- I was just curious. - Great.
- Interlock your fingers! - Interlock your fingers!
(Kwang Soo gets excited and teases them.)
Kwang Soo, you're making it dusty for our food.
- That was too much. - Okay.
The winner chooses only one person, right?
That's right.
If we want to win, a team with more members will win.
A bigger team will be more advantageous.
But to get picked, a smaller team is better.
(To win, a bigger team is better, but to get picked, vice versa.)
All right. Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
Please present the itineraries you have prepared.
- Okay. - Start the briefing now.
Why are you going to LA though?
First of all, the weather is great.
It's sunny for 300 days out of 365 days.
It's like deja vu.
When you wake up, it's just like yesterday.
When you wake up again the next day, it's the same day.
(It's nicknamed City of Angels for its weather.)
That's true. That's totally true.
- I think I might get bored. - Yes, I agree.
(Trolling from the start)
What? No, no.
The weather has to be exciting.
There must be rain, hail, and lightning.
And the sky is very clear.
- I like clouds in the sky. - Shouldn't there be some clouds?
- There should be some clouds. - That's right.
I think it might be boring.
- It should rain and snow. - Do you like clouds?
You should go to London then. Go to London then.
(Go to London if you don't like LA.)
- That would be great then. - How could you say that suddenly?
- My goodness. - Hey, Jong Kook.
You sound very angry. I mean, you're trying to gather members.
- Hear me out. You must hear me out. - Sure, sure.
All right. Here we go. I'll start.
When you land in LA, you'll get hungry no matter what.
The first place we'll go after we land is...
A burger joint?
(What is the first mouthwatering American dish they will have?)
We'll go to Koreatown and have Korean food first.
(The first meal will be Korean food.)
- Soft tofu! - Yes!
- It's amazing. If we eat... - Seafood soft tofu.
American food right away, it'll be hard for us.
The soft tofu place was right next to my lodging.
- Have you had that? - I ate that every day.
- I ate that as soon as I woke up. - Right.
Will we get to eat that soft tofu? Will we get to eat that?
- Of course. - By the way,
I've been to LA with Jong Kook a lot of times.
Korean food in LA is really good.
I mean it. I'm serious.
The best noodles in radish water kimchi...
- I ever had was in LA. - Really?
- Korean food there is exceptional. - Over hundreds of years...
- Gosh, the ribs. - Yes, soft tofu.
- I don't get this. - I'm serious.
We eat Korean food all the time. I don't understand those people...
who eat Korean food on their trips.
Exactly. Some people might react like Seok Jin.
This is the great thing about LA. If you go out of Koreatown,
you can totally feel like you're in a foreign country.
We'll go to the place you want next. It's the baseball stadium.
We must go to the baseball stadium.
Shouldn't we watch LA Dodgers' game?
(Home stadium of LA Dodgers, the prestigious team of MLB)
I'll take you to the game that Ryu Hyun Jin will pitch.
We'll go to the Dodger Stadium and watch their game.
- Is that really possible? - We'll watch their game when we go?
(Having great connections is the Champion's skill too.)
- I do want this one. LA Dodgers. - That sounds fun.
Isn't the stadium close to a Korean restaurant?
(Is the Korean restaurant the merit of the trip?)
- Yes, it's close. It's very close. - Right.
- If you... - After the game, you can go there.
- crave kimchi stew, you can go. - Okay.
- That sounds fun. - The baseball stadium sounds fun.
Seok Jin should go. He should go.
After that, we'll head to Santa Monica.
(It doesn't end in LA. They'll visit Santa Monica.)
- The itinerary is great. - Of course.
We'll head over to the beach.
When I said Santa Monica, I meant the beach.
Gosh, the beach.
(The beach exudes the romance of the West Coast.)
Gosh, sashimi from there is really delicious.
(His love for Korean food doesn't end.)
- It's really good. - There's a Korean sashimi place.
- That sashimi place, right? - Yes, that one.
The marinated crabs are great too.
- What is this? - The marinated crabs are great too.
- It's delicious. - Hey.
Will there be other guests on your trip?
- What other guests? - Well...
When we go over there,
I know a lot of healthy and great guys.
- They're younger than you? - Yes.
You desperately want romance...
- in your trip, So Min. - Yes.
It's definitely possible.
There are a lot of guys.
I know a lot of great friends in LA. I'm serious.
He really does know a lot about LA.
- Seriously. - I like many things on his trip.
I'm serious.
By the way, we can't rest...
during Jong Kook's tour.
(By the way, we can't rest during Jong Kook's tour.)
- I've been there with him before. - Okay.
There were so many things we wanted to talk about.
I was so happy,
but you come back about 7kg lighter.
(Beware of the side effect.)
- It's effective in losing weight. - Exactly.
That's exactly my point.
- Ji Hyo, it's your turn. - I like many things from his trip.
This is my first time going to LA,
so I came up with a list of things to do.
Actually,
I'm not a fan of going to tourist attractions.
- I like lounging around. - Gosh.
- You like zoning out. - Yes, I zone out.
- That's more like my style. - Gosh.
I hate following a strict schedule.
- Same here. - Right.
I don't want to go to a lot of places.
- And... - That's right.
- I like that about her trip. - That's great. That's how I roll.
If we have to do whatever has been scheduled,
- Right. - I would get stressed out...
when I have to think about where we'll have to go next.
- You're right. - That's why...
we can have free time until 5pm to 6pm.
(Dropping a bombshell)
- Until 5pm to 6pm? - Wait.
If so, isn't it better off to stay in Korea?
Should we rest when we have gone all the way to LA?
If so, we can go separately. Why would we go there together?
Why would we go to LA and rest until 5pm?
The sun would set around 5pm or 6pm.
(Yes, you guys are doing great.)
Why would we go to LA then?
It's because you want to sleep at home.
In a way, this trip might be better. We might have more freedom.
And...
as you all know, Jong Kook doesn't drink.
Yes, I don't drink alcohol.
We can go there and have drinks together with meals.
Will we play truth or dare?
- We'll play that too! - Yes!
(Ji Hyo's trump card is having drinks together.)
(Ji Hyo finishes it off with playing truth or dare.)
(The atmosphere totally changes after the announcement of the game.)
- I like this great. - Ji Hyo...
Are there any deals you'll offer us?
Like you'll tell us a secret or something?
Will you tell us the part you skipped...
when you told us about your Christmas?
That day with the balloons?
- Will you tell us that story? - She should.
(Let us elaborate on the part that Ji Hyo skipped.)
(Her ex-boyfriend filled the room with balloons for Christmas.)
(They had a glass of wine while feeling the romance of the event.)
(Everyone was utterly focused.)
(She skipped the middle part and said it was morning then.)
(This Skipping Incident has enraged everyone.)
- Will you tell us the story? - Will you tell us?
- You'll tell us what you skipped? - Will you?
I will share it!
(The story of Ji Hyo's night that piqued everyone's curiosity...)
- I'll tell you! - Yes!
I have to choose hers.
I've decided.
I have to listen to that story.
I couldn't sleep for a week.
- I even made up stories. You know? - I...
- I made up stories. - I will...
What stands out the most from Ji Hyo's tour is...
freedom.
- We get to do what we want. - We can do what we want.
- And we don't have to plan a trip. - I can do my own thing, right?
- In a way, we get to rest up. - You only live once.
- We'll divide into teams now. - Okay.
Gosh, this is hard to decide.
(The briefing is over, and they'll choose their teams.)
- Why don't you go 1st, Se Chan? - Should I go 1st?
(Se Chan will choose his team first.)
To tell you the truth,
one of their traveling styles...
matches my style completely.
It totally matches my style of traveling.
(Whose traveling style matches Se Chan's completely?)
I will go with this team.
Okay!
- Okay! - Let me explain.
I want to tell all of my colleagues about my trip.
- That's right. - I want to share my memories.
- So Min, it's your turn. - Me?
So Min, go ahead.
I really can't decide. It's really hard.
So Min might not choose my team,
but she'll regret a lot...
because I know a lot of handsome guys in LA.
- They are so handsome. - Actually,
when I travel, I go on my own.
I don't need to see a lot of stuff. That's my style.
- Just go to Jong Kook now. - Go. Go.
(You'll pick him. Don't stall time.)
- Just go. - Fine.
- Okay. - Great.
(So Min chooses Team Champion.)
- Great. - My goodness.
- Ji Hyo looks really sad. - No.
- You look sad as they chose him. - No, no.
I have been neglecting that girl a lot lately.
(Does he mean me?)
"That girl"?
I must listen to her story.
(The part of her Christmas story she skipped)
(Haha chooses Team Ace.)
I bet it's new.
Kwang Soo. Well, he will...
Kwang Soo, why don't you choose now?
- Okay. - Kwang Soo has been to LA with me.
- That might happen. - I'll do everything I did then.
(As he mentions he'll do everything he did from their last trip...)
- Remember our beautiful memories? - Seriously?
(He reminds Kwang Soo of their memories.)
(Do you remember our beautiful memories together?)
(Our friendship shone like the sun in LA.)
Remember our beautiful memories?
(He's reminded of his bromance memories.)
I choose Jong Kook!
(He has decided.)
(Kwang Soo chooses Team Champion.)
- Come. Come to me. - Gosh.
This is no joke.
I'll go with Ji Hyo.
- Okay. - Okay!
- Ji Hyo. - He didn't come for the freedom.
To be honest, I'm really curious about that skipped part.
(He only has one reason.)
I will hear the rest of the story from Ji Hyo.
- I'll make sure I hear it. - I will too.
- We'll talk all night long. - Okay.
- Come join us, Seok Jin. - Okay.
- I'll have better chances there. - Okay.
I'll go with that team.
I can see disappointment on your face.
- I'm happy. - Okay.
(Team Ace and Team Champion)
(The teams have been formed.)
(Ace)
(She's always chosen and always survives.)
(She's the queen of luck at random draws.)
(The Lucky Ace, Song Ji Hyo)
(Champion)
(He dominates the games with speed and power.)
(He's the undefeated champion, Kim Jong Kook.)
(The best members of the show will have their official match.)
(Ace versus the Champion, who will be the winner?)
Today, it's the Ace versus the Champion.
- It's a team match. - Okay.
The match will consist of three rounds in total.
Isn't this the first time they're competing against each other?
- Yes, it's the first time. - Goodness.
Depending on the results of each round,
you will be given the slots on the roulette accordingly.
- The slots on the roulette? - We'll spin the roulette.
- We'll spin that again? - My gosh, the roulette.
After the third round, you'll spin the roulette.
The chosen member will be the final winner.
This is your first round.
(Ace versus the Champion, Round 1)
It's a quiz called the Fate of Go or Stop.
- Okay! - It's a quiz?
Is the quiz related to the card game?
You'll hear the quiz. If you answer the quiz correctly,
you will choose 1 of the 10 sets...
- on the table. - Okay.
In each set, there are points, varying from 1 to 5.
And there are two cups that are duds.
- Duds? My gosh, duds. - Okay.
When you choose the cups and gain points,
you will earn the chosen points and have a chance to choose again.
If you pick a dud cup, your points will go back to zero.
- Your points will go back to 0. - It'll go back to 0?
- We'll lose points we gathered? - Yes.
(Choosing to stop before the dud is the key.)
- There's Jae Seok, the Zero Guy. - There are so many unlucky ones.
- There's Jae Seok. - You'll lose.
- He was Level Zero. - Yu Zero.
- We'll win no matter what. - My gosh.
(He went back to Level 0 from Level 1.)
After you open up cup and want to continue on,
you can shout, "go".
(The points will accumulate.)
Say that you have earned points,
- The points will accumulate. - but if it's a dud, you get zero.
- Okay. I got it. - I should keep going.
- These two are great at that. - Stopping at the right time is god.
- We should keep going. - Okay, great.
Let us tell you how this game came about.
Jong Kook is good at solving quizzes.
- Ji Hyo is great at random draws. - Random draws.
Hold on.
Hold on. Are you implying that Ji Hyo is bad at solving quizzes?
Then is she good at it?
- We didn't say that. - Ji Hyo?
(Come on, how dare you?)
- When did we say that? - Did we say that?
- Listen. - You went over that.
And you hurt her twice.
- Ji Hyo chooses not to do it. - This kind of questioning...
- would offend Ji Hyo. - Sit down.
- You hurt me twice. - Ji Hyo.
- You just choose not to answer it. - Sure.
Ji Hyo answered the quizzes a few times,
but it didn't air because her answers were too shocking.
- She goes beyond quizzes. - Hey, stop it!
The team with more points will get five slots on the roulette.
- The losing team will get one slot. - Okay.
Gosh, that's a huge difference.
My goodness, this is serious.
- Yes, there has to be a difference. - In my opinion,
- this is why Ji Hyo's team... - Okay.
is called Team Ace.
- Even if they take 5, - That 1 slot...
- might get chosen. - we can win with one slot.
- That's the fun of having one slot. - We'll show you that.
Here's why our team is great. Even though she's the team leader,
she's quiet.
- She doesn't make requests. - That's right.
- Just like her traveling style. - She doesn't bother us.
Our trip will be like that too.
- That's our traveling style too. - She won't bother us.
- We're the definition of freedom. - Our team centers around freedom.
- Freedom. - Right.
They're getting way ahead of themselves.
As for your team,
It seems like your team revolves around Jong Kook.
Are you not happy right now?
- No, I am. - You can tell us.
- I'm doing great. - Be honest.
We stay quiet if he does.
I'm doing fine, don't worry.
- Ji Hyo, let me take this off. - Sure.
- Do as you please. - I'm going to pick my nose.
Ji Hyo, I'm going to cross my legs.
- I don't care. - Ji Hyo.
I'll be natural.
Just be casual.
Okay, let's go!
If you get it wrong, the other team will hit you with a toy hammer.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Bring it on! - That's great.
- That's great. - Bring it on.
Show them your strength.
(They revolt.)
Hey, I'm only going to hit one person.
Just one.
(He gets hit.)
- Darn it. - Sorry.
(Jae Seok also only hits one person.)
I was just swinging it.
- Hey. Ji Hyo, look at him. - I was just swinging.
- All right. - Ji Hyo...
- doesn't comment on anything. - Whatever.
Just do what you need to do.
- You're my role model. - That's great.
He's a 54-year-old who gets hit on the head.
(Nevertheless, he keeps smiling.)
- You're so cool. - My eyes should've popped out.
They should have.
You're right.
First question.
Which of these words didn't originate from playing yut?
- Yut? - All right.
One, "cajole".
- What? - What is that?
Two, "only".
Three, "competent".
Four, "all the same".
Let me answer. One.
- Let me answer. 1. - I think it's 3.
I thought so too.
- I think it is. - I think so.
"Cajole".
You don't use that word when you play yut.
I don't think...
- they use that word. - Right.
- Okay! - Okay!
(They get the first question...)
(thanks to Kwang Soo.)
(Did you see that?)
(You will go down today.)
Hey, Kwang Soo.
(You're all dead.)
Darn it.
(Furious)
You're amazing. Great.
(Team Ace, what are you doing?)
(I almost fell asleep.)
How did you know?
(You just wait and see.)
- I'm so furious. - Me too.
- Good job. - I thought it was "only".
The question was easy.
- Next is Team Champion. - Let's go.
- Please pick one and open it. - Dud, dud, dud
- Dud, dud, dud - Dud, dud, dud
Let it be a dud.
- 5 or 6? - I recommend Kwang Soo.
- What do you think? - I think it's four.
- Well... - Don't pick four.
- Right. - I'm sure.
Which one do you pick?
Will you be helping us?
- The opposing team will help. - He's the helper?
You shouldn't touch them.
- Don't pick 4 or 6. - Don't.
He touched them.
(They're positive those 2 will be duds.)
- Right. - Because I touched them?
How dare you?
- Right. - Take those out.
I'm flabbergasted.
Do you think the first one will be a dud?
- It could be. - One?
- 7 or 8? - Let's go with 8.
- 8? All right. - Yes.
(Jong Kook doesn't care about their opinions.)
Wait, hold on.
Didn't you want the first one?
Yes, but I changed.
He wanted to change.
- His opinion matters. - Wait.
- Let's pick eight. - Just...
Just do as Jong Kook says.
But we should still share our opinions.
We all had different preferences, but we followed Jong Kook.
- It's eight. - It is.
(Jong Kook has the power over them.)
- Then 8, it is. - 8, please.
All right.
(This was Jong Kook's choice.)
(Will he be able to avoid the dud?)
- 5! - 5!
(It's 5 points.)
(They receive 5 points from the start.)
- Jong Kook! - Five points!
(He's surely amazing.)
- Should we stop here? - You're amazing.
- That'll be boring. - You should continue.
- Be a man. - Come on.
Shall we just stop here?
If it were up to me, I'd just stop here.
You should go on.
- Let's do four. - What?
- Let's try it. - I don't think that's right.
Just once more. Let's pick the first one.
- You should continue. - First one.
- First one. - Go on.
- You shouldn't stop here. - Go on.
I pick eight.
- Open it. - Go!
(He continues.)
- All right. - Let's go!
- Please. - All right.
- Open it. - I think this one's not right.
He already picked this one.
Dud, dud, dud.ud
(Is it a dud, or will they get points?)
(Will he make the right choice once again?)
- Dud! - Dud!
(It's a dud, and their previous 5 points don't count.)
- It's a dud - It's a dud
I knew it.
- I knew it. - How could it be a dud?
I wanted to pick seven.
- I wanted to pick one. - We should know when to stop.
We learned a lesson.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Jong Kook shares his lesson,)
(and Se Chan listens to him.)
We learned a lesson.
- We did. - You're so positive.
- You sound so generous. - I am.
Stop pretending.
I learned a lesson.
Let's win this time.
Here's the second question.
Which of these mountains doesn't exist in Korea?
- All right. - I'm confident.
One, "Mount Woo".
- One, "Mount Woo". - That's a mountain?
- Mount Woo? - What?
- Two... - Is this nonsensical?
(He asks about the question.)
No, no.
- He said, "Mount Woo". - It must be a mountain.
- No? - Okay.
- I'm sorry. - I think it's number one.
How does "Mount Woo" make sense?
Two, "Mount Ttan".
- What? - "Mount Ttan"?
- "Mount Ttan"? - Come on.
- This is nonsensical, right? - How can we pick one?
- I don't get this. - They want us to guess.
"Mount Meon".
Let me answer.
(Seok Jin attempts to answer.)
Three, "Mount Meon".
- 1 more time, please? - 3, "Mount Meon".
"Mount Meon".
(They get it right.)
You're amazing.
- He's amazing. - "Mount Meon"!
He's amazing.
(Hitting)
Why are you hitting us?
(He surprises them.)
- Why did you hit me? - Why?
- Why did he? - What?
- What? - He need to get hit.
- You should get hit too. - Why?
- Why did you hit us? - No.
- Is he insane? - Come on.
- I was just happy. - Why?
- He needs to be hit. - Why did you hit them?
- What's going on? - Why did you?
- I'm not sure. - Hit him.
- Just hit him. - I blocked it.
- Hey, you should help me. - Let's take turns.
- I blocked it. - Why did you hit us?
- I was just happy. - Why did you do that?
- I didn't mean to. - Be still.
(He takes off Seok Jin's hat and glasses.)
- Be still. - What?
Be still.
- Why? - I'm so confused.
- Why did you do it? - Why?
(Hitting)
- Why? - Why?
(He regrets his actions.)
(It hurts him a lot.)
Goodness.
- It's give and take. - Hey.
- You don't usually hit him. - I was...
- I was just happy. - You don't usually do that.
- I was happy. - You were?
I thought you're supposed to hit when you're happy.
- Okay. - I see.
Hey, hit me.
- Hit me. - Okay.
One more left.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn.)
(He hits him with the handle.)
Oh, my.
Why?
(A dull sound was heard.)
Goodness.
I was so happy that I wanted to hit you with the handle.
- Okay. - I can't believe you.
Okay.
- Why do I feel defeated? - Gosh.
(They were the ones who got the question right.)
My goodness.
- I'm confused. - I was so shocked.
I was just so happy.
All right. Pick a dud for us.
- All right. - All right.
I'm sure there will be a dud.
I'll go since I got it right.
Go with eight.
- Pick eight. - Stay still.
- There can't be consecutive duds. - Stay still.
- Right. - Let Ji Hyo pick.
Let her pick. Go.
Are you the team leader?
(Who are you to tell us what to do?)
- You're not one either. - I know but...
Ji Hyo should go.
Do you think being nice to her will make her pick you?
(I know your intentions.)
You knew, didn't you?
- He's so sly. - What is he?
Ji Hyo, please pick.
If it's another dud, that'll be baffling.
Let's play it safe.
- Let's be safe. - Then...
- I pick eight. - Okay!
- Okay. - It won't be a dud.
(Ji Hyo picks 8.)
- I pick eight. - Open it.
(Previously, 8 was a dud.)
(Will Ji Hyo's prediction be correct?)
(3 points)
- All right. - Great start.
- Let's go again. - All right.
I want to stop here.
(She's careful.)
Let's do it.
- Let's try one more time. - Wait.
Let's go with eight once more!
- Wait. - Pick eight again!
- Ask her. - Ji Hyo, just go with it.
- Let's not go with eight. - Wait.
- Ji Hyo. - Are you the leader?
- Go. - Ji Hyo.
- Go! - Go.
Let's go with eight.
(Will they receive points once more?)
(Will Jae Seok's choice make Ji Hyo smile?)
(It's a dud.)
- Okay! - Okay!
(They forgot how unlucky Jae Seok is.)
How could that happen?
There were 2 duds for 1 number.
That means the rest of the cups...
- They're safe. - are safe.
- It's safe. - Right.
- Let's pick that number. - We have to win.
- We have to. - We must.
- All right then. - Let's go.
- We must see to it. - All right.
- Go. - There are two duds.
Number eight is a jackpot.
Darn you all.
Let's go.
- We must get this one right. - We have to.
- All right. - Third question.
What is the word that refers to bluffers and liars?
Lee Kwang Soo.
Which number is it?
It's right?
(He was just guessing.)
- I'm in the choices? - Hold on.
- I'm not a bluffer. - It's in there?
It is in here.
Really? Truly?
- That's the answer. - That's great.
- I'm in there? - Great.
- One, "large-eyed herring". - That's wrong.
Two, "Lee Kwang Soo".
(He was really a part of it.)
- Lee Kwang Soo? - He's really a part of it.
I come after large-eyed herring?
- He was in the choices. - He was.
Yes.
Three, "a street singer".
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
- No, no. - That's right.
- Let me answer. - That's right.
Three, "a street singer".
(He is sure.)
Isn't it right?
(They change their answer.)
- It's number four then. - I think it is.
Use the toy hammer.
Jong Kook, let's just hit Seok Jin.
(Let's do the same thing he did.)
- Seok Jin? - Hit the one who got it wrong.
- If you don't care, I'll pick one. - What?
Okay, they don't care.
- Okay. - What?
They don't care.
(If they don't care, it'll be Seok Jin.)
- Why me? - They don't care.
- Hey. Stay still. - We pick you.
- Wait a minute. - Why?
- Aren't you afraid? - They said...
- they don't care. - It doesn't matter.
Hit him.
I'll hit lighter than before.
(Everyone pities him.)
It's lighter, right?
(They shouldn't get them wrong anymore.)
(What is the word that refers to bluffers and liars?)
- Four, "big talker". - Let me answer.
(Kwang Soo was quick.)
- Kwang Soo. - It's the last one.
(Jong Kook thinks it's the last one.)
(If they get it right, they'll receive 7 points.)
One, "large-eyed herring".
- What? Hey. - What?
(All of a sudden?)
- What? What are you doing? - Wait.
What are you doing?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Four, "big talker".
- It's number four. - Okay!
(The answer is "big talker".)
We need to hit him.
Hold on. One person from our team will...
(He suddenly pops up and hits him.)
(Fly like a butterfly and sting...)
(like a bee.)
- Is this how it's going to be? - What? You lost.
What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with you? - Why did you do that?
- I didn't think it was number four. - Me neither.
- It was right. - It was.
- I thought it wasn't right. - It's not number one.
- It was the right one. - Why did you hit me?
(Why did he hit him?)
- I need to hit 4 people? - 4?
- He needs to hit four people. - I do.
(Really?)
- No, I need to hit 3 people. - No, it's 4.
Wait.
(He quickly changes the rules.)
(He doesn't dare to hit Jong Kook.)
- Wait, you changed it. - Hold on.
- Hold on. - I want to hit him.
- It's 4. - No, it's 3.
- No, it's not. - It's three people.
- What do you mean? - Don't be ridiculous.
- It's 4 people. - It's 3 people.
Forget it. It's three.
- It's 4. - No, it's 3.
- No, it's 4. - No, I want 3.
- Just make it four. - I don't want to.
(He dodges it.)
- He dodged it. - Let it go.
Let it go.
- Let it go. - He dodged it? Gosh.
Fine, then.
Did you see Seok Jin?
He was afraid he'd get hit.
(He surrendered.)
- Okay, then. - That was hilarious.
- Let's go with eight. - All right.
- We choose 8. - 8, it is.
- Shall we do both cups? - Sure.
- Should I go? - There's no dud there.
- Okay. - Yes!
- Go! - Go!
- It's a given. - Okay!
- Six points. - Go?
- Go! - Go!
- Okay! - Yes!
- Seven points. - Let's do one more.
- Let's do one more. - Sure.
- Let's go. - That's enough.
- Let's go. - Calm down.
Ji Hyo, let's go once more.
- We should continue. - We should stop.
- Let's go. - Let's stop.
- You're the team leader. - Let's continue.
- Don't forget that. - Go on.
- Ji Hyo. - Let's go.
- 9. - 9.
- Okay. - If we get more points,
- let's stop here. - Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. - It must be 8 points.
(Ji Hyo, who's always lucky, decides to continue.)
(They wish for it to be a dud.)
(Did she make the right choice?)
- Okay. - What a relief.
(They receive 1 more point.)
- We got a point. - Let's do one more.
- They've picked seven. - Last pick.
- Okay, seven. - This will be our last one.
- Are you sure? - Seven.
- Let's do it. It'll be all right. - 1, 2...
1, 2, 3.
(No one has picked 7 before.)
(Will it be a lucky 7 or a tragic 7?)
- 1, 2, 3. - Okay!
- Let's stop here. - Let's stop.
- Great. - Amazing.
- This is amazing. - 1, 2, 3.
(Team Ace gets 10 points.)
- Stop it. I'm so anxious. - All right.
- 10 points. - 10 points.
Look at what you've done.
- What have you done? - We received 10 points.
We could've gotten it.
- Of course, it was number four. - He's telling him off.
- Stop. - Fine. What's done is done.
Sit down, Kwang Soo. Let's do this.
Next question.
The difference in 12 years of age is called zodiac similarity.
- Right. - Correct.
Then what's the word for...
- one-year difference? - I know this one.
- I know this. - This one's easy.
One, "knee similarity".
Two, "shoulder similarity".
Three, "eyebrow similarity".
Four, "head similarity".
Let me answer!
(Hesitant, Haha raises his hand.)
What is the answer?
- What? - Don't you know everything?
- I'm not sure. Maybe three? - I don't know either.
I think it's either eyebrow or ankle. Let's do eyebrow.
- There was no ankle. - It's knee.
- It's knee. - There was no ankle.
- I'm baffled. - That's like a ghost.
There's no ankle. Four was "head similarity".
- Pick 3. - 3, "eyebrow similarity".
That's the right one.
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
We need to hit them first.
- Hit them. - Do that first.
You should do it.
Give it back later.
(Who is his target?)
What was the second choice?
(He finds his target.)
- Come on. - What do you mean?
- Take off your hat. - Oh, okay.
(He makes sure to teach him a lesson.)
(Hitting)
- Wait. - What's wrong?
(Why is he hitting me?)
- Jong Kook! - What's going on?
- Jae Seok! - What?
- What was that? - What did you do?
- What? - Why did you hit me?
- How could you do that? - What's wrong?
You're impossible.
- He hit me! - Hey.
- How could you? - It's not him.
- How could you? - Wait.
(While walking towards Jae Seok,)
(Jong Kook makes an abrupt turn.)
- It's not him. - How could you?
(When a junior makes a mistake, his senior should take the blame.)
- How many more hits? One? - Wait.
- What's going on? - Okay.
- How could you do this? - Hey.
Goodness.
(He's been hit 5 times today.)
You won't get away with this!
(You should respect me.)
(What?)
How could you?
(He places his glasses upside down.)
- Okay. - You've changed your glasses.
- All right. - You changed your style.
Let me hit him next.
- Sure, you can. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - All right.
- Two, "shoulder similarity". - "Shoulder similarity".
Okay!
It was the shoulder.
My brother and I are one-year apart.
- Because they're of similar height. - I get it.
They got 10 points. We have to get this.
You won't have our luck.
- Please. Pick 2. - We got 10 points.
- I think it's 4. - No, it's 2.
- I think... - I think it's two.
Was this the one they picked?
Yes, it's seven. Should we pick that...
- and then pick another one? - I think we can pick that one.
- I don't think it'll be a dud. - Me neither.
It has to be a dud.
The second one can't be a dud.
What do you think?
Let's trust Se Chan.
- 7. - We'll open 7.
I doubt it'll be a dud.
- It's a dud. - It's a dud.
(Team Champion needs to catch up.)
(Will they be able to avoid the dud?)
- Okay! - Okay!
(They receive 3 points.)
(Let's catch up now.)
- Let's continue. - It'll work out.
- Let's do 4. - Let's do 2.
- Let's do 4. - I'm not sure about 4.
- We should pick 2. - 2?
It won't be a dud from the start.
- Did you pick four? - Hold on.
Jae Seok touched the fourth one.
And Kwang Soo also wanted to pick four.
- Right. - Jae Seok touched it.
(4 seems ominous.)
It does feel like you shouldn't pick that one.
They both wanted four.
I'm not sure.
- Wait. - Okay.
We listened to Se Chan and picked seven.
- So pick yours. - I'll...
- I'll pick four. - All right, then.
- It feels ominous. - 2, 3.
(Cup number 4 is the one Jae Seok touched...)
(and Kwang Soo picked.)
(Will this go against their expectations?)
(Will it give them points instead of a dud?)
- Dud! - It's like a miracle.
I can't believe this.
(Just like Kwang Soo, the cup turns out to be a dud.)
- It's a dud. - I'm sorry.
(He regrets believing in him.)
- I'm sorry. - You should've listened to me.
- It's over. - I'm sorry.
- I can't believe this. - This is impossible.
- How could that happen? - My goodness.
(None of them can believe it.)
- You know what? - It's so strange.
- I picked four as well. - How could this happen?
- I picked four as well. - Unbelievable.
- It really is. - Goodness.
- It's amazing. - I know.
- I can't believe this. - Me neither.
- It's all over. - How could this be?
- Okay, it's good for us. - That's why it didn't work out.
(They fail to gain any points.)
They have no points, right?
(Team Ace: 10, Team Champion: 0)
- We'll try harder next time. - It'll still be hard.
Those who frequent the US will have an advantageous.
- Okay. - That's good.
Who knows?
Whose face appears on the front side...
- of a one-dollar bill? - I know this.
One, "Abraham Lincoln".
Two, "Thomas Jefferson".
Three, "Franklin Delano Roosevelt".
Four, "George Washington".
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
- Jae Seok. - Four, "George Washington".
I'm sure.
- I'm 100-percent sure. - Isn't it Abraham Lincoln?
No, it's George Washington.
(What is the answer?)
("George Washington" was the correct answer.)
(They get it right.)
I've never really looked at it.
- Please let it be a dud. - I pick four.
- Four. - No, no.
- We should pick four. - I think it'll be another dud.
- There are no consecutive duds. - He's right.
- There aren't any. - Who knows?
- It's possible. - Really?
I think it is.
Really? Which number grabs your attention?
- Right, you should pick. - Which number?
- 2. - 2.
(Neither team chose this number.)
(Will she be lucky this time as well?)
- All right. - Two points.
(She sure is lucky.)
Let's go. Pick again.
- I told you. - We should've picked two.
(Team Champion gets gloomier and gloomier.)
I have no motivation left.
- 1 more time? - What about number 4?
- Number four? - Right? No?
- Number 4. - Number 4.
(2 unlucky members had chosen number 4.)
(What will happen this time?)
- It can't be another dud. - It can't be.
(Dud)
It's a dud again.
- It's a dud again. - It's a dud again.
- It's another dud. - Okay!
(We still have hope.)
- It's a dud again. - It's a dud again.
Gosh.
We have to get the question right. All the duds have been removed.
- We have to. - We can get past them.
This time, we have to win.
All right.
Here is the question.
"In the ondol system,"
"what is the passage for fire and smoke..."
"called?"
Seok Jin definitely knows it.
(He has used ondol.)
For generations...
His father actually...
worked for an ondol company.
(His father worked for an ondol company.)
He didn't.
(I can't go along with that.)
(Leave my parents alone.)
- Gosh. - Get your facts straight.
I mean...
My father didn't.
He goes along with most jokes,
but he couldn't this time.
He changed my father's job.
(Jokes about family are not accepted.)
All right. "Number one,"
"gorae."
"Number two, geobuk."
- "Geobuk"? - "Number three, yeou."
"Number four, ori."
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
Number one, "gorae".
(It's a chance to win 15 points at once.)
"Gorae".
- Okay! - What did I say?
- Trust me. - "Rae" means...
"Rae" means "passage".
What a shame. I knew it too.
This...
- All of number 4. - All of number 4.
- Open it! - It's "gorae".
- Five. - Okay!
(Their score goes up.)
- 8. - 8.
11.
- 7. - 7.
(Frustrated)
(The situation reversed at once.)
Unbelievable.
- 11. - 11.
(They win 15 points in total.)
15 points!
Nice!
- Stop! - Stop!
(We won't repeat the same mistake.)
(Stop)
- Go! - Go!
(They try to egg on their opponent.)
- You stop here? - Go! Kwang Soo!
You petty!
- Just one more round. - Stop!
- Just one more. - No. Stop.
- One more round. - If we make a mistake,
- we won't be able to recover. - Just one more round.
We won't be able to recover.
Okay. We have to win.
We have to win this time.
Here we go.
"The name of this island means..."
"'a beaming island'."
- "A beaming island"? - I know this one.
"Number one, Silmi Island."
"Number two, Anmyeon Island."
"Number three, Wan Island."
"Number four, Jeju Island."
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
(Team Ace wants to answer right away.)
- What's your answer? - "Wan Island".
- "Wan Island"? - "Wan Island"?
- Isn't it "Anmyeon Island"? - Let me answer!
(Team Ace is not sure.)
Number four, "Jeju Island".
(While other members are not sure, Jae Seok says, "Jeju Island".)
(If it's correct, the situation might reverse.)
It's "Wan Island"!
(Frustrated)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
(It's Team Champion's turn.)
- Isn't it "Wan Island"? - Isn't it "Silmi Island"?
- I think it's number 3. - Isn't it number 1?
(Team Champion thinks the correct answer is "Wan Island".)
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
Number one, "Silmi Island".
No.
- It's wrong. - It's wrong?
(Why did you suddenly say, "Silmi Island"?)
It's "Wan Island".
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
"Wan Island".
- What number? - Number Three.
Number three, "Wan Island".
(Seok Jin sounds confident. Is it correct?)
(Correct)
- We did it! - Nice!
- We knew it was number three. - Please.
Please discuss first.
I said it was "Wan Island" from the beginning.
- We just need 6 points. - 6 points.
- Six points. - I'm nervous.
- I'm nervous. Just six points. - Let's do this.
- They need six points. - Right.
They need more than five points,
so they'll have to keep trying.
Ji Hyo, just do whatever you want.
Gosh.
Just follow your gut.
Just do it.
(Will Ji Hyo manage to win more than 6 points?)
You have golden hands.
Go.
- Number 6. - Number 6.
- Okay. - Number six.
(No one has touched number 6 yet. What will be the result?)
- It's not a dud. - It has points.
- 3 points! - Just 1 more.
(Amazing)
- Just 1 more. - Just 1 more.
- Another 3 points. - Another 3 points.
- Another 3 points. - This doesn't feel right.
(If they choose a dud, they'll lose.)
Either number 1 or 10.
(They can't seem to decide.)
Would number seven be a dud?
I think it's a dud.
Either a dud or one point.
Please.
(What is her next choice?)
- Just relax. - Okay. I choose number five.
- Number 5. - Number 5.
(The ace's guess)
(Number 5 has not been opened either.)
Three points.
(Will they catch up?)
Please. One point.
(Or is it a dud?)
- I'll open it. 1, 2, 3. - Please.
One point.
(1 point)
- Okay. - This is not okay.
I can't do this.
I'm so nervous.
(Their life is prolonged.)
- I'm so nervous. - I can't do this.
- I don't like it. - My heart is going to burst.
Ji Hyo.
- My heart. - Please.
I'm so nervous.
- Here it comes. - Please!
- Here it comes. - Dud!
Why did it have to be one point?
- Please. - Here it comes.
- Dud! - Dud!
- Dud! - Ji Hyo, please.
It's up to you.
(It's all up to the ace now.)
(She has a hard time making up her mind.)
Ji Hyo, number 10.
(Ji Hyo, number 10.)
(Is he feeling something?)
(Jae Seok suddenly says, "number 10".)
(Number 10 has never been opened.)
- Number 10. - Don't listen. It's a dud.
(He can't be feeling something.)
I want them to listen to Jae Seok.
(The legendary unlucky man)
(Jae Seok makes Ji Hyo think.)
I choose number five.
(She chooses number 5.)
Number five?
- Please! - Number five?
- Number 5? - Suddenly number 5?
Let's go.
- Number five. - Kwang Soo, please!
- Number five. - Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
If it's not a dud, we lose.
Kwang Soo, please!
Let's go!
(They're only one point apart.)
I'll open it.
One,
two...
(How will this tight game end?)
Three.
(2 points)
(She sure is the ace.)
(Final score, 16:15)
(Team Ace wins.)
(Unbelievable)
(Is it my fault?)
- Ji Hyo! - I knew it.
(Ji Hyo made the right choice.)
- Okay. - What's number 10?
Number 10?
- I chose number 10. - See?
(Jae Seok's choice, number 10, is a dud.)
(How do you do this?)
(Good that they didn't listen to him.)
Please listen to Jae Seok.
It's okay. We did well.
Okay! We won first round!
(Team Ace wins Round 1.)
- Yes! - We fought well.
I can't believe it.
(Team Ace: 5 slots, Team Champion:1 slot)
(The historic competition gets fiercer and fiercer.)
(What is the next game?)
Players are entering!
Let's go!
Ji Hyo is unbelievable.
She is...
More than 1 person wanted to choose number 10.
She is incredible.
Here is the Round Two.
Each team starts with five slots on the roulette wheel each.
In each round, you bet a number of slots.
The winning team of the round wins as many slots as they bet.
After hearing the keyword of each round, the team leaders will...
select players for that round...
and decide how many slots they will bet on those players.
Who can I trust?
Jong Kook hates thinking.
Here are the keywords.
First round, "water".
Second round, "fire".
Third round, "foot".
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
Do you want to choose me for "water"?
- Okay. - Can't team leaders participate?
- They can. - They can.
Ji Hyo should play too.
(We need our ace to play.)
(Who will play for Team Ace?)
"Fire" might mean...
spicy food.
I can't eat spicy food.
- Right. - Right?
(They have to guess the games and select the right players.)
- Bet a lot on me. - Hold on.
(You trust me, right?)
(I love your confidence.)
Jong Kook for "foot" and Kwang Soo for "water".
We have to win this round.
- Next round... - We have to win.
Let's start.
(They have selected players and made bets.)
The keyword for the first round is "water".
The game is called...
Ball over the Water.
Blow the team's ping-pong ball.
The ball can only move...
to the cups in the team's color or white cups.
The team whose ball gets to the last cup first wins.
(It sounds hard.)
Jae Seok...
Let's hope they didn't choose Se Chan.
- Gosh. - It sounds hard.
(Who are the players?)
- Let me introduce the players. - Okay.
Yu Jae Seok for Team Ace.
(Team Ace chose Jae Seok.)
(Good that his mouth sticks out.)
For Team Champion...
(Team Champion)
Lee Kwang Soo.
(The cheater brothers will compete.)
I knew it'd be Kwang Soo.
(Every time they compete, something dirty happens.)
(The two are known for playing dirty.)
(They focus more on playing dirty than winning.)
(What will they do today?)
Okay. It'll be a dirty game.
- We'll... - All right.
- Kwang Soo. - Okay.
Today you can be as dirty...
- as you want. - Okay.
(You can be dirty too.)
- It's your day. - I choose the color green.
(Team Ace's Yu Jae Seok versus Team Champion's Lee Kwang Soo)
This cup?
We have to get there first? Okay.
You have to go diagonally.
1, 2, 3, 4. Do you understand?
We have advantage. Our player's mouth sticks out more.
Ready.
(The "water" game starts.)
Okay.
(Jae Seok cheats as soon as the game starts.)
He blew the other team's ball.
No.
(I stopped Kwang Soo.)
Good. Kwang Soo is doing well.
(Kwang Soo's ball moves on to the next cup.)
(Keep going!)
(But he fails to move the ball to the next cup.)
You should fill the cup with more water.
- Fill the cup. - There's not enough water.
There you go.
Kwang Soo, stop.
(I think it's coming.)
(The cheating spirit is coming.)
Here it comes.
(The cheating spirit fills him.)
- He used his hand. - No.
His hand...
(He touched the ball.)
(Frustrated)
- His hand... - It wasn't intentional.
I didn't do it on purpose.
You can't blow the other's ball.
You can't, right?
- Kwang Soo used his hand. - He didn't mean to.
(They're still near the starting line.)
Relax.
Put your hand away.
(Jong Kook protects the ball with his hand.)
(Blowing)
There you go!
It worked! The ball moved over.
(Good job, Jae Seok.)
Okay. Good.
(Jae Seok keeps moving forward.)
(Continue to the last cup.)
Good. Keep going.
(I can't let you.)
Keep going.
(The cheater brothers...)
(play dirty as always.)
- My goodness. - It's flooding here.
(Flooding)
Is this how this game is played?
(Is this how this game is played?)
(Yes, it is.)
The game is too dirty.
- He did it! Kwang Soo! - He did it!
(Kwang Soo pulls himself together and moves forward.)
He did it! When did you come this far?
- He's here! - Let's go.
Good. We can win.
(Will you get out of my way?)
(I don't think so.)
(Jae Seok splashes water on Kwang Soo.)
(It's as if they're playing the game in the water.)
- Jae Seok, why don't you come here? - Okay.
- Come here. - I'll try.
- Almost there. - Come here.
Good. Kwang Soo, just one more.
Kwang Soo, you can do this.
- Gosh. - Blow lightly.
Put your head away.
(Jae Seok hasn't moved.)
You're almost there.
- Okay! - Just one more!
(Kwang Soo's ball is only one cup away from the destination.)
- Good! Kwang Soo, just one more! - You can do this.
Just one more!
- Kwang Soo. - No.
Stop him.
(Jae Seok falls behind.)
Jae Seok, stop him!
Kwang Soo, focus.
(Kwang Soo's ball is right in front of the destination.)
(It's just one cup away.)
Kwang Soo, focus.
(Everything depends on Kwang Soo's one final blow. Can he finish it well?)
(Kwang Soo is preparing his final blow.)
Kwang Soo, focus.
(With Jae Seok lagging behind, I'll finish the game.)
(What?)
He did it!
(Jae Seok moved over 3 cups at once...)
(and finished the game.)
(He blew hard enough to move over 3 cups.)
(It's so thrilling to come from behind and win.)
(Shocked)
Why weren't you blowing?
I couldn't see anything because of the water in my eyes.
(Team Champion loses.)
- I did it! - Hey.
Hold on. Where did it come from?
(Let me analyze my winning factors.)
(His protruding mouth helped.)
It jumped so high.
(Thanks to his mouth, he could blow hard.)
This is amazing.
Team Ace wins the first round.
How many did they bet? That's important.
Let me tell you how many slots they bet.
- I hope it's 1. - Is it more than 2?
(How many slots did Team Ace bet on Jae Seok?)
3 slots.
(Team Ace wins 3 slots.)
(It was a good idea.)
We bet three slots.
Hold on. They bet three slots on Jae Seok only?
- How could they do that? - Three slots on Jae Seok?
Look at my team.
(You'll understand.)
(There are not many to rely on.)
He won, so I can't say anything.
Other than Jae Seok, there are not many...
- There are not... - We're like that.
- My team is like that. - We're like that.
The keyword for the second round is "fire".
The game is called One Candle.
(One Candle)
Hold a candle in one hand, and a plate in the other.
Put out the other's candle using your plate, and you win.
If you put out your own candle by mistake, you lose.
- Be careful. - It sounds fun.
You should have played this. You're so tall.
No one could have reached his candle.
(It could have protected my candle perfectly.)
If Kwang Soo played this, he would have won.
(We chose the wrong players.)
- It's a shame. - We chose the wrong players.
Let me introduce the players for the second round.
For Team Champion,
Jeon So Min.
Okay.
(So Min is the weakest one.)
- It's okay. You can do it. - And...
- for Team Ace... - We'll win.
(Who will compete against So Min?)
Song Ji Hyo.
How did we choose these two?
Good.
Unbelievable.
(Ji Hyo beat So Min twice in the past.)
(Will So Min be able to stop Ji Hyo's winning streak?)
- We still have a chance. - So Min.
- Let's do this! - So Min.
We'll teach you a lesson.
(The ace gets ready to fight.)
We'll definitely win.
Ji Hyo is tying her hair up. It's over.
Ji Hyo is tying her hair up. You can't even do that, can you?
(He's being childish.)
Ji Hyo...
"You can't even do that"?
You don't need to do that. Your hair is too short.
I'm taller.
I'm taller than her.
And my arms are strangely long.
I think you'll be fine. Your arms are really long.
They're really long.
- Finish her. - Like this...
- and this? - Yes.
Finish her.
Stand in the middle with your backs against each other.
I'm nervous.
- Let's go. - Be careful.
- If we win this... - It can go out easily.
- You can do this. - If we win this, it's over.
We can't lose.
(Ji Hyo versus So Min)
So Min, relax. It's okay. There's nothing else you can do.
- Ji Hyo, relax. - Finish her.
Ready.
One.
(Careful)
Two.
Three.
(Put out the other's candle without putting out your own.)
(The "fire" game starts.)
So Min is a coward.
She is scared of the candle wax dripping.
(He attacks with childish words.)
So Min, try to put out Ji Hyo's candle.
Attack. Good.
Use the plate.
- Good. - Okay.
- There you go. - Nice.
(So Min defends her candle.)
So Min. Be careful. Move slowly.
(Her candle almost went out.)
- What are you doing? - Move your left hand slowly.
(Ji Hyo counterattacks.)
(So Min uses her long arms.)
(But...)
No. Raise it.
(So Min's candle flickers again.)
(She revives her candle...)
(and counterattacks.)
(Flickering)
If you move, your candle might go out.
You're doing well.
- Good. - Keep going.
- It's okay. - She can't reach your candle.
- It's okay. - Attack!
You have to attack!
- Stop running away and attack! - Attack!
You have to attack. Stop running away.
- You have to attack. - Stop running away.
(Ji Hyo makes everyone run away.)
Good.
Good, Ji Hyo.
So Min, your candle is higher.
Yes.
Her arms are so long. Good.
(They take quick steps while waiving their plates.)
(It reminds you of the ballet, "Swan Lake".)
(Ji Hyo is an elegant and aggressive swan.)
(So Min is a black swan that escapes from Ji Hyo using her long wings.)
(It suddenly turns into "Black Swan".)
So Min has long arms.
Ji Hyo's arms and legs are short.
They're about the same height, but Ji Hyo's arms are shorter.
(Jae Seok attacks his team leader.)
(Why are you dissing me?)
- Jae Seok. Why... - It's your chance!
It's your chance, So Min! Attack!
Why would you attack your team member?
Ji Hyo is faltering.
(Unstable)
It might go out.
So Min, don't move too fast.
- Move slowly. - Ji Hyo.
(The black swan almost puts out her own candle.)
As you're about to go to the right, go to the left.
As you're about to go to the left, go to the right.
- Hit it with your knee. - Go.
So Min, be bold and start a physical fight.
Start a physical fight.
Ji Hyo, step on her foot.
- That's good. - You can step on her foot.
- That's good. - No, don't do that.
(She's better at running away.)
No.
(She runs away from the swan.)
(She's on her toes without realizing it.)
- No, don't do that. - Don't run away.
Don't run away.
- Just hit her. - I can't do it.
- Don't run away. - Their hands might hurt.
(Let's attack for real instead of running away.)
(Has the black swan started to flap?)
(Flapping)
Gosh, that's quite strong.
(The blow is quite strong.)
- That's good. - Goodness.
That's good.
(They're on their toes.)
- Hey. - Do it more.
(Stop running away.)
So Min's went out.
(While she was running away,)
(So Min's candle goes out.)
(Dignity of the ace of 9 years)
It went out.
(Her opponent loses for her.)
- That's amazing. - It went out as she ran away.
What's going on with our team?
- We're a perfect team. - Seriously.
(Team Champion loses again.)
We're in trouble.
How could she expose her back?
Jong Kook is very upset right now.
- Wait a minute. - Jong Kook is...
- Okay. - He's angry.
- Jong Kook. - It's over.
Good job.
The winner of the second round is...
- Team Ace. - Okay.
It's unbelievable.
- We won everything. - We keep winning.
I bet wind would come out if I stretch out my hand.
We win everything.
How many slots did the leader of Team Ace bet?
(Team Ace wins slots for the "fire" game.)
How many did they bet? That's more important.
(How many slots did she bet?)
- It's one slot. - Okay.
- What about you? - It's one slot.
- We need to get it back. - We should.
We have to get it no matter what.
Keyword for third round is feet.
- The category is... - Be something we're good at.
Give us a game that requires strength.
How about who kicks harder?
(They're confident about strength.)
Make it about strength.
Who can stomp harder?
- Goodness. - Stomping.
(It can't be a game like that.)
The game is called Why Can't You Eat?
(Foot game is Why Can't You Eat.)
- Do we eat with our feet? - Is it eating?
- Is it eating? - Do we eat with our feet?
While sitting, control a hanging piece of bread...
attached to a string with your toes.
The team that eats the bread first wins.
- We definitely can do it. - Goodness.
(The eldest Seok Jin is the hope of people in their middle age.)
(Jong kook is the champion who can do everything well.)
Goodness, okay.
Let's win everything.
Hang some chicken breast instead of bread.
(He asks for a change in food.)
(Jong Kook doesn't like flour.)
- Shake. - How about chicken shake?
Okay.
Usually Jong Kook and Seok Jin...
- don't compete with each other. - That's true.
Get ready.
(The "foot" game starts.)
He'll eat it.
(It lands immediately on his tongue.)
Jong Kook is eating it.
- Wait a minute, Jong Kook. - Jong Kook is eating it.
(Pushing)
He's angry right now.
(The eldest rookie is at east and cheats.)
Think of LA.
It's LA. He's eating it.
(His appetite increases at the thought of LA.)
Goodness, he looks scary.
- Do I eat more? - Does he have to eat all?
- He has to eat all. - Eat until where the cup is.
(Based on their performance...)
Seok Jin, you have to eat it.
(Only the champion might go to LA.)
- He only ate the end. - Jong Kook is impressive.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin, you got it.
(Seok Jin's bread is barely close to his mouth.)
That's good.
You got it.
- You're my role model. - You got it.
- You got it. - You got it.
He's melting it with his tongue.
(It's how the eldest member eats bread.)
- He soaks it while eating it. - It'll take a long time.
- It must be sweet. - He soaks it.
(He melts it with his tongue.)
Gosh, he finally ate it.
- More and more. - That's not bad.
He's eating it. He's smart.
(He's eating at a fast speed.)
A little bit more.
Use your foot. Even for Jong Kook,
it isn't easy.
It's neck-and-neck.
That's good.
(He fails to control it near his face.)
(He's good at lifting his leg though.)
I feel bad for Seok Jin.
At his age, he'd be a director at a company.
- He's 54. - 54.
- 54, 54, 54. - 54, 54, 54.
(Instead of being a director, he pours his heart to entertainment.)
A little bit more.
(He makes a veteran's sound.)
Your nose made a loud sound. Are you okay?
(What was that sound?)
(Did he get injured?)
Jong Kook is laughing too.
Jong Kook is laughing because it's unbelievable.
It's a father's challenge.
(Suddenly, he becomes a father.)
That's good. You have one chance.
Pull.
(Dad, I brought bread. Why can't you eat it?)
Poor Seok Jin.
(While Seok Jin can't eat his bread...)
- He got it. - Goodness.
(He ate one-third of it.)
Poor Seok Jin, what do we do?
He got it. Okay.
A little more.
(He takes a big bite.)
(Jong Kook has one bite left.)
You're done after one more bite.
- He's almost done. - Come on.
Just eat it in one go.
Do you think it's possible?
(Kicking)
My role model kicked me.
(Is that how he is?)
(Focus on eating.)
Okay.
(I'm working on it.)
Come on. That's it.
My role model is cheating.
(His love for Seok Jin is destroyed.)
- Be quiet. - Be quiet.
Be quiet, Haha.
Just be quiet.
It's because my leg is too long.
(Shall we cheat a little too?)
Why doesn't it work when it worked before?
It should come down.
- It worked before. - It passed.
(Slapping)
(He catches their cheating.)
It's our team's business.
You pushed it in too much.
- I'm sorry. I didn't know. - What are you doing?
- It's right here. - Yes, it's right there.
(Ji Hyo is about to feed Seok Jin.)
- Eat it. - Goodness.
I got it.
A little bit closer.
(Jong Kook's bread descends vertically.)
It came down.
(He takes his last bite with all his might.)
- It's coming. - Come on.
Okay.
- Eat the long piece. - Suck it in.
(Chew it quickly.)
(Pull it, Team Leader.)
(At that time)
(Jong Kook tears it.)
(The champion wins.)
Okay!
You got it.
- You're sweating. - Jong Kook.
(We'll take you home.)
Good job.
(My leg hurts.)
(Massaging)
- My goodness. - That's impressive.
It didn't come off.
I didn't know Jong Kook liked bread so much.
(He gets annoying.)
(He forces a new palate on him.)
Jong Kook is enjoying the bread.
Why did you eat chicken breast until now?
(You turned into a lover of bread.)
(Despite Seok Jin's efforts, the champion wins.)
The winner of the third round is...
Team Champion.
Okay.
(It's the first win for Team Champion.)
They didn't bet four, did they?
That's impossible.
How many roulette slots did Jong Kook bet?
(How many slots will Team Champion gain?)
It's two slots.
(Team Champion wins 2 slots.)
(We're still way ahead.)
- They did well. - So Min.
The current total is...
Team Ace has 9 slots. Team Champion has 3 slots.
They're not even close.
Why do they have so little?
- It's okay. - Next is the last round.
- Let's go. - We can do it.
I'll bet my life.
(Who will be the winner?)
It's the last round.
Okay, it's the last. If we win this round,
we'll be one step closer to LA.
- That's true. - It's getting better.
Ace versus the Champion, La La Land Race.
It's the last round for a trip to LA as a prize.
Trust Me Half Way.
(Trust Me Half Way)
(Ace versus the Champion, Round 3)
Within the limited time, cut the given ingredient...
exactly in half.
The person who is more accurate wins.
You win two points if you cut it exactly in half.
Two points?
- Cut it exactly? - Really?
It's important to estimate well.
Everyone, this game is...
currently very popular abroad.
- It's popular. - Many people play this?
- Okay. - We must win insider game too.
For the first round,
pick a player from your team.
Who shall play first?
- Shall I go first? - Yes, go, Se Chan.
I'll start.
- How about Seok Jin? - I'll go.
Okay.
First round is Seok Jin versus Se Chan.
Here's the first ingredient.
Please bring the ingredient.
What could it be?
What's that?
(Surprised)
- They're eggplant. - That's good.
- The top and bottom are different. - Right.
I need to find the center of gravity.
Look how scientific Seok Jin is.
You have one minute from now.
Put the halves on the scales in one minute.
Get ready.
Start.
[VIU Ver] SBS E438 Running Man
"the Ace versus the Champion"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(They both try to find the center of gravity.)
(Weighing)
(At that time)
This is it, but the left side is a bit heavier.
Seok Jin put it on his finger.
Seok Jin found the center.
He's like someone at KAIST.
Someone at NASA.
(Why can't I find the center of gravity?)
I'll try to guess.
- Here he goes. - Here he goes.
(I got it.)
You have 10 seconds left.
- 10 seconds. - 9.
- 8. - 8.
(Se Chan starts to cut as well.)
(Let's go, Seok Jin. Let's go, Se Chan.)
- 3. - 3.
(Careful)
(Seok Jin cuts confidently while Se Chan cuts carefully.)
Okay, you'll put it up 1 by 1.
Why did you cut it slanted?
(Wait a minute, why did you cut it slanted?)
That one is very slanted.
- Did you slice it diagonally? - Wait.
Why did you cut it slanted?
At least he didn't cut his finger.
It's very slanted.
Seok Jin will put them on the scales.
- Put them 1 by 1. - This one is heavier.
(Seok Jin's first eggplant's weight)
1 by 1.
It's exactly 70g.
Okay.
We don't know yet.
- We don't know. - Here I go.
I'll do this one.
(Se Chan's first eggplant's weight)
It's 66g.
That sounds good.
The sizes are similar. It's good.
- It'd be amazing if it's 70g. - That'd be amazing.
Let's see.
(How much does Seok Jin's second eggplant weigh?)
(The closer it is to 70g, he has a higher chance of winning.)
Let's see.
It's 60g.
The difference is 10g.
(Is the result 10g?)
- Why? - We don't know yet.
66g sounds good.
(Seok Jin's result is disappointing.)
I'll put it on.
(How much does Se Chan's second eggplant weigh?)
(If the difference is less than 10g, Se Chan wins.)
(Se Chan's difference is 2g.)
- Okay. - That was good.
(Is the difference really 2g?)
- Okay, it's 2g. - My goodness.
(Se Chan wins.)
- Did I do well? - You did.
- Tell me. - Good job.
(He cut it so well.)
- Se Chan wins the first round. - Okay.
- Okay. - I didn't have high expectations.
Our team is coming back.
- Scores tie if we win one more. - Who's next?
So Min or Kwang Soo?
- I'll go. - Okay, So Min.
- Who's next? - I'll go.
Haha.
- Cut it slowly. - I'm too anxious.
- That was so close. - Do it, Haha.
- It's Haha. - You're in the restaurant business.
However, I don't go in the kitchen.
Here's the second ingredient.
I hope it's an easy one.
That one is...
- What is it? - What?
What is it? Is it gimbap?
This one is difficult.
- Goodness. - The inside is protruding.
It's important where the rice is.
The timer will start. You have one minute.
It's nothing, but it's not easy.
- It makes us focused. - I'm nervous.
Trust your feeling.
- I went to many gimbap restaurants. - That's good.
I'm nervous.
This is interesting.
Try to feel the weight with the finger.
Adjust it.
If you squeeze it more, gimbap might burst.
- You'll be in trouble. - Right.
All right. 10, 9.
You have to decide.
- Decide, Haha. - Eight.
(Haha takes the knife.)
- Do it slowly. - Take your time.
(I'll show you what it means to work in the restaurant business.)
- I think this is it. - It is.
- You have to cut it carefully. - Cut it well.
- Cut it straight. - Cut it carefully.
- That's right. - Right.
- You got it. - It's neat.
That's right.
- You got it. - That was great.
You got it, So Min.
That's right.
(Slicing)
It's done.
(Haha shows his meticulous cutting.)
Let's start with Haha.
Put it on the scale.
- This is... - Right?
You did a good job.
(Haha's first gimbap's weight)
- 144g. - 144g.
- This looks heavier. - It's okay.
This one looks heavier too.
It just seems that way.
(So Min's first gimbap's weight)
Why are there two grains of rice?
134g.
- It's okay. - His was 144g.
- Both gimbap don't weigh the same. - No.
Weigh the other one.
(It's time to weigh the second piece.)
(Will the 2nd one weigh close to 144g?)
You're in the restaurant business.
(With Haha's senses)
- It's 136g. - 136g.
(Haha's difference is 8g.)
It's 136g.
(8g is a little risky.)
This is difficult. It's hard.
- Is it me? - It should be in 130s.
If it's 8g, we have a chance to win.
(How much does So Min's second gimbap weigh?)
Here we go, So Min.
You got it.
(So Min wins if the difference is less than 8g.)
- It's 136g. - It's 2g.
(The difference is 2g again.)
- The difference keeps being 2g. - 2g.
(So Min wins.)
- My goodness. - Why are they so good?
Okay, I'll go this time.
- Jae Seok? - I'll do it, Ji Hyo.
If you lose, it's over.
(If Team Ace loses again, they lose Round 3.)
- Kwang Soo. - That's right.
- Let's keep going. - Kwang Soo is good at it.
It isn't easy.
(Stop right there, Team Champion. Here comes the game expert.)
Sir.
(It's a war of nerves.)
He's a troublemaker.
Don't stab each other.
Here's the third ingredient.
- This one is difficult. - It's difficult.
- Here's the third ingredient. - This one is difficult.
It's difficult.
Goodness.
This one is too difficult.
Come on.
- It has a strange shape. - The shape isn't smooth.
It's cabbage.
It's difficult.
This one is too difficult.
How is it possible?
If your cut is slanted...
Do I have to cut it once with a knife?
Yes.
All right.
One minute on the clock starts now.
It's too difficult.
How do I do it?
- Is there a method? - It's difficult.
I can't find the middle either.
The shape is not even.
My goodness.
It's hard to find the center.
Shall I apply the Pythagorean theorem?
(Is he that educated?)
I'll use Newton's Laws.
"Newton's Laws"?
You should apply Murphy's law.
"Murphy's law"?
- It's confusing. - Isn't it protruding this way?
How about here?
There's no way.
Don't talk to him. Just trust your feeling.
Trust your feeling, Jae Seok.
(Kwang Soo searches with Newton's Laws.)
If you pin it, it will balance.
Wait.
- Don't make marks with the knife. - Don't do that.
Kwang Soo.
Don't make marks with the knife.
- Kwang Soo. - He cut it.
- He cut it. - What are you doing?
- You have to cut it right there. - Kwang Soo.
(What?)
What are you doing?
- Kwang Soo. - 10 seconds?
(It's time to cut it.)
- I'll slice it. - It's based on luck.
Cut well in the middle.
The one who cuts it well will win. Watch out.
It's too slanted.
You should cut it a little slanted.
- He cut it. - It's already done.
(There's no turning back.)
- Turn to the left. - To the left.
- To the left. - Yes, cut straight.
Just cut it.
- Okay, I got it. - He cut it well.
Everyone.
- Jae Seok, put it on first. - Goodness.
It's done.
- They weigh about the same. - Some fell off.
(Wait, some fell off.)
Put them on here.
They fell off.
Are you ready?
They weigh about the same.
If we lose, is it over?
If they weigh the same, you get two points.
- Put it on, Jae Seok. - Gosh.
(Will Jae Seok save his team?)
(Jae Seok's first cabbage's weight)
- It's 1,192g. - 1,192g.
Does it weigh 1kg?
All right, Kwang Soo.
Put it on, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo's first cabbage's weight)
It's 1,278g. Jae Seok?
It's okay. We don't know who won.
(No one knows who the winner is.)
(They weigh the first piece of cabbage.)
If you think they're similar, you're right.
(The problem is the weight of the second piece.)
(How much does Jae Seok's second cabbage weigh?)
(The closer it is to 1,192g, he has a higher chance of winning.)
It's 1,254g. You did well.
It's not bad.
- You did well. - It's not bad.
It isn't bad, right?
- It's 62g. - The difference is 62g.
- Ours will be... - Kwang Soo's was 1,278g.
- It's a bit heavier. - I think so.
(If the difference is less than 62g, Team Champion wins.)
(Will Kwang Soo lead his team to victory?)
(Let's see how Team Champion does.)
- What? - What is it?
(Kwang Soo's difference is 68g.)
(Did we lose?)
- What's the difference? - 6g.
Did we win?
- We won. - Jae Seok won.
Okay, okay.
- Okay. - Good job.
It was difficult.
This saved us.
- It's okay. - You did well.
- It couldn't be helped. - Good job.
If Ji Hyo wins, we go to the final round.
- Ji Hyo. - Let's go.
(Only two players remain.)
- It's a match between team leaders. - Yes.
- All right. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - If Jong Kook wins, game is over.
If Ji Hyo wins, we go to Round Five.
- Let's go, Ji Hyo. - Let's go.
Let's go to LA.
(What will be their ingredient?)
Next ingredient is...
eggs.
- Eggs? - Boiled eggs?
This one is difficult.
It's cooked.
(The ingredient is fragile.)
- How is it possible? - It's cooked.
It's dented.
(Key is that it's dented.)
How can you cut this in half?
Jong Kook has touched them countless times.
- Jong Kook. - But...
- You must have an idea. - This is a different matter.
It's a matter of figuring out...
- where the yolk leans. - That's right.
- Yes. - She is right.
The yolk could lean heavily to one side.
Ji Hyo, feel it lightly.
- Think about the shape. - You have a minute.
(The last round starts.)
Staring at it won't help you.
- She took the knife right away. - You can't go back once it's in.
Ji Hyo, go with your gut feeling.
There is no other way.
(Ji Hyo moves in with a knife.)
This is really hard.
Eggs are hard.
You can't make it stand.
(It's tricky.)
Move it a bit to the left.
- Ji Hyo is cutting it. - Is she cutting it already?
(At that moment)
- She is cutting it. - I can see the yolk.
- She is cutting it. - The left side seems a bit bigger.
Forget it. It's over.
- Go with it. - Which side has more yolk?
She cut it nearly in half.
I think she cut it nearly in half.
Ji Hyo cut it really well.
All right.
(Jong Kook was using the original tactics.)
- Jong Kook, the yolk... - I lost some of it.
It shouldn't be sticking out.
It lost some of it.
Why is there so much yolk on the knife?
(Why is there so much yolk on the knife?)
- What is this? - You got this.
- Gosh. - Let's go.
- Ji Hyo, put a piece on the scale. - We won.
- I think we lost. - Put a piece on the scale.
We won.
(What's the weight of the 1st half of Ji Hyo's egg?)
My goodness.
Put a piece on the scale.
(Ji Hyo's first egg’s weight)
18g.
- 18g. - I think we lost.
- I think we lost. - Ji Hyo.
We will put one on a scale.
Go ahead.
I think this one is heavy.
(Jong Kook’s first egg’s weight)
- I think this one is heavy. - 20g.
- It weighs 20g. - 20g.
Ji Hyo, put the second piece on the scale.
(Everything depends on the weight of the second half of her egg.)
If Ji Hyo wins, we will move on to the final round. Ji Hyo.
Let's go.
(What's the weight of the 2nd half of Ji Hyo's egg?)
Put the second piece on a scale.
20g. The difference is 2g.
- The difference is 2g. - We won.
She really is incredible.
(Ji Hyo really is incredible.)
If we win, we will have another round.
We won't be able to beat 2g.
You never know.
2g is...
(The 2nd half of Jong Kook's egg gets weighed.)
(If the difference is within 2g, Jong Kook will win.)
(What's the weight of the 2nd half of Jong Kook's egg?)
- What? It weighs 20g. - It weighs 20g.
20g.
20g! 20g!
(He cut it exactly in half.)
(The difference is 0g.)
We did it.
This is incredible.
(They can't help but admit defeat.)
We admit defeat.
- This is incredible. - My goodness.
The yolk on the knife did it.
- Seriously. - The yolk on the knife did it.
- We would have lost otherwise. - Seriously.
How is this possible?
We won two points.
(Team Champion gets 2 points.)
I can't believe it.
- How can it weigh 20g? - We admit defeat.
(The final score is 4 to 1.)
Team Champion gets five slots...
- and Team Ace gets one slot. - That's enough.
- Our chance is about the same. - It's enough.
- It's enough. - Team Ace has 10 slots...
and Team Champion has eight slots in total.
- Okay. We have more slots. - Our chance is about the same.
- It's enough. - We can do this.
It depends on luck.
Between the Ace and Champion, who will win?
I am curious about the result.
Who will be luckier?
The numbers are about the same, so let's take turns.
Okay.
(They fill up the slots on the final roulette.)
One slot at a time.
Between the Ace and Champion, who will win?
I am curious about the result.
Who will be luckier?
Ji Hyo is better with roulettes.
(Will it be Ji Hyo or Jong Kook?)
I am so nervous. I am so nervous.
- Okay. - There is no way of knowing.
Let's have three consecutive slots.
Gosh, that's...
That won't make us lose.
That might make us lose.
It will be incredible if it stops there.
- Goodness. - Okay.
I hope it stops at the three consecutive slots.
- It's a single take. - It's a single take, right?
- Spin it together. - Spin it together.
One should spin upward, and the other should spin downward.
Spin downward. I will spin upward.
Should I spin downward?
(How romantic!)
- What are you doing? - For goodness' sake.
- I will spin downward. - Spin downward. I will spin upward.
We get excited about the smallest things.
One.
(They still need to discern the winner.)
Two.
(The final round of Ace versus the Champion)
- Three. - Here it goes.
(They spun the final roulette together.)
Here it goes.
(Who will be chosen as the winner by the spirit of roulette?)
- I'm curious about the result. - I'm curious.
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo.
- The three consecutive slots. - Ji Hyo.
(The roulette slows down.)
(Will the three consecutive slots be effective?)
- The three consecutive slots. - Ji Hyo.
(It passes Ji Hyo's three consecutive slots...)
(and goes towards the mixed slots.)
- The three consecutive slots. - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo. Will it go past this slot?
(It stops at Song Ji Hyo.)
(Team Ace wins.)
She is incredible.
(Ji Hyo always wins.)
- Ji Hyo. - What is your deal?
I will sleep in LA!
(Ji Hyo is at the level to go to LA to sleep.)
- Ji Hyo is amazing. - Will you go there to sleep?
(I give honor to my team.)
This is incredible.
The Champion lost to Ace.
Ace is the best.
- She is the best at roulette. - You can't win...
- against Ace. - Ace is the best.
You are so lucky, Ji Hyo.
I was hoping that Jong Kook would go on a trip.
The roulette chose her.
The true ace, Song Ji Hyo!
(The true ace, Song Ji Hyo)
- I want her luck. - Seriously.
She is incredible.