(On a wintry day with the bluest sky...)
Hello. Good morning.
(Is he doing the opening segment alone?)
- Hi. - Hello.
Hi.
(Feeling relaxed since it's the morning)
- Today, - Yes.
the member with the most amount of money will win the race.
Today's race is called the Great War of Money.
(The member with the most money will win today's race.)
I just need to have the most amount of money?
You will carry out a mission with passers-by to get the basic fund.
- A mission with passers-by? - Yes.
You will freely form teams with your members...
to accomplish the mission.
The team with 4 members will acquire 800 dollars.
I must be in the team of four.
The team with 2 members will acquire 300 dollars.
If you're alone, you will go against another single member.
The winning member gets 150 dollars and the losing member gets 50.
Money, money, money!
(When teams are formed, a mission will be given out.)
I must be in the team with four members.
That means I must join the team with four members.
(Should I gather some members?)
I'm the most certain this member will join me.
We were on the same team the most.
(Let's gather some members.)
(Who is the member that formed teams with Jae Seok the most?)
- Gosh, Se Chan. - Yes, Jae Seok.
You know that you were my first call, right?
I do think so.
Where are you, Se Chan?
I'm in Gangnam now.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
We should team up. We should team up.
Who are some members you're thinking of?
I don't know what the missions will be.
As for missions with passers-by,
it'd be nice to have someone like Ji Hyo.
Right. We need a lucky member.
Which member should we pick next?
How about Kwang Soo? We can boss him around.
What?
Great idea.
I'm a bit worried that he might betray us.
Kwang Soo is the best to boss around.
It's simple.
Okay. We got it. You, Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, and me.
- Let's make a team with them. - I love it.
Okay, where should we meet then?
Where am I?
I'm in Cheongdam Neighborhood Park.
(Kwang Soo is calling.)
Hey, our butler is calling me. I'll be there later.
- I'll pick him up on my way there. - Okay, call me.
- I'll get Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- Kwang Soo. - Hello.
You...
No one is willing to take you.
- Jae Seok. - I'll let you be in our team.
I think it's the same for you too. I'll let you be...
- Hey. - in my team.
A lot of people are calling me to be in their team.
I thought I was being recruited.
- I... - I got so many calls.
My cellphone battery is 5 percent. I started at 100 percent.
- You only have five percent left? - Yes.
You must not have charged your phone.
Stop talking nonsense, and come to Cheongdam Neighborhood Park.
Se Chan and I will form a team together.
Don't say it like that. Jae Seok.
Why not?
I'm your first.
(I want to be your first colleague.)
Okay. Meet me there.
- Okay? - I'll be there.
Meet me at Cheongdam Neighborhood Park. Okay.
Hold on. Let me set out now.
Let's get going.
Gosh, Jae Seok...
He can never say these things to Jong Kook.
He always acts like a boss when he's with us.
I mean, he's coming here. He's not the team leader.
Let's get going first. Okay.
(He's badmouthing Jae Seok on TV.)
- Hi. - Hello, Haha.
I sometimes feel comfortable around you, Kwang Soo.
- So Min called me. - Haha. Yes.
- And I talked to Seok Jin too. - Okay.
Se Chan, Seok Jin, So Min, and I...
were going to make a team of four.
But what am I going to do with them?
- Haha. - I don't see a future with them.
We should team up together first.
- I'm in. - With your slyness...
- I'm serious, Haha. - and your dirty plays this time.
Or you and I could...
make a team of four...
and split the money half and half.
(He's playing dirty again.)
You and I can work together.
That's my point.
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Yes.
I'm going to call you DJ today.
(I'm going to call you DJ today.)
- DJ? - Yes.
(All of a sudden?)
Because I have a great voice?
You're a dirty jerk.
Haha!
If you say that, I'll be really upset.
Right.
- Right. - Okay.
You're pretty good at things like this.
- Right. - First,
- I'll pick a place. - Okay, okay.
I'll make Se Chan, So Min, and Seok Jin come there.
Okay, Haha. Let's meet.
- Okay. - Okay.
(He's fishing for his prey as soon as he finishes the call.)
My sister-in-law.
(Ji Hyo becomes his sister-in-law.)
You know that I'm pulling for you, right?
- Be good to me. - Of course.
Seeing how things are unfolding,
I think they decided to meet in front of a statue in Dosan Park.
- Is that so? - I'm on my way there too.
Okay, I'll be there too.
We'll meet in front of the statue.
- Should we meet there? - Yes, Seok Jin.
You should come too.
- I'll be there then. - Come meet me there.
- I'll really be there. - I'm going there. I'm not lying.
- I'm on my way now. - I have faith in you, So Min.
Okay.
(Members are heading to where they promised to meet at.)
(Dosan Park and Neighborhood Park)
- Hey, Jae Seok. - Se Chan.
Where are you? I'm on my way there.
No, listen. I'm already near Cheongdam Neighborhood Park.
You're here? Where are you?
- Yes, I'm at the park now. - Okay.
Where should we meet then?
- Meet me at the entrance. - Okay.
I'll be at the entrance.
Where are you, Se Chan?
(Jae Seok gets off at the entrance.)
- Hey. - Wait, Jae Seok. Hello?
Hey, hold on.
Are you in the car that's leaving now?
Hold on. Wait.
What do you mean? Hey, hold on.
Did your car turn on the emergency light? Is that you?
- It's not me. I'm not moving. - Hey.
- Hey. - Jae Seok.
That's not true. Your car stopped, but it's leaving now.
Hey.
- Hang up. - I can hear Jong Kook laughing.
I'm hanging up.
(The familiar voice belongs to Jong Kook.)
- Hang up. Hang up! - I'm hanging up!
(Why is he in the car?)
Jong Kook called me.
- Hey, Se Chan. - I'll be there right away.
- You know what? - Yes.
You cannot team up with these reckless members.
I won't go there. Don't worry.
- Okay, wait. I know where you live. - I will.
(You know what happens if you betray me, right?)
Come on. Don't say that.
- I know your address. Okay? - I got it. Yes.
- I'll wait for you. - Okay.
- Okay! - Let's get it.
(This is so fun. This is why people betray others.)
No, no. We can't accept a reckless member.
Hey, So Min. Where are you, So Min?
(He's in a hurry.)
So Min.
- Where are you, Jae Seok? - Where are you, So Min.
I'm near Dosan Park.
- So Min. I'll be there. - Yes?
You can't go anywhere right now.
Okay, So Min?
- You've been abandoned. - So Min.
- Hey, So Min. Se Chan... - They got you good.
Gosh, he's not decent. He's not a decent human being.
- I see. Okay. - Hey, So Min.
I'm on my way to Dosan Park.
Gosh, seriously. Se Chan.
(Boiling with anger)
I'll teach this jerk a lesson.
(I can't believe Se Chan betrayed me.)
- Jae Seok just called me. - Okay.
Hold on. Pick it up.
Let's hear what he says.
Yes, Jae Seok.
Hey, jerk.
- I escaped him right now. - Hey.
You shouldn't live such a dirty life!
- Where are you? I'm free. - You know that?
- Where am I? - I'm serious.
I got out. Where are you?
- Do you want me to scold you? - No.
I'm right behind you. You want to know where I am?
(He's at a loss for words.)
(He's talking to him while watching his acting.)
(His acting is priceless.)
Where is he? Is that him?
- What? You got out? - Is that his car?
- The black car. - I'm sorry, Jae Seok.
- You, Jong Kook. - Hey.
You already teamed up with Jong Kook, didn't you?
Hey, Se Chan.
I won't let this slide today.
This means war!
It's war!
- Bye! - Tell him again.
(Hanging up)
That jerk, Se Chan.
(Se Chan upset me so much.)
All right. Pay attention.
I see a few cars already.
(Are they all here?)
(Ji Hyo, sacrifice number 1, arrives at Dosan Park.)
(Seok Jin, sacrifice number 2, arrives at Dosan Park.)
(Kwang Soo arrives at the park too.)
Where is Haha?
(They'll have a secret rendezvous before meeting the others.)
Haha.
- There. There. - Haha.
- I'm right here. Get in. - Haha.
- Where are you? - Get in.
Where? Haha.
(They successfully make contact.)
(Kwang Soo finds Haha's car at last.)
- Hello, Haha. - Hey, hey.
- This is great. - Haha.
- We should make a team. - You know what?
I have decided.
We should only let the weak ones to get in.
(That way, it's easy to betray them.)
- Let's call So Min first. - I'm serious.
Let's call So Min.
- Let me call Seok Jin. - Okay.
(Seok Jin is as weak as So Min.)
- Haha. - So Min.
I don't know how to get there. Where do I go from the entrance?
Get out of the entrance gate.
Come to where the main road is. Hurry.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
- Run, run, run, run. - Okay.
We don't have much time. Ask people how to get here.
- Hurry. Run. - Hold on.
Let's run. Run!
- Run. - Hey, hey. Get in here. Hurry.
This way!
Close the door. Close it.
Lock the door. Lock it.
(The trio of reckless members is made with So Min.)
That was hard.
Seok Jin is over there.
We should bring him here. With him, we'll have four people.
Hey, where are you? Where are you?
Where are you? I'm about to go to you.
Hey, Kwang Soo is calling. This is getting out of hand.
Where are you?
- Right now, - Where?
I'm in the parking lot next to Dosan Park.
- What? - The diagonal parking lot.
Here, here! I'm right here!
(Here, here! I'm right here!)
Hey, do we have four people here?
- Hurry. - Do we have four people?
No, no. Come quickly.
Do we have four people?
Jong Kook and Se Chan will be here.
Gosh, if I go there, there will be four people.
Hey, if I go there, that will make four people.
Where should I go?
Come here. Quickly.
Jong Kook and Se Chan just have to get here.
(Hold on a second.)
Ji Hyo is calling. Where are you?
- We're almost there. - I'm trying to save you.
- Hey. - Who is that?
- Hey. - Seok Jin. Uncle!
Hey, don't call me Uncle.
- Seok Jin, - Uncle.
we're almost there.
If I go there, that will make a team of four.
Seok Jin.
Wait for a bit. We'll be there soon.
We're passing by the theater now.
Gosh, goodness.
(Will he get into the dream team with Jong Kook and Ji Hyo?)
(Or will he join the reckless ones to make a team of 4 right away?)
(Jae Seok is still suffering from Se Chan's betrayal.)
- Kwang Soo. - Jae Seok!
- Where are you? - Hurry, Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok. - Hurry.
- That's Jae Seok? - We just need you to come here.
Okay. Great. The last seat is mine.
Come to the statue.
Okay.
(2 vehicles are heading to the park to make a team of 4.)
- We're here. Where are you? - We're here.
- We're here. We got here. - Where are you? We're here.
- They'll make the team first! - We're here.
- We're here. - Okay, we're here.
(Will they make the dream team first?)
There it is. I see you.
There they are.
(Or will the reckless members make a team first?)
There it is. I see you.
(Which team will receive the highest mission fund...)
(and start off the War of Money?)
- Where are you? - Where?
Right here!
- Hurry. - Get in.
- Okay! - This is driving me crazy.
- Great! - I got him!
- We made a team of four! - I got him.
- Seok Jin. - We did it.
- Hey. - Jae Seok is behind us.
It's a mess over there.
- Did you see that? - Seriously.
With four members gathered here,
- Yes. - a team of four has been formed.
- Okay! - Yes!
- 200 dollars! 5 times 4 is 20. - 5 times 4 is 20.
A team of four has been formed, so it's no longer available.
- Seok Jin went there. - He went to that team.
- Really? - You have a team of two or single.
(Now, a team of 2 is available with the next highest mission fund.)
(Haha, let's go for the team of 2.)
(We were supposed to team up from the get-go.)
Jae Seok just called me.
I think Jae Seok will be left alone.
- Team of two! - Come on!
(They betrayed So Min literally behind her back.)
What is this?
A team of two has been formed.
So Min must carry out the mission alone.
Okay!
(Haha and Kwang Soo formed a team of 2.)
(A pair of dirty players)
(So Min will make a team alone.)
Wait!
Everyone, freeze.
- Wait. Everyone, freeze. - What are you saying?
- Jae Seok, it's over. - Jae Seok, you're here!
You and I will have to play alone.
- This is over. - Why?
You and I will be alone.
- Se Chan took Seok Jin. - You're alone.
You should form a team together.
(4-person team: Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Se Chan)
(2-person team: Haha and Kwang Soo)
(Jae Seok and So Min are on their own.)
The mission 4-person team will carry out is...
the group jump rope.
My goodness.
- You must invite... - This is perfect.
- 6 passers-by. - 6 people?
If a total of 10 people skip the jump rope 19 times,
we'll count it as a success.
Six people?
6 people? Hold on. 6?
It won't be easy to invite six passers-by at this time.
- We should get six people. - Okay.
That won't be easy.
- It will be really hard. - Look over there.
- Should we split and conquer? - Yes, let's do that.
Yes, let's split.
- I'll go with Ji Hyo. - Okay, go.
- Let's look for people outdoors. - Okay, Seok Jin.
- Yes. - We can invite a kid too.
- Are you going somewhere? - Are you going somewhere?
She's here to film.
- You're here to film. - I knew it. You looked pretty.
- Hey, hi. - Say hello.
- What do you model for? - What do you do?
- She's here to model in hanbok. - I see.
- Really? - You don't have time, do you?
- She probably doesn't have time. - She said she didn't have time.
(They asked just in case.)
(She firmly says no.)
- She said no right away. - She doesn't have time.
- That's too bad. - Okay.
Bye.
- Bye. - Thank you.
Which member is your favorite on Running Man?
Stop it.
(He suddenly asks a question.)
- Stop it. - It's not me, is it?
- I guess it's not me. - Stop it, Grandpa.
- People at your age like me. - Come on.
Come on, Grandpa.
(Someone captured Ji Hyo and Se Chan's attention.)
- Are you good at jump ropes? - Hello.
- Are you good at jump ropes? - Are you good at jump ropes?
I'm sorry, but you have to be good at it.
- She's good. - Really?
(She exudes an unusual aura.)
- Are you good at jump ropes? - She's good.
- We'll do it with a group. - It will take...
some time.
You can go.
- Is she your boss? - Thank you so much!
- Thank you! - She's the manager?
We just got two people.
Jae Seok and So Min. The mission you will carry out is...
2-on-2 bowling match with passers-by.
We'll have a match. If we win, we get 15 dollars.
If we lose, we get 50 dollars for our mission fund.
It'd be nice if you can help us out.
Yong Hyun, where were you going?
I was on a break from my academy.
I came here because I thought this was more important.
You're not going to take your next class?
Right now,
- I must enjoy my time. - I see.
- He wants to enjoy the present. - Yes.
- You were going to an academy. - Yes.
But I was late.
You're late. Are you sure you don't have to go?
I won't go since I'm late anyway.
- Great. - She's new to bowling.
- You have never bowled before? - Right.
- You've never played it once? - No.
Good luck to both of our teams.
- Let's start now. - We can do it.
All right.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Han Sol is in good spirits.
(She gets excited.)
Let's do this. Let's go!
Han Sol.
This must be a bit awkward to be here, but...
- You danced. - I saw that.
- I saw it. She gets excited. - She's a bit...
She's a bit similar to So Min.
So Min is the expert at this move.
(How good are the ladies at bowling?)
All right. So Min.
(So Min bowls first.)
(Looking serious)
(She bowls the first one.)
No, no!
(It rolls...)
(to the gutter.)
(Gosh, it went to the gutter. Gosh.)
(She gets 0 points.)
(He can't bear to watch it.)
(It's Yong Hyun's turn to bowl.)
It's your turn, Yong Hyun.
(He starts calmly...)
(and loses his footing.)
(Is this a deja vu? It goes to the gutter again.)
(They indeed belong to the same team.)
Seriously. That's all right.
Good job. Well done.
- The prize made me nervous. - No, no.
(Team So Min finished the first frame without any points.)
- I won't remind you. - Okay.
- You know, right? - Yes.
(It's Han Sol's turn to try.)
Good luck, Han Sol!
(Screaming)
(She bowls for the first time in her life with excitement.)
- Wait. - It's going.
(Rolling slowly)
(It rolls very slowly.)
What was that? What?
(It knocks down a lot of pins. Nice shot.)
(This bowling newbie is surprisingly good at bowling.)
- Yes! - She danced again.
What was that? What is this?
(Since I'm happy, let's shake it.)
(Team Jae Seok has 8 points so far.)
- She didn't even lift it up high. - Why did that go so slowly?
(We might lose at this rate.)
- Hello. Thank you. - Okay.
- This is Team Kwang Soo and Haha. - Hi.
- Please come in. - Hello.
- We're a team. - We're a team.
We have to play the game, 369.
We just need to go over the number 50.
- But... - But...
we clap with numbers that have 3, 6, and 9.
And we have to say, "hurray" with multiples of 10.
If it's 10, you say, "hurray" once.
If it's 20, you say it 2 times.
With that rule, we have to go all the way to 50.
I'm sorry, but please pay attention.
Please don't talk. I would like to ask you not to do that.
We can finish this in one go.
- Start. - 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4.
- 369 - 369
- 1. - 2.
- 4. - 5.
- 7. - 8.
- Hurray. - 11, 12.
- 14. - 15.
- 17. - 18.
(Swinging)
- Say "hurray". - "Hurray."
(Swinging in silence is unacceptable.)
You have to say "hurray".
This is our first time.
- We came very far. - Good job.
- We came almost halfway. - Good job.
- It's impressive. - We came almost halfway.
It's impressive.
We finished 40 percent.
- Here we go. - Let's focus a little more.
Start.
1, 2, 3, 4.
- 369 - 369
- 1. - 2.
- 4. - 5.
- 7. - 8.
- Hurray. - 11, 12.
- 14. - 15.
- 17. - 18.
Hurray, hurray.
(She says hurray 2 times.)
- 21. - 22.
- 24. - 25.
- 27. - 28.
Hurray, hurray, hurray.
Hurray, hurray, hurray, hurray.
(Moving up and down)
(I see.)
41.
- He said "hurray". - Wait.
It's his habit.
(He says "hurray" out of habit.)
- Can't we talk to ourselves? - It's his habit.
Can't we talk to ourselves?
(Unfortunately, they fail at number 40.)
How old are you?
- Pardon? - How old are you?
We're the same age.
Shall we speak casually?
Concentrate.
(Concentrate.)
Concentrate. What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
- You got really into it. - I was nervous.
Were you born in 1985?
- You two are friends. - We are.
We have to do well.
It could be our last chance. Believe in yourself.
- Let's go. - Let's cheer.
(Let's cheer, everyone.)
We can do it.
- 1, 2, 3, let's go. - Let's go.
(They have a chance of winning if they concentrate more.)
Let's go.
We're almost there.
- Let's go with this. - Good luck.
- 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
- 369 - 369
- 1. - 2.
- 4. - 5.
- 7. - 8.
- Hurray. - 11.
12.
- 14. - 15.
- 17. - 18.
Hurray, hurray.
(They reach 20.)
- 21. - 22.
- 24. - 25.
- 27. - 28.
Hurray, hurray, hurray.
(They reach 30.)
Hurray, hurray, hurray, hurray.
(I reached 40.)
(Will they successfully reach 50?)
- 41. - 42.
- 44. - 45.
- 47. - 48.
(They succeed with 1 clap and hurray of 5 times.)
(He claps once for 49.)
Hurray, hurray, hurray, hurray, hurray.
(They get to 5 hurrays successfully.)
- We got it. - We did it.
We made it.
(The one who concentrated...)
(and the one who helped him concentrate are both impressed.)
Give it to us.
You cleared your mission successfully.
(They earn 300 dollars.)
We did it.
- We'll give you a gift. - Thank you for your work.
- That's great. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
There's something for you.
Please take it.
(They're given a mysterious envelope.)
"Password Chart".
(Password Chart)
- What is it? - "1038".
The password chart shows the address of your next destination.
(Solve the password for your next destination.)
(Being sly)
(He puts it in.)
- Aren't we staying together? - Yes, but we never know.
Is this necessary? Okay.
- Come on. - Do whatever you want.
- Why are you covering it up? - Just take a photo.
(Did you catch me covering it up?)
Solve this password and arrive at your next destination.
Then you'll get a chance to increase the money you gained.
(A chance to increase the money that we gained?)
- However... - Do we have to go together?
It's given to 3 members who arrive 1st.
(It's given to three members who arrive first.)
Only they get the chance.
(Those who arrive first?)
(Grabbing)
(He's good at stealing.)
(Come on, Haha.)
(He chases him already during the day.)
(Dropping)
Goodness, Haha.
Okay.
(He disappeared so quickly with his short legs.)
Haha.
What's wrong with you?
"1038", "131", "45", "L", "B", "L".
I can never solve this.
What could it be?
You have to turn your arm wide. Hit the ground.
1, 2.
- Three. - It's too fast.
Four, that's right.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
- Eight. - Look at him.
(He does it in silence.)
Give it to me.
This is how to turn it. Start.
Make it big. 1, 2.
He's teaching again.
He always teaches.
Do it this way. It must be big like this.
Otherwise, the rope gets shorter.
When it's short, people can't go in.
Make it big.
We're grateful that he's helping us.
- Why are you teaching him? - Do it like this.
- Here you go. - Shall we try?
You have to jump 19 times.
Here you go.
You can do it.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
- Let's start. - Let's succeed.
The important part is the feet.
When it passes the feet, pull it quickly.
- That way, we won't trip. - Stop it.
- Stop. - It's difficult.
- Let's give it a try. - Okay, let's do it.
We're ready.
Let's cheer in 3, 2, 1. Let's go.
(They make their first attempt.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
Start.
- 1, 2. - 1, 2.
- 2, 3, 4. - 3, 4.
Who was it?
(They fail after 3 jumps.)
(Who was it?)
(Seok Jin is the only one inside the line.)
Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
- I'm sorry. - You're the only one on that side.
It was your fault, right?
- Seok Jin. - I'm sorry.
Many people are having a hard time.
I was on this side.
- Why were you? - Why do you go that way?
I'm sorry. Let's cheer up, everyone.
- We can do it. - Let's go.
Let's try again.
Get ready.
- Start. - Start.
- 1, 2. - 2.
Three.
(Number of jumps)
- 5, 6. - 5, 6.
- 7, 8. - 7, 8.
- 9. - 9.
(Number of jumps)
- 10. - What happened?
- Who was it? - It was me.
Who was it?
(Who was it this time?)
Gosh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, everyone.
19 jumps aren't easy at all.
It's not easy.
She's the most relaxed.
- Seriously. - She's putting a pin in her hair.
- She's good. - She's very good.
She has hands in her pockets.
- She's so relaxed. - That's very impressive.
She couldn't see in the middle of it,
so she turned directions.
- She's impressive. - Here's what I think.
It gets difficult after 12 jumps.
We have to concentrate starting then.
If we concentrate, we can do it.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- 19. - 19 jumps.
Get ready.
Start.
- 1, 2. - 2.
- 3, 4. - We got it.
Five.
- 6, 7. - 6, 7.
- 8, 9. - 8, 9.
- 10, 11. - 10, 11.
Concentrate.
(Everyone concentrates.)
(Concentrating is the only way to survive.)
- My thighs hurt. - 13.
(My thighs are hurting.)
14, 15.
- My thighs hurt. - 16.
It hurts! My thighs hurt!
16.
17.
We're almost there.
18.
(They need 2 more jumps.)
19.
(They jump 19 times.)
Okay.
(With teamwork and those turning the rope, )
(they successfully jump the rope in three attempts.)
We did it.
Good job, everyone.
Thank you again for helping us despite the cold.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
Thank you.
It's late, but Happy New Year.
Take care.
(They win 800 dollars.)
- You cleared your mission. - Why is he running?
What's going on?
- Why is Kwang Soo here? - Why is he here?
(Kwang Soo appears right after they clear the mission.)
Are you done?
- He seems to be up to something. - No.
Look at him.
- I'm not doing anything. - Stay away a little.
- Don't think that way. - Stay away.
- Stay away. You're dangerous. - No.
- I have no place to go. - What's wrong?
- Why are you here? - Aren't you on Haha's team?
We cleared our mission.
The first three to arrive at the next destination get a chance.
Haha took the hint and ran away.
Haha betrayed him.
For now...
- What is it? - What is it?
Kwang Soo, ripped his hint. Don't let him get close.
(Password Chart)
Look at this.
(Does this indicate an address?)
(Jae Seok and So Min are still busy bowling.)
Nice shot.
(It's Yong Hyun's turn.)
I hope it makes them fall.
(He throws it with all his might.)
Incredible.
- What happened? - Incredible.
(He's actually good at bowling.)
(He has full swings and swag despite his small body.)
(He gets a strike every time.)
(This is how good I am.)
(I'm the one who turns the tables.)
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
My goodness.
You did such a good job.
(So Min wins 150 dollars, and Jae Seok wins 50 dollars.)
Is it over?
(So Min wins.)
(He's sad that he lost.)
What could this be, "L", "B", and "L"?
What is this?
(Password Chart)
Do these mean numbers?
(It should be written words and numbers.)
Aren't these numbers?
- "L", "B", "L"? - Aren't these numbers?
- This is... - Could it be 464?
Considering the order.
Combine consonants and vowels.
(He compares them to numbers.)
Here it is. I found it.
(I found it.)
Here it is.
This is it.
It's 1 and 0.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
"Cheongpa-ro". "L" becomes four.
(He turns numbers to letters and vowels to numbers.)
"Cheongpa-ro 464".
(Cheongpa-ro 464?)
Sir, could you take me to Cheongpa-ro 464?
- Is it a number? - You know.
- It's... - "K", "N", "D", "L", four.
Hey, I found out.
- Do you know the order? - I just found out.
- Let's go. - Is it Cheongpa-ro?
Cheongpa-ro?
(They don't have time to waste.)
Cheongpa-ro.
- Cheongpa-ro 464. - Cheongpa-ro 464.
I could have gone there alone.
Look at her.
Hey, So Min.
(Ji Hyo gives Jong Kook 30 dollars and joins him.)
Goodness.
I should look it up.
(They haven't figured it out yet.)
- Where's their car? - It's leaving.
- Can you follow their car? - Follow it.
Whose car is it?
I think it's Jong Kook's car.
(Who will be the first 3 to arrive?)
My goodness.
I came so early.
Look at all the cameras that are set up.
Is no one else here?
(The first to arrive)
(It's Haha.)
Haha, you're the first to pull out a flag.
You'll get a special chance in a few minutes.
I'll tell you what kind of chance card it is.
(A chance card is under a veil.)
This is where you'll get a chance to increase...
the money that you earned with people's help.
- It's a betting house. - Okay.
(A betting house where they can increase their money)
(Here's our chance.)
- Here it is. - I love this game.
There are two betting zones.
The first betting zone is full of pop-up pirates.
The bet amount is different for each pirate.
If the pirate pops up as you insert a dagger,
you may win the bet amount times 2, 5, or 10.
If the pirate doesn't pop up,
you'll lose your bet amount.
The pirate has to pop up? I'm good at this.
Let's give a try.
The other zone is flipping lucky cups.
They're cups.
On the 10-dollar table,
there's a total of 30 cups.
There are three duds.
There are 5 duds at the 5-dollar table.
At the last 100-dollar table,
there are four duds.
Four? That's worth playing.
It sounds good. It's worth playing.
You must make...
1,000 dollars to leave.
(You must make 1,000 dollars to leave.)
1,000 dollars?
(They can't believe what they just heard.)
- We need it to leave. - This is difficult.
Also, if you win 1,300 dollars,
you can give away 300 dollars.
- Really? - Can we give money? Okay.
You're at a disadvantage the later you leave.
(This must be remembered.)
Which zone shall I go?
(They must make 1,000 dollars and leave as soon as possible.)
(Who will escape here first?)
- Okay. - Let's get started.
- Okay. - I bet 100 dollars.
Seok Jin is competitive.
- He has a lot of money now. - I knew it.
- I pick pop-up pirate. - Pop-up pirate?
I pick the pop-up pirate. I'll bet 100 dollars.
(He bets 100 dollars.)
You get one chance in life.
I get to leave if the pirate pops up.
- Then it's over. - I get everything.
- It won't pop up. - Seok Jin won't get it.
(He inserts his first dagger.)
It pops up easily.
(Tick)
- I thought it'd pop. - One.
(That was one.)
(It's his second dagger.)
(The second attempt fails.)
I don't think so. It won't pop.
Just do it.
My goodness.
- I have only 2 turns left. - He has 2 left.
It doesn't pop up easily.
If he fails, will he lose 100 dollars?
- Why isn't it working? - He will lose it.
I see.
There's a slot that I suspect.
Where is it? Tell me.
(Can you tell me?)
I'll tell you for 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars? - He sounds convinced.
Are you giving it to him?
- Okay. - Is there a slot you know?
- Yes. - Where is it?
(Which slot does Jae Seok suspect?)
It's around here.
(His answer is vague.)
(What do you mean "around here"?)
- What? - Give me my 10 dollars.
- Give it back. - Why? I told you.
- Which slot is it? - Wait.
- I told you. - Specify one slot.
- It'll require more money. - Give it back.
It'll require more money.
"Around there" is appropriate for 10 dollars.
That's right.
An accurate slot would cost 1,000 dollars.
That's right. It's around there.
Ding, dong, dang.
(He inserts his 4th dagger around there.)
(The fourth attempt fails.)
(1,000 dollars depend on his last dagger.)
Kwang Soo's guess will cost 20 dollars.
- Just give me 10 dollars. - Don't you need money?
- I need 10 dollars. - Don't you?
I gave Se Chan 10 dollars for the hint.
Pick one slot. Don't do it like Jae Seok.
- Okay. - Is this investment worthy?
What will you do?
Do you want 10 dollars now? Or do you want 50 dollars...
if it pops?
I want 10 dollars now.
(Are you kidding me?)
(He prefers 10 dollars now to 50 dollars he may not get.)
The trick didn't work.
He's smart.
- Where? - This one.
- This one? - The one on the left.
This one?
Okay.
I'll trust you.
(He trusts Kwang Soo's guess after paying 10 dollars.)
It's over.
(His information was wrong.)
(Punching)
Why are you hitting me?
- How would I know? - It's different.
- I lost 20 dollars. - It's different from guessing.
He lost.
Who's next?
- Is it me? - Next is Jong Kook.
Play it simple.
(Jong Kook who has 250 dollars starts.)
- It doesn't pop at times like this. - It doesn't.
- What would you like to play? - Times two.
My goodness.
(He makes a small bet.)
- He's such a coward. - I'll make several bets.
The possibility is high. It'll pop up no matter what.
Our ways are different.
He likes to bet little at a time. We like to make bet everything.
I like to bet everything.
I'll pick the middle one.
- Shall I go? - The size doesn't match him.
It's so small.
- 1. - 1.
Two.
- It doesn't pop. - That's true.
It's not popping. He put 5 out of 8.
(The third attempt fails.)
(He only has 2 daggers left.)
- Please. - Please.
Okay, please.
(He loses 100 dollars if he doesn't succeed in 2 turns.)
Okay.
(Jong Kook wins 200 dollars.)
(He's disappointed.)
Let's start over. One more time.
- 200 dollars? - Okay.
That's another way.
He's getting into it.
- My goodness. - Here I go.
(If he succeeds, he wins 400 dollars.)
(The pirate pops up again.)
Okay, 400 dollars.
(Did he succeed again?)
That's not how to play the game.
Gosh, this is not fun.
- It's not fun. - Come on.
We have to stop him. What's going on?
He should play another game.
- What is he doing? - What's wrong?
You're done if you win 500 dollars.
- If you win 500 dollars, it's over. - Right.
Jong Kook, when you make 1,000 dollars,
- give me 50 dollars. - Give me what remains.
(Give me the change.)
Okay, 500 dollars.
Excuse me, what are you doing?
- My goodness. - When you have 1,000 dollars...
- Let me play first. - Listen.
- Go bankrupt. - Seok Jin said, "Go bankrupt".
He bet 500 dollars on pop-up pirate.
Here I go.
(If he succeeds, he wins 1,000 dollars and escapes.)
- Please. - Please.
He looks amazing.
(It's his first dagger.)
- It didn't work. - Okay.
I hope he fails.
(Stay inside, pirate.)
(He has 4 daggers left.)
Okay.
(The second attempt fails.)
- Please. - Stay in for three more times.
- Please. - Here he goes.
Please.
(If he wins, Jong Kook escapes immediately.)
(His lips turn dry.)
(What will happen with his third dagger?)
(Popping)
(Jong Kook wins 1,000 dollars.)
(He has about 1,050 dollars.)
(This isn't fun at all.)
- Give me 50 dollars. - Kim Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook.
- Goodness. - Kim Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - Give me some.
(He can give the rest to anyone.)
50 dollars isn't much. Do you still want it?
- Yes. - I'll pay you back...
no matter what.
- Jong Kook. - I'll be good to you.
They have enough money already.
Okay, can you step back?
Kookookaka.
(Kookookaka)
(Jae Seok tries to be cute.)
(Just give it to him.)
You should beat him up.
- Don't you feel sorry for him? - I was scared.
Spread your hands.
(Jae Seok makes you feel sorry for him.)
(Jong Kook gives him 50 dollars.)
- Thank you. - I approve.
Stay strong.
Take the money and stay strong.
Gosh.
I can't stand it.
(This is capitalism.)
Okay!
All kinds of things happen.
(Jong Kook is about to escape.)
(Haha suddenly takes a pose.)
(What are you doing? I'm leaving.)
What's with him?
Jong Kook, you can leave now.
- What are you doing? - What's with Haha?
Dawn club!
(What's going on?)
(When Haha shouts the words, the siren goes off.)
What?
- What's going on? - What is this?
- What is this? - What is this?
"Dawn club"?
"Dawn club chance".
When the 1st person to win 1,000 dollars is about to escape,
hold up the chance card and shout, "dawn club".
Then half that person's money...
will be transferred to you.
Dawn club!
(You didn't see this coming.)
Really?
Jong Kook will lose his money?
- After giving up 50 dollars? - What is this?
- What is this? - What is "dawn club"?
What is this?
Give back 50 dollars.
- What are you talking about? - Give it back.
- Why would I? - Give it back.
- Why would I... - Is this a chance?
- Why did I... - Take it back.
- Give me back my 50 dollars. - What happens now?
- Jong Kook can't leave. - He can't?
You must be so annoyed.
(Teasing)
- Give me back my 50 dollars. - It's mine. Why would I?
- I can't believe you. - I mean...
It's mine.
- Oh, my. - Gosh, this is...
It already happened.
All kinds of things happen.
Why is it "dawn club"?
You'll find out later.
- There must be something more. - Okay.
You'll probably be clubbed by me.
(You'll probably be clubbed by me.)
(Haha will be clubbed by Jong Kook at dawn.)
That's it. That must be it.
At dawn?
(It sounds convincing.)
He gets money,
but he has to be clubbed too.
We'll find out at dawn.
The times two table will be taken away.
- Gosh. - That was a good one.
(The table the first winner chose is taken away.)
Dawn club!
What does that even mean?
I thought you were just ad-libbing.
I thought it was just a weird ad-lib.
I didn't understand what you were doing.
I didn't know why he was taking a pose.
Next player.
It's me.
Kwang Soo will bet all the money he has.
(Let us tell you about Kwang Soo.)
It's my turn.
(As soon as he picks up a dagger, the pirate gets ready to pop up.)
(This master never fails to meet the pirate.)
100 dollars, pop-up pirate.
(The legendary unlucky person makes a bold move.)
If you succeed, you'll win 1,000 dollars and escape.
(He goes for winning 1,000 dollars with 100 dollars.)
If you succeed,
- the situation will reverse. - He'll have extra 50 dollars.
When he wants it to pop up, it won't.
If he succeeds, it'll be unbelievable.
- If he succeeds... - We'll all have to recognize him.
He deserves 100 times the money he bets.
(It's in.)
(The first attempt fails.)
(Serious)
(Kwang Soo has 4 chances left to escape.)
It looks...
(What about his second attempt?)
(It's in.)
Do as you usually do.
Please try this slot.
Do me a favor. Here.
(So Min picks out a slot.)
- Here? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo sticks his third dagger in the slot.)
(It fails again.)
You just blew one chance.
(It's So Min's fault.)
- I mean... - He just blew one chance.
- Why did you do that? - It was a favor.
- What was that? - You did her a favor.
I don't know anymore.
- How many do you have left? - Two.
Just do it casually as I did.
Do you have any feelings?
- No? - Here.
(So Min butts in again.)
- Hey. - Seriously.
I mean it.
I've been thinking about that slot too.
- Either that or that. - No.
Move.
(Jae Seok butts in.)
There.
(Jae Seok points at a slot.)
- I'd go for this one. - Here?
- This one? Here? - He respects his opinion.
Still, Kwang Soo respects...
Jae Seok's opinion because he is so unlucky.
Kwang Soo respects him.
Let's go.
(Kwang Soo decides to trust Jae Seok's gut.)
You're the unluckiest one.
(Is the older unlucky one right?)
(It pops up.)
It popped up.
(Jae Seok was right.)
Jae Seok.
(It's me.)
I'm so shocked.
(What is with this man?)
Jae Seok.
(The odds were 1 in 21.)
(Jae Seok had only a 4.8 percent chance.)
I'm surprised at myself too.
(He is surprised too.)
No more club?
(Let's stop Kwang Soo from escaping.)
How much will Kwang Soo give to Jae Seok?
It popped up. He should pay Jae Seok.
- It's incredible. - I can't believe it.
Haha, you have something more?
(Kwang Soo has an extra 50 dollars.)
Ordinary club!
What's wrong?
(It's not a dawn club.)
(It's just an ordinary club.)
How did you do that?
(Give me the extra money.)
This is crazy.
- Jae Seok is crazy. - There was even a dagger left.
Jae Seok picked out the slot, right?
How do you do that? Do you see something?
There was a slot that was powerfully drawing me to it.
That's so cool.
That was amazing. It was the first time...
I'd thought it was cool when the pirate popped up.
(Everyone is amazed at Jae Seok.)
(Kwang Soo whispers he is leaving.)
- Kwang Soo, hold on. - Hey.
Let's talk first.
- Give us the extra money. - Give us the extra money.
Kwang Soo had extra 50 dollars on top of 1,000 dollars.
It's been donated to the society.
(I'm out of here.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E440 Running Man
"The Great War of Money Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
How can he...
He should have given you...
- at least 30 dollars. - He did a good thing.
I should have donated too.
(Kwang Soo leaves after donating 50 dollars to the society.)
Please turn in your cell phone.
My cell phone?
- I have to turn in my cell phone? - Yes.
(Puzzled)
Why...
Hold on. What...
(He is blindfolded too?)
What is this?
(Without any means of contact, he is forced to get in the car.)
This is how we move?
Why am I blindfolded?
I'm not supposed to know where I'm going?
(He arrives at a mysterious place.)
There has to be a huge reward for me.
(The national flag is raised high.)
There has to be.
(The building looks mysterious.)
We're entering? Where?
Do I walk forward?
(He enters the building without seeing anything.)
What is this? I hear a door.
Where... Hold on.
What is this? Hold on. Where am I?
(Where am I?)
(Locked)
What's going on?
(The door is locked.)
What is this? Why did you lock the door?
(Kwang Soo is locked up without any idea where he is.)
I mean...
(8 cells)
You have arrived...
at the final mission place.
(The clock is stopped at 100 minutes.)
This is the 100 Minute House.
With each minute passing, you'll lose 10 dollars...
out of your 1,000 dollars.
You have to escape from this place...
before you lose all your money.
(Escape before you lose all your money.)
There are two questions on the wall.
You're to answer them.
If you say the wrong answer, you'll be splashed with water.
Answer the questions as fast as you can...
and find out the conditions for becoming the final winner.
(Escape to find out the conditions for becoming the final winner.)
(His 100 minutes starts now.)
I'll answer the questions.
Gosh.
"Find the similarity among these three."
"One, Itaewon has it, but Apgujeong doesn't."
"Two, Hyochang Park has it,"
"but Children's Grand Park doesn't."
"World Cup Stadium has it, but Sports Complex doesn't."
What is this?
Number two. “On a distant day, when the skies first opened,
“Somewhere a cock must have crowed.”
(Let me guess.)
On-when-was.
A-the-a.
(It's creative but irrelevant.)
How would I know this one?
(Frustrated)
The poem...
I've never even seen this poem before.
(He is losing both time and money.)
- We have to get Kwang Soo. - We have to get him.
We have to get him.
100 dollars.
- I think this has a better chance. - Pop-up pirate is better.
If it pops up...
(Se Chan bets 100 dollars on the times 5 pop-up pirate.)
- It's the first try. - Here goes Se Chan.
- Here we go. - Se Chan!
(He has an 8.3 percent chance.)
(The first attempt fails.)
If he succeeds, he wins 500 dollars.
500 dollars.
(The second attempt fails.)
- Se Chan. - This doesn't feel right.
- Gosh. - Calm down.
He ran out of energy.
(He has 3 chances and 9 slots left.)
(The third attempt fails.)
Gosh.
This is hard.
(He'll probably fail.)
- Jae Seok, can you pick one out? - Do you have only one chance left?
I have two more.
I want to get paid first.
(His service is not for free anymore.)
(Please pay me first.)
- He wants to get paid first. - He is disappointed.
(I have bad memories.)
Give me just 10 dollars.
- I'd give him. - Okay.
(Se Chan pays him right away.)
Will Jae Seok escape with this money?
(He sells his bad luck.)
He'll become rich by doing this.
He is a psychic. A pop-up pirate psychic.
Just stick it in any slot you want.
What?
(You want me to use 1 chance out of the 2 I have left?)
He'll help you when you have only one left.
He sounds like a magician.
"Just stick it in any slot you want. It'll pop up."
Stick it in.
(Following Jae Seok's order, )
(Se Chan sticks the dagger in a slot he likes.)
- It's in. - Now,
it's his turn.
It's Jae Seok's turn.
(Jae Seok helps out when there is only one chance left.)
If it pops up, it'll be incredible.
He is good at such silly things.
(He is good at such silly things.)
What did you...
(Silly things?)
Hold on.
I'm working hard here.
I'm good at silly things?
- Gosh, I can't believe you. - My goodness.
He is not even ashamed.
He is shameless.
(He focuses on the silly matter.)
- Stick it here. - Where?
- Here. - Here?
(He transfers his bad luck.)
- Here? - Yes.
Will it pop up?
Seriously?
(If Jae Seok is right, Se Chan will win 500 dollars.)
(Will Jae Seok do another miracle?)
(It popped up.)
(Jae Seok is right for the 2nd time in a row.)
What is this?
- What is this? - What is this?
- He is surprised too. - What is this?
Unbelievable.
- Where was it? - He is...
- What is this? - He is surprised too.
- What's going on? - What did you do?
- How did you do it? - It gave me goosebumps.
It's not easy to succeed two times in a row.
You can't see anything.
(Can you see something?)
- What is this? - You can't see anything.
You earned so much by paying 10 dollars.
When I stuck it in,
it gave me goosebumps.
Yu Jae Seok chances should be forbidden.
(To be fair)
- It's too effective. - I'm scared at myself.
- It's too effective. - I don't know what I might do.
He'll be wrong this time.
How much did I bet? 100 dollars?
Unbelievable. I'm still in shock.
Two times in a row?
(Let me pay you some more.)
- You deserve it. - Thank you.
50 dollars. I earned so much.
Jae Seok has earned a lot.
(Jae Seok has been receiving fees.)
- 100 dollars. - 100 dollars?
- Which one? - That one.
(He tries the times 10 pop-up pirate so that he can escape at once.)
If I fail to escape after helping other people,
wouldn't that be hilarious?
- Right. - That means you're really unlucky.
(Will he be unlucky for himself too?)
It might not work for himself.
- Right. - Helping others is easier.
Put your face away.
(The first attempt fails.)
If it doesn't pop up, it means he is really unlucky.
It'll be so funny if it pops up.
If it pops up, give me the extra money.
50 dollars.
It's not popping up. Jae Seok is in trouble.
(What is going on?)
- Slow down. - Jae Seok, slow down.
Slow down.
Whether it pops up or not, it'll be funny.
How much did you bet? 100 dollars?
Please.
(Whenever he casually pointed at a slot, )
(the pirate popped up.)
(With only a 0.6 percent chance, he was right again.)
(He made history today as an unlucky man.)
(With 2 chances left, the pirate won't pop up for him.)
- Oh, my. - Only one left.
(Even the fourth attempt fails.)
Only one left.
(He has only one chance left.)
- Take a break. - Let's stay back.
- I'm so looking forward. - If it doesn't pop up...
You'll be humiliated.
It'll be so funny if it doesn't pop up.
If it pops up, it's a miracle.
(They all root for him.)
(If it pops up, he can escape.)
- It gives me goosebumps. - This must be it.
- Stick it in. - This must be it.
- Stick it in. - Please.
(What will happen to the unlucky Jae Seok?)
(Last chance to win 1,000 dollars)
(If it pops up, he can escape.)
- It gives me goosebumps. - This must be it.
- Stick it in. - This must be it.
- Stick it in. - Please.
(What will happen to the unlucky Jae Seok?)
(It popped up.)
(Jae Seok wins 1,000 dollars and escapes.)
(Jae Seok succeeded 3 times in a row.)
- I'm not joking. I got goosebumps. - This is crazy.
(They all become speechless.)
(This is more dramatic than any movie.)
- Gosh. Yu Jae Seok! - Are you crazy?
- Yu Jae Seok! - How can this happen?
- Jae Seok. How... - How...
I'm on fire today.
I should buy a lottery ticket.
I have no time to waste.
(This would be harder than winning a lottery.)
Jae Seok, go get Kwang Soo.
I'll get going. I'll get Kwang Soo.
- Bye. - See you.
- Is this for real? - This is crazy.
(Did we just dream?)
How can this be possible?
(I want to escape too.)
- Please turn in your cell phone. - What?
- Turn in your cell phone. - Why?
(Jae Seok has to turn in his phone too.)
Let me blindfold you.
(He is blindfolded so he can't see anything.)
- Should I get in? - Yes.
(He is transported to the 100 Minute House.)
Where are we going?
- So Min. - Okay.
100 dollars, cups.
They must have been shuffled, right? 1, 2, 3.
(She bets everything on the cups.)
Okay. 1, 2, 3.
(She wins 300 dollars at once.)
Stop!
I'll switch to pop-up pirate.
(She bets everything on the times 5 pop-up pirate.)
- I don't think it'll pop up. - So Min.
The last one...
(So Min wins 1,000 dollars and escapes.)
What is this?
(Wait for me, Kwang Soo and Jae Seok.)
- Here? - Yes.
Where...
(Kwang Soo, Jae Seok, and So Min have escaped the betting house.)
What is this? Where am I?
Where... I'm scared. I'm indoors.
Where am I?
How did she come here?
- How did she come here? - How did So Min come here?
- What is this? - So Min, how did you come here?
What's going on? There's nothing here.
Hold on.
What's going on? Why am I being locked up?
So Min, how did you come?
What is this?
Jae Seok! What is this place?
(So Min is the 3rd person to arrive here.)
What is this?
(So Min has 88 minutes.)
Do I have to answer them?
"Find the similarity among these three."
I've seen this poem somewhere,
- but I don't remember where. - "Itaewon has it, but..."
I think I learned this poem back in high school.
"Itaewon has it..." I should start from question number one.
"Itaewon has it, but Apgujeong doesn't."
Let me give you a hint about number one. It's simple.
(20 minutes pass, and the 1st hint is given.)
It's related to public transport.
- Public transport. - "Public transport"?
Bus, subway, taxi...
(Public transport?)
It can't be taxis. Buses...
(Jae Seok is lost.)
I know what number one is.
- I know what number one is! - Hey.
Let me answer!
It's near my place.
- Let me answer. - Hold on.
- Let me answer. - All right.
- So Min's answer is correct. - Okay!
So Min!
- Really? - Hey!
- Okay! - Hey!
Question number one.
(Subway Line 6)
- Correct! - Okay!
Jae Seok!
(Kwang Soo came first, but he is the only one left now.)
- Jae Seok! What's the answer? - I'm done.
(Itaewon has it, but Apgujeong doesn't.)
(Hyochang Park has it, but Children's Grand Park doesn't.)
(World Cup Stadium, Hyochang Park, Itaewon)
(Subway Line 6)
Bus, subway, taxi...
(What's the answer?)
(Does Kwang Soo know now?)
Let me answer.
(A churro shop)
I'm sure this is it.
(Itaewon has a churro shop, but Apgujeong doesn't?)
Your answer is wrong.
Is it close?
(He tries again right away.)
Let me answer.
(A fish-shaped bun shop)
Your answer is wrong.
(He tries yet again.)
Let me answer.
(A convenience store)
(Kwang Soo continues to give the wrong answer.)
What is this?
Where are we going?
Where am I?
(Seok Jin has 77 minutes.)
What is this?
Where am I?
Gosh, this is so sudden.
What is this?
(Time is passing by.)
Why can't I do this?
You have 500 dollars. How much do you want to bet?
- Bet 200 dollars. - Bet 200 dollars.
I bet 200 dollars.
- Give us the extra money. - Seriously...
- Okay. - You're my sister-in-law.
"Sister-in-law"? Did you say, "sister-in-law"?
My sister-in-law.
- Just a second, my brother-in-law. - Okay.
(Just a second, my brother-in-law.)
She's playing along.
Ji Hyo is playing along.
Which slot do you want?
You can decide.
(You can decide.)
You're good at this.
(What are they doing?)
I like this one.
(This is her 1st attempt out of 5.)
(It pops up.)
(1 shot, 1 kill)
How do you do this?
(How do you do this?)
- Sister-in-law. - Brother-in-law.
My goodness.
- I'm so surprised. - You have 300 dollars left.
- All right. - You have 300 dollars left.
Please divide it up.
I have 300 dollars left?
- Honey. - "Honey"?
(Honey)
(He plays along to win 300 dollars.)
(He called Ji Hyo "honey" to win the 300 dollars.)
Jong Kook.
"Honey"?
(The brother-in-law is satisfied.)
Honey.
You're so good.
- You're so good. - "Honey".
"Honey". We can't beat that.
Fine. Honey, you can have 300 dollars.
Good!
(Honey, you can have 300 dollars.)
(Good words cost nothing but are worth much.)
(Good words can be worth 300 dollars.)
- This is it. - Jong Kook.
Are they a couple?
Give me 100 dollars.
(Ji Hyo escapes, and it's Se Chan's turn now.)
Here we go.
I have to catch up.
(Se Chan has 480 dollars.)
It'd be funny if it didn't pop up.
(Popping)
(It pops up.)
Okay!
(He gets 1,000 dollars and a total of 1,280 dollars.)
What was that?
All right. How much do you have?
- Let's make it fair. - I have 750 dollars.
- 750 dollars? - Yes.
If I give him 250 dollars, it's a game over. Let's go.
- What? - I'll give it to you.
(Se Chan willingly gives Jong Kook the money.)
- All right, let's see. - Hold on. Okay.
- Here's 250 dollars. - Okay.
- Let's go. - All right.
We were a team in the morning.
- All right! - Good.
Haha, here's 30 dollars.
- You can do it. - Okay.
- Okay. - Jong Kook.
You took my money before. You deserve it.
(He's all alone once again.)
Dawn club!
(Sighing)
Darn it.
This is just my luck.
(He might leave at dawn.)
Can I go? Can I go in?
(Ji Hyo is the fifth to arrive.)
I hear something. What is that?
She got out early.
Goodness.
What is this?
(She has 72 minutes.)
- Who is it? - Hey.
(She has to solve the two questions in the given time.)
- What's going on? - Jong Kook's here.
Se Chan.
Where am I? Do I enter? What do I do?
(Jong Kook and Se Chan have 71 minutes.)
- It's locked. - Goodness.
None of you guys who came here first got to leave?
- No, we couldn't. - This is the 100 Minute House.
- Look at this. - 10 dollars is reduced per minute.
30 minutes have passed already.
Did the others leave?
- No. - None of them?
"Find the similarity among these three."
What is this?
The first question is easy.
- Did you get it? - Yes.
- It's easy? - It is?
It's extremely easy.
It's near my place.
Can you give me a hint?
If you take the subway, you'll know.
- What? - Oh, my.
(Is the subway the hint?)
(She accidentally discloses a crucial hint.)
I accidentally told them.
The subway?
(Jong Kook thinks about...)
(the subway map.)
(He successfully does it.)
Is this right? Let me answer.
Room 6's answer to the 1st question is correct.
Okay! Goodness.
Seriously? Room six?
(He can't believe it.)
(To make it worse, )
- Here. - Room 4's answer is correct.
(even Seok Jin gets it.)
Room 6's answer to the 1st question is correct.
Okay! Goodness.
What is the answer? What about Itaewon?
You came here first.
You even received the hint.
I have no idea.
It's the same subway line.
The subway line. Goodness.
(He has practically told him everything.)
Let me answer.
(Thanks, Jae Seok.)
(Subway Line 1)
It's very similar.
- Really? - He came first and is still here.
I even gave him the hint.
Let me answer.
(He gets it wrong again.)
(He gets drenched.)
Hold on.
(Subway Line 3)
Let me answer.
(He's determined to keep guessing.)
Pour it on me!
Let me answer.
(He's wrong again.)
Keep pouring. Do it.
(It seems like he's enjoying it.)
Let me answer!
(He's wrong once again.)
How many lines are there?
(Hang in there.)
(She can't believe he's writing every single one.)
Then...
(He finally writes the right one.)
Let me answer!
- That's correct. - Okay!
(Thank goodness it wasn't Subway Line 9.)
Hold on. The poet?
The poet.
I have no idea.
(Room 8 has yet to welcome its owner.)
Here I go.
(The owner is still wrestling with paper cups.)
(He's wrong.)
(He decides to switch categories.)
Here I go.
How do I do this?
How do you do this? Gosh.
(He'll be here before the 100 minutes are up, right?)
Is Haha here?
I want to know the answer to the second question.
(Whoever gets it right wins.)
“On a distant day, when the skies first opened,”
“Somewhere a cock must have crowed.”
(Who is the poet of this poem?)
You all know this poet.
Really?
Here is your second hint.
This poet is a national poet.
Really?
(2nd hint: national poet)
- National poet? - National poet?
National? National poet?
(Yi Yuk Sa, Yun Dong Ju, Sim Hun, Baek Seok, Kim So Wol...)
(This poem was written...)
(by Yi Yuk Sa and was named "The Wide Plain".)
(Yi Yuk Sa: He got his nickname from his prisoner number, 264.)
(He wrote "The Wide Plain", "Green Grapes", and "A Tall Tree".)
National? National poet?
(The poem is called "The Wide Plain".)
What is this?
(The answer is Yi Yuk Sa.)
- I can't remember it. - Who is this poet?
The moment you hear this poet's name,
- you will recognize him. - Really?
All right. The answer is...
(Jae Seok jots something down.)
Hold on. A poet?
(Did he write the correct answer?)
(Yi Yuk Sa)
(He did.)
Room 2's answer to the 2nd question is correct.
You are free.
- What? - What?
- What? - Who?
- Who got it? - Who?
- Who was it? - Am I right?
- Who got it? - What happened?
- It's Jae Seok. - Who?
- Who got it? - I think it's Jae Seok.
Is the poet really that famous?
- What? - Is he famous?
Okay! Yes, he is.
- Who is it? - Jae Seok,
- tell me. - Me too, please.
(What?)
Is it not over? I don't think it is.
(The staff hands Jae Seok...)
(his final mission.)
(He thought it was over.)
What is this?
Goodness.
What?
(The first four to escape are runaways. Protect your name tag.)
How could you do this?
(He needs to run.)
Wait.
Gosh!
How could you do this?
What is it?
(Curious)
What's wrong? What is it?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(Where should I go?)
(The most important thing is, )
Jong Kook needs to escape soon.
(Jong Kook cannot become a chaser.)
He can't.
Gosh, who is this poet?
Who is it?
I don't know.
(Kwang Soo peeps into Jae Seok's room.)
So Min, I don't know this one.
(Jae Seok's whiteboard is there.)
(Fidgeting)
(He suddenly ties the towels.)
Was I not close at all?
(He puts his head into Jae Seok's room.)
(Through the small opening that connects to the next room, )
(he uses the towel...)
(to flip the whiteboard.)
(He lifts it...)
(but fails to flip it.)
(Focused)
(He successfully catches the corner.)
I heard it!
(Unfortunately, it slips.)
(He's determined to escape.)
(A hand appears.)
(Whose hand does this belong to?)
I'll hold this part.
(So Min comes to his aid.)
I'll read it.
After you flip it, I'll read it.
Hold on.
- Go a bit back. - Put it over there.
(Suddenly)
(The whiteboard's owner appears.)
- Jae Seok. Hey. - Jae Seok.
(Please don't.)
(Don't take it.)
Please don't take it.
- Please! No! - Please don't.
- Jae Seok, please. - No!
No! Jae Seok, please!
(He was close.)
Jae Seok, please.
Give us a hint.
Jae Seok, is the poet's name 1 word or 2 words?
What should I do? My goodness.
I had no idea I'd come last.
(An hour has passed since the 100 Minute House began.)
- Hey. - What's going on?
(Finally, Haha joins them.)
- Haha, you will never get this. - Yes?
What is it?
(He takes his blindfold off and looks around.)
Hold on.
(What is this?)
Can I start?
(Just when he's about to solve it...)
Let me watch from afar and see who escapes next.
(Jae Seok decides to watch them.)
What should I do?
Goodness.
I need to help Jong Kook escape.
(In order to make Jong Kook a fellow runaway, he must help him.)
(Yi)
(Yuk)
(Sa)
Darn it.
I can't think of any.
(He keeps signaling until Jong Kook notices.)
(However, Kwang Soo catches a glimpse of him.)
I'm sure I know the answer.
(Jong Kook, please look at me.)
(Another person spots Jae Seok.)
(It's Seok Jin.)
- Hold on. - Gosh.
(The two immediately write down their answers.)
I have no idea.
- Let me answer. - I did my best.
(He's quick-witted.)
Room 1's answer to the 2nd question is correct.
Here! Let me answer!
Room 4's answer to the 2nd question is correct.
(They both got it right?)
What is it?
What happened?
(I didn't mean for this to happen.)
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin escape at the 38-minute mark.)
- Good job. - Let me see.
(They each receive 380 dollars.)
(He checks his final mission.)
Is it good?
What is this? Oh, come on.
Come on!
Oh, come on!
What is this?
- How could you? - What is it?
Jong Kook should've seen me.
Why did it have to be Seok Jin?
Have I learned about him before?
Yes.
You know for sure.
How is that possible?
I rarely know things for sure.
(One more, and the runaways will be chosen.)
Does it include these words?
(He's unsure.)
It's "Yi Yuk" something.
- Hold on. What? - You have to be precise.
Be precise.
It's "Yi Yuk" something.
("Yi Yuk" is part of the answer?)
Isn't it similar? Wait.
Why can't I remember it?
I have no idea.
(She writes the answer.)
Room 3's answer...
to the 2nd question...
- is correct. - No way!
(Thanks to his hint, So Min gets it.)
(It's a twist of fate.)
(So Min escapes at the 33-minute mark.)
Haha doesn't know this one.
(She's sure he doesn't know.)
- Haha doesn't know. - What about me?
- What about me? - It's impossible.
- Do I not know as well? - There is absolutely...
no way you'd know.
(She gives him no hope.)
- Wasn't I right? - Yes.
It's similar, right?
(The 4 runaways are decided.)
- Wasn't my answer similar? - Yes.
- Right? - Jong Kook.
It's So Min.
- Gosh. It's So Min. - Oh, no.
- Goodness. - This is crazy.
So Min.
- Why did it have to be you? - Why?
Why?
Darn it.
- Why did you escape? - Why?
It's "Yi Yuk" something.
Yi Yuk Sa?
- Is that it? - I think so.
Is it Yi Yuk Sa?
Room 8's answer to the 2nd question is correct.
Let's go!
(Haha remembers the answer.)
(Thanks to Haha, )
(they all get out.)
(All right.)
(Shall we start the hunt?)
(Runaways, be afraid. Jong Kook is coming.)
He's out, he's out.
He's out. They're all coming out.
(Scared)
Where can I go?
There's no place to hide.
(They need to hold out and hide from the chasers.)
You weren't the first four to escape.
You have been assigned as chasers.
(The chasers need to catch the runaways.)
What?
Also, the money you had up until now...
has disappeared.
The 1st 4 who escaped...
are runaways.
As for them,
for every minute they stay hidden, they receive 10 dollars.
(The longer they hold out, the more they receive.)
Every time you rip a name tag,
you obtain that person's money.
The one with the most money wins at the end.
- Okay. So we rip name tags? - Correct.
I can rip 2 or 3 people?
Okay, let's go. This is better.
(The race begins.)
(Who will gain victory?)
If I were a runaway, where would I hide?
Where would I hide?
(The chasers can only win once they catch them all.)
Did you see anyone wearing the same outfit as me?
There's no one over there.
- Really? - Yes.
Thank you.
(The chasers spread out to find the runaways.)
I think they're at high places.
The parking lot?
(The chasers zero in on the runaways.)
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin is looking for a place to hide.)
(He searches for a place that's hard to find.)
There's no place to hide.
(He has gained 140 dollars so far.)
How about over there?
Come here.
(He finally finds an adequate place.)
Let's go. They won't find me here.
(He hides his frail body behind some branches.)
I'm sure they'll notice me.
Why did I have to wear yellow?
(Anyone can see this suspicious-looking yellowness.)
(Is he trying to disguise himself as a forsythia?)
(He strives to survive.)
Come over here. They won't spot us.
Right?
Good, but I think they'll spot you.
(We can see you.)
Can you just give me that and leave?
Give me that and leave, okay?
Give it to me and leave.
You both can leave. Go.
Go, and I'll do this myself.
I'm currently hidden in a very good spot.
(He successfully hides himself.)
I will win no matter what.
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok is at a parking lot.)
(Since he has the most money, he'll win if he holds out.)
(He decides to use their van as his hideout.)
Close the door!
I'm sorry. Hello.
Could you hide me in there, please?
(So Min has received 140 dollars so far.)
(She also decides to hide in a car.)
(Hurrying)
What should I do? Okay.
Hold it. Get in.
(Kwang Soo doesn't go far and also hides in a vehicle.)
Lock it.
(He uses his 9-year expertise and locks the door.)
(Except for Seok Jin, the rest hides in vehicles.)
I bet they're hiding in a car.
(He's experienced.)
(Haha also uses his 9-year experience as a runaway...)
(to guess where they could be hiding.)
Gosh! Hide! Goodness.
(Haha is near Jae Seok's car.)
(One turn of his head, and he will see him.)
(Afraid of getting caught, Jae Seok refuses to move.)
I bet they're in here.
(Haha is getting closer and closer.)
(At that moment, )
(he suddenly turns towards So Min.)
(He senses something suspicious about the car.)
Is anyone approaching this way?
If someone does come,
could you just drive?
(It's like her to say this.)
Okay.
(Haha approaches her car.)
My goodness. Tell them I'm not here.
(Suddenly, the door opens.)
Excuse me.
(He hasn't spotted her yet.)
So Min is...
here!
I knew it.
(He spots So Min who was hiding beneath the seat.)
- I knew you'd be here. - Why did you have to come?
I caught you.
Aren't you surprised?
So Min.
(So Min is eliminated.)
Aren't I just awesome?
That was great.
(Haha obtains her 200 dollars.)
I was the first one to get caught.
(Disappointed.)
This was a great spot, though.
(Looking around)
(Did Haha leave?)
At ease, at ease.
Haha was right there.
(He was lucky.)
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook looks inside the building.)
(Suddenly, he senses something...)
(like a professional and goes outside.)
(Did he spot the suspicious-looking yellowness?)
(Seok Jin is hiding right across the building.)
(Just pass me by, please.)
(He begins searching outdoors.)
(Will he get caught or not?)
They won't see me here.
(He spots a forsythia.)
(He has no idea that he's spotted.)
(He catches up to him before Seok Jin can even run.)
- Seok Jin. - How did you know?
I saw your yellow jacket.
(Seok Jin had a total of 290 dollars.)
- What? - Okay!
Okay.
- How did you know? - I got you.
Okay!
How could he see me?
(The remaining time is 7 minutes.)
(There are still 2 runaways remaining.)
Where could they be?
(If the runaways can hold out, it's their victory.)
I bet Kwang Soo is outside.
There's no way he's not.
Everyone.
I may be hiding here,
(Resolute)
but I doubt you'll see me on TV.
Everyone.
Please don't forget.
I am...
hiding in the back of a truck...
(He's confident they won't find him.)
that is parked near the entrance.
Everyone.
I'll see you next week.
(He says his goodbye.)
Check the truck!
Check the truck! Hurry!
- Look there. - Where? The truck?
(While Kwang Soo was chatting away, )
(the chasers have arrived at the parking lot.)
(As Jong Kook ordered, they search the truck.)
May I open this?
(I should've just stayed quiet.)
I'll open it.
(The chasers gather near him.)
- Can we open it? - Thank you.
(Haha and Ji Hyo open the truck.)
(Kwang Soo could get caught any minute now.)
(However, )
(Kwang Soo isn't inside.)
- What about those cabinets? - Let me check.
(Haha gets inside the truck to check.)
Hi, Kwang Soo.
Goodness, it must've been hard for you to stay in here.
(He catches Kwang Soo who has been hiding in the corner.)
- Kwang Soo. - Could I rip off his name tag?
Come here.
My, oh, my. You were in here.
- Get up. Well done. - How many minutes are left?
- How many minutes? - Well done.
(They successfully catch him.)
Goodness.
- Goodness. - How could think...
- about hiding in here? - We almost missed you.
This was amazing. We got him.
(How did you go in there?)
Viewers, thank you for supporting me.
I will give the camera back to the staff.
Viewers, bye.
Is Kwang Soo out? Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(Jae Seok is the only runaway left.)
My goodness.
I could get caught any minute...
since they are combing through the place.
There is no place to hide.
We just need to find Jae Seok.
He could be inside a car. Open each car.
(Jae Seok can't run away because of the chasers.)
(Chasers search thoroughly with only a few minutes remaining.)
Hello.
He isn't in the car, is he?
I am sorry.
(At that moment, )
(Ji Hyo heads to the vehicle Jae Seok is hiding.)
(If Jae Seok gets taken out, the runaways will lose.)
She is here. She is in front of the van.
(What will become of Jae Seok in the van?)
I found Jae Seok! He is here!
Lock the door. Lock the door!
(Chasers gather around instantly.)
Lock the door.
Come on.
(If he holds out for 30 seconds, he will win.)
(At that moment, )
(Kim Jong Kook appears.)
(He opened the trunk like an expert.)
(He corners Jae Seok right away.)
(Jae Seok escaped with 57 minutes remaining.)
(If he holds out, he will save up 570 dollars.)
I ripped it off.
(The last runaway, Jae Seok is out.)
(570 dollars get transferred to Jong Kook.)
(With 10 seconds remaining, all 4 runaways get taken out.)
The final winner...
- of The Great War of Money is... - Who is it?
- Kim Jong Kook. - Is it me?
What?
(The final winner is Kim Jong Kook.)
(He won 860 dollars by taking out Seok Jin and Jae Seok.)
- I am sick and tired of it. - My goodness.
- There is no point in trying hard. - I am sick and tired of it.
- Seriously. - Jong Kook always wins.
(Jong Kook always wins.)
We gave you questions earlier, right?
Combine those questions and open the safe in front of you.
(To open the safe which contains the prize, )
(they must combine the answers of the 100 Minute House.)
(The 1st answer was Subway Line 6.)
(The 2nd answer was Yi Yuk Sa.)
(The combined number is 6264.)
6264.
- 6264. - 6264.
(What does the number 6264 mean?)
Did it open?
Turn it.
What's inside?
(What's inside the safe?)
- There is something inside. - What is it?
- It's a book. - A book?
(There is a book inside the safe.)
(What is this extraordinary book?)
They said the prize is impressive.
- What? - Is it related to dawn club?
What is this?
(My goodness.)
What is it?
(What is it?)
The race of the day commemorates the 100th anniversary...
- of the March 1st Movement. - I see.
(100th Anniversary Special of the March 1st Movement, )
(The Great War of Money)
March 1st of 2019 marks the 100th anniversary...
of the March 1st Movement, which showed Korean resistance...
- during the Japanese rule. - It's the 100th anniversary.
(It's an event which shaped Korea the way it is now.)
For the first mission, you shouted hurray with people,
jumped ropes 19 times,
and aimed to get a score of 100...
since the March 1st Movement of 1919...
was an achievement of the common people...
who transcended classes, gender, and generations.
(It was an achievement of the common people.)
- Thank you. - Here you go.
(To commemorate the March 1st Movement, )
(souvenirs were given to people who participated in the missions.)
- My goodness. - There is everything.
(Do you remember?)
(You racked your brain...)
(to decipher a code.)
(Korean code)
(It was a mission which utilized the actual code...)
(of the Korean independence activists.)
At the location of the second mission,
we included the story of an independence activist...
who was seen as a libertine all his life, Kim Yong Hwan.
He was 1 of the top 3 libertines of Joseon Dynasty.
He gambled every day and lost his ancestral house...
and his land about 600,000 square meters.
That's about 20 million dollars' worth.
He received much criticism...
because he lost all the fortune and even gambled away the money...
for his daughter's wedding.
With that kind of money, he gambled until dawn.
When he couldn't win money, he yelled "dawn club!"
Dawn club!
(This is how he did it.)
He called over subordinates who were holding clubs...
to steal all the money.
He delivered the money he gathered with much criticism...
to activists for the independence movement.
However, he kept it a secret until the day he died.
He had to keep up the pretense...
so that he wouldn't get caught.
(He sacrificed his honor for the independence movement.)
This page reads, "Do you know who these people are?"
(Do you know who these people are?)
The combined answers gave you the number, 6264.
On 1989, 45 years after the liberation,
something was found in the dusty cabinet...
of what is now the National Police Agency.
It was 6,264 cards for people...
who were under surveillance during the Japanese rule.
(I see.)
In those 6,264 cards were...
people of all ages who were restaurant owners, students,
farmers, reporters, nurses, etc.
There were common citizens as well as independence activists...
we all know such as Yu Gwan Sun,
Han Yong Un, Yun Bog Gil, Ahn Chang Ho,
Kim Won-bong, and others.
Besides the ones whose information was found 45 years later,
there must have been many independence activists.
We lived our lives without knowing who they are.
6264 is a symbol of the history that was made by people...
who wished for the nation's independence...
and a trace of nameless activists we must remember.
(The place the members are at, Hyochang Park, )
(holds the grave of Kim Gu and shrine of An Jung Geun.)
(On the upcoming March 1st, )
(remember those who made the country the way it is...)
(and the day we must not forget.)
Even besides the ones we know,
there have been many patriotic martyrs...
who gave up their lives...
for the independence of Korea.
We use this opportunity to thank them wholeheartedly.
- Thank you. - Thank you so much.
(We will remember your shout. Thank you.)
I didn't know it was that bad.
(A mysterious video appears before the Running Man members.)
(I am your judge, )
(The Bee.)
(The appearance of a cute judge makes the members laugh.)
(The first member to be judged is...)
(Kim Jong Kook.)
(When the Bee says their names, the members disappear.)
Anyone would think you are the Bee.
Is the Bee among us?
(Is someone behind everything?)
(Schemes and twists surrounding the mysterious Bee.)
(What's the shocking identity of the Bee?)
(The Revenge of the Bee)