(College 'S' in Yongsan, Seoul)
Hello.
My gosh, it is so hot. It's really hot.
What do you mean? It's supposed to hot in summer.
(Jae Suk scolds him as soon as he walks in.)
(He starts the filming with scolding.)
Hey, I think I said that last summer.
Why are you complaining? It's not like it's your first summer.
You experienced summer more than 50 times. What's the fuss?
(He's brutally honest.)
What's the fuss?
- So don't complain too much. - Right.
It's not your first summer or anything.
- Exactly. - My gosh.
- Oh, my. - What is it?
You'll get shot if you go on a safari wearing that. Be careful.
You know nothing about fashion. Isn't my outfit pretty nice?
- Yes, it's a nice outfit. - It's nice.
What's that? "UFC"?
- It's not nice. What's up with UFC? - What's that?
(He's startled.)
- It's UFO? - UFO?
- It says "UFO" there. - UFO?
It says UFO.
Why is UFO written there?
It was UFO? What a twist.
I thought it said UFC.
He's a strong man, UFO.
(It's much better than UFC.)
(Stop it!)
Stop it. That's enough.
That's awesome. You can only see "UF".
- You'd think it was UFC. - Right?
- Everyone would've assumed that. - My gosh.
He's a strong man, UFO.
(If you're a strong man, wear this.)
Unidentified Flying Object.
Hey, So Min.
Are your shoulders okay?
(Bare shoulders on a hot day like today?)
(Only her shoulders are burning up.)
- You'll burn your shoulders. - On a day like today,
- Hey, you'll burn your shoulders. - you'll get a sunburn.
- I must've done something wrong. - What?
I guess I must've done something wrong to my stylist.
If So Min's stylist gave her that outfit on a day like this,
it means that she must have been fed up with So Min.
- That's right. - Exactly.
Is that obvious?
- What? - So with this outfit, it's obvious?
Her shoulders will be burnt when she goes home.
It's like she's saying, "You should suffer too."
- Did you hear? - What?
- For our fan-meet, we received... - 200,000.
Thank you so much!
(The sign-up page for the fan-meet received 200,000 views.)
200,000 views?
- Hey. I set this up, - What?
so I could say that 200,000 people were on our website.
- I already knew that. - Why did you steal that from me?
I already knew that.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
200,000 people were on our website, but no one around me knows.
- Be quiet. Why are you saying that? - I mean...
- It's because they are shy. - What's wrong with you?
- Is that so? Is that why? - They are shy.
- Not to make you uncomfortable. - Are you here to criticize us?
It looked like your friends wouldn't watch TV.
(Jong Kook's friends from "Mom's Diary")
What did you say? Are you criticizing their looks?
What's wrong with my friends?
- It's just something people say. - What?
- Then who looks like he'd watch TV? - Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, do it now. Hurry. - Tell me.
(Suk Jin, show him the shirt.)
(Strong Man, UFO)
Describe how someone who watches TV often would look.
- Give me an example. - Jong Kook.
- This is it. - You look strong right away.
- I see. - If you yell at him on a hot day,
- you'll cause him to faint. - That might happen.
Don't do that to him. Don't provoke him.
Today,
you'll win once you retrieve your emergency fund of 6,000 dollars.
It's called the Missing Emergency Fund Race.
A 6,000-dollar emergency fund?
It's gone missing again? Why do things keep disappearing?
- By the way, - Things keep disappearing.
there are about two people among us who would actually steal money.
All right. You are siblings of six.
Each sibling had 1,000 dollars as their emergency fund...
which means the entire emergency fund is 6,000 dollars in total.
Two of us aren't real siblings.
Your father whom you've parted with a long time ago...
only left a letter...
and withdrew the 6,000 dollars behind your backs.
- Our father did? - First,
- I'll show you the letter. - My goodness.
He's not our father.
(After taking the money, he left a letter.)
He's not our real dad.
Besides, our father...
wrote the letter on the new year greeting card.
Gosh, I haven't seen that for a while.
"Read this, you brats."
- It's just "kids". - Read it how's it written.
- I read it wrong? - Yes, you read it wrong.
- Yes. - I'm sorry.
"Read this, kids."
"My friend will be doing big business overseas."
"So I sold our land and the house..."
"and am taking the entire 6,000 dollars savings from home."
"Since you're young, make money diligently from now on."
"Please wish me luck with my new business."
He sounds like an uncaring dad.
One of you can have the letter on behalf of everyone.
(Ms. Shoulders will be holding onto it.)
Why are you taking it?
I keep looking at So Min's shoulders.
- Your shoulders will be red. - She...
(Call me Queen Shoulders.)
- So Min... - What about the other two?
Among the 8 of you, there are 6 siblings.
And one of you is the father.
(Among them, one of them is the father.)
- I see. - He's among us?
He's here?
Can a woman be a father?
Yes.
A stranger is hiding among you...
in order to steal the money your father withdrew.
- Stranger? - Stranger?
- Why me? Why? - Lee Kwang Soo.
(There you go again.)
- The stranger... - Stranger Kwang Soo.
It doesn't sound like my name.
- That's not my name. - It's Kwang Soo.
- It all makes sense. - Stranger Kwang Soo.
Currently, the father has lost his memory.
The only memory he has is that he's a father.
(Our father lost his memory?)
- He lost his memory? - This is...
He lost his memory? Hold on.
- His memory... - Wasn't that a big clue?
- If he lost his memory... - You all know who that is, right?
Our father lost his memory as soon as he wrote the letter?
He's the father.
Kwang Soo is the stranger.
All right. We caught them. The end.
- We can go home. - That wasn't it?
The race will end when your father figures out his identity.
He will be able to take all of the 6,000 dollars he withdrew.
I see. When the father finds out?
No, he knows that he's the father.
- He must figure out his identity. - His identity.
If the siblings figure out who he is and eliminate him, they will win.
And the siblings will split the 6,000 dollars among themselves.
That means we each get 1,000 dollars.
- What about the stranger? - What about the stranger?
Whenever the stranger eliminates a sibling,
he or she gets 1,000 dollars.
Once the stranger eliminates the father,
the stranger can take the money he or she won.
For example, if the stranger eliminates three siblings...
and the father next, the stranger gets 3,000 dollars.
However, if one of the siblings eliminates the stranger...
who is hiding among you,
the sibling who eliminated the stranger will get...
the entire 6,000 dollars once he or she eliminates the father.
- I should catch the stranger first. - That's right.
The siblings, father, and a stranger are against one another.
It's an individual match for everyone.
Since your father withdrew all of the money,
you cannot use your own money.
You can borrow money from us to pay for the expenses of the missions.
You must pay it back at the end by winning the cash prize.
The members who failed to win the cash prize...
must pay back the money in another way.
I'll explain how to pay back the money.
- We have to take out loans. - Okay.
It's the penalty. Will we pay it back with penalties?
- He's right. That's it. - I was right.
- I'm doomed. - We must do the penalties.
(Under 100 dollars, spanking)
I've had this before. You'll die.
("Wireless" bungee jumping)
- It's the one Suk Jin did. - This will kill you.
You'll fall from 50m high without a rope.
Without the rope, you'll die.
- There's a net on the bottom. - The net?
Indoor skydiving will be hard too.
Kwang Soo and I've done it.
- It's no joke. - It goes up and comes down.
- It's scary inside. - Was it fun?
- No, it's scary. - It's scary?
For the indoor skydiving,
you're supposed to fall and not hit the floor,
but you do.
(The crash is an added bonus on top of the fear.)
(I think it's your fault.)
It means we can borrow money by doing these penalties?
- You can pay it back with those. - Pay it back? I see.
After changing into your uniform, we'll start the race.
- Go, go. - Let's catch the father.
We ought to.
- Here's your first mission. - Okay.
The member who withdraws the least amount of money will be given...
a hint of his or her choice.
It's called Lonely Meal.
- Lonely Meal? - We have to read each other's mind.
- Here's the address. Take it. - What's this?
We have to go somewhere?
I want Pyeongyang naengmyeon.
I want Pyeongyang naengmyeon too.
Hey, braised kimchi will be delicious too.
All right. Here's your rule.
You must choose one of the restaurants...
after looking at the menu and the prices by 1:30pm.
After 1:30pm, the restaurant with the least number...
of members will provide free meals.
There are free meals?
The restaurant with the most number of members will charge...
- 10 times the written price. - 10 times?
If the original price is 30 dollars, it will be 300 dollars?
- The 3rd one will be 1,000 dollars. - It's 1,000 dollars.
We'd use up all of our money to begin with.
The team in the middle will pay the original price...
and can have the meal.
I just need to be in the middle.
However,
you can change your restaurants freely during your given time.
If you're not at the restaurant when the time is up,
- That person is out. - you'll pay a 2,000-dollar fine.
- What? - It's over then.
- It's over. - That person can't eat...
and will only carry out the penalty.
Hey, it will be hard to pay it back even if I win 6,000 dollars.
Prices on Running Man are so expensive.
- They are so expensive. - Right?
The prices on Running Man are so expensive.
And the member who spent the least amount of money...
will be able to choose to receive a hint...
about the stranger of the father.
Jong Kook, aren't you going to choose Pyeongyang naengmyeon?
- I have to think what I want first. - I want to get the steak.
- But that's the perfect dish now. - It's so hot...
- right now. - That'd be perfect now.
Tell us where you're going to go.
- Okay. Overall, - I want Pyeongyang naengmyeon.
Not you. Tell us where you're going to go.
(Not you.)
(Not me?)
(I want an answer from Mr. Straightforward, not Mr. Liar.)
I wasn't even listening to Jae Suk.
- As for me... - Pyeongyang naengmyeon.
- We can set out now, right? - Where should we go?
Gosh, this is crazy.
Hey, we have a lot of time. Do you want to get some tea?
- We have a lot of time. - I'll go somewhere nearby...
and spend some time.
- Who wants Pyeongyang naengmyeon? - I want Pyeongyang naengmyeon.
If you want to switch, you can go on your own.
We'll split the cab fare to the restaurant.
The maximum number of people is 3 for 1 cab.
- Is that so? - Really?
Let's kick someone out.
Whoever loses rock-paper-scissors can leave.
- That person is out? - Yes.
- That person can't come with us. - All right.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins with paper.)
- Okay. - One more round.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo wins with scissors.)
Okay!
(We can carpool together.)
(The outcome of the last round of rock-paper-scissors...)
(is Ji Hyo's loss.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Take the cab by yourself. - Bye.
- Hey. - To Pyeongyang naengmyeon, right?
- You'll go there first, right? - Yes.
We'll settle who pays for the cab...
- on the way there. - Okay.
I have to read their moves.
(Ji Hyo is all alone now.)
(Looking up the address)
No way.
I was going to walk, but it will take an hour.
3.8km. This is crazy.
(Gosh, what should I do?)
What should I do?
(Will she take the taxi by herself? Or will she walk?)
Waffle with apple-flavored whipped cream.
- You're buying? - Of course.
Really? Thank you.
It's cheaper since it's near a university, right?
I see. That's our waffle?
My gosh, this is huge.
- Look. Sure. - Thank you.
- I'll enjoy this. - Okay.
I didn't know it was thick like this.
It's thick just like the one from Sookmyung Women's University.
- My gosh. - I can't bite it in one go.
My chin hurts.
(Opening wide)
(In approval)
(The flavor calls for an approval.)
- It's not bad. - It's good.
- It's good. - This is what I wanted.
Take a seat.
I feel bad that you spent four dollars.
(Chuckling)
It's not bad.
- I think Se Chan might have a role. - This is not bad.
- Right? - Yes. It's about time...
that he had a role today.
Did you see how he was so quiet earlier?
It's about time that he had a role.
And during the opening segment, when our eyes met,
I saw your eyes shaking.
- You're the father, right? - It's not me. I swear.
You're the father, aren't you? Look me in the eye.
Where are you?
We're on our way to...
- "We"? The four of us... - With whom?
are going to the Pyeongyang naengmyeon restaurant.
Who's there?
Including myself,
it's Haha, Kwang Soo, and Jong Kook.
(Including myself, it's Haha, Kwang Soo, and Jong Kook.)
(How could he say Jong Kook's name?)
Hey.
What did you say? Say that again.
- Hey. - Hello?
- We're at the noodles restaurant. - It's Haha,
Kwang Soo, and Jong Kook. It's the four of us here.
- Jong Kook is there? - Yes. What?
- Se Chan. - Hey, Jong Kook. Hello?
He's really there.
He hung up on him.
- I got so scared for a second. - So Min...
Se Chan.
Hey, Jong Kook. Hello?
He hung up.
(You hung up? You punk, Se Chan!)
In my opinion, I think Kwang Soo and Se Chan are going to...
- the restaurant together. - Right. And...
He doesn't want you to choose that restaurant.
- He said there are a lot of people. - He pretended it was crowded.
Which restaurant will you go to?
Doesn't your gut tell you...
to go to the steakhouse?
- I'm going there. Yes. - To the steakhouse?
I think this place will be good.
- Is that so? - I'll just follow you for now.
(Sure.)
- Let's go. - See? He's so cool.
He didn't tell me to pay for my own.
- He'll pay for the taxi. - Of course.
Gosh, of course.
I don't ask people to pay for me.
- This is nice. - You know?
(They head to the restaurant that serves seafood stew and steaks.)
Gosh, I got stuck with these guys.
I'll definitely beat you guys.
I'm going to stay at the restaurant. You've been informed.
- That's also a way to do this. - I'll just sit there.
That's cool.
How about this? Say that the three of us are sitting there.
If someone else joins, it will be four of us, so no one will join.
- Whoever loses the game... - He'll leave?
- When the time is up, he'll leave. - Okay.
- That's fair. - Great.
How much money do you have?
30 dollars.
Gosh, he's so stingy.
- You don't have any guts. - It's not that.
I don't need more than 30 dollars. Why would I borrow more?
He's so petty.
I bet Scrooge wasn't as stingy as he is, right?
I'm not being stingy.
How come...
Be honest. Have you ever bought stuff for me?
(Hey, Greedy Millipede.)
Why are you asking me that all of a sudden?
You always forget to bring a wallet whenever we hang out.
- He really does that? - It was a mistake.
- How many times have you done that? - This...
You can't bring that up here.
- I'm serious. - I'm so disappointed.
I told you. I believe that people should act the same...
- Kwang Soo. - off and on camera.
A while ago, he and I had a meal together.
- It was time to pay for our meal. - Okay.
- He was hesitating. - Are you serious?
(He was hesitating.)
"Hesitating"?
- Se Chan's younger than you. - So I...
You're amazing.
So I gave up on him.
You're going to tattoo that character on me?
(Laughing)
I'm sorry, sir. I laughed too loudly.
This is it.
Please stop here.
(They arrive at the Pyeongyang naengmyeon place.)
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay! - Let's go.
Okay.
(Haha will pay.)
That was a free cab ride.
- Thanks, Haha. - Thanks.
I want some ice cream. We have enough time.
We do.
Should we bet on ice cream?
Of course.
- Hey. - What is it?
Look at you trembling.
He's hesitating again. Come on.
- I do use my money. - Then do you want to pay?
- No, I don't. - No?
I'm not craving ice cream.
What?
Hey. Hey.
If I bought some, would you have eaten?
If you buy one, I'll eat it.
(He changes his attitude.)
But...
But that's not why.
I'll lend you some money.
Spend some money.
Are we going to have ice cream from the supermarket?
- What? Hey. - Are we going Baskin-Robbins?
- Of course. - Hey!
- What? - What?
That's a bit...
- What? - Are you being a Scrooge?
- Fine, let's go. - Okay.
I'm not craving ice cream.
How about this?
(He proposes a deal.)
The person the worker chooses will pay.
- Okay. - All right.
Will you be all right?
You seem to be confident.
Your fame will play a part.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
- Pick your flavor first. - I'd like...
- Cherry Jubilee. - I'd like Almond Bongbong.
I'd like Gone with the Wind.
Gone with the Wind?
- It's 9 dollars and 90 cents. - How much?
9 dollars and 90 cents?
Among us,
who would you like to pay for it?
- You see... - Be fair.
- Just pick one. - Anyone.
Who would it be?
(She picks Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo, the star, will pay.)
(Me?)
(We don't need to pay!)
Then please take out Gone with the Wind.
- No. - Just give all three, please.
- It's already included. - I don't want ice cream.
- Come on. - It's already in there.
- Give it to a staff member. - Right.
(His face becomes pale.)
It's already registered here.
(Kwang Soo spends 9 dollars and 90 cents.)
- Thank you. - I'm really not craving it.
Why do you always hesitate when you're in front of the register?
- Why? - What do you mean?
You should've just paid.
You were trembling.
What are you filming?
- You're trembling. - What do you mean?
- I'm not trembling. - It's as if you lost your savings.
It's only 9 dollars and 90 cents.
Can't you be a bit more generous?
Now that it has come to this...
Okay.
Fine.
I know how I'll be acting today. Okay.
(While Kwang Soo is in pain for having spent his money...)
- Until 1:30pm? - Yes.
(Ji Hyo decides to walk.)
(It's been 30 minutes.)
(She changes her destination to a nearby place.)
I'm almost there.
I found it.
It's over there.
(She enters a braised kimchi restaurant.)
(If Jae Suk and Suk Jin aren't here,)
(she'll most likely win.)
(She went through so much to save money.)
(How many people are here?)
No one's here?
(It's 12:45pm, and for now, there's no one.)
Are they not hiding in there?
(If no one else comes, she'll get to eat for free.)
I chose coffee over a cab.
It's so cool.
No one's here.
Hello.
No one came before us, right?
No, it's not time yet.
- One of us will have to leave. - Right.
Let's play a game.
For your information, we've already prepared a game.
- Really? - First one is Word ASMR.
We will write something.
You must listen to the sound.
- That's great. - Let's do that.
- ASMR is nice. - I did it often during radio shows.
- Then let's do something else. - Yes.
I was the one writing, not guessing.
If you get the first question right, we're going to start all over.
- That's ridiculous. - It's not.
It's... Wait, it's not?
- No. - Okay.
- Please start. - Put on your eye masks.
(They will cover their eyes.)
- You better not peek. - We have 20 minutes.
If you peek, you're out.
Of course.
- You shouldn't peek. - Okay.
If someone's cheating, please tell us.
- Okay. - That's not right.
- You must cover your eyes. - I'll keep an eye.
- Okay. - If that happens, I'll restart.
Get ready...
(Haha's ready.)
- What? - What?
(Did they all cover properly?)
(Why aren't you wearing yours?)
- What is this? - Gosh.
Let's not do this. We need to play the game.
Someone needs to leave.
How could not a single one of us keep the promise?
- Come on. - This is only the beginning.
- This is a simple game. - Then lie face forward.
(They decide to lie face forward.)
- Okay. - I'll start once you lie down.
(They decide to cover their eyes and lie down.)
(Looking around)
- Let me put this up. - Wait.
(His eyes are visible.)
Hey, our eyes locked.
- I don't want to do this. - Let's not.
Don't do that.
Or let's look at each other.
That's good. Give me a page of the sketchbook.
- We'll be behind it. - My gosh.
- Is this supposed to be this hard? - Is this...
Gather around.
- Raise this. - Then I can see.
- Really? - Yes.
This is impossible to see.
(Now, we're done.)
- No? - Fine.
Fine.
Fine, I'll stoop.
(Thanks to Se Chan's apology, they try one more time.)
It's... Come on.
(Glancing)
- All right. Let's really do it. - What was that?
- Let's do it. - Seriously.
We've been here for 15 minutes but haven't played a single game.
How will we cover our eyes?
We just need to cover it like this.
But no one's doing it.
- Is this... - Who is that?
- Why are you here? - You really came?
Is this the place with the most people?
What's wrong with you today?
What?
He doesn't know when to back off. He really came.
Is he the stranger?
You can't come here.
- Are you... - Are you staying here?
Of course.
How about this? Two people will leave.
- Okay. - Let's do that.
Three will leave.
- Three? - You'll be alone?
I'm all for it.
- Okay. - But you can't come back ever.
- Let's keep that promise. - Seriously.
- Keep it. - Okay.
- You can't come back. - This is a rule.
- But if one person... - The stakes are high.
If only 1 person is here, they'll probably come 1st place.
Right.
The last number is 24.
- You can press it 3 or 4 times. - It opens early, though.
- Am I the last? - Yes.
It doesn't matter how many times you press the doorbell.
It's your choice.
(Ringing)
- If you fail... What is it? - My gosh.
(What is it?)
- Why is he here? - You really came?
My gosh.
- This is driving me crazy. - We need to send four people.
- Hurry up and play the game. - We need to hurry.
- Hurry over. - We need to send four people.
- What's going on? - We need to send four people.
- We're running out of time. - We need to send four.
If you win, you'll come first place no matter what.
- We'll be sending four? - If you lose, leave immediately.
- This is the order. - If you lose, you have to leave.
- The last survivor wins. - Get ready.
You can't come back.
Okay. Go.
(They can press it as many times as they want.)
(Ringing)
(Haha loses.)
(Go!)
- Go! - Leave!
- Hold on. - Leave!
- Get lost! - Darn it.
Go out.
(Poor Haha gets kicked out.)
- Leave. - Leave.
- Get out. - Let me watch.
- Go. - Follow the rule.
You can't come back.
- All right. - You can't press it three times.
It'll open before it's my turn.
Okay, I'm done.
Suk Jin.
- That's it? - Yes.
Don't be sly like that.
- Why not? - Hey.
- How is that being sly? - Come on.
You have no courage.
No, I don't. I think the limit is five.
You won't succeed in life.
It's Suk Jin and then Jae Suk.
- Is that it? - Yes.
(Ringing)
(He suddenly transforms himself into a courageous man.)
You pressed three times?
(That petty-minded guy pressed three times?)
I bet it'll come out.
- Okay. - You pressed one time?
One more time?
(He decides to press it one more time.)
- It sounds like it'll open soon. - Press it one more time.
- 1 more time. No, 2 more times. - 1 more time.
- Once? - Once.
You can press it two times too.
(Opening)
(His greed gets the best of him.)
- Get out. - Get out.
Get out.
Hurry up.
- Get out. - Get out.
- Why didn't he stop after once? - I know.
- Why didn't you stop? - Why were you greedy?
- You better follow the rule. - I will.
Don't come back.
This is driving me crazy.
- Is it me or you? Which way is it? - This way.
- It's me? - I'm so disappointed.
Open, open, open.
- Press it hard. - I did.
You're so petty.
- Seriously. - You're so petty.
You're seriously...
What's the point of surviving through such petty ways?
- His heart is as big as a teaspoon. - A teaspoon?
It's over.
- Okay! - Get out!
(Jae Suk is eliminated at once.)
Get out.
- Get out. - Don't say a thing.
- Is it my turn? - Yes.
(Here comes the final round.)
(Ringing)
Why are you so good?
(Please)
(Suk Jin wins.)
Get out and never come back.
Does this make any sense?
You promised.
Get out and never come back.
- Let's go out for now. - Okay.
- A promise is a promise. - It's a promise.
Let's keep the promise.
Don't ever come back. Get out.
Gosh, he's amazing.
- He came... - I've...
- and succeeded. - succeeded.
I made it. Okay.
I can't believe I won.
(His petty character brought victory to him.)
I won.
We've come out.
Let's play a game to have one person enter.
- Enter where? - This restaurant.
- He shouldn't win. - We should go in.
And he wasn't present when we were talking about the rules.
- Why did he butt in? - Exactly.
- This was our agreement. - Right.
- One person will go in. - Let's play it.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's make it simple. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins.)
Okay!
(It only ended up benefiting someone else.)
Just like that?
(Se Chan heads back into the restaurant.)
How much time is left?
I can't believe I got so lucky.
- Hey. - I got lucky.
- What's going on? - We played rock-paper-scissors...
so that one person could go back inside.
Get out of here. Seriously?
(He's extremely flustered.)
But I won the game.
I won the game outside.
There are a different set of rules outside, you know.
What are you talking about?
You were just supposed to leave.
What are you doing back here?
- You... - What's going on?
(They spot someone.)
We played a game to decide who gets to stay.
- What? - The game here was over,
so we played a new one outside.
What?
This restaurant will win for sure then.
(They can't let that happen.)
Let's sneak inside and eat.
We'll play Palm Face Down or Up...
and let one more person stay.
Palm Face Down or Up
Nice!
- Hold on. - It's not all too bad.
Okay, you stay there.
We should go our separate ways.
That we should.
(And so Haha and Jae Suk head somewhere else.)
- That's not it. - What?
We played a new game.
Right, then that's that.
- It's over then. - Let's play another game.
- But... - We'll play another game...
and send someone away.
Only one will stay.
Unbelievable.
Okay.
- Does it end exactly at 2:30pm? - Yes.
The other four can't come back here.
(They have 25 minutes left.)
There isn't much time left.
I can't believe I missed another one.
(It'll be a 2,000 dollar fine if they're out on the street.)
(Meanwhile, at the steak restaurant...)
- We can't go now. - Right.
- We have to stay. - It's out of our hands now.
We'll have to kick out anyone who comes.
I'm truly sorry.
(An unwanted guest appears.)
I had no choice.
Get out.
Why did you come here?
You said you were going to the kimchi restaurant.
- I was going to, but... - It's all good.
Have a seat first.
- I got kicked out. - Sit.
You'll blackout and wake up two minutes later...
on the grass outside.
(You'll wake up on the grass outside.)
That's where you'll wake up.
- On the grass. - Seriously?
There's 3 here and 3 there.
- That means 1,000 dollars. - That's 1,000 dollars for us.
Oh, no. I have nowhere to go though.
(What's important is where Jae Suk, Haha, and Suk Jin goes.)
(Meanwhile, front-runner Kwang Soo is nervous.)
(Okay, it'll soon be over.)
It'll be over soon.
There's 20 minutes left.
(Only 20 minutes remain.)
What happens if I win again?
- You'll receive a hint, and - A hint and...
- your meal is free. - What?
(Just then!)
You see...
- There isn't time. - What do you mean?
(What do you mean there isn't time?)
- Get out of here. - There isn't enough time.
There's still 20 minutes left.
- There isn't enough time. - What are you going to eat?
What about Haha? Did you come here alone?
Yes. Why isn't anyone here though?
We played a game and Suk Jin got kicked out.
My gosh.
I only came here because the penalty would be cheap.
- My gosh. - The two of us can win.
We can still win this.
- Unbelievable. - I didn't see this coming.
It ends in 10 minutes.
(The chances of winning go up as only 10 minutes remain.)
What are you doing here?
What are you doing back here?
(Suk Jin reappears.)
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
- Why? - There's nowhere to go.
You could go anywhere.
There isn't enough time.
- Time's almost up. - What have you been doing so far?
Still, why did you come back here?
There's nowhere to go.
We won't win at this rate.
It'll be hilarious if Haha choose steak.
- That'll be great. - Then we'll be in second place.
- 2nd place means... - We'll only pay 30 dollars.
We can easily afford 30 dollars.
That'll be perfect.
Where Haha goes is most important.
He can either come in first place or last place.
It's either or for him.
There's one minute left to the game.
It's over. There's no way he made it.
- That'll be 3.8 dollars. - Right.
Here you go.
Please let 1 restaurant have 4 people.
Only two minutes remain!
(Everyone's fate is in Haha's hands.)
Where was Haha headed?
- He's probably there. - He needs to arrive there.
I hope he does.
One Pyeongyang naengmyeon, please.
(One Pyeongyang naengmyeon, please.)
What?
(The fourth customer, Haha enters.)
It was just too hot.
I couldn't walk around anymore.
- What? - Unbelievable!
Didn't anyone leave?
Why didn't you leave?
- Why didn't you go? - Unbelievable.
I thought I'd rather come in last place here.
At least, it'll be cheap.
Why did we play all those games then?
Let's have one person leave now.
- What? - It's for real this time.
Then that person will have to pay 2,000 dollars.
I should've gone to the kimchi place.
- 3, 2... - Unbelievable.
One. Time's up.
This'll cost us 300 dollars.
Four people at the naengmyeon restaurant.
At the braised kimchi restaurant,
there's only 1 person. There's 3 at the steak place.
Yes!
(What?)
Are you kidding me?
- What was that? - Are you teasing us?
The people here are terrible with numbers.
- Why were you happy just now? - Why?
I should've left this place.
You will pay 10 times the amount which is 300 dollars.
I was going to go to the kimchi restaurant.
You can eat your meal after paying the exact amount.
- We're in second place? - What? There someone else.
Jong Kook...
- See? - We're in second place.
- We're in 2nd place. - 2nd place!
The first mission was...
Lonely Meal and the winner is Song Ji Hyo.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Who would you like to know about between the father and the stranger?
(Pondering)
I'd like to know about the father.
(She chooses to know about the father.)
Sure. Here you go.
(She will learn two things about the father.)
The first one is about the father's identity.
The second one is about how the father can guess about himself.
(The hints about the father)
The father's blood type isn't AB.
What's this?
(That excludes So Min as the father.)
(The father has to guess who he is exactly.)
(The second hint would help him solve it.)
The second one is about how the father can guess about himself.
What's this?
(Jun Ji Hyun, Song Kang Ho,)
(Kang Ha Neul, Gong Yoo know their father,)
(but Shin Min A, Yeo Jin Goo, and Jo In Sung don't.)
"Jun Ji Hyun, Kang Ho Dong..."
(Kang Ho Dong?)
"They know their father."
"But Shin Min A, Yeo Jin Goo,"
"and Jo In Sung don't."
(Jun Ji Hyun, Kang Ho Dong, Kang Ha Neul?)
What's this?
(The second clue only matters to the father.)
This is quite tricky.
Anyway, I got it for now.
Thank you.
Gosh, this is good.
- It's delicious. - Gosh.
(The expenses so far)
I ate naengmyeon for 300 dollars.
We're already in trouble.
Here comes Ji Hyo.
My gosh.
- The winner. - The winner!
She was the sole winner.
How do you do this?
I'm always fascinated.
Well, I...
Why do you always win games?
- Well... - Share the clues with us.
You received a hint.
- It's unbelievable. - What is it?
(The hint is unbelievable.)
- Really? - The hint...
Actually, I received two.
(She received two hints about the father.)
I'll share one of them.
- Really? - Good.
(The generous winner shares a hint with them.)
The father's blood type isn't AB.
(The father's blood type isn't AB.)
- That excludes So Min. - So it's not So Min.
It's not So Min?
However, she could still be a stranger.
That's right. It could mean she's a stranger.
Must we catch the stranger as well?
The more children the stranger eliminates,
the more money he or she will receive.
Kwang Soo, you're awfully silent.
- I was thinking. - I find it odd...
that you came today with your hair and makeup done.
You were fully dolled up today.
(Did he come early because he's the father or stranger?)
You only saw me because you were there too.
(You only saw me because you were there too.)
I came after the time that was agreed upon.
Wait. The time that was agreed upon?
Was there a meeting?
I meant the time we had to arrive.
- Stop confusing the others. - Hold on.
- It sounds weird. - I'm talking about Kwang Soo.
A time that was agreed upon?
Don't confuse us by saying such things.
- Suk Jin. - I'm just saying.
You should be on point with what you say though.
I get things wrong all the time.
He's right about that.
My gosh!
(The steak trio returns.)
At a steep price...
What a pricey bowl of Pyeongyang naengmyeon.
What happened?
Who knows?
(It's a long story.)
No one actually left.
How...
The naengmyeon team...
(Pyeongyang naengmyeon)
I know it wasn't easy due to the hot weather.
- Right. - Next is Race of Witty Answers.
After you hear the question,
the first one to stand up...
will answer in a two-syllable word.
Then will ask another question in five seconds.
The next person will answer in a three-syllable word then question.
- The next one, four... - The game's been upgraded.
Make sure to answer in more syllables.
1, 2, 3, and so on?
Just so you know, this is my specialty.
You're the worst at this.
It's one of the games I am good at.
Here we go. Get ready.
(The first answer must be in two syllables.)
And go!
What do you wish to say to the director?
It's hot.
(She means it 100 percent.)
Who do you wish to see right now?
My mother!
(Three syllables)
Who's the second person you want to see?
(Who's the second person you want to see?)
Helen Keller.
(Four letters)
That was quite cool.
(The person he misses?)
(She's the second person he wants to see.)
- Helen Keller. - That was cool.
She's someone we all wish to see.
- Get on with the game. - Helen Keller.
The book you were most touched by.
Your five seconds is up.
(He only had 5 seconds to ask the question.)
- But... - Five seconds passed.
All I did was respond to Haha's comment.
- Suk Jin... - Why did you make me talk?
- Come on. - Why were you admiring...
your impromptu response? We don't have the time.
Suk Jin, it's too bad.
Tell me about it.
Do you know who Helen Keller is?
- Jong Kook, please. - Who is she?
Wasn't she a nurse?
(Wasn't she a nurse?)
That's right.
- Right? - Helen Keller?
Helen Keller was not a nurse.
- Nightingale was a nurse. - Nightingale was a nurse.
(Nightingale was a nurse.)
I mixed them up.
(I know, but I mixed them up.)
Haha said you were right.
Isn't she something similar?
She overcame adversity.
She created something out of nothing.
She did many good things.
None of us know exactly.
Madame Curie is...
a scientist.
(But Ji Hyo is the worst at historical figures.)
(During Race of Witty Answers in episode 460,)
(she said, "Madame Gurie", instead of "Madame Curie".)
(That's when Madame Gurie became her nickname.)
Madame Curie is...
- a scientist. - Hey,
I went grocery shopping with my family yesterday,
and there were oats, which sounds like "guirie".
Dream suddenly said,
"Oh, that's Ji Hyo's!"
(Madame Gurie left a bigger impression than Madame Curie.)
- It's true. - Madame Gurie is...
Ji Hyo.
You're becoming associated with oats.
You might even be offered an oats commercial.
Here we go.
Let's start from a two-syllable answer.
You have to be strict.
- I'll be strict. - You have to be.
Because this game exposes our ad-libs skills.
(Laughing)
You have an advantage in this game.
That's why I said it.
- Jae Suk has an advantage. - All right.
Seriously.
- It'll all be exposed. - Let me guarantee you.
- You'll sit next to Suk Jin. - Be quiet.
Let me show you how to play this game.
Ready, start.
What are you going to do after the shoot?
Shower.
(What are you going to do after the shoot?)
You're both out.
Shower.
(Jae Suk is eliminated before he gets to open his mouth.)
The ad-lib king has fallen.
- Ji Hyo, I haven't even... - Jae Suk.
- opened my mouth yet. - Jae Suk.
You should have said something before getting up this high.
- Gosh. - You should have said something.
Gosh, this is frustrating.
Look. No one left in the game can ad-lib.
(He is still worried about ad-libs.)
What are you going to do?
All the witty members have been eliminated.
(All the witty members have been eliminated.)
Who's witty?
"Witty members"?
All the good talkers including Madame Gurie are over here.
Madame Gurie and Helen Keller...
(With the witty members eliminated, the game continues.)
(In the next round, Kwang Soo and Jong Kook are eliminated.)
Here we go.
What is your secret habit?
Farting.
Is farting a habit?
Ask a question.
What part of your body has a secret?
Anus.
(Anus)
- Gosh. - Hold on.
- It's tiny. - What's with you?
I don't want to play games with him.
I told you.
- I'm being honest. - Why would you say that?
It's gross.
Make a decision.
Kids in the lower grades must be cracking up right now.
They must be going crazy.
The level of his jokes is too low.
- Is it accepted? - Se Chan is out.
- Okay! - His level is too low.
(So Min and Haha survived by confessing their secrets.)
Let's start the final round.
If So Min or Haha wins, that person becomes the winner.
- Oh, my gosh. - If someone else wins,
the three of them will play rock-paper-scissors.
How about this time...
we sit down after saying the answer?
I'll ask one question,
- and you'll answer one by one. - All right. That's better.
- Let's start. - Here we go.
Start.
What do you think of before going to sleep?
You.
(One syllable)
Wife.
Dog.
My dad.
Aunt's house.
(Once again, the ad-lib king...)
That's only four syllables.
(He should have given a five-syllable answer.)
Hold on.
You're the worst.
Jae Suk!
What's wrong with him?
- Hold on. - What's with you?
- Are you doing this on purpose? - Hold on.
Please go out. Go wash your face.
- Just a second. - Go out!
- Go... - Aunt's house...
Go wash your face.
Go stare into space for a moment.
When are you going to ad-lib?
- Go stare into space. - Seriously.
- How can he be so bad? - This is frustrating.
I can't do this.
I'm not really content with staying in the country.
(The level here is too low for me.)
- Does Korea have a long way to go? - I can't do this.
Jae Suk is hilarious.
- "Aunt's house". - "Aunt's house".
(Haha mimics the ad-lib king.)
I can't really compete with you guys.
Our levels don't match.
Here we go.
What's a nickname you want to give your boyfriend or girlfriend?
(What's a nickname you want to give your boyfriend or girlfriend?)
- Bear. - Pig.
Puppy.
(What nicknames are there?)
Little punk.
(Four syllables)
- That's cute. - Little punk.
Okay.
Love Hunter.
(What's a nickname you want to give your boyfriend or girlfriend?)
(Only Se Chan and So Min are left.)
Gas Station of Love.
(Six syllables)
"Gas Station of Love"?
What do you mean?
You're out.
(Se Chan is eliminated.)
That's funny. "Gas Station of Love".
Does he fill you up with his love?
A song with that title might be released.
A song by Love Hunter,
- "Gas Station of Love". - "Gas Station of Love".
("Gas Station of Love" by Love Hunter)
When your energy level is low, fill yourself with diesel
(Suk Jin is inspired by the title.)
(Bang, bang)
Fill yourself up at the gas station of love
(Suk Jin is so funny.)
1.435 dollars per liter
Here we go. Ready.
They're finally competing against each other.
- Finally. - Ready.
Start.
What do you want to say to the person on your right?
- Leave! - Leave!
(One syllable)
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook are eliminated.)
Ji Hyo wins.
- What is this? - Ji Hyo.
She didn't even do anything.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
If Ji Hyo wins, she'll get another hint.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
I was going to play a paper.
(So Min wins.)
- Oh, my. - So Min wins.
So Min is fishy.
- So Min is fishy. - So Min is fishy.
- She's been suspicious. - She's been suspicious.
I'm not the stranger.
- I swear. - You're suspicious.
She's been following me around all day.
And she's trying too hard today.
I'm not the stranger.
So Min.
Would you like a hint about the father...
or the stranger?
She usually doesn't win games like this.
I choose the father.
- The father? - Yes.
(What's the father hint that So Min received?)
This is too vague.
(The father is a man.)
(All male members become suspects.)
"The father didn't like rabbits, foxes, and pheasants."
"Rabbits, foxes, and pheasants".
"Foxes"? "Rabbits, foxes, and pheasants".
(The father didn't like rabbits, foxes, and pheasants.)
So Min, is it something you can't share with us?
I've helped her out today. I'm sure she'll share it with me.
I can share it with Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo has a hint too. - I'll share it with Ji Hyo.
Let's move to our next mission spot.
- Yes, let's go! - We have no hints.
- Let's start. - Okay.
This is the final mission where you can get hints...
about the father and the stranger.
It's called Quiz King, Shoot and Goal.
"Quiz"?
After hearing the choices and answer for each question,
guess what...
the question is.
We have to guess what the question is?
- This is new. - That's...
(They have to guess what the question is.)
We've never done this before.
The member with the highest score...
can choose between hints about the father and the stranger.
I have one.
Here's the question.
Guess the question...
after hearing the following choices with the correct answer.
Number one, Lee Kwang Soo.
Number two, Lee Min Ho.
Number three, Kim Soo Hyun.
- Number four, Yoo Jae Suk. - Really?
The answer is number one, Lee Kwang Soo.
Let me answer.
Which of the following...
is the stupidest?
(Which of the following looks the stupidest?)
There was Jae Suk too.
Jae Suk doesn't look stupid.
Wrong.
Let me answer.
Which of the following...
makes money by betraying others?
Why do you keep talking about money?
You've been talking about money all day.
- Let me answer. - This is driving me crazy.
Which of the following...
is scared of spending 50 cents?
When was I scared of spending 50 cents?
Lee Kwang Soo.
Correct.
The answer is Lee Kwang Soo. But I've never...
Let me give you a hint.
The question includes...
- the word, "success". - "Success"?
Let me answer.
Which of the following became successful by saving every penny?
What?
(The symbol of thrift)
(Hitting)
What? What's wrong?
That's right.
It's a good thing.
I spend quite a lot of money.
I know saving is a good thing,
but I spend a lot of money.
(A strong denial is an affirmation.)
Does it include "success"?
Let me answer.
Which celebrity do fans abroad think...
will become the most successful abroad?
All right.
- Was it even close? - It was 98 percent correct.
Maybe it's not "abroad".
Let me answer. Which celebrity do foreigners think...
will become successful in their country?
(Which celebrity do foreigners think...)
(will become successful in their country?)
Okay!
(Which celebrity will become successful in your country?)
(Kwang Soo in 1st place, Jae Suk in 2nd place)
Why is Kwang Soo at the top?
All right. Here's the next question.
Guess the question from the following choices and answer.
Number 1: Age 40.
Number 2: Age 60.
Number 3: Age 25.
Number 4: Age 35.
The answer is number 1, age 40.
"Age 40"?
Let me answer.!
Which age do you want to go back to?
The question is not about you.
(Suk Jin is 54.)
What?
Suk Jin.
- The survey... - Who would want to go back to 40?
The survey might have been among 60-year-olds.
Let me answer.
Which is the best age to get married?
(Wrong)
No. 40 is wrong. I did consider that though.
Here's a hint.
From which age can you "Blank"?
(From which age can you "Blank"?)
Let me answer!
From which age can you run for president?
(From which age can you run for president?)
- Really? - Really?
Can you run for president from the age of 40?
You can run for president from the age of 40.
- Did you know that? - Yes.
Hold on. I guess you planned to run for president.
(Candidate 0 from Running Party, Yoo Jae Suk)
- Hold on. - He must have looked into it.
- I support him! - That must be why he knows.
You should do it. I will support you.
Make me the Minister of Sports.
(Make me the Minister of Sports.)
I can do a good job.
I am sure he will do a good job.
He is perfect for the position.
The Minister of Sports!
All right. Here comes the next question.
Guess the question...
after hearing the following choices with the correct answer.
Number one, Jeon So Min.
Number two, Park Shin Hye.
Number three, Kim Tae Ri.
Number four, Jennie.
The answer is number four, Jennie.
Jennie? Not So Min?
(Surprised)
I am not even the answer!
- What is this? - So Min is one of the choices.
I am so confused since So Min is one of the choices.
- Jennie? - Let me answer.
Among the following, who do men want as a girlfriend?
(Could that be the question?)
(Among the following, who do men want as a girlfriend?)
- You are close. - What?
Let me answer!
(Let me answer!)
Who do men want to be asked out by on Valentine's Day?
(Who do men want to be asked out by on Valentine's Day?)
Valentine's Day?
(Number 1, Jennie)
I got it right!
- I see. - I got it right!
Why is So Min doing so well today?
- What is up with you? - Why are you playing so diligently?
- I mean... - She used to focus on being funny.
So Min is acting strange today.
You took on a role, didn't you?
- I really didn't. - So Min must have taken on a role.
I really didn't.
I am just lucky for some reason today.
Here comes the next question.
Guess the question...
after hearing the following choices with the correct answer.
Number one: Game console and audio equipment.
Number two: A selfie stick.
Number three: A self-defense gadget.
Number four: Instant food.
The answer is number one, Game console and audio equipment.
Let me answer.
What is needed the most in case of a war?
(What is needed the most in case of a war?)
And you think the answer is game console and audio equipment?
Gosh, do you even think before you open your mouth?
He has been strange since "Anus".
(Haha's answer is incorrect.)
Let me answer. What is needed the most for a trip?
(What is needed the most for a trip?)
(Could that be the answer?)
Jong Kook's answer was about 90 percent correct.
Let me answer!
(Let me answer!)
Let me answer. What is needed the most when you travel alone?
(If So Min's answer is correct, she will win with 2 points.)
What is needed the most when you travel alone?
My goodness.
- My goodness. - What is up with her?
What is going on?
She isn't usually like that.
- You... - I am not the stranger!
- I am not the stranger! - Hold on.
What are you doing?
- Hey. - Hey, Stranger.
Does the game end if we rip off the stranger's name tag?
We will rip it off.
- She is the stranger. - I am not!
I am not the stranger!
What do we do after we find the stranger?
I am not...
Are you the father or stranger?
I am 100 percent sure So Min isn't the father.
That's why she is desperate.
- This is driving me crazy. - She is the stranger.
- I am not... - She is determined...
to win.
So Min will receive a hint.
She will receive a hint.
(She can receive a hint on either the father or stranger.)
We need hints.
Whose hint do you want?
The father or stranger?
- The father. - The father.
It will make the matter clearer.
What should I do?
(What kind of a hint on the father will So Min receive?)
(The father uses his or her real name.)
(Combining the hint she received on the father...)
This is too vague.
(after the second mission...)
(The father candidates are 6 male members.)
(If you cross out Haha since he uses a stage name,)
(there are five father candidates.)
(The father would want to know the hint on his identity.)
"The father didn't like to move around."
(The father didn't like to move around.)
(Hint 3: The father didn't like to move around.)
(Hint 2: The father didn't like rabbits, foxes, and pheasants.)
(Hint 1: Ji Hyun, Kang Ho, Ha Neul, Gong Yoo know their father,)
(but Shin Min A, Yeo Jin Goo, and Jo In Sung don't.)
Let's move for the last race.
The hint doesn't make the matter any clearer, right?
It's really confusing.
- Is everyone here? - Yes.
Don't be nervous with your cover blown.
- Work hard. - I am not the stranger.
So Min, don't be nervous.
This is driving me crazy. I am not the stranger.
So Min.
I am not the stranger.
What are you doing?
Tell me when the race starts.
He is ready to get her.
All right. I will give you the rules.
The last mission that will reveal the father and stranger is...
Your Identity Race.
Walkie-talkies with hints on the father and stranger...
- are hidden in the building. - Okay.
You will get a hint of your choice on either...
the father or the stranger through the walkie-talkie.
I see.
If the father gets eliminated by the children,
the children will win...
and will divide the 6,000 dollars among themselves.
If the father gets eliminated by the stranger,
the stranger wins...
and gets 1,000 dollars for each child he or she eliminated.
The stranger needs to eliminate as many children as possible...
before eliminating the father to get a lot of money.
The stranger must eliminate the father...
to receive the money.
We should watch out for the stranger.
(We should watch out for the stranger.)
If both the stranger and father get eliminated...
- Kwang Soo, just let her be. - I am sorry.
- Why do you keep doing that? - I am sorry.
If both the stranger and father get eliminated by the same child,
that child becomes the sole winner and wins 6,000 dollars.
- It won't be easy. - I should aim to do that.
The father needs to find the right platform...
among the three platforms and enter his information...
in order to win.
If he becomes the winner, he receives 6,000 dollars.
The stranger and children need to rip off the father's name tag...
and put it on the right platform in order to win.
We need to find out who the father is.
If a child rips off another child's name tag,
both of them get eliminated.
If the father rips off the stranger's name tag,
he or she will receive a hint on his identity.
So it would be good for the father to rip off the stranger's name tag.
Go to your positions and we will start the race.
- Let's go. - I don't know how to approach this.
Where are you going to be?
- It's unclear. - For goodness' sake.
So Min, I will call you right away.
Why is So Min always suspicious?
This has to be a disease. It drives me crazy.
She is so suspicious.
Either So Min or Kwang Soo...
is the stranger.
Either Se Chan or So Min is the stranger.
(Kwang Soo's guess)
I have no clue who the father is.
Se Chan is suspicious. He played Woong's Father.
The father could be Haha,
Jae Suk, or Suk Jin.
I bet they picked someone young for the father.
(I bet they picked someone young for the father.)
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Start.
The race starts.
I will go here.
- Kwang Soo. - Hey.
Why are there two cameras on you?
I don't know.
- How am I supposed to know? - You make it so obvious.
How am I supposed to know?
Why are there two cameras on you?
- There must be something... - It's not a crime.
There is a rotating camera on you.
This hasn't happened in nine years.
(The rotating camera)
Okay.
Know that you are a stranger candidate.
It makes no sense that you have two cameras on you.
Don't you agree?
The walkie-talkies must be inside a box.
(Where are the walkie-talkies?)
(What?)
You should keep the door closed when the air conditioner is on.
(He saves energy.)
For goodness' sake. The air conditioner is on.
The air conditioner is on.
(Jong Kook is the best when it comes to saving energy.)
Why would you leave the door open?
This place is too big.
(Where are the walkie-talkies?)
(My goodness!)
(Hidden between the displays...)
(was a walkie-talkie box.)
No way.
I was only taking a peek.
(He is off to a good start.)
(He can receive a hint on the father or stranger.)
Should I receive a hint on the father or stranger?
(Whose hint should I receive?)
Give me a hint on the father.
The father has starred in a movie.
- What? - The father has starred in a movie.
That eliminates Yang Se Chan.
(The remaining father candidates...)
(are Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Suk Jin, and Kwang Soo.)
I will give you a hint on the father's identity.
The father's friends are...
Lee Sang Hwa, Lee Dong Hwi, and Lee Si Young.
(Why are these people father's friends?)
(Hint 4: The father's friends are Sang Hwa, Dong Hwi, and Si Young.)
This is so hard.
Haha, please give me a hint.
I will give you a big hint.
Write it down. I am giving you too big of a hint.
(What could it be?)
Lee Sang Hwa.
Lee Sang Hwa. The skater?
I don't know.
- Lee Sang Hwa? - Lee Dong Hwi.
Lee Sang Hwa.
Lee Si Young.
- What? - Lee Si Young.
(They are lost.)
What do these names mean?
- Are these names related to him? - Is that it?
The father's friends are...
Lee Sang Hwa, Lee Dong Hwi, and Lee Si Young.
The father's friends?
Hey, Kwang Soo and Dong Hwi...
are friends.
Si Young was in his team when she visited the show.
I think the father is Kwang Soo.
- How about the stranger? - Isn't the stranger...
So Min?
- The 2 of them placed 1st. - Is that your hunch?
- You don't even have a hint. - I know I don't, but...
I won't write it down.
(I won't write it down.)
A hunch doesn't mean much.
- Se Chan, you... - A hunch doesn't mean much.
When you watch this on TV, you will say after 30 minutes,
"Gosh, Suk Jin is so sharp."
I get that you are sharp, but I won't write it down.
- This is driving me crazy. - I will only write down the hint.
- Don't spread the hint. - I won't.
Okay. Let's keep this to ourselves.
Are there no walkie-talkies? There should be one here.
There should be one here.
(She searches the lecture hall.)
(She keeps her eyes open wide.)
(On top of the piano is...)
(a walkie-talkie box.)
I am torn. Whose hint should I ask for?
Let's figure out who the father is. That would be better.
Should I ask for a hint on the stranger?
No. I would like to hear a hint on the father.
The father has number four in his age.
(The hint eliminates Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and So Min.)
The father...
(The father candidates are Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and Suk Jin.)
This is a hint on the father's identity.
From 7:10pm to 7:45pm,
it was dark.
"From 7:10pm to 7:45pm, it was dark."
Kwang Soo isn't the father.
(Why was it dark during that time?)
The hints are...
(Jong Kook is a father candidate.)
(Where are the walkie-talkies?)
(What?)
(At a secluded place,)
(he finds a walkie-talkie box.)
The fact that a stranger is trying to steal my family's money...
makes me upset.
The stranger.
I will give you a hint on the stranger.
The stranger has number eight in his or her birthdate.
That eliminates Suk Jin and Jong Kook.
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook don't have the number 8 in their birthdate.)
I see. Okay.
That eliminates a lot of people.
Jong Kook, did you find a hint?
Yes, I did. I heard a lot.
- I should go that way. - What?
(He becomes intimidated...)
- What's wrong? - What?
(because Jong Kook is very confident.)
You aren't...
(He combines the hints.)
- I am not the father. - You aren't the father.
The fact they gave out hints which eliminate you...
from the father candidates early on...
- tells me you aren't the stranger. - That's right.
"That's right"?
I am not the stranger.
Since you aren't the father, you are useless today.
(Since you aren't the father, you are useless today.)
- Why would you say that? - It's true.
I guess you really aren't the father.
Ji Hyo isn't the father.
No, she isn't.
- So Min isn't the father either. - But...
(They guess who the father could be.)
(Ji Hyo, who isn't the father, appears.)
She is nothing today.
(Is Ji Hyo the stranger?)
I only have hints on the stranger.
That's what I am focused on.
The stranger has 'S'...
What? Does the stranger's name has 'S'?
What do you mean?
- The stranger's name must have S. - Share the hint with us.
The stranger's name must have an 'S'.
'S'...
(Should I share the hint?)
Is 'S' the stranger?
I heard this from So Min.
(I heard this from So Min.)
- So Min? You heard it from So Min? - She lied.
The stranger's name doesn't have an 'S'.
The stranger's name doesn't have 'S'?
- No, So Min came up with it. - It's like me saying,
"The stranger's height is less than 190cm."
It's like me saying that.
So Min must be the stranger.
She played you, you fool.
"The stranger's name doesn't have an 'S'..."
is So Min's blatant lie.
- That means she's the stranger. - Ji Hyo.
- It's proof. - I am glad you told us.
- Okay, okay. - So Min is the stranger.
Spread this information, Kwang Soo.
- Okay. - Spread this information.
(Is the hint Ji Hyo heard true or false?)
"It was dark."
(So Min is trying to figure out the hint on the father.)
Are you the stranger?
You are the stranger, right?
I am not. You want to rip off my name tag, right?
That's right.
All of my hints are on the father.
I have a lot of hints on the father.
The stranger is either you or Kwang Soo.
The stranger? I swear I am not the stranger.
I am leaving. I swear I am not the stranger.
Don't do that. I am not the stranger.
Don't you think it's Suk Jin?
There is no way his acting skills improved so much.
(Haha enters the lecture hall.)
This won't do.
(So Min follows quietly.)
(Ripping)
Gosh, I...
(Haha is out.)
Child Haha is out.
The stranger has gotten to work.
Gosh, Haha.
(Who eliminated Haha?)
Haha.
So Min has been acting strange.
She told Ji Hyo that the stranger's name...
doesn't contain an 'S'.
She must have come up with that hint to avoid suspicion.
Running Man never gives out such a hint from the start.
It's too decisive.
Gosh, I would have taken it at face value.
(Both of them have been on the show for 9 years,)
(but their thought process differs.)
Think about it, Jae Suk. It's strange.
- She is here. - Father.
(The strong stranger candidate, So Min appears.)
- Father. - Speak of the devil!
- What should we do? - She is so suspicious.
What should we do, Jae Suk?
Father Yoo and Father Kim. I swear I am not the stranger.
You think I am the stranger, right?
If you really aren't the stranger, answer one question.
When you shared a hint with Ji Hyo,
did you tell her that the stranger's name doesn't have an 'S'?
- In the stranger's last name. - What?
The stranger's last name doesn't have an 'S'.
Ji Hyo didn't say it was the last name.
She must have heard it wrong.
I told her it's the last name. I shared the hint...
because I wanted to find the father.
- Are you serious? - Yes! Rip off my name tag and see.
(That makes sense.)
Should I rip off my name tag?
Gosh, I am so annoyed. Should I rip off my name tag?
Should I rip off my name tag? I am not the stranger.
That's won't do a thing. Stop putting on a show.
Gosh, it drives me crazy to be falsely accused.
- My goodness. - I am so exhausted.
- I am so exhausted today. - There she goes again.
- She has fooled people this way. - That's right.
It's suspicious.
You know,
she once fooled everyone this way.
I am so exhausted.
I know it's wrong, but there are days...
when I don't try as hard. Today is simply an exception.
You dropped everything.
- Get your belongings. - Get your belongings. Stand up.
- I am exhausted. - Get your senses and belongings.
- I want to ride on someone's... - Get your belongings.
(She was so frustrated that her voice went hoarse.)
Go. We will let you go this once.
I don't know if you have this hint.
It's a hint on the father.
You know what it is, right?
It's a hint on the father. I am sure you know what it is.
(It's a drawing of a fox.)
(Jae Suk has reached his limits.)
Go.
- My goodness. - Just go.
- I am exhausted. - Go before I change my mind.
(Was So Min acting?)
There are no walkie-talkies.
(Kwang Soo is searching for walkie-talkies.)
(What is that?)
(Did Kwang Soo find a walkie-talkie box?)
Darn.
(Kwang Soo found...)
(a camera battery.)
(Frustrated)
It's a camera battery. I am sorry.
(It does look similar.)
(He resumes his search for walkie-talkie boxes.)
What? It's a platform.
(This is where the father must type in his identity.)
This is a platform.
(The father needs to find the right platform.)
Hold on. This is...
(Jae Suk found a platform as well.)
Gosh, I got goosebumps.
There is a flower on the screen.
(Forsythia, rose of Sharon, and cherry blossom)
- I will write it down. - Let's exchange the hints.
You and So Min aren't included.
- Of course not. - The two of you aren't the father.
That one is a good hint.
I haven't figured out that one yet.
Hey.
That hint exists.
That hint really exists. Right, Ji Hyo?
- Stop lying. This is a rabbit. - That hint really exists. Right?
That hint exists, right? That hint exists.
You will be surprised later.
I gave you the entire hint.
- What is this? - Are you saying it's Suk Jin?
It's a good hint.
Stop lying.
"The father has a big nose."
That's what I heard.
(Big nose versus Rabbit)
- What is this rabbit? - I didn't lie...
with this one. I gave you a hint.
"The father is a rabbit." That's a weird hint.
Both of you are weird.
- This can't be a hint. - Aren't you the stranger?
If the stranger gets a hint on the father...
We shouldn't focus on finding the father.
- We need to find the stranger. - We need to find the stranger.
(They have almost no hints on the stranger.)
- The stranger... - I will go after the father.
Why? Is that because you are the stranger?
- No! - You want to eliminate the father.
No.
Kwang Soo, go after the stranger. I'll trust you.
Bring me a hint about the stranger.
Why do they keep trying to find hints about the stranger?
Are they trying to take over everything?
(Who are Kwang Soo and So Min?)
I need to find a hint.
(Ji Hyo starts to look for hints.)
Someone found one here. Will there be another one?
(Someone follows Ji Hyo quietly.)
(Tearing)
Child, Song Ji Hyo is eliminated.
(Child, Song Ji Hyo is eliminated.)
See? I knew it.
Who is the stranger?
(Who eliminated Ji Hyo?)
The stranger is definitely So Min.
That's what I sense.
It's always...
Wait.
These are lockers.
(On top of lockers,)
(he finds a walkie-talkie box.)
I want to get a hint about the stranger.
The stranger is in his or her 30's.
(The stranger is in his or her 30's.)
(Stranger candidates are So Min, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan)
I think it's So Min.
(Jong Kook is convinced that So Min is the stranger.)
I must tear it off.
(Convinced Jong Kook heads to...)
So Min is over there.
(He finds So Min.)
I have to get rid of So Min.
Se Chan.
- What? - Where are you going?
What?
(So Min is more suspicious than anyone else.)
- You. - Yes?
(He heads straight to So Min.)
Why are you looking at me cautiously?
(So Min takes a sudden turn.)
You could be the stranger.
- Who? - Jong Kook.
Me?
(Jong Kook is excluded from stranger candidates.)
(Is she cornering Jong Kook as the stranger?)
So Min.
(Approaching)
(Are you the stranger who wants my family's money?)
To be honest.
Why are you saying that I could be the stranger?
What you said confirms it.
(If Jong Kook is the father and he eliminates the stranger,)
(he obtains a crucial hint about his own identity.)
(If Jong Kook and So Min are both children,)
(both will be eliminated.)
- Wait. - No, I'm not.
(So Min was not the stranger.)
(Jong Kook eliminated So Min who was a child.)
(If Jong Kook is also a child...)
- You are not? - I am not.
Really?
I'm not the stranger.
Child, Jong Kook tore off...
Child, So Min's name tag.
Both of you are eliminated.
We're siblings.
(Jong Kook was also a child.)
Jong Kook.
- Why did you give me that hint? - What hint?
Since Ji Hyo isn't the stranger,
we wanted to find the father together.
Why did you talk about the letter 'S' then?
I received that hint.
- Is there no 'S' in the last name? - There's no S in the last name.
I'd like a hint about the stranger.
There is no 'S' in the stranger's last name.
(It's the hint that So Min gets.)
Ji Hyo.
I found out that you're not the stranger.
Let's share our hints about the father.
I'll tell you mine.
There's no 'S'...
in the stranger's last name.
- In the last name? - There's no 'S'.
Why did Ji Hyo tell me...
that there's an 'S' in the first name.
Ji Hyo is forgetful.
(Is someone talking about me?)
Child Jong Kook and Child So Min are...
eliminated.
So Min wasn't it.
Four children have been eliminated.
Only two remain.
Who is it then?
Who is the father?
Is it Jae Suk?
Who's Jae Suk? What about Kwang Soo?
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, and you.
- You aren't it, are you? - I'm neither father nor stranger.
Where's Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo,
you, and me. Are there four of us left?
- Jae Suk. - Jae Suk?
(Someone is acting.)
Wait.
Kwang Soo is the stranger.
It is Kwang Soo.
It's not Se Chan.
(Father candidates are Suk Jin and Jae Suk.)
There are two children left.
(Stranger candidates are Kwang Soo and Se Chan.)
I have no idea.
What's going on?
(Who are the father and the stranger?)
(Jae Suk is looking for hints.)
(He finds a walkie-talkie box.)
Let's see.
There it is.
(Suk Jin finds something under in the stairs.)
(He also finds a walkie-talkie box.)
Okay.
I'll ask over there.
Give me a hint about the father.
(Both ask if they're the father.)
Here's a hint about the father.
Father liked the spring, stars,
and green grapes.
He liked the spring, stars, and green grapes.
"Jun Ji Hyun, Song Kang Ho, Kang Ha Neul, Gong Yoo know the father."
"but Shin Min A, Yeo Jin Goo, and Zo In Sung don't."
"The father didn't like rabbits, foxes, and pheasants."
(The father didn't like rabbits, foxes, and pheasants.)
(What does it mean?)
(The father didn't like to move around.)
The father's friends are Lee Sang Hwa,
Lee Dong Hwi, and Lee Si Young.
From 7:10pm...
to 7:45pm, it was dark.
(Hints about the father)
(Who is the father that these hints are pointing to?)
What could it be?
(He tries to figure out the father.)
What does it mean?
(Father candidates can't understand.)
"The father didn't like rabbits, foxes, and pheasants."
"Green grapes, stars,"
and the spring" sound like...
a poem.
(Green grapes, spring, and stars)
I saw them in a textbook.
It reminded me of that.
(Words that he might have seen in a textbook)
Isn't there a movie about a poet?
(Isn't there a movie about a poet?)
It's Dong Ju's friend.
(Kang Ha Neul played the main character in "Dong Ju".)
Lee Si Young.
(Father's friends are Lee Sang Hwa, Lee Dong Hwi, and Lee Si Young.)
These three are famous activists in the Korean independence movement.
The afternoon.
7pm is 19.
It's from 1910 to 1945.
Japanese occupation.
(Japanese occupation)
I think...
these are independence movement activists.
It's related to Yoon Dong Ju.
Independence movement activist.
(Is the father an independence movement activist?)
(The hints meant independence movement activist.)
We got it all. It's an independence movement activist.
It was over there.
(He must enter his identity in the right platform...)
(to win.)
(At a place where a platform is hidden,)
(Suk Jin enters.)
There's a platform.
I'll type in independence movement activist.
(He enters "independence movement activist".)
Independence...
movement activist.
(The platform doesn't open.)
Is it wrong?
(Only the father can enter the right answer.)
(Either it's not the right platform,)
(or Suk Jin isn't the father.)
(Jae Suk arrives at the same platform.)
Forsythia.
Wait, it was over here.
Gosh.
I'm getting goosebumps. Wait.
It has five syllables.
(He enters the father's identity in the platform.)
(It isn't working.)
(One of them is the father.)
(The other is a very curious child.)
(Who is the real father?)
(At that time)
(Kwang Soo finds Jae Suk.)
What is Jae Suk doing?
(This is the wrong platform.)
I don't understand.
(Why is Jae Suk over there?)
Only the father uses the platform.
(If Jae Suk is by the platform...)
Jae Suk is the father.
(Is Jae Suk the father?)
I knew it.
(Kwang Soo runs into Se Chan.)
Who are you, Kwang Soo?
Only two of us are left.
You still have two cameras.
(You still have two cameras.)
- How many do you have? - I have two.
(It's suspicious.)
Do you want to sit there?
Why are you so nervous?
Are you okay?
(Kwang Soo seems quite nervous.)
Why did you write?
Aren't you being awkward?
Go over there and read what's written.
(They keep a distance from one another.)
(One of them is the stranger.)
It's Jae Suk.
What are you doing?
- I was talking with Kwang Soo. - About what?
Interestingly enough, one of us is...
either the father or the stranger.
- It's very funny. - Right.
Interestingly enough, both of you came to where I am.
(They keep a distance.)
One right after another.
What's going on?
Which one of you is the stranger?
I know who the father is.
- I... - You know who the father is?
- Yes. - I think I know too.
- Do you know? - Yes.
He's similar to you.
- Is it me? - I think it's you.
(Is Jae Suk the father as Kwang Soo and Se Chan think?)
(Or is Suk Jin the father?)
(What are their identities?)
This is what I think.
I'll be honest.
Shall I stay away from you?
(What is he going to say?)
I'll take everything.
(If a child eliminates the stranger and the father,)
(he gets 6,000 dollars.)
You brat.
This is just...
(Is Kwang Soo a child?)
Goodness.
(Is he a child? Or is he acting?)
Hey.
(At that moment)
- I'm not it. - Kwang Soo.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
Who is the stranger?
(Who is the stranger?)
- Wait. - Who's the stranger?
It's him.
- Tear off Kwang Soo's. - I'm not it.
Who's the stranger?
- Kwang Soo. - Stay still.
- It's Kwang Soo. - Stay still.
- Who is it? Who's the stranger? - It's Kwang Soo.
(Is Kwang Soo the stranger?)
(Or is Se Chan the stranger?)
- Who is it? - It's Kwang Soo.
- I'm not it. - Who's the stranger, Kwang Soo?
Let's say it at the same time.
- Wait, who's the stranger? - It's Kwang Soo.
- It's him. - Who is it?
- It'll be over! - Who is it?
- You're going to end it. - Who is it?
- It's Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- Who's the stranger? - Kwang Soo is it.
- It's Se Chan. - Who is it?
- It's definitely Kwang Soo. - Wait.
- It's Se Chan. - Wait, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, tear of Se Chan's.
- Who? - Kwang Soo.
If you're not the stranger,
I'll tear off Kwang Soo's.
- Do you understand? - Yes.
- Then the child will stay alive. - Okay.
Okay? Wait.
Wait a minute.
- Kwang Soo. - Wait.
Jae Suk.
- If I'm the child, - It's okay.
- I'll stay alive. - Right.
- Do you understand? - Yes.
Tear it off.
- Tear it off. - Kwang Soo.
Tear it off. A child has to be sacrificed.
No.
(Se Chan refuses.)
- Wait. - Who is it?
(Who is Se Chan?)
- "Stranger". - Stranger?
Goodness.
(Se Chan is the stranger.)
(Stranger)
How could this be?
- Jae Suk. - It was my chance.
(I worked hard for this chance.)
(Before the shoot)
It's been a long time.
It's been almost two years.
(He still remembers his failure.)
You seem nervous already.
I'm so sleepy. I couldn't sleep last night.
I hope that it's something easy.
Se Chan, you're a stranger who's after a family's emergency fund...
of 6,000 dollars.
- I'm after it? - Yes.
(Stranger Yang Se Chan)
Father is...
(He searches for hints about the father.)
I should eliminate Ji Hyo.
What? Wait.
I need that.
(He had to eliminate as many children as possible.)
(He went after the children to win a bigger prize.)
Se Chan is the stranger.
(Ji Hyo who was definitely a child is eliminated.)
I knew that you were the stranger from the beginning.
(He figures things out quietly by himself.)
(He also eliminates Haha.)
Goodness.
I just checked this.
Get out quietly now.
Haha was so easy.
(He eliminated children while hiding his identity.)
Stranger Se Chan is eliminated.
Jae Suk.
Wait.
That means you'll take everything.
No, Jae Suk.
- So? - Wait.
I'm your sibling.
- Wait a minute. - I'm your sibling.
Se Chan is the stranger.
- I won't take all the money. - Hey.
(Kwang Soo goes after Jae Suk's name tag.)
(Jae Suk stands at the platform to find out the father's identity.)
(Is Jae Suk the father?)
What is Jae Suk doing?
- I won't take all the money. - Hey.
If a child eliminates the stranger and the father,
he gets 6,000 dollars all to himself.
Wait, your hand.
(If Jae Suk is the father, Kwang Soo can take all the money.)
Hurry.
(If Suk Jin is the father, Jae Suk and Kwang Soo are both out.)
Your hand.
(Tearing)
(The name tag is off.)
(Who is Jae Suk?)
We're eliminated.
Both of you are eliminated.
Why did you tear off my name tag?
(As they're both children, they're both eliminated.)
What's wrong with you?
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Aren't you the father?
Suk Jin is the father.
Both children are eliminated.
Why you...
(What are you talking about?)
Suk Jin, you're a secret agent who lost his memory.
You're a father of six children.
(Father Ji Suk Jin)
If I get caught early, is it okay that the shoot ends early?
The staff decided to risk it.
(Such honesty makes him laugh.)
- I'll show you. - Okay.
Please look forward to my amazing performance.
The stranger and remaining children are eliminated.
Therefore Suk Jin wins.
(He won without doing anything.)
I can't believe that I won this way.
(He won without doing much.)
I didn't want to win without accomplishing anything.
Okay, let's go.
(Suk Jin's one-man show that started with regrets)
(Suk Jin arrives at the platform.)
I hope this is correct.
"Independence". Is this correct?
"Movement activist."
Is it correct?
(You won! Watch the video with the other members.)
(Wow.)
(Yes.)
This is amazing.
Was it right?
(He performs with enthusiasm.)
Thank you. I was an independence movement activist.
Long live Korean independence.
(Long live Korean independence. The end of his one-man show)
The winner of the Missing Emergency Fund Race is...
the father, Suk Jin.
(The final winner is Suk Jin.)
Good job. Due to Kwang Soo, we were eliminated.
I thought it was definitely Jae Suk.
- I thought he was the father. - You got greedy.
You must be curious about...
who the father is.
- Let's watch the video together. - Okay.
(I did not...)
(know...)
(who my father was.)
(Father hid money under the bed.)
(However he was miserly and made his children work.)
The father hid money.
(Until I was 12 years old,)
(I never saw my father's face properly.)
(Due to our father's absence, we didn't have food to eat.)
(We ate vegetables from restaurants' trash to keep from hunger.)
(Due to our father, we had a very difficult life.)
(Then we found out after our father died.)
(Our father was...)
(an activist in the Korean independence movement.)
See? I knew it.
(To protect his beloved family, he hid his identity.)
I got goosebumps right now.
(Money that our father collected under the bed was...)
(the independence fund to deliver to the provisional government.)
(We couldn't see our father often...)
(because he was busy with independence movements abroad.)
(We were always hungry...)
(because our land and house were sold to fund the movement.)
(Our father loved us more than anyone.)
(He was a proud activist in the Korean independence movement.)
It's moving.
(Father was an activist in the Korean independence movement.)
Our independence fund was...
The 6,000 dollars was for the independence movement.
The 6,000 dollars represented...
the funds from Lee Hoe Yeong who founded Shinheung Military Academy.
He gave everything he had for the independence movement.
I feel so bad.
I spoke nonsense during the opening of the show.
Family members of independence movement activists...
resented their fathers very much before finding out...
- who their fathers were. - Right.
They misunderstood when...
their fathers took money from the family.
Today's real theme is the secret of the father.
Father's identity is an independence movement activist.
It warms my heart.
I got tears in my eyes as I was watching it.
The father's letter you read that sounded cold reflected...
how they had to keep their identities secret...
to protect their families.
Right.
They were cold to their families in reality.
- They had to keep their secret. - Yes.
To prevent information from leaking.
(Yoon Bong Gil's letter to his two sons,)
(Yoon Jong and Yoon Dam)
(Did you say that you were jealous of Doo Soon for having a father?)
I'll explain the three dishes you had for lunch.
The braised kimchi was made by Kim Gu's mother,
Kwak Nak Won.
She picked cabbage leaves that were thrown away on the ground...
and made this dish for independence activists.
Pyeongyang naengmyeon was Kim Gu's favorite dish.
Seafood stew is what Seo Young Hae ate in France...
while he fought abroad for Korean independence.
I see. I had no idea.
"Jun Ji Hyun, Song Kang Ho, Kang Ha Neul, Gong Yoo know the father,"
"but Shin Min A, Yeo Jin Goo, and Zo In Sung don't."
These are the actors in movies such as "Assassinations"...
and "The Age of Shadows"...
that relate to the independence movement.
The hint that said "Father didn't like rabbits, foxes, and pheasants."
That was jargon used by independence movement activists.
So rabbits meant Japanese police,
foxes meant Japanese secret agents,
and pheasants meant Japanese collaborators.
- What about the moving around hint? - I know.
"Moving around" is a Japanese expression.
"Going back and forth" is a Korean expression.
The other expression is from Japanese.
The stranger's identity had many meanings.
It could have been a Japanese soldier,
a Japanese collaborator,
or someone who ignored the independence movement.
- An informant. - It could also represent us...
who are indifferent.
Why did you pick me...
to represent a Japanese collaborator or an informant.
To represent a Japanese collaborator or an informant.
I'll eliminate you.
Was it me?
Fine, I'll accept it.
I was the best choice.
The 6,000 dollars that Suk Jin won...
will be donated to Korean independence organization...
and will cover for any penalties incurred today.
That's amazing, Suk Jin.
- Give it with joy. - I'll feel better this way.
- Seriously. - Of course.
- It's the right thing to do. - You're amazing.
We learned a lot today.
- Yes. - It's history that...
we should not forget.
We can live on this land today.
I say this all the time.
They protected us with their blood and tears.
As there were many independence movement activists,
we could live in this country today.
We thank them again wholeheartedly.
- Thank you. - We won't forget you.
Thank you.
(Members are involved in a dangerous competition.)
(Whatever they choose, it's for the final victory.)
(They have only one chance to bet.)
(To members who can't make a daring bet)
(The real ones appeared.)
(They came to put an end to this round.)
(Difficult opponents are here.)
(It's hard to know their strategy.)
(They're tricksters.)
(A competition with the real ones)
(Who will be the final winner?)
(Deity of Games: Don't Trust Anyone)