(Last week)
(Grand New Year Project, the Level Up Race)
(When a member reaches Level 10, it's a win, and the project ends.)
(To reach the highest level,)
(the cutthroat race has begun.)
(When it comes to leveling up, there are no foes or colleagues.)
(The disloyal members chose betrayal and leveled up.)
(The disparity between the levels is increasing.)
(What is at the end of this race?)
(At a cafe in Ilsan, Gyeonggi Province)
- Hello. - Hey, there.
Hello.
- You're wearing playful glasses. - Hi.
- How playful will you be today? - Hey.
Gosh, he's wearing playful glasses.
Jae Seok wears that pair when he's in the best mood.
- I wonder how playful he'll be. - Those playful glasses.
(Turning into a mischievous guy)
Yu Jun Sang.
(Look at his outfit. It's Jun Sang's outfit from "Winter Sonata".)
From "Winter Sonata". Yu Jun Sang.
(He looks older than Jun Sang.)
(We apologize to Bae Yong Joon.)
- It's from "Winter Sonata". - Why are you laughing?
- Laugh when you can relate. - Hey.
- I knew the outfit looked familiar. - That's so funny.
- The outfit does look similar. - You're Mr. Big Nose.
Today, it'll be Part Three of the Level Up Race.
It's Level Fabrication Incident.
(Level Fabrication Incident)
- What's this now? - Level Fabrication Incident?
(The levels were fabricated?)
(Before the filming, they took their level badges.)
(Among these, some levels were fabricated?)
(What on earth is happening?)
- Did someone steal it? - The levels were fabricated?
Three of your level badges...
had been stolen and fabricated then.
- They were fabricated? - Did someone steal them?
(Then the culprit is...)
Gosh, come on.
(Without asking any questions, he goes to Kwang Soo.)
I'm sick of this. It wasn't me!
- Because of Jae Seok... - Jae Seok could be the culprit.
Yes, he might be the culprit on the contrary.
- Two members stole the levels. - Really?
And there is one more forger who helped the thieves fabricate.
I'll present five suspects including the forger.
What?
(5 suspects including the forger are revealed.)
There are five suspects?
Five suspects including the forger?
- There are five? - What?
(Someone among these 5 guests is a forger.)
(Who is it?)
- It's Lee Dong Hwi. - Hey, Lee Dong Hwi.
- Hello. - My gosh.
(5 guests with an unusual presence)
(5 suspects for forging the levels: Gong Myoung, Jin Sun Kyu,)
(Lee Ha Nee, Lee Dong Hwi and Ryu Seung Ryong)
My gosh, Ha Nee.
(Is this really happening? It's the best list of suspects.)
- My goodness. - Hello.
- Hey, Seung Ryong. - The whole cast rarely comes.
My gosh, Seung Ryong. Usually, only 2 or 3 guests join us.
All five of them are joining us today.
(They came to rule the variety show as well as the movie industry.)
If I'm not mistaken, all of these guests have...
- never starred on our show before. - Is this your first time?
- It's everyone's first time? - Yes.
- Yes, it's my 1st time. - Ha Nee, this is your 1st time...
- as well. - It's my first time.
As for Seung Ryong, isn't this...
- your first variety show? - Right.
- Yes, it's my 1st time. - Isn't this your 1st variety show?
- The 1st variety show? - The 1st variety show?
- It's an honor. - Seriously?
I'd like to ask you to introduce yourselves one at a time.
I was really surprised to see him here.
Well, okay. I'm Ryu Seung Ryong.
Gosh, I'm a big fan.
(As for this suspect,)
(he's the best actor who can pull off any role or any genre.)
(He reached the highest level in the movie industry.)
(Ryu Seung Ryong, a mega-hit actor with 1,000 faces)
(Feeling awkward)
(A diehard fan intrudes.)
Hey.
Hey, you're not supposed to make these stars uncomfortable.
Tell you what. You are all my close colleagues.
If you make them uncomfortable, I won't let that slide.
- I'm a fan. - Anyway,
I consider him as almost my real brother.
- How many brothers do you have? - That's enough.
(How many brothers do you have?)
- He's your brother? - He has a lot of brothers.
- He's like my cousin. - You always change the family tree.
It's your first official appearance on a variety show after your debut.
- Officially, it is. - Yes.
Were you nervous yesterday?
- Gosh, I didn't get any sleep. - Really?
I have two sons, and this has been their wish too.
He's been talking about our show for a long time now.
- How old is your eldest son? - He'll be in eighth grade now.
To them, we are like their heroes.
(Brimming with confidence for no reason)
- Stop it. What's wrong with you? - Gosh, Seok Jin.
- You're embarrassing me. - Stop it.
- Hello. Hi. Nice to meet you. - What's gotten into him?
- Come on. Exactly. - You're no hero to them.
- I'm sorry. - Seriously.
By the way, we came across an unexpected nickname.
Your nickname in your 20s was Psycho.
(His nickname in his 20s was Psycho.)
(His nickname was Psycho?)
- Why is that? - Do you remember this?
I wanted to be different.
- Like the off-the-wall type? - Yes, off-the-wall.
- I had a lot of stuff inside. - You couldn't express it.
- I couldn't express it. - I see.
That's why I used to carry around a big box of matches.
- Yes, there was this huge box. - I see. That box?
- It was huge. Restaurants had them. - I see. That?
- I know what it is. - I carried an alarm clock too.
I showed that to people when they asked for time.
- So he didn't wear watches. - He carried around a big clock.
- Your daily life was like a skit. - He had an alarm clock.
You had long hair because of the nanta show.
- His hair was this long. - Up to his shoulders?
- It came up to your shoulders? - My hair used to be long.
But considering everything, isn't he a real psycho?
(Isn't he a real psycho then?)
- That's true. - I meant the nickname.
- I was talking about his nickname. - That's right.
All right. When you star on a variety show,
we ask the guests to show a few impressions time to time.
- It's hard to do that suddenly. - That's right.
I know that he doesn't do them, but I'd like to ask him this.
Can you do the line from "Miracle in Cell No. 7",
"Ye Seung, eat your beans"?
- I really want to see that. - Can you just do this one?
- "Eat your beans"? - Yes.
- "Ye Seung, eat your beans." - Only this line.
(It was during a scene when he was feeding his daughter beans.)
(Ye Seung, you must eat your beans. Eat your beans.)
(He'll do that famous line...)
I really want to see it in person. I really want to.
- I'm getting excited. - Gosh, I'll see that in person?
I really want to see that.
(What will the famous line sound like after 6 years?)
Ye Seung, you must eat your beans. Eat your beans.
(Ye Seung, you must eat your beans. Eat your beans.)
(Laughing)
Say, "Sailor Moon", please.
- Sailor Moon. - "Sailor Moon".
Sailor Moon.
(Poor Seung Ryong)
- Sailor Moon. - He looks shy.
(Chocking suddenly)
- Ye Seung. - Right. Seung Ryong...
- Seung Ryong feels very shy. - Yes, I am.
- I see. - Right.
- I could feel it with his hands. - I really like that.
- "Stop it." - "Stop it."
- "That's enough." - "Stop it."
- "Gosh, stop it." - Oh, my. I'm all red in the face.
- All right. - He's charming.
My goodness. Next, we have Lee Dong Hwi.
(Second suspect: Lee Dong Hwi)
(A hot rookie the public loved with his performance of a retro role)
(He's a fine supporting character as well as an impressive main lead.)
(He has a broad spectrum when it comes to his acting.)
(A new rising star of supporting characters, Lee Dong Hwi)
- It's Lee Dong Hwi. - Gosh.
He's so fair-skinned. Seriously.
When he first walked in, I thought...
- Tak Jae Hoon was walking in. - Seriously.
When he first walked in, I thought Tak Jae Hoon was walking in.
Seriously. They resemble each other so much.
You look just like him.
(He's the younger version of Jae Hoon.)
I thought he was Jae Hoon.
- Seriously. - I thought he was here.
- He's the same age as Kwang Soo. - That's right.
- Were you two friends? - We are close.
- You two are friends. - Yes.
- They were in "Entourage". - That's right.
I met Seok Jin when I was filming the drama.
- When? - Yes, that's right.
- I was a cameo for the drama. - Cameo.
- We ran into each other. - That's right.
- I really wanted to tell him this. - We ran into each other...
I told Kwang Soo this several times.
Out of all the celebrities that I've seen in my life,
he was the most fascinating, and I was the most nervous.
(He was the most fascinating, and I was the most nervous.)
That's true. He did mention that a lot.
You are indeed my role model.
I know why Dong Hwi feels this way.
He's too arrogant compared to his popularity.
(He's too arrogant compared to his popularity.)
Compared to his popularity...
That is probably why...
- he left an impression on Dong Hwi. - Probably.
This is why our meeting was so fascinating.
Usually, people are different...
- on TV and in person, - That's right.
but he said hello how he would say hi on TV.
"Hey, nice to meet you. My gosh."
"I see."
He kept the same tone.
- That arrogant tone of his? - No, I wouldn't say arrogant.
- I'm the same on and off camera. - "I see. Nice to meet you."
We had a short interview with Dong Hwi.
Let me introduce Ha Nee now.
(It's time to interrogate the third suspect.)
- The third suspect! - Lee Ha Nee.
- Lee Ha Nee! - Lee Ha Nee!
(Hey. Hello, everyone. Do you know who I am?)
(Nothing is impossible for this lady who seems to be too perfect.)
(She excels in acting and hosting shows. What is her limit?)
(The perfect role model, Lee Ha Nee)
- Lee Ha Nee! - Lee Ha Nee!
(Praise Ha Nee!)
(The third interrogation begins with a vigorous cheer.)
Gosh, seriously.
She's so pretty.
- You are so beautiful. - You are Se Chan's ideal type.
- She's totally my type. I'm a fan. - She's so pretty.
Seriously. Se Chan mentioned you...
- a lot for his ideal type. - I always said it was you.
- Right. - I'm such a big fan.
Se Chan, since when have you been her fan?
When did it start?
- I saw "Tazza-the Hidden Card". - "Tazza-the Hidden Card".
But she is such a great actress.
But when you do a scene from the movie series,
- you do Kim Hye Soo's impression. - That's true.
That's just for my impression.
Her lines are a bit too explicit.
- It's inappropriate to do it on TV. - Is that so?
- Yes. - Is that so?
Can you do just one line?
"Gosh, you witch." This one.
(Copying Ha Nee)
She did such a great job with this line.
- That was done perfectly. - I know which one.
- That's right. It was really good. - When I heard that...
- Yes, that's right. - The thing is that...
Hearing such an unexpected line...
- with her innocent face... - That's right.
captivated me.
That's how well she delivered the line.
All right.
I asked him to do a few lines earlier.
- Me? - Could you...
- I'll do a different one. - Sure, sure.
Do a different line, please.
How old are you?
Yes, that one.
(Exuding a scary presence)
(Reenacting the scene perfectly)
"How old are you?"
That's the one.
- Yes, that line. - She said that to Shin Sae Kyeong.
Of course. Next up is...
- I almost didn't recognize him. - Same here.
- He grew out his hair so much. - Right.
- It's Jin Sun Kyu. - Yes, my hair did get very long.
Right.
(He captured the audience's eyes whenever he was in the scenes.)
(He became popular rather late after the role of his lifetime.)
(In real life, he cries a lot.)
(Please don't get the wrong idea.)
(He seems ruthless when he acts, but he's very soft-hearted.)
(The actor with the finest acting, Jin Sun Kyu)
Now, I feel a bit awkward with long hair.
Really?
- Yes. - He looks great with long hair.
It looks like a wig.
(He can't lie.)
(He sounds firm.)
(Really?)
That's what I thought as well this morning.
(He's so innocent.)
- We tease him too much. - Why do you do that?
We just want to.
Is he really responsive?
- Yes. - I see.
I beat him up a lot in the movie too.
- Is that so? - Yes.
It's weird, you know.
She's just scary.
(Ha Nee is just scary.)
- She's scary. - When I raise my hand, he gets...
- He's startled? - Yes.
He was startled just now too.
- Even just now... - I see.
You were scared just now too.
Yes, Ha Nee is younger than I am,
- but she feels older than I am. - I see.
- Some people are like that. - Right.
Actually, Seok Jin is the oldest among us,
but Jong Kook acts like the oldest among us.
(Jong Kook acts like the oldest.)
- He's the boss in this industry. - He's...
He's the boss in this industry.
We don't care about the age. That doesn't matter here.
I call him during the national holidays to give him my regards.
I check the time too...
- to see when he'd call. - Right.
You check the time?
(He's scarier than Ha Nee.)
(After the innocent-looking suspect number four...)
Next, we have...
Gong Myoung.
(The last suspect, Gong Myoung)
- He's so handsome. - Right.
(He won over the viewers with his big-puppy-like charms.)
(Hobby: Exuding cute charms, Special Skill: Winning over ladies)
(He can be a straightforward man and a lovely younger guy.)
(A perfect actor and TV personality, there's no one like him.)
- He has such a great proportion. - His body proportion is different.
Yes, he is indeed handsome.
Gosh, the coat...
If you want to be tall, you should have his proportion.
(Flinching)
- The moment you said it... - Hey, what's wrong with you?
- Hey, you're embarrassing us. - You don't usually wear coats.
That's it. That's how it should be.
- This is your 1st time on our show. - Yes, it is.
What are you anticipating and what are you worried about?
Well, as for me,
This... I mean...
- I was excited to see you all. - That's right.
- It was the same for all of us. - Especially, which member?
(Which member did he want to meet the most?)
For me, it was you.
No, not him. Don't include him.
- Why not? - Why wouldn't he?
Everyone would choose him. Let's not include him.
- Why would we not include him? - He's...
- Please exclude me. - Pick one excluding Jae Seok.
He has high expectations because Dong Hwi said he liked him.
Okay. Which member then?
(Well, if I were to choose again...)
(Glancing)
(Could that be me?)
I've never met...
(Gong Myoung has never met...)
- Mr. Jee Seok Jin. - Seok Jin?
It's my first time meeting everyone here, but...
(She feels defeated for some reason.)
- You were curious about him. - You've never met him before.
- It's my first time meeting him. - You've never met him?
No, never.
You've never seen him on TV?
Yes. No, no.
(I've never seen him on TV.)
(No, no.)
This is his first time seeing Seok Jin.
I've been on TV for 20 years. You think that's possible?
- That's possible. - You know?
- He might not have seen you. - This is almost...
- I've never met him either. - Who?
Mr. Gong Myoung.
- I've never seen him. - It's my first time seeing her.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- Go get him. - He forgot about me.
- No, that's not what I'm doing. - Okay.
- These days, So Min is... - She's getting started.
- following Kwang Soo's footstep. - Right.
- She's the romantic. - Yes, a bit.
- The female version of a romantic. - She's the romantic?
- She's the first female. - It will continue on.
We're telling you in advance,
- so you're not flustered. - Okay, okay.
You've seen So Min, right?
- Yes, of course. - You've seen her on TV.
How was it?
She's much cuter in person.
Thank you.
She started. She's getting her move on.
She's getting started.
- What's wrong with you? Stop. - Gosh, So Min.
- This signals that she started. - She pushes back her hair.
- She applies ointment on here... - Because she scratches.
because she does that all the time.
All right then.
Since we're on the subject, use his name...
- to come up with an acrostic poem. - Yes, you must go for it.
- With his name. - Take it seriously.
- This is too hard. - Okay.
Should I start with the first syllable?
Gong Myoung is talking.
(Gong Myoung is talking.)
The second syllable.
(What did I say?)
(Barking)
(Myoung, Myoung, Myoung!)
- That was cute. - That was cute.
- Well done. - Great job.
She did well.
- That was great. - You're good.
All right. I'll tell you the rules now.
Today is the third episode of the Level Up Race.
It's the Level Fabrication Incident.
Out of these 5 suspects, 1 of them...
is a real forger who is helping the thieves.
And one of the suspects is a police officer on his or her stakeout...
- to catch the thieves. - Is it a detective?
- I see. Out of these 5 suspects? - Just 1?
- 1 is a police officer. - 1 is a forger.
(A forger and a police officer are among them.)
Before the race ends,
if the civilians find and eliminate thieves and forger,
it's Team Civilian and Police's victory.
If the thieves and the forger conceal their identities to the end,
and eliminate the police and members whose levels were stolen,
It's Team Thieves and Forger's victory.
Gosh, my head hurts now.
As for the members, you will earn the levels of the thieves...
- whom you eliminate. - I see. This?
Something was fabricated here?
(They set out for the first mission to find the clues.)
The first quest will begin.
(A quest has been discovered.)
The first mission is...
- Suspect's Preference. - Preference?
Preference.
To answer yes-or-no questions,
you will choose either O or X.
After presenting the first argument,
you can share your opinions with each other.
You will decide for the second time.
Depending on the result, the majority will earn one point,
and the minority will face a penalty with the toy hammer.
This game is about being the majority.
However, if there is a unanimous decision,
the person next to you will execute the toy hammer penalty.
We can't have a unanimous decision.
(Let's avoid being the minority and the unanimous decision.)
The one who wins the mission...
will be given a hint of his or her choice.
(The winner can get a hint about the thieves or the police.)
Here's the first question.
(A war of wits to avoid getting a unanimous decision)
Here it goes.
The leader of a team...
must pay for the first round of the gathering and head home.
If you agree, choose O. If you disagree, choose X.
Did you come up with it because of Jae Seok?
Probably.
This is your first decision.
1, 2, 3.
(7 members become the majority, and 6, the minority.)
- Well, as for this... - He should go home.
- You chose X, right? - It should be X.
He should leave at the right timing.
- That's the mature thing to do. - Honestly speaking,
with the leader there, the others can't talk freely.
- Leaders are meant to be lonely. - Right.
Director Kang Woo Seok is like that.
During team dinners, after giving a toast a few times,
he disappears quietly.
Then the real party starts.
Only then.
Exactly.
Team dinners are different from other events.
Ha Nee, you chose O too?
- Yes. - Why?
Knowing when to leave...
is a virtue of good leaders.
That makes sense.
- It's X. - The leader should be responsible.
- He should take care of the team. - To the end.
He should pay for the second round too.
I think the leader should stay for the second round.
- Stay for the 2nd round. - Stay for the 2nd round.
- He should pay. - Of course.
Seok Jin, what did you choose?
- I chose O. - Why?
The leader should leave at the right time.
- And why didn't you? - What do you mean?
(You're the oldest. Why didn't you leave?)
After the Entertainment Awards, Jae Seok left first.
Seok Jin stayed, obliviously.
Why did you stay?
The conversation was so lively.
(It was so fun talking to the younger guys.)
They all listened carefully to what I said.
(I enjoyed having everyone listen to me a bit too much.)
- I couldn't bring myself to leave. - That's why.
Still, your opinion is this.
Once, we had a year-end party.
After we had dinner together,
Jong Kook and I wanted to have a drink somewhere alone.
But Ji Hyo kept following us.
(We wanted to be alone.)
- It was a very awkward moment. - In the end,
we had to go to my place.
And Ji Hyo had her manager tail us.
(Ji Hyo had her manager tail them.)
(Follow them.)
She followed us to my place.
I was there too.
(Why leave me out?)
(Seok Jin was there?)
- I didn't know. - I thought we were alone.
- I was there too. - That's right.
I can't believe you.
- Know when to leave. - Know when to leave.
Kwang Soo, why did you choose X?
I have a different opinion.
I want the leader to hand over his or her credit card and leave.
- And not come to the dinner at all? - No.
- Not even to the dinner. - Seok Jin is my leader forever.
Seok Jin is my leader forever.
(Remember the leader's role.)
My leader.
My role model.
What do you think, So Min?
So Min changed from O to X because of Gong Myoung.
(Guilty)
I think the leader should stay.
(Gong Myoung chose X?)
(So Min changed her opinion.)
(I want to have the same opinion as Gong Myoung.)
Is this "Love Studio"?
I agree with Gong Myoung.
(Whatever his opinion is,)
(Gong Myoung and I are one.)
- You agree with him? - So Min.
- I love her character. - I can't believe her.
She took over the character completely.
Kwang Soo, you don't have to worry.
She took over your character.
- I feel proud. - My goodness.
She took it over completely.
Everyone, we'll take another vote.
But we have to avoid a unanimous decision.
And you want to be in the majority.
The discussion made me consider changing my mind.
It's hard to predict. It'll be half and half.
Let's go.
(Final decision)
(In the 1st vote, only 1 more person chose O.)
(Will the result be different?)
Put it up.
(12 people choose O, 1 person chooses X.)
Is it unanimous?
- I'm relieved. - I'm relieved.
Dong Hwi.
You...
I knew this would happen.
Dong Hwi.
Dong Hwi!
- Dong Hwi. - Bye, Dong Hwi.
- Only Dong Hwi? - Only one person?
Only Dong Hwi chose X.
Thank you, Dong Hwi.
- Thank you. - You saved the entire team.
Have you been hit by one of these?
- No. - No?
It's your first time.
(This is my first toy hammer experience.)
(And I will be hit by my idol, Seok Jin.)
(I'm overwhelmed.)
(Thud)
(The idol's powerful blow)
Was it too hard?
Pull his head out.
(So this is how it's done on a variety show.)
- He needed to experience it. - Good.
He needed to...
- Otherwise, it wouldn't be fun. - Did you see that?
- Dong Hwi, see? - He's taking off his jacket.
- Dong Hwi is a bit upset. - No.
- Here is an easy one. - Okay.
Here we go.
After eating meat, should you eat spicy noodles or cold noodles?
(This is too hard.)
This is...
(It's never easy.)
O for cold noodles,
- and X for spicy noodles. - I share with others.
(What is their 1st choice?)
This is...
It's obvious.
1, 2, 3.
Spicy noodles, of course.
(10 people choose O, 3 people choose X.)
- It's cold noodles. - It's spicy noodles.
- It's spicy noodles. - Really?
- It's spicy noodles. - Of course, it's cold noodles.
There is one more person who chose spicy noodles.
- It's spicy noodles. - It's spicy noodles.
Let me tell you as someone who runs a barbecue restaurant.
Spicy noodles is something you eat during the meal.
- With meat. - You eat it with meat.
At the end, you cleanse the palate with cold noodles.
Okay?
If you eat spicy noodles to finish off the meal,
your breath smells like garlic all day.
Cold noodles wash down...
Your breath can smell like cold noodles too.
The radish kimchi broth is so refreshing.
It makes you smell like radish kimchi.
- What are you talking about? - Yes.
After the meal, the spicy noodles...
freshen up your mouth.
Only when you finish with the spicy noodles,
(Ha Nee chooses spicy noodles.)
you feel fulfilled.
That's what you feel after eating the cold noodles.
- With some ice. - With vinegar and mustard.
Exactly.
Then we'll all choose O...
and be penalized together.
(We'll all choose O and be penalized.)
- He is threatening us. - If you keep doing this...
If you don't help us...
- Help us, or I'll take action. - Why is he doing this?
Let me tell you again.
Some of you should open your hearts to us.
Otherwise, we'll all choose O.
Let's choose O.
Personally, my favorite is...
adding a cup of cold noodles to spicy noodles.
- That's nice. - Right.
It still counts as spicy noodles.
- Let's say that's spicy noodles. - Yes.
All right. Let me ask you for the last time.
O for cold noodles, X for spicy noodles.
One...
(Only 3 people chose X in the 1st vote.)
- One, - O.
2, 3.
(Will Team Spicy Noodles' secret strategy work?)
(12 people choose O, 1 person choose X.)
(I'm the only one who chose X?)
Jae Seok...
- Ha Nee, I said O. - Jae Seok.
- I said O. - He's so mean.
(You didn't hear me?)
- Jae Seok. - Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok. - I said...
- I said O. - When?
I said O, didn't I?
I heard it and changed my mind.
Exactly. I said O.
You said you were going to pick spicy noodles...
What?
You said you were going to...
- What? - Speak clearly.
- You were craving spicy noodles. - I was,
but the majority was choosing O.
- Se Chan will have to... - Okay.
- As her fan. - It's too sad.
(Do you remember?)
(You are my dream girl.)
(With all my love...)
(Thud)
(She is hit hard by her fan.)
It was out of my love for her.
(He pulls out her head too.)
(It looks scary.)
How was it?
I've never been hit like this since I became a grown-up.
It's a new experience.
Here is the last question.
It will be a tricky one again.
At a team dinner, what do you sing to brighten up the mood,
a dance song or a trot song?
(Not this again.)
(It's another difficult choice.)
(A dance song makes everyone dance.)
(A trot song makes everyone sing along.)
- It's hard. - A dance song or a trot song?
It's hard.
It's another hard one.
O for a dance song, X for a trot song.
1, 2, 3.
(8 people choose O, 5 people choose X.)
- It's a dance song. - No.
(It's definitely a dance song.)
It's a trot song.
- It's a dance song. - It's a trot song.
When someone sings a dance song, you're pressured to dance.
It brightens up the mood.
But a trot song is easy to sing along to.
Trot songs are witty.
- If you sing in an amusing way... - I'm tired now
(Let us show you.)
(Team Trot becomes one.)
They sing along immediately.
(Team Dance fights back.)
(They start dancing immediately.)
(Nothing brightens up the mood like a dance song.)
All right.
(Fill me with your love)
(A trot song is better.)
(This is it.)
(It's not working.)
Even though Jong Kook chose dance,
he sang along to the trot song.
Seriously.
(You saw that?)
(As soon as he hears Jin Young's song...)
(Dancing)
(Kwang Soo catches it.)
Seriously.
He reacted to Jin Young's song immediately.
- No. - Of course.
When you go to a karaoke bar,
what do you usually sing?
Among trot songs,
"Daring Woman".
(It definitely brightens up the mood.)
You clapped your hands.
It suits her.
- It suits her. - Can we hear it?
- Please. - "Daring Woman".
- Okay! - Play it!
Kwang Soo, play it before she changes her mind.
We'll show you how it brings everyone together.
It'll bring us together?
I love this song.
- Ha Nee. - "Daring Woman".
This song is nice.
I love it.
(What should I do? Something like this?)
(Daring steps)
(She is warming up.)
Everyone, come forward!
Now that we're here...
We're here to promote "Extreme Job".
Please send a lot of love to "Extreme Job"!
(A brave knee slide)
Let's go!
(Ha Nee's cheerful intro gives Team Trot confidence.)
- Go, Ha Nee! - Go, Ha Nee!
- Okay! - Lee Ha Nee!
(You're not smiling on purpose, right?)
(Poking)
- Right? - Right?
(Everyone sings along.)
(A trot song is fun, right?)
(Even Team Dance sings along automatically.)
(I know you're afraid of falling in love with trot)
Lee Ha Nee!
(Ha Nee shoots hearts at Kwang Soo.)
You pretend uninterested
(You want to join Team Trot?)
- Eyes! - Kwang Soo.
- Here it comes. - Love Giraffe!
(He stares into space.)
Ha Nee.
She's amazing.
(Seductive)
(Cute)
(She moves her shoulders in a cute way.)
(Heavy shoulders)
Lee Ha Nee!
(Se Chan leaves Team Dance.)
This is fun.
(Her boldness explodes.)
Let's go!
(I can buy you anything.)
I will!
(Kwang Soo starts dancing.)
(He has difficulty describing his feelings right now.)
(His vigorous joint movements speak for them.)
(This is what a trot song can do to you.)
(Cute, sexy, and brave)
(Daring woman Lee Ha Nee)
Lee Ha Nee!
(Will Ha Nee's performance affect the final result?)
It was amazing.
- Come on! - This is trot.
- This is the power of trot. - Come on!
(Proud)
It's trot.
This is trot.
- It's trot. - I admit it.
- I admit it. - Let's sing a dance song now.
- Dong Hwi. - It's your song.
This is it.
Let's go!
(Why did they give the microphone to Dong Hwi?)
("Gimme Gimme" by Country Kko Kko)
(Tak Jae Hoon of Country Kko Kko is a carbon copy of Dong Hwi.)
(Team Dance warms up.)
- Okay. - Seung Ryong.
My back.
- Here we go. - Let's go!
(Let me dance.)
(Flashy)
(His flashy steps will definitely bring up the mood.)
Look at that.
(Show them the power of dance!)
- He's amazing. - This is nice.
There you go.
Yes!
- Look at him. - He is just like Jae Hoon.
It's Tak Jae Hoon.
It's perfect.
(He is just like Tak Jae Hoon.)
(Shocked)
(A party needs a dance song.)
Let's go!
(Dong Hwi is sexy.)
Here it comes.
- Let's go! - Hands on shoulders.
(Team Dance, are you ready?)
(Let's dance together!)
(They do the twist all together.)
(This will make the majority vote for dance.)
(Dancing)
(Team Trot is having a meeting.)
(We have to do something.)
- Let's go! - Nice!
(Team Trot will join Team Dance like destiny.)
(Dong Hwi fought Ha Nee back with "Gimme Gimme".)
Let's go!
- Let's go, Team Trot! - Let's go!
Good!
Nice!
(Team Trot has Seok Jin...)
(and Jin Sun Kyu, who looks just like Seok Jin.)
(The trot twins will bring victory to the team.)
Together!
(Team Trot has to win!)
(Call me when you need me)
(I, who look just like you, will run to you)
They might win.
(As Team Trot is doing well,)
(Seung Ryong changes teams.)
- Together! - Let's go!
(Singing)
Jin Sun Kyu!
(This is trot.)
(It's pretty fun.)
(We will run to victory.)
(Trot is the best.)
(It can't get more fun than this.)
(We did a great job.)
(The other team feels threatened.)
(Team Trot seems to be winning.)
- Trot! - Trot!
Let's do this.
Let's go.
- We have to do this. - This is going to be crazy.
- We have to. - Crazy.
- You do the intro. - Okay.
We have to put it on.
("You in Vague Memory" by Hyun Jin Young)
(The hoodie look is the key to this old Korean hip-hop dance song.)
Put on the hood.
You will have to join in.
- Definitely. - Right.
You will want to.
(The light covers up my body)
(They sing along.)
It'll be hard not to sing along to this one.
(They are done warming up.)
Put on your hood!
Let's go!
(Disciplined movements...)
(and rhythmic choreography are the key points.)
(Perfectly...)
(on...)
(the beat)
Let's go!
(Who is this?)
(Sun Kyu suddenly joins Team Trot.)
Let's go!
(Group hypnosis)
What is Sun Kyu doing?
Everyone is dancing.
(Let me see.)
(Even Team Trot is dancing.)
Look at me!
(It's too fun. Whatever.)
(I'll just dance.)
(The dance brings everyone together.)
(This is why everyone loves dance songs.)
Go!
(My singing will bring up the mood even more.)
(Team Trot is doomed.)
Go!
Haha.
(He can't resist.)
(Let me help you, So Min.)
(Team Dance is the best.)
(Frivolous)
Jump!
(Team Trot is being forgotten.)
(We might lose.)
Together!
(Worried, Ji Hyo fights back.)
(The "Love Battery" attack)
(I might be leaning towards trot.)
(Gong Myoung continues the attack with "Ddaeng Bul".)
(Enjoy the dance as well.)
(He sings at the top of his lungs.)
(I might vote for trot after all.)
(Team Trot has to win!)
Team Trot wins!
- I feel so happy today. - Sir, the first round is on you.
- Let's go for another round. - No!
Just go home.
Go home after the first round.
Director Ryu is still here too.
- Ryu Seung Ryong! - Dance.
(Seung Ryong will save his team with his dance song.)
- Dance. - Let's go!
("Tarzan" by Yoon Do Hyun)
Is this the song?
(When I was little)
(Director Ryu, you're amazing!)
(Awkward)
(I only had absurd dreams)
Why are you not having fun?
She is not having fun.
They aren't either.
No one is having fun.
(Forced)
(We're not having fun either.)
(Only the director is having fun.)
(This is why I love team dinners.)
(Team Trot is chatting.)
Hold on. I can't believe you guys.
- Hey. - I'm sorry.
- Hold on. - I'm sorry.
How can you do this?
Who is sleeping?
Seung Ryong saw everything.
Seung Ryong, but it was too boring.
(I'm sorry, but it was boring.)
(Even Manager Yu criticizes him.)
- I mean... - Hold on.
I've never heard a dance song this boring in my life.
- Even I got bored. - I...
(Team leaders should go home after the 1st round.)
- Shall we take a vote? - It's really...
I don't know anymore.
I'm afraid we'll all choose trot.
O for dance, X for trot.
1, 2, 3.
(The final decision)
(In the 1st vote, the majority chose dance.)
- It's dance. - No.
2, 3.
(Everyone chooses trot.)
- What? - Are we unanimous?
- We're unanimous. - Gosh.
Trot was so fun.
After singing it, we could see.
Sadly, no one wins any points.
Please hit the next person with the toy hammer.
All right. Let's start from Haha.
- Okay. - Here we go.
Keep going.
You have to hit harder than the person before you.
If you don't hit hard...
Don't worry. I've been hit many times.
Are you sure? Will you be okay?
Here?
(Can I hit you here?)
(Let me wake up the Wi Seong Rak inside me.)
(If you're really okay...)
Okay!
(The Wi Seong Rak punch)
(Oh, my. What did I do?)
Her head went in a bit.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
- Are you okay? - It was...
I'm okay. The thing is,
it was a completely different kind of blow.
Actors are different, right?
- I mean... - It's Wi Seong Rak's blow.
Usually, the top of your head hurts.
But not this time. My teeth hurt instead.
(My teeth hurt, not my head.)
It means he's good.
It went deep.
- It did. - Yes.
Please do it properly.
(Thud)
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
(I'm sorry.)
I'm sorry.
(Give as good as you get.)
(The love is passed down in the toy hammer relay.)
Jae Seok is pretty good.
Have you ever been hit with a toy hammer?
- Never. - Never?
I've been hit with a real hammer though.
(He wants to sound like a tough guy.)
(He might die after getting hit twice.)
A real hammer?
This is nothing then.
We're on a variety show.
Just look forward.
(He turns around.)
(Freaking out)
(It's only a toy hammer.)
- What's wrong? - Don't worry.
You're supposed to be a tough guy.
- Don't be like that. - Stop it.
It's so shameful.
Look at how manly your beard is.
I saw many people dodge once,
but he dodged three times.
Be charismatic, Seung Ryong.
You look great, Seung Ryong.
(Yes, I'll be charismatic.)
(Coward Seung Ryong comes back after getting hit.)
(He pumps charisma into him.)
Are you okay?
- Are you okay, Seung Ryong? - Is it my turn?
Aren't you a tough guy?
He hit with the opposite end.
Here comes the main part.
(Today's main event for toy hammer relay)
- What's going on? - This is great.
(He climbs on his chair.)
- No. - You can do it.
- You can do it, Seung Ryong. - I'll pass it onto the next guy.
I'm worried you might hit me in the next round.
(Thud)
(We can feel the impact just by listening to its sound.)
That was hard.
(Jong Kook is red with anger.)
- Next is Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(He senses danger.)
It's over, Kwang Soo.
(Shuddering)
Okay.
(Okay!)
- It broke. - Okay.
(Will I also end up like that?)
- Did you see it? - The wave became much bigger.
Are you going up?
Yes, it's because...
- Seung Ryong went up. - That's right.
We should get first aid ready.
Is he allowed to do this?
Where are you going?
Do you want to come up too?
(Dragging)
(He climbs up on a chair as well.)
- We can stand on the chair, right? - Okay.
(Lifting up)
(I give back as much as I receive.)
He'll come down anyway.
- He might fall. - He came down.
Okay.
(I'm worried about Kwang Soo.)
I don't want to get hit.
Goodness.
(He aims at the target.)
(He hits with a toy hammer.)
- Thank you, everyone. - Okay.
(Thank you, everyone.)
(He wraps it up suddenly.)
(We should inverse the order now.)
If we start again, it won't end.
Do you want to continue?
- Did the wave end with me? - It did.
Okay.
The wave has to end at some point.
(Toy hammer relay ends by force.)
Let's play Race of Wits.
We'll stand up instead.
(Too many of their scores tied.)
(Those with the same score play Race of Wits.)
(People keep being eliminated.)
Okay, I'm the winner.
(The final winner is Jae Seok.)
I'll give you a hint that you want.
(Between a hint about thieves or police,)
(he may choose one.)
(He secretly asks for a hint.)
- He could be a thief asking. - Right.
If he's a thief,
- he'd ask for a hint about police. - Right.
I got it.
(Jae Seok chooses a hint.)
- Right? - Yes.
All right.
(Everyone watches him with curiosity.)
- Right? - Yes.
All right.
(He finally gets a hint.)
(If the hint is about the police,)
(it's likely that Jae Seok is a thief.)
(What is Jae Seok's identity?)
(He picks a hint about the police.)
(The police uses his real name.)
Here's a hint about the police that you asked for.
Okay.
(Jae Seok is a thief.)
Two of you are...
level thieves today.
Why do you always assign us as thieves?
Why do you always pick us?
(Yu Jae Seok is a level thief.)
Goodness.
(The police officer doesn't go by his or her stage name.)
(Who are the guests that use their real name?)
(It's 1 of these 4.)
- What is it? - He's thinking a lot,
so I think he's a citizen.
I don't think he's a thief.
All right.
(Thief Jae Seok narrows down the candidates for the police.)
(Divide into 2 groups and get in the car.)
In this car,
- there's a culprit. - Definitely.
- There's more than one. - There's more than one.
(She turns around.)
(Is it you?)
(I'm definitely not it. I'm a newcomer.)
I heard what Sun Kyu mumbled to himself.
(I heard what Sun Kyu mumbled to himself.)
- What did he say? - He said...
He said, "I'm bad at things like this."
I heard him say it.
They didn't give me any special instructions.
That's why I asked him a while go.
When did they tell you that?
Those who come early usually get the mission.
- That's usually the case. - He came the earliest.
- He did. - Then I arrived.
As you know, the shoot was delayed.
- Later... - I think I know.
- Dong Hwi is strange. - Dong Hwi.
He keeps cornering Sun Kyu.
- He does. - I see.
It's a habit of inexperienced criminals.
I don't think he's someone outgoing and talkative.
But he keeps cornering Sun Kyu.
I've always been strange.
No, Dong Hwi.
He feels cornered.
He must be very flustered.
(Is one of them a forger?)
We must get hints no matter what.
Yes, we should.
It's impossible without hints.
- What's the hint, Jae Seok? - Share it with us.
- Please. - It's too exposing.
As I said, if I share it,
- you might think I'm a thief. - Right.
It could be one of us,
so I can't.
- The first hint is too general. - Right.
- That's why. - Okay.
(He lets it slide.)
I bet Gong Myoung is a citizen no matter what.
It seems that way based on his face.
(It seems that way based on his face.)
He's definitely a citizen.
(His face looks that of a citizen.)
(I believe your face, Myoung.)
My goodness, So Min.
Seriously.
I'd love to have a son like him.
Come on.
He doesn't have the face of a forger.
- It's impossible. - His face?
Who has the face of a criminal?
(Who has the face of a criminal?)
You know what? Seung Ryong...
(She answers immediately.)
I'm sorry to say this,
but he has the look of a forger.
(He's already been proven guilty according to his face.)
I think he's either the police or the forger.
- He's one of them. - You fit the character.
You really do.
I don't understand...
what everyone is saying. It's my first time here.
Isn't it strange that he keeps smiling?
More importantly,
my team works so well as a team.
Our identities will be revealed later, right?
- I think I'll be extremely shocked. - Right.
(We'll leave Seung Ryong's worries behind for now.)
(Team Seung Ryong arrives at the restaurant.)
The smell is unbearable.
Everyone, here's a mission...
with a chance to win hints and meal cards.
It's Ultimate Cham Cham Cham.
(Ultimate Cham Cham Cham)
Based on the result of Cham Cham Cham,
if the offense is successful, you win.
The final winner of a tournament wins...
a meal card and a hint.
(The final winner gets a meal card and a hint.)
(Tournament matches)
This will be easy.
(Kwang Soo versus Jae Seok)
- Let's go. - You can do it.
- Seriously. - It's a big match.
I don't want to lose against him.
I wanted to play against him.
Okay.
Here we go. Get ready.
Start.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo gets to attack first.)
(What's going on?)
(He hits with the toy hammer.)
What are you doing?
- You should play Cham Cham Cham. - Play Cham Cham Cham.
Kwang Soo.
Listen, I'll explain. Play rock-paper-scissors.
- I'm sorry. - Then...
play Cham Cham Cham.
(Laughing)
Why did they play rock-paper-scissors?
I don't understand.
This is very upsetting.
We should play Cham Cham Cham.
Okay.
Here we go. Get ready.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok gets to attack.)
I told you.
This is upsetting.
- I should've played something else. - You get one chance.
(I need to calm down.)
Jae Seok is very nervous.
He is.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Jae Seok fails to attack.)
- He didn't turn. - Did he turn?
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(I'll hit him first.)
- Did he turn the same way? - No, he didn't.
(He definitely failed during Cham, Cham, Cham.)
What happened, Jae Seok?
(Seung Ryong learns how to play dirty.)
Did he turn?
(The bigger rule breaker catches the rule breaker.)
I won.
Did he turn the same way?
- He didn't. - He didn't.
Do you win if you lie like this?
No.
(Do you win if you lie like this?)
You shouldn't learn from him.
- This doesn't count. - Don't learn from him.
He was joking.
We're veteran members.
- Jae Seok is quite flustered. - He's very flustered.
- He's very flustered. - Okay.
The score is 1 to 1.
- Okay, here's our last round. - It's 1 to 1.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
(This round will determine the real winner.)
(Jae Seok gets to attack.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Kwang Soo turns toward Jae Seok's hand.)
(If he successfully attacks him, Jae Seok wins.)
(Is Jae Seok grabbing the pot?)
(He holds down the pot and attacks with the hammer.)
Just hit him.
Just hit his head.
(It's a dirty mess.)
Hit his shoulder.
(It's a demonstration of a dirty play.)
(They're too old for such nonsense.)
(Thud)
Game is over.
Kwang Soo lost.
(He's tattered.)
(He's the best in playing dirty.)
You should've been quicker to reach for the pot.
(You're amazing, Jae Seok.)
It was meaningful.
It was a great game.
(It was a great demonstration of how one can play dirty.)
Gosh, it's so irritating.
(He understands how Running Man works.)
Here we go.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min versus Myoung)
I'm nervous. Why am I so nervous?
Why are you nervous?
(Why are you nervous?)
(Why are you nervous, Myoung?)
(Embarrassed and flustered)
Wait, are you on a date?
- What are they doing? - What are you doing?
- Just play rock-paper-scissors. - What?
Wait a minute.
"Why are you nervous?"
What's going on?
He said that he's nervous.
He keeps saying that he is.
(Myoung says that he feels nervous in front of me.)
(It must be good to be young.)
Start.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Myoung gets to attack.)
Why couldn't I grab it?
(He misses the toy hammer.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Myoung makes a mistake with the toy hammer.)
(What's going on here?)
Myoung couldn't grab it.
- Myoung. - He's rather shy.
Are you going easy on her?
(Are you going easy on So Min?)
Are you going easy on me?
- Or... - I'm sure of it.
He could have finished it.
- It'd be finished already. - Is he going easy on her?
I think he's going easy on me.
(Look at these two.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They start to play seriously.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Myoung gets to attack.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Thud)
Myoung doesn't go easy on others during games.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Thud)
(Hold on. Myoung?)
Myoung is quick.
(Myoung is no longer suspected.)
He doesn't go easy.
He doesn't.
Why didn't you go easy on me?
(Goodness)
- It really hurt. - It's a game after all, So Min.
Myoung is quick.
I'm okay.
Wait, hit me one more time and hug me.
(Will you hit me one more time and hug me?)
(I already lost, so I'll win something else.)
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
It didn't hurt.
(Seung Ryong versus...)
We met for the first time today.
We did.
It's best to play when we don't know each other.
- Let's see. - Don't hit with the pot.
Don't hit with the pot.
Next is Seung Ryong.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Se Chan gets to attack.)
(He leans forward.)
(He pushes out his face.)
(Seung Ryong is so cute.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Bumping)
(He hits his own face with the pot.)
Are you okay?
(Poor Seung Ryong.)
(He attacks himself with the shield.)
Are you okay?
- Oh, no. - Are you okay?
Are you all right?
I never saw this happen during Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Hang in there, Seung Ryong.)
- I thought it was serious. - Get used to it, Seung Ryong.
I'm a little dizzy.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Se Chan gets to attack again.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(He turns towards Se Chan's hand.)
(If Seung Ryong doesn't block him, Se Chan wins.)
(Squeak)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(His head lowers due to the impact.)
Oh, no.
- Why did you stand still? - Seung Ryong.
Why did you stand still?
He stood still for me to hit him.
(He gets hit by the pot and the toy hammer.)
It was a great game.
(Se Chan moves up to the final round.)
Are you okay, Seung Ryong?
(Variety shows are difficult.)
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Cham, Cham, Cham semifinal continues.)
(As soon as they start, he hits with the toy hammer.)
- Myoung is quick. - Who lost?
Here's the final round.
- I have to win this. - He's quick.
Cham, Cham, Cham.
(With the snap of his wrist, the game is over.)
He's so quick.
(Myoung is undefeated during Cham, Cham, Cham.)
I knew it.
(Myoung gets a hint.)
(Team Ha Nee arrives at the restaurant.)
The smell is amazing.
It smells like jeon.
Your mission here is...
Leg Split.
The loser of rock-paper-scissors spreads his legs.
You lose when you can no longer spread your legs.
The final winner of the tournament...
wins a meal card and a hint.
(The final winner wins a meal card and a hint.)
We're doomed.
(Ha Nee versus Jong Kook)
Isn't Jong Kook very flexible?
- No. - Not as much as you think.
- Your legs are so long. - No.
Her legs are really long.
(We expect Jong Kook to struggle against Ha Nee.)
Jong Kook.
Her legs are long too.
(I'm quite flexible too.)
My legs.
Look at him.
You can't win just because you can split your legs.
(Spreading wide)
(During the warm-up,)
(she dominates him successfully.)
(Gaping)
(How is that possible?)
(He almost tears his muscles while trying to copy Ha Nee.)
Even if I can do it...
It doesn't matter if I lose rock-paper-scissors.
(Winning rock-paper-scissors is more important.)
Go a little farther.
- Jong Kook. - I think it's over.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Rock-paper-scissors)
(I can't go any farther.)
If he had won...
(Sun Kyu is her rival in acrobatics.)
Okay.
This is the final round.
- It's the final round. - It's the last.
(She barely reaches his toe, and Sun Kyu is nervous.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Their fate depends on this round.)
(Screaming)
Good job.
That's it.
It's about Han Ki Beom's height.
(Sun Kyu, can you do it?)
Let's see.
He might be able to do it.
- Okay, stop there. - It's as far as I can go.
Here he comes.
Did he reach?
He reached.
(His legs are split straight.)
He's so good.
- Be careful. - Did he reach?
- He reached. - Get longer.
(Will Sun Kyu succeed?)
He can stretch far.
- Seriously. - Be careful.
I lost.
(I lost.)
Okay, Ha Nee wins.
She's the winner.
It's what we expected.
- You know about Ha Nee, right? - She must be the forger.
- There's a forger? - We're watching you.
I have no idea.
(What kind of hint will it be?)
I'm watching you from the back.
(Ha Nee gets a hint.)
(Myoung also gets a hint.)
(What hint did the two of them get?)
(The forger made his debut before 2010.)
(Ha Nee in 2006, Sun Kyu in 2005,)
(and Seung Ryong in 2004)
(Who is the real forger out of these three?)
A quest has been discovered.
Here's a chance to arrest the thieves and the forger.
This is your last mission.
It's Ultimate Level Up War.
(Ultimate Level Up War)
Among current Running Man members,
three level badges have been forged.
- 3? - 3 of them?
It's three badges.
(Which ones are forged?)
Find hints that are hidden in this place.
If you eliminate thieves and the forger,
- the citizens and police win. - Okay.
Running Man citizens gain...
the level of a thief that you eliminated.
Police and guest citizens win...
a gold badge.
(Police and guest citizens win a gold badge.)
(They're determined.)
Once thieves are arrested,
their level goes to zero.
(Thieves' level goes to zero when they're eliminated.)
(It's over once they're arrested.)
They're placed last.
If the police and citizens are eliminated,
- the thieves will win. - What will happen to them?
Thieves' level will rise to 10.
(When thieves win, their level rises to 10.)
- Will it be over? - Really?
They will be the winner of this project.
(They'll be the final winner of Level Up Race.)
Only Kwang Soo would be willing to take such a risk.
- Why would I? - Kwang Soo.
- Why me? - You.
Only Kwang Soo would be willing...
to take such a risk.
That's such a groundless and sudden accusation.
Okay.
The police may discuss among themselves.
They can tell their identity to those...
whom they think are citizens.
They can reveal their identity.
They can't tell in case one of them is a thief.
- Right. - That's correct.
Please go to your places.
You'll start individually.
(Who's helping Jae Seok, the thief?)
The forger may be Seung Ryong,
Sun Kyu, or Ha Nee. There are three candidates.
I suspect Ha Nee.
I'm starting to see unusual sides of Ha Nee.
I have to remove Seung Ryong.
I think Sun Kyu is the forger. I think it's Jin Sun Kyu.
He keeps on avoiding making eye contacts with me.
He's not his usual self.
He's too nice to maintain a poker face.
Dong Hwi kept on doubting me.
Dong Hwi? He kept on pointing the finger at me.
He did.
(They are suspicious of one another.)
(Who's the forger out of these three?)
The race is about to start.
(There are 2 level thieves from Running Man,)
(and 3 level badges have been forged.)
(The police and forger are among the 5 guests.)
The race has started.
(The final race has started.)
(As soon as the race starts...)
Why is there nobody here?
(Thief Jae Seok is...)
(waiting for somebody.)
Nobody is here yet.
(He's waiting for somebody.)
(At that moment!)
(Jae Seok is glad to see somebody.)
(It's the other thief and the forger!)
How do we eliminate the others?
Do we rip their name tags off?
This is the hidden elimination rule for your team.
What is it?
Each person received a notebook and a pen...
to make notes.
(Everybody received a pen.)
Yes, I have it.
You must borrow the pen of the person you want to eliminate...
to eliminate their name tag.
(Jae Seok laughs after hearing about the hidden rule.)
- Hello. - Yes, hi.
You two are the level thieves for today.
Your job is to steal others' levels and reach Level 10.
I'm going to steal So Min's for sure.
I'll take Haha's level for sure.
Yes, I think so.
I think it's about time...
Jong Kook learns what it feels like to lose.
Then you have chosen So Min, Jong Kook, and Haha.
We have to run and rip their name tags off.
We can't hesitate.
Where are the hints?
(The thieves and the forger must find hints about the police.)
It won't be here, right?
(The police and civilians must find hints about thieves and forger.)
I need to find some hints.
(That's the only way to uncover each other's identities.)
(He searches fervently.)
Where are the hints?
(Dong Hwi is looking for the hints.)
- Who is that? - You scared me.
Where are you going, Dong Hwi? Why?
I'm not a thief.
I just...
(He's on full alert.)
Dong Hwi, I'm not...
(She finds a hint!)
(She takes it and goes away.)
Why is she doing that?
It's nothing.
She just took...
(He searches the scene of the incident.)
- So Min just... - Do you have anything?
- She... - You're not supposed to write that.
You're supposed to write about what you found. You don't write...
- "So Min opened the door." - She took it from here.
- So Min, can you share it? - No, not with you.
- I'm a civilian. - You're a suspect.
You're a suspect to me. No, not you.
- So Min... - You're kind of...
How did she know that there was a hint here?
(How did So Min know?)
(How did So Min know the location of the hint?)
She saw me from far away...
and said, "I'm not a thief."
Who are you talking to?
Dong Hwi.
- Well... - What are you doing?
Hold on.
(Dong Hwi's Mystery Files concludes abruptly.)
Why is he running away?
Why are you doing that?
Hey! Why are you... Did you find the hint?
(Why is Dong Hwi talking to himself and running away?)
What are you? Are you a thief?
What are you?
(He gets caught.)
- Did you find anything? - No.
I was a thief last week.
I finally found out.
Found out what?
I found two people...
who said they were thieves last week. Finally.
I was thinking about that the whole time.
Seok Jin and you...
- Did Seok Jin say that too? - Yes.
It was Seok Jin and me.
(Because it was Seok Jin and me.)
You were telling the truth.
Yes.
You should have watched the previous episode.
I take back what I said earlier.
- This isn't right. - Who are you talking to?
You're with me. Why are you talking to the camera?
This is not "Unanswered Questions".
I'm sorry. I wasted your time.
- Anyhow, see you later. - See you.
(They want to know who the thieves and the forger are.)
(Seung Ryong is a leading forger suspect.)
Hold on.
(If he's the forger, he needs hints about the police.)
(He finds one in the corner.)
This is it, right?
(Who is the hint about?)
(Thief B is unmarried.)
(That excludes Seok Jin.)
(He found a hint about the thief,)
(but he tries to destroy it.)
(Is he the forger...)
(who tries to destroy the hints about the thieves?)
Shall we go down?
Should I go this way? Since I'm here.
(Sun Kyu goes around with a failed poker face.)
I found it. This is it, right?
(What hint did he find?)
"Thief B is a male."
(If it's a male,)
(it's either one of these two.)
I hope I bump into somebody from my team.
Why are you here?
You're a suspect as well, so you should be careful.
You and Jae Seok are Level Two, right?
People with the lowest levels are...
probably the thieves. There's a high possibility.
- Are you doubting me? - Yes.
I'm doubting you too.
- Me? - Who is that?
(At that moment!)
You're both here.
- Are you Level Two? - My suspects...
- Yes. - Let's talk first.
He's Level Four, so he's so arrogant.
- What do you mean? - Come here, Jae Seok.
I know...
you want to turn the game around,
but this isn't the right way.
You should climb the ladder one level at a time.
Why would you steal?
Who are you talking about?
Are you a prosecutor or a judge? Why would you decide?
I'm already sad I have a low level, and you point the finger at us?
- Understood? - This is driving me nuts.
- You two... - I'm so upset.
- Did you find anything? - No.
Leave.
(Leave if you don't have any hints.)
- I'll leave too. - I'm mad.
(It's not easy borrowing his pen.)
(Will he be able to borrow Jong Kook's pen...)
(and eliminate his name tag?)
Jong Kook probably threw it away.
(He doesn't know what's going on.)
Jong Kook, is there anything you'd like to share?
This is my intuition. Se Chan...
behaved a little bit different.
That's my intuition. Anyhow,
Jae Seok is a bit strange.
(According to Jong Kook's logic, Kwang Soo can't be a thief.)
Oh, gosh. You scared me.
(It's Jae Seok again.)
Good luck.
Hold on. I'm going to the bathroom, but I'm upset about this.
Are you doubting me...
because I'm Level Two?
Do you have anything to prove us wrong?
If there's anything convincing, we'll trust you.
- Right? - I'm speechless.
Why are you pulling your sleeves up?
I'm going to the bathroom.
- For washing your hands? - Yes.
I mistook you when you pulled your sleeves up.
- It's the police! - You scared me.
(His heart almost drops.)
- Why did you get scared? - Why?
- Why did you get scared? - Why were you startled?
Is this when "a guilty conscience needs no accuser"?
All right. I got it.
- Excuse me. - Sure.
May I borrow your pen?
(May I borrow your pen?)
- My pen? - Yes.
I have to write down something. I let somebody borrow mine.
(Will he be able to borrow Jong Kooks' pen?)
Ask him.
(Borrow Kwang Soo's.)
Can I borrow yours? I'm dumbfounded.
(Jong Kook catches on fast. He's not easily manipulated.)
You really lent him your pen?
There's something I need to write.
You shouldn't lend your pen to just anyone.
He's going to catch you as soon as you run away.
- My gosh. - What are you writing down?
Hold on. I'm going to...
- Do you have something? - put together the hints I have.
I was going to the bathroom to do that when you stopped me.
Anyhow, thank you.
Hey...
Jae Seok is so strange today.
I think there's something going on.
(It's difficult borrowing other people's pens.)
This is difficult.
(How will he borrow three?)
Jae Seok.
- Yes? - I'm a civilian.
Catch the thief with me.
(That came out of nowhere.)
(Does she think I'm a civilian?)
Are you really a civilian?
Let me tell you my hint. Thief A is...
taller than 170cm.
Hold on. I'm going to write this down.
(So Min thinks Jae Seok is a civilian.)
Can you tell me one? Do you have anything?
- I don't have any. - You got one.
I don't have a pen.
You got one. Can you tell me?
(Will So Min...)
(give him the pen without question?)
Here.
(He borrowed So Min's pen!)
- Give me one hint. - I don't have any.
You got one earlier.
- It's too general. - I still want to know.
There are 5 guests. It's 1 of them.
- The thief? - No, what is that?
- The forger? - Yes.
You're lying to me, aren't you?
That's the hint I got.
(She gets anxious and looks around.)
No...
You're not a civilian.
- I am. - You're not.
(Jae Seok acts suspiciously.)
- My gosh. - Why aren't you telling me?
I'm going to look for more hints. I don't have enough.
I have to find another hint.
(At that moment!)
I'm getting thirsty.
This is thrilling.
(The forger suspects are on the move.)
I want to go up. I'll go later.
So Min.
(So Min doesn't know anything. Somebody is following her.)
(Who's calling me?)
Why is somebody following me?
(The person following her is...)
(Seung Ryong, who is a forger suspect.)
(He starts running all of a sudden!)
(He runs after her,)
(and she runs away.)
(It's a chase.)
So Min.
- Yes? - So Min.
Come here.
(She can't get away.)
Is there an exit here?
No, there isn't.
(It's a dead-end.)
What are you doing then?
- Are you running away? - Yes.
(Are you running away?)
(There's nowhere for her to hide.)
There's always a twist.
You have to help me.
(Ripping)
What was that?
Civilian Jeon So Min is out.
(According to Jae Seok's plan, So Min is out.)
You have chosen So Min, Jong Kook, and Haha.
(There are only Jong Kook and Haha left.)
For Jong Kook,
(Will he continue the momentum and eliminate Jong Kook as well?)
there's going to be a moment of chance.
"Can I borrow your pen?"
Then I have to rip his name tag off right away.
(Eliminating Jong Kook is their biggest dilemma.)
(Will he be successful?)
What are the hints?
- Do you want to hear me out? - Okay, let me hear you.
All right.
Let me show you.
You can calculate it.
For Levels 4 and 2, this person needs 6,
and this person needs eight.
So Min is Level Six, so they can steal hers,
and they can steal 2 Level 2s.
That or 1 Level 4...
and 2 Level 2s.
That's difficult.
Do you have a hint? Let's talk.
Do you have a hint?
Thief B is...
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are also speculating.)
unmarried.
Unmarried?
(Jae Seok, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo are in one spot.)
- Kwang Soo. - They scared me.
You probably have an insignificant hint.
Look at you trying to play us.
- Sorry. - Do you not have a pen?
I lost mine.
Where did you put yours?
- I'm begging for pens right now. - What are you?
They stole...
- They stole the levels. - the levels of three members...
- and achieved the highest level. - That's right.
Both of them?
Both of them will achieve the highest level...
if a Level Two...
- Level 4. - and a Level 4...
If Level Four take So Min's,
- they get Level 10. - Level 10.
- If Level 2... - And if Level 2...
takes 2 Level 4s, they reach Level 10.
That's how they win.
If they take a Level Four...
- and instead of two... - I have to find the hints.
- Ha Nee. - I have to find the hints.
(Ha Nee, another forger suspect, is here.)
I have to find the hints. They're nowhere to be found.
- Is it so hard to find? - Yes.
I can't find anything.
I looked in the trash.
Excuse me, but why are you angry?
(Why are you yelling at us?)
You'll find it. You'll get one. Don't worry.
There's nothing.
I kept on looking. I went through 1st to 3rd floors.
- You have to keep looking. - Goodness.
Do you have any hints?
I don't.
If you have any, please share.
It's not in the trash. Don't look in there.
(Se Chan leaves the conversation.)
There's a possibility.
The trash... What is it?
- It sounds credible, right? - Yes.
It does. It's very possible.
I'm certain.
- This makes sense. - What is it?
- What is it? - This works.
(Jae Seok was looking for a chance.)
Are there 3 Level 4s?
Can I borrow a pen?
(He tries to borrow Jong Kook's pen again.)
For Jong Kook, there's going to be a moment of chance.
(Can he borrow it this time?)
I'm sorry.
Why do you keep borrowing pens?
It's something we talked about.
Hold on. Let me figure this out.
Let me figure this one thing out.
(Please...)
(He has to take it out.)
- Let me figure this one thing out. - Is there...
a mission where you have to borrow everybody's pens?
(He catches on fast.)
Gosh, this is annoying.
(Will he not be able to borrow the pen?)
- My pen... - You get tricked all the time.
(Jong Kook hesitated, but he lets Jae Seok borrow it.)
- Hold on. My pen... - You get tricked all the time.
Hold on.
- Hold on. This... - We do that a lot.
Hold on. Let me figure this out.
- I trust you unconditionally. - Okay.
(The moment Jae Seok borrows the pen, he makes the move again.)
(Will Jong Kook get eliminated like So Min?)
You have to trust me. You saw me.
- I know. - When's your birthday, Jong Kook?
- Would it be somewhere here? - April.
Can it be here?
Look. There are 3 Level 4s.
Haha...
You know it's not me, right?
If it's neither you nor me, there's no other Level Four.
(Like Se Chan said, is Level 4 the other thief?)
- Shouldn't it be here? - It's Haha.
What the...
(All of a sudden!)
(Ha Nee rips off Jong Kook's name tag.)
(Kwang Soo couldn't do anything.)
(Ripping)
(The second target, Jong Kook, is out.)
Sorry.
(What happened?)
Here's the assistant who'll help you ...
with the forged level badges.
- Is there an assistant? - Let me introduce the forger.
(The forger who'll help the thieves is...)
Hello.
(Ha Nee!)
- Hello. - Ha Nee.
- Oh, dear. - Hi.
(The truth gets uncovered.)
(Here was the thieves' strategy.)
Here. Give me one.
(Jae Seok borrowed the pen.)
(Ha Nee approached So Min without telling her she's the forger.)
(Ripping)
(That's how So Min got eliminated.)
(Sorry, So Min. I'm the forger.)
What are you?
- In any case... - Jong Kook,
I'm going to keep this at my house...
- as a family treasure. - All right.
I'll take this.
I love you, Jong Kook.
(Thanks to Ha Nee's perfect acting, Jong Kook is out.)
Civilian Kim Jong Kook is out.
(Seung Ryong was surprised to hear that. What is his identity?)
(SBS waiting room before filming)
- Hello. - You're...
a police officer who is on stakeout to catch the thieves and the forger.
(Seung Ryong is a police officer.)
(He was searching around...)
(and found a hint about the thieves.)
I have to do this for justice.
(Thief A is taller than 170cm.)
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Se Chan)
So Min!
(So Min and Haha are shorter than 170cm,)
(so he tries to win them over.)
You have to help me.
I'm the police.
(You're the police?)
- Help me. - Are you the police?
- Are you serious? - I know.
- Are you the police? - Why can't you trust me?
(Do people lie to you all the time?)
Okay?
Seung Ryong.
Are you the police?
How did you know?
Salute.
First of all...
(He approached Haha as well and said he was the police.)
I'm so nervous.
Gong Myoung, come here.
What was the hint?
I'll give you one if you give me yours.
- Do you want a hint? - Yes.
- I'm the police. - Really?
(He won over people whom he was certain were the civilians.)
I'm the police.
(He formed a team to catch the thieves.)
You have to help me, okay?
Okay.
Civilian Kim Jong Kook is out.
(Civilian Kim Jong Kook is out.)
Then...
- Hold on. - He's an innocent civilian.
He is.
I figured it out now.
- Jae Seok has to be the thief. - Right.
[VIU Ver] SBS E435 Running Man
"RPG Level Up Race Part 3: Level Fabrication Incident"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Gong Myoung found a hint.)
(Thief A is in their 40s. Jae Seok, Jong Kook, Haha)
What?
(The last hint said he's taller than 170cm.)
(Haha is not over 170cm, so he's excluded.)
(Jong Kook just got eliminated,)
(so Jae Seok has to be the thief.)
Jae Seok has to be the thief.
Right, I said it was him too.
We have to catch and eliminate him.
- Let's rip his name tag off first. - Okay.
He's the thief for sure.
Let's go. Be natural.
I can't be eliminated,
- so you two go. - Okay.
(I'm not saying this because I'm scared.)
(He prefers to be on a stakeout.)
This...
We're halfway there.
(Jae Seok doesn't know that his identity got uncovered.)
(Haha and Gong Myoung are looking for him.)
Jae Seok.
Who do you think it is? Who is it?
(They approach Jae Seok by asking him a question.)
(Jae Seok doesn't know his identity got uncovered.)
I thought...
it was Jong Kook and Se Chan.
But Jong Kook is out.
(Jae Seok doesn't know they're here for him.)
So Min is out too.
She's Level Six, so that was an easy guess.
- What are you? - What do you mean?
- Where were you? - What?
What do you mean?
Why are you guys...
(They start moving!)
(Jae Seok is cornered.)
(He realizes it and tries to get out.)
(Level thief Yu Jae Seok is out.)
We were right.
(Level 4 Haha eliminated Level 2 Jae Seok. He's Level 6.)
I'm so mad.
I'm mad.
- I'm mad. - You're Level Six.
(Haha succeeds to catch a thief and level up.)
Thief Yu Jae Seok is out.
(Jae Seok got caught.)
The race ends if the police gets caught, right?
What is going on?
(The remaining thief's identity is unknown.)
Okay.
(Seung Ryong apprehended a thief by using his agents.)
(Forger Ha Nee and Thief B...)
(versus Police Seung Ryong and civilians)
I made deductions until my notebook became tattered.
I knew Jae Seok was a thief.
(Dong Hwi wants to know.)
I will get to work.
Now, I only have my cold judgments to trust.
(What?)
Dong Hwi.
(Seok Jin is sitting down because he ran out of energy.)
Dong Hwi, I am exhausted.
- Do you... - I think you are a civilian.
Do you admit your deductions were wrong?
I am a civilian too.
- That's right. - You know, right?
I never thought you were anything else.
- Right? - Right.
Who do you think it is?
(Give me the answer.)
I figured it out.
(He used his deductive skills.)
How did you do that?
I combined the hints.
(I combined the hints.)
- Who is it? - The forger thinks...
I am being fooled.
It's Sun Kyu, right?
(Sun Kyu?)
- How did you know? - Because it isn't Ha Nee.
(He went with his hunch.)
I have been walking around with Sun Kyu.
He thinks you are on his side.
He thinks he got me fooled.
I figured it out.
(The clueless duo sets out to catch Sun Kyu.)
The civilians are doing all the work today.
(Meanwhile, Sun Kyu is tired of being suspected.)
(I really am a civilian.)
(The clueless duo spots him.)
- There is a civilian. - Yes.
- Dong Hwi. - Did you eliminate Ha Nee?
- Ha Nee. - No, I didn't.
We need to rip off Ha Nee's name tag.
- That's right. She is an assistant. - I am 100 percent sure.
- She is an assistant. - Let's go.
- That's right. - What?
What are you doing?
(The clueless duo begins to apprehend him.)
(Sun Kyu's name tag gets ripped off right away.)
Fools.
- Is he a civilian? - Jin Sun Kyu is out.
- Is he a civilian? - Fools.
(Jin Sun Kyu and Lee Dong Hwi are out.)
You said it's him.
You fool.
Civilian Jin Sun Kyu is out.
Thief Jin Sun Kyu?
Civilian Jin Sun Kyu.
(He collapses.)
Civilian Lee Dong Hwi is out.
Ha Nee, Ha Nee!
(So Ha Nee is the forger.)
(This is a disaster!)
I know for sure that five people are civilians.
(Seung Ryong made a list of civilians before the race.)
I think Ha Nee is a civilian...
for sure.
I am the police.
You are the police? Don't lie.
Why would I lie about it?
Help me, okay?
- Okay. - Okay.
- Don't tell anyone. - Are you really the police?
Of course I am.
(He trusted her.)
(His brain stopped working.)
This is a disaster.
(I revealed my identity to everyone.)
(How will I win when they know my identity?)
I need to rip off Haha's name tag.
(Ha Nee is looking for Haha, the last target.)
If I hold out until the end, I will survive.
(Se Chan is behind Haha.)
Se Chan is behind me.
Haha.
(Why is Se Chan following Haha?)
It's Se Chan.
(He is suspicious.)
(Haha suspects Se Chan.)
When you are cornered,
you begin to act in a strange way. That's what I am doing.
I don't know. Let him rip off my name tag.
(Se Chan's behavior turns Haha's suspicion into conviction.)
Se Chan.
- Okay. - Don't be mistaken.
- Haha. - See you later.
I won't rip off your name tag. I know you aren't a thief.
(Is Se Chan a thief?)
- What should we do? - It can't be helped.
I swear I am not a thief.
You look like you are telling the truth.
I am.
(Kwang Soo is under suspicion.)
Okay. Let me talk to Gong Myoung a bit more.
- I will look for hints. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo leaves to look for hints.)
Either Se Chan or Kwang Soo is a thief.
Civilian Haha is out.
- What? - Civilian Haha is out.
(Kwang Soo was with them just a moment ago.)
What was he?
(This means...)
Civilian?
Civilian Haha is out.
(Is Haha out?)
(It's time for me to step in.)
A good agent got eliminated.
(Is he acting?)
(What?)
(He suddenly begins to warm up.)
(Creaking)
(He stops due to back pain.)
Gosh, why is it so heavy?
(What?)
(He resumes warming up.)
(This is how an actor warms up.)
(He sets out to catch a thief.)
(Forger Ha Nee and Thief B...)
(versus Police Seung Ryong and civilians)
Seung Ryong can't be seen anywhere.
(1 forger, 1 thief,)
(1 police, and 4 civilians remain.)
Gong Myoung, I need to level up.
- Okay. - Help me.
(The thief and forger just need to catch the police.)
(Let's catch a thief.)
(Seung Ryong suddenly ties his shoelaces.)
(His preparations are neverending.)
My shoelaces keep coming undone.
I didn't think...
(At that moment)
Seung Ryong.
(Ha Nee spots Seung Ryong.)
Ha Nee.
- Seriously... - What is it?
Sun Kyu got eliminated.
- Who? - Sun Kyu got eliminated.
Who eliminated him?
(How will I rip off his name tag?)
Come on.
(They face each other at a dead-end.)
You are the police, right?
- Yes. - Be honest.
(Rip off the other's name tag or get your name tag ripped off.)
Come on.
(It's time to put an end to this.)
(They begin.)
(If Seung Ryong's name tag gets removed, Team Thieves win.)
(To remove his name tag, she should have borrowed his pen.)
I need to write it down since I am stupid.
(Right after Seung Ryong confessed his identity to Ha Nee)
Let me borrow your pen.
- Don't you have a pen? - No, I don't.
(Trusting Ha Nee to be a civilian, Seung Ryong let her use it.)
(Ha Nee made all preparations.)
(It's a golden opportunity.)
(She must seize it.)
(Grabbing)
(The one who grabbed Seung Ryong's name tag is...)
(Gong Myoung.)
(Gong Myoung comes to protect Seung Ryong's name tag.)
Hey.
- Come on. - Who is it?
Who is it?
Come on.
Get Ha Nee's name tag.
No. No!
(Forger Lee Ha Nee is out.)
I am sorry, Ha Nee.
All right.
Ha Nee, you...
(I was so close to ripping off his name tag.)
- What is she? - What is she?
Ha Nee is the forger.
- She is the forger. - Really?
Is it even possible to rip off your name tag?
- Ha Nee isn't the forger. - It won't come off.
- See? - Are you the forger?
I am the forger.
Help me up.
Ha Nee is the forger.
- It didn't get ripped off? - No, it didn't.
(Grabbing)
(Kwang Soo aims for Seung Ryong's name tag.)
(That means Kwang Soo is...)
(Thief)
(Kwang Soo is the other thief.)
I'll think of this as the last chance.
Those who were eliminated were So Min and...
Gosh, my legs hurt. Seung Ryong, Sun Kyu...
(Kwang Soo got to work when Ha Nee borrowed Haha's pen.)
- Ha Nee! Ha Nee! - What is going on?
What is going on? What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Grab his body.
Grab his body. Grab his body.
(Kwang Soo and Ha Nee succeeded to remove Haha's name tag.)
Grab his body.
(Kwang Soo and Ha Nee's perfect teamwork)
What was that?
Is she the forger?
Hurry up and run away.
No, it didn't.
(He will win if he removes Seung Ryong's name tag.)
(Slipping)
(They protect Seung Ryong's name tag.)
(The tables are turned.)
I got his hands.
(Gong Myoung removes Kwang Soo's name tag.)
Did you rip it off?
- Hey! - Oh, you should have done it.
(The last thief, Kwang Soo is out.)
Gong Myoung removed it.
She didn't get to level up.
I was close.
- I see. - I was close.
I know. We were close.
It's okay.
You might be okay, but I'm...
(He grits his teeth.)
I am Level Zero now!
(How am I Level 0 despite working hard all day?)
I mean...
I was leading the race by myself.
That serves you right.
(You shouldn't have been greedy.)
It was the third episode of the Level Up Race.
The final victory of the Level Fabrication Incident...
goes to Team Civilian and Team Police.
We did it.
(This is the highlight of starring on Running Man.)
(That was so close. We almost had it.)
- We won. - We won in the end.
The hidden police officer was Ryu Seung Ryong.
This is a new style. He's the king of stakeouts.
Yes, I was on a stakeout.
I didn't see him once.
- I never saw him too. - He was so good.
Where were you hiding at?
He was in the darkest corner of the wardrobe department.
The thieves were Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.
(The thieves were Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.)
(Their levels reset to Level 0.)
- My goodness. - You did steal the levels,
but you failed to win the race. Your levels will be...
- zero. - My goodness.
No one reached Level 10, right?
- Okay. - And Haha eliminated Jae Seok.
You will be Level 6 as your level increased by 2.
(He reached Level 6 after getting Jae Seok's levels.)
This is so rewarding.
Even if our level is zero, we still have a chance, right?
- That's right. - Let me try this one more time.
(I still have one shot left.)
- One more shot. Okay! - I'm starting again!
- I'm starting afresh! - It counts starting now.
- Let's go, go, go! - Next week will be a new beginning!
The winning guests will receive a prize.
Here comes the pure gold.
I can still win a prize after doing such a bad job?
Four of them will get it except for Ha Nee.
I'm jealous.
- I'm jealous. - My goodness.
(The prize is a gold sheriff badge.)
- Hey, this is... - Gosh.
I'm sure they'll give you one too.
No.
(We thank the guests for running so hard with us since the morning.)
Thank you once again. Thank you.
Thank you.
- Level 0! - Level 0!
- Look forward to next week! - This is just the beginning!