(The show starts with full of energy on a spring day in March.)
- Hello. Hi. - Hi.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
(Hello, everyone.)
You're wearing matching outfits. You two planned it, right?
(Is the theme of your outfit the twin look?)
- It just happened this way. - It was a coincidence?
I was going to change my outfit.
But the clothing brands are different. It just happened.
- You guys didn't plan this? - No, we didn't.
They are like soulmates.
- I think mine looks better. - This is embarrassing.
(If I have to choose, I think mine is better.)
- Hey. - I want us to vote for this.
- His jacket looks great too. - Personally,
I like Jae Seok's jacket more. I like his more than the yellow one.
- My color combination is better. - Your jacket has better colors.
- Right. I agree. - His jacket is too much.
Unbelievable.
But with that jacket, you won't be in a car accident.
If you wear that, you won't be.
(It's a checkered jacket with neon-yellow.)
(Safety first! Seok Jin, the Light Bar)
- My goodness. - The colors pop.
(I see. My jacket was for my protection.)
Aren't I right? His jacket is great for that.
We asked you to bring an object you don't need immediately,
but you can't throw out because it's valuable.
We asked you to bring an object each.
(After last week's filming, their mission was given out in advance.)
("To the members of Running Man"...)
(What is the mission that was delivered to the members?)
(It's to bring useless but valuable objects from home.)
Let's check what kind of objects you brought today.
- What's that? It's a mirror. - It's a full-length mirror.
- Is that a snowboard? - It must be a snowboard.
- It's a surfing board. - Isn't that a panel?
- It's a surfing board. - What's that?
Is that a golf club?
- Are those skis? - Everything is so big.
- Everyone brought big stuff. - What's that?
- What's that? - All right.
I was looking through my stuff.
- I brought us a hat I made. - Let us see.
It's pretty big.
(The fashion genius, Haha's hat?)
- This is it. - That looks interesting.
(Haha's item: a fedora hat, made by Haha.)
- Didn't you wear that before? - I used to wear this a lot.
- I think you wore that before. - I wore it often.
- You wore that. - Yes, I wore this...
- I remember that. - about 6 to 7 years ago.
- Right, right. - I made this hat.
- I wore this in different colors. - It looks great on him.
You look cute.
The hats got crumpled, so I threw them out.
- Does it look great on anyone? - Yes.
It looks great on anyone.
- It doesn't look good on him. - It looks terrible on him.
- It looks terrible on him. - What? It looks great on anyone?
- Doesn't it look great on him? - No, it doesn't.
It really doesn't look good on him.
Are you the King of Beggars? Are you?
Do I look okay?
What do you think? Do I look good?
Wear that to "Comedy Big League" and act as a beggar.
With this hat? But this is fashion.
What about you, Se Chan?
Me?
It's one of the things I always wanted to try out.
I always fail to do this.
I want to go on a diet.
That's why I got ambitious...
- You bought it. - The supplement for your diet?
Yes, I bought the supplement. It's brand new.
(Se Chan's item: unopened protein powder)
- It's brand new. - That's the protein powder.
- Protein. - It's protein.
- Anyone who works out buys that. - I must buy this.
- I bought this immediately. - I can totally relate.
- That has nothing to do with that. - Right.
- Is that strawberry-flavored? - Yes, it is.
- Gosh, it's strawberry-flavored. - So...
- this is easiest one to swallow. - The strawberry one is good.
This says it's chocolate.
- Chocolate? - This isn't strawberry-flavored.
(No, you're wrong.)
- I guess it's chocolate. - "Chocolate milkshake".
- It's not opened. He doesn't know. - He has to open it to know.
(He doesn't know.)
- I never tasted it. - I thought it was strawberry.
He thought it was strawberry because the bucket was red.
- This is chocolate. - It's chocolate?
Not everything in red is strawberry.
- It had the strawberry color. - Not every supplement is like this.
- He brought the protein supplement. - Yes.
- Who's next? - Kwang Soo is the wild card.
It was for the movie, "The Accidental Detective 2".
I was promoting the movie.
It was when I went to the screenings.
- Come on. - Come on.
(Kwang Soo reveals his cherished item.)
- It's because... No, no. - Come on.
(Kwang Soo's item: life-size cutout of the Prince of Asia)
- Let me explain. - Why did you bring this?
- When I was promoting the movie, - What's wrong with you?
- I used to bring this around. - What are you doing?
After the promotion...
Why did you bring that?
I can't throw this out per se.
Why did they choose this photo out of all those photos?
You should handle this. Why did you bring it here?
Listen.
It's a bit iffy to throw this out.
- This means a lot to throw it out. - Right.
- You should give that to someone. - That's true.
Some people can use that as a dartboard.
You should give that to someone.
- Dartboard? - Why would they do that?
- Get the nose, and it's 10 points. - Right.
Or people can use this for the ironing board.
- How can they use this for ironing? - The ironing board.
- My gosh. - It's a life-size cut-out.
He sure brought a life-size cut-out.
Why did you say it like that?
He asked what you meant by it.
What do you mean by that?
(Please don't get the wrong idea.)
(Feeling insulted for some reason)
- Why do I feel insulted? - No. Wait.
- I mean, it is a life-size cut-out. - But it is a life-size cut-out.
- Right. It is. - Right.
- What did you bring, So Min? - I brought...
- She brought memories again. - No, I didn't.
My hobby is painting.
- I used to go to an art academy. - Really?
- This isn't my original painting. - Really?
It's a copy. After looking at a painting,
- I copied the painting. - You copied it.
- You did a great job though. - Right.
- Did you draw this? - Yes.
- You drew that? - My gosh.
You're good at painting.
- My gosh. You really drew these? - Goodness.
- Yes. - It looks like a print.
- These are fantastic paintings. - I...
There are parrots.
- Yes, there are parrots. - So Min, you drew them?
- This is a watercolor painting. - You did a great job on them.
I used acrylic paints for this.
- How can you draw that well? - You're so cool.
You can do this once you learn how.
- You did a great job. - She drew them very well.
Did you like your art teacher or something?
- They are great. - They are kissing. Look at this.
- She is talented. - They're kissing.
(Two parrots are kissing.)
I bet there is a meaning behind this painting.
In my opinion, I think So Min...
brought all of her paintings on purpose.
- She could've brought only one. - Right.
I wonder why she brought all of them.
I'd like to raise suspicions on why she brought all of them.
- Did you bring them for someone? - No, no.
It's not that.
Do you want your ex to watch this, so you can hurt him?
- "I'll get rid of these." - I think...
She films "Love on the Air" on our show.
- Someone must be crying now. - Exactly.
- You can't end things like this. - Right.
She's driving me crazy.
All right. We enjoyed looking at So Min's paintings.
- As for me... - Okay.
- Isn't that a guitar? - I brought a guitar.
- Really? - Really?
I wanted to learn how to play it back in the days.
- Woo Seung Min gave me this. - Here.
He gave me this as a present.
- It's beautiful. - Really?
- The guitar is very beautiful. - It's beautiful.
- It's beautiful. - How pretty.
(Jae Seok's item: an electric guitar for a wannabe rockstar)
- It's a beautiful guitar. - Yes, so this is...
It's so cute.
- If you can play the guitar well... - My gosh, how much is that?
It's just collecting dust at my house.
- And I feel terrible about it. - It's completely new.
- I didn't play it at all. - My goodness.
- I really want that one. - It's better for the guitar too.
This is the place. You just need to hook it up here.
You can plug it in here.
You can make it sound like this.
- I see. That? - You can do this with it.
What? No, that's not the spot.
(Transforming into a rockstar)
- Doesn't that go there? - That's not the spot.
No, it goes here.
- Wait, am I wrong? - That's not it.
- If you're not sure, don't do that. - It has to go up.
- That's for the cord. - That's the output jack.
How can you plug that in there?
He plugged it in the jack.
Let me check.
My gosh, he plugged it in the wrong spot and bragged.
"Don't you know this?"
(He's a star who's the best at bragging.)
- Instruments have their owners. - That's right.
- I want someone to take this. - Okay.
I want someone who can play the guitar take this.
It's my turn now.
- Go ahead. - Okay!
- Let me tell you what I brought. - Seok Jin.
I thought long and hard about what to bring.
I have a guitar that I bought when I was in ninth grade.
- I had the guitar. - From the 80s?
- From the 70s? - It's a guitar.
I like everything about my wife,
but what I don't like about my wife is...
that she throws out stuff too easily.
She threw out the guitar.
But she managed to keep you around when she throws out a lot of things.
(He's brutally honest.)
(All of a sudden, she became a dutiful wife.)
Anyway, she's a saint.
- He's so brutal. - You're unbelievable.
I didn't think that far. In hindsight, I should be grateful.
- Exactly. - I should be thankful.
- She throws out a lot of things. - That was a hard blow.
Anyway, she threw out the guitar,
so I brought this after much thinking.
- Back in the days, - What is it?
there was a time when I was into fashion.
Back in the days, Seok Jin...
was very interested in fashion for some time.
There was a phase when I bought a lot of clothes.
- Really? - Was that in the 80s?
But the thing about Seok Jin is that when he was interested in fashion,
he would wear white pants.
He was hooked on white clothes.
(Seok Jin was the leader of all-white outfits.)
When was that? That must've been...
- During the white-clad folk times? - White-clad folk times?
Are you talking about the white-clad folk times?
How long was that?
- A long time ago, - 70 or 80...
I learned that we used to be white-clad people in school.
- That must've been true. - White-clad folk?
- White-clad folk. - His outfits were all white.
- What is it? - I thought I should dress better.
I thought I should dress young.
So I bought clothes.
- This isn't cheap. - Seriously.
What's that?
What is that?
- This is my jacket. - It looks nice.
(Seok Jin's item: blue vinyl jumper and white pants)
(Memories of Fashionable Seok Jin)
(Ta-da! That looks amazing!)
- You think so? - It's nice, isn't it?
- This... - People who can't dress well...
think the jacket looks nice.
(It suits the taste of people who don't know about fashion.)
Why? It looks nice.
People who can't dress well must think that's nice.
I sort of thought it looked nice too.
- This is... - I thought the same thing.
- People like us find it nice. - Hey, this is...
- I can... - It doesn't look cute.
- It doesn't look cute. - Why not?
- Look over here. - It's futuristic and nice.
This is a cutting-edge jacket because inside, there is...
- a hole to put your earphones. - Is that what it's for?
- You didn't know? - My jacket had a hole,
so I was about to get it refunded.
- I didn't know this was for that. - Why don't you try it on?
Why don't you put it on? We must check how it fits.
My gosh, Seok Jin.
It looks nice.
I understand now why these two wore the matching outfits today.
- During the opening segment? - Gosh.
It's not easy to buy that with that much money.
I'm supposed to zip up this jacket.
You look great.
- Doesn't he look like a mackerel? - My gosh.
(A happy mackerel outfit)
- He's a blue fish. - A blue fish like a herring.
- A herring. - A herring.
Anyway, I ended up buying this.
- My gosh. - That's too much.
- Se Chan wants to try it on. - I want to.
- I really want that jacket. Yes. - Really?
- Do you want to try it on? - Yes, Seok Jin. Let me.
But Seok Jin, that's...
Gosh, paying that much for that jacket is too much.
(Reckless Se Chan is digging his own hole.)
As long as it fits...
Hey, that's totally you!
Hey, that belongs to you.
(I'm a baby mackerel!)
(Now, I'm the shabbiest mackerel!)
- My gosh, look at me. - Give him the guitar.
- All right, Se Chan. - Okay.
- Jae Seok. - Seriously.
- He's the musician of the street. - Everything belongs to me.
- Se Chan. - Are you serious?
- My gosh. Today is your day. - I love it.
I guess this guitar belonged to you.
- My goodness. - You know?
- It was Se Chan's. - It went to its owner at last.
My gosh, this is crazy.
(I'm the worst dresser of this area.)
- Hey, stay right there. - Haha.
Gosh, this is...
That's yours.
This is totally you.
- Se Chan, it belongs to you. - Jae Seok.
- My gosh. Are you serious? - You know...
I was wondering who would take this, but it was you.
- I love it. I'm serious. - I get what he likes.
I can't believe he actually likes it.
Great. It's Ji Hyo's turn.
Actually...
- What is it? - That's big.
- Is that a golf club? - No.
I'm sure you've never seen this before.
- I... - What is it?
- As you know, I'm scared of bugs. - Right.
- I can't step on them... - You despise them.
- or smack them to kill them. - That's true.
I talked to my manager about this, and it took my manager...
- several days to find it. - He looked it up online.
He bought it from overseas and gave it to me.
I'm so embarrassed.
My mom scolded me after my manager gave me this as a present.
- Why? - She thought it was useless.
This...
- What is that? - What is it?
- What is that? - What is that?
(What is that?)
What is that?
- That's a flame thrower. - Isn't that dangerous?
It says, "Caution, Burn Hazard".
(Everyone is shocked.)
(It shocks everyone instantly.)
(What is this unidentified object Ji Hyo took out?)
(Ji Hyo's item: a flame thrower that catches bugs?)
(No! It's a flame weeder that burns weed.)
- That's a flame thrower. - Just to catch bugs?
I really thought hard about it.
- I almost bought a flame thrower. - Seriously?
- You used that in your house? - To catch bugs?
No, I use it outdoors.
- Let me see. - And...
the bugs fly away when I turn this on.
- Unbelievable. - I see...
cautionary signs for burns all over this thing.
This is the only part I can actually grab this with.
- Why did you... - Hey...
This will look great on Jong Kook.
It will look great on Jong Kook.
- We should bring things like that. - Right.
- This is it. - Right.
- I'm in trouble now. - What did you bring, Jong Kook?
Today,
I brought RPR's CD.
(Reggae, Peaceful Like a River)
(Jong Kook's item: his number 1 butler, Haha's CD)
I brought RPR's CD.
Darn you.
(The butler is mad.)
- The thing is, - That's a bit...
I don't need to use this CD.
But I can't throw it out because it's precious to me.
Isn't that right?
I'm at a loss for words.
I don't think I have one.
- Me, neither. - It looks like a parcel.
I only gave them to those who came to my concert as guests.
- I didn't make many of them. - It's a special edition.
- You're right. - He signed it.
There's a cassette tape and a badge.
- Really? - Really?
- It's a gift set. - You're right.
- It must've been expensive. - It was.
I'm glad you didn't sell it on a secondhand site.
You had it with you.
My name was written here, so I couldn't sell it.
So you've thought of doing that.
(Jong Kook thought about selling it.)
No, it's not like that. I just had this on my mind.
Why did you tell us to bring these?
I'll explain it to you.
Today, the team that can find out how to win...
after opening boxes will win.
It's called the Unboxing Race.
(Unboxing Race)
You'll be divided into three teams...
and will have to bid for the boxes.
You can sell or exchange the items you have brought...
in order to get money for this mission.
This is how you'll divide into teams.
Have you registered your fingerprints on your phone?
- Yes. - Yes.
Unlike the previous phones, you can register at the front.
(They registered their fingerprints.)
Done. Look.
- I'm all done. - Done.
I'm finished.
Your phones are being used to charge earphones.
- You charge it at the back. - Right.
Once the earphones are done charging,
- they'll turn green. - How convenient.
- Goodness. - Is it charging?
- It is. - Wow.
- They're just the right fit. - Goodness.
They're perfect.
She's right.
It's very comfortable.
- You put them on wrong. - Really?
(Seok Jin needs to get used to technology.)
This is how you'll split into teams.
Each of you will call someone randomly.
You'll partner up with the receiver on the other line.
I'll call now.
(Seok Jin goes first.)
I can press on any number from 1 to 8, right?
(Whom will he call?)
(Anticipating)
- He's calling. - What?
- What? - It's Se Chan.
Tap, tap. Hello?
Hello?
- Why did you press six? - Who is this?
Okay.
- Come here. - I'll be on my way.
This is nice.
- Okay. - It's the protein and old clothes.
- This will be a problem. - You'll be with Seok Jin.
Since money matters,
we'll need to partner up with those who have...
- Expensive items. - good items.
It's either Jae Seok or Ji Hyo.
You're right.
The worst is Kwang Soo.
No, you're wrong.
- He's the worst one. - Wait.
Why do I feel insulted?
It's... It's...
Hello?
Ji Hyo, it's me.
Hi, Se Chan.
- Seok Jin, Se Chan, and Ji Hyo. - We're a team.
Them three?
Who is this?
It's So Min.
So Min, hi.
- Haha. - Hi, So Min.
- Is this Haha? - Yes, it is.
We can do it. We're best friends.
Then are Jae Seok and I a team?
Okay!
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are a team.)
This is terrible.
Okay!
We'll definitely win!
WIth Jae Seok's guitar, we'll win!
(Team Jae Seok, Team Jong Kook, Team Seok Jin)
Let's go to Sangam-dong since the stations are there.
You're right.
No one will buy mine.
- Wait. - Ji Hyo.
- The seller needs to speak well. - Right.
- Right. - Se Chan.
- I trust in you. - Don't worry.
Yours won't be a problem.
But you know what?
I'm a bit worried about yours.
(These stage costumes from the past aren't that tempting.)
- Hey. - I understand why you picked them.
But they're old-fashioned.
- I like them, but... - That's why...
they're the best for idol singers.
Idol singers will love them.
- If we come across any, - Then...
they'll definitely like these.
We could meet them at the music shows.
You're right.
Let's go to Sangam-dong first.
Right, let's go first.
(Team Jong Kook is also going.)
Is there anyone who'd swap with me?
(Haha is reminded of someone.)
Hello?
(The receiver has been sleeping.)
Sang Yeob.
(It's Lee Sang Yeob, a regular on this show.)
- Are you alive? - Hi.
- You're our substitute man. - Are you with So Min?
- I'm your substitute man! - Yes, you are!
(He is called the substitute man.)
(The substitute man is a new character on the show.)
(He's known to substitute for all painful penalties.)
Do you have any items that aren't cheap...
but that you want to throw away?
It'd be nice if you give us some nice items since...
- we can only call three people. - He's right.
(He hints So Min to help.)
- We called you first. - That's right.
- Then... - Yes?
I do have a good one.
- Really? - Really?
- Sang Yeob. - Okay!
- This is your time... - Right.
to show us how much you're worth.
- Let's do it! - Okay!
2019!
(He asks So Min to help once more.)
- World star! - The rising star of variety shows!
(They fail to be in sync.)
- Once more. 2019! - 2019!
- The rising star of variety shows! - The rising star of variety shows!
- Lee Sang Yeob! - Lee Sang Yeob!
(They praise him.)
We love you, substitute man!
Give us your address!
(Meanwhile, where is Team Jae Seok?)
Gosh, this is insane.
I had no idea it'd be like this.
(They haven't departed yet.)
(Kwang Soo gets in first.)
I don't know if it'll fit.
(It's taking ages.)
First...
- Let's... - What is this?
Your guitar.
If that breaks, we're done for.
- Be careful. - Okay.
How do we do this?
Goodness.
(They're going through so much turmoil.)
All right. Can you take us...
to Hwanghak-dong?
(Hwanghak-dong is known for its flea market.)
(It's a treasure chest full of everything you can imagine.)
Why did you bring this?
Gosh.
Did you really have to?
I had no idea.
If I knew better, I would've brought something else.
Who'd buy yours?
Sir, do you have any intention of buying this cut-out?
Not in particular.
Would you buy it for 50 cents?
Well...
I wouldn't buy it for 10 cents.
(He's being honest.)
(Only valuable items are worth selling.)
That hurt.
- I know what he means. - He was very...
- He wouldn't buy it for 10 cents. - straightforward.
- But I agree with him. - How could he?
For someone who doesn't need this,
this will be nothing but trash.
All right. Let's just go to the flea market...
- and find out its worth. - Okay.
Okay? Let's go first.
(They arrive in Hwanghak-dong's kitchen alley.)
By the way...
(They're lost.)
No one will buy this.
(No one in this kitchen alley will buy his item.)
They sell kitchen utilities.
I doubt anyone would buy this.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Where are you going?
(Let's see.)
How about exchanging that with this basket?
This is worth more than that.
- What? - I'll give it for free.
- But still. - Take it.
(She's willing to give it for free.)
- Ma'am, do you perhaps need this? - Ma'am.
- That cut-out? - Yes.
- No, I don't. - Okay.
Do you want me to place it there and advertise it?
(She asks if he needs help with his own PR.)
No, that's not why.
I don't need that.
(She can set it up, but it's still not worth buying.)
We'll come back later if we need your help.
Thank you.
- I can't believe she offered that. - See?
- It's really of no use. - Don't say that.
You heard her, right?
She offered to advertise it for you.
Like what our driver said,
it's not even worth 10 cents.
That's not true.
- That can't be. - I'm frustrated.
- Hello. - Hello.
Goodness.
(They arrive at a market.)
Look at that.
They might need it.
Look at this. They have everything.
(They have many cheap used goods.)
- Goodness. Hello. - Hello.
Why are you carrying that?
- Why? - We'll sell it.
(A lady becomes interested.)
- We'd like to exchange this. - We're going to swap.
Because we have a mission today.
Would you be interested in setting this up...
in front of your store?
Since many tourists visit here...
How much do you think this should be?
- This cut-out? - Yes.
(How much is this 2m-tall cut-out worth at this market?)
The highest would be two dollars.
Two dollars?
(She'll offer 2 dollars at most.)
- Two dollars? - Yes, then I'll be able to sell it.
- 2 dollars? - 2 dollars.
- Okay, we'll be back. - Okay.
- We'll be back. Thank you. - Two dollars?
- Two dollars. - I won't sell it for that price.
(He expects it to be more expensive.)
I would've sold it for 30 dollars.
It's worth two dollars as of now.
They're shooting that show today.
"The Show". It's a music program.
(Which idol groups are present?)
Seok Jin, look here. It's SF9.
(SF9 has caught Se Chan's eye.)
(SF9 is a group of 9 talented members.)
(SF9 has been appearing on dramas and variety shows.)
This is SF9. Wow.
Please introduce yourselves.
Okay. 2, 3.
- To be a sensation. Hi, we're SF9. - To be a sensation. Hi, we're SF9.
They're amazing.
He was in "Sky Castle".
He played the role of Woo Ju.
- We loved the drama. - Thank you.
I made sure to watch it every week.
It was so good.
It's nice to meet you. We're here...
because...
Take out your items.
(He tells them to take out their items.)
- All right. - We have quite a bit of stuff.
- Hold on. - Which one should we do first?
- Should we go with the pants? - Sure.
All right. Check out these pants.
(He starts off confidently.)
(They're not too excited.)
Any one of you can wear them.
- Goodness. - They're vintage.
- Sorry? - They're vintage goods.
- What? - Not at all.
You may think that way, but it's a popular brand.
It's not worn out. This is how it should look like.
Chani, you'll look good in them.
Do you want to try them on?
(That?)
- Just try them. - Wear them over yours.
- Over mine? - Yes, try it.
- My size is 29. - This is 30. It'll fit. Try them.
Sizes 28 to 32 will all fit.
Anyone can wear them.
- I knew it. - It fits just right.
(He looks good in them.)
- You really do look good in them. - He's right.
- It's like a stage outfit. - I'm not joking.
You can wear them on stage. Just tighten the back.
And...
- Where is the jacket? - They're pretty.
- Where is the jacket? - I'm wearing it.
- Oh, my. - Look at him.
(Rowoon looks good in it.)
Look at this.
- Stand next to Chani. - That's the same jacket?
It's the same jacket.
(Rowoon makes it look better.)
- They look so good. - It suits them.
They make the clothes look better.
Your stylist looks shocked.
These clothes are better than her picks.
(He tries to persuade them.)
She feels like she needs to try harder.
Do you have anything you can exchange them for?
I do.
I have a bluetooth speaker.
- Really? - Seriously?
- We've been using it. - Really?
I can't believe it.
Hold on. How much was this?
- I'm not sure. - Roughly?
But I'm sure it wasn't too expensive.
Really?
Then I think you should take that off.
(He won't sell the jacket.)
- Seok Jin. - This jacket is worth a lot.
- No way. - We need to sell it to him.
- Not many people like it. - I can't!
Most people don't like it.
- Let's take back the pants then. - No.
It's rare to find someone who looks good in them.
They were so expensive.
- It's rare, you know? - That's true.
- Do you want these? - What?
- This is really good. - It's a gift from us.
Can you give us one more?
- Is that a shaver? - It is.
- What is this? - It's perfume.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Good luck, SF9!
Good luck with your performance.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
You guys really look good.
(They exchange the clothes with the members' belongings.)
- I wonder what he'll bring. - I'm so curious.
- I'm anticipating. - He's here!
(They haven't seen him in a while.)
Come in. What is that?
(What did Sang Yeob bring?)
(Lee Sang Yeob, also known as the substitute man)
What have you brought?
(What's in your hands?)
- Hey, what is that? - What is that?
- Isn't that a monitor? - What is that?
Isn't that an antique?
- Hey. - What is that?
- It's heavy. - It's a very old item.
It's our family heirloom.
- This is good. - I like this one.
How could you bring your family heirloom?
(At a glance, you can see that it's a very old item.)
(It's the oldest vintage item so far.)
This is amazing.
It's our family heirloom.
If my parents find out, they'll kick me out.
This could be several centuries old.
Shouldn't this be placed in a museum?
You're right. It's pretty much a national treasure.
- What is this used for? - I don't know.
- How do you use this? - What is this?
- What is this? - This is used...
as a heater.
(Is it a brazier that was used to warm their bodies?)
- You use those chopsticks. - You put charcoal in this.
- You move it with the chopsticks. - That's correct.
The reason why I brought this was because...
- I wanted to know how much it was. - Right, you must be curious.
- I am. - Do you like paintings?
(She gets ready to sell their items.)
- Paintings? All of a sudden? - Yes.
We should give you something in return.
This is an exchange.
(You're going to give me a painting?)
Do you feel lonely these days?
How do you feel these days? We have several paintings.
We have paintings for all moods.
- I am lonely. - They're like talismans.
We have paintings that bring someone helpful into your life,
make you rich, or make you fall in love.
There's also one that brings you peace.
I'd like...
a helpful person to come into my life.
- A helpful person? Hold on. - Helpful person?
- So Min. - Yes.
Oh, really?
(Let's see.)
That one.
(Ta-da)
(Haha encourages him on.)
- This one is quite nice. - What is this? "So Min"?
- I painted it. - It's nice.
- Isn't it nice? - Isn't this one too pricey?
Still, he said he's lonely.
(They talk as if her painting is worth just as much...)
(as Sang Yeob's brazier.)
But still, I think the painting is worth far more.
- Right? - From what I've heard,
she had a great love life when she had this painting.
- Really? - It's truly a talisman.
It is.
And she's giving it to you. It's amazing.
That's right. And a celebrity drew that, you see.
I know that you guys fell in love in the drama.
But in real life, do you really not feel anything for each other?
We're just doing business.
- Nothing at all? - It's just business.
- It's just business. - Really? Nothing at all?
We're like family.
But I was slightly disappointed last time.
She said that she and I were like family,
and I could totally understand that.
(She was asked if there was an actor she fell for recently.)
(She said it was Kim Ji Suk.)
(Isn't Sang Yeob in that drama too?)
But for him...
(He's like family to me.)
(Her reply was very brief.)
Is there absolutely no way for you two to be dating?
- Not at all. - She said we're like family.
Sang Yeob seems to be disappointed.
I'm not his style to begin with.
- Really? - Whenever I say something,
he says, "How could you say that as a woman?"
("So Min, don't say such things!")
He's the pure type.
He's very pure.
- He's very naive. - I see.
- That's what makes him interesting. - Is he conservative?
- Very. - Really?
- Hey, no wonder. - You're right.
(No wonder)
(The item he brought seemed very conservative.)
- It's our family heirloom. - Okay, we got it.
Okay.
- We understand. - That's conservative?
He's very conservative.
I finally found out my true personality.
- He's conservative. - He is.
- He's conservative. - You're right.
I had no idea.
(So Min exchanges her painting with Sang Yeob's heirloom.)
(Where are Jae Seok and Kwang Soo...)
I feel helpless.
(while the others are succeeding?)
(They haven't been able to do much.)
I'm going crazy. What should we do?
(They've been wandering the streets for 30 minutes now.)
I don't think anyone would buy yours.
- Well... - I'm serious.
I'm so embarrassed.
(Suddenly)
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's a record store. - It's an LP store.
(An LP store catches their attention.)
It's an LP store. An old record store.
That's Michael Jackson's old record.
(This vintage store has many old records.)
This is amazing.
May we enter? Thank you.
If we exchange ours with these records, it'll be pricey.
LP stores are popular among young people these days.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I was so startled. - Hello.
You'd rather come here than stream songs online?
It's my hobby.
- Listening to LP records? - Yes.
It's vintage.
They are examples of new-tro.
- You're right. - We need to exchange something.
Do you happen to need Kwang Soo's cut-out?
Jae Seok, don't say that.
(He didn't need to point out that it was Kwang Soo's.)
You can just say that it's a cut-out.
- It's my cut-out. - Our mission is...
to exchange our items.
Do you need his cut-out?
(He asks them.)
(Kwang Soo is known as the Asian Prince.)
(Is she a fan of his as well?)
No, thanks.
(She rejects.)
- Okay. - You don't need it.
It was too sudden.
Right. How old are you?
(He asks them their age.)
Why would you ask that?
(Flustered)
- Why would you ask that? - We're 18.
You were born in 2002.
You're so young, but you're listening to LP records.
Anyway, you can enjoy listening.
We need to talk to the owner.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
- Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo. - Hello.
We came here to exchange this cut-out...
- with an item of yours. - My daughter is a big fan.
Really?
(His daughter is a big fan of Kwang Soo's.)
- Seriously? - She loves him.
- Thank you. - How old is she?
She's in fourth grade.
She only watches Running Man at home.
My goodness.
How much would you pay for this?
(How much is his cut-out worth?)
Since my daughter likes it,
- I'll pay 50 dollars. - My goodness!
(He's the highest bidder thus far.)
It's too expensive.
I could've actually given you a higher price.
- 50 dollars is more than enough. - Thank you.
- This is... - Do I pay you in money?
There's only one of this in the world.
There will never be a duplicate.
- 50 dollars is too expensive. - Really?
(Jae Seok stops him.)
What kind of cut-out is worth 50 dollars?
Is there a belonging of yours that you'd exchange with this?
- Do you have any? - Then how about this?
It's a bit old,
but the Academy Awards ended recently.
I have LP records of the "Bohemian Rhapsody".
- Are you serious? - Yes.
- It's not easy to get those. - Seriously?
- Freddie Mercury? - Yes.
- Can you show us? - How much do you sell those for?
It's worth more than 50 dollars.
I heard it's extremely difficult to find those these days.
(He willingly offers it for his daughter.)
- Isn't it too expensive? - Queen is on the rise.
(They're in awe.)
This is so rare.
I had actually looked for one.
It was so hard to get one.
Since my daughter likes you, I can offer you that.
But still, how could you exchange this with his cut-out?
(Jae Seok still can't understand.)
Come on.
Don't say that.
- That's true. - Stop saying that.
You're really going to exchange this with that?
(Trading Kwang Soo's cut-out is successful.)
Thank you so much.
This is unbelievable.
Should we try using it here?
We came here to use it.
- Let's try it. - We should.
We need to show a demonstration first.
- I need to see if it has fuel. - Our clients.
They're here.
(They're finally here.)
- They're coming. - Hey.
(Who's the savior that came without knowing the trading item?)
Hello.
- Hello. - Come here.
(Eating coach, Moon Se Yoon)
(Indispensable man, Choi Seong Min)
(Se Yoon and Seong Min,)
(funny next door colleagues that Se Chan invited.)
- We are... - Can you explain it to them?
- What is this? - Well, this is...
Would you like to see our item?
Okay, let's see your item.
- Are we trading with it? - Take it out.
- The bigger one first? - Yes, the bigger one.
- The bigger one. - Can we reject it?
Just have a look at it first.
- Here we go. - We...
(A flame weeder enters without a chance to reject it.)
What is this?
- Here we go. - We...
- What is this? - We have more than one item.
- Is this a bazooka? - No.
What is it?
Don't you like camping with your children?
- Right. - When you're cooking the meat...
as their father...
"Kids, I'll show you a magic."
(Your dad will cook the meat with a flame weeder.)
The meat will be cooked straightaway.
- This... - This is really good.
This is going to cook a whole farm.
- No. - No, but this...
- With this... - We will...
- show you how strong the flame is. - We will show you.
- But... - This is locked.
Am I allowed to reject this offer?
- Have a look first. - Yes, have a look.
- How do you work this? - Well...
- Do you not know how to use it? - I'm telling you this first,
we received permission from the fire station.
- We have permission. - If you do take this,
we will give you this for free.
(If you take it, we will give you a fire extinguisher for free.)
We will give it to you. It's for free.
- Just in case. - Use it while you're cooking meat.
Try it. It should work.
(We will show it to you straightaway.)
Is this how it works?
- Wait. - Hold on.
This works well.
- Hold on. - Don't worry about it.
I'm quite disappointed about the show.
- Look. - You called to show me this?
(Please work)
- It's not even working. - You can't see because it's bright.
- It's working. - What is this?
What is this?
Wait, it's working.
It's working.
- It's working. - It is.
(A small fire ignited a flame successfully.)
- Do it again. - Try it again.
You have to keep pumping it.
- You have to pump it. - Do it.
(They're working hard together.)
You need three people for this.
Keep pumping.
The oil is dripping out.
It's too strong right now.
(After one fire show,)
(the flame weeder cools down.)
Is it broken?
(The oil drips out instead of a flame.)
The gas should come out.
Urine is coming out instead of gas.
(The flame weeder is urinating on the street.)
- I guess it was urgent. - What's happening with this?
- I guess it was urgent. - This isn't going to work.
- Just take out the next item. - I was worried about...
my item when I came along.
- But I can't do this trade. - Hold on.
- It's a bluetooth speaker. - That looks alright.
I like listening to music when I go camping.
- A member of SF9... - Really?
used it.
On top of that, we have perfume...
- The shaver. - Take the shaver.
He needs it.
It's difficult to shave when you go camping.
- That looks good. - It's a shaver.
- We will give them to you as a set. - By the way,
- I prepared this after the call. - We need to see it too.
- I know. - I brought these.
- What is it? - It'll be unbelievable.
- What is this? - Well...
We haven't decided yet. We will after we have a look.
- Well... - Is this liquor?
They're all food.
(Se Yoon's item: Biscuits, nutritions, Chinese liquor)
It's around there.
I think we'll have to look into Se Yoon's bag.
(I think we'll have to look into Se Yoon's bag.)
- Sorry, but I heard everything. - Did you?
We just wanted to check what was in your bag.
This...
- Open it. - We have to blur out the bag.
- There's nothing to show in my bag. - Really?
There's something shiny in it.
- What is it? - What's that?
It's a golden ring.
(A hidden golden ring is discovered.)
(What is this?)
A golden ring.
- Was this on purpose? - No.
You took it off before coming here.
- This... - He has a reason behind this.
My mother...
told me that if...
I want more job offers from shows, I need to bring around gold.
I took off my wedding ring and wore it for two weeks.
- I lost two jobs after that. - Yes, that's right.
(A cursed golden ring that takes away jobs.)
- You took it off straightaway. - Yes, I did straightaway.
I was going to get rid of it or sell it. But I thought I should...
just carry it around, so I put it in my bag.
But since you have bad memories from it...
- You should... - You need to get rid of them.
Bad memories aren't good for the new year.
Since it's not a good memory, and my mother is okay with it.
- Are you sure it's okay? - It's okay.
Yes, I didn't even use it. It was mostly in the bag.
- Yes. - I see, okay.
Se Yoon, thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(A golden ring and snacks are swapped with SF9's items.)
Is it here?
We're at Jong Kook's kid's cafe.
- Hey. - Looks who's here.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello, excuse us. - It's quite big.
(Which customer is waiting at Jong Kook's stage?)
Where is he?
Hello.
Are you faking it?
Why are you pretending to work hard?
Why are you standing like that?
(Actor Oh Chang Seok, Jong Kook's gym buddy.)
(A handsome and tall guy)
(A handsome actor with great acting skills.)
(He was also So Min's partner...)
(in the drama, "Princess Aurora".)
- Sorry for this Chang Seok. - No problem.
Sorry for disturbing when you're working out.
- I know how it feels... - Hello.
to be disturbed while you're at the gym.
- Not a problem. - You look like you were waiting.
- You look dressed up for this. - No, not at all.
(It's what I usually wear.)
- Really? While you listen to music? - I usually dress like this...
and always listen to music.
(Chang Seok is fashionable at the gym, and music is a must.)
Are you always dressed well?
- Yes, I do. - Hold on.
Chang Seok should be on our show properly.
- I know. - Exactly.
- I heard the rumors. - Why didn't you?
Well, I never got asked,
but I think featuring like this is enough.
- No, you have to come one day. - No, it's okay.
- You should... - I heard his sense of humor...
- He... - Not at all.
- He's not like how he looks. - He looks normal but...
he's actually very unique.
I'm cost-effective.
(I'm cost-effective.)
That was a great line.
- Chang Seok. - Yes.
If you have any good items...
- Like what I mentioned earlier... - But...
I got the call this morning.
I heard that others were bringing audio equipment.
I looked around the house the whole morning.
For me,
I used to like collecting shoes.
Yes, that's a well-known fact.
I don't buy them nowadays. But I still have them.
So I brought a few pairs.
- That's great. - Perfect.
- Is it okay if they're worn? - It's okay.
It's okay. Can we have a look?
Yes, sure.
- There they are. - There they are.
This isn't an expensive pair.
- It's just running shoes. - Running shoes.
But once you wear them,
This is a great item to those who collect shoes.
- Really? - Yes.
- Is it worth it? - Yes, it is.
This is a worthy item.
This is an approved item to those...
- who like collecting shoes. - Really?
We got something big from him.
- Yes, and our item... - Yes, our item.
You have to explain it properly.
- You like collections, right? - What kind of collections?
- You like collaborations too. - A collaboration...
To put it in simple words,
you like collecting items that are worthy.
Look at it this way.
- It's like how Bob Marley... - Bob Marley.
gave something to Michael Jackson.
- His signature is on it too. - Bob Marley signed it.
You can look at it that way.
- It's a limited edition. - Is it?
- It is limited. - Okay.
- I can't even purchase it. - None of us can.
You can't purchase it. There's only one of it in this world.
The only one...
But this is...
This...
(To Michael Jong Kook from Ha Marley)
This is Haha's RGP album.
- Haha gave this to me... - Is it a CD?
"Jong Kook, my only partner."
"I love you". He signed it for me.
It's like how Bob Marley signed an album for Michael Jackson.
That's how much it's worth.
(He's done with the promotion.)
There's no way I can listen...
to a CD as of now.
- But thank you very much. - You can listen to it in the car.
- You can't open it though. - That's right.
You have to keep it like this.
- Yes. - Just in case,
if something happens to one of us,
- It's going to be worthy. - It'll become worthy.
- You never know. - I guess.
Yes.
(Feeling bitter)
Your expression tells us everything.
- I can't hide my feelings. - He's disappointed.
- He's an honest guy. - He can't hide anything.
I can't hide it.
- You have to show it. - Shorry took the hat.
He was actually going to take this, but...
- Did he change it? - I was handing it to him but...
he suddenly changed his mind.
The collaboration between Bob Marley and Michael Jackson.
The collaboration or...
the handmade hat.
Choose one.
(He didn't even look at the CD and chose the hat.)
He likes fashion.
Really...
I think I'll really love this hat.
(He feels bitter too.)
He suddenly wanted the hat.
I think anyone would've taken the hat instead.
(He says it firmly.)
(An honest confession)
You can at least use the hat.
That was a big blow.
- I don't have a CD player. - That's right.
I guess CDs are old-fashioned now.
- This is just a collected item. - Look at him.
He looks normal, but he's actually...
Inside this, there's a RGP badge.
- That's right. There's also a tape, - Yes, that's right.
It's also meaningful since it's a gift from me.
It's been passed on between us.
I really respect him as a friend.
I really like him.
Then you should do something together.
- Also... - Moreover,
- you'll receive... - That's right.
10 free lessons from coach Kim Jong Kook.
(10 free lessons from Coach Kim Jong Kook)
(Hold on)
I have something to say about this.
Jong Kook... To be honest...
People can...
People might think that I avoid you...
- because I dislike you. - I guess.
So please make no misunderstanding.
But that's not it. I really like him personally.
But at the gym...
- You haven't experienced it, right? - I haven't.
It's exhausting.
You don't know the limit.
(Jong Kook doesn't know when to stop.)
Son Heung Min limped off the field.
You're right.
If I had his body,
- I can't go to work. - Right.
I am not planning to be like him!
But it seems like he wants to make everyone like him.
(Jong Kook wants to turn everyone like him.)
That's what he wants.
I'm not exaggerating,
Jong Kook exercises like this.
He turns the volume to max, mostly hip-hop.
This is how he does it.
- Can I show them? - Yes, you can.
Do you think you can?
Show us, use the equipment.
Let's say he was using this.
And he'll be like...
I'm for real.
(Getting into position)
[VIU Ver] SBS E443 Running Man
"Unboxing Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
He'll be like... I'm for real.
(Getting into position)
(Shouting)
(Exclaiming weirdly)
Oh, that is tasty!
(3 sentences summary of Jong Kook's workout)
(Weird shoutings and, "Oh, that is tasty!")
(The gym to Jong Kook is a five-star restaurant.)
Oh, that is tasty!
- He says that? - That is too tasty!
I mean,
Jong Kook.
You're not in a restaurant.
- Why are you saying it's tasty? - It is tasty, isn't it?
- That is tasty! - Wow, that's crazy.
So he's feeding his biceps,
and he thinks it's tasty.
Jong Kook!
- It's cool, isn't it? - It's very cool.
- It's very unique. - I'm in style.
Well, thank you.
(Chang Seok switched his collection of rare shoes...)
(with Jong Kook and Haha's CD.)
(All teams have exchanged their items.)
You're already here!
Hello.
Hi, I'm the host of today's unboxing auction,
Jo Jeong Sik, a newscaster of SBS.
(All the goods will be appraised with our special guest, Jeong Sik.)
He's good-looking.
First, I will introduce you to our evaluators...
who will help with the assessment.
Really?
He is a fair friend of mine.
We will begin with today's evaluation.
Which team would like to start?
- We'll be evaluated first. - Let's do that one first.
We have here that was eaten by Qin Shi Huang.
Qin Shi Huang?
(Team Seok Jin has the flame weeder, various supplements, and gold ring.)
We'd like to have this one evaluated first.
Many people have coveted this, but we didn't sell it.
- People did covet this. - Many people did.
It's a flame weeder.
It breathes flames and burns those little weeds.
We could've exchanged it with a costly bracelet,
- but we decided not to. - She's right.
This one will be evaluated by Park Ki Young.
This looks like scrap metal.
(This looks like scrap metal.)
(He takes the magnet to it.)
(The magnet stuck to it!)
Mr. Park.
Wait, he's using the magnet.
(It's magnetic scrap metal, will it affect the estimated value?)
He's using the magnet.
- Did you figure out its material? - Yes, I did.
Let's weigh this.
- It should be weighing a lot. - It's heavy.
- It must be heavy. - Wow.
- It's almost 3kg. - 3kg?
(This flame weeder weighs almost 3kg!)
It's 3kg. Goodness.
- Are you finished? - Yes, that's it.
- Wait, that's it? - Yes.
(Evaluation was finished in a minute.)
That's it?
How is it over?
- Do some more! - It's over already?
- It's... - Please look at it again!
- That was it? - You're done?
Okay. 1, 2, 3, show us the price!
(All he did was stick a magnet and put it on a scale.)
(What will the price of the flame weeder be?)
- 1 dollar? - 1 dollar!
(It is priced 1 dollar.)
- One dollar? - That's just mean.
This kind of hurts.
Just one dollar?
You only estimated it as scrap metal?
Yes, unfortunately.
If you sold this on a secondhand site, you could get more.
- But for us, - Excuse me, sir.
Are all non-magnetic stuff of no use to you?
- Yes, this is only scrap metal. - It's just metal.
(If it's magnetic, it is useless to a recycling expert.)
How much if it wasn't magnetic?
If it wasn't,
I'd say about three dollars.
(So non-magnetic is better?)
- Non-magnetic is better? - Yes, it is.
Why is that?
Because then it means it's stainless.
If it's magnetic, it's junk.
- I see. - Yes.
So non-magnetic was better!
Okay, one dollar.
I think you will be surprised by this one.
(It's the gold ring from Se Yoon.)
- A ring? - Is that gold?
- A gold ring. - Is that gold?
- A gold ring. - This is real gold.
- It's 24 karat. - A 24 karat gold ring.
- Who gave you this? - What did you swap this with?
- It was... - Try this on.
Seok Jin, are you sure?
(It fits right into Jae Seok's finger.)
No, this is bad.
Se Yoon lost 2 shows after wearing this.
Oh, really?
(Se Yoon lost 2 shows after wearing this.)
So his plan was to put this ring...
on your finger so you can focus on Running Man only.
He wanted to make Running Man your one and only show.
We have a 24 karat gold ring on the table.
He pulled out a magnifying glass!
This is serious, he's serious.
He's got a flashlight, too!
It was about time.
What if it's fake?
It looks a bit crooked...
- I think it's real. - Yes, I think so, too.
What matters now is the weight.
It depends on its weight.
This one has taken the longest yet.
Should we use the magnet?
(The metal evaluator steps forward.)
The magnet?
- The magnet. - The magnet?
(It's supposed to be real gold.)
Does it stick?
- Does it stick? - No, it doesn't.
It could be just copper.
- You mean plated? - I hope that's the case.
- Just copper plated with gold. - Please reveal your price.
(It's definitely not junk. The price for the gold ring is...)
(420 dollars)
- 420 dollars! - 420 dollars?
(Se Yoon, you're the best!)
(The high price of the gold ring rattles the nerves of other teams.)
That's expensive.
They have a total of 600 dollars.
(Team Seok Jin's total: 606 dollars.)
Let's move on to our second team's items.
These are our first items.
We will go with fashion items.
Young Jin, try to be more difficult.
Expert Oh Young Jin is up for the first time.
This one has Shorry's pride on the line.
You can't get these anywhere else, even if you wanted to.
(Rummaging through the clothes)
You can find these at vintage shops around Hongdae.
(You can find these at vintage shops around Hongdae.)
But not this particular brand.
- This brand... - You can't find it.
(Sighing)
He's tilting his head!
(He's trying to make up his mind.)
- He's tilting his head! - Just be straightforward.
Young Jin!
- You are on television. - I guess they are not worthy.
You're the expert, so just go ahead.
You can find this particular brand at vintage shops.
Where!
(He gets personal.)
- Haha. - Take it easy.
- We want fair evaluations! - Why would you say that?
No, I was just...
He can't make a fair decision if you act so childish.
- There are many places. - No, what I meant was...
why couldn't you find one for me the last time I asked?
- There's this exact brand at shops? - Not the bigger sizes, though.
You won't be able to find bigger sizes of these.
They usually have women's sizes.
Oh, this one's for women.
(It was for women.)
Okay! He's an expert for sure.
He's very honest.
He's just trying to make me feel bad.
(He feels hurt somehow.)
Please come up with the total price.
- Yes, of course. - The total of all those.
They have a ton of those at Dongmyo.
- Namdaemun and... - You'll find a ton of those...
- if you go to Dongmyo. - For like 2, 3 dollars.
I've seen a hundred people wearing those at Dongmyo market.
Dongmyo is a very hip place.
The evaluation is done.
It is?
(The total price of clothes from Shorry is...)
(155 dollars.)
155 dollars.
(Well, that's not too bad.)
That's actually a fine price.
How are those so expensive?
- Okay, alright. - Okay.
That's actually a generous price.
- It really is. - That's a bit too much.
Okay, we've got more.
We have an ace in the hole. Sang Yeob gave us...
his family heirloom.
(That is no ordinary item.)
- What is that? - It looks expensive.
Expert Jung Se Woon could be drooling over this one.
That looks genuine.
(It has a unique aura not like the previous items.)
This could be very expensive.
Look at the details on the legs.
(The detailed touch almost brings them to life.)
(He carefully begins to appraise.)
You can tell how old it is.
Is it magnetic?
Of course, it's not...
(It stuck. It is scrap metal!)
- It stuck! - It's magnetic?
It's magnetic! That must be cheap.
It's cheap when it's magnetic.
That can't be right.
(She's disappointed.)
Is the bottom one magnetic, too?
- No, it's not. - Thank goodness.
Please look at it carefully.
It's been used quite often.
This is made of iron,
but this is made of bronze.
Is it bronze?
- It's bronze. - It's really bronze.
Isn't it gold, silver, and bronze?
Is it really bronze?
How much is bronze?
(Opposite reactions make them excited about the appraised value.)
- What do you think? - They're discussing.
(They suddenly get serious about it.)
(They have high hopes.)
Please turn it around when I say so. Show us the price.
(The appraisal is done after a long time.)
(This is amazing.)
(He brought his family heirloom.)
If my parents find out, they'll kick me out.
(Sang Yeob brought it without telling his parents about it.)
(Looking rare and precious, it's hard to know how old it is.)
Sang Yeob's father is expecting a lot.
(How much is the price that everyone is hopeful about?)
It's 150 dollars.
(150 dollars?)
- We can still win. - It's worth about 150 dollars.
- We could win. - We'll win.
Could you explain?
There are many like this in Korea.
There are many, but this is clean.
(It's not rare, but it's well-kept.)
- Is it well-kept? - Yes.
If you keep it for a while, it'll be worth it...
to take to a museum.
(It's extremely valuable.)
- Really? - Yes.
For how long do you have to keep it?
It should be kept for over 50 years.
(It should be kept for over 50 years.)
- 10,050 years? - 50 years?
- About 50 years. - Right.
It'll be when Sang Yeob hands it...
down to his children.
- That's unfortunate. - It's okay.
(Team Jong Kook's appraisal is done.)
(Team Jong Kook's total: 526 dollars)
It's our turn.
We have antiques too.
I gave my cut-out for this.
- What's this? - This is...
It's very popular these days.
He brought this album.
(What is the item that he swapped his cut-out with?)
(LP record by Queen appears.)
It's an LP record by Queen.
(That's unbelievable.)
How did you get it?
(People get excited as they see Queen's album.)
- I saw this movie. - I see.
I found it terrible.
(This movie was terrible.)
Wait, was it terrible?
- It was terrible? - He was wearing a tank top.
It created a sensation all over the world.
It's a man who sings in a tank top.
Yes, but don't you know Freddie Mercury?
I know him, but he isn't my type.
What about as a recyclable?
I swapped it with cut-out.
- It's Queen's... - I'll weigh it.
- What are you doing? - Don't weigh it.
(I'll weigh it.)
(What are you doing?)
- What are you doing? - Don't weigh it.
What are you doing? You can't put it there.
- That's impossible. - That's harsh.
The whole world is crazy about Queen right now.
He puts everything on the scale.
Let's find out the price. Please turn it around.
(What's the price for LP record by Queen?)
- 40 dollars. - 40 dollars?
- We're satisfied with it. - Yes.
Does Team Jae Seok have two items?
No, we have one more.
(We have one more.)
- Do you have one more? - What did you change it to?
In the world... Be careful.
It could cause a sensation in the world.
Then why did you bring it in a plastic bag?
- Isn't that harsh? - Wait.
(Is the worldwide item inside a plastic bag?)
This is how people carry things in Dongmyo.
- He said it's a worldwide item. - Everyone hangs it on the wrist...
and carries it like this.
- Isn't it a worldwide item? - It's how it's done in Dongmyo.
Listen.
We're very careful about it.
What is it?
- Is it a brazier? - Is it incense burner?
Even the seller didn't know its value.
He gave it to us for the price that we asked for.
It's rusty.
- It means it's old. - Right.
(It looks more than 100 years old.)
He turned on the flashlight.
- Finally, he turned on the light. - He turned on the flashlight.
It should be weighed.
It should be tested with the magnet.
Sir, could you try and see if the magnet gets stuck?
Yes.
(The magnet sticks.)
(The magnet is...)
(stuck.)
Don't stick it.
- It sticks. - Don't stick it.
- Don't stick it. - Take it off.
- Come on. - Take it off now.
- Why would you stick the magnet? - Why would you?
- Why? - The sound was clear.
It could be a cultural asset.
- I was startled. - The magnet got stuck.
I was startled.
(He continues to appraise it carefully.)
- I'm curious about its value. - Me too.
(Those who are watching)
(Those who brought it)
(Everyone is curious.)
(How much is the item from Dongmyo worth?)
It's two dollars.
(2 dollars?)
(There must be an error.)
I knew it since you brought it in this bag.
- What is it? - Wait a minute.
- Why? - Listen.
We bought it for 13 dollars.
Isn't it quite old?
- It's about 10 years old. - 10 years?
(It's about 10 years old.)
- 10 years? - How is it so rusty?
- It's 10 years old. - Is it 10 years old?
Was it made when Running Man started?
It's made with iron, so when 10 years pass,
it gets damaged.
The total price is 742 dollars. It's the highest total.
742 dollars?
- I'm glad that we kept the guitar. - We did the right thing.
(We returned the items after the shoot.)
We'll start Unboxing Auction.
- What is unboxing? - What does unboxing mean?
It's an auction that takes place...
while we remove items from their boxes.
Gosh. He's an insider.
- He is. - Look behind you.
You'll see 50 boxes.
There are 40 types of items.
There are cellphones in 10 of them.
(There are cellphones in 10 of the boxes.)
- Cellphones? - Yes.
In 10 cellphones, there are 2 different instructions.
1 type of instruction is written on 5 cellphones.
Find cellphones with different instructions written on them.
Combine the sentences...
and clear the mission. Then you can go home.
(It's important to find cellphones with instructions written on them.)
- There are so many. - We have to find the instructions.
Discuss and decide which box...
- you'd like to start. - Shall we open a big box?
- All right. - Let's open up a big one.
- There's one in the back. - Seok Jin.
Hand it to me.
(Could it be in such a big box?)
This is great.
This is almost...
- It's in 1 of the 2. - It's very long.
Would you like to start with the big box?
- We'll start with a dollar. - One dollar.
- Jae Seok called a dollar. - Two dollars.
- 2 dollars. - 3 dollars.
3 dollars. 3 dollars?
- 4 dollars? - 5 dollars.
You can increase it by a lot.
13 dollars.
(Is he destroying his team?)
- Seok Jin. No. - 13 dollars?
- He doesn't have the right. - 13 dollars? Okay.
- 13 dollars? - We didn't call 13 dollars.
- How about 10 dollars? - 13 dollars?
- No. - Is 13 dollars the last call?
No, no.
20 dollars? We have 20 dollars.
- See? - 20 dollars?
- It could contain the instruction. - Right.
20 dollars? Anyone else? 1, 2, 3.
20 dollars? Okay.
(Team Jae Seok wins at 20 dollars.)
- We'll pay 20 dollars. - I wonder what's inside.
- This is why people watch unboxing. - Let's see.
- Unbox it now. - It'd be amazing if they get it.
That would be amazing.
(What will be in the first box?)
(What?)
(There's something inside.)
I told you that there was something inside.
(They find a cellphone and a mission card.)
Go to the gallery and check the instructions.
Were they inside?
(They can't believe that they found it in the first box.)
- Were they inside? - This is annoying.
We got it for 20 dollars.
- Seriously. - Were they inside?
(They get a cellphone with instructions.)
- That's amazing. - Go to the gallery.
Check the instructions.
- Okay. - I had a good feeling about it.
(What instructions will they find?)
(The sole of your left foot)
(What does it mean?)
(Mysterious)
I see.
Is there something?
- One isn't enough. - You can't know with one.
You need to find both.
- We need to find them. - Then we have to connect them.
Let's stay put.
- Keep it a secret. - Did you find something?
- Is there something written on it? - But...
(Someone becomes impatient as unlucky brothers do well.)
What are you doing, Seok Jin?
We'll know if we find one more.
- I have a good feeling about it. - Do you?
Seok Jin brought a box. Shall we proceed with it?
- Yes, how about this? - Okay, let's go.
We'll start the auction.
- 15 dollars. - We have 15 dollars.
- 30 dollars. - 30 dollars.
- They have a lot of money. - 38 dollars.
- 38 dollars. - We'll raise it to 50 dollars.
50 dollars? 50 dollars.
- 52 dollars. - 52 dollars.
- 60 dollars. - 60 dollars.
- 60 dollars is a lot. - 62 dollars.
- 62 dollars. - It's expensive.
62 dollars, 1, 2...
64 dollars.
(64 dollars)
- We called 62 dollars. - 64 dollars.
(Why did he increase his own price?)
We called 62 dollars.
- Seok Jin, we called 62 dollars. - Why?
That was our price. What's wrong with you?
- He's an auction machine. - 62 dollars is enough.
- What's wrong with you? - Don't say anything.
- There's definitely a cellphone. - 1, 2.
- 70 dollars. - 70 dollars.
We have 70 dollars. Is there more than 70?
- 1, 2. - 73 dollars.
73 dollars.
Just increase it by two dollars.
I want you to go beyond yourself.
- Is there 74 dollars? - 76 dollars.
He's my role model indeed.
(He goes beyond himself.)
That's not how you do it. Don't listen to others.
- 80 dollars. - 80 dollars?
- Come on. - He's like Usain Bolt.
He breaks his own records.
It's better to raise it high all of a sudden.
- 80 dollars? 1, 2. - 80 dollars.
Three.
I can't go over 80 dollars.
(Team Seok Jin wins at 80 dollars.)
Seok Jin picked the box himself.
We can't go over 80 dollars.
I hope he'll find a brick inside.
(What is inside Team Seok Jin's first box?)
Okay.
(Is there a cellphone as Seok Jin predicted?)
What is it?
(There seems to be something inside.)
(Is there another cellphone?)
What is it?
(Inside the box...)
- Wait. - There's something.
- What is it? - Wait.
"Guess what this item is used for."
"The team that wins this box..."
"has the right to answer the question first."
"If the team answers correctly,"
"they're paid two times more than the auction price."
"If the team doesn't answer correctly,"
"other teams get a chance to answer."
"If another team answers,"
"the auction price will be paid to the team."
This is the item.
What is it?
Do we guess what this is?
- Yes. - Let's see.
What is it?
Why did you buy it for 80 dollars?
If we answer correctly, we win 160 dollars.
Do we guess what it is?
- Yes. - I know.
- I think it's used this way. - What?
- Is it a mousepad? - Is it?
- Mouse? - It's for the mouse.
It can't be used as a mouse pad.
Isn't it used for bowling?
Do you put it on like this?
- Is it used for bowling? - That's amazing.
He's so smart.
(He tries to make Seok Jin believe him.)
He's gullible. Don't say things like that.
- That's amazing. - He's very clever.
- Give me your answer in 10 seconds. - What does it say?
10, 9.
(What does Team Seok Jin think it is?)
Seven.
(It's used for sports.)
- Five. - This is our answer.
It's to prevent your cellphone from slipping.
Is it a pad that is used to prevent your cellphone...
- from slipping? - Yes.
Is that your answer?
(Does it prevent the cellphone from slipping?)
Is that correct?
- You failed. - It's wrong.
(Team Seok Jin's answer is wrong.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Team Haha.
When you're exercising,
you put it on so that you don't get any callus.
Then you grab the weight.
If Team Haha answers correctly,
they'll take 80 dollars.
Jong Kook said that...
it protects the hand while lifting weights.
(Team Jong Kook's answer is a pad to prevent calluses.)
You failed.
(Team Jong Kook's answer is wrong.)
Let us take a look.
- Isn't it a pad? - I have no idea what it is.
You put it on your finger and use it.
Put it on like this.
Kwang Soo.
It's the foot.
(He changes the thinking.)
Isn't it for the foot?
You're right.
He's smart.
It's for the foot.
- It's to prevent you from slipping. - It's a foot pad.
Foot pad.
Foot pad? What is it used for?
It could prevent from slipping...
or getting calluses.
- That's it. - It's made with silicon.
Pad for the sole.
That's correct.
(Foot pad is the right answer.)
Kwang Soo. This is insane.
It's insane.
It was a pad for the foot.
That's right.
Goodness.
- Kwang Soo. - Let's escape.
(After getting a cellphone, Team Jae Seok gets another chance.)
Team Jae Seok had a lot of money from the start.
(I went beyond my limit, but Jae Seok takes the money.)
- We keep winning. - Let's go.
You got it right for 20 dollars.
(I have a good feeling about today.)
- This is it. - There are 10.
- We should get one of them. - Let's get it right.
Let's get it right.
We'll proceed with this box.
20 dollars.
- 20 dollars. - 20 dollars.
- 20 dollars. - 26 dollars.
- 20? 26 dollars. - 26 dollars.
- 30 dollars. - 30 dollars.
- 32 dollars. - 32 dollars.
- 40 dollars. - 40 dollars.
- I call 50 dollars. - 50 dollars.
- Right. - We have 50 dollars.
- 80 dollars. - 80 dollars.
80 dollars?
(So Min calls 80 dollars.)
- 90 dollars. - Team Jae Seok called 90 dollars.
100 dollars.
- 100 dollars. - Yes.
Why am I getting angry?
- 100 dollars. - Let's stop.
100 dollars, 1, 2, 3.
(Team Jong Kook picks the third box.)
(Team Jong Kook wins at 100 dollars.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
Okay.
- It'll definitely be in it. - This is it.
(What is in the third box?)
(Cellphone? Chance?)
I hope they get mud.
- We pick the box next time. - Okay.
(Curious)
(She opens the box.)
(There's something inside.)
Is it a cellphone?
(Is it another cellphone?)
See? I told you.
(There's a cellphone inside.)
Really?
See? I told you that I had a good feeling about it.
Didn't I tell you?
You two are amazing.
- I should have kept going. - It's disappointing.
There are only 10 out of 50 boxes.
It's unfortunate.
If I called a higher price, we'd have gotten it.
(What's the set of instructions written on the cellphone?)
(Is it the same as what Team Jae Seok found?)
(Or is it a new set of instructions?)
(Unfortunately, they got the same instruction as Team Jae Seok.)
- Okay. - What does it mean?
- I know. - We need the second set.
They could have the same set of instructions.
Jong Kook.
We'll start the auction with a dollar.
- I'm getting this one. - Which team will it be?
- 30 dollars. - 30 dollars.
- 50 dollars. - 50 dollars.
- Goodness. - 60 dollars.
60 dollars?
- They have a lot. - 60 dollars?
- 80 dollars. - 80 dollars.
- 100 dollars. - All right.
That's too high.
We have to open a box.
Why did you increase it all of a sudden?
- 120 dollars. - 120 dollars.
(Team Jae Seok keeps other teams in check.)
- They're so certain. - Team Jae Seok called 120 dollars.
- 125 dollars. - 125 dollars.
Se Chan called 125 dollars.
128 dollars.
My goodness. I called it.
You're annoying me.
He likes to call higher than himself during the auction.
He punches his own face and passes out.
(It's the best comparison.)
128 dollars. 1.
- 100. - 2.
130 dollars.
138 dollars.
- 138 dollars. - He doesn't listen to me.
- I'm sure about this. - Two.
- Three. - Okay.
138 dollars.
(Team Seok Jin wins at 138 dollars.)
It's taken.
I'll open it.
You don't have lucky hands.
(He opens the box.)
(There's something inside.)
I think they're doomed.
(It's a tangerine.)
Okay.
(No, there should be more.)
Good job, good job.
This is terrible.
It's a tangerine that cost 138 dollars.
Please enjoy it.
This is the charm of unboxing.
- Yes. - Of course.
Seok Jin is good at auctions.
He paid 80 dollars for a foot pad...
and 138 dollars for a tangerine.
(He wins 80-dollar foot pad and 138-dollar tangerine.)
- I'll try this. - Okay.
Next auction item is...
quite big.
We'll start the auction.
(What kind of item will be inside?)
- We bid 80 dollars. - What?
Kwang Soo bid 80 dollars.
- 80 dollars? - 80 dollars.
- Let's stop. - One.
Two.
3. It's 80 dollars.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(If they find the other set of instructions, the auction is over.)
He increased it up to 80 dollars all at once.
(What?)
- What is it? - Look at them.
- They're late. - They didn't get a cellphone.
(Is it a cellphone?)
(Inside the box is...)
80 dollars.
It's worth 80 dollars.
Delicious potato chips.
(They're potato chips instead of a cellphone.)
(Thank goodness)
(I thought it was a cellphone. That's unfortunate.)
I want some.
(Peekaboo)
(A snake that was hibernating appears.)
(That was surprising.)
It's a snake.
- I said that I wanted some. - That startled me.
This is upsetting.
Then...
how about this?
(The king of auction picks the sixth box.)
Have I ever been wrong?
We'll start the auction.
- We bid 30 dollars. - 30 dollars.
- 60 dollars. - 60 dollars.
63 dollars.
- 65. - 65 dollars.
- 74. - 74 dollars. 1,
2, 3.
(Team Seok Jin wins at 74 dollars.)
Seok Jin picked...
- the box. - It has potential.
- This time... - We're sure.
Ji Hyo, you open it.
- Have some chips. - Why?
(Please fall for the trick.)
What?
(Peekaboo)
(It's so much fun to tease Seok Jin.)
Goodness.
(He calms down and focuses on unboxing.)
He got startled.
(He finds something.)
Seok Jin got startled by it.
He just got startled.
He got startled by this too.
(It's those potato chips again.)
(After being startled by the snake, he's startled by potato chips.)
(There were the same potato chips inside the box.)
It's so funny to see Seok Jin startled.
What's that box, sir?
There are two boxes.
- These? - You can choose them too.
What are those? They look special.
- I pick this one. - Please move it.
That's the box.
I shouldn't have said anything.
- Why was I curious? - It looks different.
We'll start the auction.
- 20 dollars. - 20 dollars.
60 dollars.
Team Haha bids 60 dollars.
I bid 100 dollars.
- 100 dollars? - Let's stay out of it.
- Let's stay out. - I agree.
It's 100 dollars in an instant.
They have a lot of money. Let them earn more.
- Okay. - 100 dollars?
- We'll stop. - 1, 2, 3.
(Team Jae Seok wins at 100 dollars.)
Please open it.
(What's inside the white box?)
1, 2.
They get to choose again.
(There are three different boxes.)
What's this?
"Clear Lucky Box Mission."
"There's a Lucky Card in 1 of the 3 boxes."
"Dud in the other two boxes."
"If you pick the one with a Lucky Card,"
"you win two times your bidding amount."
(They win 2 times your bidding amount.)
It's two times the bidding amount.
I am not worried because both of them are unlucky.
I hope it's dud.
You and I will pick dud each.
- We'll pick the remaining one. - It'd be amazing if they get it.
- I'd respect them if they win. - Goodness.
Pick the one you want.
This one.
- You pick this one? - Yes.
- Take it out. - It's excluded.
Pick either 1 or 3.
(What will unlucky Jae Seok choose?)
I want to pick this one.
It's either 1 or 3.
- Please choose. - I'm confused.
I give you 10 seconds. 10,
9, 8, 7, 6.
Number three.
Number three is excluded.
We took out two duds.
- They picked number one. - Please.
One.
(Box 1 didn't get chosen by the unlucky brothers.)
In 1, 2...
(Will the unlucky brother's plan succeed?)
- The Lucky Card! - No way!
(They win the Lucky Card!)
- Are you serious? - My goodness.
They joined forces and found the Lucky Card.
- Unbelievable. - We picked two duds.
You and I... My goodness.
These are duds.
(The lucky brothers)
What is going on?
- We ruled these out. - This is incredible.
- Let's give them a big hand. - I got goosebumps.
(Haha got goosebumps.)
It's a good trick.
- No way. - It really is a good trick.
Two unlucky members turned the tables.
This is unbelievable.
This is crazy. This is unbelievable.
I am tearing up.
(He is moved.)
We will start the auction for this box.
- We bid 90 dollars. - 90 dollars.
- This is a disaster. - This is driving me crazy.
Kwang Soo bid 90 dollars. 1.
140 dollars.
- Haha bid 140 dollars. - 140 dollars.
- 150 dollars. - That's the highest bid.
This is driving me crazy.
152 dollars.
152 dollars. Seok Jin bid 152 dollars.
160 dollars.
- For goodness' sake. - It's the highest bid.
- 160 dollars. - Outbid us if you can.
- 160 dollars. - 165 dollars.
165 dollars.
180 dollars.
(How dare you!)
(My goodness.)
No, no.
(We can't outbid that.)
- 180 dollars. - 1, 2.
We shouldn't bid more.
Three.
That's a valuable box.
It seems that way.
This is a 180-dollar box.
Please. Please.
- What? - Please.
(What?)
What is it?
(Inside the box is a cellphone.)
- Again? - It's a cellphone.
- Since we don't have money... - Let it have the same instruction.
Please let it have the same instruction.
(Did they get the same instruction?)
Team Jae Seok acquired the second cellphone.
It's the same instruction.
- Okay. - It's the same instruction.
- Thank goodness. - Hurry up and pick a box.
Okay. They are done.
- It's the same instruction. - It's the same instruction.
(Did they receive the same instruction?)
(Are they acting after receiving the different instruction?)
They are acting.
Hold on, hold on.
Do they need to remove someone's name tag?
- Be careful. - It might be like that.
Be careful, everyone.
- Be careful, everyone. - This is hard.
Maybe it's their mission to remove Jong Kook's name tag.
We will start the bid for this box at a dollar.
20 dollars.
Team Seok Jin bid 20 dollars.
- 50 dollars. - 50 dollars.
- We bid 70 dollars. - 70 dollars.
- 80 dollars. - 90 dollars.
120 dollars. 120 dollars.
So Min bid 120 dollars.
Team Jae Seok, will you not place a bid?
- The highest bid is 120 dollars. - How much is it?
- 120 dollars. - It's too expensive.
120 dollars.
- We are not the type to overspend. - 120 dollars.
You have the most amount of money.
1, 2, 3.
- 150 dollars. - 150 dollars.
- 160 dollars? - 160 dollars.
- What? What is going on? - Stop him.
I think he is doing something.
(Kwang Soo suddenly gets up.)
(Jae Seok touches the sole of Kwang Soo's foot.)
The winners of this race are...
- Yu Jae Seok and Lee Kwang Soo. - Why?
(When their feet touched, the race ended.)
Yu Jae Seok and Lee Kwang Soo.
(Are Yu Jae Seok and Lee Kwang Soo the winners of this race?)
- Why? - What are you talking about?
(Why are they the winners?)
- What did they do? - Their feet...
Their feet touched.
The final mission was...
(The final mission was...)
What? Hold on.
(They received instruction through the first auction.)
(The sole of your left foot)
(Then they acquired a cellphone through the 8th auction.)
(Inside it...)
(was another instruction.)
(And the sole of another member's foot must clap.)
(The sole of your left foot...)
(and the sole of another member's foot must clap.)
It's the same instruction.
(To carry out the mission secretly,)
(they put on an act.)
(While the other members were focused on the auction)
(Clap)
(They succeeded to clap their feet.)
I was stopping Kwang Soo.
Is the race over?
Here is the prize of the day.
- What is it? - The prize.
Choose a box each from the remaining boxes.
We will give you what's inside the box.
(There are 41 remaining boxes.)
Even if there is a cellphone inside, will you give it to them?
Even if there is a cellphone inside,
- we will give it to them. - Really?
- That's incredible. - You must be happy.
- Really? - You must be happy.
That's incredible.
- I choose... - I am so jealous.
I choose the biggest box.
Okay.
How about the one on the bottom?
- Jae Seok is lucky these days. - He is lucky.
He chose a cellphone first.
- Right. - Seriously.
- That one. - This one?
(The lucky Jae Seok chooses a box after much deliberation.)
It's a small box.
(Will the box contain a cellphone?)
You never know.
Let's unbox in turns. Kwang Soo should go first.
(Kwang Soo unboxes first.)
- I am jealous. - I wonder what's inside.
- All right. - This is fun.
You will give them what's inside the box.
We will give them the entire thing.
(Will there be a cellphone inside?)
(He opens the box.)
There could be a person inside.
- There is nothing. - It's an empty box.
(Empty)
Take the box.
(They give him the entire thing.)
(Kwang Soo wins a huge box for a prize.)
- It's empty. - It could replace...
your cut-out that we exchanged.
Go inside the box to imitate the cut-out.
Go inside the box to imitate it.
(For goodness' sake.)
- Jae Seok. - All right.
I bet Jae Seok's box has something.
Jae Seok is lucky these days.
- I should win a prize... - That's right.
- if I am lucky. - That's right.
(There is a mission card inside the box.)
This is good.
- There must be a cellphone. - He is insane.
(Will he discard his old image and win a cellphone as a prize?)
It's a jump rope!
(A cellphone, my foot.)
It's a jump rope.
Jae Seok.
He is reverting back to his old self.
He is unlucky.
That was incredible.
That's Jae Seok.
(The door opens,)
(and a shocking sight unfolds before them.)
- Is it a room escape? - It's room escape game.
(Staff member A died in a mysterious way.)
Nobody move!
(The door gets locked again.)
(Is it a trap by the culprit?)
(Traces of the crime are scattered everywhere.)
(Find the clues and figure out the cause of death.)
(Search for the culprit begins in earnest.)
(The whole story gets revealed.)
(Who could be the culprit?)
(Case Number 444)
(The Invisible Danger)