- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
(The show starts at an amusement park.)
Jae Seok, are you trying to make us laugh with your outfit now?
- I'm sorry. - Is it starting today?
- What's wrong with your outfit? - Haha's outfit isn't ridiculous.
- That's why I wore this. - I must've influenced your outfit.
It was Oh Hyuk. Oh Hyuk influenced me.
- I'm Yu Hyuk now. - What is this?
- I'm Yu Hyuk. - My goodness.
- Oh Hyuk and Yu Hyuk. - Come on, unbelievable.
- I'm Oh Hyuk. - Okay, okay.
(Jae Seok, let's go shopping together.)
A newspaper agency ran a questionnaire recently.
It was about leading celebrities of the Korean Wave.
The first place went to...
Jae Seok.
(1st place of leading celebrity of Korean Wave, Yu Jae Seok)
I knew it. Of course.
- Yu Hyuk. - My gosh.
- It's thanks to my colleagues. - That's right.
It's all thanks to you.
- Yu Hyuk. - Thank you.
The second place went to...
(The next leading celebrity is...)
Lee Kwang Soo, comedian who used to be a model.
- Me? - You should work hard now.
- It's Kwang Soo. - Me?
That's so cool.
Great. Kwang Soo, the comedian got it.
That's right.
And Jong Kook was in fourth place.
This is so hot.
- Three were from Running Man. - This is so cool.
Are there any more?
And...
Look thoroughly. Look at the bottom.
It's been 20 years since Seok Jin made his debut.
Please take a close look at the list.
- Good luck. - Let's do our best!
(Let's do our best until the day Seok Jin rules Asia.)
- We can do it! - Let's do our best.
My gosh, Seok Jin...
- didn't make it to the list. - You should check thoroughly.
But he's the leading celebrity in riding coattails.
He is the best leading celebrity in riding coattails.
- He's barely riding the cattail. - I don't care what's I'm best for.
I don't care what it is for as long as I'm in first place.
You're barely making it. You barely made it to the coattail.
Before we start today's race,
you have gathered here today for a reason.
- What is it? - The episode aired yesterday.
It was because of the result for the most-searched words.
- That's right. Right. - My gosh.
(It's time to check the result.)
(Their mission was to be the most-searched name online.)
(With the support of popular guests such as...)
(EXID, SEVENTEEN, Kim Hye Yoon, and Han Bo Reum,)
(the race ended as Team Kim Hye Yoon won an additional keyword.)
Two teams accomplished to go viral online.
Who are they?
Two teams?
(Which 2 teams won 1st place?)
The first team is Team Han Bo Reum.
- Gosh. - Jong Kook.
- Bo Reum kept trending up. - That's right.
- It was Running Man Han Bo Reum. - Exactly.
And the second team is Team Kim Hye Yoon.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo were in 1st place of the list.)
And Kim Hye Yoon also was in first place.
- Right, right. - Yes!
Both the name of the team and her name topped the chart.
Gosh, Hye Yoon.
I bet people who didn't know who she was looked her up.
Therefore, the final victory goes to...
- It was long. - Bo Reum's name stayed there long.
- Her name lasted a long time. - Her name was on the list for long.
The word, Running Man Han Bo Reum...
(The duration in 1st place...)
stayed in 1st place for 49 minutes.
- 49 minutes? - That was long.
It lasted a long time.
And the duration for Running Man Kim Hye Yoon...
- You combined them. - and Kim Hye Yoon...
- It lasted quite long. - They'll combine the names.
(The duration of the names in 1st place is...)
- It's 29 minutes. - Really?
- Bo Reum stayed on the list long. - That long?
She went viral for that long? My gosh.
- Do we have a prize? - Yes!
- She stayed there for a long time. - We were so close.
All right.
Here's what the teams except for the winning team will do.
At this amusement park,
- there's Jecheon's special ride... - My gosh.
which is scarier than the pirate ship in Wolmi Island.
- The ride is on your right. - The engine is ready.
- We'll ride that? - I mean...
(Forget about the pirate ships you've been on so far.)
(The extreme angle of the pirate ship will test your guts.)
(When the ship goes up, you'll see the door to the other side.)
Is this one scarier than the one in Wolmi Island?
I think they might pass out. They're going to pass out.
However, only one team will be chosen to ride the ship.
- Just one team? - That's great.
Everyone, it's simple.
You'll play the Ghost Leg.
But we were able to go viral. Can you exclude us?
- That's right. - Sadly, you won second place,
- so we'll let you draw the lines. - That's great.
- Okay, okay. - I'll let you do that.
That's right. They had to win the whole thing.
(I'm so jealous.)
(They're designing the Ghost Leg seriously.)
- Should we stop here? - Yes.
- This is pretty good. - This is pretty good.
You should add one of these.
- You know what I'm talking about? - Right. Draw one more there.
Draw one more since there's a lot of space there.
- Here? - That's right. Just like that.
- There you go. Do that. - Okay.
- All right then. - My gosh.
- I'll pick. I choose number two. - You're better than me.
Number 2? Okay. We'll check number 2 first.
- Please! - This is for Seok Jin and Haha.
Please.
(We're making our way down.)
- Please, please. Please don't be. - Please.
(Will they be able to dodge the penalty?)
(What's the result?)
- We passed. We passed! - "Pass".
(Seok Jin and Haha will pass the pirate ship penalty.)
- I knew it. - Did you see that?
I'm so happy.
- Number 2 was good. Good. - Gosh, number 2 was the best.
- It's your turn, Ji Hyo and So Min. - You should pick.
- Ji Hyo and So Min. - You get lucky with these things.
- We'll go with number 3. - Number 3?
(Lucky Ji Hyo chose number 3.)
(All right! Number 3 is going down.)
- It's number one. Please! Please! - No, no.
Please, please.
(If they pass, Jae Seok and Kwang Soo will face the penalty.)
(It's Lucky Lady versus Unlucky Brothers.)
(Which team will face the penalty?)
(Will Ji Hyo be able to get lucky this time too?)
(Praise the Lady. Her luck will last forever!)
- This is amazing. - How is this possible?
I can't believe this.
- Who are you? - Seriously.
- This is so weird. - Why does it always happen to you?
What's wrong with you?
This is so weird.
They are the 1st and 2nd leading celebrities...
of the Korean Wave.
- How is this possible? - This is crazy.
- They are in 1st and 2nd places. - They are in 1st and 2nd places.
Go have fun, Jae Seok.
My gosh, this is so stressful. Seriously.
(This is so stressful. Seriously.)
Hello.
(They are devastated...)
(while the other members are just laughing.)
- They can't ride that. - Why not?
Look at this.
"Ugly people are not allowed to ride it."
Hey, Jae Seok!
- Where? - You can't ride it.
- Why not? - Both of you cannot.
(If you're ugly, you can't ride the pirate ship.)
(There's hope of exemption at the end of their despair.)
- What? - Ugly people can't ride it.
- It only works for Jae Seok. - Both of you.
(They are under-qualified with their ugly looks.)
Only Jae Seok can dodge this. What is this?
You can't ride that.
Hey, if you admit that you're ugly, you don't have to ride it.
That means you're uglier than Se Chan.
(That means you're uglier than Se Chan.)
(This is the biggest crisis ever since he's been branded as ugly.)
(You can only dodge the ride if you're ugly.)
(However,)
(you must admit that you are uglier than Se Chan.)
I can't believe that's a rule.
I can't be uglier than you, Se Chan.
(He can't bear to be uglier than Se Chan.)
(You must be uglier than me.)
- Okay, I got it. - You look so handsome!
- You look handsome. - They look down on me.
Kwang Soo, what are we going to do?
I'm going to throw up again.
(It's his natural reaction to the pirate ship.)
- That's for sure. - I'm going to throw up again.
Why did you draw the last one?
Why did you?
I only drew the last one, but you drew the rest.
(Jae Seok, we were both unlucky.)
Hey.
(Startled)
(They were laughing.)
(Terrified)
(It suddenly begins without a warning.)
- Hey, hey. That... - My gosh.
- I feel nauseous just by watching. - This is a scary ride.
Hey, it's going up high.
It's...
It's already...
My bottom is already lifting.
- My gosh. - It's going up really high.
It's going to go up higher.
My gosh, it's going up really high.
(The pirate ship is slowly approaching the underworld.)
Stop it. Stop it.
Sir, this is enough.
I might throw up.
- My gosh. - We're already going up high.
- Kwang Soo! - We're already high up!
- He's ugly. Why did he ride that? - Exactly.
How did this happen to them when we played the Ghost Leg?
(Their ugliness goes beyond Korea.)
(Their ugly looks are definitely contenders for the ugliest looks.)
(Not everyone can become a comedian.)
(You can be a leading celebrity of the Korean Wave with these looks.)
(They are the best on variety shows.)
Their bodies are lifting.
(The pirate ship is heading to the top.)
- I'm dizzy. Stop. - I'm dizzy.
- I'm dizzy. No! - No!
Stop it.
(To protect their looks, the ride will stop here.)
I'm so dizzy.
We're done. Gosh, we're done now.
It's over now. Good job.
(The pirate ship is over. Good job.)
Well done.
It doesn't mean that you're handsome because you rode it.
(They carried out the penalty.)
- It means you're not ugly. - They're not ugly.
Everyone, today's special episode...
will air on May 5 for the Children's Day.
(Look forward to it.)
It's Children's Day.
Recently, this guest has been filming a movie with children...
and claims that he knows a way to the hearts of children.
He has come back as an actor whose movie sold 16 million tickets.
- I'll introduce today's guest. - Who is it?
- 16 million tickets? - 16 million tickets?
16 million tickets?
- The carousel is turning. - Who is it?
(When the carousel starts turning, the guest shows up.)
(Who is today's guest?)
- It's Dong Hwi. - Dong Hwi.
Dong Hwi.
("Extreme Job", 2nd highest-grossing movie)
(The man of 16 million audience captivated Korea.)
(His hobby is talking to himself.)
(His special talent is looking at the camera.)
(He's a mysterious man whose mind can't be read.)
(This time, he's here as a solo guest.)
(He returns as the man of 16 million audience.)
- Dong Hwi. - You're the solo guest today.
- Dong Hwi. - Did you come here alone now?
- What an entrance. - Is he the only guest today?
You're the only guest now.
(He's on edge.)
- Where is he going? - He passed us.
He's the only guest today. My gosh.
- Gosh. - Come here, Dong Hwi.
- Hello. - Hi.
I love this guy. He looks suspicious.
Come to the center.
- He just looks suspicious as he is. - Dong Hwi.
Jae Hoon, come here.
Tak Jae Hoon?
- You look just like him. - Right.
- You look like him even more. - Seriously.
Is he the only guest?
- He's the only guest now. - He's the only guest?
Recently, he was here for his movie, "Extreme Job".
- He joined us in January. - Right.
- I didn't know he'd be here alone. - Now, he's the only guest.
It's an honor.
Your movie, "My First Client",
- will be released on May 22. - Yes.
Our movie centers around an ordinary guy.
After he faces an incident...
Is it the way you talk?
You're talking half-heartedly.
(You're not qualified to promote your movie.)
- If you don't want to, don't. - No, no.
- It's the tone. - If you don't want to, don't.
- I'll try harder then. - Why don't you try to sound happy?
Why don't you try to sound happy?
Our movie centers around an ordinary guy.
(Sounding energetic)
I sound angry.
But it doesn't look like you're giving your all here.
(I can see it in your face.)
That's what I see.
I mean, he works hard, but it doesn't look like it.
It looks like he's being lazy.
He has the face of a lazy guy.
Everyone, today's special episode is for Children's Day.
Today's race was designed...
by the youngest writer, Lee Ha Neul, of Running Man's crew.
- Really? - Really?
- I'm curious. - What did she come up with?
It's the Case of Missing Names.
(Children's Day Special Episode: the Case of Missing Names)
- Missing names? - Missing names?
(What does that mean?)
The names are missing?
Everyone, do you know how Children's Day came about?
- Bang Jeong Hwan. - That's right.
Back in the days, children weren't properly addressed.
- "Baby", "youngster", - Really?
or "kids". These were how they were called.
the word, "child", didn't exist then.
- It didn't. - Really?
Bang Jeong Hwan came up with it.
Bang Jeong Hwan found it sad they weren't properly addressed.
He gave them a word for their entity, "child".
To celebrate the day when they were recognized as separate entities,
Children's Day was created.
- I didn't know. - I had no idea.
- I had no idea. - Seriously.
Right now, all of your precious names...
- are gone. - Who did that?
(The names of the members are missing.)
- Our names? - Our names are missing?
- Again? - We don't have names?
(Grabbing)
It's you, right?
- You're the culprit. - He's here for a reason.
This is why you came.
I'm sure they gave you a big role, the culprit.
- There's no culprit today. - There isn't?
- I'm sorry. - He's a victim too.
- I'm sorry. - That's right.
- Sorry. - You'll break into three teams.
The team that finds the names first will win.
As teams?
- We must find our names. - Everyone's names?
All right. The team leaders for each team...
will be the dads who know a lot about...
how children feel.
(The Avengers of Fathers)
Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Haha will be the team leaders.
- He's a dad. This is so weird. - Seok Jin.
Actually,
the youngest has 3 kids, I, 2, and the oldest, 1.
- That's right. - 3, 2, 1.
- Then, Seok Jin is at the bottom. - Right.
- He's at the bottom. - Hey.
- Say hello to them. - We'll use age.
Attention, attention, attention.
- What are you doing? - You're at the bottom. Attention.
My goodness.
You don't know anything about raising kids.
- Why don't I know that? - My gosh.
- He knows nothing. - I teach my kid a lot.
Seok Jin's wife raised his child all on her own.
You're at the bottom. Attention.
(Seok Jin is again riding his wife's coattail when raising their kid.)
- Team leaders, come this way. - Okay.
They're team leaders?
My gosh, I'm a team leader.
It feels weird to see Haha with them.
I can't believe I'm with them.
How about this?
- I would choose someone... - Okay.
- How do you want him to turn out? - how I want my child...
- to turn out. - That's the criteria?
- How I want my child to grow up? - Right.
Jae Seok, you have to choose me.
My mouth is protruding.
It has to be me.
You have to pick me then.
- You have to pick me. - You must choose him.
- You must pick me. - You...
- He's your son. - I made a mistake.
I shouldn't have said that.
- I shouldn't have said that. - He's your son.
- I shouldn't have said that. - Please find me, Dad.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin loses.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - You were so loud.
- I wanted to win. - He was so loud.
- Let's play it. Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok wins.)
It's Jae Seok.
All right. Let's find my son.
- It has to be me. - He's right there.
That's your son.
- Right. - Dong Hwi?
I bet that Dong Hwi has a big clue today.
Not at all.
- Okay, Dong Hwi. - Dong Hwi.
- Okay. Dong Hwi. - Thank you.
- Yes, this is understandable. - I chose Dong Hwi.
Then, I have to be Haha's daughter.
- Why? - I love daughters.
- I want to have daughters. - What?
He's the coolest and the most handsome dad.
- You're so pretty. - He is.
If I want a daughter, I want a pretty daughter like you.
- Dad. - Daughter.
(Sighing)
I have no choice.
It's Children's Day. And she's young.
So Min!
- Come here. - I'm a kid.
- Come here. - Dad.
(Acting cute)
- You're scary. - She's scary.
My gosh, she was scary. She was scary.
(It's Seok Jin's turn next.)
- Seok Jin. - Me?
You're not trying to get on my team.
You're not trying.
Jong Kook, why did you lower your head?
- Look at Seok Jin. - My neck hurts.
(Pushing him away)
Why does it hurt all of a sudden?
- Will knowing about kids help? - That's right.
- Lee Kwang Soo! - Okay.
(Lee Kwang Soo!)
Did you just pick me?
(In a daze)
- Did you choose me? - Of course.
- Yes, you must choose Kwang Soo. - He lowered his head.
Here's what we'll do next.
- There are six of us. - Okay.
- They will choose their teams. - Okay.
- They'll play rock-paper-scissors. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins.)
Okay. I won.
Dad.
(Dad)
(The Protruding Father and Son meet again.)
He's driving me crazy.
- This is crazy. Goodness. - We have the same mouths.
- Come on, seriously. - We have the same mouths.
- Okay. - We have the same mouths.
I'll...
go to Haha's team to even out the genders.
- I can do that, right? - I'll go to Seok Jin then.
Okay!
- Jong Kook! - Hey.
- My gosh. - Two siblings that get along well.
- This was bound to happen. - I tried so hard to dodge you.
(The teams are formed.)
And right now,
- your names are missing. - Okay, okay.
Until you retrieve your names,
- you'll have temporary names... - Really?
that you'll use as your name tags.
They're not proper names.
- What is this? - This doesn't feel good.
No, it doesn't.
I don't want to be called so.
"This One", "The Other One", "That One".
- "This Guy", "That Guy". - I like "Joe".
- Yes. - Right.
- You can take "Baby". - Okay.
(She likes it more than her own name.)
- Which one should I pick? - I like this.
- I like this nickname. - You're Baby.
- "Child". - Yes.
- I'll use this one. - Okay.
Hold on. Which one should I pick?
(Next is Team Jae Seok's turn.)
- Do these. - We'll use these.
- Don't. - We'll pick these.
- Okay. - That's good.
"This Guy", "That Guy", and "Hey, There" are left.
(These are the remaining ones.)
Kwang Soo can take "Hey, There."
But...
You should do "This Guy" and "That Guy".
Hey, There.
- "This Guy", "That Guy". - I hate being called this.
- This Guy! - This Guy, That Guy!
This Guy!
- My gosh. - Feels like I'm a servant.
I'm going crazy.
(They pick their new names.)
Baby!
Baby is coming!
Baby is here!
Baby!
(She's an old baby.)
- Baby. - Yes?
You're not "Babe", but "Baby".
This Guy!
- Hey. - This Guy!
- I was just calling you. - Hey.
That Guy!
He looks weak.
(Scribbling)
What did you write?
(Jae Seok wrote something.)
- What is it? - He wrote something.
(So Min used to be called Baby.)
- He changed your name to Gill. - It's Gill.
- Gill. - Gill.
He's so mischievous.
He is.
What about mine?
- Petty man. - Petty man.
(It suits him better than "Child".)
Petty man?
That's perfect.
I'm Child.
This upsets me all of a sudden.
Okay. This game is...
a traditional game called The Aging Game.
(The Aging Game)
(The Aging Game?)
- The Aging Game? - Seok Jin has the upper hand.
(It's the best game for him.)
- I know. - He's already...
- old. - He's aging.
He doesn't have the upper hand.
He can't get any older.
You can't!
(Do I really have the upper hand?)
- You'll play at the same time. - Okay.
From this moment on,
you're all five-year-olds.
I'm five!
I'm five! So Min is five.
- Seok Jin... - Seok Jin...
reacted to being five years old,
but no one responded.
He didn't look cute at all.
I'm five.
- No one responded. - I'm five years of age.
"Five years of age"?
- 5 years of age! - 5 years of age.
- He is five years old. - I am.
Since the opening scene,
Seok Jin kept nudging me towards Ji Hyo.
Is it because she's sick?
He dragged me.
Come on.
- It's because she's sick, right? - You're...
- too harsh. - He's been doing that all along.
This Guy and That Guy...
- are impossible. - What?
- My gosh. - Not me, though.
- You're both impossible. - Not me!
Hey, There.
- I'm just... - You're impossible.
- "Impossible" should be a name. - Come on.
- It's not like that. - I know.
- Gosh. - That's too harsh.
(We'll be nicer.)
Okay. You have 10 minutes.
- 10? - Yes.
In the given time, the team that has...
the oldest age accumulated wins.
Okay. How do we age?
You can touch the opponent who is younger than you.
If you're the same age,
play rock-paper-scissors and win.
In these cases, you'll gain five years.
But let's say your opponent...
is older than you.
If you hold hands with your teammate,
your ages will be added.
However,
both of you who have won or lost...
need to go home and tell your moms about it.
- We need to touch them? - That's how it gets recorded.
There are rabbits tied to the poles.
(Their rabbit moms are waiting.)
There's a way...
- to turn the tables. - What is it?
If your opponent touches your house,
their age will double.
(The one who touches someone else's house will double their age.)
We shouldn't let them get near our house then.
- You need to defend. - Someone needs to stay behind.
If the defender touches you during your attempt,
- your age will become zero. - Okay.
Your age becomes zero.
Then we can be aggressive, right?
But if we touch you near our house,
we will take your age.
How about we touch you like this?
- Hold on. - What will you do about it?
Touch.
(Touch)
(They will get beaten up.)
- Joe. - Hey.
- Joe. - This was not the touch we meant.
This is...
This is for Children's Day.
- This is for Children's Day. - That's not the touch we meant.
Joe!
- That's quick. - You can't do that.
- You're fast. - We can do that?
- Okay. - Fine.
(I'll get aggressive too.)
(Joe is ready to go.)
The winning team...
will get four syllables of their names back.
One of us will get our name back.
You're right.
- You get it, right? - However,
if the syllables you've picked...
are also in your opponents' names, they'll retrieve them as well.
For example, let's say that Team Jae Seok won...
- and picked "Seok". - Seok Jin.
Then Seok Jin will also get a "Seok".
Really?
- That's not good. - No, it isn't.
"Lee" isn't good either.
- There's Lee Kwang Soo. - You're right.
- I don't overlap with anyone. - He doesn't have one either.
Our last names don't overlap.
- You're right. - Our last names don't overlap.
Except for the winning team,
all of those who haven't yet find their full names...
will be penalized.
What?
- Then within your team... - It's a competition.
- All right. Please spread out. - Let's go.
- Where should we go? - Let's go to our house!
We need to win at rock-paper-scissors.
(They start off at their respective houses.)
This is a serious game. It's frightening.
(Team This One, Team This Guy, Team Child)
Jae Seok, one person needs to be on defense.
You're right.
Dong Hwi, do you want to do it?
I can do whatever.
Then you can go out there.
- We need to take turns anyway. - Right.
(Jae Seok will defend while the others attack.)
- Then... - I'll stay. I need to guard here.
Right. If we win once,
we'll be able to conquer this field.
- We need to hurry. - The sum of our ages is big.
- Okay. - So go attack.
(Okay, let's do this.)
Let me tie my shoelaces first.
Since that's too far,
- we'll attack that one. - That one.
That one?
If you and I hold hands, we're 10 years old.
(They plan to target Team This Guy that is closer.)
If we hold hands and attack, we'll win for sure.
- We need to attack as a team first. - Right.
- Okay. - It's better than anything.
Someone needs to stay behind to guard here.
Let's take turns.
Sure.
You need to run a bit first.
You're the most likely to succeed.
So catch one of them.
- What? - The first rock-paper-scissors...
- is very important. - You just want to stay behind.
(Ji Hyo is sharp.)
No, that's not it.
This Guy.
Don't call me that when it's just us.
- This Guy. - This punk.
- What did you say? - Enough.
That Guy.
(Their teamwork crumbles from the start.)
Do you want to just give up?
- What do you mean? - No.
- Hey, That Guy. - We can't give up.
You punk.
- The countdown will start now. - Let's go!
- Get ready. - Let's go!
That team is going the same way.
Should I stay behind?
- No, you can come out this much. - Then...
- It's too far. - They might run towards us.
They're coming towards us.
- Let's protect this. Touch this. - They're coming.
Why are they coming?
- Why are they coming? - We just need to touch this.
One of them...
They need to do rock-paper-scissors anyway.
Let's go.
They plan to hold hands.
- Do you want to catch them? - Let's do that.
- Hey. - We have the same plan.
(They all thought the same.)
No, wait a bit.
If we all hold hands,
- we'll catch them. - Right.
We just need to hold hands.
If they all hold hands,
- we'll lose. - Right?
We'll lose.
But since So Min is slow,
we can run away from them if they try to hold hands.
We'll walk this way and then dash to the left.
To the left.
Get ready. Come with me. Let's go.
(They run towards Team This Guy's house.)
They're coming.
Our house is guarded, though.
- Ji Hyo, guard our house. - She's guarding it.
(As long as she's touching it, they have the upper hand.)
They're coming here.
(They plan to counterattack.)
- Grab them! - We need to grab hands!
(Meanwhile, Team Child's house is unguarded.)
(While running away, Dong Hwi heads towards the house.)
Let's go.
(Our house is in danger!)
Wait! Two of us won't make it!
(Team Child returns back home.)
We need to run!
(Come here.)
(Joe is here! Let's run away!)
Jae Seok, guard our house.
Those punks.
(How dare they?)
Gosh, I'm already exhausted.
Are you all right?
I ran for a brief moment.
(He's completely out of energy.)
Shall we go again?
I'll go over there.
- Don't lie. - Se Chan is behind you.
- Don't lie. - He's behind you.
- Move away! - Shall we have a match?
You have to touch this.
- Let's touch Haha. - Behind you!
(How dare they target our house?)
We can just pick one.
(They target Haha.)
(They're both the same age now. They should do rock-paper-scissors.)
Rock-paper-scissors?
(He attempts to touch Kwang Soo...)
(but fails.)
Seok Jin! Hurry!
Seok Jin!
Should we go together?
(Seok Jin needs to come to win.)
(However, it's That One and The Other One.)
Get lost.
- We can catch one of them. - Right.
(They go on a hunt as a team.)
(No matter how much Kwang Soo cries out, Seok Jin stays behind.)
- Should we go together? - Hurry up and help him!
- We can catch him. - Get lost.
Touch!
(They touch Kwang Soo.)
- We did it. - We touched Kwang Soo!
(Dong Hwi and Se Chan successfully touch him.)
- We touched him. - We touched Kwang Soo.
Let's go back over there.
Why didn't you come?
Why didn't you?
(They each gain 5 years.)
Hold on. Let me go.
Good job.
(He has exhausted all his energy.)
Jae Seok.
(Trudging)
- Come here. - Jae Seok.
We need to tell her.
- Right. - Tell Mom.
- Mom. - Mom.
- What was my name again? - It's That One and The Other One.
- Mom. - Mom, we...
- caught that punk. - We touched...
- that punk. - Good job.
We're 25 years old now.
- That's great. - We're invincible.
(Team This One is 25 years old in total.)
(They now have the upper hand.)
- We're older now. - Yes.
Dong Hwi, you look very pale.
- Are you all right? - This is only the beginning.
I'm...
Can I make it?
- Seok Jin. - Go, Seok Jin.
Why didn't you come...
- when I asked for you? - I was...
I was guarding our house.
Come to your senses, will you?
- You... - This is not the time...
- to joke around. - You only looked that way.
- They were creeping up behind you. - You can't stay behind.
- They're both 10 years old, right? - Yes.
Yes.
If they hold hands, they're 20.
Even if the three of us hold hands, we won't make it.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Guard it.
(Let's form an alliance.)
Let's attack together.
Let's do this.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors and let one person win.
- Let's do it. - Okay, come here.
- Hurry. - Let's meet halfway.
- Come. - Hold hands.
Let's do it.
If they come, we need to run.
- Really? - Yes, we need to hurry.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - You want to do it?
- Hurry. - They're 10 years old.
It's okay if we form an alliance...
(They form an alliance.)
(However)
- Okay. - We did it.
(Kwang Soo suddenly runs away.)
- Hey. - Hey, he let go.
- We won! He let go! - You let go!
- You let go! - Touch.
(Kwang Soo touches their house.)
No, we won.
- Seok Jin and I high-fived. - We...
But Kwang Soo let go and ran.
Then we all get...
- 5 years more. - We're 10 years old now.
You touched him?
(Here's what happened.)
It's okay if we form an alliance...
(Before they high-fived, Kwang Soo let go.)
(Since it was 10 versus 15, Team Child received 5 years each.)
What happened?
(He helped the other team.)
We're a minus now.
- What? - We're a minus.
- Why? - Because it was the three of them.
I didn't think they would touch us.
(Team This Guy is 20 years old.)
- I can walk alone now. - Me too.
- I have nothing to fear. - They might not know.
- They don't know. - They might not know.
Did you win?
- I don't know. - You don't?
I don't think they won.
I have nothing to fear now, right?
Yes, we're all the same age.
But if they hold hands, we'll lose.
- That's true. - You're right.
Se Chan, come here.
How old is So Min?
- She's 5. - 5?
Hurry up. Come here.
(Se Chan, who's 10, approaches her.)
You don't have to run. You can do rock-paper-scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- How old are you? - Let's do it.
Come here. They shouldn't hold hands.
- They're younger than us. - Yes.
How old are you?
- 5. - You're 10, right?
- I know you're both 10. - No, we're 5.
(Being the same age, they have a match.)
- Touch. - No, no.
(Before Jong Kook joins, they touch each other.)
- No, no. - It's a touch.
- It is. - It's not.
- We're 10. - We're 10.
- Why? - We won over there.
I was on my way. You should've touched them later.
Have a match. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Dong Hwi wins.)
Okay! Okay!
No. We need to tell Mom.
Let's go.
We lost.
- We're done for. - They're 20 now.
(These two have been watching.)
- Let's go. - But...
But it won't work.
- He's alone. - From here to there...
Let's separate. Let's split up.
No, we shouldn't.
Jae Seok is five.
- No, he's 10. - How old are you?
- Oh, he's 5. - I'm 48.
- What are you saying? - He's five.
Not your real age.
- He's five. - Split up.
Okay. If we touch the house, we'll be 20 years in total.
(Their ages will double if they touch it.)
I got him.
(Jae Seok touches him.)
(Kwang Soo touches the house.)
- I touched the house! - I touched him.
(Seok Jin gets touched and becomes zero years old.)
(Thanks to Seok Jin's sacrifice,)
(Kwang Soo doubles his age.)
- I touched Seok Jin first. - I touched their house!
Hurry up and come here!
I touched their house! I did!
Kwang Soo is 20 now!
We're older too.
We won.
- How old are you? - We're...
- We won. - We're 10, so...
Are you okay? You look sick.
- We won. - We're...
- Us two will win against anyone. - Okay.
- We'll win against them all. - Take a breath, Dong Hwi.
We will win. Hold on.
Dong Hwi's lips are pale.
Breathe.
You and I should go.
- He's 10. - Haha.
They might want a match.
Then we'll give it to them.
- Kwang Soo, you can do it. - They don't know my age.
Just go.
(Kwang Soo approaches them.)
How old are you? You're older than me, right?
How about you?
(They ask each other first.)
I'm 10.
- Are you older? - How old do you think I am?
Find out how old Haha is.
(They go against each other.)
(Seok Jin comes to help.)
Come here, come here!
- Come here! - Hold hands.
We need to hold hands.
- Hold on! - Hey.
(Kwang Soo is frightened.)
(He lets go of Seok Jin.)
Run!
Jong Kook.
(Kwang Soo saves himself.)
(But what about Seok Jin?)
- We did it. - Good job.
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin were older together.)
(Seok Jin gets caught.)
- Good job. Let's go. - Seok Jin.
(Haha and Jong Kook are each 15 years old.)
- Gosh. - Okay.
- We got 5 years. - We each got 5 years.
Had we held hands, we would've won.
I can go alone.
- I don't know their age. - How old are they?
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- Don't bring Seok Jin. - Okay, let's do it.
- We won't hold hands. - Leave This Guy behind.
Don't call me that!
Okay, let's do it.
Hey, That Guy.
- Come. I'll have a match with him. - Stay behind.
- I'm serious. One on one. - Okay.
Let's do it.
- Okay! - Why?
(Kwang Soo touches So Min.)
- I'm 25 years old! - What?
No, you're not!
I touched So Min!
I touched So Min.
When did That Guy age so much?
Aren't we 15 years old?
- Yes, we are. - We should hold hands to beat him.
We'll win if we hold hands.
- But they're touching it. - Right.
- We need to hold hands. - What?
They're 35.
- Who? - But we're older than them.
Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
(One house is empty.)
(Do you see that empty house?)
Hey, they're coming!
(Kwang Soo attacks.)
Wait a minute!
- Wait! Kwang Soo! - Hey!
I touched her!
(Kwang Soo touches So Min and becomes 30 years old.)
- Go home! - They're coming!
(Meanwhile,)
Jong Kook is coming.
(Jong Kook runs towards the empty house.)
(We need to defend!)
I'll go.
Se Chan, let's hold hands.
(He successfully touches it.)
Darn it.
(Jong Kook is 30 years old too.)
I thought he was in a car. A car just passed me by.
He was fast.
Jong Kook. We lost.
I'm 30 now.
Did you hit it? You're amazing.
Then let's hold hands and go.
- Hold on. - You have two minutes left.
We need to target the house on the left.
- Right? - Yes, that's our best bet.
All right.
(Great minds think alike.)
We're still older.
Jae Seok is five.
- Aren't you a baby? - What?
- Aren't you a baby? - He's an infant.
Wait. Aren't you a kid?
(They feel each other out.)
(Kwang Soo, 30 years old, attacks.)
Okay. If we touch him, we'll win.
- Touch him. Touch! - Touch!
- Touch! - How old are you?
- I'm 30. - Really?
I am. I'm 35.
- How is that possible? - Is he...
- 35? - I touched the house twice.
We didn't know his age.
(Kwang Soo is on a roll and is now 35.)
- We had no idea. - I touched Se Chan!
He's really old now. We need to defend.
Soon, he'll be 60.
Kwang Soo will turn 60 soon.
Kwang Soo, you'll be 70...
- if you touch their house. - Yes.
(Their team is still in 2nd place.)
(With only 30 seconds remaining, he needs to make the last run.)
Come here if you dare. Hey.
(I need to attack Jae Seok's team.)
Are you That One or The Other One?
- He's That One. - Which one are you?
He's This One.
This One. Hey, This One.
- Come here, This One. - Come here.
(Jong Kook chooses to defend.)
Run, run.
(After teasing him, Kwang Soo attacks.)
(He lunges at Jae Seok at full throttle.)
(Suddenly, Jae Seok switches directions.)
(Kwang Soo spots an empty house.)
(He switches directions...)
(and dashes towards the empty house.)
(Se Chan runs towards him.)
(Who will arrive first?)
- Touch! - Good job!
(Kwang Soo arrives first.)
(He turns the tables around by doubling his age.)
I'm 70 years old!
We're in last place.
I made it!
It's over.
I'm older than Seok Jin!
- Hey! - We're in last place.
- Time's up. Please come here. - Good job.
(This can't be.)
The winners of this round are...
This Guy, That Guy, and Hey, There.
(They acquire 4 syllables.)
(They're disappointed.)
We'd like the syllables "Lee", "Kwang", and "Soo".
Hey.
- What? No, right now. - No.
- That means you get a syllable too. - Right.
- That's a relief. - Yes.
I hope they ask for "Lee" and "Seok".
- Dong Hwi shares your last name. - Then "Song"...
- They don't have "Ji", right? - No.
- "Song" either. - "Ji".
"Song", "Ji", "Kwang", and "Soo".
- Thank you. - That's good.
- You'll get those four syllables. - It's final.
It's final.
(They receive "Song", "Ji", "Kwang", and "Soo".)
Wow, I was amazing.
You were our hero.
You looked so cool while sprinting.
Kwang Soo becomes a hero since he's with Seok Jin.
Yes. Now, you can call me "Kwang Soo".
Call me by my first name.
- That Guy. - No. No more That Guy.
- All right, Kwang Soo. - You're still That Guy.
- You don't have a surname yet. - It needs to be combined.
- Shouldn't they be combined? - That Kwang Soo.
- That Kwang Soo. - That Guy Kwang Soo.
(There are two choices.)
- That Guy Kwang Soo. - That's not right.
- That doesn't work, right? - That Kwang Soo.
- That Kwang Soo Guy. - That Kwang Soo Guy.
- You don't need to combine them. - That Guy Kwang Soo.
If our team had won...
and we picked "Ha", I would've found my full name.
- You're right. - That's right.
- Exactly. - He just needs one syllable.
- You're right. - He has an advantage.
He has an advantage.
- You're right. - He does.
Had I known, I would've named myself "Kim Kim".
(He makes up a ridiculous name.)
- I'd choose "Yang Yang". - I would've done so.
- "Yang Yang". - Only if I had known...
- I'd pick "Jeon Jeon". - "Jeon Jeon" and "Yang Yang".
- "Jeon Jeon". - I'd pick "Jee Jee".
But in your case, you'd get a syllable...
- from Jae Seok. - Yes, "Seok".
- We overlap. - I won't choose "Seok".
(He's curt.)
(I'm going to be "Yu Jae" for today.)
- Hey. - You'd rather be penalized.
I'd rather be penalized.
I'll never ask for "Seok". Over my dead body.
- Unless he asks for it, right? - Yes.
Unless he asks for it, I won't ever do it.
- That's great. - As if.
- I will never ask for "Seok". - I just need "Lee".
- If Dong Hwi wins, I'll get it. - Dong Hwi!
Don't ever find "Lee".
- But then you can't win. - We don't have to.
- What do we get for finding it? - Nothing.
We're never finding "Seok" and "Lee"...
even if it means all of us failing...
except for Se Chan.
(We'd rather get the penalty than help this team.)
You still have to find them even though it'd help us.
- Come on. - So that's it.
We're never finding "Seok" and "Lee".
Nice weather.
(They arrive at their next mission with cherry blossoms.)
- We'll find it. - We'll find it.
I've never wanted to find my name this much.
For this mission,
you'll need the innocence of children and luck to win.
- It's Kids Quiz! - Great.
Kids Quiz?
- It's about kids. - Kids Quiz.
This is my thing.
- Kids Quiz. - Kids Quiz.
We'll be giving you questions suited to the children's eyes.
When a team gets the correct answer,
they can draw one from the drawing board.
We used to do that when we were kids.
- We did. - Right.
The board has the names of snacks of your memories,
and one note that says, "Number 1".
If you draw that note, your team wins right away.
(As you draw the Number 1 note,)
(your team wins and the game is over.)
- Good. - Seriously?
- We need luck. - Even if we draw it at first?
Let's do it this time.
The winning team will receive syllables.
We must get this.
- Then it's over. - Then we win.
If we win, the game's over.
"Let me answer" will be confusing.
So come up with your slogans.
- "This, that, the other guy"? - "This, that, the other guy".
We'll go with "This, that, the other guy".
- Baby! - Baby?
- We're going with Baby. - Baby.
How about, "Let's go, Baby"?
- Baby. - Like, "Let's go, Baby".
How about "Dandies"?
(How about "Dandies"?)
Seok Jin wants to name our team, "Dandies".
(You heard what Seok Jin just said?)
(Why would you tell them? It's embarrassing.)
- It's... - "Dandies"?
Here come the Dandies!
This is the worst team name I've ever seen...
- in 10 years! - The dandy gentlemen.
- Come on, "Dandies"? - "Dandies".
Just go with "This Guy, That Guy"!
We'll go with Pretty Boys.
(We're going with Pretty Boys if they're using "Dandies".)
Come on.
That's better. Pretty Boys.
- We're the Pretty Boys. - Okay.
- Pretty Boys, it is. - Pretty Boys.
Dong Hwi, you're the most handsome in that group!
You're number one.
You can't even get to second place when you're in this group.
How about Cute and Small?
Are you serious?
We'll go with Cute and Small.
Let's summarize, we're Baby.
- Cute and Small! - Cute and Small!
- Pretty Boys! - Okay, then the game starts now.
(They're going to stick with Pretty Boys.)
It sounds hilarious.
I think it's fine.
- Right? - There are flowers in the back too.
- Right. - There are flowers.
- It's hilarious. - Film us with the flowers.
- Pretty Boys. - Here's the first question.
- The name doesn't suit them. - I'll tell you...
a part of a test solved by an elementary school child.
Guess exactly what the child wrote as the answer.
- Yes. - We should think like them.
(What did you think it was grand?)
"Write one thing that you thought was grand".
- So we should think like kids. - Baby!
Baby! Let me answer.
The school field.
- That's not it. - It's not?
(Wrong answer)
- Pretty Boys! - Pretty Boys!
(Dong Hwi goes for it.)
Your own poop.
- Right. - That's right.
(Wrong answer)
I was going to say that.
- Elementary school... - Cute and Small!
(Seok Jin goes for it.)
Dad's tummy.
(Dad's tummy.)
Wrong answer.
"Grand"?
(What could they have thought it was grand?)
- Grand... - For your information,
- Seok Jin was close. - I knew it.
(The answer was close to Seok Jin's.)
Baby!
It's mom.
(I figured it out. It's mom.)
Mom's tummy after she ate.
Be more specific.
Mom's potbelly!
- Good answer. - Mom's potbelly?
Mom's tummy.
- Choose your answer. - Mom's tummy.
- Tummy. - Tummy.
(Will it be correct?)
Come on.
(Mom's tummy was correct.)
(Haha was the president of elementary school kids after all.)
I think like a child!
"Every Music Box!"
The answer was "Mom's tummy".
- I was so close! - Seriously?
If I said "Dad", you should say "Mom"!
That was close.
But they still have to draw the Number 1 note.
Here we come.
Let's go, Haha.
If you draw the Number 1 note, you win.
This is...
Which one?
- I like the right lane. - Go for...
the bottom on the left.
- Left? - The bottom one.
- And you like the right ones? - Yes.
This? The right one?
It's your choice. Go with So Min's idea.
The second bottom one on the right.
(The second bottom one on the right as So Min wants.)
- This one? - Yes.
1, 2, 3.
(They choose based on So Min's decision.)
(Will it say "Number 1" like So Min thinks?)
It's the ring candy.
(Instead of the note)
- I haven't seen it for a while. - That sounds sweet.
- It's been a while. - I like ring candy.
- It's been a while. - They still make those?
That's it. That's ring candy.
(He earned the nostalgic ring candy.)
It melts on your fingers.
- And it gets sticky. - Right.
That's the one.
- It's the ring candy. - Next question.
Next is related to cartoon characters.
- Good. - We got this.
Guess the name of the character correctly.
I don't know any from recent ones.
- Me neither. - It's the old one!
Baby!
- Let me answer! - Let me answer!
- No, it's Cute and Small. - Cute and Small!
Ken and Jun from "Science Ninja Team Gatchaman".
Pretty Boys!
- Cute and Small! - You need the character's name.
- Cute and Small! - Go ahead.
Chul Soo and Young Hee.
I think it's right.
- Is that wrong? - For your information,
the girl's name is Young Hee.
(The girl's name was Young Hee.)
So it's not Chul Soo.
- Baby! - Baby!
(Jong Kook goes for it.)
June and Young Hee.
- That's not it. - Pretty Boys!
- Pretty Boys! - Pretty Boys!
- It's our turn. - It's our turn.
Hoon and Young Hee!
- Say it again. - Hoon!
- And? - Young Hee.
(The correct answer is Hoon and Young Hee.)
(Jae Seok got the correct answer!)
Jae Seok!
Right, it was either Chul or Hoon.
- Right. - That's how they named it.
Dong Hwi, you draw.
Go ahead.
If I draw the winning note, then will we win?
(Their odds to draw the winning note is 1 in 27.)
- Should I go? - Go for it!
(He chose without hesitation.)
Please be the winning note.
(Will it be another snack, or the miraculous winning note?)
Dong Hwi, it's over if it says "Number 1".
(Let's win those 3 syllables and find our names!)
- It's coke candy. - Not bad.
(They won the coke candy.)
(It's not bad.)
What's not bad?
- This is it? - It's not good either.
I used to eat those.
This is exciting.
This time,
you'll be listening to the theme songs of cartoons.
(Listen to the song and guess the name of the cartoon.)
- We got this. - Theme songs.
I know all the theme songs to cartoons.
- What did you get? - We got this!
I know everything!
We'll be playing the prelude for three seconds.
After listening to the songs, please guess the name of the cartoon.
- We don't get the lyrics? - If no one gets the right answer,
- we'll play until someone can. - Don't you worry about that.
(The music will play until we have a correct answer.)
(Music playing)
Pretty Boys!
- "Future Boy Conan". - Really?
("Future Boy Conan" was correct!)
(He only listened to the prelude for 3 seconds,)
(and guessed the correct title!)
No way.
- No way. - How do you know that?
What are you?
He's an old person.
Mom, do you see why I watched all those cartoons?
You watched them for this?
- What? - You watched it for this quiz?
Of course.
You planned this a long time ago.
That experience helps him now.
He's not going to draw the winning note.
How about the third one?
- This one? I thought so too. - Yes.
(The problem is, he's an expert in drawing duds.)
(Their odds to draw the winning note is 1 in 26.)
(Will his luck continue?)
Hardtack.
(He won the hardtack.)
Hardtack is fine.
(It's delicious, right?)
I feel dry already.
Hardtack in this weather?
- It's not too good, right? - It's fine.
It's not so good for this kind of weather.
(It's a combination of dryness.)
How did the song start?
Beyond the far blue ocean
It wasn't in my generation.
- Different generation. - It's too old for me.
To the sky
(Let's play the whole song for the younger generation.)
I bet he didn't listen to his mom.
How do we guess this?
(It's still not familiar to them.)
I think I remember.
(Now they remember.)
Right.
(There's new hope for us)
(To the sky, to the sky)
"Our dreams".
Our dreams bloom
"Earth is waking up".
Earth is waking up and the sun opens
(He sounds like a dolphin. He's singing really high notes.)
Who sings a cartoon theme song that high?
That's not how you do it.
- This is the original note. - Come on.
I thought he was Sim Soo Bong.
It ended too quickly,
so we'll give you another theme song quiz.
We only have to draw the winning note.
(Listen to the song and guess the name of the cartoon.)
(I don't get it.)
- I know this one. - Pretty Boys!
- What is it? - Pretty Boys!
(Jae Seok only listened to one bar of the prelude,)
(and he's ready to answer already.)
5, 4,
(Will he get it right again?)
Super, super, super
"Science Ninja Team Gatchaman"!
(It was correct.)
You did it!
(Jae Seok gets two in a row. He makes it again.)
(He's an expert in this field.)
- You knew it from the beginning. - I did.
- I loved this song. - Didn't you have any friends then?
Hey.
(He naturally reacts to the song.)
(Today is Jae Seok's day.)
(What is he dancing?)
(He's improvising the dance.)
(He is something else.)
I've watched that cartoon so many times,
but I'm not familiar with the song.
I know everything.
I watched cartoons even as a teenager.
(Jae Seok when he was a teenager.)
- I still watch them. - You were too old for that.
Let's go for this area.
Sure, let's try it.
(They have the third chance of drawing thanks to Jae Seok.)
- Let's go with this one. - If they...
(Their odds to draw the winning note is 1 in 25.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E450 Running Man
"Children's Day Special Eps: the Case of Missing Names"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(He chose one note.)
- Let's go with this one. - If they...
(Their odds to draw the winning note is 1 in 25.)
It's the Popeye snack.
(They own a Popeye snack.)
How long do we have to eat these?
- They're all dry. - I'm thirsty.
Do you have any soda?
It's too dry.
Here's another question...
suited for the children's eyes.
We've asked the elementary school children about their dream jobs.
Number one was an athlete.
Athlete?
Number two was a teacher,
number three was a doctor and...
- number five was a video creator. - Baby!
(Baby!)
We have to guess number four?
Team Baby.
- It's number 4, right? - Number 4.
Number four, a youtuber!
Right, a youtuber.
Cute and Small!
A video creator includes youtubers.
- Cute and Small! - Cute and Small.
- A celebrity. - A celebrity.
It's the right answer.
(Their answer is "a celebrity".)
No one hasn't yet gotten it right.
Pretty Boys!
Government official.
No, that's not it.
(Wrong answer)
Come on.
I thought it was a trend.
Here's a hint.
This job is often on TV nowadays.
Nowadays?
- What is it? - Cute and Small!
- Cute and Small! - Yes.
A chef?
- Cute and Small! - Cute and Small!
- A chef. - A chef.
(Their answer is "a chef".)
Yes!
(Chef was correct.)
(They got the right answer for the first time.)
- We got it! - You got it.
We did it.
Right. A chef.
- Right. - Right.
I came up with patissier.
Please don't draw the winning note.
(Their odds to draw the winning note is 1 in 24.)
Kwang Soo.
This is our chance. Let's finish this game.
(If they draw the winning note, they're one step closer to winning.)
No way.
Of course it's another snack.
(They already have 4 syllables.)
- Fish jerky? - Fish jerky.
(They win a fish jerky.)
- It's a fish jerky. - Another dry snack.
(This salty and chewy snack bring back their old memories.)
(We're the ones who should feel choked.)
- Boyfriend and girlfriend. - Boyfriend and girlfriend.
It's another candy.
- "Sailor Moon"! - "Sailor Moon"!
- A conch snack. - A conch snack.
(Now there are only 21 notes left.)
- It's a corn snack. - Great!
I'm full.
It's too sweet.
There are not many left.
- Next question. - Here we go.
We asked elementary school students,
"What do you want to hear from your parents the most?"
Number five was, "You can play with your phone."
Okay.
Number four was, "Do you want more money?"
Number three was, "You can skip your lessons today."
Number two was, "I love you."
Really?
What's number one?
- Pretty Boys! - Pretty Boys!
Pretty Boys.
"You can go to the Internet cafe."
Baby!
(Wrong answer)
"You can watch Running Man."
("You can watch Running Man".)
I wish it was, but it's the wrong answer.
Cute and Small!
"This house is under your name."
(He's approaching completely from an adult's point of view.)
Baby!
(I think I got it.)
"Be happy."
What?
(It's wrong, but all fathers are happy to have you.)
Pretty Boys!
(I think I got it too.)
"Thank you for being born."
I almost cried on that one.
(These fathers are about to cry.)
- Just be healthy. - Just be healthy.
Baby!
"Just be healthy. I don't care about your scores."
Pretty Boys!
Mom!
(Dads are feeling sad.)
(Are my kids watching this?)
Pretty Boys! "Do you want to go on a trip"?
- No. Wait. - Baby!
(It was correct.)
- Yes! - That was the answer.
(It's a dad's superpower.)
Isn't it, "Let's go on a trip".
Number one was, "Let's go on a trip".
This is really sad.
We're all too busy. Both parents go to work,
and we don't have time to be with them.
They could draw the winning note.
Let's end this game now.
- How about this one? - This one?
- This one. - You two choose.
Let's go.
(Their odds to draw the winning note is 1 in 21.)
I hope it's the one. Let's win this, Dong Hwi.
What is it?
Give me a whistle candy.
(Give me a whistle candy.)
(We got the most correct answers.)
We got the most correct answers.
- What is it? - Another snack?
- It's candy. - It's a whistle candy.
Right. That one.
I ate that a lot.
Here's another survey question.
- Good. - Survey.
"What do you do..."
"before you open the bathroom door?"
Baby!
(Without hesitation)
- Go ahead. - Before opening the door?
"Hold my nose".
- Cute and Small! - That was cute though.
- Cute and Small! - Cute and Small!
"Turn the lights on."
Pretty Boys. "Take my pants off."
(I got a good feeling about this.)
Before you open the door?
You take them off and open the door?
Baby!
It was really close.
Baby! "Open the zipper."
(I got it.)
Okay.
Yes, you have to get ready.
They open their zippers?
Before they open the door?
It says, "Open my zippers."
(It's tough to guess from an adult's point of view.)
This is the one I told Haha...
to pick from the beginning.
- Really? - Please.
(Jong Kook have chosen this from the beginning.)
(He chose the one in the bottom and on the left.)
(He's going for the note he chose.)
- Please. - It'd be awesome if it is.
(If he's right,)
- Please. - Please.
(they'll win and earn 3 syllables.)
It's a noodle snack.
(It's a noodle snack.)
(He was completely lost.)
You don't even eat noodles!
(They can't say anything because it's Jong Kook.)
(He's embarrassed.)
You don't even eat noodles!
We have to get it this time.
We have to.
(They seem awkward all of a sudden.)
Here we go again.
It's another cartoon theme song.
- Again? - Yes. Listen.
(Listen to the song and guess the title of the cartoon.)
(This song that everyone is familiar with is...)
(from "Tongki, the King of Dodgeball")
(All children imitated many scenes from this cartoon.)
(They instantly realize what it is.)
- Let me answer. No, Baby! - Pretty Boys!
(Jong Kook didn't shout their slogan.)
(What will Jae Seok's answer be?)
"Moero! Top Striker"?
(It was completely wrong.)
(Jong Kook has a chance, and he shouted out the answer.)
(It's a very famous song. Will he get the correct answer?)
"Dodge Top Striker".
("Dodge Top Striker". What did he just say?)
Jong Kook...
(It's "Tongki, the King of Dodgeball".)
Cute and Small!
("Moero! Top Striker"? "Dodge Top Striker"?)
- Cute and Small! - Go on.
- "Tongki, the King of Dodgeball". - He's right!
("Tongki, the King of Dodgeball" is correct.)
(It was really easy for him thanks to the other two.)
I said "Dodge Top Striker".
- I knew the answer. - You were confused.
I knew it.
I was confused because of you!
(The sun rises up)
(The sea spreads endlessly)
(Let's just sing.)
I was so close.
(Breathe in the fresh air Let's all go for a run)
(He dances like an old man.)
Why did I say that?
You were confused by Jae Seok.
(The best dodgeball player In the world)
- Fiery throw! - Fiery throw!
I got it thanks to Jong Kook.
Right.
- Go for it. - We can do this.
Go ahead.
(They let Ji Hyo choose.)
(Their odds to draw the winning note is 1 in 19.)
(Will she get lucky again?)
"Number 1".
(She picked the Number 1 note.)
- Okay! - Yes!
- Did she draw it? - We won.
Ji Hyo picked it?
This is awesome.
We did it.
- We were... - When you said,
"Moero! Top Striker", I was laughing at you.
I came up with the correct title, but it didn't come out.
It was so close.
Imagine if So Min or I said "Dodge Top Striker".
(Then you won't get away with it easily.)
- We did it. - She did it.
It's all thanks to Ji Hyo.
(They won thanks to Ji Hyo.)
(Team This Guy is winning with 4 syllables.)
Team This Guy has won...
- this round. - Good.
You may choose three syllables.
- 3 syllables! - 3 syllables.
There's still chance...
for Seok Jin to face the penalty.
Here's a suggestion.
We play rock-paper-scissors for each word.
You're being greedy.
We're getting three syllables.
If I win, I'm only choosing my name.
- Yes. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
(This Guy has lost.)
(Why do I lose every time?)
Why do I lose every time?
One word for each win?
Rock-paper-scissors! Rock-paper-scissors!
(Kwang Soo naturally loses.)
(It's not a surprising result for the unlucky members.)
- Ji Hyo won again. Ji Hyo, choose. - Choose a syllable.
- "Hyo". - She is done.
Song Ji Hyo retrieves her name. She will get her name tag.
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo is unbelievable. - I am jealous.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
I finally got my name back.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(Between the Unlucky Brothers, Kwang Soo will choose first.)
Okay!
- Pick a syllable. - "Lee".
- "Lee". - You got a syllable back.
- You got a syllable back. - "Lee".
- I will choose... - Kwang Soo got his name back.
Does anyone has "Jin" in his or her name?
No, no one does.
- "Jin". - Choose "Seok" instead.
Okay.
We will now move for the last round.
- This is driving me crazy. - I lost my chance.
Seriously.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo found their names.)
As you know,
to complete the team members' names,
Team This Guy has one syllable to go.
Please stop calling us That Guy and Hey, There.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo completed their names.)
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, and This Guy.
(This Guy hasn't found his name.)
Since This Guy is the team leader, they should be Team This Guy.
- That's right. - Team This Guy.
Unless Seok Jin completes his name,
he will receive a penalty.
You are right, but the odds are in my favor.
- Think about it. - You are right.
That won't make any sense.
They will help me.
Team Child...
- We need 7 syllables. - That's right. 7 syllables.
The last round...
will let you obtain as many syllables as you want.
- It's Beep Beep Bicycle. - Beep Beep Bicycle?
The buildable bicycles you see over there...
have three balloons each.
Each time...
you pop other team member's balloon on a bicycle,
you will obtain a syllable.
Pop one balloon.
- We just need one balloon. - That's right.
- We need... - What you need...
are a bicycle,
balloons,
and a toy hammer you can use to pop the balloons.
- Okay. - Now, a member from each team...
will get in the cable car...
and have a match. The top one will get a good tool...
and the top three will get a bad tool.
It's one on one on one match.
It's an individual event.
- Now, step forward... - Okay.
if you want to participate in the toy hammer match.
One,
- 2, 3. - You should do it.
Nice.
One...
(Who else will compete for the toy hammer?)
(A weakling versus an ace member versus a weakling)
You can win.
- The toy hammer is important. - Ji Hyo...
found her name!
- I know. - I have a team member who hasn't.
Ji Hyo isn't going to be passionate about this.
Ji Hyo, my name isn't complete yet.
- Don't do this half-heartedly. - Of course not.
Do this half-heartedly, Ji Hyo.
- Three. - Jong Kook, go.
(The list of other matches are complete.)
This isn't half bad.
Hey.
(Balloon: Se Chan, Seok Jin, and Jong Kook)
(Bicycle: Dong Hwi, Kwang Soo, and So Min)
- Okay. - Okay.
Gosh, why is the bottom clear?
(The bottom is clear.)
This is...
This is scary.
I can't do this. I need to sit at the edge.
- Jae Seok, come here. - Ji Hyo, I can't sit in the middle.
- It's so scary. - I can't look at the bottom.
Why did they make us ride a cable car with the clear bottom?
Shall we go?
Why is the bottom clear?
Will we play a game in here?
How will we play a game?
- We need to be careful. - You are always anxious.
The bottom is...
(What kind of match will unfold in the cable bar?)
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
This is incredible. The view beneath us is incredible.
Why would you look down?
(Their four eyes look into the distance.)
- My goodness. - Look into the distance.
My goodness.
- The view beneath us is incredible. - Why did you pick this cable car?
- My goodness. - Thank goodness Jae Seok is here.
He understands me.
(I'm glad that you're here too.)
- How nice! - How nice!
This ride will be amazing with a lover.
This is incredible.
The view is amazing.
The view will be great at night too.
Look at the view. It's incredible.
It will be great to come here with the family.
It's perfect in this weather.
I wish I could come here with my mom.
Hurrah!
This feels so good.
The view is really nice.
What's the game?
Your mission to obtain the toy hammers...
is Open the Children's Book.
It must be about the number of people on the page.
I am good at this. Okay.
I am not really good at this.
Pick a children's book.
We will play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors!
(Haha gets the right to choose first!)
- Okay. - Rock-paper-scissors!
(Ji Hyo is next.)
Did you have to win?
(You found your name.)
Did you have to win when you found your name, Ji Hyo?
Jae Seok, the view is incredible under your feet.
This is crazy. I got a look.
Hurry up.
I will choose "The Most Precious..." That one.
I will choose the pink one.
- "I Had a Scary Dream Again". - "I Had a Scary Dream Again".
It's your turn, Ji Hyo. In 1, 2, 3.
(You need to get...)
(the most number of people on the page to win.)
1, 2. 2 people.
Two people with their faces showing.
It's my turn.
(If he gets less than 2 people, he will lose.)
- 4 people. - 4 people.
(Jae Seok's page has 4 people.)
This is no joke.
Please, please.
(If Haha gets more than 4 people. he will win.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(What will be Haha's result?)
- No one? - No, no. Look.
(There are people on the page.)
(Everything is in shadow.)
No, no. Look. Look.
- They don't count. - They are people.
They are shadows, not people.
- Then I have three people. - They are people.
Let me go again. I didn't know.
- Their faces aren't visible. - You didn't tell me the rules.
Go again.
On Ji Hyo's page, we didn't count the figure without a face.
- That's right. - So the face must be visible.
- The face must be visible. - Okay.
Then only you should go again.
Okay. I will go again.
In 1, 2,
- 3. - 3.
Okay. Three people.
(3 people?)
(Haha's page has 3 people.)
- I won! - For goodness' sake.
(He figures out the situation belatedly.)
(Jae Seok wins with 4 people and Haha loses with 3 people.)
- The winner is Jae Seok. - Yes!
- I will explain the rules. - Okay.
The mission for balloon size is...
Kiss the Beautiful Scenery.
- What? - Kiss?
(They feel awkward for no reason.)
- What? Do we need to kiss? - Kiss?
- No way. - No way.
We don't need to kiss each other, do we?
Apply lipstick on your lips...
and open your mouth widely to stamp your lips.
The person who leaves the biggest mark is the winner.
- Okay. - His mouth is...
- Look at the mirror. - Look at the mirror.
- Look at the scenery. - The scenery is nice.
The scenery.
(He docks his lips on an acrylic board.)
(He gives up on his looks in order to win.)
Once you stamp your lips, it's over.
- Okay. - It's not bad.
- Okay. - It's not bad. For goodness' sake.
Okay. It's not bad at all.
(Don't do so well.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Come on.
- Make a big mark. - That's good.
My goodness.
That's incredible.
You did it nicely.
(His mark is as big as his face.)
I want to write letters in here.
- It's like a parenthesis. - I know.
- I hope I don't come in last. - Here I go.
His mouth is big.
What is he doing?
(His lips are about to rip.)
I got the two ends.
This is hard.
Did I do it wrong?
I will measure til the inside.
That's only fair.
- Whose is this? - 6.5cm.
Seok Jin's is 6.5cm.
6.5cm.
How did I do?
This is bad.
Mine isn't half bad.
- I... - My goodness, Seok Jin.
7.5cm.
Right? 7.5cm.
I didn't do it right.
(He is nervous.)
- I didn't do it right. - Yours doesn't look bad.
- Let's go. - My goodness.
- 6.5cm and 7.5cm. - Mine is 6.5cm.
Hey.
(He stretched his lips to his limit.)
(What will be Jong Kook's measurement?)
- Hey. It's 6.8cm. - Yes!
- 6.8cm. - Okay!
(Jong Kook's measurement is 6.8cm.)
- My goodness. - 6.8cm.
- All right. - Okay.
Okay.
(Team This Guy will get big balloons that are disadvantageous.)
Your mission will decide...
- on the bicycle. - Yes.
The mission to obtain the bicycles...
- is the Shark Teeth of Chance. - It's a game of chance.
I was going to go easy on Kwang Soo.
- I won't be able to do that. - It's a game of chance.
I will explain the rules briefly.
You will take turns to take out a bait at a time.
The person who gets bitten loses.
A member of the loser's team...
will get a tricycle.
- It's just the loser, right? - That's right.
Now, decide on an order and take turns.
It might be more advantageous to go first.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors without Kwang Soo.
No, no. Hold on.
It won't hurt you in any way.
I still need to play fairly.
- I will play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
(Dong Hwi will go last.)
Nothing is going well today.
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
(Kwang Soo will go first.)
Go ahead.
I will take this one.
(He chooses daringly.)
I passed.
(So Min passes as well.)
The first round won't be a problem.
- We just need one loser. - I have a bad feeling.
I have...
(Clicking)
(The bait gets caught on its way out.)
(Did it get caught?)
That must be it.
(Could it be...)
(It comes out.)
(I'm relieved.)
(Does Kwang Soo suddenly get acrophobia?)
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
Look before you pick one.
(I'm looking.)
Shall we put it on the floor?
(Why would you put it down?)
Pick one.
Pick one, Kwang Soo.
(The view makes him get acrophobia.)
(He's forced to pick.)
- Look before you pick one. - What are you doing?
(Snapping)
I knew it.
(The great white shark smells his unluckiness.)
The unluckiness never betrays you.
No one can replace him.
One member of your team...
will ride the tricycle.
You're in first place.
But...
Still...
It's over.
Do you want to try it for fun?
(Does he want to play for fun?)
Just pick one for fun.
What if the loser gets flicked on the forehead?
(How about this instead of playing for fun?)
- That sounds good. - A flick on the forehead.
- How will we flick? - With our hand.
- This one. - This?
Will you be okay?
- How about a punch? - A punch?
Okay, that sounds good.
- Really? - Punch.
Okay.
- Okay. - I'll pick first.
(They decide to play another round.)
(Dong Hwi)
(So Min)
(Everyone goes once.)
(They're getting nervous.)
(Dong Hwi passes.)
Pick one.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn again.)
I'm nervous.
(Clanking)
(He flinches as well.)
Good job.
(He really needs to ward off his unluckiness.)
How is this possible? Do you know which to pick?
The two of us will punch you.
Can you see it?
Both of us will punch you.
Don't be like that.
What?
Will you really punch me with a fist?
I changed it to punching.
Okay, I'll get punched.
Wait.
Hold your neck. It could hurt your neck.
Hold your neck.
Holding my neck won't be necessary.
(Punching)
(It's an explosive punch.)
(It sounded like something broke.)
(He feels dizzy.)
My goodness.
I never heard that sound from punching one.
(It's shocking.)
It sounded like a gourd was breaking.
It's your turn to punch.
Kwang Soo.
- It's okay. - Go ahead.
I suggested the punch, but...
- Go ahead. It's okay. - Really?
- But... - What should I do?
- My hand hurts. - What should I do?
It's okay.
(I should keep the promise.)
What's this?
(However...)
(He uses the side of his hand.)
Didn't you learn how to fight?
How can you hit me with that?
(It appears in martial arts films.)
(It's a death blow with the side of the hand.)
How can you hit me with that?
(Thud)
I hit the wrong spot.
(It sounds quieter than before.)
Look.
- It hit here. - No, Dong Hwi.
- It's red. - I hit the wrong spot.
It didn't look like it'd hurt,
but it's really painful. It wasn't fun either.
I hit the wrong spot.
(After playing two rounds, they arrive at the peak.)
You look good with it.
Take a seat. Can you get on it?
Try it first.
(He struggles to bend his body to fit.)
You look very comfortable.
- Does it move forward? - Wait.
(Looks unstable.)
Can you move?
Can you move forward?
He's moving.
It works.
(It does move forward, but it looks unstable.)
It's very unstable.
How can it be so fast?
(Will he be able to pop balloons on it?)
(Current status)
(They obtain items of different sizes.)
What are these bikes for? Which ones are ours?
I can see the balloons.
There are small bicycles too.
Goodness.
Gosh.
Ours are big bicycles with small balloons.
Are ours big?
- Did you not work hard? - Listen.
That wasn't possible because the game was random.
Ours are the best bicycles.
We have big bicycles with small balloons.
All of us won the games.
Everyone.
The game consists of the first and second half.
Two members from each team will play.
- Okay. - Is that so?
- Good. - Every time you pop a balloon...
of another team,
you obtain one syllable.
The team that completes the members' name tags the fastest wins.
All we have to do is pop one balloon.
(1 syllable, 8 syllables, and 7 syllables remain)
- Let's go. - Let's go, Jae Seok and Dong Hwi.
- All we need is just one ballon. - Just one.
- Just one. - Just one.
Make sure you hold out during the first half.
If you pop your own balloon by mistake,
- you give up one syllable. - Nice.
Be careful, Dong Hwi.
Get ready.
Start.
(The first half of the game starts.)
It's hard to move it forward.
(When he sees Seok Jin who can't move forward...)
Dong Hwi, pop a balloon.
Everyone is after me.
(He's picked as a target.)
Let's go to the center.
(He heads towards Seok Jin.)
(Then he makes a quick turn.)
(Ji Hyo doesn't pay attention to her balloons)
(Jae Seok tries to pop hers.)
(Unfortunately, he fails.)
This is scary.
(Ji Hyo tries with all her might to run away.)
Go after her.
Defend!
Vroom, vroom.
(Seok Jin can't move his bicycle.)
Stay away from me.
(Boom)
(If Haha pops Seok Jin's balloon, he obtains a syllable.)
(Popping)
(Seok Jin pops his own balloon.)
He popped his own.
What have I done? It only touched the balloon gently.
(He turns in a syllable as he popped his own.)
(I'll definitely protect my last balloon.)
(Try to protect it if you can.)
(He pops two balloons of Seok Jin.)
(As Haha pops Seok Jin's balloons,)
(Haha obtains 2 out of 7 syllables.)
- Hey. - Look.
Are we eliminated if all the balloons are popped?
This doesn't move.
The bicycle doesn't move.
Ji Hyo.
Go after her.
Defend yourself.
- Go after her. - She's fast.
- Ji Hyo is fast. - You're fast, Ji Hyo.
Make an attack.
Attack.
No.
(It finally pops.)
Nice.
(As Jae Seok pops Ji Hyo's balloon,)
(Team This One obtains one syllable.)
(Ji Hyo tries to run away.)
Run away, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
(Dong Hwi blocks her.)
(Jae Seok chases after her.)
(He smashes her balloons.)
(Jae Seok pops Ji Hyo's.)
(Team This One obtains 2 out of 8 syllables.)
(Ji Hyo pops Dong Hwi's balloon.)
Be careful behind you. Jae Seok, on your left.
(Peekaboo)
(I've been working out my thighs for this moment.)
(He boosts energy into his muscles and charges forward.)
(Popping)
(He pops balloons of Jae Seok and Dong Hwi one by one.)
Hold on. This doesn't work anymore.
(Jae Seok pops Ji Hyo's balloon.)
(Jong Kook pops Dong Hwi's balloon.)
All my balloons are popped.
(Dong Hwi is out.)
(Now Jae Seok from Team This One...)
(and Jong Kook and Haha from Team Child remain.)
Jae Seok, it's a fight of stamina.
- We don't know yet. - Turn.
I can't hit both right and left.
You go right. I'll go left.
Corner him. We can do it.
Run away, Jae Seok. Behind you.
Behind you, Jae Seok. Jong Kook is behind you.
- Dodge him. - He'll be caught.
- Jong Kook is so fast. - He's so fast.
At this rate...
Jong Kook is so fast.
Jae Seok, go to your left.
- Turn to your left. - What's going on?
(Popping)
Jae Seok, do something.
The bicycle doesn't go easily.
I was startled by how fast Jong Kook was.
To your right.
(His last balloon pops.)
We got it.
(He obtains a total of 7 syllables.)
I knew it.
(I can't defeat that thigh engine.)
Each team, go to your corner.
What happened to us?
Here's the result of the first half.
Team This One won three syllables.
- I was so close. - Next is...
For Team This Guy, Ji Hyo popped one balloon.
Seok Jin popped his own.
1 minus 1 is 0.
Seok Jin might get penalized.
We just need one.
If you didn't pop yours...
I know.
It would have been good.
Team Child popped...
seven balloons.
- No way. - Didn't we win?
- It's over for us, right? - We popped seven.
- You did. - Yes!
That's amazing. How is it possible?
That was too easy.
The second half will...
- determine who places last. - Just pop one, Kwang Soo.
- Aren't we playing? - Just pop one.
Let's start. Are you ready?
- You can do it. - You can do it.
The game is over once we pop one balloon.
- Just pop one. - Then this game is over.
We need to pop five balloons.
Get ready.
(Who will win this round?)
Start.
(The second half starts.)
Just one.
- Go to where there's space. - Okay.
Kwang Soo.
What are you doing, Kwang Soo?
He can't move.
Kwang Soo isn't moving.
- Kwang Soo. - He's falling down.
(Falling)
(Today's lesson. Ride a bicycle of your body size.)
(This is my chance.)
It's now.
Use your feet to go forward.
Corner him.
They're coming.
- Seriously. - Kwang Soo.
(Swinging)
Work hard.
I'll pop a balloon when they arrive.
Do that.
Just pop one.
Hey!
(Running with the bicycle may be better.)
(They try to attack Kwang Soo who fell down.)
(He reacts very fast.)
He's safe.
He saved himself.
His balloons aren't popped.
Corner him.
- They're like hyenas. - Okay, okay.
They're coming. Be careful.
(Team This One is cornering Kwang Soo.)
(Popping)
(Jae Seok pops Kwang Soo's balloon.)
(Se Chan pops Seok Jin's balloon.)
(They obtain 2 syllables instantly.)
Run away.
- Run away for now. - Run away.
- It's a fight of stamina. - Let's run away.
(If they pop 3 more balloons, they'll win the second place.)
They're coming.
Just one.
Pop just one, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo's bicycle is...
(He wants to pop too.)
too short for his legs.
It's uncomfortable for him.
Pop his balloon when he falls.
Goodness.
(Struggling)
Just push with your feet.
(Even people watching him feel nervous.)
(Breaking)
Hey, Kwang Soo.
(His bicycle couldn't resist his weight.)
(He charges towards fallen Kwang Soo.)
Wait.
(It's their golden opportunity to pop balloons.)
(Se Chan pops Kwang Soo's balloon.)
(Team This One has to pop only two more.)
(It's a dangerous moment for Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo is in bigger trouble.)
(It could be very dangerous to ride a bicycle of wrong size.)
Why do things like that always happen to him?
- What's wrong with you? - Now is the chance.
(He forgets his terrible pain.)
(He struggles to protect his balloons.)
(He obtains a unicycle by surprise.)
It's a unicycle.
He has a unicycle.
No, Kwang Soo.
(Team This One attempts to make a series of attacks.)
(Jae Seok successfully pops Seok Jin's balloon.)
Hold out, Seok Jin.
- What are you doing? - It's over if one of ours pops.
It's over if one of ours pops.
Gather.
They'll be so disappointed if they lose now.
How many are left?
They're being careful because they never know.
They have to pop 1, and we also have to pop 1.
They have to pop one.
- It's a fight of one. - It is.
Turn, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan put pressure on the opposing team.)
Here we go.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan put pressure on Kwang Soo and Seok Jin.)
Be careful.
We need to defend ourselves.
Come. Put the balloons in between us.
Come here.
- I'll come to you. - Come here.
Seok Jin!
(Will the game end like this?)
(Swinging)
Seok Jin!
(He defends himself at an incredible speed.)
Stay alert, Seok Jin.
- That was really quick. - That was amazing.
Turn that way.
Hang in there. It's a fight of stamina.
(A good match is taking place.)
I'll protect you.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan target Kwang Soo.)
There's not much Kwang Soo can do.
(While only defending himself, Kwang Soo makes a choice.)
(He throws his toy hammer to attack them.)
Kwang Soo has no toy hammer.
Goodness.
(He has lost his toy hammer and his bicycle.)
What are you doing?
(His toy hammer is too far.)
It fell right in front of him.
I'll get it for you.
Be careful.
(He takes a risk to get the hammer.)
(He takes his chance.)
(He attacks unarmed Kwang Soo.)
No! My toy hammer!
I got it.
(Se Chan has lost his toy hammer.)
- Hey, hey. - I got it.
Pick it up.
- No. - He got it.
Here I go.
- I can't go forward. - Protect your balloons.
We have a big one.
- Give that to me. - It's a big one.
Give that to me.
Kwang Soo, give that to me.
Okay.
- We're in trouble. - Come here.
(We don't know who will win.)
This is so much fun.
It makes me want to watch.
It's interesting.
- We never know. - We really don't.
Go and pop their balloons.
What do you think?
Let's just charge forward.
- Let's throw ourselves into it. - For the last time?
We just need to pop one.
Just one.
(Both teams plan to attack. Who will be the winner?)
(Both teams are careful about their attack.)
Just go for one.
Get ready.
They're coming.
(It's like the calm before a storm.)
(They aim for one.)
We can pop it when they arrive.
Let's attack when they come.
(Neither of them can attack hastily.)
(Just then)
(Kwang Soo moves forward little by little.)
Your balloon.
(However)
(His balloon falls off.)
(His balloon isn't protected.)
(Se Chan goes toward the balloon.)
(Protect your balloon, Kwang Soo.)
My balloon is here.
(Will Se Chan pop the balloon and end the game?)
(Or will Seok Jin protect the balloon and continue the game?)
- Okay. - No!
(Popping)
My balloon is here.
(Se Chan hits it accurately and pops the balloon.)
Goodness.
(The fate of two teams is swapped due to Kwang Soo's mistake.)
(Popping)
(We'd have won if we had popped one.)
This is insane.
(Team Seok Jin in third, Team Jae Seok in second,)
(Team Haha in first)
The winning team today is...
- Could it be? - Team Haha.
(Team Child is today's winner.)
That's amazing.
Second place isn't bad.
- It isn't bad. - Second place isn't bad.
We thought we'd face the penalty.
We only had to pop one.
We'd have won if we had popped one.
Wait.
He's thinking.
- We bought "Seok". - We have "Seok".
"Seok" also includes me.
He bought "Seok".
- I bought it. - Me too.
The only person whose name isn't complete is...
Seok Jin.
Did Seok Jin pop your balloon, didn't you?
Yes, it's because I was very angry.
Goodness.
(Seok Jin popped a balloon.)
- That's right. - Why did you pop it?
Why did you pop it?
I was too angry.
- Seriously. - Seok Jin.
- You could have won your name. - I was so upset.
I see.
- There was no penalty today. - There was no penalty.
- Right. - There was no penalty.
Why did you make it worse?
(It's the butterfly effect of the balloon that he popped.)
Do we have to take one out?
You have to take out one syllable.
Wait.
- If I lose 1, shouldn't he lose 1? - Right.
If you take out "Seok", both will be penalized.
(Both Seok Jin and Jae Seok will face the penalty.)
That's right.
What?
(I worked so hard to get my name back.)
- That's right. - What are you talking about?
- What about "Lee"? - Lee from Lee Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo's last name is Lee.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - I didn't know.
Does the winner of rock-paper-scissors...
decide which syllable to take out?
Yes, the winner decides.
That's right.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Will it be a beautiful end?
- Play. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Yes!
"Seok".
(He doesn't hesitate a second.)
We'll take out "Seok".
"Seok".
- Come on. - I took out "Seok".
- No. - Think about it again.
Come here.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- You just wait and see. - I won't forget this.
(This One and This Guy will face the penalty.)
Their names together are "This One, This Guy".
- This One, This Guy. - This One, This Guy.
This One, This Guy.
Get ready.
- Okay. - 1, 2, 3.
(Splashing)
That was a good throw.
(You wait and see.)
That was love.
- Right? - 1, 2, 3.
(Splashing)
(When will it come?)
(Now)
(We thank Lee Dong Hwi for being with us today.)
It felt refreshing.
(They finish the race where they went back to being children.)
(There is secret history that isn't in the records.)
(Historical pieces are given to 8 members)
(All hints point to 1 person)
(Sejong the Great)
(Find sealed heritage secretly left by Sejong the Great.)
(They start to search the treasure.)
(It's an intense psychological war among 8 members.)
(All hints point to one mysterious place.)
(That place is...)
(a huge, unidentifiable basement where treasures are hidden.)
(The worst penalty awaits those who don't pass the test.)
(The owner of the treasures starts to get revealed.)
(Who will win the sealed heritage?)
(Deep-rooted Secret)