(On one rainy day that subsided the heatwave,)
(there are...)
(mysterious-looking wigs.)
(Who do these wigs belong to?)
- Hello. - Hello.
Are those for me?
- Those are my wigs? - Yes.
There are a lot of wigs indeed.
(Seok Jin became the owner of the wigs because...)
(Seok Jin was last in a race 3 weeks ago.)
(As the penalty, he will put on a costume for an opening segment.)
I feel empty without the makeup.
The shape of your head is nice.
(The shape of your head is nice.)
- Hey. - Yes?
- Really? - Yes.
No, you're being nice.
I mean it.
(As he shows off his nice head,)
(his head is getting bald little by little.)
(When Seok Jin is getting ready...)
You're here.
(Door sliding)
(Someone is coming into the makeup room.)
(Another member who will face the penalty with Seok Jin)
(So Min is here.)
(She only laughs out loud.)
(She's about to go home as soon as she comes to work.)
("What have I just seen?" She can't believe her eyes.)
I just saw an egg in there.
(I just saw an egg in there.)
Whatever. She doesn't know what's coming for her.
- Why do you look like an egg? - What?
- Hey, come here. - You look like a warty sea squirt.
Hey, this is your future.
(3 months ago, So Min put this down as the penalty.)
(Leading the opening segment with a weird costume on for a male guest)
(She will wear the worst costume only once for her acting career.)
Please make me look pretty.
Hey, pretty? Jigsaw can't look pretty.
It's embarrassing that only two of us are doing it.
It's really embarrassing.
They are going to make fun of me a lot.
They'll make fun of you.
But it's comforting. I don't think I could have done this alone.
I don't know why Seok Jin and I are getting clumped up together.
(I don't know why Seok Jin and I are getting clumped up together.)
(Forbidden shot of So Min and Seok Jin together)
Lately, whenever we draw for pairs, I end up pairing with you.
Right. Why is that happening? Seriously.
(The forbidden couple's makeup is about done.)
(Meanwhile, without knowing anything...)
- Hello. - It's raining today.
It's nice to film indoors today.
- Hello. - It's cool in here.
This is nice.
- I'm sure you remember this place. - This place...
- Of course. - It was for the hopscotch.
- Right. We played hopscotch. - Back then,
- That's right. - it was Se Chan's first appearance.
- Right. - Really?
(Se Chan filmed the show as a guest for the first time here.)
- He's indeed the ace. - Na Rae was on the show with us.
That's right.
- I was first! - How did you know that?
(Back then, winning the race was the focus instead of being funny.)
Se Chan didn't do much during that episode.
- Right. - It's because...
- I was with Seok Jin and Kwang Soo. - he was with me and Seok Jin.
The thing is that I was a big fan of him,
but when he was on our show, he wasn't funny.
(Being brutally honest for the 2nd time)
- I was very nervous back then. - Right now...
I was wondering why he wasn't funny.
(But he's funny now, so it's all right.)
Anyway, I don't see Seok Jin...
- and So Min. - So Min isn't here.
Do you remember that they had the penalty of wearing a costume?
Right.
Today is the day.
They will be doing it together.
That must mean that So Min might be interested in this guest.
- Is that so? - In the guest?
Seriously. You are such a viper.
This serves her right.
- I guess we're having guests today. - Of course.
- By the way... - All right.
- We should... Yes. - Let's call them out.
- Come on out. - Where are they?
- Where are they? - Come on out.
- I'm curious about their costume. - Same here.
Oh, my!
(Goodness!)
Who is that?
(Who is So Min dressed up as?)
(So Min the Jigsaw)
(Starting now, the penalty will begin.)
- So Min, you're Jigsaw. - Goodness.
Look at her.
- That was scary. - What was that?
(It makes their jaws drop.)
Hey, Seok Jin is the highlight.
- He's the highlight. - So Min.
- What is that? Oh, my. - Let me see.
- What is that? - He scared me.
Who are you?
- He's the highlight. - Come here, So Min.
- That's too harsh. - He's the highlight
Hey, he's the highlight of the segment.
(Who on earth is Seok Jin dressed up as?)
(He's from the underworld.)
(King Byeonseong)
What is that? Goodness.
- What is that? - He scared me.
He's the highlight.
- He's the highlight. - I wonder who the guests are...
- for him to go such lengths. - This is amazing.
Come here.
You have brought the sin upon yourself.
- He's so scary. What is that? - What is that?
Wait, isn't that character in "Along with the Gods"?
(Taking a selfie with King Byeonseong)
- What did he use for the makeup? - It looks nice.
Hey, I've already forgotten about So Min.
What's the name?
- It's King Byeonseong. - "Along with the Gods".
- He was in "Along with the Gods". - King Byeonseong in the movie.
- Right, right. - "Along with the Gods"?
They did a great job with that.
Seok Jin, this is the real deal.
You think you won't look that awful next to Seok Jin.
But yours is terrible too.
For you, it has to be more shocking than Yondu.
- That's true. - Right, no one can beat that.
First, you need to be bald.
Unbelievable. I didn't know I'd have to go this far.
(Screaming)
- This is so uncomfortable. - Come on.
Seok Jin is trying to get all of his airtime in the opening segment.
It took two hours.
(Trying to get as much airtime as he can)
That's not how you do it.
Seok Jin, that's not how you do it.
You guys,
welcome to the underworld.
(He hasn't seen "Along with the Gods".)
First of all, our penalty isn't important right now.
- We have guests today. - We're having guests now?
- We should bring them in now. - Yes.
We have special guests who have come to join Running Man today.
- How can I greet them like this? - Are they coming out?
Guests, please come on out.
I think they invited guests So Min likes today.
- I can't wait to find out. - Are you here?
Guests, please come on out.
- Are they coming out? - It's Ji Yeon.
- Lim Ji Yeon. It's been a while. - Hello.
(Lim Ji Yeon, Park Jung Min, and Choi Yu Hwa)
- Ji Yeon. - It's been a while.
(As soon as they enter,)
(they are shocked.)
(Here comes King Byeonseong. Move out of his way.)
(They are shocked by his appearance.)
They are shocked.
- This is the least I can do. - Ji Yeon.
- It's been a while. - After all, it took two hours.
(When a male guest, Jung Min, enters...)
- Hello. Come this way. - It's been a while.
- It's been a while, Ji Yeon. - Hello.
- Ji Yeon. - Hello.
- Hello, come this way. - Hello.
- So Min, hurry up and say hi. - Please look at So Min.
- Hello. - Ji Yeon.
- What's up with the makeup? - "What's up with the makeup?"
- "What's up with the makeup?" - Why?
Today's guests are an actor and actresses.
- So Min is a bit embarrassed. - Right.
- Hello. - She heard you were coming.
She wanted to look especially pretty, so hence the makeup.
- These three guests are joining us. - What about us?
- We'll do the segment like this? - Yes, of course.
Kwang Soo and the guests are back with "Tazza: One Eyed Jack".
- It's the third one. - We have many actors and actresses.
They are joining us today.
By the way, I didn't see Kwang Soo in the trailer.
- Is he in the movie? - I'm in the movie.
- He's in the movie. - He is?
- He has a small part. - I saw all three of you.
But I didn't see him in the trailer.
That's how secretive and important my role is.
You got fooled once again.
- From what I've heard, - I wasn't fooled.
Kwang Soo is only making a cameo appearance.
No, I'm not.
- But he's promoting it with you. - No, no.
He wanted to join us, so we let him.
- What are you talking about? - I knew it.
You should just focus on your career.
- Comedian? - What's my career?
Focus on being a better comedian.
(Not a movie actor)
Join projects as a comedian.
- What's the matter with him? - You're doing a good job.
Shouldn't he stand in the middle? Since he's in the movie too?
- No, no. Stand over there. - Stand there.
- What's wrong with him? - Jae Seok.
- You will stand there. - He hates seeing Kwang Soo.
- Jung Min is joining us today too. - Yes.
It's our first time having him on our show.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello, my name is Park Jung Min.
Kwang Soo and I worked on a movie called "Tazza: One Eyed Jack".
Our movie is soon to be released, so I came here to have fun.
(This is his first time on our show through an official invitation.)
(A real blue chip with awe-inspiring acting performances)
(He can perfectly pull off any types of roles.)
(He's the genius actor whose acting spectrum is endless.)
(Park Jung Min!)
Jung Min,
you even published a book. You have a lot of talents, don't you?
Right.
He attended Korea University...
- Stop it. - at first and transferred.
- Really? - Really?
Don't you know the times we live in? Why bring up schools?
(Sharp advice)
Why did you mention his school?
- That wasn't my purpose. - Why did you mention that?
- What did you major in? - At first...
I was in liberal arts for a short time.
You must've gotten good grades.
- No. - Your grades must've been good.
- He indeed has many talents. - He's versatile.
In the movie, "Sunset in My Hometown",
- He rapped in the movie. - he even rapped.
- I saw it. - He rapped.
- He asked us not to make him rap. - Of course.
Rap for us.
- No, no. - I'm awful.
- Why not? - We were instructed not to ask.
Until when will we follow orders from the guests?
(King Byeonseong explodes.)
- That's right. - We must get them to do things.
- Seok Jin, don't be so angry. - He's so scary.
I think he should rap.
You should rap. Now.
(King Byeonseong shows no mercy.)
- Hurry. - Stop it.
This is an order from King Byeonseong.
- What's wrong with you? - Rap for us.
- Why are you doing a skit? - What's wrong with you?
- Until when will we let them? - You should show him.
Listen up.
- You're here, Jung Min - Stop it.
(You're here, Jung Min)
- Listen. - Why are you doing a skit now?
- He was about to do it. - Why did you do that? Stop it.
I want to take that from his head and twist his legs.
- Rapping is the most embarrassing. - Exactly.
Although he didn't rap, we discussed it for a long time.
It's because of Seok Jin.
It's because of that clueless guy.
Right. Jung Min just introduced himself.
Why don't you go next?
Hello, I'm Lim Ji Yeon. I'm Kwang Soo's partner...
in the movie, "Tazza: One Eyed Jack".
Ji Yeon, it's been a while.
(Lim Ji Yeon, movie actress of refreshing candor)
(An irresistible actress that dominated the movie screens)
Actually, as for Ji Yeon,
- she's on the show several times. - Yes.
- This is my 3rd time. - It's your 3rd time.
- Really? - That's amazing.
Since the last time, it's been about two years.
- Right? It's been a while. - Yes, it's been a while.
Jung Min and Ji Yeon went to the same college.
Who and who?
- Jung Min and Ji Yeon. - They attended the same college?
- They went to the same college. - She went to Korea University too?
- No. - I didn't go to Korea University.
Why were you shocked when you asked if she went to Korea University?
(I saw that.)
Not Korea University. He transferred to another school.
Why are you doing that to me?
"Why are you doing that to me?"
Ji Yeon said, "Why are you doing that to me?"
Have you worked on a project with So Min?
- No. We just had drinks together. - So Min...
- We just had drinks together. - Really?
Ji Yeon, have you seen how So Min behaves when she gets drunk?
- When she gets drunk, - Go on.
she picks up a fight.
(She's honest.)
She picks a lot of fights. Her eyes...
- That's the worst. - shoot a laser beam.
- Right? - Why do you do that?
Pretend you didn't hear her when she talks to you drunk.
- If you go along with that... - Once your eyes meet...
What does she pick a fight about?
A long time ago,
So Min called me at night when I was working out.
- I did? - Really?
She told me that she was filming Running Man.
- At night? - She was in the middle of a game.
- She told me to come to her. - At night?
- We don't film at night. - We don't film at night nowadays.
It was past 9 p.m.
I told her that I couldn't go. I was sweaty too.
- Oh, no. - I told her I couldn't make it.
- She kept calling me. - Why?
- But she wasn't filming the show. - Kwang Soo made me call him.
- Kwang Soo made me call him. - I'm sorry about that.
- Se Chan... - Me? I wasn't there.
No, you were with me then.
- What are you talking about? - What?
Are you drunk? Are you all right?
- You dropped the show's name? - No...
- You used the show as an excuse. - Never. I never call when I drink.
Hey, look at your face.
Get a grip.
(I'm glad that I have you.)
- Get a grip. - My gosh, they were with me.
They were with me when I made the call.
- Why are you angry? - We were with you that night?
We were drinking together then.
- All of us. - What? That's not true.
You look meaner with the makeup on.
(You look meaner with the Jigsaw makeup on.)
You look meaner.
Don't fix your hair. It's so weird.
- You look so weird. - Don't do it. Why are you doing it?
Why don't you introduce yourself next?
Hello, my name is Choi Yu Hwa.
Yu Hwa.
(She became an actress after debuting as a model...)
(at the age of 20 with her sole passion for acting.)
(It's already been 10 years since her debut.)
So Min has the nickname of Crazy Poet.
She writes many emotional posts...
- on her social media. - That's right.
- Yu Hwa writes such posts too. - I see.
- Let's take a look. - Yes.
Yu Hwa uploaded this post.
"There are times when I look for a word..."
"or a sentence to be hooked on."
- She's pretty good. - Yes.
"I'm not ready to get snowed on yet."
What's wrong with her?
(She's not ready to get snowed on yet!)
- She's not ready yet. - What was that?
- What did she write? - Right.
(That was too much.)
- Yu Hwa. - Yes?
- What does this mean? - What is it?
- What on earth happened? - For posts like this,
our Crazy Poet should interpret the post.
- Interpret it. - What is this about?
- It has double meanings. - Like what?
It could mean she's not ready to face the snow or...
- to connect with someone else. - Is that correct?
It means that she's not ready.
She's totally spot on.
She is?
I guess crazy girls see eye to eye.
(Feeling creeped out)
I guess crazy people have their own language.
Is there a club where crazy poets assemble?
Seeing how she posted it on her social media,
- it means she wants attention. - No.
No, this is just creative writing.
- With this... - I think...
you might have forgotten how you look right now.
- Should I show you a mirror? - Do you know how you look now?
By the way, Yu Hwa...
- is the same age as Kwang Soo. - Yes, we're the same age.
- She looks she's younger than him. - She looks younger than her age.
You're older than me. You were born in 1985?
How old are you, Ji Yeon?
I'm five years younger than her.
She's older than you?
(Exchanging eye contact)
(Ji Yeon is 5 years younger than her?)
Ji Yeon also looks younger than her age.
But five years younger?
(But five year younger?)
- Why are you being so mean? - Ji Yeon.
- Listen. - She's young.
- That's meaner. - "Five years?"
- Oh, my. - "Five years?"
What are you talking about? Five years?
(Let's stop talking about age now.)
- She looks younger than her age. - Yes, she does.
- She looks really young. - I was so surprised.
Today's race will be an individual match for all 11 of you.
Today's race is called Deity of Games, Betrayed by Your Trust.
Okay.
Hey, he wasn't done.
I think I've been quiet.
You can accumulate R Coins through missions.
The more coins you gather, the bigger benefits you'll have.
Bring in the prizes and the board.
- Prize? - There are prizes?
- Here they come. - Be careful.
That's Korean beef set.
(Awesome prizes from an LED mask to a Korean beef set)
There's that prize.
- What is it? - This is amazing.
- Look at that. - I'll look like a hero.
- You'll look like a hero? - My kids will love this.
Haha loves gadgets like that.
What's that?
- You need to press this here. - Press it.
It's working now.
This is awesome. I can see right through this.
This is amazing.
This is really pretty.
- This is "pretty"? - That's nice.
I bet the kids will love it too.
Stop it. Why would kids put this on?
This is something the whole family can enjoy. This is amazing!
Hey, that's not how you advertise a product!
(A capitalist fool who can't advertise a product)
- Advertisement? - They'll pull back the offer.
- Check the prizes and penalties. - What are the prizes?
If you get more than 51 R Coins, you'll get the LED mask.
With R Coins between 31 and 50, you'll get the Korean beef set.
- I want the LED mask. - Between 11 and 31, it's a juicer.
For R Coins between 0 to 10, you'll get a portable fan.
- The makeup and the costume. - We have penalties.
That again?
- It's the opening disguise. - Our points will be accumulated.
You better not get that one.
If you do well, you'll receive the gifts.
If you don't do well, you'll be penalized.
- Let me continue. - There's more.
There are two ways to acquire R Coins.
There are many rules.
You can either win games that have the coins at stake.
You can also pick colored coins...
during the Full House after the mission.
According to the result, you'll be able to acquire the coins.
There are blue, red, and black R Coins.
You can each pick one.
If everyone picks black,
you each get 10 R Coins.
If only one of you picks black,
that individual will receive 20 R Coins.
If there are two or more people who pick black,
those who pick blue or red will receive five R Coins each.
Those who pick black will have to give five R Coins.
If no one picks black,
those who pick the majority...
will receive five R Coins each.
After the final round, depending on the R Coins you have,
you'll be either rewarded or penalized.
(Current Number of R Coins)
(They already played a mission beforehand.)
What is this?
- What is this? - What is this?
It's like a karaoke.
A karaoke?
Let me explain.
For this round, you'll be divided into teams of 3, 4, and 4.
Team of 3, 4, and 4?
This first mission is called Mic High Low.
(Mic High Low)
- High Low? - You'll be singing.
The team with the highest score will win.
But if both digits are the same number,
that team will win.
Instead of getting 93 points, you'll win with 77 points.
(He gives an example.)
In other words, it's called a "ddaeng".
(In other words, it's called a "ddaeng".)
"Ddaeng".
(He uses a gambling term.)
That's a gambling term.
- "Ddaeng". - All right.
You'll win if you get a "ddaeng".
You need the same number.
What if you get 38 points?
(It's the highest "ddaeng".)
- It's a "gwangddaeng". - It's a "gwangddaeng".
Does that work?
No, it doesn't count.
The amount of coins you'll receive will equal...
the first digit of your score.
For example, if you get 93 points,
you'll each receive nine coins.
If you get a pair,
the staff will reward you with the amount of the first digit.
For the last digit, you may pick a member...
- to receive that amount from. - Oh, no.
We'll steal from them.
Let's say you got 99 points.
Then we'll reward each of you with nine coins.
If you want to take the remaining nine coins from Kwang Soo,
you can do that.
Even your example involves Kwang Soo.
(He's happy.)
(He has nothing to say.)
Because he has 10 coins.
- We should pick him. - Seok Jin and I are in first place.
- You're right. - We should target them.
Each team will get to sing once.
We'll start in five minutes.
The remaining two teams...
will hide for five minutes.
(They will hide before the song begins.)
- And? - You're allowed to hide anywhere.
This is hide-and-seek.
Where could we hide?
Two members from the singing team have to find the members in hiding.
They must touch and eliminate them.
Every time they eliminate a member,
the microphone will come down.
(The microphone will come lower.)
The team members will matter.
It's best to pick people who are good at singing or hiding.
(The guests will play rock-paper-scissors.)
Those who are good at singing or hiding?
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Yeon wins.)
Yes.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Kwang Soo.
(You lose, Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo, come this way. - Come.
Who won?
- She did. - You did?
Ji Hyo.
(Yu Hwa picks Ji Hyo.)
She's neither good at hiding nor singing.
(Jong Kook states a fact.)
She needs to be good at singing.
- I'm sure I'm good at one of them. - You don't get the rules, do you?
You've failed already.
(Team Members)
- Have you picked your team members? - Yes.
Team Red will go first.
- Please wear these eye masks. - Okay.
We need to hide well.
(Where should I hide?)
If they spot us but haven't touched us,
we're not out, right?
- Right. - I'll make sure I do.
(I'll make sure I do.)
- If it's you... - I can do it.
Please pick two members who will sing...
and two members who will eliminate the others.
We'll eliminate the others, and they'll sing.
We'll eliminate them.
You two can sing.
Get ready.
(It's 5 minutes before the search team goes out.)
Set.
(The other two teams begin hiding.)
(They need to hide before Team Red begins singing.)
Can they not see for sure?
(Hesitating)
There aren't that many places to hide.
You're right.
I bet there's someone hiding among the staff.
(His sixth sense is at work.)
I bet.
I'm certain.
They probably changed into a staff member's clothes.
They're probably holding onto a camera.
(She runs away.)
- Where should I hide? - Ji Yeon.
Hurry up and hide.
(Hurrying)
Let me go behind.
(They probably won't find me here.)
My neck hurts.
Right now, 2 minutes and 30 seconds have passed.
How much?
(They don't know where to hide.)
By the way...
Can you raise me up?
(Kwang Soo attempts to go on top of the mattresses.)
1, 2, 3.
Raise me up. 1, 2, 3.
More, more.
You can do it. When did you become so weak?
Step on me.
- Here. Step on me. - Step on you?
(Pressing)
Go up!
- Go up! - Endure it.
- What are you doing? - Help me up.
- Hurry. - Go.
- Goodness. - Hurry!
They won't be able to touch me.
(He successfully goes on top of the mattresses.)
(They won't see me up here.)
Can you see me? No, right?
You have a minute left.
How much?
There's a lot of electromagnetic waves in here.
I'm going to lie down here.
(He goes behind it.)
(I'll hide here.)
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's over.
(Their time is up.)
You can take off your eye masks. We'll start once you pick your song.
We'll sing "Tatata" by Kim Kook Hwan.
"Tatata".
Do we need to sing to that?
(They need to sing to the mic on the ceiling.)
Here it starts.
(How will Team Red manage?)
Jung Min.
- Go, go, go. - Jung Min.
(We'll sing our hearts out.)
This will come down once they eliminate the others.
(You don't know me)
He has a loud voice.
(Screaming)
(Giggling)
(She can't believe she's singing a duet with him.)
(This is a love duet for her.)
(There's no harmony.)
(She forgets about their search team.)
(This is very nice.)
(While the two are singing, the search team is...)
(Let's see.)
(He touches him.)
What was that?
(Se Chan was hiding under the sheets.)
(Jong Kook eliminates him.)
I'm out already?
I eliminated one!
(Thanks to Jong Kook,)
(the microphone comes down.)
Can you lift me up?
(Of course)
(So Min, get on top.)
Just give me a piggyback ride.
No, just get on my shoulders.
Really?
- I'm heavy. - It's okay.
- I'm really heavy. - Here I go.
Hold on!
Here I go.
(This is a movie about a young couple.)
Sing!
(She chokes him.)
Hold on.
(It turns into a wrestling match.)
I'm sorry.
- I was too heavy. - Did they catch one person?
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook, who looks like a pro wrestler, is searching.)
(Where are you all hiding?)
How are they hidden so well?
(Be quiet. Look over there.)
(Peeking)
(I will now begin the hunt.)
Haha, she's going that way.
(She tries to escape.)
- Which way? - She's going.
- It's Ji Yeon. - Where?
Come here. We need to stop her.
(They corner her.)
(Jong Kook eliminates her.)
- She's out. - Done. Are you okay?
(Ji Yeon is out.)
Done. Are you okay?
- Hold on. - Are you okay?
(After eliminating her, they continue their search.)
Come out.
(Let's see.)
(Screaming)
Come out. I caught him.
He's eliminated.
(I'm out.)
(Is anyone else in here?)
(The song is nearing the end.)
(Singing)
What are they doing?
What are you doing?
No way.
Let's hope that we get a pair.
Right, we should hope for that.
That's the worst score ever.
(They're ruined.)
It's the worst. You're done for.
- They're done? - It's over?
(Where are the rest?)
Gosh, you startled me.
(Peekaboo)
(You were there?)
- I was so startled. - He was there.
I barely managed to survive.
You weren't eliminated, right?
No.
I wasn't.
Your score is...
28 points.
(It's a very low score.)
- They just caught two. - They sang?
Good work.
We wasted so much time over there.
We did.
All right, next team, please.
They caught me hiding under the sheets.
So who should sing? How about Ji Yeon?
- Ji Yeon, go ahead. - Shouldn't it be Kwang Soo?
- No, because... - The others need...
to catch those running away.
More than anything though, I want to hear you sing.
(Straightforward)
(Me?)
That's the biggest reason.
We should hear the guests sing.
Ji Yeon, come on.
Then I'll sing "Love Battery".
- That's a good one. - It's upbeat.
I like her choice.
- Charge me with love - It starts when the masks are on.
Ready, set...
(What will be the result?)
Where do I hide?
It's Se Chan.
(I'm good at guessing.)
- At least one went this way. - Right.
- Some went behind us. - Exactly.
(A single blow)
(Thump!)
It's Haha.
(His second guess)
(So where should I hide?)
Everyone here ended up getting caught.
Let's just hide though.
Getting caught isn't the issue. Not getting touched is the key.
(Meanwhile, Yu Hwa is in the closest waiting room.)
(She decides on the classic move.)
Kwang Soo, you run the other way.
I'll run to the end first.
- Take a look around as you go. - Sure.
You have another 30 seconds.
(What?)
(Laughing)
(Haha kept thinking of a place to hide.)
(Can I borrow your shirt?)
(He transforms right in front of them.)
(They won't know, right?)
(And so he transforms into the show's main writer.)
(The beacon does not shine on its own base.)
(Prim)
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
(The search begins.)
(Did Kwang Soo already spot Haha?)
(What's that?)
It's taking longer than I expected.
You can run once the song begins.
(Who says he has good hunches?)
How do I get up there?
(Ji Yeon thinks of using her surroundings.)
- Ji Yeon, sing it well. - Sure.
(Hold on!)
(Kwang Soo suddenly heads to the waiting room.)
(He guesses that someone's in here.)
(Yu Hwa is right behind the door.)
(Will Kwang Soo be able to tell that she's there?)
(Swoosh)
(There's no one here. I'm out!)
(She now begins to sing.)
Charge me with love
(At the top of her lungs)
(Bouncing)
(They probably won't find me.)
I can't live without you
(She's in bed with the enemy.)
(She keeps singing without realizing anything.)
(Meanwhile, the perceptive Kwang Soo...)
There's no one here.
What?
(What startled him like that?)
(It's Jong Kook who's way up there.)
There's no one here.
(He pretends to not have seen anything.)
Is this really necessary?
Why...
How on earth did he get up there?
(When the others went into hiding,)
(Jong Kook chose to go somewhere where he'd be unreachable.)
(He's on top of a wall.)
(Catch me if you can.)
You just can't help yourself.
(Kwang Soo pretends not to have seen Jong Kook.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok is where Yu Hwa is hiding.)
(Where is everyone?)
Is there no other exit?
(Swish)
(Screaming)
What are you doing here, Yu Hwa?
Yu Hwa's out.
- There's someone here. - Where?
(Jae Seok continues...)
(to find another victim.)
It's Seok Jin.
Seok Jin's out.
Still, I managed to stay hidden for quite a while.
(The microphone has come down quite a bit.)
(They're good at finding people.)
(They won't find me though.)
(The song is now almost at the end.)
- There's no one here. - If I'm by your side
Were you caught?
[VIU Ver] SBS E465 Running Man
"Deity of Games, Betrayed by Your Trust Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(What?)
(Gosh, I'm caught.)
- There's someone outside! - The song is almost over.
(Hurry!)
- Hurry up. - He's out there.
(The top agent is coming for you.)
(Jung Min, just you wait.)
Jae Seok!
(The song is over.)
- It's over. - Unbelievable.
- The song's over. - Unbelievable.
This isn't how the game is supposed to go!
- What's her score? - How did she do?
(The song is over. What's here score?)
(It must be higher than 43 or have two same numbers.)
Don't let it be a pair.
- What? - It's only 22.
It's 2 and 2!
(They scores a pair.)
- It's a pair! - It's 2 and 2!
I can't believe it.
- Ji Yeon. - It's a pair of two.
They scored a pair.
(No way...)
- Is it a pair? - Yes, we scored 22.
- Okay! - Our score is 22.
(A pair can nullify poor searching and singing.)
The song is over, so ask everyone here.
- It'll be a while for Jong Kook. - Do you know where Jong Kook was?
He was close to the ceiling.
It's as if he was way up there.
How are we supposed to catch him up there?
(Just thinking about it makes him angry.)
What on earth is wrong with him?
You can see him, but you can't touch him.
Isn't it great to be on the same team with him?
Yes, it's not bad.
- Jong Kook's here. - What was your score?
- They scored 22. - Really?
Really? They scored a pair?
- It worked out. - But they only had three members.
So only Haha seems to still be missing. Haha?
(Standing up)
Did you say 22?
Wasn't it Mi Yeon?
22 points?
Was your score 22?
I thought it was Mi Yeon!
- 22 points? - No way.
Gosh, I really didn't know.
I was sitting here the entire time.
I really thought it was our writer.
No way.
You will receive two R Coins each.
Also, you can take two coins from any person you want.
(Since they received a pair, they can steal 2 coins each.)
- Two each? - Yes.
I'll take two from Seok Jin.
(He didn't even hesitate.)
- Seriously? - Then...
- I'll take Se Chan's. - What if...
Mine? Okay, fine.
Kwang Soo, who would you take the coins from?
I'll take Jong Kook's.
- You fool, I don't have any. - Then you'll have minus two coins.
- Really? - Yes.
(Jong Kook now has minus 2 coins.)
(Kwang Soo got the best of him.)
(He's trying to hold back a smile.)
I see you were quite annoyed with me.
(Earlier...)
Yes, I just couldn't let you get away with it.
So you were pretty annoyed.
Okay.
So everything's been sorted out.
Now it's time for Full House where extra coins can be won.
- Full House? - Full House.
Full House.
We'll start with Team Red...
who scored the lowest in the previous round.
You will head over to the Full House and each choose a coin.
If none chooses black and you either choose red or blue,
those who chose the majority color will receive five coins.
If you all choose the black coin, you'll receive 10 coins each.
But what if all three coins were chosen?
If more than two people choose the black coin...
- The odds are low. - Those who chose black...
will be robbed of 5 coins while the others receive 5.
If only a single person chooses the black coin,
that person will win 20 coins.
(The only person who chooses black will win 20 coins.)
It's quite the temptation.
- You'll be a front-runner. - If we unite,
we can all receive 10 coins each.
Kwang Soo wouldn't risk it and choose the black coin.
He already has a lot.
I already have a lot.
There's no reason for me to take that risk.
No, Kwang Soo will take the risk.
There's a higher chance of losing if you choose the black coin.
But Kwang Soo will still choose it.
You...
(What are you saying?)
You shouldn't have got on Jong Kook's bad side.
Kwang Soo will.
- I would if I were him. - You're on Jong Kook's bad side.
- He would. - Jong Kook...
- If I were him... - He stole two coins from Jong Kook.
Can I return what I took from him?
- Can I? - You made the wrong move.
The Kwang Soo I know would choose black.
Just so you know, he'll hold this against you even next week.
Next week?
No, this month.
- This month. - What?
How suffocating.
- He said "this month" just now. - You shouldn't have.
- He's now a target. - You should apologize.
- Then until the fan meet-and-greet? - Exactly.
Then let's just all choose the black coin.
- Exactly. - We'll all receive 10 coins.
Let's begin the race fair and square.
Let's choose the black coin.
We'll all choose the black coin, all right?
- Everyone's going black? - Yes.
(Should I trust him?)
- I'm not kidding. - Okay.
- Let's do this. - Time's up, guys.
Jung Min, will you choose the black coin?
Yes, I'm on board.
Okay, let's choose the black coin.
(After coming to an agreement, Haha goes to choose the coin first.)
Please choose a coin between the black, the blue, or the red.
I'll be mad if only one ends up choosing the black coin.
I doubt it.
(He chooses one after pondering.)
(I don't know what'll happen.)
I have no idea how this will pan out.
I'm sure he chose the red coin.
No, I kept my promise.
I do think that many will end up choosing the black one.
No one will dare do this.
Only I can make this choice because I'm rich with coins.
Gosh, my pouch is bursting with coins.
It took you that long to choose the black coin?
That's not it.
(You're mistaken.)
- Just watch me. - Okay, go ahead.
- Sure. - See how long it takes me.
I'll see if you're a coward or not.
Do I just take it?
We're watching you, Jae Seok.
So what you said...
You chose the red coin.
The pouch seems red.
- He chose the red one. - It's definitely not the black one.
Unbelievable.
(Everyone chooses a coin while distrust swirls over them.)
The result is in.
We'll open it 1 by 1...
- Is the result interesting? - starting from Haha.
- It is very interesting. - Is it?
- Let's see. - Haha said he'd pick black.
(Is the result interesting?)
I'm serious. I really did.
Let me see.
- I'm serious. - Just take it out.
(What's Haha's coin?)
- Here. - I knew it.
- My gosh. - I had no expectations of him.
That's good.
- I can get 20 coins this way. - I'm sure he picked red.
Why would he pick blue when he's wearing a red vest?
(Jong Kook picked red.)
I don't understand him.
- Okay. So Min, you're up. - You're unbelievable.
I'll tell you later.
(So Min picked blue.)
You're wearing a red vest.
Jung Min.
(He shows blue bashfully.)
(Park Jung Min picked blue too.)
Se Chan?
- Okay? Did you pick blue? - I picked black.
- Jong Kook. - Okay!
This is good.
I picked red.
No one picked black?
(There's no one who picked black.)
- Red? - Good.
The score is 3 to 3 now.
It's Yu Hwa's turn.
(Yu Hwa picked blue.)
- What if someone picked black? - This is amazing.
You'll finally get to see black here.
(What are the remaining 4 people's choices?)
(If no one chooses black,)
(those who choose the majority color will receive 5 coins.)
(If only a single person chooses the black coin,)
(that person will win 20 coins.)
Red!
It's 4 to 4.
(With a score is 4 to 4,)
(Ji Yeon shows a red coin.)
(4 blue coins to 5 red coins)
All right. We have two people left.
Will there be one black coin?
They will show their coins at the same time.
I said I picked black.
(What did Kwang Soo and Jae Seok choose?)
Jae Seok, open yours first.
The score is 5 to 5 now.
(The current score is 5 blue coins to 5 red coins.)
Depending on the last person's coin...
(If Kwang Soo chose black, he will get 20 coins alone.)
Is it black?
(If Kwang Soo chose blue or red, his team will get 5 coins.)
Open it.
(Yes!)
(Kwang Soo is the only person who chose black.)
I can't believe this.
(Speechless)
He's a hoodwinker.
- This is unbelievable. - Yes!
Did you receive instructions or what?
- He took a risk. - If Kwang Soo doesn't lose coins,
he will at least get Korean beef set.
(He has 34 coins now.)
- That's good enough. - But I just can't stop here.
I want the LED mask.
No, I can't let you have it.
I'll give it to my mom.
- I'll make my family happy. - Kwang Soo is unbelievable.
This is amazing.
I told you.
He has a lot of coins, so...
(Mom, I'll make sure to win the LED mask.)
(Current Number of R Coins)
(After the fierce mission...)
(They get on the van to move to the next destination.)
(They all sit where they want.)
Have a seat. It's okay.
It's funny. It's a funny seat.
(Is this a funny seat?)
Let's go.
(She just takes a seat without knowing anything.)
Hey.
(Seok Jin is getting in.)
(Letting out a single cry)
(Yu Hwa is...)
(in my seat.)
(Hesitant)
(He sits in front of Yu Hwa after hesitating a little.)
What?
(That's my seat.)
(Seok Jin just lost his seat.)
(Why are they laughing?)
Why do you think it is?
- What's funny? - Look at her.
- Seok Jin is... - She's so cute.
- Yu Hwa's sitting there. - He hesitated for five seconds.
- I see. - This is so funny.
I haven't seen anything like this for the past 10 years.
I didn't even go to the restroom.
For your seat?
This is good. Yu Hwa, I'm glad you're sitting there.
He was standing next to Yu Hwa for about five seconds.
Anyway, Kwang Soo was unbelievable.
I have 34 coins.
I think I'm done here.
This is just the beginning.
I should've picked black.
I was going to pick black.
But I didn't want to lose 10 coins.
Seok Jin, do you want to go home? Why are you looking out the window?
What are you thinking about?
I don't think it's about your wife.
Who are you thinking about?
- Why are you looking out? - I don't think it's your wife.
No. I wasn't thinking...
Why?
Why are you thinking about my wife?
No, I was thinking about R Money.
You seem flustered.
Why did you think about Byul?
It's not that I thought about Byul.
You just said Byul.
I thought this was a star.
Don't you know that you're my role model?
I do, you punk.
(I do, you punk.)
You know what?
I haven't found anyone attractive for a long time.
I only care about my wife.
So Min is crying looking out the window.
(So Min is crying looking out the window.)
"What am I then?"
Honestly, I wanted to be the last one to leave the waiting room,
but Jae Seok wouldn't leave.
(There she goes again.)
Can we do this?
(He's not even sure if they can make jokes like this.)
(Seok Jin and So Min's forbidden love)
- Can we do this? - As long as his wife is okay,
I like this joke.
I don't think we can do this in Korea.
We can't, but So Min keeps making that joke.
(We can't, but So Min keeps making that joke.)
- I can't say anything. - No, you can't.
So I just stay quiet.
Even when you're quiet, I can see your heart is fluttering.
(Even when you're quiet, I can see your heart is fluttering.)
- You seem excited. - He's blushing.
His cheeks are red.
My heart is filled only with my wife.
That's romantic.
Jung Min doesn't appear in a lot of variety shows.
I want him to talk a lot.
Jung Min died in the movie.
- What movie? - What's the one with Lee Byung Hun?
- "Keys to the Heart". - It was fun.
He played the piano in the movie.
- What? - He played the piano himself.
How did you do that?
He must've practiced so hard.
I practiced hard.
- That's amazing. - For how long?
For about six months.
- Six months? - Yes.
You played the song for six months?
- Did you play the piano before? - No.
- That's impressive. - He's amazing.
(Jung Min is unbelievable.)
What is this place?
I smell sesame oil.
- It smells so good. - It smells delicious.
They have seafood stew here.
- Seafood stew? I love it. - It sounds delicious.
It must be really good.
You will be divided into three teams here.
It's a team game again.
The second mission is...
Call My Name.
- Call My Name? - Call My Name.
It's a match among three leaders of each team.
Each of you will pick one card...
and put it on your hat without looking at it.
You should guess who the figure in your card is...
by asking questions and answering to each other.
If you give a wrong answer, you'll be hit with a toy hammer.
The team with the highest score wins the game,
and they get five coins each.
They also get to steal five coins...
from a member you want.
The team in second place don't get coins,
but they will get to eat a meal.
The losing team gets only rice and laver.
Let's win the game and eat.
Now you should divide yourselves into three teams.
All right then.
I'll divide you guys into three teams.
(I'll divide you guys into three teams.)
Why would you do that?
(He pretends to be generous.)
- Who do you think you are? - Excuse me.
You don't even have many coins.
- Let's give it a try though. - All right.
- Let me... - Who do you think you are?
With my big data,
I'll make the best teams.
Jong Kook, stand there.
- Me? Okay. - Yes, please.
This is based on the number of R Coins.
That's important.
- I'll form good teams. - Okay. That's good.
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
Let me check the big data again.
- You should trust me. - Okay. We will.
- Is that the big data you have? - Yes.
(Is that the big data you have?)
This is the big data.
- Is that it? - I thought there'd be more.
This is big. It's big data.
That's the only thing you have.
- This is big data. - Okay. Good.
- It's cutting edge. - First,
- Jong Kook should be there. - Okay.
Jung Min.
(Jung Min joins Jong Kook's team.)
- Jung Min. - They're in the same team?
- Okay. - Jung Min is there.
Let me see.
And Yu Hwa.
- Gosh. - What's wrong?
(Letting out a sigh)
Wait. You don't like her?
- What was that about? - His reaction was...
He didn't seem too happy in his reaction.
- Jung Min. - That's not true.
It's surprising.
I have two guests on my team.
And there's Seok Jin.
Jee Seok Jin.
- And Jeon So Min. - No, I don't want to.
(No, I don't want to.)
Don't do this.
- Stop it. - It's just the big data.
It's from the big data.
It's just from the big data.
- This is good. - What data is that?
- Is there any ground? - He has 10...
He has 10 coins and So Min has minus 5.
That's good.
- No. - Just join his team.
- Go, So Min. - It sounds perfect.
- In total... - Let me join them.
The three teams need to have similar numbers of coins.
Okay. Come here.
- It's done. - This is it.
You should put the card on your head.
You shouldn't look at it though.
We can't lie about the cards.
Can we ask direct questions?
Like "Is it a man or a woman?" Can we do that? Is it okay?
Please put it on your forehead.
You guess the name on your head.
(Song Ji Hyo is IU.)
All right.
(Jee Seok Jin is Bruce Lee.)
(Choi Yu Hwa is General Yi Sun Sin.)
This is hard.
(The first person to give the right answer gets 3 points.)
Am I attractive?
(Am I attractive?)
- Am I attractive? - Yes.
(He's so attractive.)
Very attractive.
Am I a man?
Yes.
An old man?
(Am I an old man?)
I've never thought that way.
But he is quite old.
Wait. The question is...
Am I a man?
(Am I a man?)
She has very little chance of being a man.
What was that?
(She has very little chance of being a man?)
You should just say no.
- What is he talking about? - You can't do that.
What am I supposed to say then?
Am I alive now?
- Yes, you are. - I'm alive now?
Am I alive?
It might be a man?
Am I alive now?
You can't just ask Seok Jin questions...
and ignore his questions.
(You should answer his questions too.)
How can he guess?
Why aren't you answering Seok Jin's questions?
How could you pretend not to hear him?
Please answer my question.
Please meet Seok Jin's eyes...
and answer his question.
No one answered his question.
Am I alive?
No, you aren't.
(She finally answers.)
How old am I?
(How old am I?)
How old are you?
(That's a good question!)
You are less than 40 years old.
(You are less than 40 years old.)
My goodness.
- It's true. - That's right.
- This is insane. - It's true.
- It's true. - It's true.
- It's true. - He didn't lie.
- This is insane. - It's true.
It's true.
- Am I a comedian? - What?
A comedian.
No, you aren't.
Thank goodness we made her go first.
We have no expectations for her.
I have seen a comedian play this man.
- That's right. - He is right.
- Good job. - What's my last name?
I can't give you your last name.
Ask about your profession,
not your last name.
- What's my profession? - Your profession?
(Flustered)
(What should I say?)
- What? - Say it.
- Your profession? - Yes.
You are a civil servant.
A civil servant.
(General Yi Sun Sin was a civil servant.)
- A civil servant. - Don't be like that!
- It's true! - Just tell her the profession.
It's true. A civil servant.
It's true, but...
- Tell her the profession. - I will do that. Okay.
- You are a soldier. - That's right.
You are a soldier.
- What's my profession? - Your profession?
(What's my profession?)
You are a multitalented entertainer.
- That's right. - It's true.
What's my profession?
(It's my turn.)
Why won't anyone answer my question?
Hey! Answer his question!
- Everyone ignoring me! - He doesn't know anything.
Yu Hwa.
- You aren't telling him anything. - Seriously.
You need to answer his questions.
I don't know anything.
- Tell him the profession. - Please do that.
Give him a clear answer.
He only has one profession.
- No, he doesn't. - What's my profession?
- A multitalented entertainer. - That's right.
- A multitalented entertainer. - You are really good at sports.
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
(Did Ji Hyo figure out that she is IU?)
Baek Jong Won.
He told you that you aren't a man.
What is wrong with her?
Ji Hyo asks questions but forgets the answers.
- She forgets the answers. - I know. This is driving me crazy.
Oh, I am not a man.
- Am I alive? - What?
Am I alive?
(That's a sharp question.)
That would be hard.
What is your problem?
That would be more than hard.
- "That would be hard"? - Give a clear answer.
- You... - Let me answer.
- If he is alive... - Go ahead.
General Yi Sun Sin.
(She isn't sure but...)
- He was a soldier. - Correct.
No way! No way!
(Yu Hwa guessed the answer, "Yi Sun Sin",)
(from "A middle-aged soldier who passed away".)
How did you know?
- How did you know? - Yi Sun Sin.
He was a soldier...
from back in the days.
- "A soldier who passed away". - No way.
- She realized he was someone great. - That's right.
It was a hard one.
The team gets three points.
We need to place second.
- We can eat that way, right? - Let's place second.
What do I do these days?
(Bruce Lee asks, "What do I do these days?")
You are on hiatus.
(I am on hiatus?)
- Ji Hyo! - It's true!
What else am I supposed to say?
- That's too much. - He is on a hiatus.
Am I alive?
Oh, I passed away.
I answered that question.
- Didn't you ask that question? - Didn't you know?
- I answered that question. - I don't remember.
I was sullen...
because everyone ignored my question.
Would it be okay if I throw in a white towel?
- Seriously. - We have...
- He is really bad at this game. - We have...
no hope.
Am I a foreigner?
Yes, you are.
You should ask another question.
Am I a foreigner?
Your name sounds foreign, but...
I mean...
(He mistakenly shares a valuable piece of information.)
- It's a big hint. - Why did you tell her that?
It's a big hint.
I made a mistake.
- Ji Hyo, use this hint. - I made a mistake.
I am a woman...
whose name sounds foreign, right?
Seok Jin tried to twist his answer.
Let me answer.
(What will be Ji Hyo's answer?)
whose name sounds foreign, right?
Seok Jin tried to twist his answer.
Let me answer.
(What will be Ji Hyo's answer?)
IU.
(Correct)
Correct.
Okay!
(Ji Hyo places 2nd.)
(He hits her because he is annoyed.)
- Okay. - That was too easy.
- It couldn't be helped. - Bruce Lee.
It couldn't be helped.
Seok Jin wouldn't have been able to get it right.
- I thought it was a Westerner. - He didn't have a chance.
Now, pick...
- the next set of members. - I will go next.
Sit down.
(Jung Min is Sejong the Great.)
(So Min is Cinderella.)
Who wants to ask a question first?
(Se Chan is...)
(Ah Gwi?)
(Ah Gwi is a character in his 40s or 50s...)
(with a knack for gambling and a coldhearted personality.)
(Will Se Chan be able to get it right?)
Who wants to ask a question first?
- All right. - So Min, you can go first.
All right.
Am I alive?
(Cinderella asks, "Am I alive?")
(She isn't a real person.)
It's hard to say.
- Is it hard to say? - It's really hard to say.
- What's hard to say? - It's not hard to say.
Can your answer be like,
- "You are alive in my heart"? - That's right.
Of course.
- You are alive... - That's the perfect answer.
- You are alive in our hearts. - You are alive in our hearts.
You are forever alive in my heart.
Am I not a person? I'm a person, right?
Would you go out with me?
- What? - Would you go out with me?
Gosh, if you would give me a chance...
(He grabs his chance.)
I would go for it.
- Anyone would go for it. - I would go for it.
- Anyone would go for it. - Even if I spend all of my money...
It's strange to see Se Chan say that...
to So Min.
I would go for it.
Am I a man?
- Yes. - Yes.
Am I...
in the entertainment business?
(Ah Gwi asks, "Am I in the entertainment business?")
You know,
- it's hard to say. - That's a bit...
Was that a sharp question?
I don't know which side of you I should focus on.
- Is it hard to say? - To be honest... No, no.
You have nothing to do with the entertainment business.
I have nothing to do with it.
- You have nothing to do with it. - He is a separate character.
- Thus, - That's right.
- he has nothing to do with it. - That's right.
He isn't in this industry.
Really?
- Jung Min, ask a question. - Ask a question.
Am I a character?
(Sejong the Great asks, "Am I a character?")
You are a character at times.
- Yes. - There could be merchandise.
- That's right. - Don't give away too much.
I have a hunch.
I think this question will tell me everything.
(He is certain.)
(What is Se Chan's crucial question?)
I am popular these days, right?
No.
(He doesn't have a clue.)
No. No.
It was so funny to see you act like you have a hunch.
I must be popular these days.
- No. - It was so...
- He makes me laugh. - Se Chan, you were an eyesore.
Our faces are turning red.
Okay. The answer is no.
I thought I had a hunch.
In my case, what is my nationality?
- Nationality? - Which country am I from?
- It's important. - That's right.
It's a sharp question.
- Can I make a guess? - Yes.
I think you are British.
(That's my guess.)
(Is that because she uses English in the animated movie?)
Say what you think.
- That's what I think. - That's right.
I think you are British.
What do you think?
I think...
- she is Norwegian. - Our answers are close.
- Really? - Norwegian?
Is it Xylitol Gum? "Hyva, hyva."
(Shouting)
- Ignore that. - Stop it.
(Hyva, hyva?)
Don't get fooled.
- Don't get fooled. - Don't pay any attention to him.
Haha is lying...
- when he does something like that. - Don't look at him.
- Don't get fooled. - Don't pay any attention to him.
Don't... Don't pay any attention to me.
Jung Min, ask a question.
I am...
(I am...)
Did you say I am a celebrity?
He lost his focus.
- Jung Min, what are you doing? - Jung Min, eat some chocolate.
- Jung Min. - Would you like some chocolate?
(Okay, okay.)
Am I... Am I a person?
- Yes. - Yes.
- My goodness. - Of course, you are.
Jung Min, what are you doing?
- What is your problem? - Seriously.
- He isn't as smart as I thought. - I know.
- Go and wash your face. - Everyone is a person.
Your eyes are unfocused.
- He isn't as smart as I thought. - Hey.
Everyone is a person.
You know,
I had intentionally saved him for later.
- All right. - I was mistaken.
I made a mistake earlier, but I have a good hunch now.
You have a good hunch.
Let's focus.
Please ask...
- a sharp question. - Please refresh us.
- Please refresh us. - Okay.
(One question that will refresh the frustrated onlookers' hearts)
I am young, right?
No.
(I am young, right?)
- You aren't young. - You were young once.
That's right.
(He doesn't have a clue.)
- He doesn't have a clue. - Seriously.
- What is he doing? - Seriously.
He doesn't have a clue.
- What are you doing? - He doesn't have a clue.
Give me two turns.
(Okay!)
After two turns, I will give the right answer.
Just you wait.
- Give me two turns. - He is ridiculous.
It's so funny to see him pretend to be sharp.
- Okay. - You are nowhere near the answer.
- Jung Min, ask a question. - Ask a question.
- What's my profession? - There you go!
You write.
- I write? - Yes.
Here is the thing.
- What people say... Jung Min? - Yes?
People twist the words to drive you further away...
- from the answer. - Really?
- You write. - Don't take them literally.
Jong Kook won't let you come back if you fail.
Jung Min, I will speak to you casually.
- Okay. - He is angry right now.
He is a bit annoyed. You need to concentrate.
Jung Min, you are doing a good job. Okay.
You are...
a high-ranking civil servant.
(Here is a hint.)
That's not half bad.
- I put it bluntly. - That's not half bad.
Listen to that answer.
- It's true. - Jung Min, combine the two hints.
That's right.
What do I write?
You write Korean.
- You write Korean. - What?
(It's a daring hint.)
My goodness.
(A high-ranking civil servant who writes Korean?)
- Let's go. - Jung Min, let's go.
Did I live back in the days?
- Yes. - Yes.
(Jung Min also figures out that he lived back in the days.)
(Did he figure out the answer?)
Han Seok Bong.
(The best calligrapher of Joseon, Han Seok Bong)
(He ruined his chance.)
Han Seok Bong.
Han Seok Bong! Han Seok Bong!
I can't believe him!
- Hey! - No, he could think that.
- For goodness' sake. - He could think that.
Did I go in the wrong direction?
- A high-ranking civil servant. - That's right.
- I gave all the hints. - The three of you...
should make a show.
This is the best.
- Hey. - Jung Min.
"The Fools' Show".
I will ask a question.
Please ask a sharp question this time.
I got an idea when I heard his answer.
- Really? - I was like, "That's right!"
How much do I make in a year?
(How much do I make in a year?)
- It's the worst. - It's the worst.
- It's the worst. - It's the worst question.
- What? - It's performance-based.
- Performance-based? - Yes.
Do I have a performance-based salary?
- For goodness' sake. - Performance-based?
Performance-based?
- Jung Min, that was a good one. - Performance-based?
- That was a good one. - A performance-based salary.
- Good job. - I have a performance-based salary.
- That means... - Jung Min, that was a good one.
It's a big hint.
- A performance-based is? - That's right.
(A performance-based salary)
So Min, ask a sharp question.
Is there a song I sing?
Is there a song about me?
I have heard it.
- There is a song. - Please sing it.
- You can hum it. - That's right.
I don't know the song.
I will sing it.
(Some time)
Hey!
What? What?
What? I was singing the song.
If you don't know it, just say so.
- If you don't know it, just say so. - I was singing the song.
If you sing it as you please...
I was singing the song.
Where did "Some time" come from?
Kwang Soo, sit down.
Let me answer.
- A high-ranking civil servant. - Cinderella?
(Cinderella?)
I can't believe it.
Cinderella.
Correct.
(Team Blue gets 3 points.)
- How did you know? - It just occurred to me.
My goodness.
How did you know?
It just occurred to me.
Jung Min, let's place second.
- Let's place second. - Jung Min.
You are almost there.
Am I alive?
- No. - I am dead.
You know you lived back in the days!
(You know you lived back in the days!)
Jong Kook.
He already said you lived back in the days!
It was basically the same question.
- Jung Min, don't lose to Se Chan. - You are almost there.
Jung Min, I told you everything.
- You are almost there. - Let me answer.
- Sejong the Great. - All right.
(Jung Min beats Se Chan and gets 1 point.)
So Min shouldn't have said anything.
- All right, Jung Min. - You almost had it.
- You could have won. - Look at yours.
- You surprised us. - Look at yours.
Ah Gwi?
(He never imagined it.)
How are we supposed to know how much he makes in a year?
That's right.
(After the 2nd and 3rd round)
All right. This is the last round.
I won't joke around this time.
I will show you what I can do, Jong Kook.
Okay.
(Jae Seok is Count Dracula.)
(Count Dracula is a fictional character...)
(who was based on a Romanian king.)
(He is a rich man...)
(who lives the life of a vampire at night.)
My goodness.
(Se Chan is Freddie Mercury.)
(He is receiving more love thanks to "Bohemian Rhapsody".)
- This is... - Go, go, go! Look.
- Look at Se Chan. - You can do it.
- Kwang Soo. - Let's go, Kwang Soo.
- Let's place 1st. - If we place 1st this time,
we will receive the coins.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
I'll go first.
- What? - You lost.
- I will ask... - Why would you do that?
- We never decided on it. - The winner goes first.
We never decided that the winner goes first.
All right. Let's go in this direction.
Okay.
In this direction?
Shouldn't it be clockwise?
No, we are righthanded. We should go in this direction.
Do you want to go first? Go ahead.
- Go first. - Okay.
Am I alive?
(Jae Seok asks, "Am I alive?")
(He is well and alive before your eyes.)
- You are alive. - Yes.
- You are alive. - You are alive.
Read the first letter.
(Read the first letter.)
- For goodness' sake. - What?
- You can't do that. - What?
- Who am I? - Read the first letter.
- Then I could ask the same thing. - Read it.
Asking you to read the entire thing would be against the rules.
Just read one letter.
- I will give you a crucial hint. - Okay.
- If I tell you the first letter, - What?
you will be able to guess the full name.
The full name.
Then I will cancel this question.
(Is that so?)
- What? - You can't cancel it.
- What is your problem? - You didn't read the first letter.
- Don't be ridiculous. - In that case,
what's my profession?
- Your profession? - Yes.
I will know the answer after a few questions.
You run a business.
- No, he doesn't. - He does too!
- What? - He doesn't run a business.
I will end you if I later find that this information is wrong.
I can tell you.
- You are rich. You are rich. - That's right.
You do something bad.
- I do? - Yes.
- I do something bad? - Stop sharing information.
Why are you telling him everything?
Each question is taking an hour.
I will ask a question. What's my profession?
- You are... - It's very clear.
in a popular field.
That's not a profession. Am I a singer or...
You can't word a question that way!
(You can't word a question that way!)
(What?)
What did I do?
You can't do that.
What's my profession?
- A celebrity. - A celebrity?
Am I a singer?
(He has a hunch.)
(Hesitant)
The thing is...
- Personally, - Go on.
I have seen him sing.
- Is that allowed? - This is driving me crazy.
"I have seen him sing."
Seok Jin, are you going to drink coffee?
(What?)
(Am I seeing things?)
He wanted a cup of coffee.
(Is he getting coffee in the middle of the shoot?)
- What are you doing? - That was so sudden.
- Keep going. - That was so sudden.
- What was that? - Don't mind me.
- I thought I was seeing things. - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - We are having a shoot!
How could you get coffee in the middle of the shoot?
Just keep going!
(The members of Running Man are strange.)
Have you seen me sing?
Just tell me that.
- I have seen you sing. - That gives you...
the answer.
I am a singer. Okay.
- I have a question. - Okay.
Tell me...
(I have a question.)
if you have met me.
(Jae Seok asks, "Tell me if you have met me.")
I haven't.
(Thinking)
Why won't he answer?
Hurry up and tell him.
Answer the question.
Tell him honestly.
- Have you met me? - Hurry up.
- Yes, I have. - Have you met me?
Yes, I have.
(Does that mean I am a celebrity?)
What's my nickname?
- What do you think is my nickname? - It's a sharp question.
- Your answer must make sense. - It's a sharp question.
- Your answer must make sense. - It could be...
a nickname from childhood.
What's my nickname?
- I don't know. - I think it's Tiny.
- Tiny? - Yes, Tiny.
(How is my nickname Tiny?)
Tell the truth!
- That's how he is called. - Yes.
I have heard that nickname.
- All right. Let me ask a question. - Do I have a tiny body part?
- Is it about a body part? - It's not like that.
It could be about their height.
- He doesn't know. - Tiny?
Let me answer!
- Haha. - You jerk!
(Haha)
(Haha gets dragged into this.)
That's right. That's right.
That came out of nowhere.
- If my nickname is Tiny... - Don't be like that.
I was just thinking about the nickname.
I can't believe you.
- I will give you a hint. - Okay.
Sticky Rice.
(Does Jae Seok have that nickname?)
- Sticky Rice. - That's right.
- I have heard of it. - Why Sticky Rice?
- He was called that for a while. - Sticky Rice and Tiny.
- Sticky Rice? - That's right.
Tiny Sticky Rice?
All right. What do I wear?
(It's a sharp question about Count Dracula's attire.)
You wear something like Song Hae's outfit.
(Something like Song Hae's outfit?)
Song Hae?
Isn't that right?
Something like Song Hae's outfit?
- Is there a certain style? - Well...
Tell me what kind of clothes I wear.
You wear oversized clothes.
- Oversized clothes? - Yes.
(You wear oversized clothes.)
(Oversized clothes?)
That's right.
He does wear oversized clothes.
- All right. - Oversized clothes!
Oversized clothes!
He said oversized clothes!
Let me ask a question.
Sing a line of my famous song.
(This is a disaster.)
It's a good one.
You have to get the melody right.
You can go first.
(Running Man)
Running Man?
What?
(A famous song by Freddie Mercury, "Running Man")
What was that?
Sing the lyrics.
- I sang the part I remember. - You sang that song.
- You know the song, right? - It's that song.
- I sang it. - That's right.
- I was going to sing that part. - Really?
- We heard it. - Okay.
(Safe)
(Hey, yo)
- "Hey, yo"? - Does that song really exist?
Hey, yo
(Does Freddie Mercury have that kind of a song?)
- "Hey, yo"? - "Hey, yo"?
(Hey, yo)
Isn't it that song?
(Isn't it the line that symbolizes the singer, "Ay-oh"?)
He sang it well.
- Okay. - Kwang Soo told him everything.
- It's a very nice hint. - I am almost there.
I am almost there.
What's my nationality?
They don't know that.
- I don't know if it's true, - You have to tell him if you know.
but maybe a Czech.
(Dracula is Romanian but Kwang Soo thinks he's Czech.)
I'll ask a question.
Let me answer. Dracula?
(Let me answer! Dracula?)
- Hold on. - Correct.
(Jae Seok wins 1st place.)
(He took "Czech Republic" as a hint and deduced the answer.)
I did that to confuse him.
(Team White scores 1st place with 7 points.)
They're a singer and not in an idol group.
Kwang Soo, focus on the nickname.
- That's the most certain hint. - Sticky rice.
- It's my turn. - Tiny.
- Tiny. - Answer me.
How many characters is it?
- That's too direct. - Number of characters.
Number of characters?
- He won't know. - He won't know.
He won't know.
- Tell me the number of characters. - He won't know regardless.
Six characters.
What?
Six characters?
He's shocked.
See?
I'll ask a question.
Do you personally think... Be honest.
Is this person handsome?
(Am I handsome?)
(Give him a good answer, Se Chan.)
- Personally, okay? - Tell him!
- Do people think he's handsome? - Yes.
No.
(No.)
(Goodness, Se Chan.)
Okay!
People don't think this person is handsome?
That's enough.
You got everything.
Think about it carefully. You got everything.
It's an ugly, tiny, Glutinous Rice,
an all-around entertainer, and a man.
(Kwang Soo accumulated many hints.)
- Can I ask more... - Let me answer.
- What is it? - Haha.
I mean...
(Haha is surprised.)
No, that's not what I meant.
Goodness.
That's the answer.
- This can't be Haha. - He got me.
Question.
Has he been on Running Man?
(Have I been on Running Man?)
- Yes. - He has.
Was he a guest?
- He has. - Yes.
It was a tiny man?
- He's ugly and tiny. - This is so frustrating.
- He's close. - He's so close.
Is this one person?
- Is it one person? - Yes.
- What is it? - It's one person.
- Wait a minute. - His name has six characters?
He was a guest, but Jae Seok hasn't met him?
No.
He was a guest on Running Man, but Jae Seok hasn't met him?
(Are you sure?)
Oh, gosh.
(The secret behind the unseen guest)
He was an ugly kid on Running Man,
but he hasn't met Jae Seok?
He hasn't.
He hasn't met me.
- You're so close. - Kwang Soo.
- Question. - Let me answer.
(Se Chan sounds confident.)
(It's one person with six characters in their name who sings "Ay-Yo".)
Freddie Mercury.
(Freddie Mercury)
Correct.
(Se Chan wins 2nd place.)
(He beats Kwang Soo and saves his face.)
How did you know?
Hey!
(Who am I?)
That was frustrating.
- Hey! - Idiot.
That was frustrating. Tiny.
I had many nicknames,
but when I used to eat a lot of sweet rice donuts,
my friend called me...
Sticky Rice momentarily.
I had no idea.
So first place is...
Jung Min, Jong Kook, Yu Hwa, and Jae Seok.
You'll get five R Coins.
As a bonus, you can pick people to steal five coins from.
You can steal the coins.
We did so well.
Whose coins do you want to steal?
- I'll steal Kwang Soo's. - Of course.
All four of you?
Hold on. Is that allowed?
- Is this allowed? - It's up to them.
I had black.
Will he have four left?
- He'll have four left? - He will.
Is this allowed?
How many will they take?
- He still has 4 left. - I started with 34.
I'll deduct 20 from Kwang Soo.
He lost all he had.
You still have four left.
Jae Seok has 19.
We'll keep moving along.
This is your chance to win additional coins.
Let's proceed with Full House.
Let's all go for black.
All black?
- Kwang Soo will go for black. - I'm certainly going for black.
Please step up one-by-one.
(What will the result be this time?)
(Se Chan picks the coin first.)
(Everybody picks.)
Okay, should we turn this around?
Okay!
- Okay! - This time,
- when I count down, - I won't let everybody win.
- raise it over your head. - Okay.
- 1... - 1...
(They can get anything from plus 20 coins to minus 5 coins.)
two,
three!
(What is the result?)
- I'm relieved. - How many blacks are there?
(Haha, Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and So Min for red coins)
(Ji Yeon, Yu Hwa, and Jong Kook for blue coins)
(Jung Min and Jae Seok chose black.)
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin as well.)
- Black... - Good.
Since we have black,
blue and red will receive five coins.
- Okay! - Yes!
- Black is minus five. - Since there's black.
Four of you. Kwang Soo, Seok Jin,
- Jung Min, and Jae Seok. - He's kind.
Kwang Soo, you get a penalty.
Kwang Soo is falling to the bottom.
- Did I have four? - You did.
- Is he minus now? - He is.
Let's go eat.
- Okay! - Okay!
I knew it.
- This looks good. - This is awesome.
There are crab and soybean.
This is all crab.
(Crab and clam bibimbap are great with rice.)
That looks good.
This is driving me nuts.
That looks so good. This is driving me nuts.
- This is good. - Seaweed soup is really good.
- This is awesome. - Try one.
I feel sorry for those who can't eat.
This is a delicacy.
I like all everything that's served.
Seaweed soup is really good.
Kwang Soo.
(Ta-da)
(How's my card-flipping skill?)
- "One Eyed Jack". - "One Eyed Jack".
(He's happy they're promoting his movie.)
What are you doing on September 11?
Why?
"One Eyed Jack".
(Let's all go watch it.)
(Sliding)
You're unbelievable.
- I want to give him some. - Shouldn't we give him some?
(Should we give him too?)
What are you doing on September 11?
Me? Watching "One Eyed Jack".
(He pays the promotion fee.)
Is it out already?
(Thank you but it's so random.)
Does it taste like "One Eyed Jack"?
Gosh, "One Eyed Jack".
(Gosh, "One Eyed Jack".)
(He's buying time so that Se Chan can keep doing it.)
The seafood soup tastes like...
- "One Eyed Jack". - "One Eyed Jack".
The seafood soup is so good.
(They promote the movie and finish eating.)
We're here.
What's this?
- What's this now? - What's this?
We're going to get wet.
This is it.
We have to reach the other end without falling in.
- Is this a quiz? - Yes, it is.
It's a quiz.
The last mission will be conducted in three teams.
It's Poker Face Quiz.
(Last Mission: Poker Face Quiz)
Is this the last one?
Choose one person to represent each team.
One person from each team will do somersaults,
and whoever reaches the buzzer first...
will get to answer the question.
If they cannot reach the buzzer in five seconds,
the entire team will get one coin deducted each per second.
(The entire team will get 1 coin deducted per second.)
We're in trouble.
The rest of the team can fill out the answers...
according to the questions.
The person representing each team...
can pick one person from a different team...
and guess whether their answer is right or wrong.
If the person is correct, they will get two R Coins...
and get to pick another person.
(Team Red, Blue, and White)
- Let's go. - If you are over five seconds,
you get one coin deducted for every second.
So Min, roll fast.
Let's go.
(The entire team gets 1 coin deducted for every second over.)
Ready...
(They get to answer questions in the order they press the buzzer.)
Set...
(The game starts.)
(They are on standby and start doing somersaults.)
So Min...
Good job. Hurry, Jung Min.
(Splashing)
(Jung Min can do somersaults.)
Good job.
(Next is Haha.)
Oh, gosh.
(Splashing)
(Canon ball)
(She rolls sideways and falls butt first in the water.)
(This is her specialty.)
(At that moment,)
(Jung Min charges ahead.)
Good job. Hurry, Jung Min.
(He reaches the buzzer first.)
Press it. There's no time.
(He touches the buzzer.)
(He gets to pick first.)
So Min, go. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
(She falls in the water again.)
(She was lined up correctly,)
(but goes off course.)
(She can't go straight when she does somersaults.)
She has no sense of balance.
I think she's so funny.
(Meanwhile,)
(Haha touches the buzzer.)
(This is a battle with herself.)
She has no sense of balance.
I think she's so funny.
(She falls in the water the 3rd time.)
- Are you all right? - I think she's so funny.
(She repeatedly rolls sideways.)
(1 splash)
(2 splashes)
(3 splashes)
Are you okay?
So Min.
(She consistently rolls sideways.)
So Min, you're awesome.
She fell all three times.
(Haha: 5 seconds over, So Min: 15 seconds over.)
So Min, you have to guess right.
I'll guess right.
I only fell here, not there.
Here's the question.
In this novel,
this person's step-mother is Ppaengdeok.
Who is this person?
I learn so much on variety shows.
I'm serious. I used to be the worst.
I'm slightly confused.
I'm sure everybody knows. Kids know too.
(Peeking)
(He covers his answer.)
Here's the answer.
Ppaengdeok's step-daughter is...
- Shim Cheong. - Right.
I knew. I knew too.
- Everybody knew. - Please pick one person, Jung Min.
(Jung Min gets to pick one person.)
(He has to guess whether they got the question right or wrong.)
This is tricky.
Ji Hyo, did you know?
She asked me.
She asked if it's the story where they slap with a rice scoop.
"Heungbu and Nolbu"?
Seok Jin, isn't it that?
Where they get rice...
They hit his face...
(It's still bad to mistreat Heungbu or Shim Cheong.)
So I told her she was incorrect.
Yes, I'm confident.
(I'm confident unlike Ji Hyo.)
Seok Jin is...
(Seok Jin is...)
incorrect.
Me?
- He might be incorrect. - Incorrect for this?
- It's possible. - Who doesn't know this?
(If Seok Jin is incorrect, Team White wins 2 coins each.)
(What is his answer?)
(Shim Cheong)
(He's correct.)
(Jung Min's turn concludes, and he wins no coins.)
I hesitated whether to change it or not.
I almost wrote "Shim Shim".
What did Ji Yeon write?
I was certain about the answer.
She doesn't know.
(He's lying.)
- She doesn't know. - Really? How is she?
I'm really curious.
She's a little bit more...
- than Ji Hyo. - Really?
I'm serious.
(She's very pure.)
(Ji Yeon wins.)
It's hard to believe, right?
- I'm serious. - Don't say that.
Ask Jung Min. I'm serious.
There's more that she doesn't know than she does.
(There's a witness.)
(He understands how Ji Yeon is now.)
Ji Yeon, you're correct.
You're correct, right?
(Was she right or wrong?)
(She's incorrect with "Kongjwi".)
- Kongjwi. - Incorrect.
(Haha's turn concludes, and he wins no coins.)
She didn't know.
Ji Yeon meant it.
She was serious.
(Thanks to Ji Yeon's purity, it's So Min's turn to pick.)
Kwang Soo, you knew, right?
I didn't fool around.
Okay.
Kwang Soo is incorrect.
- All right. - Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Was Kwang Soo right or wrong?)
(Chun Hyang)
I knew it.
I'll tell you a funny story.
Kwang Soo whispered this to me just now...
quietly.
"Shim Cheong and Chun Hyang are different people, right?"
(That was a shocking question.)
I got confused.
You're incredible.
(When the answer was revealed)
- Are they different people? - What?
Are they different people?
- Yes. - They're not the same, right?
(Shim Cheong and Chun Hyang are not the same, right?)
(He's Korea's most purist celebrity.)
- You shouldn't criticize Ji Yeon. - I just got confused.
Then was Jong Kook correct?
- He's incorrect. - I think he's incorrect.
- Then Jong Kook is incorrect. - Incorrect.
(She thinks Jong Kook is incorrect.)
I wrote "Chun Sik".
- Was he incorrect? - All right.
(Team Blue earns 2 coins.)
Ji Hyo knows this much. Ji Hyo is correct!
(She thinks Ji Hyo is correct.)
(Ji Hyo is correct.)
Yu Hwa is incorrect.
(She thinks Yu Hwa is incorrect.)
(Yu Hwa is correct.)
See?
I still guessed a lot.
- Good job. - Good job.
(Current Number of R Coins)
(5th to 10th places will get punished.)
Let's conduct Full House one-by-one.
If there are only blue and red coins and no black,
the majority wins five coins.
If everybody picks black, you all win 10 coins each.
If there are more than two blacks with some blue and red,
black gets minus 5, and the rest gets plus 5.
If there's one black,
only that person...
wins 20 coins.
Please go up one-by-one, and make your last decision.
(Kwang Soo picks first.)
I'm going to do blue or black.
This is driving me nuts.
(He had 34 at maximum, but he's at minus 3 now.)
There can't be just one black.
This is driving me nuts.
(This is his last chance to change his destiny.)
(What did he pick?)
All the games today were...
mental games.
(It's Seok Jin's turn to pick.)
This is driving me nuts.
I have to decide.
(He picks one.)
I have to do this. I have to decide.
(What did he decide to do?)
Will I get some green juice?
(They continue to take turns.)
(Everybody is done.)
The last Full House is over.
When I count down,
please raise your coin...
over your head.
Let's do this.
One,
(This vote will determine their destinies.)
two,
(What is the last Full House result?)
three!
(Yu Hwa picks blue, and Ji Hyo picks red.)
Please.
(Jae Seok picks blue.)
(There are red and blue intermixed in close proportions.)
Is there a black coin?
Three!
(Seok Jin picks black.)
There's a black coin.
(If he's the only one, he gets 20 coins and wins the prize.)
There's black everywhere.
Why did you two pick black?
(Jung Min was safe from penalties, but he still picked black.)
Four of you will get five coins deducted.
Rest of you will get...
- plus five coins. - Yes!
- Why did you do that, Jung Min? - I'll take the portable fan.
He wasn't supposed to get penalties, but he does now.
Why did you do that, Jung Min?
We'll bring the prizes first.
Noni is really good for gout.
- This. - It's popular these days.
I'm envious.
Thank you. I didn't expect anything.
- Congratulations. - Jong Kook...
- cares about his health a lot. - I like this.
- I wish you good health. - This is good.
Jae Seok, Yu Hwa, and Se Chan, please take the fans.
Does Jae Seok get a fan too?
(He thought Jae Seok had bad luck.)
There are penalties left now.
However,
we didn't know so many people would be getting the penalties.
There's only one whipped cream,
- and 2 water bombs. - There are 2.
We'll save two people...
from 5th to 7th places,
and save 1 person from 8th to 10th places.
The rules are simple.
I'm getting my hopes up again.
There are blue, red, and black coins in the bags.
Rock-paper-scissors
(The person who chooses a black coin gets the whipped cream penalty.)
Out of this group, the person who gets black...
will get the penalty.
I started at Korean beef set. That's where I started.
I'm different from them.
In three, raise it above your head.
Let's go.
One,
two,
three.
(The person who pulls out black gets the whipped cream penalty.)
What?
(Who will it be that 1 person?)
(Jung Min is exempt.)
(Who will it be from these two?)
Who is it?
It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo gets the penalty.)
(It was going to be him anyway.)
I'm not even shocked.
- Kwang Soo. - It was going to be him.
He almost had Korean beef set.
This is not fun.
It's us now.
(It's time to decide the water bomb penalties.)
This.
No, this one.
I don't know. There's only one spot.
Only one person survives. The person who gets black survives.
- Only one person survives. - One,
two,
three.
(What is the result?)
(Seok Jin gets black.)
(He's exempt.)
(I won't get soaked today!)
It's raining.
- Let's hurry. - We have to hurry.
Congratulations, Seok Jin.
(He won't be completely dry because of the rain.)
We'll start at the same time.
We'll do the whipped cream and water bomb at once.
- Let's go. Good luck! - Let's go. Good luck!
Here we go.
1, 2, 3.
(The penalties are launched.)
Goodness.
(Exploding)
(You never get used to this face.)
Yes!
(This washes away the heat.)
So Min got pushed forward.
She got short.
Good luck with "Tazza: One Eyed Jack".
Thank you.
- Good work. - Good work.
(Jung Min, Ji Yeon, and Yu Hwa, thank you for joining us.)
(They're glad to see Sunny...)
(and SUNMI.)
(Actress Kim Ye Won and Announcer Jang Ye Won)
(They display their charms during dance time.)
(The dance party gets heated.)
(So Min and Ji Hyo intrude.)
(This is part of initiation on Running Man.)
(And...)
(They suddenly get handed a mysterious book of prophecy.)
(Is there a dark force among them?)
(They start doubting each other in order to find the dark force.)
(This gives me the most chills.)
(They're shocked by the truth.)
(The battle between darkness and light. Who will win?)
(War of Light: Black and White)