- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hi.
Hello. Hi.
There are so many hearts here.
- Will there be a male guest today? - Yes, I think so.
- There must be a male guest today. - Yes!
Wait, is Jong Kook the guest?
Look at his outfit. That's a pretty color.
- Hello. - Hi, there. Hey, you.
"Hey, you"?
- What's up with your outfit? - What's wrong with it?
- Look at the color. - Your outfit looks fancy.
- It's fancy. - Why? It's nice.
Goodness, Jong Kook is changing.
- Se Chan. - Move to the side a bit.
Why are your pants inside out?
What do you mean? No, this is fashion.
You wear them inside out.
So Min is wearing her sweater inside out. They're a couple.
- It looks like it's inside out. - She's wearing it inside out.
- I guess this is trending nowadays. - I like it. It's for the LA Lakers.
- What's wrong with you? - Stop that.
(Her sudden shaking move flusters them.)
Stop doing that!
- We were looking at the picture. - Why do you...
Why do you do that?
It's like the illusion picture.
- "Illusion"? - "Illusion"?
(Her behaviors are indeed cheerful.)
So Min asked this to Se Chan.
"Why weren't you at the Sunday service yesterday?"
He said that he had to do something else.
She said, "My gosh, I looked so pretty yesterday."
(I was the prettiest one at the church.)
(The flow of conversation is beyond their expectation.)
Goodness.
She always keeps all of her options open.
So Min...
When I heard that, I clapped for her.
- What she said was... - He complimented me.
It was amazing. How could she come up with such a sweet line?
- It's usually in the textbooks. - Right.
That was amazing.
- Detective Lee, what do you think? - "Detective Lee"?
(He looks like a veteran detective in the crime division.)
(Is he on a stakeout?)
Me? Were you talking to me?
- The color matches my soft at home. - Right.
- Why would you bring that up now? - The color...
- This suits the season well. - That's the color of my sofa.
By the way, Seok Jin...
- asked me this earlier. - Ask what?
- He'll go on a trip by himself. - To where?
- He asked if the Czech Republic... - By himself?
- is a good place to go alone. - Really?
- But you never go on trips alone. - I'm planning to do that this time.
I was going to go with my wife, but...
- He must be seeing another woman. - No, that's not true.
(This is rated-12. What are you saying?)
- No, that's not true. - You're not?
What are you talking about? Hey.
- He said he was seeing a woman. - Hey.
Can we talk about this on TV?
- Can we talk about this? - Hey.
Jong Kook, you must think this is an American TV show.
In my opinion, he might've been kicked out of his house.
(Jee Seok Jin, a 54-year-old man in a crisis)
- That might've been it. - No.
- Seok Jin, stay in the dry sauna. - That's not true.
He's planning to go to a dry sauna in Prague.
- Or places like that. - Right.
- None of my friends went there. - I see.
Thank you for letting me go.
That's interesting.
By the way, I can see we're having...
- a lot of guests. - I see hearts.
I like hearts.
So Min and Ji Hyo will go behind the door today.
- They'll be part of it too? - So we're not having six guests.
Ji Hyo.
- They should think about us too. - Hey.
- They always invite... - Actually, I saw it coming.
They never invite guys.
- Great. - This is nice and free.
So Min and Se Chan might be a couple today.
- That's true. - My gosh.
It's only for the games. You'll be a game partner.
- Good luck. - We don't expect anything.
(I'll be the third guest.)
Did you see? She'll be the third guest.
- Let's go. - Number eight?
I'll be the third guest. Se Chan, I'll be number three.
Go. Just go.
Just go.
(What will happen to So Min and Se Chan?)
Can you remove the hearts before we start?
I guess there are photoshopped pictures.
- What's that? - What is it?
It's a fox.
- Fox. - What does that mean?
(Why does it say "fox" on it?)
- Rabbit. - Rabbit. Like the Year of Rabbit?
- Pig. - Pig.
- I see. Pig. - Bear.
- Tiger. - Tiger.
- Snake? - They are Chinese Zodiac animals.
Is fox one of the animals?
No, fox isn't. Then, that's not it.
- And bear isn't one of the animals. - Today,
six couples of animals will participate in today's race.
Excluding Ji Hyo and So Min,
four female guests who will partner up with you...
have chosen an animal and are waiting behind the doors now.
You will play I Can Hear Your Cries...
to choose your partners.
(Mysterious Animal Farm Race: I Can Hear Your Cries)
The male members can ask questions to the female members.
And the female members will answer in their altered voice.
After asking the question, if you like the answer,
up to three male members can line up in front of the door.
- Three is the maximum. - My gosh.
The male members who lined up...
will listen to the animal's cry and choose 1 from 3 choices.
The member who picks the correct number will pair up with that guest.
All right.
We must listen to the cries.
- It's their special talent then? - But won't this be...
- really obvious? - We'll figure it out.
The first female guest will receive questions now.
Male members, you can ask questions to the female guest.
- Are we starting with the fox? - The fox?
- Ms. Fox. - Hello.
Hello.
Ms. Fox.
Yes, it's me.
(The way she talks sounds familiar.)
- Ji Hyo? - By the way,
- I don't think so. - By the way,
are you a regular member of Running Man?
No.
She's not.
Have you been on our show before?
- Have you? - Yes.
- Really? - She's been on our show before.
What do you think your charm is?
(Hesitant)
Dance?
- Dance? - It's dance?
I guess it's not Ji Hyo.
By the way, why did you choose the animal, fox?
I look like a fox.
- You resemble a fox? - I guess she looks like a fox.
- She must resemble Ko So Young. - Right.
Next up is Ms. Rabbit.
- Hello, Ms. Rabbit. - Okay.
Hello.
- What was that? - Is she a ghost?
(Is there a patient among the guests today?)
- Hold on. She did that on purpose. - Is she a ghost?
- It has to be one of them. - It's Ji Hyo or So Min.
- It's one of them. - We got them.
She didn't want to get caught.
- We'll move on. - What?
- This is So Min. - I think it's So Min.
Aren't you So Min?
What?
You altered her voice, but it sounds so obvious.
- Are you... - Why did you alter the voice?
(As expected, the rabbit is So Min.)
Have you been on our show before?
No, it's my first time here.
- Then, it's not Ji Hyo. - Who did you want to meet among us?
My gosh, I'm really shy.
(This voice...)
- It's So Min. - This is weird.
- It's So Min. - This is So Min.
- It's So Min. - It's So Min.
She's confusing me.
- She's shy? - Okay.
- Okay, Ms. Rabbit. - This is hard today.
- Ms. Pig. - Yes.
- She sounds confident. - She sounds confident.
Aren't you Ji Hyo?
- No. - Yes.
- Ji Hyo wouldn't sound like this. - Right.
Are you a singer?
- Or are you an actress? - An actress?
I'm...
a singer.
- Singer. - Singer.
(Ms. Pig is a singer.)
Why don't you sing for us?
- Why did you ask that? - Come on, Seok Jin.
(Why would you ask that to a guest?)
- Come on. - Seok Jin.
- Sing your favorite song. - Her voice is altered.
- Why would you ask her that? - Why not? She can sing a song.
From head to toe
My gosh.
- That's a great song. - That song...
Isn't that Jin Young?
- Who? Hong Jin Young? - Jin Young.
(She does sound like Jin Young.)
All right. Ms. Bear.
Yes. Hello.
- It's Ji Hyo. - This is Ji Hyo.
This is Ji Hyo.
I'm 100 percent sure.
- It has to be her. - I'm certain of it.
(The identity of the bear who altered the voice herself...)
(is really Ji Hyo.)
(Okay. Ji Hyo is the bear.)
Do you live in Mapo?
No,
- It's her. - I don't live in Mapo.
- It's Ji Hyo. - Hey.
Ms. Bear. What was your opinion of Seok Jin?
Mr. Jee Seok Jin is just Mr. Jee Seok Jin.
She's not witty.
- It has to be Ji Hyo. - It's Ji Hyo.
She doesn't improvise on the spot. This is Ji Hyo.
She doesn't improvise.
- All right. - All right.
- We got it, Ms. Bear. - Hello, Ji Hyo.
Ms. Tiger.
My gosh, hello.
- What did she say? - Hello.
- What did she say? - What did she say?
Ms. Tiger, why did you choose the tiger?
Well,
I sort of have an unexpected charm.
I'm quite strong.
- Her voice sounds husky. - Her voice is hoarse. It's husky.
You can't hide a husky voice even when you alter the voice.
- I know who it is. - Who is it?
(She's surprised.)
Ms. Tiger.
- Yes. - Her voice is husky.
Aren't we in the same line of work?
(Do they work in the same field?)
(Is Ms. Tiger a comedienne?)
- Hey, it's Lee Gook Ju! - My gosh.
- Lee Gook Ju. - Aren't I right, Ms. Tiger?
Don't we know each other?
Didn't we film together last week?
It's my first time meeting you, Se Chan.
- It is her. - It's her first time?
- It's Lee Gook Ju. - Did you not change her voice?
They did, but I know it's Gook Ju.
I don't think you altered her voice.
Ms. Tiger.
- Gook Ju. - Gook Ju.
Nice to see you, Gook Ju.
- Ms. Tiger, don't you know me? - Gook Ju.
- Don't we know each other? - Did you hear her laugh?
Move back.
(Move back.)
(Ms. Tiger is Lee Gook Ju.)
(Bursting into laughter)
It's Gook Ju.
- My goodness. Gook Ju. - What did you say?
You invited me here! Darn it.
- The voice alteration didn't work. - Hey.
You guys invited me here. How dare you treat me this way? Hurry up!
I'm sorry.
Hey, her voice couldn't be altered.
- Ms. Tiger. - Yes,
Have you ever taken a dump at my house?
(Have you ever taken a dump at my house?)
(Nice words)
Everyone at SBS knows that. Stop it!
Seriously.
(She freely takes a dump at his place.)
Because of you, people still call me Rotten Toenails.
(She's the source of Rotten Toenails.)
Rotten Toenails of Seongsu-dong.
It's definitely her. You can't fake this.
You can't fake it.
- Okay. - All right.
- Next up is Ms. Snake. - Let's move onto Ms. Snake.
- Ms. Snake. - Yes.
Please introduce yourself to us. Tell us who you are.
This is...
my first time here.
(A hint about her identity)
It's her first time here.
- Really? - I think it's her first time.
What did you do yesterday?
I practiced yesterday.
- What? - What?
What kind of practice?
I practiced special talents.
And I practiced what I should do on variety shows.
- This must be her first. - She doesn't work in this industry.
- She must be new to this. - She's new.
How long has it been since your debut?
- It's been only 7 months. - 7 months?
- She's an idol singer. - Seven months?
- Wait. We can figure it out then. - Right.
We can figure it out then.
- ITZY debuted less than a year ago. - ITZY?
- ITZY debuted less than a year ago. - It hasn't been a year yet.
Is it ITZY?
(Is Ms. Snake a member of ITZY just like Se Chan's guess?)
- Hold on. I got it. - You got it?
- I have no idea. - First of all...
First of all, let's avoid Ms. Tiger.
Let's avoid Ms. Bear.
- Ms. Bear is Ji Hyo. - Ms. Bear is Ji Hyo.
- Ms. Tiger is Gook Ju. - Ms. Bear and Ms. Tiger.
Which one is So Min? Is it Ms. Rabbit?
- We'll start with Team Fox. - I forgot who she was.
- I forgot her interview. - Her interview was short.
I don't know who she is.
I forgot everything.
- I hope... - Okay.
Seok Jin...
- and Kwang Soo will choose me. - Why?
- Why? - Is she in Apink?
- I guess she wants to stand out. - I thought it'd be fun...
- to play games together. - Is she in Apink?
She doesn't know who will be her partner,
but she wants someone she can easily control.
- Jae Seok. - Hey, that's not true.
- She likes bossing people around. - Right.
- She must like bossing men around. - Yes.
- No. - What are you saying?
Don't make her misunderstand this. I'm not a pushover.
- Go forward. - Go forward.
- She picked you. Go. - Go.
- I'm curious about her. - Me too.
All right. Seok Jin and Kwang Soo are in front of Door One.
You'll hear three different animal sounds.
If you can guess which one's the guest's,
- you'll become a couple. - This is easy.
- We can't mimic them perfectly. - We need to pick the human sound?
Here it is.
This is number one of a fox's cry.
(1st fox sound)
- What? - What is this?
(This is a fox?)
This is a fox?
The second cry.
(2nd fox sound)
I have no idea.
(The sounds are too strange for them to differentiate.)
(Dazed)
- This is it. Number 2. - Number 2?
- That one was strange. - This is the third cry.
(3rd fox sound)
- This one sounds strange too. - Really?
(Listening)
It's either number 2 or 3.
This is crazy.
She's talented. How could she do that?
- This is hard. - I pick the second cry.
I pick number two.
You?
- Kwang Soo? - I pick number three.
- Number three. - If neither of you gets it right,
we will move on.
I pick number one.
The answer is...
(Is it Kwang Soo's pick, number 1?)
(Or is it Seok Jin's pick, number 2?)
(Or perhaps, is it number 3?)
It's number two.
(Number 2 is the answer.)
(Seok Jin wins.)
(Number 1 was a real fox.)
(And so was number 3.)
Fox, please come on out.
(Her identity will be revealed.)
- Who is it? - Who could it be?
(Who is the woman who could mimic a fox so well?)
- Who is it? - Who is it?
(What's the identity of this woman...)
(who wanted a pushover as her partner?)
- Hello. - Hey, Han Na.
Han Na.
(She has conquered the screens...)
(with her amazing acting skills and beauty.)
(She has shown her funny side on the show once.)
(Acting cute)
(You must be...)
(terrible at problem-solving.)
(The talkative lady is back.)
(Crying)
(She did her best to mimic a fox.)
- Han Na. - Han Na.
- Why didn't you pick us? - Han Na.
None of you picked me back then...
when I acted all cute.
My goodness.
- I was waiting for you. - Hey.
It's Han Na and the weak man.
Hello.
It's been a year.
Next up is the rabbit.
Right.
I'm not sure about this one.
- Doesn't it sound like So Min? - It does.
I think it's one of the members.
From the way we see it,
- it's So Min. - If this isn't So Min,
then it'll be tricky.
- I think it's her. - I'm not sure about this one.
I think it's her.
Please talk to us.
Okay.
- I want a handsome partner. - Darn it.
(The moment she talked...)
Then it's me.
Come on.
- That's me. - Don't be ridiculous.
- Come out. - Only three are allowed.
- You want a handsome partner? - Hey.
- Get out. - Okay.
- Det. Lee, leave. - Why would you call me that?
- She wants a handsome partner. - Jae Seok needs to leave.
Get out.
She wants a handsome partner.
Are any of us handsome?
- It's Jae Seok, Se Chan, and Haha. - What do you say?
Except for one, the rest aren't handsome.
(Except for one, the rest aren't handsome.)
And who is that?
(Who is that handsome guy?)
Haha.
(Yes)
Go back.
This must be So Min.
Go back. This isn't right.
Did you hear her?
He's loving it. It was So Min.
Get in line from the handsomest to the ugliest.
This is frustrating.
I'm in first place.
- I'm in 1st place. - He's in 1st place.
- Get in order. - I'm in first place.
- What? - I'm in first place, Se Chan.
- Really? Okay. - Yes.
Here are some rabbit sounds. Here's number one.
Number one, rabbit.
(1st rabbit sound)
- This is... - This is definitely a rabbit.
Do rabbits make that sound?
Do they?
A human can't mimic that.
Here's number two.
(2nd rabbit sound)
(Crying)
I'm not sure.
Here's number three.
(3rd rabbit sound)
I have no idea.
(Whining)
- Isn't this a dog? - Isn't this a dog?
It's when you accidentally step on their tail.
(It's similar to when you step on its tail.)
I have no idea.
- This is hard. - I have no idea.
(It's difficult to differentiate them.)
- She's good. - Is it number two?
They all sound like animals.
- I have no idea. - I think it's number three.
- Number three? - Yes.
I pick number two.
- Then I pick number one. - Are you sure?
Okay, the answer is...
(Which one was So Min?)
Number three.
(Number 3 is the answer.)
(Haha gets it right.)
(It's the desperate cry for love.)
(Giggling)
(Pick... Pick me.)
I think she'll get along with me pretty well.
That was good.
It's So Min.
- It was So Min. - See?
(Ta-da)
It was So Min.
(Hopping)
- You did well. - Right.
How could you make that sound?
Hey, why didn't you get in line?
- I did. - He did.
(She leaves Haha.)
Then why couldn't you get it right?
- I thought it was number two. - It was intentional.
What does this make of Haha?
(What does this make of Haha?)
You greeted him.
- Oh, no. - Poor him.
They look great together.
- He's a rabbit. - Be quiet.
- He looks like a rabbit. - Hop.
It's a rabbit.
So Min is hilarious.
- I'm going to pick the pig. - Me too.
We must.
- I'll go. - Kwang Soo.
- You should go. - I don't think it's Ji Hyo.
- Right. I think she's the bear. - Right.
It'll be easy to differentiate the pig sounds.
Right, it'll be easy.
(They anticipate to become a couple.)
- Ms. Pig. - Yes?
Currently, Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo are in line.
Thank you.
Which one of us would you like to exempt?
Is there one?
(Thinking)
Kwang Soo...
Me?
- Kwang Soo? - Jae Seok, come here.
- Why me? - Get out.
- We'll take him out. - Get out.
- Kwang Soo is out. - Get out.
- Leave. - Okay.
I think she watched "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
What do you mean?
- That was a long time ago. - Really?
I think she watched it.
She saw his back.
She saw Kwang Soo's back.
- I watched it. - See?
(I watched it.)
(Irritated)
She watched it.
Kwang Soo, she saw it.
- Get lost. - Get lost.
Det. Lee, get lost!
- Det. Lee, get lost. - Okay.
- My gosh. - She witnessed his bare back.
Here come the pig sounds. Let's start with number one.
Please play it.
(1st pig sound)
- This is a real pig. - You're right.
- This sounds pretty real. - This is real.
If this is actually her,
- That'd be awesome. - I'll give her my respect.
- Right. - That would be awesome.
- That would be amazing. - This really sounds like a pig.
(2nd pig sound)
(Focused)
Isn't this a snoring sound?
I have no idea. I'm in trouble.
I'm in trouble. I'm becoming anxious.
(3rd pig sound)
(Crying)
If this is her, I'll have so much respect for her.
- Which one is it? - Number three is...
It's...
- This is hard. - Hey.
Those who are good can make this sound.
Number three?
This is too hard.
I... I pick number one.
It sounded too artificial.
- I pick number 3. - I pick number 1.
I pick number 2.
- The answer is... - Which one is it?
number two.
I just picked whatever was left.
(Number 1...)
(and number 3 were actual pig sounds.)
She's too good.
It's number two?
If that's true, she must be a pig herself.
- Seriously. - If she isn't, this is impossible.
How is she so good?
We're partners. Who are you?
(Curious)
- Hello. - What?
- Come on out. - Come on out.
You can come out.
I'm dying to know who it is.
(Who is this pig expert?)
- It's HyunA! - Who is it?
(She's the solo queen who's made a comeback with "Flower Shower".)
(She showed her lovely side on this show.)
(The irreplaceable queen is back.)
(Snoring)
(Oinking)
(The lovely pig is HyunA.)
- HyunA! - It's been a long time!
It really has been.
She and I used to be partners.
HyunA.
- Yes? - How did you make that sound?
My dog kept making pig sounds lately.
- So you mimicked him? - Yes.
(She learned it from her dog.)
- Really? - It was really good.
That's amazing.
By the way, why did you exempt Kwang Soo?
- Why? - Why did you?
I really like him.
But I...
(Hesitating)
Is it because you watched "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks"?
(Is it because you watched "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks"?)
(Is that true?)
Did she?
- Did she watch it? - Did she?
Next up is the bear.
Would you like to say something?
I hope many of you will come.
That was random.
- That's Ji Hyo. - It's her.
If you want to partner with the bear, come out.
Come on!
(She has a raspy voice.)
"Come on" itself seems outdated.
Come here.
No one stepped forward, so we'll move on.
(The director's official words)
(We'll hold off on Team Bear for now.)
Is it Ms. Tiger then?
- Ms. Tiger is up. Ms. Tiger? - Ms. Tiger.
Hello, guys. I hope someone will step forward.
Speak up on the count of three then.
Step forward if you want to.
One...
(Whoever wants to join her will step forward.)
Two.
Please step forward.
- Three. - What...
(Kwang Soo volunteers?)
- Goodness. - How nice.
He stepped forward.
You still have to guess which one is her.
Don't think about deliberately getting it wrong.
- If I don't answer correctly... - This could be your only chance.
Unfortunately, we won't be teamed up today.
Here we go then.
Please play tiger number one.
(1st tiger sound)
(Focusing)
- This is the real deal. - It's a real tiger.
Here's tiger number two.
No way.
That one seemed too real.
Here's tiger number three.
(3rd tiger sound)
(Growling)
(What...)
Are you kidding me?
(Gook Ju proves it's her for the 2nd time.)
Why growl like that?
It's definitely number three.
This...
If you don't get this right, it'll count as cheating.
You can only get this wrong on purpose.
- The sound... - Anyone can tell it's number three.
She should've at least tried.
How is that different from saying "Growl"?
(Growling)
(She actually did her best.)
So what's the answer?
Say the answer in 1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo chooses number 3.)
- Number 3. - Yes, number 3.
Let's see if you're right.
- You could be wrong. - The answer is...
(The answer is...)
- It's number three. - Yes!
(Number 3)
We don't know who it is yet.
- We don't know. - Exactly.
Stop messing with me.
- We don't know yet. - Of course not.
Come on out Ms. Lee.
(Okay!)
(Ta-da!)
It's really hot in there.
(His toenail is rotting.)
(She tells everyone that his toenail is rotting.)
(Tilting)
(The chair went this far into the ground!)
(The two showed great chemistry with their banter.)
I wished it to be anyone else but him.
You're the show's official couple.
- So next up... - It's the snake.
The snake.
(Se Chan and Jong Kook step forward.)
I can't tell.
Here's snake number two.
This one is a person.
Here's snake number three.
That's from a real snake.
- Make up your minds. - I choose number one.
- 1? - You think it's number 2, right?
Then I'll choose number two.
- I choose number one then. - Okay.
The correct answer is number two.
(Number 2)
(Jong Kook guessed right.)
- Really? - No way.
Please come on out.
That last sound...
Who is it?
(Who is the rookie that debuted only 7 months ago?)
(Sihyeon of EVERGLOW)
(Hot rookie EVERGLOW won 1st place...)
(with its debut single "Bon Bon Chocolat".)
(The talented and beautiful Sihyeon is the team's lead vocalist.)
Goodness.
(But...)
I don't know who she is.
(Who is she?)
(To be honest...)
Hello.
(Then her name is shown on a sketchbook.)
She is Sihyeon of EVERGLOW.
- EVERGLOW. - EVERGLOW, right?
- Sihyeon of EVERGLOW. - EVERGLOW.
- What... - EVERGLOW!
She's called Sihyeon because she delivers.
- EVERGLOW. - To be honest,
we don't know much about EVERGLOW, so we apologize.
- It's fine. - Still,
joining us today is Sihyeon...
of EVERGLOW.
And Ji Hyo was the bear like we expected.
(The Pair-up)
(Team Fox, Team Rabbit, Team Pig, Team Bear, Team Tiger, Team Snake)
Let's give it up for everyone who's joining us.
- Thank you. - I wanted to be here.
- Thank you. - Well,
- Han Na is like... - She's like family to us.
- I've been dying to be back. - Right.
Han Na has been quite active in several TV and variety shows...
while she was away.
- Not now though. - No?
- Yes, I've been resting at home. - I see.
What do you do in your free time then?
I mostly just lie down.
- I love it. - I like that answer.
I've been lying down so much that I should buy a special pillow.
- My neck's stiff. - Nice one.
- It's good. - She's one of us.
- I love what you just said. - A special pillow.
This could lead to a TV commercial.
Kang Han Na's pillow for the spine.
Isn't it great?
- For the spine. - The spine.
Han Na can deliver in every way.
An actress promoting a special pillow for the spine?
- Why not? - It's a bit weird.
What's the issue? Han Na, would you...
- accept the TV commercial? - Of course.
(Must you ask?)
(She doesn't hesitate to take the bait.)
- I like how passionate you are. - She's definitely one of us.
I'd love to be in that commercial.
In an old interview,
you once said that you'd love to be married by 32.
How's that plan coming along?
The last time I was on the show...
- was last year. - Right.
- I experienced a breakup. - Really?
(I experienced a breakup.)
- Oh, really? - So I...
There's a reason why you stayed in bed.
- Aren't my eyes misty? - Yes.
- They are. - You had a reason.
- That's right. - You'll now meet your last love.
- Really? Thanks for saying so. - And you can marry next year.
- That's nice of you to say. - I think...
you'll experience one more breakup first.
(What?)
She's the expert on relationships.
Have you become a shaman lately?
(Shaman So Min is the expert on love.)
Anyway, Han Na experienced an unexpected...
- breakup. - An unexpected one?
She's been having a hard time,
so let's cheer her up.
You can love again!
(Don't cry!)
- Good luck. - Thanks.
At times like this, we should stick together, right?
We should all help her bounce back from the heartache.
- But... - Let's all tell her a way...
to get over a breakup.
It's been a while since I've gotten over it.
It's fine. Just let us help you.
- You haven't moved on. - I have.
- No, you haven't. - Your eyes are misty.
Jae Seok's making it worse. He's blowing it out of proportion.
- Han Na said she's fine. - I've moved on.
- Let's bring her out. - He said to bring her out.
- Han Na, let us help you. - Hear us out first.
- Han Na, come on. - You're still hurting.
No, I'm not.
- It's all right. - I've moved on.
- The pain is still there. - Hold on.
You just don't know it.
Everyone tells me I look great.
- You're not all right. - But I am.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Is there a nice song to listen to after a breakup?
- After a breakup? - Yes.
It's better to work out.
He's always heartless.
When I experienced a breakup,
I ran up the apartment staircase.
(Right after a breakup)
Really?
- Really? - I immediately ran up the stairs.
- So after a breakup... - Exercise.
- you run up the stairs. - Exactly.
- Sihyeon, what about you? - I guess I'd go on a trip.
- Have you experienced a breakup? - Is it safe to mention this?
(Is it safe to mention this?)
I haven't been on a trip before though.
(She suddenly put on the brakes.)
- There's a manual. - You haven't been on a trip?
She follows the manual to get out of it.
- It's freaky if you ask me. - She got out of there.
- She made a U-turn. - I've never...
- been on a trip before. - The manual...
- So that's what you'd do? - Dating...
Let's say you just broke up. Where would you go?
- The Czech Republic - The Czech Republic?
Did you experience a breakup?
You must've broken up with someone!
Of course not.
He must've broken up with someone.
My wife allowed it.
Seok Jin, it's been a while since you've broken up with someone.
Well...
What I'd like to say is this.
Is this your image now?
Are you sure you're okay with this image?
You used to stay home for three days in a row drinking.
- That was a long time ago. - With snacks...
- Did that really happen? - Back in the day.
- That's right. - Is that so?
- How much did you drink? - What?
- How many bottles of soju? - One and a half.
For three days?
For three days...
- So in a day... - A bottle and a half each day.
Were you drinking it like cough syrup?
What was that?
- Cough syrup? - You drink small portions of it.
He doesn't have the best alcohol tolerance.
Half a bottle a day...
I've moved on, so there's no need to...
- Just stay still. - It's all right.
- You don't have to say anything. - You just don't know it.
- Listen to your elders. - You're hurting!
- Han Na. - Yes?
Just stay still for the sake of the show.
- I don't want it to last long. - Let us talk.
- Please help me. - HyunA.
- Yes? - I know it's not appropriate,
- but what do you think? - Well,
I'm happy right now.
Right, she's in a happy relationship.
- She's in love. - She doesn't need to consider it.
I've never thought about it.
- So we'll move on. - Right.
- Gook Ju. - Yes?
- What do you think? - I'm saying this...
- Keep it honest. - for Han Na and not for fun.
You should have fun like a piece of trash.
- Right? - Have fun like a piece of trash.
(What?)
- Wait. - Do what you wouldn't do.
- Come on. - You have a dirty mouth.
A person is hurting right now.
- "Have fun like a piece of trash"? - Go to Itaewon...
and be like this all the time.
(Go to Itaewon and be like this all the time.)
What are you doing though?
(Ex-boyfriend, goodbye.)
At a club?
(I'm getting drunk tonight.)
Gook Ju, you're the best.
Gook Ju, why are you covering your face?
It's the side that's covered in tears.
You leave one side uncovered for a new encounter.
The other side is for your tears.
That's realistic advice.
If you start wailing, turn around.
It's realistic advice though.
Even though she's supposed to be sad,
I thought that getting stomped by her would kill me.
Just imagine her stepping on your toes.
You'd die.
It was a piece of realistic advice.
She needs realistic advice like this.
- It was very realistic. - She should dance and have fun.
Det. Lee, tell us what you think.
- I think... - Is he a detective?
she should have many conversations with people around her.
Boo!
(That's boring.)
(Han Na joins.)
- Jo Kka Chi. - What?
(Everyone is shocked.)
The name of his character is Jo Kka Chi.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(It's the character Kwang Soo plays in "Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".)
(It should be pronounced carefully.)
- I was shocked. - I was shocked too.
I was shocked that everyone was shocked.
- Goodness. - That's right.
- Gosh. - I play Kka Chi.
- You've become a better talker. - I saw it in a theater.
- That's not it. - This is only the beginning.
- She's incredible. - It's the name of his character.
- Se Chan. - Like Gook Ju...
Do you have a bit of dating experience?
What kind of question is that?
- I do have a bit of experience. - Really?
How do you get over a breakup?
I gather friends...
- and go to a club. - That's good.
- Just like Gook Ju. - Let's do it together.
But I'm a bit different.
"I'll find another girl!"
Because there are guys like him,
- I should do this. - It's Lee Gook Ju!
- Since he wants a new start... - It's Lee Gook Ju!
Wait!
(A new love starts after a breakup.)
- What is this? - Wait!
Two heartbroken people shouldn't meet.
All right.
That was Han Na's breakup story.
Han Na, you can get over it!
- Get over it! - You're strong!
- You're strong! - You can get over it!
Find new love!
I hope you'll find a new relationship.
- Thank you. - You'll be thankful someday.
- Han Na, smile! - Thank you.
Following Han Na,
let's talk to HyunA.
It's been so long.
She recently released...
a new song.
- "Flower Shower". - We've been waiting for it.
The title is so pretty.
Before anything else,
- let's see her performance. - I can't wait.
- Let's see "Flower Shower". - Okay!
"Flower Shower".
Is that why you're wearing a floral-print jacket?
(It suits the title of her song.)
(She throws her headband off and gets ready to dance.)
(She looks completely different.)
That's so cool.
She looks like a different person when she dances.
She becomes a completely different person.
I wish I could dance like her.
(Lame imitation 1)
(Lame imitation 2)
We can never dance like her.
I wish I could.
HyunA is incredible.
She's different.
You're an amazing dancer.
Actually, Gook Ju has covered...
many of HyunA's songs including "Red".
I might have danced to "Red" more times than HyunA has.
Let's see "Red".
- I'll dance to "Babe". - "Babe".
I'm trying to take this song away from her too.
Don't lose it to her.
- Don't lose it. - Show us!
Please understand even if my belly is exposed.
- Your belly? - My top is a bit short.
(The song thief takes the lead from the beginning.)
HyunA, you should use more of your hips.
(HyunA is surprised at how good Gook Ju is.)
HyunA, you started from the left.
(Gook Ju is confident even next to HyunA.)
- Here it comes. - Gook Ju is lonely.
- She's lonely. - Here it comes.
- Gook Ju. - It's a Jimmy Jib.
Itaewon after a breakup.
(The feminine HyunA dance in the day)
(The sexy breakup dance at night)
Itaewon after a breakup.
(Goodbye, old love. Hello, new love.)
Come back.
- That's crazy. - Come back.
- Okay. - Gook Ju is crazy.
Gook Ju.
- That was amazing. - That was incredible.
By the way, HyunA's boss is PSY.
- Right. - Her boss is PSY?
- Yes. - She's at P NATION.
PSY told me,
"Please be nice to HyunA."
"Don't make her talk too much."
"Just make her dance."
("Don't make her talk too much. Just make her dance.")
(Her boss has a clever strategy.)
HyunA is a good talker, PSY.
- She is. - She is.
PSY also said,
- now that he runs a company, - Right.
he realizes how difficult it is...
to negotiate with celebrities.
He had a bit of difficulty.
It's hard to negotiate?
Oh, my.
PSY said,
"I'm a celebrity too,"
"but it's so hard to talk to celebrities."
It must have been a difficult contract to sign.
- Be nice to PSY. - Of course.
- I'll work hard, Boss. - Right.
- Mr. PSY. - Mr. PSY.
(PSY's support gives HyunA energy.)
PSY seems to care a lot about HyunA.
- I'm scared. - PSY said that.
- Let's move on to Gook Ju. - Me?
- I thought we were done. - No.
- I did this. - We're done.
- Aren't we done with Goo Ju? - We are.
- Aren't we done? - We're done.
- We should talk to her more. - Is there more?
- Gook Ju. - Yes?
Thank you for being with us today.
Pardon? Is that it?
(He ran out of things to ask Gook Ju.)
Wait.
I didn't get to promote anything like HyunA.
Go, Gook Ju!
(We root for you!)
- Let's do this! - What?
All right.
Let's move on to Sihyeon.
- Sihyeon. - Sihyeon.
EVERGLOW debuted only seven months ago,
- but Sihyeon... - Yes.
I did a few survival shows before that.
You've been on many audition shows.
Do you have any tips?
I practiced impressions a lot.
- Impressions. - I worked on impressions a lot.
Then let's see it.
(Sihyeon worked on impressions all night long.)
(Excited)
- You need many weapons. - Right.
Your unique strength.
- Let me mimic the sound of a siren. - A siren?
It's how I warm up my voice.
(Curious)
(She mimics the sound of a siren.)
(Only 3 seconds in, and the atmosphere becomes awkward.)
(What do we do?)
Thank you.
Well...
Is this what she practiced?
- She's so cute. - You're so nice.
Sihyeon must have reminded HyunA of the old days.
- I think she's so cute. - Thank you.
I used to work so hard on things that won't work too.
- "Things that won't work"? - What?
(She said it too straightforwardly.)
Hey, what?
(Is this something that won't work?)
- "Things that won't work"? - She tried so hard.
- She practiced it all night long. - "Things that won't work"?
HyunA, "Things that won't work"?
- You should thank HyunA. - PSY, are you watching?
HyunA is a good talker.
- It does feel refreshing. - That was straightforward.
- HyunA saved Sihyeon's part. - Right.
PSY, are you watching?
- HyunA is a good talker. - Thank you.
- HyunA saved a person. - That was funny.
My team, EVERGLOW...
- EVERGLOW... - Try it.
- Can I promote EVERGLOW? - Go ahead.
(We want to see it.)
Do it.
She threw her team headband.
- The game is not important. - EVERGLOW is more important.
Of course, it is.
Is this poop or a snake, anyway?
It's green poop.
- Who knows? - Let's face it,
- she doesn't care a bit about you. - Of course not.
- She only cares about EVERGLOW. - She hasn't said anything to him.
Right.
Sihyeon only cares about herself and EVERGLOW.
(Her goal today is to promote herself and EVERGLOW.)
- Let's go, EVERGLOW! - All right.
("Bon Bon Chocolat" and "Adios" by EVERGLOW)
"Bon Bon Chocolat".
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
(Sexy)
Oh, my.
Her dance is...
- very energetic. - She's a good dancer.
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
- They're known for their dance. - Pardon?
- They're known for their dance. - Really?
(Powerful dance)
She's a very talented dancer.
I love the song.
Her dance is exceptional.
It's so cool.
(This is what So Min dreams of.)
All right.
"Bon Bon Chocolat".
She's an amazing dancer.
(The new singer is relieved now.)
You should have danced from the beginning.
The thing is,
I'm nervous on variety shows.
HyunA.
What do you feel after doing something like that?
"I at least did something."
(I at least did something.)
- That's very honest. - She's a good talker.
PSY, are you watching?
PSY, HyunA is a good talker.
- She's an amazing talker. - She's a great talker.
(Sihyeon successfully introduced herself thanks to the great talker.)
The teams are decided now.
Before starting the race,
- watch a video first. - A video?
- Someone... - Someone filmed something.
There's someone.
(The video starts playing.)
Once upon a time, on this farm,
many animals lived in harmony.
Animals?
A clean stream flowed across the farm all year round,
and there was always something to eat.
But then one day,
animals that shouldn't be allowed on the farm intruded.
(Animals that shouldn't be allowed on the farm intruded.)
Animals intruded?
- What? - What?
(Animals that shouldn't be allowed on the farm?)
The intruders turned the farm into a mess,
and the animals trembled with fear.
After a long time,
the farm is finally livable again.
The animals may come back home now.
However, do not bring the forbidden animals...
who will destroy the farm.
There are two forbidden animals among you.
Find and eliminate them.
(2 forbidden animals)
(There are two forbidden animals among them.)
Goodness.
- There are 2? - There are 2?
- There are two? - Forbidden animals?
There are two forbidden animals?
But they aren't necessarily a team.
- You're right. - You're right.
You win if you find and eliminate all forbidden animals.
You lose if you get eliminated by the forbidden animals.
The forbidden animals must carry out hidden missions...
before the final race.
They will be eliminated before the final race...
if they fail their mission.
(They will be eliminated before the final race if they fail.)
In each round, the winning team...
will receive a hint about the forbidden animals.
Let's get the race started.
(A match between 2 forbidden animals and 10 regular animals)
It's all about betrayal.
(The current teams)
(Who would be the 2 forbidden animals?)
Forbidden animals can get started on the hidden missions now.
- Are there hidden missions? - There are hidden missions.
If you try anything funny with me, I will take out your teeth.
- Your teeth are too uneven. - Watch yourself.
I am a bit suspicious of Han Na.
- It's about time she gets a role. - Me?
Han Na visited Running Man many times.
- She is good. - She is good.
I think I know who it is.
- Who? - Kwang Soo.
(She goes with her gut feeling.)
(Is it me again?)
- She doesn't know anything. - That's not true.
- He gets suspected every week. - When the talk...
of the hidden mission came up,
Kwang Soo's eyes looked weird.
- You should know this. - His eyes are always like that.
- His eyes are naturally weird. - What!
(His eyes are naturally weird.)
My eyes aren't weird!
- Kwang Soo has weird eyes. - This is how my eyes normally look.
- Kwang Soo's eyes are weird. - Even off-camera.
Is no one going to talk about HyunA's hat?
- That's right. - Jong Kook!
- It's pretty on HyunA. - What?
- It's pretty. - She looks cool.
It's a hat I actually own.
I like this hat.
Really? It's reminiscent of the late Korean Empire.
The hat is cool...
and I get that HyunA likes it,
(The hat is cool and I get that HyunA likes it...)
but it doesn't suit the current situation.
(It doesn't suit the current situation.)
I just want you to know that.
- I just want you to know that. - There are snacks hanging.
- I am sure she knows. - I know,
- but I like the hat. - Okay.
- It gives me confidence. - Everyone, shut your mouth.
- What? - "Shut your mouth."
- Shut your mouth. - Okay.
She can wear whatever she likes.
Hold on. Who started this?
Jae Seok can be so mean.
- Do you want to lose your teeth? - What?
Why is Jae Seok so rough today?
Could it be a hidden mission?
The two forbidden animals...
must complete the hidden mission before the final race...
- to avoid getting eliminated. - Okay.
They get eliminated if they fail to complete it.
The first mission to acquire a hint on the forbidden animals is...
Trust Me Halfway.
(Trust Me Halfway)
Watch a dance video with half the screen covered...
and guess the song title and singer.
If your answers are right, dance to the music to succeed.
If you can't dance very well,
another team could steal the dance.
- Yes! We can steal. - Really?
My goodness.
The team that gets the most number of questions right...
will receive a hint on the forbidden animals.
This is a game for Gook Ju.
Gook Ju has an advantage.
- Gook Ju knows all the dances. - I know the old dances.
The teams that eat the snacks the fastest...
will have a priority.
We will show 10 seconds of the video.
- After you come out... - We come out if we know it, right?
That's right. For your information,
we will play an unrelated song in the background to confuse you.
- Really? - I see.
We need to guess from the dance alone.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
(Nervous)
Play.
(Watching carefully)
(Will they able to guess the song with just half the screen?)
[VIU Ver] SBS E476 Running Man
"Mysterious Animal Farm Race: I Can Hear Your Cries"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Let me answer! Let me answer!
- Let me answer! - Does he know the answer?
What's the answer? What's the answer?
Go up.
- Go up. - This is impossible.
- Can you get it? - A bit more?
- Hold on. - Go up.
Go up.
(So Min steps on Haha's back. Jong Kook lifts up Sihyeon.)
I can't step on your back.
- How am I supposed to do that? - It's okay. Go up there.
You should do it.
(They change the footstool.)
Can you reach it?
(Gook Ju, I am sorry. Let's win!)
(Kwang Soo, you can do it!)
- Can I climb on your back? - Go ahead.
1, 2, 3.
Haha, I can't reach it. I can't reach it.
What?
(He screams and stands on his tiptoes to no avail.)
- Haha, that won't work. - I can't reach it.
(Heave-ho)
She can reach it. She will get it.
(Sihyeon succeeds first.)
- They did it. - We did it!
I think I am going to kiss So Min.
- I think I am going to kiss So Min. - HyunA!
- HyunA. - So Min.
HyunA, don't lose.
I can't reach it, Haha. I couldn't eat it.
(Only one snack remains!)
- This is it. - Here I go.
Don't fall.
- This is it. - I need to go down.
You need to get higher.
(The siblings are competitive.)
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo grab each other's hair.)
(Hair-grabbing in self-defense)
(The siblings have a fierce match for a snack.)
Ji Hyo!
(Ji Hyo is the last one to succeed.)
Good for her.
The one who succeeded first, Sihyeon, will answer.
(Can Sihyeon identify the song from the dance?)
What's the answer?
"Invitation" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
Is it right?
("Invitation"?)
Okay!
(It's a sexy dance that uses a fan.)
(Team Snake will receive a point if they pull off the dance!)
(The singer from the 20th century and the singer from 2019)
(He is as sexy as their backs.)
(Han Na comes forward to steal the dance.)
Let's go!
How did the dance go?
I don't know this part.
(She came forward without knowing the dance.)
(She dances as she wants.)
She is good.
(She only claps at the right moment.)
She is Uhm Jung Hwa!
(I am Uhm Jung Hwa's doppelganger, Gook Jung Hwa.)
(She steals men's hearts with her lethal charms.)
(The main stage is a mess,)
(but she doesn't stop channeling Uhm Jung Hwa.)
What is Gook Ju doing?
- Come here. - Sihyeon got it right.
Thank goodness.
- Say, "Ding, dong, dang." - Sihyeon, ding, dong, dang.
Okay!
(Team Snake receives 1 point!)
All right.
It hurts my back less.
- Let's go. It's okay. - But you can't move far this way.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
- Hold on. - 1, 2, 3.
Hold on.
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
(They practice hard for victory.)
I am heavy.
What is going on?
You know,
you should give Gook Ju a lift.
I want to do that.
I am trying my best.
Can't you carry Gook Ju on your shoulders?
- Can you? - Of course.
- Go ahead. - I can do it.
- You might get injured. - Don't worry about it.
- Hold it. - No matter how heavy you are...
Lower your torso. There you go.
It won't be easy to get up in that position.
I know.
(My goodness.)
All right.
(Jae Seok was confident.)
(Will he be able to carry Gook Ju on his shoulders?)
(Jae Seok, are you sure about this?)
(Gook Ju, I work out.)
(He gathers his strength.)
Okay, okay.
- Slowly. - Jae Seok fell asleep.
(Jae Seok fell asleep.)
- He fell asleep. - Get up.
- Get up. - My goodness.
- Anyone can do that. - Get up.
- We will support you. - Jae Seok.
- Gook Ju. - Yes?
Come down.
(Come down.)
(Gook Ju disembarks.)
His body almost folded in half.
- His body almost folded in half. - Don't say that.
Gook Ju, I am sorry.
Not many people can carry me on their shoulders.
- I am sorry. - Don't overexert yourself.
Not even my dad did that.
(Not even my dad did that.)
He never carried me on his shoulders.
- Let's move on to the next one. - Okay.
Play the video.
(It's even more confusing because of the song.)
What is it?
- I know the answer. - Okay.
- Do you know the answer? - I think so.
(They have a fierce fight for a spot.)
Hey, what are you doing? Get out of the way!
Go up. Can you reach it?
Can you reach it?
Can you move a bit to the side?
- A bit to the side. - Okay.
- I did it. I ate it. - Did you eat it?
We ate it.
- I ate it. - Okay.
Go up.
(Kwang Soo also falls asleep during the game.)
(This must be a bad nightmare.)
(Seok Jin-borghini starts from the garage...)
(because he can't get up by himself.)
(0.1 horsepower)
(0.1-cylinder engine)
(The engine sound is 1000dB.)
Here. Go up there.
Move forward.
I can't move forward. Gook Ju is blocking the way.
(The self-driving mode gets turned on because of Gook Ju.)
(Thanks to Seok Jin-borghini, Han Na places 3rd.)
- I ate it. - Did you eat it?
- I ate it. - You ate it.
(Sihyeon has a chance to answer first.)
(Will Sihyeon get the answer right this time as well?)
Sihyeon, what's the answer?
"Bad Girl, Good Girl" by miss A.
(I think she got it right.)
(Correct)
Did she say "White blood cell"?
"White blood cell"?
I don't know a song called "White blood cell".
- "White blood cell"? - "White blood cell"?
She said, "Bad Girl, Good Girl".
"Bad Girl, Good Girl".
Where did "White blood cell" come from?
I know the song.
(The intro makes their bodies move.)
- It's Suzy. - I know the song.
HyunA, let's go.
"You don't know me."
What are you doing here?
(The dancing queen does her own thing.)
- Do you know the dance? - Of course, I do.
- I need space. - She is incredible.
What are you doing, Gook Ju?
- That's her private camera. - Okay.
(It's perfect teamwork between miss A and the A plus team.)
What's that, Jong Kook?
He's really pretty.
- I know this. - Shut up, shut up
(She moves over.)
(She walks to the center,)
(and plops down.)
(She starts dancing.)
- Look. - What is she doing?
She's right.
- Look at So Min. - What is she doing?
This is the choreography.
I'm speechless.
Next.
- Next. - HyunA
Here she goes.
(Dance Queen HyunA is ready.)
- What about you? - You have to dance too.
- Why don't you know it? - I'll do it too.
(She's got the groove.)
Why don't you know it?
- What's that? - What's he doing?
(Glancing)
- Do you know this? - She's amazing.
- She's amazing. - She knows everything.
(The scorpion move was unnecessary.)
- What's that, Jae Seok? - What are you doing?
(She gets rid of the scorpion.)
Don't get in her way.
- He got hit. - Keep going.
Go, So Min.
Here I go.
(She's the brave dancer of this territory.)
She's cute.
Get out of there.
- Tell her to get out. - Move.
- Move. - Tell her to move.
- Let's do it together. - I don't know this dance.
Go, Han Na.
What's that?
Goodness.
Nice one.
Han Na.
Nice, Han Na.
(She destroyed the choreography and the rhythm.)
(It's all about the feel.)
Good job, Han Na.
(I'm good, right?)
She's good.
Get back.
(They don't move.)
Hey.
This is a one-man show.
Hold on, Gook Ju.
When you were going down, I thought you were The Undertaker.
(When you were going down, I thought you were The Undertaker.)
(She's a legendary professional wrestler.)
- The Undertaker? - I thought you were him.
Stop it.
You said that last time too.
- Sihyeon wins. - All right!
- We did it. - We did it.
- Good job. - We have to get it this time.
We have to get it.
It was so funny when you went down.
Was it okay?
I thought you were The Undertaker.
I've never seen this person.
Make sure you don't collapse.
Haha made me feel worse.
- "You look similar to him." - I'm serious.
- He used to be really popular. - Really?
He rolled his eyes.
- The Undertaker. - Like this?
(You look like me.)
- You look the same. - Is this right?
You look the same.
I don't know what this is. I did whatever they told me to do.
(Swinging)
Jae Seok looks very free today. There's something going on.
- Right? There's something going on. - He's moving a lot on purpose.
There's somebody who's doing something irrelevant to this game.
- Look at his face. - It's not Jae Seok.
(Look at Kwang Soo's face.)
(Han Na's gaze is fixed on Kwang Soo.)
It's not me.
- I'm just looking around. - It's not Jae Seok.
He wasn't looking around.
When we were talking, he was looking off in distance.
- No, I didn't. - Why were you looking at the jib?
(His eyes rested on the jib.)
- I wasn't looking at that. - What were you doing?
Nothing.
This is a difficult question for two points.
- Here's the next question. - Let's go!
Please play the video.
- This one is for two points. - What?
Let's go.
It's an old song. Wait.
(It's not an easy question.)
- Who is it? Chakra? - Who's that?
- Chakra. - I'm not sure.
- Eat first. - Go this way.
- I got it. - 2, 3.
Little more.
- Where? - I ate it.
- Did you eat it? - You can't push me.
Kwang Soo.
- I got it. - Go left.
- She ate it. - I got it.
- Come down. - Look at the outfit.
- There were two people. - Do you know who it is?
Ji Hyo was first.
I'll leave it up to her.
What's this? Nobody knows yet.
The singer is...
(Will Ji Hyo and Se Chan get the answer?)
- Baek Z Young. - Baek Z Young. The song is "Dash".
They got it.
Right?
- How did she know? - I didn't know.
("Dash" is known for the powerful Latin dance.)
(The song plays.)
- What is that? - They don't know it.
- What is that? - What is that?
What dance is that?
- What are they doing? - What is that?
- Is this "Dash"? - They're incorrect.
(I don't agree with this "Dash".)
- Gosh. - I don't know the dance.
- I don't know it. - Move.
Let's go.
Do it like this.
(They have the Latin soul...)
(on their faces.)
- They're good. - What's that?
Move. 1, 2, 3, 4.
(They continue the vibe, and do the samba.)
How's this "Dash"?
(This is a tank dash.)
(This is a collection of old dances.)
- What are you doing? - Stop it.
(The Undertaker is in Itaewon after a breakup.)
What is she doing?
(She tries to overcome the pain with dancing.)
(Is she here alone?)
(This freestyle dance duo is here together.)
We have to give it to Han Na.
We have to give it to her.
She deserves it.
Okay.
What's this now?
What's this?
- What are you doing? - What's this?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - This is "Dash".
What's that?
What?
- When were you ever interested? - You are a dirty punk.
We got the question right. Give us the points.
Producer.
- I danced to everything. - Are you okay, The Undertaker?
Give it to us. We weren't bad.
Team Bear got the question right,
and Team Rabbit will get a point for the dance.
(Team Snake: 2 points, Team Rabbit: 1 point, Team Bear: 1 point)
- We have two points. - Okay!
This is not bad. Good job, Ji Hyo.
We have two points.
The teams that will receive hints about the forbidden animal...
- are Team Bear and Team Snake. - All right.
- You did it. - Okay.
- She did it. - We did it.
Team Bear and Team Snake, please come on up and check.
Okay, let's check.
(They're still doing that.)
- Just the four of you. - Se Chan.
What is that? Is that for the mission?
- What? - What's is that on your foot?
Let's see. Lift your left foot.
Lift it like this. What is that?
- What is it? - What is it?
(Ji Hyo's name tag is on the sole of his foot.)
- I think he stepped on it. - Why do you have her name tag?
(Why is it on the sole of his foot?)
Why does he keep putting it on his shoe?
(He had something on his shoe in previous episodes as well.)
(It's suspicious that Ji Hyo's name tag is on his shoe.)
This is strange. Why is this here?
What are the chances of getting that stuck on his shoe?
- It can. It comes off easily. - Why is this stuck here?
Did you take mine?
Have a look at the hint.
Ji Hyo.
I'm here.
My name tag is gone.
I'm mad.
(What?)
- That's good. - I should have done this.
Jae Seok is acting strange.
- Why? - Why would you climb that?
He's amusing like that.
- Why are you taking his side? - How did you get that scar?
- I was fooling around. - Right.
He's fooling around too.
Kwang Soo was climbing that too.
I was going to eat that.
Sit down.
- Is it over now? - No.
I mean the airing.
How's it over? It's not over.
It's not over?
Is this it?
(It'd be funny if this was it.)
- I'm so tired. - I know.
We used too much energy.
I think I danced well today. Wasn't it pretty good?
You were really good.
- I was pretty good today. - You improved a lot.
- I think I got better. - You improved a lot.
- That's right. - One team at a time.
Hold on.
Then...
(They look confused.)
- It's something to do with a snake. - Did you see it?
This is not about a person, right? It's a hint about the animal.
I'm narrowing down now.
(What hint did they get?)
Round one is over now. Let's move on to the next location.
- Okay! - Okay!
(They move on to the next location after receiving a hint.)
Sihyeon...
resembles Suzy a bit.
- You do look like Suzy. - I thought of that too.
I was wondering who you looked like. You look like Suzy.
I thought it was Suzy when she first opened the door.
- When she came through the door. - Stop it.
- Thank you. - Stop it.
- Stop it. - He exaggerates.
Kwang Soo.
For goodness' sake.
Sihyeon didn't say, "That's not true."
- I mean... - I bet she heard that often.
I am sure Sihyeon heard that often.
- She looks like SUNMI too. - Right now...
- She looks like SUNMI too. - I see the resemblance.
- She looks like Noh Joo Hyun. - She looks exactly like him.
- I see the resemblance. - Seriously.
(They could be a father and a daughter.)
She looks like Han Min Kwan too.
That's right.
He is a lucky man.
Min Kwan!
Jong Kook looks like Park Se Ri.
(Park Se Ri)
There is a strong resemblance.
- I look exactly like her. - Even the hairstyle is the same.
Se Chan looks like Han Moo.
- Kim Kap Soo. - You are right.
Haha looks like Lee Hwi Jae.
- Lee Hwi Jae. - Lee Hwi Jae and Lee Moon Sae.
Lee Moon Sae.
- Kwang Soo looks like Han Ki Bum. - Han Ki Bum.
He resembles Ki Bum a lot.
- The Undertaker. - The Undertaker.
I look like Kwak Do Won, okay?
There is another one, but Se Chan won't tell us.
Tell us. Who is it?
- There is another one. - Tell us.
- Tell us, Se Chan. It's okay. - Promise you won't be upset.
- Promise. - I promise.
She won't get upset.
The Penguin.
You little...
(You beautiful little man.)
Come on. You said you won't get upset.
Isn't The Penguin better?
- What? - My goodness.
The Penguin is cute.
It's not a penguin character...
- you know of. - Really?
I dressed up as The Penguin in "Comedy Big League".
- That's right. - I don't like dressing up that way.
I prefer telling jokes.
Park Na Rae and Jang Do Yeon came up with a scheme...
to make me dress up as The Penguin when I went to the restroom.
Everything moved speedily. As soon as I sat down, they went,
"You can dress up as The Penguin, right?"
"Dress up as The Penguin, okay?" That was how it happened.
I was so embarrassed since it was my first time...
to do something like that.
I closed my eyes and fell asleep.
All the comediennes took photos and said, "This is Hollywood."
- They took so many photos. - It was perfect.
Send the production crew a photo.
They can find it themselves.
I don't want to find it.
(She sleeps when she is embarrassed.)
I don't think HyunA resembles anyone.
She doesn't have any lookalikes.
- Has anyone mentioned anybody? - HyunA would have...
lookalikes in the US.
I don't have any lookalikes.
That's right.
Is that mole real?
- It's real. - Did you draw it?
Oh, it's real.
Seok Jin, is that age spot real? Did you draw it?
(He is genuinely curious.)
- It's real. - It's not an age spot!
Did you paste the hair on your ears?
- I don't have hair on my ears! - I guess it has a function.
Ant legs were sticking out.
Ant legs!
- Ant legs were sticking out. - Ant legs!
(Seok Jin has an age spot and ant legs.)
Forbidden animals, you can do your mission now.
They can do their mission now? I guess they aren't doing it.
We don't know what the mission is.
Won't tell us if they did it earlier?
- Why won't you tell us this time? - I guess they did it.
We will tell you before the final race.
I guess it can be done sitting down.
People in the back are suspicious.
Kwang Soo is too quiet. Everyone is guessing,
- but he isn't saying a thing. - It's not like that.
Seriously, Kwang Soo. Why are you so quiet?
- Seriously. - I think it's something you say.
I don't think that's the case.
(Everyone is suspicious of Kwang Soo.)
(Could he be 1 of the 2 forbidden animals?)
I prepared an acrostic poem.
She prepared an acrostic poem.
- That came out of nowhere. - Do everything you prepared.
It's no wonder she only got an hour of sleep.
She prepared many things.
- Whose name did you use? - Whose name?
- Yang Se Chan. - It's hard to make...
an acrostic poem with my initials.
- Should I prompt you? - Okay.
Y.
Yes, I want to eat lamb skewers.
S.
Say, I want to eat it three times.
C.
Carefully, I will chew.
Why did she only get an hour of sleep?
Seriously.
The thing is,
I prepared a series about eating.
A series about eating.
Sihyeon, it's time to see the real deal.
- Let's go with Jee Seok Jin. - J.
- J. - Jeez, I am hungry right now.
- S. - S.
Seok Jin, did you eat?
- There you go. - She called him by his name.
- This is good. - I know.
J.
Just tell me if you did.
- The impromptu one is better. - This one is better.
The impromptu one is better.
- That was funny. - Good job.
Since Sihyeon gave us acrostic poems,
Seok Jin will return the favor...
- as the representative of the show. - That's right.
Give us one with HyunA.
- HyunA? - Yes.
- H. - HyunA released a new song.
- A. - Ah,
I don't remember it.
(Seok Jin showed a bad example of an acrostic poem.)
He failed.
(He failed.)
He failed to make a decent acrostic poem.
(He failed to make people laugh too.)
I couldn't think of anything.
Kwang Soo, you should give us one.
"Tazza".
Are we still bringing up "Tazza"?
(It's on VOD now.)
- What? - You won't let him forget.
"Tazza" is the last thing I want to hear about.
- Z. - Zip it.
See? That's funny.
"Zip it."
Let's hear another one.
- Another one? - Yes.
- Se Chan, do one with HyunA. - I can't.
- H. - Hey, who is the prettiest idol?
- A. - Ah, it's Irene.
You are right.
Okay, okay.
Someone make an acrostic poem with Han Na.
Se Chan, give us one.
- H. - Go, Se Chan.
Let's go.
- H. - Han Seok Kyu.
- N. - Na Young Seok.
- That was funny. - Good job.
That was a good one.
- He is good at this! - Seriously.
- He is good at acrostic poems. - His poems catch you off-guard.
- That was funny. - That was nice.
Why are there so many things hanging?
This is scary.
It has been a while since I played this game.
This one hurts.
This round is the last chance...
the forbidden animals can do the mission.
Otherwise, they will be eliminated.
- They will be eliminated. - They must be anxious.
- This must be nerve-wracking. - Who is nervous?
- Look at him. - Kwang Soo is too quiet.
He isn't saying much today.
I am confident it's Kwang Soo.
I hope you wouldn't misunderstand.
Kwang Soo isn't good at talking.
(The fool)
What can he do well?
He can do slapstick comedy well. He can't talk well.
He isn't very witty.
(The master of slapstick comedy)
The second mission for a hint is Yes or No, Answer Me.
- Yes or No? - Yes or No, Answer Me.
There will be 10 rounds in total.
In each round, six members will play.
If you succeed once in 10 rounds,
all 12 members will receive a hint on the forbidden animals.
Here are the rules.
The production crew will give you a category...
with a "Like" or "Dislike".
If it's "Like", pick a word that fits the category.
If it's "Dislike", pick a word that doesn't fit the category.
Let's say I said, "I like Korean food."
Then you can answer, "Kimchi stew I like."
- How about "Dislike"? - Let's say I said,
"I dislike Korean food."
Then you can answer, "Pasta I dislike."
Okay, okay.
- I got it. - Spaghetti.
Please pick three teams for the first round.
(Team Pig, Team Fox, and Team Snake)
We will watch you like hawks.
This isn't a difficult game.
It would be strange to make a mistake.
We should suspect anyone who makes a mistake.
I am not a forbidden animal, but I could make a mistake.
No, no.
Don't make excuses.
A mistake means that person is a forbidden animal.
- Let's go. - It means that person is a fool.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Yes or no, answer me
I like Korean food
Kimchi stew I like
(Since it's "Like", Jae Seok chose something that fits the category.)
I dislike Western food
Pasta I like
It's "Dislike".
- It's "Dislike". - "Dislike"!
Will all of them get hit?
(She should have answered, "Such-and-such I dislike.")
- All of us got hit. - I am sorry.
- But... - Only HyunA should get hit.
- HyunA, this is... - HyunA.
If it's "Dislike", you need to say...
what you dislike.
- HyunA. - Yes?
If the producer says what he dislikes, do the same.
- It's not up to you. - Hold on.
I might like what the producer dislikes.
(I might like what the producer dislikes.)
- It's a rule. - It's not like that.
PSY, HyunA has a way with words.
It's a rule.
If it's "Dislike", say what you dislike.
- Repeat that part. - Let's begin.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like Chinese food
Yusanseul I like
I dislike tropical fruits
Apple I dislike
It's right.
I like beverages
Coca-Cola I like
He is acting strange.
I dislike desserts
Yukgaejang I dislike
(Seok Jin passed without a problem.)
(Only HyunA and Jae Seok remain!)
They are almost done.
I dislike Korean movies
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks" I dislike
("Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks" I dislike)
Hey!
She is acting strange!
- You just dislike the movie, right? - HyunA.
She looked at me when she said it.
HyunA, what are you doing?
- She looked at me when she said it. - HyunA.
(When the producer said his line,)
(she stared at Kwang Soo.)
(She stared at Kwang Soo when she said it.)
(Furious)
- She said it so confidently. - HyunA.
I mean...
- She shouldn't have annoyed me. - My goodness.
Did I do something wrong?
Why did you star in that movie?
Was it wrong of me to star in that movie?
I mean...
Why did you star in that great movie?
What are you saying?
PSY would be proud when he watches the show.
- What? - PSY.
That was hilarious.
The first round was a failure.
- Will you switch the players? - Let's switch.
- Let's switch. - Let's switch.
- Let's switch. - The other teams can go.
- I don't know. - It isn't easy. It's confusing.
I don't know about HyunA.
Once you sit there,
you will become a fool.
- You aren't a fool. - You sound like a fool now.
You will have that experience.
- Okay. - Can Se Chan go first?
- Should I start from Se Chan? - Why?
- Why? - Start from that side.
- Have Se Chan go first. - What should we do?
I want to see how Se Chan and Ji Hyo do.
Let's start from Se Chan.
You missed the way...
So Min leaned forward to see you, right?
(I want to see Se Chan.)
(Winking)
For goodness' sake!
(Se Chan, take my love.)
What was that?
- He took a blow. - It was a critical blow.
- He took a blow. - Seriously.
- I got a bruise. - He took a blow.
- Let's begin. - Please give us an easy one.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like amphibians
Penguins I like
- Hey. - Hey.
(Penguins are amphibians?)
You don't know what amphibians are.
- Frogs. - What is it?
- Frogs are amphibians. - Frogs.
Like frogs.
I thought it was fish.
- I thought it was fish. - He thought it was fish.
He doesn't know what amphibians are.
Why did you give him a difficult one?
- Jong Kook. - He doesn't know what they are.
- Why? - I didn't know.
Don't be suspicious of me.
- I didn't know. - By the way, Ji Hyo.
- Yes. - He saved you.
(Thanks, Se Chan.)
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like comedians
Lee Kwang Soo I like
(Lee Kwang Soo I like)
- He's correct. - He's correct.
- Why not? - I was correct.
- He was right. - He has two occupations.
- He's right. - He's a comedian and actor.
If Kwang Soo approves it, we'll give it to him.
- Approve what? - You have to approve it.
Kwang Soo is a comedian.
You can go from an actor to a comedian.
Are you embarrassed to be a comedian?
I paid your dues for several months.
My dues?
Approve it!
- Approve. - Approve.
That didn't count.
It's controversial, so we won't count it.
- He's a comedian. - Just approve.
- Imagine if the edge falls on you. - It'll be so painful.
It'll be really bad if it falls vertically.
Hold on.
- Hold on. - This is worrying.
(As they get more fearful, their concentration increases.)
Go now.
(Calm down, trays.)
Let's go.
Let's start from Haha again.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I dislike actors
Lee Kwang Soo I dislike
(Lee Kwang Soo I dislike)
He's right.
- Because he's a comedian. - Haha's right.
- Because Kwang Soo's a comedian. - He's right.
- He's a comedian. - Right, he's an actor.
Haha knew.
Let me go again.
- I'm getting suspicious. - That was too obvious.
- Start with Se Chan. - Let's go with Se Chan.
- Let's start with you. - Give me an easy one.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like foreign masterminds
I...
- What? - I don't...
(I...)
(Incorrect)
You always say Bell.
Hold on. He's serious. Look at his face.
- Goodness. - Look at his face. He's serious.
Who are the foreign masterminds?
- Thomas Edison. - Thomas Edison.
- Marie Curie. - There are so many.
He asked who foreign masterminds are.
Foreign masterminds.
Come on. We can't get past two people.
Let's watch Ji Hyo. Her fans are waiting.
- I'm a fan of hers during quizzes. - Me too.
During quizzes.
Let's start.
I have to get this right.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like spicy food
Tteokbokki I like
I dislike desserts
Coffee I dislike
(Coffee I dislike)
- What? - Coffee's dessert.
- You can have it as a meal. - Gosh, Ji Hyo.
- You can have it as a meal. - I have coffee as a meal.
I mix rice with coffee.
- Stop it, Ji Hyo. - I have coffee with soju.
Stop it, Ji Hyo.
A really easy one then.
- A really easy one. - Just one more time.
- I'm serious. - What's easier than a dessert?
I have desserts as my meal.
Let's go again.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like fish
Freshwater fish
I like
Freshwater fish I like
(Fish and freshwater fish?)
What?
- Name a fish. - I don't know any.
You have to name one type.
Isn't she worse than me?
- She's amazing. - I can't believe this.
There's tuna!
I thought the producer was being too nice.
- He was being nice to her. - She's worse than me.
- Freshwater fish. - I was right.
- She was so lovely. - Freshwater fish is fish.
- Mackerels. - Fine.
I wish you were a spy!
(I wish you were a spy!)
She has to be a spy.
Please. She has to be one.
- You have to be a spy, Ji Hyo. - I'm sorry.
Make sure you change the spy to her right now.
We have to save Ji Hyo.
Chul Min, save Ji Hyo.
- Freshwater fish I like - Freshwater fish
(This is the new catchphrase.)
That's all I could remember.
- Ji Hyo, I'm a fan of yours! - HyunA.
This is your main commodity.
Okay, Ji Hyo?
Watch the fish. I mean, watch Gook Ju.
"Watch the fish."
Please be the spy!
- Let's get it right this time. - We can't get past two people.
- We need the hint. - Yes, let's get the hint.
Let's start.
Good luck, Kwak Do Won!
(That was random.)
(Let's do this.)
- Kwak Do Won. - Good luck, Han Ki Bum.
Good luck, Noh Joo Hyun.
Good luck, Lee Moon Sae.
- Good luck, Han Moo. - Good luck, Han Ki Bum.
Good luck, everybody!
Let's start.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like people with mustaches
Kim Heung Gook I like
I dislike spicy food
Water I like
- It's dislike. - You idiot.
Dislike.
- Hey. - Isn't he weird?
- He's weird. - I didn't do it on purpose.
- He told me all the answers. - That was too obvious.
- Then... - I don't think it's him.
We failed round two.
- You should say, "Water I dislike". - Leave these two.
- Leave these two. - Switch us.
Leave these. Go, HyunA.
- Go, HyunA. And Han Na. - HyunA and Han Na.
Do you know the rules, HyunA? Do you understand?
I understand the rules,
but I can't do it.
This is a minefield.
- She's honest. - This is a war.
Let's go.
(They only have 3 chances left.)
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I dislike birds
Frogs I dislike
I dislike amphibians
Fish I dislike
She's driving me nuts.
What fish?
- Eagles. - Say it.
Eagles.
What does fish have to do with this?
Are you enemies with fish?
She's a spy.
I'm sure.
- She's a spy, Haha. - She has to be a spy.
Are you doing your mission?
This...
I can't trust her.
There has to be at least one out of them.
There has to be. I'm sure.
Do you want to switch? Do you want to go first?
Okay. Let's switch.
- Do you want to go first? - What?
- Do you want to switch? - No.
(Se Chan tries to move back.)
Try it.
You'll be good.
I'm suspicious of Han Na, so I want her here.
There's no point switching. It won't come this far.
Ji Hyo is on my right.
Why would you switch seats?
(There's no point in switching.)
I didn't even get to say a thing.
You never know.
(You never know.)
That was sharp.
I don't like Haha sitting there.
Why? Don't you get it?
Stop pretending like you know everything.
Should we switch Haha in for Han Na?
Switch out Han Na.
- Come here. - Haha.
- Fine. - You're suspicious.
Show them.
- Han Na. - I want to...
answer quiz questions here.
Do you want to do it?
(He's confident.)
Let's go.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like Korean movies
"Tazza" I like
I like cartoons
"Dodge Danpei" I like
I dislike birds
Dolphins I dislike
(I dislike birds, Dolphins I dislike)
(She finally passed!)
I like amphibians
Frogs I like
I like hardy plants
What are hardy plants?
(What are hardy plants?)
(He doesn't know what it is.)
- Sweet potatoes. - Sweet potatoes and potatoes.
- Sweet potatoes and potatoes. - Sweet potatoes and potatoes.
- What was that? - You don't know any hardy plants?
- I was serious. - What's wrong with you?
- I didn't know. - Did you really not know?
You were showing off, and you didn't know.
I'm really sorry.
- Haha is so dumb. - I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Don't you learn about this...
in elementary school? Potatoes and sweet potatoes?
You weren't even smiling. You were serious.
"What are hardy plants?"
I'm really sorry.
- Were you serious? - I'll go one last time.
Is this the last round?
- Last. - Last one.
Let's start with HyunA.
- Yes or no, answer me - Yes or no, answer me
I like carnivores
Hippos I like
(I like carnivores, Hippos I like)
- She's right. - Hippos are carnivores.
I dislike herbivores
Tigers I dislike
I like birds
Mackerels I like
(I like birds, Mackerels I like)
(Mackerels are birds?)
- Birds. - Birds!
- Birds. - Birds. Flying birds.
- That was really odd. - Birds.
- That was really... - What are flying creatures?
Birds.
(He finally realizes.)
I can't watch this anymore.
- I know. - I can't watch.
Hey, you're this bad,
and you say all sorts of things to your junior comedians.
I didn't know he was this dumb.
- I thought I misheard. - I was nervous.
He's unbelievable.
So you won't be getting the hint on the forbidden animal.
- We did pretty well though. - I feel dejected.
They succeeded.
Let's have Ji Hyo and Se Chan compete next time.
Ji Hyo and Se Chan...
- will be close. - They have to be spies.
I'm still very confused, so can we share the hints?
- Do it. - Tell us.
Tell us.
- We should do this together. - Let's share.
Hurry. I know.
The forbidden animal...
lives in a herd.
On water?
(The forbidden animal lives in a herd?)
- On water? - They live in herds.
Okay, let's look at the hint.
(They got the hint at the end of round 1.)
- Do we check it together? - Yes.
(The forbidden animal lives in a herd.)
Then...
I'm narrowing down now.
- Hold on. - Jong Kook.
It's not a tiger.
(The forbidden animal lives in a herd.)
- Pigs and foxes. - Rabbits too.
- What about snakes? - I'm sure about pigs.
- Boars live in herds too. - Boars.
That's true.
Rabbits and foxes.
(Are rabbit, pig, and fox left?)
- All right. - Got it.
(Thanks to the first hint, they narrowed down a lot.)
- Bear... What were we again? - Tiger and snake.
- Snake. Tiger. - Tiger is out.
Lions live in herds but not tigers.
It's everybody except those.
- Pig, rabbit, or fox. - It's 1 of those 3.
- Pig, rabbit, or fox? - Yes.
- Rabbit, fox, or pig. - It's not me.
- I swear. - Watch her carefully.
Watch her carefully.
(Is So Min the forbidden animal like everybody thinks?)
I swear it's not me.
It could be Haha too.
- What are you? - It's not me.
- I'm a tiger. - It's not us.
- It's not you. - It narrows down to six people.
If it's not you guys, you really got the questions wrong.
- I faked it. - Jae Seok.
- Did you fake it? - I faked it.
Fish...
- Jae Seok. - No?
- I didn't. - We help them.
So Ji Hyo is not the bad animal?
She's not.
- She's not, HyunA. - Hey.
- She got it wrong. - See me after we finish here.
Don't leave after we finish today.
- I can't let this slide. - Oh, no. Goodness.
- You stay behind today. - My gosh.
All right. We'll move onto the final race.
I told you earlier that if the forbidden animals...
can't carry out the hidden mission, they'll be eliminated.
- They must have failed. - Really?
- I guess they succeeded. - Both of forbidden animals...
executed their hidden mission.
- Really? - They did it.
- When? - We don't know that.
Ji Hyo, what did you do?
It's not Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - My gosh, Seok Jin.
- Gosh, Ji Hyo. - My focus is on you today.
She looks so suspicious, but it's not her?
- We'll go to the final destination. - Let's go.
They did the mission?
(Which one of them is the forbidden animal?)
(A series of strange incidents...)
(keeps confusing the animals.)
(Is something wrong with today's race?)
(The forbidden animal is lurking around to eliminate them.)
I'm sorry.
(The moment they are eliminated one at a time,)
(the hidden truth is unraveled.)
(And the members of the Running Man must be informed of this story.)
(Late at night, editing room at SBS)
(Did you tell the new producer about the ghost story?)
(How could I tell her when she just joined our show?)
(You don't know the ghost story of our TV station, SBS, right?)
(It's my first time hearing it.)
(You don't know about Clacking Ghost and Coughing Ghost?)
(No, I don't.)
(Listen.)
(A long time ago, a main producer and an assistant director...)
(wrote a legendary proposal that guaranteed 40 percent TV ratings.)
(Another competing producer and a writer were envious of them.)
(One night, the competition producer and the writer eliminated them.)
(But the producer was Coughing Ghost because the producer coughed a lot.)
(The writer was Clacking Ghost because the writer wore high heels.)
(And after they had gotten eliminated,)
(every night,)
(there were clacking and coughing sounds.)
(They are roaming around the building to find that proposal.)
(Didn't you guys twist the story too much?)
(Let's just go home.)
(Ghost Story of a TV Station: Legendary Proposal)