- Hello, Ji Hyo. - Hi, Ji Hyo.
My gosh, this is such a nice house.
- This is a rich person's house. - Goodness.
Turbo had its first practice right here in Yeonhui-dong.
- Really? - Really?
- In Yeonhui-dong. - How many has that been?
- About 20 years ago. - That was in 1995.
(An old story 24 years ago)
Gosh, that was in the 1990s.
Most of our memories we talk about...
- happened over 20 years ago. - They are from 20 years ago.
You came a long way.
It has to be more than 20 years to be called a memory.
- Right. That's so true. - Of course. Exactly.
Seok Jin has memories from 50 years ago.
That's right.
(Seok Jin has memories from 50 years ago.)
- That's right. - Of course.
During the Korean War?
He used to carry around three pairs of straw shoes.
- He'd change when they got old. - They would change into new ones.
When all three of them wore down, he'd weave them all together again.
Seok Jin's nickname is Straw Seok Jin.
- He always wore straw shoes. - Exactly.
- Straw shoes. - I've been observing this,
but Seok Jin gets attacked when he hasn't done anything.
- That's true. - No, I don't see it that way.
(No, I don't see it that way.)
Why do you assume that?
- I like it. I'm getting attention. - Do you like it?
- Yes, we're giving him attention. - That's right.
- Of course. - He's an attention-seeker.
Yes, I'm an attention-seeker.
By the way, So Min and SORAN finally...
- started to perform together. - My gosh.
- Without Jae Seok. - Right.
You're going to events without us? That's not fair.
- Jae Seok isn't joining you? - My position is very flexible.
- You don't need to perform? - But So Min and SORAN will perform.
- Someone can easily take your spot. - Right.
Besides, Ko Young Bae adjusted the key to his, to begin with.
Right, right.
For the fan-meet, he divided it into three parts.
But he already adjusted the key to his.
By the way, they can perform this song at events now.
Jong Kook, you can perform that alone, can't you?
- Yes, I can. - Yes.
- I have a year-end tour. - You'll sing it there?
I'll try to sing it with Haha during that concert.
- We'll sing another song too. - Anyone can sing his part, right?
(Anyone can sing his part, right?)
Get someone from the street and practice for an hour and a half.
- I think that could work. - But there should be...
- a comic relief in that song. - Is that so?
- Well, I see. - It's entertaining for my audience.
- Okay. - He needs to do it.
Did you meet Byul?
- Did you meet Byul? - She...
(A surprise meeting between So Min and Byul)
- She wanted to treat me to a meal. - I saw it on your social media.
So we met up because she wanted to treat me to a meal.
All of a sudden? How did that happen?
- Why did they meet? - We wanted to have a meal together,
but we never got to for the past 2 or 3 years.
And she asked me when I would be coming to see her.
I see. So Byul gave you advice on dating when you shared your problem.
She...
- Can I share this? She said, - What?
"So Min, men are all foolish."
"You need to find a less foolish man among foolish men."
- Really? - That's what she said.
Then why did she marry such a fool?
If I'm following her logic, she found the most foolish man.
She got the most foolish one.
(According to her, she found the most foolish one.)
(He only cares about his wife.)
- He's the fool of the fools. - Right.
And she scolded me a lot. She said, "Cut down on drinking."
From what she told us,
I think...
she's a bit bossy.
- Yes, she is. - Yes, she's bossy.
- Right? - She's bossy.
I didn't peg her to be bossy.
- She's bossy. - She can be quite bossy.
You know that I talk a lot, right?
During the meal, I couldn't get a word in.
Right.
- Is she chatty? - Yes.
- She talks... - Does she talk a lot?
- so much. - Byul...
- She does the same thing. - When it comes to dating,
she has a lot of wisdom to share.
- She's confident in that area. - Yes, she is.
(She's almost an expert.)
- All right. - Everyone,
- it's pretty hot today, right? - It's so hot.
Since it's hot today,
you will stay inside the house...
- until 6 p.m. - What?
(The current time is 12 p.m.)
- Really? - That's nice.
- I like that we don't need to move. - That's nice.
- Let's order jjajangmyeon. - Yes.
- That sounds delicious. - You'll stay inside the house.
You will discuss the schedule that you will follow today.
Come up with more than five activities.
- Please come up with a schedule. - That sounds fun.
- Five? - Then...
let's take Byul's crash course on dating one more time.
- Let's invite her over. - Right.
- Like a guest? - Yes.
She can go on for six hours all by herself.
- She'll need more time. - I'm sure of it.
- Suit yourself. - She can talk by herself.
To start today's race,
- you'll enter the house. - Okay!
(To start today's race, they enter the house.)
They turned the house into a studio set.
- It's not a house, but a set. - It's like a vacation rental house.
- This is a beautiful house. - There are a lot of houses...
in Yeonhui-dong.
Gosh, this is a nice house with a nice view.
I'll give you the paper for your schedule.
You're making us write a lot these days.
It's not like we're at a school.
All right. "Schedule".
Let's see.
We should eat first.
- Lunch. - We should.
I'll go with jjamppong.
- In that case, - Okay.
- let's get jjajangmyeon. - Yes.
- I like it. - Chinese food.
- Let's get jjamppong and tangsuyuk. - Tangsuyuk.
- I like that. - Let's dip it in the sauce.
- Let's get a rice dish. - No, let's get jjajangmyeon.
This area is famous for burgers.
- All right then. - Let's get a rice dish.
- Let's gather everyone's opinions. - Okay.
- Let's speak one at a time. - Okay.
On a day like this,
I think Chinese food will be perfect.
- Like jjajangmyeon and jjamppong? - Yes, jjajangmyeon and jjamppong.
- You can go next, Haha. - Yes.
I'd like to get a burger. We can get burgers...
- and wings. - Wings?
- I'll go with Chinese food. - Chinese food.
I want to get tacos.
(I want to get tacos.)
Why not?
Tacos are great. Let's get tacos.
- We can get Mexican food. - I like tacos.
- That's great. - Burritos are good too.
- I can get a burrito. - Right.
What else?
- I want to get Chinese food. - Chinese food.
- We have three votes. - What else?
- Vote for burgers. - I actually want to cook lunch.
- You want to cook lunch? - On this hot day?
We're here, after all.
I see a rice cooker there. And we're here together.
Hey, ramyeon would be good.
We can cook ramyeon and fried rice. We can eat them together.
- We can put a fried egg on top. - Fried egg and ketchup.
- That sounds good too. - Yes.
All right, then. We've got a decision, Seok Jin.
What about my vote?
(Chinese food gets 4 votes.)
(Seok Jin's vote won't matter.)
We're following the majority rule.
- Seok Jin, why did you sit there? - Hey, ask my opinion too.
- I've been thinking the whole time. - But...
- You come here. - Why did you sit at the end?
Okay.
- Let's try this again. - Yes, try it again.
- What do you want? - I wanted to eat kalguksu.
How about kalguksu?
- Forget about that. - The noodles will get soggy.
Let me tell you.
I'll give you a chance to think...
of a dish that will change our minds.
- I don't need to think. - Go ahead.
I make really mean kimchi fried rice.
- I can cook kimchi fried rice. - You'll cook that?
- You're going to cook? - I'll cook it.
- If you're cooking... - Fine, I'll eat it.
- I can cook it. - We don't need to help at all?
- I'll eat it if you cook it. - You don't need to help.
- I'll cook it. - Really?
You'll wash the dishes too?
- No, someone must wash the dishes. - Wait, no.
- Do I have to do that too? - Wait.
- Hey. - You're disappointing us.
- He got mad at washing the dishes. - He's really mad.
You're disappointing us.
- Why are you so mad? - I wasn't mad.
- They want me to wash dishes too. - Why are you angry?
The chef has to clean up too.
No, I'll just cook.
- You'll really cook everything? - Kimchi...
I can cook kimchi fried rice.
- We don't have to help at all. - Right.
All right. Set some time for lunch on the paper.
- You can decide on the menu later. - Okay, let's do that.
My gosh.
It took that long to decide on food?
We can eat for an hour, right?
- We at least need two hours. - We need to digest the food too.
- We need to buy food and all. - Right. We get to decide.
Let's eat until 2 p.m. What should we do until 3 p.m. then?
- We should have fun. It's a break. - Snack.
We can play games during the break.
- Let's play table tennis. - Then...
- let's write an indoor activity. - Indoor activity.
- We don't what it is. - Indoor activity.
- Indoor activity. - Indoor activity.
From 3 p.m. to 4 p.m., we'll have snacks and desserts.
- We keep eating. - Of course.
- We eat and play. - Hey, when you go on a trip,
- eating is all you do. - That's nice though.
- From 4 p.m. to 5 p.m... - Games.
Let's play Truth or Dare.
- Truth or Dare? - Fine.
- You like playing Truth or Dare. - Let's do it. Let's play a game.
- Indoor game. - It's an indoor game.
Wait. What's the difference between indoor activity and indoor game?
- They are different. - They are?
- Meals and desserts are different. - They are different.
- "Indoor activity". - Indoor game.
Won't we be hungry after we play an indoor game?
- Right. - Right.
We should eat.
- Refreshments. - Yes.
(They are not snacks or desserts. They are refreshments.)
(Refreshments: a general term for tea and snacks)
- Hey, we eat and sleep. - Refreshments.
"Lunch, an indoor activity, snacks, an indoor game, and snacks"?
- Refreshments. - Refreshments.
Refreshments.
- Are you set until 6 p.m.? - Yes.
- We're done. - All we'll do is eat and play.
- We eat, play, and go home. - All we'll do is eat and play.
Everyone,
- please look at the TV. - Okay.
(What? Look at the TV all of a sudden?)
We just received this breaking news.
(Goodness. What's going on?)
- What is this? - What?
(Breaking news?)
A mysterious virus has been rapidly spreading mainly in Seoul.
It's called the REA Virus.
"REA"?
- "REA"? - "REA"?
(What's that?)
Once you are infected by the virus,
it will wipe out your emotions and appetites.
It will reset everything in your bio-system.
It will get rid of our appetites?
It will reset everything.
As the route of the infection hasn't been located yet,
refrain from going outside...
and when you do, you must be especially careful.
(Everyone is panicking at this breaking news.)
However,
the bio-terrorist...
that spread the virus to the whole world...
- is among you. - I knew it.
I knew it.
What? It's not me.
- Hey. - I have nothing to do with that.
- You spoil my appetite. - Wait.
- You ruin my appetite. - What?
Wait, your singing kills my appetite.
- Why me? - Your singing kills my appetite.
- Why me? It's not me. - You know?
I think it's Se Chan.
- It's because... - No, it's not.
your singing kills my appetite.
I agree with that, but it's really not me.
Within six hours, you must carry out everything on your schedule.
And if you expose the bio-terrorist and eliminate him,
surviving members will win the race and win a prize.
And the bio-terrorist and infected members will face a penalty.
If all of the members are infected,
or if you fail to do everything on the schedule within the time limit,
the bio-terrorist will win.
Two of the infected members, chosen by the bio-terrorist,
will face the penalty.
And outside this house, there are four mission routes.
If you cannot carry out the activities in the house,
one of the members can choose a route and go outside.
But if you fail, you may be infected with the REA Virus, so be careful.
You can find out how the infection spreads by going outside.
Once you are infected by the virus,
- there will be a mark on your face. - On the face?
The infected member will come back home and follow the schedule.
Once infected, you must rip off the name tag with your mouth...
- to spread the virus. - With our mouth?
(Remove the name tag with your mouth to spread the virus.)
(We have to use our mouth to do it?)
- How could we do that? - Those of you...
with a protruding mouth...
Jae Seok and me?
However, if you're bothered by the infected member,
remove the name tag with your hand.
And the member will stand against the wall for five minutes.
I see. We'll be able to tell if someone is infected. We'll know.
- That person will be a zombie. - For five minutes.
Can the bio-terrorist infect us?
- I would think so. - What can...
- the bio-terrorist do? - The bio-terrorist...
can't infect the other members.
The bio-terrorist has to go outside.
Actually, the bio-terrorist is immune to the virus.
(The bio-terrorist won't be infected by the REA Virus.)
- He or she won't be infected? - Even if that person goes out?
It'll be obvious if someone comes back without getting infected.
- Right. - We should suspect that person.
- If that's the case, we should. - Right.
That person could have succeeded in the mission.
My gosh, you added a twist.
As for a way to eliminate the bio-terrorist,
I'll tell you if you use all four of the mission routes.
We have to do all of them.
- You can follow your schedule now. - My gosh.
Bio-terrorist...
(Seok Jin is stuttering from the start.)
Do they know who they are?
It must be your first time hearing the word.
So you're going to get rid of Seok Jin first?
I just remembered this.
I saw him in the room this morning, and when I went inside,
the stylist kept drawing his eyebrows after seeing me.
His eyebrows were already drawn though.
- The stylist kept drawing... - Seok Jin...
- his eyebrows again and again. - Seok Jin...
- As if he just got started? - I have a photo.
I have one too. It was really odd.
What's this?
- My eyebrows were that dark? - Look at this, everyone.
- His are darker than Sin Chan's. - Really?
Then, we have no choice but to go outside.
Do we have to?
Don't we, if we want to eat?
I hope the bio-terrorist goes out for us...
- I mean, - if someone has to go out.
to cook ramyeon...
- We have to go out and buy it. - If...
We can find food in the house.
- Right here. - Let's look for food.
(Will there be food inside the fridge?)
See? I knew it. There's nothing to eat.
(Empty refrigerator)
There's nothing.
In that case...
Hey, I found rice here.
(He found rice in the cabinet.)
- We have rice? - Let's cook rice.
- Let's cook rice. - We need more food though.
- We can't just eat rice. - We need side dishes.
We should go out and buy tteokbokki or something.
All right. Here's my opinion.
We should go to the convenience store...
- and raid the store. - We need to buy food.
- We have no choice. One of us... - Right.
Let's choose someone suspicious.
Someone who's not likely to succeed the mission.
- Seok Jin. - Someone like Seok Jin.
- I think you should go out. - Why would I do that?
- He's our prime suspect. - Right.
- So we should make him go. - We ought to.
I think he might end up facing the wall the whole time.
If you come back after getting infected,
we can just feel sorry.
(It's so simple.)
(I'm sorry, Seok Jin.)
- All right. - It was a close call.
It's not me.
But you're the safest bet.
I'm not the bio-terrorist.
- Come on. - Can you go and buy ramyeon?
- Seok Jin, buy tteokbokki. - Tuna.
- Eggs. - Triangle gimbap.
- Tuna. - How about dumplings?
Get frozen ones.
- And they sell cheese too. - I know.
- Go raid the convenience store. - Buy some buns too.
- Buy some eggs. - Crabmeat too.
Seok Jin, you need to ramyeon for us to have lunch.
And buy a bottle of cooking oil too.
Seok Jin, buy some snacks too.
- Snacks? - Hey, I like Snack Noodles.
- Okay. - And jjajang ramyeon too.
Okay!
That's enough! I'll buy them.
(Calm down and come back safe.)
Seok Jin, go buy some food.
Gosh. Why did they pick me?
(What kinds of missions are awaiting?)
What is this?
(He spots something right away.)
(There are 4 phones in front of him.)
What are these?
Please pick your route from 1 to 4.
Do the routes differ depending on what I pick?
Yes.
(The route he'll take depends on which phone he picks.)
(He's in a dilemma.)
- This? - I pick this one.
(He picks the farthest right.)
You picked the first one.
Route One.
(What mission will it have?)
(He checks the hidden mission.)
(Curious)
(Don't Laugh.)
What? "Don't laugh."
"If you don't laugh until you arrive at the destination, you pass."
On your way to the convenience store,
you won't be infected if you don't laugh.
But if you do, you will be infected immediately.
I'll succeed if I don't laugh?
(He'll pass if he doesn't laugh.)
That's easy.
I'm confident. This will be easy.
(Will he truly succeed?)
I think four cups will be enough.
Will we eat this much?
- This is more than enough. - Is this enough?
Trust me. I can do this.
I'll make stir-fried rice.
Where's Kwang Soo?
(By the way...)
(Kwang Soo has disappeared.)
Keep an eye on him.
Where is he?
Kwang Soo.
(Where did he go?)
Where is he?
Hold on.
(Is he upstairs?)
- Kwang Soo, what are you doing? - Yes?
(They find him at the terrace.)
I was just looking around.
(Why was he upstairs alone?)
- I was just looking around. - Guys.
- Hey, you're the bio-terrorist. - Come here.
- It's not me. - You're the virus.
It's not me.
- He's acting strange. - What is it?
There was a camera with him.
He was wandering around.
- He probably has a mission. - I think he was marking things.
It's nothing suspicious.
I was just looking around.
- He's Kwang Virus. - He's Kwang Virus.
- You're related to it. - What do you mean?
What did you do upstairs?
I was just looking around. There was stuff up there?
Why would you go up there?
Just in case.
(Is he being suspicious because he's the bio-terrorist?)
The mission starts now, right?
You'll be infected the moment you laugh.
That's easy.
I'm confident.
This is too easy.
"Route Four".
The routes are here. Here's Route One.
Okay, Route One.
(He finds his route.)
(Why are they telling me not to laugh?)
Don't laugh.
- No way! - Please give me your autograph.
Sure.
(No way! Please give me your autograph.)
- Sure. - Hold on.
- I'm sorry. - Can we take a photo?
- Sure. - One time.
- Han Byul, come here. - Hurry up.
- I can't smile or laugh. - Really?
- Hello! - Hello.
Hello!
(Han Byul arrives.)
(She has nose hair.)
(Hello, I'm Han Byul.)
(She arrives while boasting her long nose hair.)
Please take a photo with me.
(They lock eyes, and he's in a crisis.)
Hold on. I need to tidy up my nose hair.
How do I look? Am I pretty?
- Please look at me. - You're pretty.
Really?
- You're pretty. - He said I'm pretty.
Let's take a photo.
Excuse me.
Come on, let's take a photo.
1, 2, 3.
(He's trying hard not to laugh.)
- Okay, goodbye. - You're so handsome!
I hear that often.
(He leaves them.)
My gosh.
I almost laughed there.
That was crazy.
I barely held it in.
I get it now.
I was startled.
(He purses his lips and gets ready.)
(But he spots something.)
(He spots someone making fish-shaped buns.)
Have some fish-shaped buns.
(It's lady Yondu.)
(She's a strong match.)
Have some.
I have red beans and choux cream.
Please try some.
Which one would you like?
Which flavor would you like?
Which one?
Which one do you want?
What? Which one?
Come on. Pick one.
Which one do you want?
Which one?
- Which one? - I want both.
(He bursts into laughter.)
You fail.
- You laughed. - I want both.
(He fails in stage 2.)
Are you a lady?
- Yes. - Are you female?
- You are? - Yes, I am.
(It's too funny that his legs become weary.)
I'm a female, and I'm like this. What should I do?
You look so hilarious.
(She's just as funny-looking as So Min.)
My gosh.
You are infected.
What are you doing?
- You get your face drawn on. - Look up.
(Seok Jin is infected by the virus.)
(The others don't know.)
Do you want to have a quiz competition?
1-on-1? Kwang Soo should play too.
- No. - You should play.
Don't include me.
Not you. You should beat him first.
For the indoor game,
- Let's do a quiz. - we'll play this quiz.
And Ji Hyo should...
- also participate. - You're right.
- You should show them. - You should.
Show us how stupid you are.
A member from the losing team will go outside.
All right.
What is taking Seok Jin so long?
- Maybe... - No, we made the right choice.
- Yes. - We thought a lot about this.
His eyebrows will be drawn.
If he comes back with nothing,
I won't think he's passed.
You think he'll be infected?
I'd think he was the bio-terrorist.
(He'll suspect him as the bio-terrorist.)
(But he's not.)
(Suddenly...)
I can't believe this.
(He suddenly acts like a zombie when no one asked him to.)
(He's too into it.)
(Due to the actor being immersed in it, we won't use CG.)
I'll infect everyone else.
- He's here. He's a zombie. - He's here?
- He's here? - Did he not buy anything?
- He's infected. - Look carefully.
- He didn't buy anything. - Seok Jin.
(The zombie is back.)
- My gosh. - No way.
(He's horrible at acting.)
- Look at him acting. - What is this?
Seok Jin.
- What is that? - Look under his eyes.
What is that?
- What is that? - What's going on?
What's wrong with your eyes?
(He runs towards Kwang Soo.)
Rip off his name tag and make him stay still for five minutes.
What happens now?
(His name tag is torn off.)
He needs to stand by a wall for five minutes.
You need to.
- I'm sorry. - He's not it.
You should've told us.
He loves being in the center of attention.
My gosh.
Did you not buy anything?
(He's still into his character.)
You can talk.
- I couldn't. - What?
What happened?
You should find out for yourself.
- What happened? - You should go yourself.
(He's confident that Jae Seok will fail as well.)
- He couldn't buy anything. - This is driving me crazy.
Does that mean we can't eat anything?
Do I have to stand still for the entire day?
- It's for 5 minutes. - Just for 5 minutes.
Five minutes?
You don't have to grunt like a zombie.
- What? I'm going to. - You don't need to.
- What do you mean? - Don't sulk.
- We'll see how long you'll do it. - I'm going to act like a zombie.
Let's see how long you'll do it for.
Your acting is so awkward.
I'll do it from time to time.
- Sure, do that. - I will.
- Fine. - Fine, I'll do that.
My gosh.
This was useless.
Who's next?
For the stir-fried rice, we need eggs and ham.
(The rice is ready.)
The rice is ready.
- One person should go. - Do rock-paper-scissors.
- Jae Seok. - Do rock-paper-scissors.
(Ripping)
(Seok Jin tries to rip his name tag.)
You must've gone insane!
Don't do that!
(He barely saves himself.)
Hey, you...
Stand there.
This is upsetting.
- This sure is. - Stay still.
How dare you try to rip off my name tag?
You were in front of me.
I'll set the timer...
and rip it off every five minutes.
(They plan to make it endless.)
You're right.
(I'm going to do that.)
(He sets the timer for 5 minutes.)
Who should go?
I pick Jae Seok.
Jae Seok is overall good at missions.
- You're right. - Should I go, then?
But if I get infected...
If you pick the same route as I did, you'll get infected for sure.
What about me?
For you,
you'll have a 30-percent chance.
- You should go. - You should
- Go. - You should go.
If another person gets infected, it will put us at a disadvantage.
I don't suspect you because he said you had a 30-percent chance.
So you might succeed.
(He goes for Jae Seok's name tag once again.)
My gosh, you startled me!
(Kwang Soo rips his name tag once again.)
(He gets punished.)
(He spanks him.)
- I just... - My gosh!
I just did it without realizing it.
I can't help it.
He surprised me!
- Yours almost came off. - I know! Put it back on!
Make sure it's on well.
- Should I go? - Yes.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
- Succeed and buy ramyeon. - Buy...
- delicious ones. - Got it.
- I'll buy ramyeon. - And ice cream.
- I know what to buy. - Cooking oil.
- Eggs. - Eggs. Don't worry.
(He sets out.)
I must succeed.
- What is that? - Since Seok Jin chose Route One,
you'll go with the same one. It's simple.
You must not laugh.
- I shouldn't laugh? - No.
Isn't that too easy?
Let's go.
That's so simple.
It's easy for me not to laugh.
Will someone touch me?
The rice looks good.
- It's already done? - It smells nice.
- You can't eat it. - Seok Jin.
- You don't have an appetite. - You don't have an appetite.
- I don't? - That's right.
Let me keep my appetite.
You're not supposed to. That's where the name comes from.
You're not supposed to have emotions or an appetite.
- You're back to factory settings. - Virus, virus.
(Virus, virus)
(Seok Jin suddenly starts murmuring something.)
Virus, virus.
(What's going on?)
If you repeat the word "virus" to the bio-terrorist,
the bio-terrorist will reply by saying "vinegar".
(The infected must work with the terrorist...)
(to infect as many people as they can.)
(Seok Jin is checking to see if Jong Kook is the terrorist.)
(Is Jong Kook the bio-terrorist?)
Virus, virus.
(Jong Kook only repeated what Seok Jin said.)
Do you want some rice?
- Just warm it up... - So Min,
- I think it's Jae Seok. - It's too dry.
- Why? - It's a hunch.
Well, you suspecting him seems suspicious to me.
Even your sunglasses are suspicious.
Seriously? Haven't I played the villain enough?
Also, viruses are small.
Wait, that's actually a big clue.
Viruses are small.
That means it's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok's the small one.)
(Running Man's official Mr. Tiny?)
Is it Jae Seok or Haha?
Jae Seok, of course.
He made me a man.
Everyone in Mapo-gu knows about him.
(Everyone in Mapo-gu knows about him.)
I'm the least jealous of Jae Seok when it comes to my neighbors.
Right?
I'm not kidding about the rumors.
(I want to laugh with them too.)
Hold on a second. You can't laugh.
- Wait. - You can't laugh.
- You shouldn't laugh. - Don't laugh!
- But it's funny. - You should be emotionless.
It's been five minutes, so join us.
Stop biting our name tags though.
I won't.
This is too easy though.
(The younger comedian is confident about his mission.)
- Can we get your autograph? - We love you so much.
(The girls come from the alley like before.)
(He's figuring out what's going on.)
Hold on. Han Byul, come on.
Can our friend get one too?
- Sure. - Han Byul, come on.
I get it now.
- All right. - I get it now.
Why?
(Did someone call for Han Byul?)
(He turns away.)
(Han Byul runs over with her nose hair flying.)
Come on.
Hello, I'm a huge fan of yours.
- My gosh. - It's nice to meet you.
- No way. - It's a pleasure.
Can we take a photo?
- Yes, of course. - Awesome.
Hold on a second. Let's put this side up.
No, she looks prettier with it left down.
Hold on.
(They attack him by tucking her nose hair.)
(2nd critical moment)
(The staff snorts.)
(Laughing)
- You're more handsome in person. - Really?
- Goodness. - You're pretty too.
- Really? - Really?
- Yes. - What if I got a perm?
- A perm? Sounds good. - Right?
You'll look even prettier if they came down the middle.
Exactly.
(Ms. Nose Hair, be a comedian someday.)
Thanks, guys.
- Good luck. - Thanks.
Thank you so much.
No way.
(That was close.)
Did Seok Jin laugh at the sight of her?
I can't tell you.
That was stage one?
Think sad thoughts.
(He collects himself before reaching stage 2.)
(Inhaling)
Have a fish-shaped bun.
(A fish-shaped bun sold by Yondu?)
There's red bean flavor and choux cream flavor.
(I must not laugh.)
- Please try one. - Okay.
- It's really good. - I see.
How is it?
- It's good. - Is it?
- This must not be easy. - Right.
(It's best not to look at her.)
(She's wearing all that makeup in this hot weather.)
Taking off the makeup is actually harder.
(She relates to his words and lets her guard down.)
- I'm not kidding. - I know.
- I wish you a good day then. - Oh, no.
(You too.)
May I keep going then?
(Se Chan relates to the lady and passes without laughing.)
Unbelievable. You guys are unbelievable.
(He carries onto the convenience store.)
They all seem like hired actors.
(He keeps his guard up.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E473 Running Man
"A House Without an Exit Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Hello.
(A random lady is standing in the alley.)
- I'm a fan. - Thank you.
- Can we take a photo? - Sure.
(He's about to take a photo with the lady.)
Here we go.
- I got it. - Thank you.
- Where did you get this phone? - This?
(She winds up.)
(The phone is kicked away.)
(After kicking the phone away)
(Yippee!)
(What?)
(The staff bursts out laughing at the sight of her cartwheels.)
(See you!)
(He's close to laughing.)
(Get a grip on yourself.)
(The cartwheels almost sent him over the edge.)
Everyone will probably laugh at this.
I almost laughed too.
(Stage 3 almost got me.)
She just kicked the phone.
It's one that actually works though.
I'm finally here.
(All he has to do is buy the ingredients.)
- Judging by how late he is... - He must've succeeded.
He might succeed.
Or he could be the bio-terrorist.
Isn't it about time that Ji Hyo was the villain?
- It's not me. - There must be a reason...
why you're so quiet today.
A bad day?
Is it something personal?
Are you burdened by the upcoming quiz?
(Are you burdened by the upcoming quiz?)
- No. - It won't be you.
You don't have to do it.
- You don't have to. - Is it really the quiz?
(Just then)
(Ripping)
(Zombie Seok Jin rips So Min's name tag off.)
(If your name tag is ripped off, it means you've been infected.)
This fast?
(Ripping)
- Seriously? - That was so out of the blue.
It felt so random.
I shouldn't have sat next to him.
I think it would've been wiser to keep So Min uninfected.
That was really fast though.
- What's with her? - My gosh.
What does she have on her cheeks?
What's that?
(An infected zombie enters.)
That's not how zombies are.
I'm dizzy.
Oh, dear.
- "REA Virus" is written on her. - What?
(Wait!)
(Why is "REA Virus" written on her cheek?)
(Is she the bio-terrorist?)
- What's this? - What's going on?
She wrote it herself. That's why it's reversed.
Friend. Family.
Dad.
No.
She's drawing a line.
- What? - She's drawing the line.
- Dad. - No.
- I'm not your dad. - Wait...
I'm finally here.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan's almost at the convenience store.)
(However)
(A suspicious man is standing in front of it.)
You will receive money to complete this mission first.
From him?
Here's your money.
(He takes his glasses off.)
(Another pair is drawn on his face.)
(The glasses almost made him laugh.)
Here you go.
Hold on a second.
(He takes off his cap.)
(He's bald!)
(Se Chan almost laughed.)
Here you go. And now...
(Hold it back a little more.)
(Snorting)
(He's close to bursting into laughter.)
(He seemed normal on the outside.)
(But he has a face of an angel.)
(Se Chan had no idea the director was this sweet.)
(His angelic face...)
(makes Se Chan lower his guard.)
(Laughing)
(He rolls on the ground.)
(The comedian gives up.)
(He shows his gums which is like a white flag.)
Did you have to go this far?
(You people...)
(Do your parents know that you're working this hard to earn a living?)
What on earth is this?
(It's for the second time, but he still laughs.)
Seriously?
(Se Chan fails at stage 4.)
Se Chan, you've been infected.
The baldness I could take,
but that face...
(Se Chan has been infected.)
(Still, he gets to buy the ingredients.)
Unbelievable.
(He walks into the convenience store.)
(He bursts into laughter.)
(Laughing)
(The staff is unbelievable.)
(This I must film.)
(Laughing hysterically)
(He can't hold it back anymore.)
Are you kidding me?
(What is stage 5 of the Don't Laugh challenge?)
- He's back. - Is he?
He's here.
- Did he buy the ingredients? - He did.
He has the ingredients!
- Nice. - Let's boil the water.
Amazing.
- Se Chan. - His face is clean.
- Hold on. Him too. - He's infected!
- Really? - He's infected.
You're infected?
(Se Chan has been infected.)
What?
- We're family. - Family.
- Family. - There are three of them now.
Why are you infected?
(He bursts into laughter.)
(He meets another family member who is also a weak link.)
Why were you infected?
Don't. No one should go.
- What... - You won't believe...
what they have in store for us.
- He still bought these. - Right.
Let's make them.
- But... - Three zombies make it dangerous.
We really are in danger.
I survived until the final stage, but gosh.
Is it that funny?
You have no idea.
No one can beat the final stage.
It's been designed for us to fail.
- It's fine. - Let me take them.
- The rice... - No.
- It was cooked perfectly. - Virus, virus.
(So Min says "virus" to Haha.)
Vinegar, vinegar.
(Haha replied by saying "vinegar.")
(Only the bio-terrorist knows the code.)
(Is Haha the bio-terrorist then?)
- Who do you think it is? - Not even water?
Try saying "virus" to Dong Hoon.
I did.
(Haha came to Seok Jin while Se Chan was out.)
You need to tell me.
- Virus, virus. - What?
- You need to tell me. - Virus, virus.
(The code of the bio-terrorist, virus)
Virus, virus.
It's not him.
- No, he said "vinegar' to me. - He did?
(Haha said "virus", not "vinegar".)
(Is Haha the bio-terrorist, or was it just a coincidence?)
Look at this. I cooked it so well.
Where?
Gosh, look...
Look at this.
(Quietly)
Go away.
Oh my gosh! I thought...
I just want to watch.
(Ripping)
We need to start eating.
- Go away. - He's right.
Zombies have the right to eat.
Go away.
Please, stay in character!
- Maybe you haven't heard, - Stay in character!
- but zombies get hungry. - You need to get your own.
Let's try it.
You're so mean.
I bought that.
(Slurping)
He's the neighborhood fool.
Isn't that Dong Goo?
- Why do you look so... - That's Dong Goo.
- It's Dong Goo. - Dong Goo!
What do you mean?
Can you say, "It's hot"?
(He blows on the food and looks just like Dong Goo.)
- See? He's even blowing on it. - It's Dong Goo.
He's even blowing on it.
- No, I'm just eating. - It's Dong Goo.
- You're acting like Dong Goo. - This is just me eating.
Don't you need to hurry if you want to take all four routes?
Don't you wish they all took our route?
Why?
I was eliminated before I could get to the end.
I heard from him that in the end, it was no joke.
- I can bet my whole fortune on it. - Really?
Then how does this sound?
We can wager one crucial clue about the bio-terrorist...
and two people can challenge...
- the route they just took. - Okay.
It has to be someone who said they're not the bio-terrorist.
The bio-terrorist can fail it.
So that we can't get the clue.
- So you have to do it. - I guess I should do it.
- You and Kwang Soo. - You're right.
To be honest...
I don't know what it is, but if I try hard enough, I can...
Then Kwang Soo and Jong Kook will go.
- Yes, you two should go. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook decide to attempt the mission.)
- Then, Jong Kook and Kwang Soo. - Do they go together?
- Let's try it. - I'm curious, though.
Can't we just watch?
- Yes, let's get that clue. - We'll be back.
That vinegar-man... What was it again?
- The bio-terrorist. - The bio-terrorist.
Let's just get him sorted.
- I will explain Route One. - Yes, sir!
You will have to go to the convenience store and back...
within 30 minutes, without running.
- However, - There's something else.
you cannot laugh.
I think I can do that.
Me too.
You will just have to buy a drink.
I think there is something else.
It's making me nervous.
(Smirking)
We should laugh it out now.
Gosh, I keep laughing because we can't laugh.
Get angry. Think of something that makes you angry.
(They try to get angry so that they won't laugh.)
Jong Kook, should we slap each other?
- I'm serious. To get a bit... - Sure.
(Then I'll go first...)
(Slap!)
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook. This is for a really important clue.
Yes.
Right? It's because...
- Why else would I hit you? - Sure.
We need to feel a bit offended.
I'm offended a lot.
I'll be offended,
but you might not be able to walk.
(I'll be offended, but you might not be able to walk.)
To be honest,
I was a bit startled by the sound.
(To be honest, I was a bit startled by the sound.)
I didn't put any makeup on, so my face is sticky.
I won't hit you hard.
(It is Kwang Soo's turn to get slapped for the mission.)
(Slap!)
(Let's see...)
It's weird because it wasn't that loud, but it hurts.
(He is the best at this.)
No! It wasn't loud, right?
Right? It wasn't loud.
- Are you sure it wasn't your fist? - Yes.
Why? Did that upset you?
DO you need another slap?
(You're the one who hit me. Can't you tell?)
Let's go. Now is the moment.
All right, wait.
(While the two stifled their laughter with anger...)
What is it?
It's...
trying not to laugh.
- You can't laugh, but... - And?
These high schoolers come and ask for your autograph,
and the third girl...
has a unibrow and a mustache out of her nose hairs like this.
She has a mustache, and she tucks it behind her ears.
I wouldn't have been able to hold it back.
They're professionals. The kids know how to make it funny.
They're really great.
I couldn't hold back at the second stage...
because some woman was making fish-shaped buns...
with her face painted blue.
- She looked like Yondu. - She was smiling like Yondu.
I asked, "What are you doing dressed like this?"
She said, "I know. I don't know why I'm here like this either."
(She suddenly realized her situation.)
Was that where you laughed?
I burst into laughter at that point.
The buns were really good too.
- Was that what you ate? - They were good.
It was really good and that made it even funnier.
Everything was funny.
(They hope Kwang Soo and Jong Kook hold out.)
I'm very upset right now.
- Kwang Soo, I... - What is it?
I can keep myself from laughing.
- Of course! - I tend to keep it in.
- You had that part in the movie. - Yes.
- When you had your ankle cut. - Yes.
- We're huge fans! - We're huge fans!
- Could I get your autograph? - Could I get your autograph?
- Can we also take your picture? - Of course.
Wait a minute.
- Han Byul! Come here, quick! - Han Byul! Come here.
- They have a friend. - She looks suspicious. Be careful.
(He sensed it coming.)
(Han Byul gets ready.)
What is it?
(What is it, guys?)
- Come here. - Oh my gosh!
Han Byul.
(He has his first crisis as Han Byul appears.)
- It's her nose hair. - Hello.
- Let me put my nose hair aside. - Han Byul, stop.
Hello. It's my nose hair.
Oh my gosh!
(Her nose hair flies around with her excitement.)
- You can't close your eyes. - No?
I'm a huge fan, Kwang Soo.
Oh my gosh, you look even more like a giraffe!
(Why is "giraffe" so funny today?)
You're so handsome.
Han Byul, let's take a picture.
Let's take a picture!
Look here.
(Stop, Han Byul.)
Your nose hairs are so long.
(Kwang Soo?)
- You look prettier like this. - Really?
(His random comment makes the third crisis.)
- I grew them out. - Han Byul, this looks better.
Don't you think we should go already, Kwang Soo?
1, 2, 3!
I almost laughed while taking the picture.
(Spin)
Oh my gosh.
But...
It's not funny at all...
when our members do it, but...
- This is so. - But...
I didn't expect nose hairs.
- Kwang Soo, - Yes?
I'm concerned about something these days.
Well...
My nose hair keeps falling out these days.
I don't know what to do.
Thank you.
If it falls out,
try eating lots of black beans.
- Are you sure that will help? - Of course.
- Black beans... - My uncle uses a wig.
- helps with hair loss. - A wig.
Does he?
- Why won't you look at us? - Let's go. We should go.
- Goodbye. - Good luck.
- Good luck! - Here's your autograph.
Goodbye.
- You're so handsome! - Goodbye!
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
Kwang Soo, to be honest,
that was really hard for me.
- It really was. - I know.
- I wanted to give up. - I know.
I could tell by the look on your face.
That was the first time I felt like crying for stifling a laugh.
- Promise me one thing. - What?
Don't try to make any funny comments.
- What do you... - Just...
- don't answer them. - Don't say anything back?
- Okay. - I keep laughing...
at the comments you make.
Are we not allowed to laugh now?
- You cannot laugh at all. - Okay.
- Don't make any comments. - Okay. I get it.
- Why was that funny? - I don't get why that was funny.
- We see that all the time. - I know.
- Where is the convenience store? - Wait.
Get ready.
- Why? - Just get ready.
(Unlike her makeup, she looks very calm.)
It's just funny to have you next to me.
Will you slap me again?
- Let's do that. - Okay.
(Slap me as well.)
(They get ready in front of the fish-shaped bun stand.)
You cannot laugh here.
(Don't make any comments.)
- Hold it in. - Okay. I'll hold it in.
- We're very angry. - Yes.
- We're angry. - We're almost there.
We're very angry.
(She slowly looks their way.)
Oh, gosh...
Would you like some fish-shaped buns?
I have both choux cream flavor and red bean flavor.
(She is too kind.)
Come on here and try some.
- But... - Why are you just watching me?
Come over here.
(He looks at the sky. He closes his eyes.)
Why are you closing your eyes?
Come here and try some.
(Stubborn)
Are your eyes open now?
Just try crying.
Open your eyes and take a bun.
(No matter how angry or sad he gets, the woman looks calm.)
I don't think I can do this. What do I do?
I actually have something I really want to say.
Me too. If I say it,
- We're going to laugh for sure. - Why I'm... Yes.
I'm going to laugh for sure.
I'm a fan!
(Stop...)
Let me see your face. I'm a fan.
(They weep. She's a fan.)
(Wailing)
(She's a professional who won't budge at all.)
(Let's just go.)
Don't cry. Why would you cry when I'm a fan?
(Freeze)
(Think sad thoughts.)
- Which one would you like? - We need to cry.
Red bean or choux cream?
Which one?
Choux cream or red bean?
I can't stand it!
(Please stop.)
(Punch)
(We are angry right now!)
Red bean flavor?
- Let's go. - Red bean flavor?
Would you like the red bean flavor or the choux cream puff flavor?
- Any flavor is fine. - Don't cry.
- Which one... - Any flavor is fine.
- Choux flavor? - Take the red bean flavor.
Red bean flavor?
Why won't you look at me? I am a fan.
(A long-time fan begs Kwang Soo to look at her.)
I looked, I looked.
- Did you look? - I looked.
Kwang Soo, won't you look at me?
(Taking a peek)
What's wrong?
- Kwang Soo, cry. - Why won't you look at me?
(I shouldn't have looked.)
1, 2, 3.
(Bawling)
Did something bad happen?
Why are you crying?
- I guess something bad happened. - We will get going now.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Ma'am, we are sorry. - We are sorry.
What's wrong?
(They suppress their laughter with tears and pass stage 2.)
(I came close.)
Crying really works.
I wouldn't have passed that stage without crying.
(They stop crying and eat the tear-soaked fish-shaped bun.)
(What is this taste?)
It's tasty.
The fact that it's tasty makes me want to laugh.
(She is the master of the fish-shaped bun.)
Don't laugh.
You know,
she really seems like a food cart owner.
(It seems that way.)
(Crying)
(We are sorry, ma'am.)
Are you laughing?
We are crying.
It really seems like she sells fish-shaped buns.
- Stop it. - Okay. Let's go.
- Stop with your comments. - Okay. Let's go.
Okay.
Seok Jin went pretty far.
Doing this task as a group of two makes it worse.
- Everything seems funnier. - I know.
Had I been alone, I wouldn't have had a problem.
That's why I am not looking at you.
- Seeing you suppress laughter... - I know.
Doing this task as a group of two makes it worse.
You are right.
Se Chan even made it through here.
There is...
I sense something from the right. Get ready.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I am a fan. May I take a photo? - Sure.
Thank you.
(All of my fans are in this neighborhood.)
Cry.
This is...
(They aren't sure if she is a real fan or a hired actress.)
- What is this? - I want a photo.
(Jong Kook cries already.)
Thank you.
(Kicking)
(She takes a selfie...)
(and kicks the phone without hesitation.)
(Cartwheeling)
(Oh, no!)
(Like a fool,)
(he ended up looking at the woman!)
(The intense way she goes home is unforgettable.)
(Antsy)
(Get a hold of yourself, Kwang Soo!)
(Suppressing laughter)
You didn't see her leave, did you?
(Don't talk about it.)
She cartwheeled down the street.
(You could have walked comfortably.)
(Why did you use such a difficult method?)
(Cartwheeling)
I thought I was seeing things.
(Crying)
She tumbled her way back home.
(Please stop talking!)
(Trudging)
She looked like a regular woman, but she tumbled...
(It's etched on my mind.)
(They pass stage 3 as they bawl.)
When I arrived at the convenience store...
- What? - I was so startled.
The employee at the convenience store...
(Is the employee surprising?)
(They burst out laughing.)
They will laugh for sure.
He stood like this.
I had no choice but to laugh.
Seriously.
They'll definitely laugh.
I couldn't hold it in.
You should go and see.
I already feel like I have been there.
We keep crying after a short conversation.
I know.
This is driving me crazy.
- This is where Se Chan failed. - We came so far.
Se Chan? Okay.
- Okay. - There are two of us. You...
- I won't open my mouth. - Get ready.
What? There is a convenience store!
You startled me.
Be careful when you enter the convenience store.
There has to be something inside.
(They set their minds once again.)
Okay.
I am angry. I am very angry right now.
(For goodness' sake!)
(Crying)
(An overly solemn assistant producer makes an appearance.)
(Let's have sad thoughts.)
(They can sense that stage 4 is extraordinary.)
(Feeling nervous, they approach the assistant producer.)
- Is that the assistant producer? - Be careful.
Hurry up and cry, Kwang Soo. 1, 2.
(Bawling)
(Okay. We are almost there!)
I will give you money for the mission.
(Hurry up and give it to me!)
Hold on.
Here you go.
(Cute)
(Why did they go to this extent?)
(Get your anger level up!)
Please get a cash receipt.
(The assistant producer worries about totaling the payments later.)
(I won't look.)
(They barely manage to pass stage 4.)
(Only the grand stage 5 remains.)
Be careful. There must be something inside.
Keep your guard up.
(They will succeed if they buy a bottle of water.)
(Will they be able to pass stage 5 without laughing?)
(Only the grand stage 5 remains.)
Be careful. There must be something inside.
Keep your guard up.
(They will succeed if they buy a bottle of water.)
(Will they be able to pass stage 5 without laughing?)
(Kwang Soo bursts out laughing.)
What is it?
(He collapses as soon as he takes a look.)
What is it? What is it?
(What could be stage 5?)
(Who is this man?)
(Han Ki Bum, Ex-basketball player and Kwang Soo's doppelganger)
(Sultry)
(A single glance knocks Kwang Soo out.)
What is it? What is it?
(Kwang Soo fails at stage 5.)
(What could it be?)
(Beyond imagination)
(Rolling on the floor)
Don't. Please don't.
Don't go in.
Give up right here and now.
(The boss of stage 5, Han Ki Bum)
- I am too scared to go in. - I can't believe it.
This is cheating!
I am too scared to go in. Is it that bad?
- Is it that bad? - I mean,
it might be rude to say it's bad, but...
What is he doing there?
- Jong Kook, go in. - What is he...
I will succeed no matter what.
Seriously. Don't come in.
We suffered too much to fail here. Don't laugh.
Is it funny? Is it funny?
Jong Kook.
(Give up.)
It will be beyond your imagination.
You won't be able to guess. I am serious.
Buy a bottle of water and come on out.
- Jong Kook. - I just need to buy water.
You just need to buy water. It's not hard.
I ask for water,
- Buy water and come out. - hand him cash,
- and he rings me up. - Yes, then walk out.
(It's the easiest mission in the world.)
(A strong man)
(A weak man)
(If he perseveres and succeeds, he will receive a crucial hint.)
Just get a bottle of water. Get it first.
Okay. Water.
(He walks over to get a bottle of water.)
(Halting)
I think I saw him in the corner of my eye.
(I think I saw him in the corner of my eye.)
(Bawling)
Water. Where is water? Water.
(I saw a big silhouette.)
(Kwang Soo is still suffering.)
He is like a cheat code.
This is cheating.
Did he see him? Did Jong Kook see him?
Water.
(Jong Kook is desperately searching for water.)
(He loads up his tears...)
(and marches towards the cashier.)
(He can't do it.)
(Bawling)
(Kwang Soo can't breathe.)
(You did your best. Just give up.)
(He's calm.)
Why?
(He braces himself and tries again.)
(He retreats again.)
I can't do it. I can't go in.
(He can only watch.)
Go inside.
(He breathes rapidly as if he has heartburn.)
How much is it?
(They finally meet.)
It's 7.77 dollars.
(It's 7.77 dollars.)
(He's flustered by the unexpected joke.)
Hey, that's wrong.
(Female owner: Hey, that's wrong.)
You're in high school, and you still can't do math?
(You're in high school, and you still can't do math?)
(He's in high school?)
- I'm sorry. - You should be.
You're a student. You should be able to calculate that.
I'm sorry.
He's a student.
(He's a student.)
(The man's identity is a mystery.)
I'm sorry.
(A huge mosquito bit me!)
It was itchy
A huge mosquito bit me!
(It was really...)
I forgot the lines.
(He's jolly.)
Let me try again.
(A huge mosquito bit my foot!)
(He chants passionately with blood vessels in his neck showing.)
(He feels much better.)
(Why are you trying so hard, my hero?)
It was itchy
But...
(He attacks again.)
(Quit it now.)
Is it still not funny?
(Student: Is it still not funny?)
No.
- What? - Is it still not funny?
(Jong Kook struggles to count bills. He's vulnerable.)
How much is it?
7.77 dollars.
- 7 dollars! - 70...
Here!
(He tries to leave in a hurry.)
- Do the math. - Take your change.
- I don't need it! - Take your change.
I don't need it!
- Take seven cents back. - Keep it.
What do we do?
Why is he there?
(Staggering)
(Laughing)
He's a strong opponent.
- Jong Kook. - Am I okay?
- It's over. - I'm going to tear up.
- How did you resist that? - Goodness.
I got water and walked up to him.
I almost died.
As soon as I got inside...
(He came out in 1 second.)
Hello.
I almost died of laughter.
He's intense. He didn't laugh.
I was shocked.
He's so intense.
- Have you been well? - Yes.
- It's been a very long time. - My brother Kwang Soo.
- As soon as I saw him... - He drove me nuts.
Even if I resisted in the beginning,
I wailed.
I would have collapsed at the student part.
(I would have collapsed at the student part.)
Thank you.
Kwang Soo failed, but Jong Kook succeeded.
- I'm relieved. - You passed. I'll give you a hint.
Thank you.
Great work.
He should have come first. You came before him.
(We would like to thank Ki Bum for helping despite his busy schedule.)
- Are they back? - Jong Kook.
- Wasn't that insane? - Hey.
I'm drained.
- Why? - Why are you drained?
For trying not to laugh.
- You didn't laugh? - I...
- You failed, right? - I did.
He did it.
How did you not laugh?
- It was really hard. - He held it in.
- How did you do it? - I can usually stop myself.
I almost cried this time.
I resisted until the end, but as soon as I opened the door...
(He collapsed as soon as he opened the door.)
As soon as he opened the door, he rolled out.
(It was like a laughing gas chamber.)
Give us a hint.
I'll give you a hint.
I'll give it to you during the final judgment.
It's a decisive hint.
We know this now.
Jong Kook succeeded,
so he's not the bio-terrorist.
- Right. - He can't be.
It can be you.
- This is a hint. - It is.
It's a hint, so it can't be me.
I personally think it's 1 of these 3.
I went with Jong Kook, and I don't think it's him.
Why can't it be you?
Why is it not you?
- Exactly. - Your personal thoughts?
He resisted but laughed in the end. If I were him,
I wouldn't have been able to stop myself either.
I actually peed myself.
I'm serious. As soon as I saw him.
Weren't you startled?
(The bio-terrorist's identity is still unclear.)
Don't forget. You have to finish everything by 6 p.m.
- We have to do an indoor activity. - Indoor activity.
What time is it? It's past 2 p.m.
After the indoor activity, we have to get dessert.
- A quiz. - Let's do a quiz.
- In teams. - Let's do that.
The losing team has to do the next mission.
Right.
The zombies have to be among us too.
Let's have Jae Seok and Seok Jin's teams.
- Sure. - Okay.
Do rock-paper-scissors. Pick your teammates.
The infected members can't go even if they lose.
We can't go.
- That's true. - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin wins.)
Pick one person.
Jong Kook.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok has to pick one person.)
Hey!
(So Min bites his name tag.)
Oh, my goodness. Look at her.
- Goodness. - She almost had it.
- She almost had it. - Oh, gosh.
- Jae Seok, did you see me? - Goodness.
Jae Seok. Jae Seok!
Hey, hold on.
You could have ripped off his name tag.
Kwang Soo came pretty late.
No, Jong Kook.
- Really? - No.
- I thought he was out. - If I were the bio-terrorist,
I wouldn't have blocked her with my body.
- Kwang Soo, that was... - Hey, you.
(The suspicion grows.)
(Team Seok Jin: Jong Kook, So Min, Kwang Soo)
(Team Jae Seok: Haha, Ji Hyo, Se Chan)
Pick one person from each team.
So Min.
- Me? - Is it So Min?
- Let's do Ji Hyo then. - It's Ji Hyo.
Good luck!
Good luck, So Min.
Here's the question.
A farmer with 20 bananas sold all but 7 bananas.
How many does he have left?
Let me answer.
(She raised her hand as soon as she heard the question.)
18.
- Incorrect. - No.
20 and 7.
13.
- Incorrect. - What's the question?
- What's the question? - Let me repeat the question.
A farmer with 20 bananas sold all but 7 bananas.
How many does he have left?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer. 13.
- Incorrect. - Let me answer. Seven.
- Correct. - It's seven, Ji Hyo.
(It's 7, Ji Hyo.)
Right.
- What did he say? - It's a play-on-words.
He sold all but seven.
That's confusing.
- Go, Se Chan. - Okay.
Kwang Soo.
This is the final match.
I must win.
- He sold all but seven. - It's a play-on-words.
I'll use all the knowledge I have.
Good luck!
(He's the rising power of ignorance.)
- Se Chan doesn't know anything. - I'm not kidding.
Don't worry.
- It's Se Chan. - It's unpleasant for me to hear it.
- I know. - Your pride will crumble...
- if you lose to him. - Here's the question.
- In the solar system... - What?
- Solar system. - Solar system?
- In the solar system... - You know what it is, right?
On the rooftop,
(He's flustered times 100.)
- there are boards. - Those are solar panels, you punk.
Hey.
(He's annoyed.)
- Hey! - Oh, gosh.
He's on our team.
- Mars and Jupiter? - Those are solar panels.
- Mars and Jupiter. - Good luck!
I got this.
What am I doing sitting here?
Here's the question.
A submarine made out of lead can hold 60 people.
30 men and 29 women got on it,
but it sank. Why?
Let me answer.
They were too heavy.
(They were too heavy.)
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
It's made out of lead, so it sinks. Because it's lead?
(It's lead, so it sinks. Because it's lead?)
- Incorrect. - What?
It's not correct?
Let me answer.
When you add 30 to 29, it's 59,
but the lead is 60.
What are you saying?
- Incorrect. - I'm not sure either.
- I don't get it. - 30 men and 29 women?
- Let me repeat the question. - Okay.
- I got it. - A submarine made out of lead...
can hold 60 people. 30 men and 29 women got on it,
- but it sank. - It's a submarine, so it sinks.
Why?
(Right, it's a submarine.)
That's true.
That's right.
- Let me answer. - Yes?
One woman is missing.
Incorrect.
This is really...
Let me answer.
There was a pregnant woman.
- Incorrect. - No.
- You're wrong. - No. Don't you get it?
Think about it carefully.
Hey, listen to the question.
Someone didn't wear any lead.
Hey!
(He says whatever.)
So...
- So... - It's because...
The correct answer is that it was a submarine.
- Goodness. - It's a lead submarine.
- It's a submarine. - Submarines sink.
He said it's a submarine. They sink.
- Don't give them these questions. - I thought I had to use knowledge.
I get it now.
Are you verifying how stupid you are?
He said one person is pregnant.
(He's embarrassed.)
Here's the question.
This paper is used to see if a solution is acidic or basic.
It turns red for acidic solutions and turns blue for basic solutions.
Don't you know this?
- This is so easy. - They should know.
Let me answer.
- Pita... - This is so easy.
- Go. - Spoize?
What is it? Spo...
Spoize?
No.
It's something like that.
- Silence. - The one that changes colors.
- Here's a hint. - A hint?
- It has "s" in it. - Hey.
- It has four characters. - "S" is at the end.
Four characters.
He's never heard of it.
Here's another hint.
- The first character is... - You have to get it.
- "li". - Let me answer!
(He yelled out as soon as heard the hint.)
- He doesn't know. - He doesn't.
- He doesn't? - It's "li".
- It starts with that. - "Li".
- It ends with "s". - Four characters. "S".
- 4 characters. You only need 2. - "Li", blank, blank, and "s".
- "Li", blank, blank, and "s". - Kleenex.
(Kleenex)
Kleenex? Do you think I'm stupid?
(Kleenex? Do you think I'm stupid?)
I am annoyed.
(I am not stupid.)
- I don't think this is the answer. - Give it a try.
Let me answer.
Rimowa.
Rimowa!
- That's a luggage brand. - That's a luggage brand.
Rimowa is a luggage brand.
Adding "s" at the end would make Rimowas.
- I will give you the third letter. - Okay.
The third letter is...
- M. - M.
- So you have L, blank, M, and S. - You have everything.
Let me answer. Is it "Litmus"?
Correct.
(Litmus is correct.)
- I did it! - You fool!
(I won!)
- For goodness' sake. - For goodness' sake.
- For goodness' sake. - You fool!
(I can't believe I lost to Se Chan.)
I did it!
- All right. - I can't believe you.
I brought that up from the corner of my brain.
- The score is 1 to 1. - Litmus.
1 to 1.
Let's have a group match.
- Okay. Let's have a group match. - It's time for a group match.
- Okay. Okay. - A group match.
Let's have a quiz on four-character idioms.
If you give us the meaning of the idiom,
- we will say the four characters. - A character each.
The order will be important.
Here comes the question.
The literal meaning of the idiom is, "A mantis blocks a wagon."
It depicts the weak who foolishly challenges the strong.
Let me answer. "Sa".
- Incorrect. - Let me answer. "Dang".
- Is it right? - It must be right.
It's right!
- Really? - Is "Dang" correct?
- Jae Seok. - "Dang".
"Rang".
"Dang" and "Rang".
- 3, 2... - "Dang", "Rang"...
- "Kwon". - Incorrect.
("Kwon" makes no sense.)
Let me answer.
- "Dang". - "Rang".
- "Bang". - Incorrect.
- "Geo". - "Ji".
- Incorrect. - "Dangranggeoji".
- "Geo" - Incorrect.
- "Dang". - "Rang".
"Geo".
- Boom! - Incorrect.
(She uses a palm blast.)
What character could there be?
- I will give you a hint. - Okay.
The character starts with C.
- C? - C.
- "Dang". - "Rang".
"Geo".
- "Cha". - Incorrect.
- "Chu". - Incorrect.
- "Chang". - "Cho".
- "Cheon". - "Cheo".
- "Chang". - Incorrect.
No, no.
I will give you the last hint.
- Okay. - The last character...
is right in front of your eyes.
Right in front of our eyes? Look.
It's right in front of our eyes.
- Right in front of our eyes? - That's right.
Camera.
- Camera, producer, writer... - Hey!
Right in front of our eyes?
(They scan the scene in front of them.)
- Camera, producer, writer... - Hey!
Hey! There is Chul Min.
- "Dang". - "Dang".
- "Dang". - "Rang".
- "Geo". - "Chul".
Correct.
(Dangranggeochul is correct.)
I see.
I have never heard of that before.
- I forgot Chul Min's name. - I've never heard of that before.
I am sorry,
but this is making us look stupid. Let's play something else.
Seriously. This is making us look stupid.
We were yelling out "Cha", "Chya", "Cho", and "Chyo".
- All right. - Do you want one more question?
- Go ahead. - One more question.
Here it comes.
(The last question)
The literal meaning is "Unable to forget night and day".
This idiom depicts the situation where one can't fall sleep...
due to longing or too many thoughts and worries.
(The answer is Ohmaebulmang.)
Say "Let me answer" first.
(Ji Hyo, here is the answer.)
Let me answer.
- "Son". - For goodness' sake!
(Wasn't that what you told me?)
Let me answer.
- "Bi". - Incorrect.
(Ji Hyo, look again.)
(Oh, I get it now!)
Let me answer. "Deung".
- For goodness' sake. - Come on!
(Is "Deung" incorrect as well?)
(O)
(A?)
Let me answer.
- "Oh". - That's right!
"Mae".
"Bul".
"Geo".
("Geo"?)
- Incorrect. - Come on!
- "Geo". - Incorrect.
Come on!
(He ruined it again.)
Let me answer. "Oh".
"Mae".
- "Bul". - "Mang".
Okay!
- Correct. - Okay.
(Ohmaebulmang is correct.)
- "Ohmaebulgeo"! - "Ohmaebulgeo"!
- I am sorry. - What's "Ohmaebulgeo"?
It was "Ohmaebulmang".
When I pointed at Ji Hyo's hand,
she said,
"Son".
(She is the type to look at the tree, not the forest.)
When I pointed again, she said,
"Deung".
- Was that what it was? - Yes.
Ji Hyo.
- The score is... - It's tied.
- tied. - One last question.
- One last question. - Let's go.
One last question.
Here comes the question.
The literal meaning is...
"Lying on firewood and swallowing bile".
It's a four-character idiom about...
enduring all kinds of hardships to take revenge.
(The answer is Washinsangdam.)
- Let me answer. - I know the answer.
- Go ahead. - "Wa".
- That's right. - "Wa".
- Incorrect. - Hey!
(What a surprise.)
Think of bile.
"Swallowing bile"?
- Hurry up. - Think of bile.
- "Wa". - "Shin".
- "Bile". - Incorrect.
What comes next?
(Team Seok Jin fails.)
- Go ahead. - Let me answer. "Wa".
- "Shin". - "Sang".
- "Gan". - Incorrect.
("Washinsanggan"?)
What even is "Washinsanggan"?
- Bile. - What's the answer?
(The mention of bile threw him off.)
Again. Again.
(Their livers hurt from laughing.)
- What even is "Washinsanggan"? - Let's go.
All right.
- Think of something that pours out. - Think of bile.
Think of bile.
- "Wa". - "Shin".
"Sang".
"Juice".
("Washinsangjuice"!)
- What even is... - All right.
- Let me answer. - We won't tell her.
What's bile?
Does it come from the liver?
Let's go.
- "Wa". - Don't tell her.
- "Shin". - We didn't tell her.
"Sang".
- Hold on. - Leave him be.
- Let him try. - 5, 4...
(Se Chan points to his gallbladder.)
(Will Se Chan be able to complete the answer?)
"Lung".
(Take this.)
(No one imagined such a lousy answer.)
He drives me insane.
You will name all the organs at this rate.
Go.
- "Wa". - "Shin".
- "Sang". - "Dam".
("Washinsangdam")
- Correct. - Okay!
How did you know?
- "Dam" is a character for "Bile". - That's it.
(The final score is 2 to 3.)
Thus, Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, and So Min's team wins.
Yes!
To be honest,
I was startled two times.
The first time was when I said "Wa" and Ji Hyo said "Wa".
The second time was when Se Chan said "Gan".
"Washinsanggan".
"Wawasanggan".
(It was a hilarious match.)
- Unbelievable. - "Wa" and "Wa".
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Okay.
- You don't get to participate. - You don't get to participate.
Oh, I am a zombie.
- Okay. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok will go out to buy snacks!)
Jae Seok.
Is it Jae Seok?
- He was the most suspicious anyway. - Okay.
I will be back.
Bye.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
(Jae Seok leaves the house by himself.)
- Humans should sit together. - That's right.
- Come on. Let's mingle. - We should mingle.
Mingle, my foot!
This isn't a group date.
(This isn't a group date.)
Send the zombies away.
- Go down. Sit on the floor. - You could take off our name tags.
So Min, hurry up and sit on the floor.
- Sit on the floor. - Sit on the floor.
That's right. Sit on the floor and lean against the sofa.
Let's go up.
Se Chan.
You look like the fourth hitter.
- Seriously. - Really?
I knew someone like him back in school.
- Someone like me? - Yes.
If the bio-terrorist is in here,
he or she should give us zombies...
- a sign. - That's right.
I haven't received a sign.
- Don't disregard us. - At this rate, you will lose.
(Not even those who got infected know the bio-terrorist.)
At this rate, you will lose.
Is the bio-terrorist not in here?
Does that mean Jae Seok is the bio-terrorist?
(Jae Seok comes out of the house by himself.)
What is it?
Choose from Route 1 to 4.
Route Three.
Please check the phone for your mission.
For goodness' sake.
(Which mission did Jae Seok choose?)
What?
"Photos That Kill"?
This is a two-man mission,
so pick a member who will accompany you.
(Whom will Jae Seok choose?)
For the two-man mission, Jae Seok has chosen Haha.
Me?
I choose Haha.
See you later.
I might come back as a zombie.
I think he plans to turn me into a zombie.
If both of them become a zombie,
one of these three will be the bio-terrorist.
(Will Jae Seok and Haha be able to avoid the virus?)
(Taking a peek)
- Jae Seok. - What?
(Extremely nervous)
What's the mission?
- He is here. - All right.
This is a two-man mission,
Photos That Kill.
You will go to a convenience store to buy snacks.
If you get less than three photos taken by the paparazzi...
which show your name tag,
or your face with either your eyes, nose, or mouth, you succeed.
(Get less than three photos taken by the paparazzi...)
(which show your name tag or eyes, nose, and mouth.)
- We can hide our faces, right? - Let's stand like this.
This pose will show our faces.
- It will show your face. - That's right.
We can do this.
We should walk...
like this.
(Hide your face with swagger like a hip-hop musician.)
Can we go now?
I picked you because you're the most suspicious.
- I am suspicious of you. - I am suspicious of you too.
- Don't be like that. - I am serious.
Why are you suspicious of me?
Today, you are...
too quiet.
(They set off suspicious of each other.)
(Clicking)
(I got you.)
(Are they paparazzi?)
(Clicking)
Hold on.
(Sir!)
Thank you.
(They soothe their hearts with a yogurt drink.)
(You didn't expect this, right?)
(My goodness!)
(Terrified)
(Is this how it's going to be?)
I don't know who the paparazzi are.
- Me neither. - There is no way of knowing.
I can't tell if they are just regular people...
- or the paparazzi. - My goodness!
What is it?
(I am a paparazzo.)
Are you really going to take photos so openly?
(Diligent)
Come on, stop following me.
I think they took a lot of pictures of you.
Me?
It's you, right?
- What? - Seeing how many you got taken.
- No, it's not me. - We won't fail,
- so it's you. - It's not.
It has to be you.
(What's the conclusion of this uncomfortable partnership?)
- Here's the result. - Okay.
Am I right? He got so many pictures taken.
I didn't.
Your name tag or face has to be in the picture.
Both of you...
(What's the result?)
Both of you didn't get more than three.
- Really? - Really?
You both succeeded.
See? It's not me.
I turned slightly and avoided them.
It's you.
(Did they succeed because one of them is the bio-terrorist?)
- I swear it's not me. - It is you.
I swear it's not.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
- You're questioning me a lot. - I swear it's not me.
I never try this hard.
- It's not you? - I don't think it's Jong Kook.
- It's not Kwang Soo either. - I think it's either...
Jong Kook or Kwang Soo.
I think it's Haha.
It's either Dong Hoon or Jae Seok.
It's either one of you.
Why aren't you questioning each other?
(Sliding in)
Hey.
(She punishes him.)
(She hits him reflexively.)
Hold on.
Don't do that to him.
(She's also stunned.)
He's 54.
- Don't do that. - He's 54.
- I heard the sound. - Punk!
- I'm sorry. - Nobody has slapped me like this...
- in a long time. - I'm sorry.
- Hey. - Ji Hyo.
I'm sorry.
- He's eating the snack. - The snack.
- Why are you eating that? - Why are you replenishing glucose?
- I thought you had no appetite. - I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry.
- They're back. - They're back.
They took a while.
- They're back. - They took a long time.
Their faces are clean.
Both of them?
Haha, what's that?
- What's up with Haha? - Neither of them?
It's not the mission.
(This is the right timing.)
(Ripping)
- What? - All right.
(The old zombie attacks.)
(Here's one more infected member.)
What?
(He's dazed.)
Did he just rip it off?
Why do people keep dying in a disappointing way?
It's time for you to come to our side, everybody.
What's wrong?
Anyhow, on this route,
- both members succeeded. - What is it?
(Haha and Jae Seok aren't infected.)
(The bio-terrorist is among them.)
Is the bio-terrorist doing their job?
What do they do?
- Not getting caught. - Is that their job?
I guess then...
you're looking for the bio-terrorist.
We have to.
We haven't found the bio-terrorist yet.
Jae Seok,
did you think you succeeded with the mission?
I thought he failed for sure.
He got many pictures taken of his backside.
Haha is starting to corner Jae Seok, right?
(Is he cornering Jae Seok?)
That's what he does. He corners people.
This is driving me nuts.
- Because you two went. - So I...
- asked at the convenience store. - Sure. Listen to me.
(You be quiet.)
Two of you went out together this time.
I think you got caught.
It's not me. It's him.
Haha, it was the two of us.
If Kwang Soo or I laughed, we were eliminated.
You can see it.
Who can confirm it?
(He creeps up slowly.)
(He goes behind Jong Kook.)
(He tries to rip off Jong Kook's name tag.)
(Ouch!)
(Jong Kook punishes him immediately.)
(It's fun for everybody watching.)
That looks so painful.
That looks really painful.
(Goodness)
(He almost choked to death.)
I heard a thud when you bumped heads.
Jong Kook is incredible.
He had his chance.
This much of his hand was in my mouth.
Why didn't we get a hint?
I'll give you the last hint.
This is the hint Jong Kook and Kwang Soo earned.
There are two routes left,
- but I'll erase one. - Good.
(He erases one route.)
(The race is over once they use one route and finish the tasks.)
What do we need to do then?
Play a simple indoor game, then eat refreshments. That's all.
An indoor game.
Jong Kook, you can pick one person...
to do the mission.
Who should I send? Give me your opinions.
- Ji Hyo hasn't gone yet. - I haven't gone.
- She hasn't gone? - We can test her.
Sure. Go, Ji Hyo.
I'll go then.
But I swear I'm not the bio-terrorist.
Either way, if you succeed, we'll be suspicious.
- Ji Hyo, make sure you succeed. - If you fail...
If you succeed, we'll know the way.
- I know. We have to know. - How to kill the bio-terrorist.
See you later.
Let's go.
I pick four.
Check the phone.
"Before you reach your destination,"
"you have to face four bullies in the neighborhood."
"You succeed if you win three times."
- You have 30 minutes. - Okay.
Can I do something else?
Can I hit or curse at them?
How do the zombies win?
Once everybody is infected.
That's so difficult.
At this rate, humans will win.
- That's true. - Humans will win.
Is that right?
- Ji Hyo went... - If there's one human left.
- Did you see how shocked he was? - What's wrong, Jae Seok?
(Did you see how shocked he was?)
Hold on.
He was surprised to hear the humans might win.
- I'm a true entertainer. - Really?
(Is he making an excuse?)
I forgot what my role was...
- and reacted. - That's right.
I'm a professional.
What's the penalty today?
We have to think about Ji Hyo too.
- She's... - Acting skills.
I'm not sure about her.
- She could be acting. - But we know nothing.
(What is Ji Hyo's identity?)
This is driving me nuts.
I'm going to practice Tetris.
(She has the mark under her eyes.)
(She lost twice and got infected.)
I'm going to practice Omok.
Virus, virus.
(She's not the bio-terrorist.)
(There are three suspects left.)
Ji Hyo's infected.
- Is she out? - She's a zombie.
She failed.
Ji Hyo.
You're a zombie?
Jae Seok.
Was it hard?
Anyhow, you finished everything on the schedule.
You went through all the routes,
so I'll tell you how to eliminate the bio-terrorist.
(He reveals how to eliminate the bio-terrorist.)
What is it?
- What? - It's a water gun.
When you shoot water on the bio-terrorist's face,
he's eliminated.
(If you shoot water on his face, he's eliminated.)
However, if you accidentally shoot water on a human,
the person behind the water gun and the target are both out.
Who's going to use the water gun?
Jong Kook will.
Jong Kook is human.
(He will shoot.)
Why are you giving it to me?
Does he have a responsibility?
- Why? - Why?
- Jong Kook is human. - I see.
It's one of them.
- Finally. - I think...
Jae Seok's reaction earlier...
- It was unbelievable. - I understand your concern.
Right?
(Jong Kook's deduction: Jae Seok was shocked...)
(when he heard humans might win. Is he the bio-terrorist?)
(Why did he get so startled?)
I was just reacting.
- That's possible. - You said...
you're a professional entertainer.
- Right. - That's your point.
Listen to me. I just got goosebumps.
I thought I failed when Haha mentioned that.
But I didn't fail.
- So... - It's one of you.
that's where I got the idea.
To tell you the truth,
I picked him as my partner for a reason.
- Why? - I wanted to check him.
- Did you call him? - Yes.
(He wanted to check Haha.)
But I don't know.
What should I do? Will they be standing?
They'll be standing, so pick one person and shoot water on them.
- I've never been this calm. - He's calm.
Here I go.
(Who will he pick?)
- Just in case though. - What?
(What?)
Do you want to see me lose it?
(What is going on here?)
He's getting started.
I'm not saying it's you.
Just in case.
Jong Kook...
(He became a person of interest with an inappropriate reaction.)
(He became a person of interest with the "vinegar" comment.)
(Who did he pick?)
(Jae Seok)
Good job.
(Did he end up picking Jae Seok?)
This is annoying.
- The bio-terrorist is... - Let's see.
Let's see. Hold on.
No.
- The bio-terrorist is... - No.
(If he was wrong, the bio-terrorist wins.)
(Who's the bio-terrorist?)
Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok)
- I'm relieved. - I'm so relieved.
- Were you confused? - Yes.
At the end.
- Was it really you? - My fellow bio-terrorists.
(I'm sorry, fellow bio-terrorists.)
Today's race is A House Without an Exit.
You're a bio-terrorist who resets...
people's emotions and appetite.
What was that?
(When So Min tried the password on Haha,)
(he saw that Haha replied "vinegar" without having a clue.)
(He decided to corner Haha.)
(He approached the infected members.)
(It's you.)
(My babies)
(Welcome, leader.)
(Eliminate the humans.)
(He almost won.)
We found out too late.
Anyhow, you two survived as humans.
- Oh, my. - It's been a while.
You didn't have to give us this.
We can't share.
You didn't have to.
- Oh, dear. - Goodness.
I didn't know.
Look at this.
If Jae Seok won,
he would have picked two infected members for the penalty.
Since this happened,
Jong Kook and Haha will pick...
two people to be exempt. Everybody else will get the penalty.
Except for two?
(Everybody but 2 chosen by Haha and Jong Kook will get the penalty.)
- Except for those 2? - Except for 2.
- But Jae Seok will get the penalty. - Right.
(Jae Seok will suffer the penalty.)
(What kind of penalty awaits the 4 unlucky members?)
(Let's go.)
(A secret organization of fierce members, R)
(I'll show you how a professional rolls.)
(Stop filming.)
(Go Min Si and Hwang Bo Ran have joined R too.)
(The organization's goal is the gold bars.)
(At the end of the secret mission,)
(they successfully acquired the gold bars.)
(They do a mysterious celebratory performance.)
(However,)
(a thief has betrayed the organization.)
(The room of truth is open.)
(You betrayed us, didn't you?)
(It's not me.)
(Is it you, then?)
(It's not me, either.)
(As they laugh and chat, the gold bars keep disappearing.)
(And the shocking identity of the thief is revealed.)
(Betray for the Gold Bars)