Don't walk, run! This is Running Man. Hello, viewers.
(Running Man has been airing for 9 years without a break.)
(So many of the fans have supported the members of Running Man.)
(We have prepared this special episode to repay their support.)
(The very first fan-meet in Korea, Running Man's Fan-Meet)
(Opening song by all 8 members)
(The opening song by the members was about gratitude for the fans.)
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo showed nice chemistry unexpectedly.)
(And Jong Kook put on an amazing performance as expected.)
(The 3 youngest members brought things back to the 1990s.)
(Jae Seok and Haha put on a performance as a pair too.)
(Joint performances with musicians)
(And here are the performances to come.)
(At last, the final episode of the fan-meet special will air.)
(The joint performances have been hidden away from the viewers.)
(And the highlight of the fan-meet, the group choreography)
(And the theme song, "I Like You" which was written after 9 years)
(Sadly, this is the last story of Running Man's fan-meet.)
(The members went on a long journey of 100 days for the fan-meet.)
(The race starts!)
"There is..."
(There is a spy among you today.)
We asked the spy to be the most passionate today.
(The audience already knows who the spy is.)
(There are hints?)
(When the members finish their performance,)
(if the cheer from the audience is over 120dB, they get a hint.)
(Here are the hints obtained after the cheer reached 120dB.)
(The spy likes cafes but not restaurants.)
(Who on earth is the spy?)
(Who is the spy?)
(After Pink Nose Light's turn, it's Hyo Chan Park's turn.)
(I heard that somebody incredible is coming.)
(Who is it?)
(Who is this incredible secret weapon from Hyo Chan Park?)
(As their curiosity about the secret weapon is intensifying,)
(Nucksal and Code Kunst's entrance to the stage excites them.)
(Looking totally relaxed)
(Just by entering, they can dominate the stage.)
(Dazzling aura)
Nucksal.
Gosh, they look cool. They look so cool.
Are you ready to have fun?
- Yes! - Yes!
(They're professionals who have participated in TV competitions.)
(Meanwhile, he's a rookie who is not relaxed at all.)
(Utterly nervous)
(The video plays before the performance.)
(Will the video tell us who the secret weapon is?)
(Ji Hyo is pretty today as always.)
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Yang Se Chan)
(Hyo Chan Park, 9 Years of Running Man)
Hey, we're going to start recording now.
(They are nervous to record the song.)
Darn it.
(Letting out a deep breath)
I don't t think you're ready. You're only pretending to be.
Why would you be nervous?
Let's see.
Before we record, let's listen to the guide track.
- And we'll record next. - Okay.
Dr. Co will be the main director of today's recording.
- I'm very strict. - He is. So be careful today.
No matter how good you are, I'll reject the first three tries.
(Warning in advance)
(Trembling in fear)
Okay. I should mess up the first three tries.
(I should mess up the first 3 tries.)
(You'll do what?)
(Unintelligible singing)
- Fine. I'll say, "Okay. Come out." - "Let me do it again."
(Then the project will be halted right away.)
"Let me do it again. I didn't start yet."
First, let's start recording.
- Se Chan, go inside. - Okay.
Se Chan will go in.
(Se Chan will go in first.)
Okay.
(He clears his throat and starts recording.)
Pump up the volume, get excited
Why is this beeping?
(Why is this beeping?)
Why is that beeping? It happened the other day too.
Was that arrogant of me? Should I ignore it and keep going?
- No, no. You're right. - I'll just do it. I'm sorry.
- No. - You're right.
Or the microphone might be rejecting you.
Or you might be getting electrocuted.
(Dr. Co sounds strict, and Nucksal is joking.)
- I should be careful then. - Electrocuted?
- He's high-maintenance. - He's getting annoying now.
(Teasing again)
Hey, Se Chan is pretty good.
- He's really good. - He's good.
- The Gang approves you. - You were good.
- Okay. Great. Do it just like that. - Okay.
Okay.
(Ji Hyo starts recording next.)
I'm nervous.
- All right. - She's nervous.
We'll start now.
Don't forget you're a rapper now.
I'm a rapper.
Yes.
(Messing up the lyrics)
Beautiful memories
Turn it off.
(The instrumental is turned off.)
Stop it.
- This is getting annoying. - I'm sorry.
You're really nervous, so your pitch is shaking.
Oh, boy.
(She starts recording again after preparing herself.)
(Looking serious)
(His countenance grows stiff.)
Her voice is shaking too much. Will that work? Let's hear it again.
- Okay. Let's try a few more times. - Yes.
(Ji Hyo keeps recording again and again.)
Ji Hyo, you're doing great.
Do I just keep doing what I've been doing?
But you're nervous, so your voice is shaking.
Or do you want to do it sitting down?
- No. Standing up will be better. - Some people sit down and do it.
- Okay. All right then. - I'll try.
- Take your time, Ji Hyo. - Okay.
You're doing great.
Ji Hyo, don't worry. Just be yourself.
We have a lot of time.
(Will she overcome her nervousness on stage?)
(She's been preparing for 3 months for these next 3 minutes on stage.)
(Feeling nervous)
(3 singers are watching the clips.)
My gosh, look at their faces.
(Don't be nervous, and go for it!)
(Hyo Chan Park's performance with the incredible secret weapon)
("Bonjour, Hi" by Hyo Chan Park)
(The heart-fluttering feeling before entering a club unfolds in notes.)
(Hyo Chan Park)
(Let's get it!)
Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and Code Kunst.
(They prepared a park where people can have fun at.)
At last.
(Looking forward to their performance)
(The decibels are slowly going up too.)
(Se Chan is fully ready to enter the stage now.)
(Get ready, Se Chan will start now.)
(Se Chan enters with full of swag without any hint of nervousness.)
(My gosh, he's really good!)
(Muscular swag)
(His perfect rapping impresses them.)
He's cute.
(The lyrics with perfect rhymes written by Se Chan himself)
(This is so exciting!)
(This catchy chorus makes the audience sing along.)
(Bonjour, hi)
(Hyo Chan Park wanted to have fun with the fans together.)
(The decibels for "Bonjour, Hi" are pretty high.)
(When everyone is enjoying the show,)
(the identity of the secret weapon is becoming a bigger mystery.)
(Se Chan has been rapping furiously.)
(And he points somewhere.)
(Surprised!)
(It's Ji Hyo!)
(The audience who's been grooving looks at something.)
(Surprised)
(Everyone's eyes are fixated on the left.)
(While grabbing everyone's attention,)
(Ji Hyo shows up on the lift.)
She looks so cool.
The lift was a great idea.
(They are impressed and proud of Ji Hyo's perfect entrance.)
- Gosh. - She's good.
(Ji Hyo wrote the lyrics herself while looking back on her 9 years.)
Scream, everyone!
(Her sincere lyrics excite the audience even more.)
(When the atmosphere is reaching its peak,)
(the mysterious secret weapon shows up.)
(No way!)
(I can't believe this!)
(I can't believe I'm seeing this rapper in person.)
(The secret weapon that made everyone's jaws drop)
(The rapper that entered the stage amid the fervent cheer is...)
(Am I dreaming? Is this really happening?)
(Unable to talk)
(The secret weapon Hyo Chan Park has been hiding is...)
(the best female rapper in Korea.)
(The queen of hip-hop artists, Yoon Mi Rae)
(Yoon Mi Rae was the secret weapon!)
(Even the members didn't know about it.)
- Tasha! - Hey.
T.
(With her entrance, the audience's cheer is the loudest.)
(The queen of hip-hop artists rule the stage by her mere presence.)
This is Yoon Mi Rae!
(The performance is at its climax with its catchy melody and Mi Rae.)
(Everyone, put your hands up!)
One more time.
Running Man!
("Bonjour, Hi" by Hyo Chan Park with Yoon Mi Rae)
(Their performance calls for amazement.)
(That was the best!)
Hyo Chan Park! My gosh, that was so cool.
Hey, Yoon Mi Rae!
- Make some noise! - Thank you.
(Mi Rae's singing made an already perfect performance more perfect.)
Hello, everyone.
We're Hyo Chan Park. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
(Your performance was so good!)
Hello. I'm Yoon Mi Rae. Nice to meet you.
(We should be saying that to you!)
(Fervent welcome)
(Thank you for the warm welcome.)
Mi Rae was our secret weapon.
So she joined us as a surprise.
Right. Thank you for inviting me.
How was it? Please tell us how it was.
I wanted...
to do a good job.
- You were amazing! - I'm sorry.
- Everyone did great. - You were great.
By the way, you were so good.
Thank you.
And your outfit looks really good on you. You look cool.
- This is all Code Kunst. - My gosh.
The song was great too.
- Thank you. - I...
I should've done better. I'm sorry.
(I should've done better. I'm sorry.)
(She ends her conversation with an apology.)
Seriously.
But thank you so much for having me today.
I'll do a better job if you give me another chance.
Please give her a round of applause.
Thank you.
- Have a wonderful time. - Okay.
We have another performance coming up next.
Please enjoy the show until the end.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
Be happy.
(The second joint performance that excited everyone is over.)
(We had so much fun!)
- It was so fun. You were so good. - My gosh.
(They are satisfied with their perfect performance.)
Thank you.
- Mi Rae. - Thank you!
I'll call you later. I'll treat you.
- Whenever. - Thank you.
- See you next time. - Great job today!
- Well done. - Our eyes met, right?
Hey, we did great. Seriously.
- We did well. - We did well.
- We did well. - Did we go over the number?
Yes, the decibels of Hyo Chan Park...
(They got the audience to sing along.)
(And they even utilized a secret weapon, Yoon Mi Rae.)
(Did they go over 120dB?)
- It's 124. - My gosh.
- You accomplished your mission. - My gosh.
- There was a mission? - You can choose...
- 1 of these 3 hints. - Code Kunst, you should choose.
- Okay. - Code Kunst, pick one.
- This one. - This hint is important.
- Give it to Se Chan. - Can I read it?
- Yes. - Yes.
(The spy was lucky today.)
"The spy was lucky today"?
(The spy was lucky today?)
- The spy got lucky today? - So...
Could that be it?
Jae Seok and Haha didn't get lucky, so they did the penalty.
Does that mean Jae Seok and Haha can't be the spy? Is that possible?
Okay. I got it. Let's go and try to figure it out.
- This is giving me a headache. - This is crazy.
- Anyway, - I just...
- We did well. - Hyo Chan Park's "Bonjour, Hi"...
(Hyo Chan Park's "Bonjour, Hi" was amazing!)
(We did so well.)
- I'm in such a good mood. - Let's go.
Say, "Ho"!
(When the audience is hyped up after Hyo Chan Park's performance,)
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin show up,)
(encouraging people to participate with a hip-hop style cheer.)
Ho, ho, ho.
(Ho, ho, ho!)
- Thank you. - Thank you so much.
Seriously. We can't calm the excitement in here.
I mean it.
We're more excited by how excited you are.
(The next group will continue with this excitement.)
Anyway, next up is...
Jae Seok...
(My gosh, it's Jae Seok.)
- So Min. - And...
(If these two are performing, it must be with SORAN!)
That's right. It's SORAN.
(The third group is Team SORAN.)
- Let's do a cheer, Jae Seok. - Okay.
- Gather around. - Let's do it.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
(Let's go!)
Please welcome Team SORAN with a big round of applause!
(SORAN)
(Jeon So Min)
(Yu Jae Seok)
(Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok, 9 Years of Running Man)
(17 days before the fan-meet)
All right.
Today, we'll be recording the song.
All of a sudden,
we're here.
You listened to the song.
- Yes, we did. - How is it for you?
I like the song.
Seriously.
Under the strict supervision of Jae Seok,
I fixed the song a lot.
- These days, - He helped.
I even sleep excitedly because you told me to make it exciting.
("Make it more exciting. More exciting, Young Bae.)
So how should I say this?
As a music enthusiast who loves music,
I suggested making a song that the public would like more...
to Young Bae.
Young Bae gave it more thought.
- That's how this song was born. - Yes, I love the song.
He worked so hard.
- Thank you so much. - I love the song.
(This exciting song was made under Jae Seok's supervision.)
I like everything.
But the lyrics... How should I say it?
(What's wrong with the lyrics?)
I'm disappointed that I wasn't able...
to participate in the lyric-writing session.
- Right. - I had another filming that day.
I'm sure you could have rescheduled, but you two...
(I'm sure you could have rescheduled, but you two...)
I thought about why you chose a day when I was unavailable.
I realized that from the get-go, you guys wanted...
to make me...
a puppet.
(You guys wanted to make me a puppet.)
You took me in because you wanted to use me only on stage.
- No, that's not true. - That crossed my mind.
- That's not true. - Really?
- We didn't plan it. - So...
a name for the team came to my mind.
It suits this situation perfectly.
Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok.
(A perfect name, Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok)
- No. That's... - Hold on.
"Jeon SORAN"?
(And a guest singer, Yu Jae Seok)
- From my observation, - I...
it looks like the five of you will form a group.
So Min, aren't you happy?
- I'm so happy. - Right.
(I'm so happy.)
(So they decided on the name, Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok.)
Here's why I'm scared of these lyrics.
- You know why, right? - Why is that?
So Min told me a few stories about her past relationships.
And they are in the song.
(So Min's past relationships are in the song.)
(Her parents are shocked.)
I'm not just enjoying this music.
I feel like I'm relaying her message to someone.
I just wrote my thoughts.
You asked me to write the lyrics,
so I did.
There was this guy whom I really liked.
But he just wouldn't confess his feelings to me.
It was obvious that he liked me,
but he wouldn't say it.
"Just say one thing. That's the only way I'd know."
"Please say something."
"Say that you love me or that you like me."
"Forget about that. Just kiss me."
(Forget about that. Just kiss me.)
(Her straightforwardness is reflected in her lyrics.)
She wrote this much.
I wrote a lot.
(The entire screen is filled up.)
I'm relaying her message to someone.
(Jae Seok and SORAN are her avatars.)
I became afraid of her.
(The truth behind the lyrics is finally revealed.)
I understand her completely.
But if you put that aside...
and just read her lyrics,
she is a genius.
The people around me are shocked.
I do understand that,
but this part, "Do you want to kiss me?"
(Her lyrics are very explicit.)
- It's a bit... - You see,
my mission is to make this song very popular...
so that he'll have no choice but to confess his feelings.
(So that he'll have no choice but to confess his feelings.)
(We cheer for you.)
(Did our daughter really write...)
("Do you want to kiss me?")
(Her love story is out in the open.)
Do you get it?
- So Min. - I'm going to torture him...
- so that he'll have no choice. - "You just need to speak up."
- I know. - "Just kiss me."
What's your take on this?
I think her lyrics are real...
and sincere,
- so I really like it. - Right?
- It's energizing. - Isn't it nice?
Imagine that you're the guy...
in her lyrics.
I'd be quite uncomfortable.
(He sings a different tune.)
(Her straightforward lyrics would make him uncomfortable.)
Right? See?
That's what I mean.
So Min.
- Let's record it. - All right.
- Show us. - Good luck.
- He's good. - No, I'm not.
He's good. I saw him last time.
- Really? - Yes.
(What do you want to eat?)
(I'll buy them for you)
(The lyrics are based on her story and there's a cheerful melody.)
(They like the song.)
(Confess to me)
(Just do it)
(Say something)
(You're driving me crazy)
Confess to me, just do it
(They burst into laughter at the lyrics.)
They're laughing at the lyrics.
(She's embarrassed.)
- That was nice. - The end wasn't nice, right?
- "Say something," was nice. - And "You're driving me crazy"?
When you sing that...
You're driving me crazy
Act like it's really driving you...
- crazy. - Okay, I got it.
(He wants Jae Seok to show his emotions.)
- Crazy. - Okay, I got it.
Here we go.
(Laughing)
(Their eyes meet.)
- That's good. - Our eyes met,
and I hated it.
(Our eyes met, and I hated it.)
- I like this. - and I hated it.
- I hate this. - My story is being made.
She looked so happy.
(He truly thinks that he's an avatar.)
Give it another go.
- Here we go. - Okay.
(They resume the recording.)
(After his powerful singing...)
(Before this song is over)
Try it again.
(She puts in too much emotion.)
It's too high-pitched.
("Confess Already" by Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok...)
(is filled with So Min's innermost thoughts.)
Race start.
(The performance will be revealed now.)
(SORAN appears.)
(Drummer: Pyun Yoo Il, Bassist: Seo Myun Ho,)
(Guitarist: Lee Tae Wook)
(Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok also appear.)
(Ko Young Bae, Jeon So Min, Yu Jae Seok)
- I'm looking forward to this. - I've been anticipating.
(The fans cheer for them.)
Should we tell them to stand up? Should we? All right.
(Young Bae, an experienced singer, signals them to stand up.)
(They listen to him.)
(So Min's parents also stand up.)
- Good luck! - Good luck!
They look laidback.
(She tells the audience on the 2nd floor to stand up.)
(Let's have fun together.)
(Everyone is standing.)
("Confess Already" by Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok)
(Confess already)
They look so cute.
(They look lovely and cute.)
(They begin their performance by urging the confession.)
(The band's performance complements the atmosphere.)
(They show fantastic harmony.)
Jae Seok looks like a band member.
Right?
(They show a harmonious ensemble, unlike their group name.)
(Just kiss me)
(The crowd gets louder thanks to her kiss.)
She's a natural.
She's naturally cute.
(Okay, I got it)
(She's already singing along.)
(Before this song is over)
(He sings a high note.)
He's good.
(Before this song is over)
Scream!
(It's dancing time.)
(He shows some elegant grooves.)
(I'm a femme fatale.)
(Jae Seok approaches the audience.)
(The singers in the green room can also feel the vibe.)
That looks nice.
- They're good at dancing. - I know.
(The fans are having their own dancing time too.)
(Before this song is over)
(Hush)
(She's excited.)
(The melody builds up,)
(and the vibe is similar to that during the Running Man festival.)
(Confess today)
(Or just kiss me)
(She sings some high notes.)
(Confetti, the highlight of festivals, shoots out.)
That's just my style.
That is.
(So Min gives a signal by singing a high note,)
(and the confetti falls down.)
Scream!
(It exceeds 120dB.)
(The confetti helps liven up the atmosphere even more.)
(To be honest,)
(I don't like it)
(The lyrics are 100-percent relatable,)
(and the band's performance complements it.)
(No one can resist confessing their feelings...)
(after hearing this song.)
(Before this song is over)
(Young Bae sings the high note clearly.)
(Confess already)
(They finally approach the part where they'll liven up...)
(the atmosphere even more.)
Jump!
(He urges them to jump.)
- Scream! - Jump!
(They reached 133dB which is the highest yet.)
They're all having a good time.
(It's as if they're the main event.)
They're all enjoying their performance.
Isn't it a great song?
(The fun energy doesn't seem to end.)
(SORAN ends the song...)
(with the most band-like noisy instrumental ending.)
(The icing on the cake!)
(Screaming)
(The song was based on So Min's real love story.)
Thank you.
(And the performance was like that of a romantic comedy musical.)
That was amazing.
How was it? Was that fun?
- Yes. - Yes!
Thank you. As we said earlier,
this song is called "Confess Already".
I'm so embarrassed.
Are you all right?
Well, the song is based on...
So Min's real-life experience of love.
It openly expresses the real aspects of love.
- Many women can relate to it. - Jae Seok...
(So Min must be lonely.)
There's something I'm curious about.
You separated yourself from us...
and even named us Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok.
- So what's with the flashy outfit? - Tell me about it.
(What's with the flashy outfit?)
- This was on purpose. - How could you?
He wanted to stand out.
What on earth are those flowers too?
It's called stoloniferous trigonotis.
Stoloniferous trigonotis?
- They're all over you. - I haven't heard of it,
- but that's what it is. - The mic...
There are too much.
To be honest, I didn't want to be intimidated.
You wanted to stand out.
I needed to stand out as well.
Go, Jae Seok!
(Make some noise!)
(Stand tall, Jae Seok!)
It's now time for the final collaborative performance.
(No one can sing quite like Gummy.)
The focus of this team...
- has to be Haha. - That's right.
He's performing with two exceptional singers.
(Gummy and the Mosquito are great vocalists.)
I don't know how Haha will hold his own.
Then let's hear from them right away.
We were Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We were Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok.)
(Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok are the best!)
(Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok step down after a successful show.)
Young Bae, the song is amazing.
- Thank you so much. - I love the song.
- The song is amazing. - Jeon SORAN and Yu Jae Seok.
Yes? Oh, our clue.
There's no doubt we received over 120dB.
- We must hear this. - The decibel you reached was...
(The crowd was the wildest.)
- You received 133dB. - Gosh, that's high.
(They reached the highest at 133dB which warrants them a clue.)
- That's really high. - Right.
Please choose 1 of the 3.
- So Min, go ahead. - No, you choose.
- Me? - Yes.
(Which clue did Jae Seok choose?)
"The spy has been on Running Man for nine years."
(The spy has been on Running Man for 9 years.)
- Then... - It's not me...
- or Se Chan. - It's one of the original cast.
This excludes So Min and Se Chan.
- They're excluded. - It's not me or Se Chan.
(So Min and Se Chan joined in 2017.)
Good luck and good job.
- You did great too. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
Nice.
The spy has been with the show for nine years.
(The audience hasn't calmed down from the previous song yet.)
(Ballad Queen Gummy appears.)
(My gosh, it's Gummy!)
(The boss enters to begin the last collaborative performance.)
Hello, I'm Gummy. It's nice to meet you all.
(She wins them all over by just appearing.)
I don't know what to do with your enthusiasm today.
I'm sure you know who I'll be performing with.
- Yes. - Yes.
What do you think? Are we compatible?
- Really? - Yes.
Once you listen to our song, you'll know...
why we were chosen to perform last.
Let's get to it. Thank you.
(They can't wait.)
(Gummy steps on the center stand.)
(The two men who will accompany her)
(Haha)
(Jong Kook)
(What kind of performance will they bring?)
- Amazing! - Go, go!
(Gummy)
(Kim Jong Kook)
(Haha)
(F-Killer, 9 Years of Running Man)
(The day of F-Killer's recording)
- That was good. - I have a question.
Gosh.
If you're only going to sigh, let me rap instead.
That's not it.
(Out of the blue)
(You misunderstood me.)
Right?
- I never sighed. - It's infuriating, you know.
Haha, please.
(Why is Haha upset?)
(When Cho Jung Seok was on set a few weeks back...)
(While driving,)
(I said that it'd be amazing to have her and Jong Kook sing...)
(while Haha raps.)
(But Gummy...)
(She shook her head saying that Haha wants to sing.)
(We finally know how Gummy really feels.)
(He doesn't know his place.)
(Haha's hurt.)
(I'm sorry to tell you this,)
(but the conversation ended at that moment.)
(He's been torn to pieces.)
(Haha was wounded since that day.)
I just said that you were singing too,
and he said, "Really?"
- Then what? - The conversation ended there.
Why though?
- I don't know. - So what now?
- It's fine. - I can still rap if you want.
It's all right.
(I can rap instead.)
(Old-school rapping)
(What on earth was that?)
What on earth was that?
Jung Seok did say something else.
- As in what? - "He's not a bad singer, right?"
- Stop it. - I'm not kidding.
- Gosh. - He really said so.
I might have a unique vibe, but I'm not that good of a vocalist.
No, you're good.
My nickname is Blowfly.
I was called that because of my name.
So how about Spider, Blowfly, and Mosquito?
We might shoot a commercial for a bug killer product.
Yes, the three of us.
What should we name our team?
How about F-Killer?
(It goes well with them since they're insects.)
Can we not use it because it's the name of a brand?
We'll go with F-Killer.
- F-Killer? I like it. - Nice.
The F can stand for fans.
(The interpretation is even better.)
- We'll kill the fans. - Nice.
Set them on fire.
(F-Killer means that they'll entertain the fans.)
I love it.
(F stands for fans!)
(They're ready to die.)
I love it.
I know it's a cliche, but I want you two to battle it out.
- Just go crazy. - You keep saying that.
It's definitely needed.
(After naming the team, Gummy starts recording.)
- Okay. - Why are you applauding?
Finally.
What is this for?
Gosh, please don't. Now I feel pressured.
I can't wait to hear you sing your section.
There's no way you can't sound cool singing this.
- Come on. - You know that, right?
(Even her warm-up is cool.)
(She's ready.)
Yes, thank you.
Gummy, let's do a practice round.
Sure.
(It's the only ballad among the collaborative performances.)
(She gets into the mood like a true professional.)
(It already sounds like a huge hit.)
(In awe)
(Hearts race.)
If I had a voice like that, I'd excitedly sing all day.
Me too.
I remember your sparkling gaze
I'll try that again.
(She's the best.)
This is amazing.
I listen to your voice
The first part is good in that powerful voice,
but the second part sounds better with the added emotion.
You should hit the first part quite strongly though.
That's what I think too.
- What... - Let me finish!
(Intercept)
- Let me finish! - Hold on.
When singing the next part though,
say "sparkle" twice, all right?
(He pushes it too far.)
"I remember your sparkling, sparkling gaze"
Let's hear it.
All right. I'll try again.
What if you extended the note like so?
It sounds a bit bland, so add on to it.
(Like this?)
Like this?
I'm listening to all his requests.
That's enough feedback from me then.
I'll stop.
I feel bad about ruining the mood.
(Just like Haha ordered)
(Another one of Haha's orders)
Can we record this version just for fun?
Just once so that I can personally keep it.
Really?
- Should I sing it that way? - I'm serious.
All right.
(The generous Gummy does it for him.)
(Seriously)
(Remember)
(Gummy did it for me!)
What did Mr. Producer think?
Okay, that was great. Let's listen to it and then move on.
(She hopes this healed his wound.)
(Next up is Haha who is a singer despite how he seems.)
(He's dead serious.)
(He gets in the mood and calmly sings the song.)
(Blowfly isn't that bad.)
- Haha, that was great. - Right.
Since we have an identity now,
you should call him Blowfly.
(You should call him Blowfly.)
(Oh...)
- Mr. Blowfly... - Yes?
(Mr. Blowfly)
Was that Mosquito speaking?
Yes.
Listen to your voice
- "Vo". - Try that part again.
- "Voice", that part. - Voice
(Like this?)
- Like this. - Voice
Bring your bottom lip to your top teeth.
"Voice".
- Voice - I listen to your voice
- There you go. - Okay.
(After some practice,)
(Haha manages the "V" sound.)
That sounds great.
(You're doing great.)
That sounds really nice.
He pulled off "voice".
(Embarrassed)
(Following Haha, Mosquito records his part.)
- He's incredible. - I can't believe him.
(It's finally rehearsal day.)
You can do this!
(Let's do this!)
Mosquito, Gummy, and Ant, you can do this!
(They're a team of insects.)
- Am I Ant? - Yes, you are.
Let's start.
Be confident, Haha!
Don't compete with Jong Kook and Gummy!
(With the other members cheering, they start rehearsing.)
(Jong Kook's soft singing...)
(is followed by Gummy.)
(Haha steals all the attention.)
(Haha focuses more on dancing.)
(The mood is ruined.)
(Laughing)
(What is he doing?)
(I'm here too.)
(Ant does have a lot of presence.)
(They're 2 singers and 1 dancer.)
Good job!
Be confident!
Good job, Mosquito, Gummy, and Ant!
Ant, we're on your side!
(This is Haha's first time singing a ballad.)
(He will sing with...)
(amazing singers Jong Kook and Gummy.)
(We can't wait.)
I've been looking forward to this.
(What will F-Killer's performance be like?)
("Raise Your Voice" by F-Killer Gummy, Jong Kook, Haha)
(Haha starts the song calmly.)
I shouldn't laugh.
I can't stop thinking of "The Gang".
(This reminds you of his 1st album, "The Gang".)
The Gang.
(Serious)
(This is cool.)
(The audience is surprised at Haha's new side.)
(Even when I'm tired)
(I have you in my life)
(Who held my hand)
(Don't you know)
(How precious you are to me)
(Mosquito adds emotion to the song with his beautiful voice.)
(The female audience falls in love with his voice.)
(Here comes the ultimate singer.)
I listen to your voice
(Shocked)
(Gummy's powerful voice leave the audience speechless.)
(It's a real treat to the ear.)
It's almost like the light only falls on Gummy.
I wish I could sing like her even once.
(Don't you know)
(How precious you are to me)
(You are the world to me)
(That never withers)
(Gummy's main melody and Haha's bass...)
(are beautifully harmonized.)
(I love this song.)
(When you think it's dark and there's a long way left)
(Raise your head Can you see it?)
(The night sky full of stars)
(The three of them sing in beautiful harmony.)
(Fantastic vocals)
(Everyone is in love.)
(This is F-Killer.)
(Haha sings the low notes.)
(Perfect harmony)
(The audience cheering reaches way over 120dB.)
(If we hold each other's hand)
(Raise your head, can you see it?)
(Countless stars singing together)
(Explosive high notes)
(The fan killers sing the high notes passionately.)
(The three singers sing in harmony.)
(Jong Kook's soft voice)
(Gummy's powerful voice)
(Haha's attractive low voice)
(F-Killer is a fantastic combination.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E469 Running Man
"Running Man's Fan-Meet 2019"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(That performance was incredible.)
(Their passion even reaches the green room.)
- That was crazy. - This is the real hit song.
(The stage is still full of emotions.)
- F-Killer. - Thank You.
(Your performance was the best, F-Killer.)
Come here, Haha.
- He really set the mood. - Why are you so shy?
I tried so hard not to look the audience in the eye.
What did you think of Haha's singing?
- What did you think? - Thank you.
- See? - It was an honor.
It was an honor to sing with these two.
Not a single person laughed.
- He was worried. - I saw a few people laugh.
(I saw a few.)
- Where? - A few over there.
I heard someone laugh over there too.
- It's okay. - They cheered for us so much.
- Even from the beginning. - I almost cried.
- It helped a lot. - Thank you.
I was touched.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(You were all amazing.)
- Thank you. - Actually,
- Gummy is injured. - I'm fine.
- I'm really fine. - She was in a lot of pain.
- I'm fine. - Please give her a big hand.
- Thank you. - It must have been hard.
(Despite her injury, she did her best like a pro.)
She was wearing a cast,
but she put on tape...
- and shoes for the performance. - Seriously...
If it weren't for my injury, I would have danced for you.
- I'm sorry. - That's a shame.
I'm so touched. Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Now all our collaborative performances are over.
- That's right. - We're...
feeling more and more pressured.
We'll do a group dance...
(The next performance is the much-anticipated group dance.)
And we'll sing Running Man's theme song.
Those are our two last performances.
- Should we go and get ready? - Sure.
- We'll go in now. - We'll go in.
- We'll go in. - Thank you. See you in a bit!
- Thank you! - See you. Thank you!
(You can see the performances shortly.)
(Surprised)
Are we getting a hint?
Are we?
- Give us a hint. - Are you giving us a hint?
The audience cheering for you reached 124dB,
so you're entitled to a hint.
Oh, my. I'm relieved.
- Choose 1 hint out of these 3. - This one?
- You choose. - Can't we get one for each person?
What is this?
"The spy was lucky today."
The spy was lucky today?
Who was lucky today?
(What do these hints mean?)
- All right. - All right.
(The hints are confusing. Who is the spy?)
Who do you think is the spy?
The spy buys coffee once in a while.
"Once in a while"?
Doesn't Bo Pil buy coffee once in a while?
What are you talking about?
He's our assistant director.
He might be the spy.
It doesn't have to be among the members.
Jae Seok doesn't drink coffee at all.
He's excluded.
It must be either Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, or Haha.
(Seok Jin suspects Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Haha.)
Why am I excluded?
Because of the coffee hint.
Why?
You never buy coffee.
I buy coffee often.
- Really? - Yes.
I don't know who it is,
but it must have been hard for the spy today.
Preparing for the performances and carrying out missions...
I'm sure the spy has missions. It must have been hard.
- I acknowledge the spy's hard work. - Me too.
- It must have been stressful. - He's filming us again.
(He's filming us again.)
What's with you?
(Am I suspicious?)
Does this make sense?
Does this even make sense?
What is this?
Why are you doing this?
(You crave attention at 54.)
Is this your mission?
Are you the spy?
He must be the spy.
- It's Seok Jin. - But Seok Jin...
He never buys coffee.
That's the confusing part.
- "Once in a while". - Let's just practice.
- Ready... - Hold on.
- Ready, start. - Ready, start.
(Seok Jin is still sitting in his chair.)
If you're not dancing with us, get out of our way.
(He only moves his upper body.)
Get out of our way.
Move over there.
I'm tired.
Where did you even get this chair?
It's a nice chair.
I am exhausted. You guys are practicing hard.
(Who could be the real spy?)
(Meanwhile, the surprise guest appears on stage.)
(The cheerful music livens up the atmosphere!)
It's Jin Young!
(It's Running Man's family,)
(Hong Jin Young!)
Hello, I am Hong Jin Young. It's nice to meet you.
(She suits everyone's tastes.)
("Love Battery" by Hong Jin Young)
(I am excited.)
(While Jin Young livens up the atmosphere on the stage,)
(the members do a final check backstage.)
I am so nervous.
Seriously.
- Are you okay? - I am okay.
Are you okay? Will you be able to do the lift?
- Will you? - Tonight...
- My goodness. - Seriously, that dance move...
with Jong Kook...
Jong Kook, can you lift me up?
(Jong Kook calms So Min down.)
(You are the best)
Thank you.
(The next performance is the group dance!)
- Should we remove the microphones? - Yes.
We need to remove the microphones.
We are removing the microphones.
- Remove the microphones. - My goodness.
(Both the members who are preparing for the performance...)
(and Lia who taught the dance are nervous.)
You will do a good job. You can do this.
(Will they be able to pull off the group dance?)
(Project Group Dance)
What is this?
(When the choreography of the group dance got revealed,)
(the level of difficulty shocked everyone.)
(The dancers in white T-shirts have the Running Man members' parts.)
That's the dance?
- Can they do that dance? - Seriously.
(Can the Running Man members do that dance?)
- I don't think we can do that. - Seriously.
Okay. Shall we begin?
Se Chan, take this path.
Take this path all the way...
to here.
- Come in front of So Min. - Okay.
Then boom! Jump and throw your hands...
in the air.
(After jumping, confidently walk to the front.)
I will make this as cool as possible.
All right. Let's go.
(He walks to the front in a cool way as he learned.)
(Kwang Soo suddenly attacks his neck.)
(What is that?)
- What? - It wasn't intentional.
- I was just doing my move. - You blocked me.
I do this when you pass by.
Am I supposed to get slapped as I walk by?
- Am I supposed to get slapped? - You should dodge.
If the members hold real knives, you will dodge well.
(Real knives?)
Real knives?
That would be funny.
(He will need to risk his life for a formation change.)
I will bring a knife next time.
That will get him to dodge you.
Make a line.
Haha is the very front.
Se Chan,
- you will stick out to the left. - To the left?
You will do this to Haha's chest.
1, 2, stop, stop. Okay.
A bit up.
- Should I raise my arm? - Raise it up to here.
One and... Okay.
(Jong Kook bursts out laughing.)
- That was nice. - Good work, everyone.
For this move,
only our arms should stick out. How about the head?
(Kwang Soo's head sticks out.)
Kwang Soo.
I keep meeting your eyes.
His head is sticking out.
You are uselessly tall.
I suddenly realized that he is really tall.
Kwang Soo's head and our arms...
look like a centipede.
Kwang Soo's head and our arms look like a centipede.
- You are right. - Right?
You are right.
We are an insect.
Kwang Soo, get down.
(Kwang Soo, get down.)
(He gets down.)
5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3...
(They resume the practice.)
(Floundering)
6, 7...
Seok Jin.
- Get it together, Seok Jin. - Please.
Act your age.
- "Act your age." - I made one mistake so far!
Okay. Let's go. We can do this. We aren't fools.
Shut up during practice.
(He is strict to Seok Jin.)
Shut up and concentrate.
- I am a fan. - Seriously.
Left foot and right hand.
Pull and pull.
Then do this twice.
(This move involves powerful hip thrusts.)
I know this dance move!
If you bend your knees and move your hip,
you will get a hip-hop vibe.
- My back hurts. - It's hip-hop.
Is that hip-hop?
(This is hip-hop!)
- Is that hip-hop? - That looks dirty.
Don't do that.
Bend your knees.
Just do this.
My goodness.
He is the worst.
Stop it!
Kwang Soo, smile.
(I need to smile.)
Smile. Smile.
(Smiling)
(Kwang Soo's smile spreads happiness.)
(It looks fine when I smile, right?)
I am about to go crazy.
(A new type of dancer...)
- That was incredible. - My goodness.
(works hard today.)
I am not a fool.
- Okay. - It's the specialty time.
You will start from here.
We showed waves in the video,
but I am sure the audience wants to see specialties.
So we should do...
- freestyle dance. - Show what you want to show.
You should just keep this in mind.
If the last member finishes with the chin,
(They need to start with the last member's last move.)
- continue with the chin. - The chin.
(They begin to practice right away!)
My goodness.
There you go.
(They suddenly deliver the chin move.)
(They have good teamwork with things like this.)
This is fun.
(So Min tosses it to Lia!)
Lia went along with it. Lia went along with it.
(She is a true teacher.)
Lia went along with it.
If someone throws it with their shoulders,
the next person receives it with their shoulders.
Where are you going to toss it from?
I am going to do this for a long time.
Come on and toss it already.
I am going to do this for a minute.
- All right. - A minute.
What are you going to use?
Hurry up.
- Seriously. - What are you going to use?
He took it back.
- Hurry up. - Did he toss it?
Spit it in the air.
He spat it out. Haha ate it.
(Haha receives it with his mouth and shoot it out his bottom!)
(Se Chan receives it with his bottom and...)
- Se Chan! - What was that?
- It's hip-hop! - Hey!
(Complaints flood in due to his dirty hip thrust.)
What was that?
- It's hip-hop! Isn't that hip-hop? - How is that hip-hop?
- You said it's hip-hop. - How is that hip-hop?
You said it's hip-hop.
I am sorry. I apologize. I apologize.
I am sorry.
Decide which part of your body you will use to toss.
The one who tosses should decide.
I will receive it with my chest.
- Then go down. - Then I will toss it with my foot.
- Se Chan. - And out my face.
There you go. Toss with your face.
- I will receive with my face. - Receive it with your face.
Then I will toss with my shoulders.
- Shoulders. - Here I go.
It will come up and...
Why did you spit?
(Spitting)
(Are you really going to spit?)
- Why did you spit? - I mean...
- Did you feel like spitting? - My goodness.
- I just felt like it. - Come on.
Okay.
- Receive it like this. - Receive and toss with your hips.
(Seok Jin receives with his hips.)
1, 2, 3, 4.
- Will you kick? - I have an idea.
Collapse as if he really kicked you.
Collapse.
That's easy.
(Kwang Soo pulls it off.)
He is good. He is good.
(I told you I can dance.)
- He is good. - He is good.
(Kwang Soo receives it with his legs...)
(and tosses it with his chest.)
I will do this.
- Now, - Then...
- I will receive it. - Show us what you learned.
Spin and...
(So Min finishes up with the Wheel Dance.)
Yes. That's good.
It's the Driving Dance.
(The practice for their specialties end.)
5, 6, 7, 8.
Come on up.
- 5, 6, 7, 8. - 5, 6, 7, 8.
- Put her down. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
Gather around.
All of you worked hard.
Please show us a great performance.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(How will be the group dance the members spent 3 months on?)
(When the members appear on stage,)
(the audience cheers loudly.)
(The Running Man members are here!)
(They take their positions on the dark stage.)
My heart is about to burst.
(Both Lia outside the stage...)
(and the members on the stage are extremely nervous.)
(They feel like their hearts are about to burst.)
(It's the highlight everyone has been waiting for.)
I am so excited.
I think it will be cool.
(Will they make it through without a mistake?)
("Boom and Just Blow" by Running Man members)
(The strong intro...)
(makes everyone's jaw drop.)
(Se Chan manages to get through without getting hit by Kwang Soo!)
(They have perfect teamwork.)
(It's Seok Jin's time!)
(The audience watches in awe.)
(This is incredible.)
My goodness.
(When the music changes, the atmosphere becomes cheerful!)
(Jong Kook and So Min will show a difficult move.)
(It's a clean success.)
They did an amazing job.
(The teamwork they built up in the past 9 years...)
(explode on stage!)
(It's Ji Hyo and So Min's time.)
(Everyone cheers loudly!)
They are good.
(They show a sexy side they haven't shown on the show.)
(Here comes Kwang Soo!)
(They quickly make a line.)
(They pull off the line formation.)
They are incredible.
(The jump livens up the atmosphere.)
(It's time for their specialties!)
(So Min wraps up with the Wheel Dance.)
(Everyone's cheer explodes.)
(It's a cool ending for the 1st fan-meet in 9 years.)
(Even after the group dance, the members keep their positions.)
(The audience continues to cheer at their exceptional performance.)
(It was really cool!)
Bravo.
Ji Hyo can dance.
Ji Hyo's facial expressions were professional.
I would be in tears after a performance like that.
Wasn't it touching?
- I know. It makes you emotional. - Yes.
(Lia knows how hard the members practiced.)
(She feels thankful for the good performance...)
(and sorry for the members' hard work.)
(After a while,)
(the members on the stage smile.)
(Everyone wondered if they would be able to do it,)
(but the 8 members of Running Man showed an exceptional performance.)
(They encourage and support each other.)
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
At the end,
we shouldn't have done that.
In an emotional state, we did something unsightly.
- We shouldn't have made a circle. - Seriously.
I told everyone...
- not to make a circle. - "Don't make a circle!"
- "Don't make a circle!" - Who initiated it?
Who initiated it?
- Who initiated it? - Who initiated the circle?
I am sorry.
In any case, for three months,
Lia, Jin Lee,
- You Jin, - You Jin.
and many other dancers...
helped us create this performance.
To be frank,
I am someone who is emotionally dry.
When the group dance ended and everyone clapped,
I suddenly felt emotional.
I felt that emotion thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
I haven't felt so emotional in 20 years.
It has been a while.
I hope you mean it.
It's real.
(He means it.)
My goodness. I...
What are you saying?
Are you calling me a liar?
Don't be angry.
- I am not angry. - Don't be angry.
- Seok Jin is rarely angry. - That's right.
- I am grateful for him. - He doesn't know anger.
Ji Hyo.
All right.
(All right.)
(Feeling grateful for the fans who supported the show,)
Thank you.
(Ji Hyo becomes speechless at the support of the fans.)
We promised not to cry.
This is exactly what Seok Jin wanted to do.
Ji Hyo did it perfectly.
It was so natural.
- That's right. - Seok Jin finished too quickly.
Seok Jin has artificial tears in his pocket,
- but he missed his chance. - It was really nice.
I...
(Ji Hyo tries to calm down,)
(but she can't.)
You did a good job.
You did a good job!
Thank you.
(Thank you.)
(Ji Hyo's short comment contains a lot of meanings.)
Ji Hyo became emotional.
Kwang Soo, please continue.
Kwang Soo isn't a fool!
What?
(Kwang Soo isn't a fool!)
- What? - Kwang Soo.
- Don't say that! - "Kwang Soo isn't a fool!"
- "Kwang Soo isn't a fool!" - How do you know that?
- "Kwang Soo isn't a fool!" - Why would you say...
something so obvious?
They know because they are big fans...
- of the show. - That makes sense.
- He said something so obvious. - They are viewers...
- of Running Man. - That's right.
- You know, - They are part of the family.
I would again like to say this as his close friend.
Kwang Soo is not a fool.
Why would you say something so obvious?
(Kwang Soo gets annoyed.)
- Of course, I am not a fool. - Please spread...
this information.
Why would they spread this information?
(We will be sure to spread this information.)
For 3 or 4 months,
we prepared hard...
whether the cameras were running or not.
A period of three months may seem short,
but it feels like a year went into this fan-meet...
What?
(What?)
(Jae Seok motions him to stop.)
Do you want me to hurry up?
- We are running out of time. - I just started.
They need to take public transportation.
- What? - Everyone...
They need to take public transportation. I am sorry.
- Public transportation... - Is it okay?
- Yes! - Yes!
(Kwang Soo is a fool, Jae Seok is a fool for his fans.)
As happy as we were,
we hope you would keep this memory for many years to come.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(You were incredible.)
As always, thank you. We won't forget this moment.
We hope you will stay healthy and happy.
The last song is the theme song that came to be after nine years.
Jung Joon Il composed "I Like You".
It's a stylish song.
- That's right. - It's quite nice.
That's right.
(The theme song was composed for the fan-meet.)
- Who will compose the theme song? - The theme song?
(Then a talented singer-songwriter appeared for the special task.)
(Composer Jung Joon Il)
(Members write lyrics for the theme song.)
(They do their best and finish recording.)
(Members' first theme song made with 9 years of Running Man)
(How did it turn out?)
("I Like You" by Running Man)
(Song Van)
(It's okay, stay strong)
(I will run with you)
(That's how we became one)
(Now I will be on your side)
(I can't understand everything)
(But I will lean on you little closer)
(Because I like you)
(Difficult today and tomorrow)
(It's okay, stay strong)
(I will run with you)
(That's why we shone much brighter)
(Remember us)
(His standing wasn't planned.)
(There he goes again.)
(Remember my high note.)
(Someday)
(On the day we stop this walk)
(Thank you so much, I was you)
(The day when we cried until our eyes hurt)
(The day we could laugh even though it rained)
(They never expressed their true feelings over the last 9 years.)
(All the days are soft and dry)
(I like you)
(The first song they sing to each other after 9 years)
- We love you. - Thank you.
- I like you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Kwang Soo, pay the comedian fee.
What?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- We won't forget it. - Goodness.
Thank you very much.
(They encourage and cheer each other with their looks.)
I'm so grateful that I don't know what to say.
- Seriously. - Song Ji Hyo is my type.
(A male audience shouts, "Song Ji Hyo is my type.")
(His confession stops her tears.)
- Song Ji Hyo is my type. - Thank you.
Please respond to "Song Ji Hyo is my type."
You're my type too.
(His wish is granted.)
Thank you.
This is our ninth anniversary.
- 10th anniversary. - 10th or 20th anniversary.
Until the day when...
Seok Jin turns 100 years old.
Until that day.
I don't know that it'll be possible for me.
I don't know if it's possible.
- On the day Seok Jin turns 80, - 80.
we'll come back here.
That's possible because it'll be soon.
It's possible.
It's coming up soon.
We'd like to thank you again.
I thought of the spy at this moment.
I forgot to say it.
- Spy? - I forgot.
There's a spy.
I thought of the spy all of a sudden.
- That's right. - Who's the spy?
I had forgotten about it.
I thought of it all of a sudden.
- I think I know who it is. - Why?
As I was thinking...
I'd really like to know.
Do you know who the spy is?
(The audience knows who the spy is.)
That's amazing.
- They know. - Lee Kwang Soo.
(Is Kwang Soo the spy?)
Is it Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo? - Kwang Soo?
Is it?
What about Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo? - Me?
Is it Kwang Soo?
- Hey, you. - You're starting again.
- It's not me. - Is it not?
- I swear that I'm not. - Among the members,
we suspect that it's Seok Jin.
- I got a very definite hint. - For now,
here's the hint that we got.
- Here's the hint. - Friday instead of Monday.
He prefers Friday to Monday.
"The spy buys coffee once in a while."
"The spy has been on Running Man for nine years."
- The spy prefers cafes. - The spy prefers cafes.
- The spy doesn't like restaurants. - Right.
"The spy can be with balls,"
- "but not dice." - "but not dice."
Also, the spy is lucky today.
- Right. - Who got the hint about Monday?
- I think I know. - The spy likes Mondays.
Friday, Seok Jin.
- What? - The Chinese character.
(If the Chinese character for Friday is the same as "metal",)
Kim Jong Kook?
- Jong Kook? - That's what I think.
- Restaurants. - He runs a restaurant like me.
(Jong Kook who runs a restaurant seems relaxed for some reason.)
Wow.
(Was it you, Jong Kook?)
- What about Kwang Soo? - What?
(Jong Kook stands out all of a sudden.)
What about Kwang Soo?
(The spy is Kwang Soo.)
Is it Kwang Soo?
It's not me.
- It's not me. - Is Kwang Soo the spy?
(Flustered)
- Is Kwang Soo the spy? - It's not me.
What about the hints?
- Let's end this. - Okay.
We'll wrap this up quickly.
For now,
- the spy likes Fridays. - I put mine in.
(A person who has no idea and another who got the answer)
I put mine in.
- The spy likes cafes. - I put mine in too.
- I'll put it in too. - I'll follow my feelings.
Also...
- I wrote someone's name. - I put mine in.
I don't know. Let's just do it.
Jae Seok,
Kwang Soo, and Se Chan wrote...
- Seok Jin as the spy. - Seok Jin? Let's get together.
- Come on. - Here's why.
Come on. He was very strange today.
(Is it Seok Jin who cleared the spy mission?)
Seok Jin is on a radio show.
- He likes Fridays very much. - Right.
Seok Jin acted strangely in the waiting room.
- He took photos of us. - He took photos of us.
- He was so passionate today. - If he's not the spy,
I'm sorry, but I promised to hit him after the show.
(I'm sorry but I promised to hit him after the show.)
Really, Seok Jin?
- What's next? - Seok Jin, So Min, and Haha...
- picked Jong Kook. - Right?
It's because of this hint.
"The spy suits Friday, but doesn't suit Sunday."
He also likes cafes.
- He likes cafes. - Cafes.
- I see. - Right.
Only Ji Hyo picked...
Haha.
- I knew it. - Why did you pick him?
Seok Jin doesn't like coffee.
Jong Kook doesn't suit Friday either.
I narrowed it down to Haha.
Jong Kook...
- Whom did you pick? - arrested...
the spy.
(Jong Kook arrested the spy.)
(Only Jong Kook successfully arrested the spy.)
Jong Kook? Whom did you write?
(Did he arrest the spy? Who could it be?)
(Only Jong Kook is exempted from the whip cream penalty.)
Who is it?
- Is it you? - It's not us.
Right?
(Praise Jong Kook, Jong Kook.)
(As always, Jong Kook is the winner.)
Who is it?
- Is it Ji Hyo? - Really?
- Who is it? - Is it Ji Hyo?
In the count of three,
the audience will announce today's spy.
Who's today's spy? One.
(The spy performed most passionately today.)
Two.
(Who is the spy?)
Three.
(We're the spy.)
I knew it.
(The spy is the fans.)
- He wrote it. - I wrote it.
It's the fans.
Is that right?
I almost wrote it.
(The fans and the staff had a secret meeting beforehand.)
Hello, everyone.
As today is Running Man's fan-meet,
today's spy is...
(You're the spy.)
(Are we the spy?)
As you're the spy,
you have to clear a hidden mission.
(The spy's mission is to be the most passionate today.)
Your mission is to enjoy yourselves most passionately today.
Was it you, the fans?
I almost wrote it.
(I thought about it for a while.)
Goodness.
- That's right. - It's all of you!
I thought that couldn't be true.
- It's true. - I was like "No way".
When I heard the hint that the spy is lucky today,
I wondered who was lucky today. I was watching them.
They were picked to be here.
- What? - That's true.
They're lucky.
The spy likes balls.
Was it ballpoint pen?
That's right.
- Isn't it ballpoint pen? - What ballpoint pen?
"The spy can be with balls, but not dice."
- Ballpoint pen. - Ballpoint pen.
- Whose ballpoint pen? - What's a ballpoint pen?
The coffee hint meant the coffee truck the fans sometimes send.
- They do. - Cafe.
- What's that? - Does it mean fan cafe?
- Yes, it's fan cafe. - Ballpoint pen?
- Fan cafe? - Fan cafe.
- Also, - Right, it's fan cafe.
- Friday. - Friday, frying pan.
What did you say?
(Is it frying pan because it's Friday?)
- How would we know that? - Isn't that harsh?
- Boo. - That's harsh.
Frying pan was too harsh.
I thought it was because people like Fridays in general.
Do we finish after getting penalized?
Whip cream penalty is prepared for only four members.
Do we have a chance?
We're picking.
There are 4 blue and 3 red in the spoon container.
Those who pick 4 blue spoons will be penalized with whip cream.
Okay.
- Let's start with Haha. - Don't look right now.
Don't look right now.
Here you go, Kwang Soo.
The unlucky people have gathered again.
Today...
- Including me... - Seriously.
Today, I think...
(Who will be the three going home dry?)
I have a strange feeling it won't be me.
I bet mine is red.
Let's look one by one.
Start with Haha. 1, 2, 3.
It's blue.
(Haha is chosen to be penalized.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(They cheer for the first person to sacrifice.)
- Is it blue? He'll be penalized. - Ji Hyo.
- Is blue being penalized? - Yes.
1, 2, 3.
- Let it be blue. - I'm unlucky with this.
- That's right. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo is chosen to be penalized.)
(Ji Hyo joins to be penalized.)
- There are two left. - What?
Did Ji Hyo get blue?
- Ji Hyo picked blue? - Seok Jin.
Seok Jin, it'll be amazing...
- if the four in a row are selected. - I hope it'll be consecutive.
Seok Jin, 1, 2, 3.
(Seok Jin survives.)
(Seok Jin gets lucky without any consideration.)
- It's not fun, is it? - No.
- There are two left. - Jae Seok.
(These two are next.)
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Lee Kwang Soo.
- There are two left. - Lee Kwang Soo.
- Yu Jae Seok. - There are two spoons left.
- Kwang Soo. - Let's do it together.
- We'll reveal it together. - It's over if both of you are blue.
It's over if both of us have blue.
- 1, 2, 3. - Please.
(Only Kwang Soo is selected to be penalized.)
Three.
(He enters the class live.)
I knew it, Kwang Soo.
It was expected.
(It was expected.)
(Fans' big picture becomes true.)
Look at that.
Se Chan and So Min are next.
- One of them will survive. - Please.
- Please. - Do we do it together?
One of you will survive.
- 1, 2. - So Min.
- So Min, So Min. - So Min, So Min.
- 1, 2, 3. - Okay.
(So Min is selected for the penalty.)
Okay.
(So Min couldn't get away from the fans' curse.)
Scream!
(Things turn out as the fans wish.)
I got dizzy all of a sudden.
Seriously.
Before the penalty,
I'll introduce the artists who were with us today.
(Artists who collaborated today come on stage.)
Please come out on stage.
You worked very hard.
- Apink. - Even though...
everyone was busy,
they took the time and performed with us today.
Please give a round of applause...
to everyone who was with us including Gummy.
Thank you.
All right.
(The whip cream penalty is ready.)
Let's count to three together.
Are you ready?
- Yes. - Yes.
- 1. - 1.
- 2. - 2.
- 3! - 3!
Three!
(It's a successful and refreshing finale.)
(That's amazing.)
(That's worth a photo.)
(Watching members get penalized makes them the happiest.)
(It's time to appreciate the members covered in white.)
So Min got hit directly.
So Min got hit directly today.
- They got hit directly. - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo got hit directly today.
Everyone, you were with us today.
We'll say goodbye now.
Thank you, everyone.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(Although they were awkward and may have lacked in areas,)
(the fan-meet was possible with their gratitude for the fans.)
(Thank you for being with us today. We'll be back again.)
Thank you for leading Running Man for nine years.
I'll continue to enjoy it.
I hope that it continues longer...
so that we can come back with my second child.
Please continue for a long time.
I'm grateful because they prepared a lot.
(We thank everyone who was with us for the fan-meet.)
(Their vacation starts after the fan-meet.)
(They go to a vacation spot together.)
(What awaits them is the smell of a field.)
(They're flustered by a new type of vacation.)
(Yu Jae Seok, what's the point of playing?)
(When will we eat?)
(Eat as much as you want.)
(Eat as much as you can catch.)
(Even if they can't catch anything,)
(it's too early to be disappointed.)
(A secret guest comes to comfort them.)
(They're speechless due to their eventful vacation.)
(What's the vacation under the veil?)
(What Happened at Their Holiday Spot)