(Last week)
(It was a special episode...)
(to celebrate So Min's birthday, April 7.)
(Thrilling Real Variety)
(The first date was with Kim Ji Suk, her co-star in her drama.)
(She couldn't stop smiling the whole time.)
- I'm pretty? - Yes.
(However,)
(the members are going to pay for So Min's date?)
(They must eliminate So Min to avoid paying and facing the penalty.)
(So Min who's looking for love versus jealous members)
(The first mission to locate So Min was the escape room.)
(He figured out the hint. "It's 'Watch out'.")
(They checked the clocks.)
(Hints from the clocks: "Even I will disappear"...)
(and "If standing up straight")
(What do these two sentences mean?)
That means that you're standing up without moving.
- Standing still. - Standing still isn't the same.
Standing still is...
- the origin of standing upright. - I figured it out.
(Did Kwang Soo figure something out?)
- On So Min's social media... - That's right.
- "Standing up straight". - That's right. She wrote that.
- Those sentimental lines? - That's right.
(Her writing on her social media made everyone cringe last winter.)
"Even if I walk all day long to reach you..."
"Standing up straight will even make me disappear."
(These two sentences were key lines of her pretentious poem.)
(In other words, the hints are pointing to So Min's poem.)
- That's right. - That must be it.
Yes, I think I've seen that in her poem.
My gosh, So Min.
Hey, this is what I think.
- I think batteries will be inside. - That's right.
- Then... - We can insert batteries somewhere.
(The password consists of 10 letters of the alphabet.)
"Standing up straight will even make me disappear."
My gosh, how are we supposed to open this up with that?
She posted the poem on the day of the first snow.
(What do these hints mean?)
(Searching for clues to open the safe)
What is this? There's nothing here.
I'm getting so frustrated. I hate escape rooms.
What does that mean?
Hey, they're almost done with their meal.
(He's startled.)
- Let me see. - We must hurry.
We can still catch them.
This is terrible.
(Will they be able to put a stop on her date?)
I'm so full.
I can't eat a lot.
You usually eat a lot.
Yes, I usually eat a lot.
(She just said that she was full.)
(But she's gulping down a glass of water.)
(Actually, this wasn't an ordinary date either.)
(So Min received a hidden mission before Ji Suk arrived.)
(She must complete everything on the list to move on.)
(Hearing "pretty", "I'm excited", "jealous")
(and getting him to cut her steak and to wipe her mouth)
(It's impossible unless I have the sweetest guy.)
(When she was dejected about the hidden mission,)
(the sweetest guy showed up.)
(You've gotten prettier.)
(Before she tried anything, Ji Suk cleared most of the list.)
(She was able to complete 3 out of 5 on the list.)
(Having two tasks left for the mission, the steak is served.)
It made me wonder if you ever said those before.
I thought you were attractive and cute.
- When the three of us had sashimi? - Yes.
(It's because she needs the steak for the hidden mission.)
I'm sorry, but could I get one more knife?
(Asking a question all of a sudden)
(She gets started on "getting him to cut her steak".)
Me too. Wait, no. I have a knife.
(You have a knife, but I don't.)
They gave me one.
(Staring)
(Wait, So Min doesn't have a knife.)
- It's over there. - I see.
- Because you used it before? - Yes.
(This sweet guy is very observant too.)
(She starts her plan and waits for a new knife with a lame excuse.)
(She's silently pressuring him.)
(This sweet guy is slow to figure out her cue.)
(I don't have a knife.)
- Do you want me to cut yours? - What?
(Her plan works! He finally got it.)
- Thank you. - I'll cut yours with the new knife.
Thank you.
(Her silent protest gets her desired answer.)
- Thank you, Ji Suk. - Sure.
Thank you. No one has ever done that.
- No way. - Seriously. No one did that for me.
No one has ever cut steak for me in my life.
(She finishes the fourth task too.)
I'm serious.
- So Min, I cut the steak, - Okay.
- but it looks ugly. Is that okay? - That's okay. Thank you.
- Thank you. I can eat them. - Okay.
You will... You will...
You'll feed me from there?
(She's flustered.)
(This sweet guy does a bonus task.)
- Do you want the garlic? - Yes, I like it.
I love garlic.
Great. All right.
(The plane is taking off now.)
Come on, what was that?
(His sweet act is more than she can take in a day.)
Come on.
My gosh. Gosh.
Thank you.
Right there.
(Thanks to this sweet guy, she only has one task left.)
This is so hard. Anyway...
This is good.
This is really good.
Anyway, we should talk about jealousy and heart fluttering.
- That came out of nowhere. - Yes.
Okay.
I don't remember what I said.
Sang Yeob kept telling me...
Why are you bringing him up again?
Why did you bring him up?
I asked that only because I wanted to hear something.
Like...
how he felt about that.
(I'm curious about that.)
- What? - How I felt?
Gosh, you know.
He said he felt something.
He felt something of us.
(He felt something of us?)
- He felt we were affectionate? - No.
(That's not it.)
(While So Min is trying hard to get him to say the word, "jealous"...)
I think we have to hurry.
So Min!
My gosh, I bet that's expensive. This is terrible.
Hey, they had steaks.
It's a poem. Is it "poet"?
- What? - Poem?
P-O-E-T.
- There's no T here. - It's the poem.
- What does "poet" mean? - This is the poem.
Don't you know it means, "poem"?
I see. "Poet" as "poem".
I can't participate in this discussion at all.
This is driving me crazy.
I'm not sure about that.
- I can't do it. You hurt my ego. - It could be simple.
- Could it be, L-O-V-E? - Hey.
L-O-V-E?
(Since the poem was about love, is the password "love"?)
(They can make the word, "love". Will it open with "love"?)
"Love" is not it.
My gosh. Seriously.
(What is the password then?)
Where did So Min go?
(Where did she go when she wrote that?)
- Japan. - Where in Japan?
She went to Sapporo.
(She went to Sapporo when she wrote the poem.)
Would "Sapporo" work for that?
(Since she wrote it in Sapporo, is the password Sapporo?)
- The password might be simple. - Try "Sapporo".
O-O-R-O.
No, O.
(Will it work this time?)
(It's the sound of the safe opening.)
("Sapporo" was the password.)
- It was really "Sapporo"? - You're a genius!
(Haha achieves a splendid feat.)
It was Sapporo where she wrote the poem.
- My gosh. - Something is in there.
What's that?
- It's a scroll. - What's that?
We'll use these?
I guess we have to use the lantern to read the scroll.
We can read with the lantern.
- "Hope shines..." - Right there.
"in the darkest moment."
(Hope shines in the darkest moment.)
(Wait, what does this mean?)
(And a mysterious lantern is next to the scroll.)
- My gosh, this... - We have to use that to read it.
- We have to use that. - The drawing.
- Gosh. - It's working.
No, no.
- Jae Seok. It's not that. - Why don't you shine it here?
- We have to turn off the lights. - We must turn off the lights.
- Turn off the lights. - "Power off"!
(There's a power-off button underneath the safe?)
- This is it. - Yes, we must turn off the lights!
(About 30 minutes ago)
(Even Kwang Soo with long arms...)
(wasn't able to reach the power-off button.)
(It seems they must use the toy car and the remote to press the button.)
(Hold on. This...)
(However, they couldn't drive it as they were out of batteries.)
(But there was a lantern in the safe?)
- We'll use the batteries here. - I see. We'll use these?
We'll take them out and put them in the car.
- That's right. This is it. - Let's do that first.
(They insert the batteries into the toy car.)
- My gosh. - We'll use that.
They came up with quite an exquisite set-up.
- Whom are you talking to? - What?
You're supposed to talk to us.
- You should talk to us. - He did that from time to time.
- The producer is over there. - Unbelievable.
- The producer is over there. - My gosh. Seriously.
Why are you flattering him throughout the game?
- Flatter? - I was just looking at him.
- People won't know, but he's there. - Put it in front of the safe.
- Try it. - It's ready now.
(Meanwhile, they finish putting in the batteries.)
There you go. I knew it.
- Here it goes. - It worked.
(Crashing)
- A little... - The lights are off.
(The lights are off when the button is pressed.)
Where is the lantern? Where is it?
- The car has the batteries. - We must do it later.
- The lights are off. - We need the batteries.
- Back up the car. - Did you take them out?
Take out the batteries.
- Take out the batteries. - I know how to take them out.
I know this because I've been to a lot of escape rooms.
The clues will be either on the paintings...
or the walls.
(Hope shines in the darkest moment.)
Nightglow is the only thing that lights up in the dark.
Yes, that's the only thing.
Then something must glow in the dark here.
- Something glows in the dark? - Look around.
(Something glows in the dark?)
This is it.
This glows in the dark.
(This is it. This glows in the dark.)
(Something is on the wall Ji Hyo was looking at?)
- That's it. - What is it?
- This glows in the dark. - This is it.
- Is it glowing? - Yes, it glows.
- The lights are back on. - What's going on?
(The lights are turned on when they touch the frame.)
This must be it.
When will we find So Min at this rate?
(Is there a secret in this painting?)
This... Is this the only clue?
Something is written there.
- This is it. It's English! - That's it.
(What? What's on the painting?)
("NIMOS" is written on the bottom of the painting.)
"NIMOS".
(This brings them to think...)
(Five English letters are needed for the lock on the entrance door.)
(Then is "NIMOS" their last password?)
They're in this building.
- They finished eating. - It's M-O-S.
(Awesome! We found the password, NIMOS.)
I put it in, but it won't open.
(But the lock won't open with the password.)
(And at that time,)
(So Min is still trying to accomplish the last task.)
- I'll give you a quiz now. - Okay.
If you don't answer it in 30 seconds, you can't eat that.
- Okay. - All right.
On the day of our press conference and first team dinner for the drama,
after seeing how close I was with Sang Yeob,
you said this.
(Thinking)
My gosh...
(What did I say?)
(Please tell me that you were jealous.)
"I'm jealous."
(He finally says the magic word!)
- Correct! - I already said that.
So Min, you completed your mission.
(So Min, you completed your mission.)
You were doing a mission just now?
Yes.
You wouldn't say that,
so it was so hard.
It was to get me to say all those things.
No, that's not true. It's not true.
Please. It's not what you think.
- What was that? - It's love.
- Were you acting the whole time? - No, no.
That's why you kept acting awkward.
We can't get caught. If they catch us, we can't go on dates.
- We have to run. Hurry. - So Min.
This was all for the show.
- Hey, I'm so disappointed! - No, it's not that.
I'm so disappointed.
If we don't do this, I have to pay for everything.
- Really? - Yes. We can't get caught.
We have to be on the run no matter what.
Let's go.
Hold on. Do I put S on this side?
Does it start from here?
No, it's N and I.
It spells "So Min" backwards!
- "So Min"! - You're right!
(Jong Kook realizes something.)
(If you read it backwards, it's "So Min".)
It spells "So Min" backwards!
S, O, M, I, N. Yes!
(It was an easy one.)
(At the same moment,)
(So Min and Ji Suk are still in the room.)
(Once he puts in the passcode...)
- It worked! - Good!
- NIMOS. - NIMOS.
(They finally go to where So Min is.)
- We need to go up. - No.
I smell the food. They were upstairs.
How did you get it?
- It spells "So Min" backwards? - Yes.
- It was broadcast live. - We came to the right place.
Right?
(Will So Min and Ji Suk get caught?)
- We were late. - This is the right place.
(They left already.)
- Oh, no. - They ate our food.
It was our money.
- They ate everything. - You're right.
- This looks expensive. - You're right.
(What happened to So Min and Ji Suk?)
(3 minutes ago)
(Just before the members reached the staircase,)
(they made a successful escape.)
Where should we go?
Do we get in?
- We need to run away. - Finally...
Let's go.
- Who should pay? - 30.
(They need to pick a member.)
Se Chan.
Why?
- You were in the same troop. - Yes.
I want to see him panic.
We need to find them once again.
- Yes. - They already left this place.
- We need to search again? - Yes.
- Gosh. - Where should we go next?
They had a date here, and now, they're on the move.
- Hello. - My goodness.
- Since they have already left, - Yes.
- Se Chan, - Yes?
you should pay.
- You need to pay. - It's for you.
(Se Chan will pay for the 1st round.)
It's for you.
(Dumbfounded)
- We need to pay every time. - They picked Se Chan.
- But... - Pay up.
Bring your card.
- How much is it? - It's...
- How much is it? - It's not that cheap.
Right, this is a restaurant.
(Glancing)
- How much is it? - They ate a lot.
- I will find them no matter what. - All right.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- We need to stop them. - Let's go.
Let's hurry and catch her.
Go faster.
We need to run away.
If you get caught, do you need to pay for everything?
You got something on your face again.
My mission is over.
You looked so awkward back there.
My goodness.
(She always gets stuff on her face.)
Forget my pretentious attitude back there.
I'm serious. I'm not joking. Please believe me.
We'll be on the sixth floor.
It can't be boxing, right?
(They arrive at their next destination.)
(Sighing)
I'm right. I was.
Oh, no.
(They're given dancing costumes and a stage.)
I don't want to go inside.
We don't know the genre yet.
Dan Ji.
(It's a familiar voice.)
Lee Yi Kyung!
(He is her second date who has been waiting for her.)
Come here now!
(Lee Yi Kyung, the innocent boy)
(When acting, he shows the manly side of him.)
(But in front of So Min, he's just a young boy in love.)
- Yes. - This is Lee Yi Kyung.
It's been a while.
(Startled)
(He gives her a flower.)
- What was that? - I heard that...
she likes tulips.
I remembered.
Yi Kyung, thank you so much.
- Don't mention it. - Thanks a lot.
- You're a grown man now. - You see,
we met when I was still quite young.
But I'm all grown up now.
- Am I your rival? - Let me get in between you.
(Ji Suk comes in between.)
(I can't accept this.)
Yi Kyung, I'm so happy to see you.
Come over here.
(He pulls her towards him.)
I'm so happy to see you.
So Min.
It's been a long time.
(Suddenly, it's a love triangle.)
I'm getting jealous. I am.
I'm getting jealous!
(I finally understand how it feels to be jealous.)
- You should've hugged me sooner. - I'm so jealous!
We had a date just now.
What did you do?
- We... - It's a secret.
- It is a secret. - I want to know!
(He won't tell.)
(It's a war of nerves.)
It's a secret.
This is the best birthday I've ever had.
- All right. - This feels great.
This time, you will learn...
how to tango with these two men.
(Have the Last Tango With Me)
- You'll succeed once you get... - Tango?
- all the moves correct. - Tango?
But after So Min learns the dance,
she needs to pick one of you to become her partner.
(She will choose one person.)
- Oh, no. - What about the other one?
She'll pick the one she can dance better with.
The one that doesn't get chosen...
will be eliminated.
(One of the two men will be eliminated mid-race.)
- Really? - Oh, no.
What should I do?
The members are chasing after you...
- as we speak. - They are?
- We need to hurry. - You must learn quickly.
We need to hurry.
After you change,
you will learn the tango.
Okay.
I've never tangoed before.
- What should I do? - I'm worried.
I'll be eliminated for sure.
Don't say that.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
We're professional dancers.
- I'm Kim Jin Woong. - I'm Kang Se Na.
- Hello. - It's nice to meet you.
But you see, we don't know anything about tango.
Do you think we can still dance?
Compared to other genres, tango is more...
- of a walking dance. - Is it?
I'm sure you can follow.
All of their costumes look so pretty.
Look at him.
(Everyone's clothes look nice except for...)
(Ji Suk's tight costume.)
This top goes all the way down...
to my legs.
So it's a bit tight.
(His entire body is squeezed inside the tights.)
I actually want to wear that.
Really?
- I already look like a dancer. - I've never worn such a dress.
- Goodness, So Min. - Goodness.
(Her red dress makes her look sexy.)
I've never seen you in such an outfit.
(You look like...)
You look like a true tango dancer.
- Really? - You do.
You look so pretty.
(He's good with words.)
Can you play some music?
(He decides to dance.)
That's great.
Although I've never learned tango before...
That's awesome. Show me.
(He's a tough match.)
Let me see.
(What kind of music will it be?)
I'm a bit...
(They all recognize this song.)
(It's So Min's favorite song.)
This is...
(Flustered)
Hold on.
(He starts dancing.)
(His dance moves are groovy.)
(He's good.)
(Afterwards,)
(he freezes in a cute way.)
(It's funny but charming at the same time.)
(He squirms.)
You already know how to dance.
(He does the worm dance.)
You know how to dance.
(I can dance too.)
(Suddenly, it becomes a couple dance.)
(They squirm together.)
(They're a perfect match for each other.)
That's it.
(Was it all right, So Min?)
I liked it!
I don't know much about tango, though.
- He was good to begin with. - I need to watch you dance too,
- Ji Suk. - He's way too good.
- You're too good. - Let's see it.
Show us.
Play a more upbeat song.
Play me anything.
You can play the same song.
I'm a bit flustered.
His outfit has already won some points.
(His outfit makes him look like a passionate dancer.)
(Squirming)
(Ironically, he shows off some adorable dance moves.)
You look cute.
You're very adorable.
(She likes it.)
(You're mine, So Min.)
You dance like this.
(You're cute.)
(Don't be fooled by him!)
(Would you like to dance with me?)
(Twirling)
(After a smooth spin,)
(he charms her even more with a powerful twist.)
(They seem to be getting along too well.)
(So Min, pick me.)
Thank you.
That was nice.
That was awesome.
Your styles are different. Yi Kyung is more hip-hop.
I don't know Ji Suk's genre.
You did well.
(Whom will So Min pick?)
Now, we will show you...
- the choreography. - All right.
(They anticipate.)
(They start off by gently holding each other's hands.)
(It's a sentimental separation...)
(followed by a passionate reunion.)
I'm getting goosebumps.
(It's only beautiful to watch.)
We have to do that.
(She suddenly flips her hair.)
I'm not flexible enough to bend backwards like that.
(They push and pull as if they're in a relationship.)
(They rely on each other...)
(and passionately march backwards.)
It's so amazing.
(They follow it up with a passionate head shake.)
(How do we do that?)
(In every cautious step they take lies their fervent love.)
It's too hard.
(She walks away coldheartedly...)
It's amazing.
(but comes back once again.)
(They gaze at each other.)
(This is tango, a dance for lovers.)
(It's a lovely finale.)
That's their finale.
(It is indeed mesmerizing.)
How do we do that?
This is a problem.
(They can only escape if they master it.)
I got goosebumps, watching you dance.
But it's frightening to think that we'll have to do it.
(Will they be able to run away from Team Chasers?)
Goodness, So Min.
Where did she go this time?
- It's not here. - It's over here.
- What is that? - What is it?
You dance here.
- It is. - Really?
That's out of the blue.
Hold on.
- It's fancy. - When can we meet her?
What kind of date could they have here?
Where is she right now?
- Look over there. - That's So Min.
(What lead have they found?)
I guess So Min danced.
- There's a guy. - That was their date.
- I see. - Look at how close they got.
That's Ji Suk.
- It'll feel different. - Right.
Someone else is there.
That's Lee Yi Kyung!
That's him?
That's him on the far end.
I'm frustrated.
We need to watch her on live.
What do we need to do?
What?
My goodness.
Hello, J-Black.
Hello.
(It's J-Black and Mmary, their old choreographers.)
(They're miracle workers who helped the members learn how to dance.)
(They're a well-known choreographing couple.)
- Hello. - Hello.
How are you, my teachers?
- J-Black. - Hello.
- Hello. - It's J-Black.
- They were our mentors. - Hello.
They've visited us once again.
(Why are they back?)
We're here to find So Min,
but why are you here?
You need us in order to catch her.
- What? - Why?
(They need the couple's help.)
First, we have a mission for you guys.
What is it?
Do we need to dance again?
Do you know the song "IDOL" by BTS?
- Yes. - Yes.
You need to learn...
the dance moves for a part of the song.
(Their mission is to master the dance for "IDOL".)
Goodness.
(The choreography for this song is very detailed and structured.)
(They can only trace So Min once they pass this mission.)
- Goodness. - We need to catch her quickly.
- We have no time. - The choreography is difficult.
We need to do this if we want to catch her, right?
If you succeed in this mission,
we will tell you where she is.
We should hurry.
If we succeed before she does,
- we can get her. - We need to hurry.
We should hurry.
We each have a role.
You can pick.
This is only for idols.
You chose V?
- You chose V? - Then who will do him?
Who? Take off your glasses then.
(He can't say anything.)
Are you confident enough?
He's ignoring you.
He knows how he looks without the glasses.
- You shouldn't be Suga. - Suga.
(He's the Suga of Running Man.)
- Suga. - No, you're fired.
- Yes, you are. - Yes.
- You're fired. - I am?
Yes.
(Kwang Soo picks Jungkook.)
You're "Jangkook".
Yes, you're "Jangkook".
(He befits a nice warm soup.)
"Jangkook"?
Yes, you are.
Come on.
- What? - That's what you are.
(Kwang Soo has found his role.)
You can be "Jeans".
- He'll be Jeans. - Yes.
Jeans.
Please show us.
Yes, we will show you once.
- We'll show you. - We should watch closely.
- We need to. - Yes.
I bet this won't be easy.
BTS' choreography isn't easy.
They're a globally-renowned group.
(They'll be dancing to the highlight of the song. How hard will it be?)
(It starts off easy.)
- Look at that. - They look nice.
(As if they're riding bikes.)
(The choreography looks very realistic.)
(After turning on the engine, they hop.)
(Kwang Soo also turns on his engine.)
(I can do this much.)
(Now comes the hard part.)
How can we do that?
(He moves skillfully.)
- How can we do that? - That's impossible.
- We can't do it. - My gosh.
- My gosh. - How can we do it?
We can't do this.
It's as hard as twirling a sangmo, a traditional dance move.
(Floundering)
(The arm movements make it even harder.)
- We can't do that. - How can we do this?
We can't.
(I can.)
How can we do this?
(He might dislocate all his joints.)
The dance moves look pretty.
How can we pull that off?
We can't.
(They move all their limbs.)
(It's an exciting choreography that contains traditional dance moves.)
(This is what they need to do.)
- Hold on. - That's all you need to do.
This is it.
How can we do this?
- How? - Is that it?
- Yes. - That's impossible.
This is easier than the one we did last time.
Don't lie like that.
Do we need to know our positions as well?
At this rate, we will never be able to catch So Min.
We really won't be able to.
Let's do it. We're running out of time.
- Right. - Let's do it.
Let's stop whining and just get to it.
- Right. - Where do we start?
Please tell us.
(They need to succeed before So Min does.)
(How far has So Min learned?)
Since there are 2 men and 1 woman,
- you will stand next to her. - Okay.
And for the men, Yi Kyung...
- Yes? - Step forward.
When you grab each other's hands, do it slowly.
When you pull her in, do it slowly.
All right.
Now...
- You're doing well. - We're a perfect match.
(They get along from the start.)
We're a perfect match.
(You're a perfect match?)
(I'll show you.)
For this part, you will hug the woman who has returned.
- Slow, slow, slow, hug. - Slow, slow, slow, hug.
I'm not very flexible.
You don't have to be flexible.
- Get ready. - Now,
- Set, go. - do I lean back?
Slow, slow...
(She leans back.)
(She collapses.)
(She gets dragged.)
- Hold on. - It's my fault.
I have weak arms.
I'm weak.
- I am. - No.
- I'm heavy. - No, I'm weak.
- You couldn't hold me well. - I'm very weak.
- Now, we'll switch partners. - Okay.
- From the slow, slow part? - Will you be okay?
- Of course. - Ready, set, go.
Go.
Slow.
(So Min, I don't want to go home just yet.)
(That depends on how well you do.)
Slow, slow.
- Lean back. - Slow, slow,
slow, slow.
- Okay. - Slow, slow.
(They succeed.)
That was good.
(Pick me.)
(We're a good match.)
That was good.
Why does she look more comfortable with him?
You're right.
- You look more comfortable. - He holds onto me well.
The male needs to be upright.
I'm an upright person, you know.
- I shouldn't follow her? - No.
If you try to help her, that will only make it difficult.
- So... - That's the type of person I am.
He's the giving type.
And he's the selfish type.
That's not true.
(Ji Suk is considerate.)
(Yi Kyung is far from that.)
You're accurate.
- I'm always upright. - Like this...
(Which one will she pick?)
- Okay. - We have a long way to go.
I see.
(Ji Suk, your shoelaces came undone.)
You'll trip. Tie it like this.
(The once rivals are now taking care of each other.)
Wait, I'm curious. What if they decide to become a couple?
(What if they decide to become a couple?)
No, it's just that his shoelaces kept coming undone.
What will happen to me?
(You two won't leave me behind while you escape, right?)
We'll go right into a dance move.
- Right away? - Here it goes.
Position yourself as if you're riding a bike.
Lean your head towards the direction you're going.
We'll start from the left. Lean left...
- like this. - I know this.
Then you lean towards your right.
Then you turn on the engine and get up.
- I see. - This is easy.
It is.
- It's quite easy. - I know.
It's simple, right?
(Yes, it is.)
(She's terrified.)
- I feel bad for BTS. - I know.
This is where it gets a little bit tricky.
(The complicated parts start now.)
(This is the part that they were all worried about.)
The timing for jumping...
- is quite tricky. - I see.
- 5, 6, 7, 8. And you jump at 8. - Okay.
- I'll start off slowly. - Your right foot comes first.
(They need to be alert in order to catch So Min.)
(You jump at 8.)
(And then, you shake your legs.)
(The members are following well.)
Like this.
So that's the beat.
You need to end with your left foot forward.
(Kwang Soo makes strange movements.)
- Are you mimicking a zombie? - I know.
- Right? - He looks like it.
Isn't that the Choi Hong Man dance?
It looks creepy.
(They're infected with a virus.)
It's so creepy.
All right, now we will continue.
When you kick, push your other foot backwards.
- And kick. - And kick.
And kick.
- From here, you switch feet. - Kick.
- Kick. - Kick.
(Kwang Soo dances frivolously.)
Isn't this the Tetris dance?
- Kick. - Isn't it?
Kick from there.
(He dances to the beat.)
(This is a magic show where idol's dance moves become...)
(a Tetris dance.)
(Kwang Soo attracts a crowd.)
- You're good. - He is.
Right.
(The Tetris performance meets a successful end.)
Tetris.
- Jangkook, that was good. - Right?
- Wasn't I good? - Wait a minute. My pants are...
(What's wrong with his pants?)
Oh, come on!
- What is that? That's disgusting. - Hey!
(Mmary is shocked as well.)
What's wrong with him?
(My jeans were making me uncomfortable.)
Look at him.
(He wears a pair of tights.)
What's wrong with you?
(Why did you take off your pants?)
- Why did you take them off? - What's wrong with you?
(They force him out.)
What has gotten into him?
- Gosh. - These are sportswear.
What do you mean?
- They are. - Why is he like that?
Look at her face.
He must be exhausted.
- Those were sportswear. - Just wear those pants.
- Hi again. - That was awful.
They were sportswear.
I hated looking at that.
- Okay, I'll continue. - All right.
- Are you disgusted with us? - No.
(It feels like he is.)
All right.
I'm sorry.
We'll learn the next moves.
- It's so hard. - This is the important part.
From the outside to the inside.
- I see. - From the outside to the inside.
- It's hard. - Put it in.
Put it in. Use your arms.
(She's impressed by Haha.)
(He squirms around, and that doesn't look bad.)
That's it.
Can you do that a bit faster?
- This is right? - One, two.
(Did I miss something? This is right?)
One... To the inside. No, I mean...
- Is this right? - Not like that.
This...
- I meant the feel of it... - You look so cool!
- You look like an idol. - You have the feel,
but it's different.
From here, one...
- Then go down to your left, - How about the hands?
- Cross it. - Go like this.
Cross it.
Now your left shoulder. This is a bit more difficult.
Gosh.
Like this.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(He copied the dance exactly the same way.)
Gosh, I knew it.
It must be nice for you, Jong Kook.
Perfect. That was perfect.
(Jong Kook picked it up perfectly, starting to lead the whole team!)
You each have to memorize it.
(Thanks to Jong Kook's guidance of the dance and movements,)
(the Bangtan Adults slowly start to dance correctly!)
(They will have to succeed before So Min does to catch her.)
(Will they be able to chase past her this time?)
(Meanwhile, Team Love Triangle Tango...)
(will clap the slate, first.)
How are you going to do it?
- Spin around. - 1, 2, 3.
(I'm going to do it in a beautiful and cute way.)
(I am the slate fairy around here.)
It's so nice and harmonious without the other boys.
(It's so nice and harmonious without the other boys.)
They're always mean to me,
but they both keep saying that I'm pretty.
It feels so nice.
It doesn't feel like I'm on the usual show,
but like we're doing a whole new show just for you.
Yes, it feels like a different show.
- Let's go on to the next step. - Okay.
Spin your female partner...
- and ta-da! - Ta-da!
Then, the female partner comes back...
and the male takes her in his arms,
then the male holds her leg up.
(Gosh!)
(That much physical contact...)
Gosh.
That is the end.
(Will they be able to pull off this move?)
Let's do it.
I will have to leave this up to So Min.
Now...
Where do we begin? Here?
- Let's begin. - Is it here?
1, 2...
(For this couple,)
(in the drama, Yi Kyung was a macho who led So Min.)
Spin around and go,
then come back.
(How will they be in real life?)
Leave it up to me!
You have to grab on to here!
(You have to grab on to here!)
(Pinch)
How could I? No, no.
Come on.
You don't have to keep your manners.
- Hold it up, it's just dance! - Okay.
Like this,
then lean back.
(Do it properly. We can't escape if we get it wrong!)
(No!)
(I'm shy.)
(Staring)
- That was intense. - So Min,
why are you practicing with Yi Kyung?
(Jealousy explodes.)
No, it's not like that.
- I'll just practice on my own. - No.
(Ji Suk is being childish.)
I'm disappointed!
No, it's because he's easier to control without feelings.
Don't lie. Dance with me, too.
It's because I'm shy.
- It's much simpler with him... - Whatever.
(Passionate romance is not easy, even with the competition up close.)
I have to go like this, then...
(Practice with Ji Suk begins.)
Don't lean me back, but hold on to me first.
You have to hold me so I can do this.
Is this where I need to bend back?
- Yes, you bend back slowly. - Bend back, then...
(Ji Suk, by the way,)
(this eye contact...)
(doesn't seem too unfamiliar.)
(It's like we've gone back to when we were Kang Soon and Yoo Baek.)
(Should we just...)
(No, So Min!)
- Do this, then... - Kiss.
Do I get back up after this?
Is it like this?
Hey!
(Hey!)
I'm not sure, yet.
I'm just practicing.
- Come and practice over here - I'm just practicing, Yi Kyung.
(Are they suppose to be completing a mission, or doing a drama shoot?)
(Will they even be able to complete the mission?)
Should we see each of you from the beginning?
- From the top? - Yes.
Okay. Let's take it slowly.
I can't remember the sequence.
So Min, do you remember all the steps?
(Ji Suk and So Min go first.)
If I don't know...
- I'll just go with the flow... - Oh, we're doing it with music?
- even if something goes wrong. - Okay.
(How will Yoo Baek couple's tango turn out?)
Slow.
(Ji Suk leads So Min smoothly with his words.)
(Is it a plot twist? Their teamwork doesn't seem too bad.)
(Looking unstable)
(They start to look somewhat unstable.)
What's next?
Step backwards.
(Missed a step)
(I like how it's going.)
Let's go.
(It's too early to give up. Let's try again.)
(The music stops abruptly.)
- Wait. - Wait.
(Wait!)
- It stopped! - Let's try and finish it.
- Let's try and finish it. - It stopped.
(There's a long way left, but they weren't cautious of the time.)
- No. - I wish there were more music left.
(Their "Last Tango" ended with too much vibe and no time.)
(Next up is Yi Kyung, who only looks up to So Min.)
Let's do this.
I didn't think putting more feeling into it was this hard.
Now, your gaze.
Okay.
(Concentrate the mind...)
(and set the gaze.)
It's all set.
(Yi Kyung takes the perfect lead with his gaze set.)
(Snap!)
(Shy Yi Kyung is gone, now he owns the stage with strong energy.)
[VIU Ver] SBS E447 Running Man
"Sulliver's Love Race Part 2"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Perfect teamwork)
(I got you, So Min.)
Stretch it, one, look back,
now turn...
and spin!
(I lost. I respect you, tango macho.)
(The Running Man dancing queen...)
(and the Havana B-boy's "Last Tango".)
(Will you dance your "Last Tango" with me?)
(Shaking)
Don't move.
(The tough woman is back. Hold on!)
(What a relief!)
Yi Kyung is so good at this!
You're so good.
Should we try one more time?
(Yi Kyung's macho tango stole her heart.)
You're making me jealous!
Gosh, that was like Haha. I should stop.
So Min, you will now have to choose one partner...
to continue on with the next date.
Oh, no.
It's too cruel.
Before we end, I was really happy to be with you.
- Me too. - Although it's a competition.
It seems like I'm the bad one.
(Who will So Min choose, between the two?)
(Despite full of mistakes and being bad at dancing,)
(the one who shared a heart throbbing gaze, Ji Suk?)
(Or...)
(the shy boy...)
(who turns into a macho when dancing!)
(The surprise heartthrob, Yi Kyung?)
I will choose, now.
(Who will be the man...)
(to have stolen the birthday girl's heart?)
1, 2, 3!
(The next date will be with Ji Suk.)
(The cry of happiness)
I think I'll be standing like this until tomorrow.
(On the other hand, the tango macho...)
(is cuddled by the tango teacher's arms.)
It's so thick.
It's so thick!
(The teacher's pet and the teacher make a new couple.)
Thank you.
- No, Yi Kyung. - It's okay. I'm really happy.
Sometimes it's good to just be a passerby.
- I'm really sorry. - Don't say that.
- Thank you so much. - Don't mention it.
I'll get going, then.
You have to leave while dancing the tango.
Yes. While dancing the tango, nicely.
Tango, my foot!
(Tango, my foot!)
I'm leaving.
(Yi Kyung leaves with his heart broken by tango.)
Goodbye.
When you get the hang of it,
- you can begin. - Okay. We will.
- Let's do this, BT. - Okay.
- Okay. - More like Shabby.
(So to speak...)
(If BTS is the flashy idol on stage,)
- Running Machine. - Running Machine!
(we are the Shabby BTS.)
Shudder.
Ji-Hyope.
Buffet.
- Kim Jimin. - Fired.
Jangkook.
(Finishing off with Jangkook.)
Let's do this!
(Let's get it, Bangtan Adults!)
(Start the "IDOL" dance!)
(I'm the hip hop gangster around here.)
(They have unexpectedly amazing teamwork.)
(And they nailed the major dance move.)
(They show perfect unity when dancing the difficult moves!)
(The zombie's arms and legs move separately.)
(Let's go, Hip Zombie!)
1, 2, 3, 4.
(With Running Machine's chant, they force immediate unity.)
(The small show-off tries to act cool.)
- Let's go! - One, two, three, and let's go!
(Will they complete the dance...)
(in their first try?)
Oh, It's this side!
Come on!
(They failed because Seok Jin used his other hand.)
- It's discouraging. - Turn the music off!
You're discouraging us.
(They attack with criticism.)
It's this. Why would you do this?
I thought it was this hand.
I'm sorry. I'm...
- left-handed. - Come on!
Okay, I get it now.
You have to act cool.
You're going to try again, right?
- Yes. - Let's do it.
Music, please!
Our last try.
(I'm the center.)
(Push)
(The variety gangsters fight vigorously for the spot...)
(in order to get the solo angle.)
Look, they look so cool.
This is the coolest part.
(They work towards the middle of the song without a hitch.)
(This is the part where Ji Suk failed.)
(He now succeeds easily.)
(It's now the last part!)
- "Tang, tang, tang-tang-tang"! - "Tang, tang, tang-tang-tang"!
(Ji Suk finishes it off early.)
Oh, come on.
Please!
What?
Why are you the only one different?
I just...
- It's "tang, tang, tang-tang-tang". - Okay.
(This is how you do it.)
(He's off-tune and off-beat.)
No, that's not it.
(Try to dance to this beat.)
Seok Jin, try this.
Tang, tang, maeuntang.
("Tang, tang, maeuntang".)
(You like maeuntang.)
Tang, tang, maeuntang.
- That's easier. - It's easier, right?
There we go.
- That actually worked? - Of course, it did.
(That actually worked?)
- What is that? - It's custom training.
- It's custom training. - Sure.
For bad dancers like him,
there's a certain way to teach them.
I can't believe that worked.
- "Tang, tang, maeuntang". - "Tang, tang, maeuntang".
Let's keep going.
- Let's go! - There's no time.
- It's our last chance! - Our last chance. Cue the music.
(They need to hurry up to catch So Min!)
(Bangtan Adults take the stage.)
(I want to be at the center.)
(He looks determined.)
(Here comes the group dance!)
(We're the Bangtan Adults.)
1, 2, 3, 4.
(With the ace's cadence,)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Bangtan Adults are going at it.)
(They'll get a hint of So Min's location if they succeed here.)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - Let's go!
(Here comes the highlight.)
(He's dancing passionately.)
(This is where Seok Jin makes mistakes.)
(Now he's done it perfectly!)
Nice, nice.
(You got this, Seok Jin!)
(There's only the problematic part left.)
(Will they be able to succeed with "maeuntang" training?)
("Tang, tang, maeuntang".)
"Tang, tang, maeuntang"!
(And a synchronized finish!)
(Dancing "IDOL" by BTS is a success.)
- We did it! - The "maeuntang" worked.
(The "maeuntang" worked.)
Good job!
We made it, right?
I'll give you guys a pass.
(He announces their success.)
(Now they're given a hint that tells So Min's location.)
- We did it! - "Tang, tang, maeuntang" did it.
- Right, "Tang, tang, maeuntang". - "Maeuntang" saved us.
Now we need to find So Min.
(It's time for them to go after So Min.)
Since you've succeeded...
Thank you, sir.
- Let's go, everyone. - Thank you!
- Bye, now. - Yes!
Thank you.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go get her! - Hurry it up.
We need to find So Min.
We just can't afford to get the penalty for this.
(At this moment)
Why is Yi Kyung calling me?
(Suddenly, Yi Kyung called him.)
- He did? - What does he want?
- What does he want? - Answer the phone.
Hey, Yi Kyung.
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
- I was stood up. - Where are you?
I was stood up by So Min. I'm at the tango place alone!
(Anger explodes.)
- I was stood up. - He was stood up?
You were stood up?
I thought he just got here.
(Why did Yi Kyung call the members?)
You have not been selected by So Min.
You are now the incarnation of revenge.
You may join the Running Man members,
and eliminate So Min's name tag to win the game.
Okay.
(Join the members and eliminate So Min's name tag!)
Jeon So Min.
How dare you ditch me?
(I'll get my revenge on you.)
She abandoned me and hurt my feelings.
But you're such a sweet guy!
We're on the way there.
No, she already left without me!
Already?
(So Min had left the tango place?)
(So Min and Ji Suk did their last tango...)
(to win the mission.)
(Ji Suk was very bad at practice,)
(and now he's leading her!)
It was a success.
- Thank you. - Thank you!
(And the tango date will be charged to...)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I choose Kwang Soo.
You got it.
(So Min decided to charge Kwang Soo for the lesson.)
Thanks, Kwang Soo!
Thanks!
Shall we move on?
- Let's go! - Okay.
(And they move on to the next destination.)
You did well.
(So Min chose me.)
(It's fine as long as she didn't choose me.)
So should we go where you are?
Or somewhere else?
- Don't come here. - Okay.
Go to Munbal-dong, 554 and 3.
- 554, there you go. - and 3.
- Okay. - We got it.
- Go get them, guys! - Okay.
(Go get them, guys!)
I'll break them apart!
All right, I'll see you soon.
- I'll see you soon. - Okay, bye.
- We'll meet him later. - Yes.
So she's still with Ji Suk.
- Yes. - They ate a meal.
Does she have feelings for him?
I think there's another guy who is expecting us.
Who is it now?
(So Min and Ji Suk are moving on to the next place.)
But...
(They're headed to a rural area.)
Where are we going?
(They can't see a thing.)
What is it?
(Where is their next destination?)
What is it? Where is it?
But...
(They're headed to a rural area.)
Where are we going?
(They can't see a thing.)
What is it?
Where is it? Where are we now?
- We're going kart racing. - Kart racing?
(They're going kart racing!)
(What will they be doing?)
(The refreshing feeling of getting cool winds on your face.)
(Kart racing is a perfect date to cool off the tango heat!)
Can you give me 30 seconds?
(She's wearing makeup.)
(You don't know who's going to be there.)
Why are you putting on makeup?
You've changed again.
(That's not it.)
Let's go.
You're really enjoying this, aren't you?
So Min.
(So Min, we've been doing great until now.)
(You're not leaving me, are you?)
(Ji Suk...)
(We'll see what happens.)
Seriously?
(She's firm.)
(What will happen to them in the next date?)
So there's another guy in there?
(Another date...)
(waiting for So Min?)
(You can tell...)
(that he's a sweet guy.)
(Oh my goodness)
Hey!
(He puts a smile on So Min's face.)
(On the other hand,)
Hey!
(Ji Suk had been dreading for this moment.)
This is unbelievable.
Hey!
Oh, my gosh.
(It's the smart and sexy actor, Ha Seok Jin.)
(They looked very good together...)
(in the TV series and in reality.)
(She's glad to see him,)
(and runs to him.)
Hey!
It's been a while.
Seok Jin!
(She's very glad to see him.)
Seok Jin.
- What's wrong? - You've got to be kidding me.
- It was Ha Seok Jin. - Thank you, both of you.
I love this.
I got two handsome men on both sides.
(They did not see this coming.)
I need to check my face.
You look fine.
That mirror looks good on you.
(That mirror looks good on you.)
My lips are dry.
(What's he doing?)
I've noticed that So Min doesn't look as happy...
as when she saw Yi Kyung.
(She doesn't look as happy as when she saw Yi Kyung.)
No, I like this very much!
(Seok Jin's trying to look calm.)
- Fine. - That's not true.
- What's not true? - I like you.
(I like you.)
I think I already won!
(Why do I feel like I've lost already?)
You two look great, by the way.
- Especially you. - What do you mean?
You lost a lot of weight.
My weight hasn't changed.
- No way. - You're being weird.
No, you absolutely look better.
- It looks awkward. - She does that to everyone.
- She's being weirdly welcoming. - Right, she is.
I felt it oo.
(You got me.)
We talked about you earlier.
How many kissing scenes have you done with So Min?
(Abruptly)
(Why now?)
We often did it even though it wasn't on the script.
We were too!
We kissed like 40 times.
I thought I was the one who kissed her the most,
- More than me? - and I wasn't.
Seok Jin and I kissed once per episode,
Ji Suk and I kissed more times.
(This is about the pride now.)
How was he? Was he any good?
(How was he? Was he any good?)
I wouldn't know.
It's just different, Seok Jin's more of a manly kisser,
and you're more of a sweet kisser.
(They have different kissing styles.)
It's like...
- we're two ex-boyfriends. - That's what I was thinking!
(It's like we're two ex-boyfriends.)
That's how I feel! It's weird.
We need to be chosen by her.
(The battle of the ex-boyfriends begins now.)
How? On what grounds?
We've prepared a mission.
It's called Love Love Kart.
Love Love Kart?
So Min will choose the one...
between these two men.
And she will get on a kart with the chosen one.
And she'll race with the other who isn't chosen.
(The chosen one rides with her, the other one rides alone.)
But, same as last time,
the one who isn't chosen by So Min...
and loses the race will be eliminated.
And his date is over.
But last time,
she chose one after the dancing competition.
And she's just choosing a guy now?
To ride in the same kart,
- you need good teamwork. - Right.
We have another game to figure out...
what types of guys you are.
It's Pit-a-pat Jenga.
The two of you will take turns,
and ask her questions.
If So Min doesn't choose you as the answer to the question,
you take one block out and put it on the top.
We need to ask questions where she can choose between us.
I see.
(They need to ask questions so she can choose one of them.)
It's been so long since I last played Jenga.
- It's Pit-a-pat Jenga. - It's all set now.
(Which ex-boyfriend will win this game?)
I need to ask her questions...
and make her choose me.
Go ahead.
Between the two of us,
who would you call...
when you're drunk?
(Who would you call when you're drunk?)
(She's thinking.)
- Seriously? - Yes.
Who would I call when I'm drunk?
- I'm calling? - Yes.
(Smiles)
(Her smiles...)
(make them happy.)
The smile makes me feel sad already.
Should I just say it?
1, 2, 3.
(The one she would call when she's drunk.)
(Which one she will choose?)
Ha Seok Jin!
(She chooses Seok Jin.)
Wait, let's hear why.
If I remember correctly,
Seok Jin was the only one I drank with...
to the point I got drunk.
You drank more with him than when you drank with me?
(He's in a rage.)
That's how I remember.
- At a team dinner, - Are you for real?
I don't remember drinking that much with Ji Suk.
I was hammered when I drank with you.
Really?
Is this a competition?
I thought she was going to choose me.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you go ahead and take one block out?
Go ahead.
With a light one.
That's easy.
(Someone loses as the Jenga falls.)
This is bad.
- You touch it, you can't change. - Which one is it?
- You can't change the block. - Is that it?
(He goes for the lower block.)
I think it's going to fall.
I don't think so.
Please keep your hands off the table.
Sure.
Keep your hands off.
(He tries to focus again.)
(Shaking)
- I'm getting nervous. - I like seeing...
- friends competing... - Wait, wait, wait.
- Keep your foot off. - over me.
(It looks risky.)
(To disturb Ji Suk)
Please don't.
(I just want to win.)
They always try to solve quizzes...
- Stop talking. - Okay.
I'm just talking to myself.
Why am I getting so nervous?
He also hurt his finger.
- I heard. - Yes.
Can you believe he broke his finger while taking a shower?
Can you?
- Look at it. - That could happen.
- It's your turn. - Is it my turn?
I'll just be direct.
Which one do you want to take more care of?
Oh, no.
Why are you doing this to me?
(She's going to choose me.)
(Who will So Min choose?)
Ha Seok Jin!
(She chooses Seok Jin again.)
(It's Seok Jin again?)
That's not it.
- I have a reason. - You don't have to be nice...
- to him because he's new. - I have a reason.
- Just listen to me. - I feel great.
- Hear me out. - It better be reasonable.
You take good care of yourself on your own.
Then what about him?
I can't take care of myself. I need someone to put my socks on.
(I need someone to put my socks on.)
- Are you serious? - From what I've seen,
even on the set, I tried to take care of him.
He makes me want to take care of him.
I'm hurt for real.
- I've been hit on the head. - He's attractive.
Don't be mad at me.
(The battle between ex-boyfriends is firing up.)
Where are we now?
What is this place?
There's a sign. It's a roller-skating rink!
What?
- Roller skates? - Yes, a roller-skating rink.
I really loved this place.
Only if there weren't kids like Jong Kook.
I went to this place a lot.
It's my first time coming here.
It's nostalgic.
They usually play music.
- You're right. - Right.
(They're excited to be here.)
That was playing all the time.
But didn't Yi Kyung told us to come here?
- There's Yi Kyung! - Yi Kyung!
- Yi Kyung! - Hello.
She didn't choose me!
(Screaming)
You look ugly today.
(He's pitiful today.)
She made me tango, and do all the other stuff.
- I feel bad for you. - You just got ditched.
So where is So Min?
The moment she eliminated me,
they took off in a car.
We need to catch her.
- So Min. - Where is she?
- We need to catch her. - What do we do?
Do you want to catch So Min?
- Yes! - Of course we do!
- We need to catch her and stop... - Of course!
- increasing their debts. - Right.
We installed a tracking device on So Min...
without her knowledge.
- Yes! - You could've told us that earlier.
This is your last chance to earn the tracking device.
All of you will be wearing the roller skates.
And move the flour in relays...
to fill half the cup.
- Okay. - I got it.
Let's go get her, everyone!
- Shall we go? - Let's go!
Let's go get So Min!
Let's go, it's a hunt!
(I will never forgive you, So Min!)
Let's go, take as much as you can.
(First attempt, start!)
We can't take a break.
There's no stopping.
No rest!
Be careful not to drop it.
( Jong Kook carefully delivers it to Jae Seok.)
(They're being careful.)
- That's quite a lot. - Good.
No fooling around this time.
One more time. Jong Kook, keep going!
(The point is to keep delivering it.)
(It is delivered to the next runner, Seok Jin.)
(Dripping)
(Seok Jin blows all the flour.)
- Seok Jin... - Why did you blow!
His face makes me laugh.
Seok Jin's the problem here.
Good, good.
(Trying not to laugh seems to be much harder.)
Stop laughing!
Why are they laughing?
Why!
We only did a little bit.
(It's delivered to the last runner, Kwang Soo.)
(That's all they got.)
(They're all gone because they laughed.)
(He's putting it in the cup.)
We can't make it at this speed!
This isn't going to work.
(They have less than half the time.)
Good, you're doing great!
(Jong Kook and Jae Seok got the hang of it.)
Okay, okay.
Don't laugh!
(They did it without laughing.)
(However,)
(Seok Jin slipped.)
Should we change the order?
(He drops it in various ways.)
(Now he bumps into Yi Kyung.)
(What are you doing?)
Let's switch!
It's going into my nose.
(Seok Jin keeps making excused.)
Hey.
(They still try their best.)
Kwang Soo!
(Where's Kwang Soo?)
What are you doing?
(Ta-da)
(He looks very comfortable like a giraffe.)
No!
What are you doing!
(Even a giraffe sometimes slips.)
(We're done for.)
This is it, guys.
Let's go again.
(He tries to shake all the flour.)
- Come on. - Why can't you...
- do it right? - Seok Jin keeps spilling.
- You spill too much. - My bad.
Kwang Soo should go first.
- It's difficult. - Because...
he's having a hard time receiving it.
- You go first. - And this...
- the table's too low. - You go first!
I'll be the last one.
Haha and I will be at the end.
All right, let's see how it goes.
- We'll see. - Are you guys ready?
- Yes! - Let's go!
Let's go!
Ready...
(Second attempt, start!)
(He scooped a lot.)
That's a lot.
(Then he grabs Jae Seok by the collar,)
(and falls.)
- No! - I'm sorry.
- Come on! - Let's go again.
- I'll go again. - Who put those two together?
Do not put them together!
I'm going right away!
Forget it.
(He falls again.)
Come on!
Forget it.
(What's your problem now?)
You need to hold him.
Yes, hold him.
Kwang Soo, you need to bend down your neck.
(Blowing)
(The battle of flour between Kwang Soo and Jae Seok.)
Don't pour on my nose!
You blocked my nose!
- Okay. - How do you want me to breathe?
That's it, we're done.
We're finished.
(Blowing)
(The second battle of flour.)
What are you two doing?
This is a mess.
Please.
He started it!
Let's just give up.
Let's just ride the roller skates.
(They gave up chasing So Min.)
This isn't working.
- I feel dizzy. - I don't want to lose any of you.
- I don't want to lose any of you. - No, I'm dizzy.
- Now... - Ask your question.
Among the two of us,
(What's he going to ask her now?)
who do you think liked you more?
(Who do you think liked you more?)
As a man.
- Right. - As the opposite sex.
Which of us did you think really liked you?
(What do I do?)
(Who does So Min think liked her more?)
Ha Seok Jin.
(She chooses Seok Jin.)
- So Min, are you moving on? - No,
- Because you had dates with me? - No, that's not it.
- That's it! - No, it's not!
I'll call you.
- I'll call you later. - Don't. Call him first!
I'm sorry.
I'm serious, don't call me.
- Text me. - Come on.
Why am I feeling so bad over this?
- What do I do? - What should I do with this Jenga?
You should try your best.
What are you going to do?
I thought it would collapse here.
Which one should I pull out?
You'll find it if you closely look.
Let's see.
Piling it is the problem.
- Wait. - As you pull it out...
What are you doing?
(He hugs her from the back.)
(Ji Suk, are you cheating?)
Wait a minute.
(Jenga is nothing if I'm with you.)
Take a photo of us.
- Can you go forward? - Send it to them.
Send it to Se Chan and Kwang Soo.
- So Min. - I got it.
(He pulls one out.)
- He pulled it out well. - Ji Suk.
This is the power of love.
That was amazing just now.
(He even piles up another one with the power of love.)
He did it.
(You look cool today.)
I will ask...
- a hard question. - Okay.
Based on your opinion,
with whom do you look better in a photo?
(Ji Suk's question)
Shall we try it?
Can you get us on camera?
(Can you get us together on camera?)
(Ji Suk and So Min are a top star couple.)
How about us?
(She takes a photo with Seok Jin as well.)
(So Min and Seok Jin are 1 percent couple.)
My goodness, I look good with both of them.
(They're neck and neck.)
1, 2, 3.
(Which one does So Min think matches her better?)
Kim Ji Suk.
(She finally picks Ji Suk.)
(Is it the effect of his hug from the back?)
Really?
- Why? Why? - What?
(Doesn't it upset you?)
Here's why.
I thought I looked good with you before.
A lot of time passed.
We recently finished shooting a drama together.
If I say that...
- we look better together... - The warmth still remains.
If I say that we look better together,
more people might watch our drama again.
(Is that why you chose me?)
It just gave me goosebumps.
So is it for business?
Is this a business?
- That's great too. - Right?
(It's great as long as I'm chosen.)
Our drama "Something About 1 Percent" had...
so many reruns.
Now it's time to support "Top Star U-back".
- I understand. - What will you do about this?
- The result depends... - Now...
- on this round. - it's almost over.
I bet you'll make it.
No, it's too unstable on the top.
(Shaking)
Wait.
(It's too unstable.)
- Watch. - Let's see.
(He picks a block to pull out.)
It will be difficult to pile it up.
Gosh, that's enough.
(He pulls it out successfully.)
They aren't fighting over me.
They're just being competitive.
(Did she just realize that they're just being competitive?)
It makes me feel...
bad little by little.
(Are they here to compete?)
This is difficult. Try it.
(Seok Jin defends successfully if he piles it up.)
(He piles it.)
(Then it collapsed.)
(Seok Jin loses the competition.)
I thought I got it.
- You put it with too much force. - I thought you got it too.
(Their competition ends.)
It's over now.
It was a game to get to know each other.
Let's go to the cart.
- I'll choose. - Yes.
You will choose.
(They move to the cart track.)
It's time to make your final decision.
This is too difficult.
(Chosen by So Min versus abandoned by So Min)
Please sit in your cart.
Okay, where should we sit?
It's cold. Button up.
(He acts sweet suddenly.)
(He makes a sweet comment full of trickery.)
- Goodness. - It's cold.
It's cold, it's cold.
This is what he does.
He's good at that.
(Two men are very different.)
(It gets harder for So Min to decide.)
It's too difficult.
I feel like I'm in trouble.
(Which one will be her last date?)
(First man is Ha Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin.
(It's been a long time.)
(There's warmth in his words that he says carelessly.)
(His warmth makes So Min fall for him without realizing it.)
(Ha Seok Jin, the man of her fate.)
(Or...)
(Just by seeing him makes her laugh.)
(He's the sweetest man.)
(He gets playful like a friend.)
(He puts So Min at ease.)
(He arrives at the beginning of her date.)
(Kim Ji Suk, a man So Min was meant to meet)
(She hands something to Ji Suk.)
Ji Suk.
(Is it a heating pad?)
Take it since it's cold.
It's okay.
I don't need a heating pad.
- Why not? - It's okay.
(So Min feels bad for him in the cold.)
You should take a heating pad.
(She hands a heating pad to Seok Jin as well.)
(What's going on?)
(He ends up seeing who she has chosen.)
(So Min chooses Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin is relieved.)
I didn't think she would make me happy.
I feel great.
I'm sorry, Ji Suk.
Yi Kyung.
(He thinks of Yi Kyung.)
(I'm sorry about what I did.)
So Min chose Seok Jin.
The two of them will have a date on Love Love Cart.
Both teams will complete one round of the track.
So Min and Seok Jin must arrive first to win.
What if they don't win?
They have to compete until they win.
(If Seok Jin and So Min lose, they must keep competing.)
If we fail?
We should go fast.
(Will So Min be able to get to her next date spot safely?)
(I'll show you the strength of single.)
Seok Jin.
(They're happy and cheerful.)
(He's charged with anger.)
(The two men's pride depends on the cart race.)
We can do it.
(Ji Suk represents singles, and his engine sound is full of anger.)
(Seok Jin represents couples, and he's relaxed.)
It's fast.
(They speed up from the beginning.)
It's very fast.
(Mad Max: Road of Fury)
(Bumping)
(Laughing in surprise)
(Singles can be scary.)
(Ji Suk speeds up and don't care about the gap between them.)
(He's right after them.)
(Ji Suk becomes bold and tries to outrun them.)
(They get surprised while having a conversation.)
(It's the last corner before the finish line.)
(This is the last chance.)
(Did Ji Suk get on the inside lane?)
(It's his last chance to interrupt Seok Jin and So Min's date.)
(Will Ji Suk be able to outrun Seok Jin?)
(Spinning)
(Ji Suk stops after spinning.)
(Next to a smiling couple that passes by,)
(the representative of singles collapses.)
(Crying)
(I'm sorry, but we're leaving.)
Look.
We ditched him.
(Without a surprise,)
(the couple wins.)
(They go to their final date as they win.)
I thought he was going to outrun us.
I'll charge it to Jong Kook.
(What's their next date?)
- Let's start. - Start.
Let's go.
Get ready.
(The first player is Kwang Soo again.)
(What?)
(He improved in a short period of time.)
It's a huge pile.
(Kwang Soo carries a huge amount.)
That's a lot.
(At this rate, he could succeed.)
(Being careful)
It's not bad.
Hurry.
Speed is more important.
(Kwang Soo shows off his skill while Yi Kyung moves it.)
(Seok Jin also does a good job.)
It's half filled.
(They succeed if they transfer a little more.)
We'll make it. It'll be possible.
(They have 15 seconds left.)
It's the last one. You're almost there.
We're almost done.
(This is the last pile of flour.)
(Will they fill it up and succeed?)
5, 4.
(What will be the result?)
- I think we'll make it. - 3, 2.
(They've finally made it.)
(They've filled more than half of the cup.)
You cleared the mission.
(Mission cleared)
(They made it.)
That was amazing.
- Tell us where So Min is now. - Hurry.
- Everyone. - Yes.
You can find So Min with this GPS tracker.
Track her down with it.
- Let's go now. - We should go there.
You'll succeed if you eliminate So Min's name tag.
Let's hurry. Let's go.
(GPS tracking starts.)
Let's catch her now.
Let's tear off her name tag.
Someone should run after her when we get there.
Tear off her name tag immediately.
Catch her and tear it off.
- I'll tear it off with my teeth. - Okay.
Yi Kyung is angry.
Let Yi Kyung do it.
Can you see where she is on the GPS tracker?
See if she's moving.
She's moving.
So Min hasn't called us once.
(At that moment)
So Min.
(Did So Min call them finally?)
- What? - Be careful.
Is she on the phone?
- We're on our way. - I think she called him.
(So Min suddenly calls Yi Kyung.)
Are you happy?
Here's Seok Jin. Wait.
Give me the phone.
Who is it?
So Min.
- Hasn't it been too long... - So Min.
- Ask where she is. - since she called us?
Come here, Yi Kyung.
What's this?
(The call was a joke.)
It's his first time on Running Man.
Seok Jin got duped by Yi Kyung.
Hey!
(Seok Jin isn't experienced at all.)
Yi Kyung, why you...
- My goodness. - Sorry.
It would be strange if she called.
Ji Suk is calling me.
- Is he? - Yes.
Hello?
This is Ji Suk burning with desire for revenge.
Did So Min abandon you?
Ji Suk as well?
Did So Min ditch you?
Goodness.
I think she dumped him too.
How could So Min change like that?
Is she usually like this?
I had no idea. We shot a drama for six months.
I didn't know she was such changeable.
He's very angry.
Seriously. I'm shocked.
(I know exactly how you feel.)
- Ji Suk. - I'll come find you.
- See you soon. - Okay.
Okay.
(He used to be a sweet man, but he's not over her.)
So Min.
I will tear off...
your name tag.
I bet Ji Suk is sulky now.
(Her prediction is correct.)
- He gets sulky easily. - He does.
He was disappointed when he left.
Why didn't you choose him?
(So that he isn't sulky?)
I picked you to keep you here.
(Everyone is chasing after Seok Jin.)
This is so funny.
We arrived in Hyeri.
(They arrive at the last dating spot.)
Let's go.
(Let's go on a date.)
Go to three spots in the photos.
They're hidden in your last dating spot.
Take a selfie at each spot. That's how you complete each mission.
- Shall we walk faster? - Do we have to run?
We never know, so let's walk fast.
What if we get caught?
When a group of cameras arrives,
we can run away then, can't we?
- They're very fast. - Really?
It's over once we see them.
That's how it will be.
We're here. Here it is.
It's Hyeri.
(They arrive at Hyeri where So Min and Seok Jin are on a date.)
Look at the GPS tracker.
- Let's see. - We have to go up north.
- Really? - Yes.
We caught them.
We got them. Who is this?
- It's over for So Min. - We caught her.
What kind of date is this?
We should be able to talk.
Shouldn't we have time to look around and walk?
- Where is she? - She's very nearby.
- Really? - She's very near.
- Based on the GPS, she's behind... - Behind?
- I think so. - Go to the back.
We're in a hurry, so this isn't a date.
(They haven't cleared one mission.)
There's one.
Isn't that one of them?
Look.
This is it.
- This is it. Hello. - Hello.
You've found here.
Here it is.
Thank you.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
(Let's have a date while being chased.)
1, 2, 3.
(They clear the first mission.)
Come this way, Seok Jin.
Let's go this way.
Isn't this it? Look, where's the car?
(They head to...)
(their next destination.)
What's this?
- What? - They're right in front of us.
Jae Seok, park the car right here.
Let's walk around.
Let's get off here first.
- I know. - Shall we get out?
- Get out. - Get out?
(Shall we go catch her?)
Where is she on the tracker?
Do you see the stream in the front?
- Cross it. - We must cross it.
- That way? - Right.
Wait for me.
Ji Suk.
(Someone cries to stop Team Chasers.)
- Are you okay? - I'm sorry about what happened.
- Ji Suk. - Yi Kyung.
- I understand how you feel. - Ji Suk.
It's all right.
I'm full of vengeance.
They're men duped by So Min.
- After eating... - Is this how it felt?
- Don't even mention it. - Let's hurry.
Let's catch her.
So Min made many cry. What does the GPS tracker tell?
We're over here, and So Min is here.
Is it the other side?
Yes, it's by the container.
- With the train track. - In the background?
With this in the background?
(They're on a date without realizing that they're being chased.)
We have one left.
(They clear the second mission.)
(If they clear the last mission, Seok Jin and So Min win.)
I don't know where the giraffe is.
I haven't seen a giraffe here.
(They haven't found their last mission spot.)
Let's go to the bigger road.
(Team Chasers are searching everywhere.)
- Have you seen So Min? - Here?
- They went this way. - It's this way.
(A passerby gives them an important hint.)
This way?
Really?
We don't have time.
I can sense it.
Where is she?
(Will they run away or get caught?)
I think they're here.
There they are.
Run to the opposite side.
My goodness.
They don't care about the shoot. It's all about catching her.
We must catch her first.
Everyone's eyes look determined.
It's frightening here.
It's really frightening.
(It's a battlefield.)
We'll see the giraffe.
We'll see it...
since it has a long neck.
(They're looking for the giraffe in the photo.)
I'm afraid that I'll see Kwang Soo first.
I'm very scared.
It'll be finished if we see Kwang Soo or Jong Kook.
- Aren't they very fast? - They're very fast.
(They only need to clear one more.)
Let's take the stairs.
There they are!
(There they are!)
(They're right behind them.)
- No! - My goodness. Run.
There they are!
- Where? - In front of us.
- There they are. - In front of us.
(Two men with broken hearts)
(They run forward very fast.)
(Everything will be over once we get caught.)
- Wait. - They're very fast.
I'm done for.
They're ahead of us.
(Just wait until we catch you.)
So Min.
Run. We must run away.
- Hey. - Enjoy the present.
(He mumbles while gripping his jaw.)
The giraffe.
(At that time)
Where's the giraffe?
There it is.
(They find the giraffe statue.)
I think...
So Min has a mission over there.
Eliminate her name tag.
(Seok Jin and So Min get close to the final spot.)
(They clear the mission once they take a photo.)
(However)
Tear it off, Yi Kyung.
(Tear it off, Yi Kyung.)
It's the giraffe.
- Tear it off. - No.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Stop.
Tear it off.
- Tear it off. - Wait.
(Today is So Min's Birthday Special.)
(It was her big wish.)
(She became the center of passionate romance.)
(With men she had feelings for,)
(it was a day full of laughter.)
(Where did it go wrong?)
Wait.
Let's talk.
I tore it off.
(Tearing off)
(They eliminate her name tag successfully.)
Please.
(Seok Jin and So Min fail to complete their final mission.)
So Min.
Seok Jin.
(So Min's passionate romance is finally over.)
Come here, So Min.
How did you find me?
Let's continue, Seok Jin.
(I won't give up.)
It's over.
Once it's torn off, you aren't a couple.
- So Min. - It's our date.
You abandoned Yi Kyung and Ji Suk.
Let's take a photo.
Stop following us.
(Ji Suk begs for love persistently.)
(Love comes back.)
He wasn't included in the photo.
Let me see it.
Don't we look good together?
This was a special episode for So Min's birthday.
Abandon if your heart doesn't flutter.
The final winner of Sulliver's Love Race is...
Running Man and Team Chasers.
(Running Man and Team Chasers)
Two of you, come here.
This is amazing.
That was great.
Although they weren't chosen by So Min,
Ji Suk and Yi Kyung took an active part...
as chasers.
They win a diamond ring as a prize.
Are you giving them to us?
Is it a real diamond?
Thank you.
As So Min failed,
she'll pay the entire date expenses.
- Pardon? - She'll be penalized.
Me?
So Min looks upset now.
- When did I say that I'd eat? - Is this it?
(When did I say that I'd eat?)
- The meal cost 300 dollars? - Ask your agency to pay.
She has to be hit.
"Hit"?
We'll say, "Happy Birthday".
Okay.
- Happy Birthday. - Happy Birthday.
(Happy Birthday, So Min.)
(Birthday)
(Cake)
(They're surprised by what they've never seen before.)
(This is a real birthday cake.)
She turned into an alien.
(I'm Groot.)
Take selfies with her.
- It's a frenzy. - My goodness.
So Min is so popular.
Congratulations.
(We thank Kim Ji Suk, Lee Yi Kyung, and Ha Seok Jin.)
Happy Birthday, So Min.
(The 2019 war of the real-time trending keywords starts.)
(4 teams participate.)
(Running Man, Seventeen)
(Running Man, Kim Hye Yoon)
(Running Man, Han Bo Reum)
(They fight to be number 1 trending keyword.)
(To attract people on the Internet,)
(they show off their personal talents.)
(Members go over the line to be searched online.)
(Is everything allowed to do just to be number 1?)
(A strange phenomenon that calls for obsession)
(And)
(A hint that can change the rank is inside the balloon?)
(A suffocating chase for trending keywords)
(Who will win the throne of the most trending keyword?)
(Search Running Man next week.)
("Please Search Me", a war of real-time trending keywords)