- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Hi. You came to the airport.
Gosh, you guys came to the airport.
- We just came back... - We just got back.
- from Vietnam. - We just got back.
We rested for a bit at a capsule hotel nearby.
- It was nice. - It was nice.
I've never been to one before.
It'd be nice to rent the room on a monthly basis.
- Why don't you do that, Suk Jin? - If I do, won't I get a discount?
You're always trying to leave home whenever you can, right?
He's pretending to be a bachelor.
And recently, Suk Jin...
went to Vietnam with his wife on a trip.
- Right. - He taught So Min about Vietnam.
- It was your first time there. - Yes, that's right.
So he taught So Min how to eat pho property.
"Hey, you need to add everything on that plate."
"I don't add the cilantro since I don't like it."
"You must squeeze the lime hard. That's not how you do it."
"Hey, that's not authentic pho then."
- "Do you want to switch with mine?" - "Don't say that you had real pho."
"You never listen to me. Gosh."
- I was... - "You never listen to me. Gosh."
- I was... - "What is this?"
"What is this?"
That really happened.
"Why do I smell cilantro?"
"Hey, is this cilantro?"
"This grass is cilantro. Goodness."
It was hilarious.
Their cilantro has a rectangular shape.
- Right. It looks different. - Right.
Vietnamese cilantro looks...
- different from the Korean one. - Right.
- It was so funny. - He was the worst.
Anyway, a lot of people in Vietnam...
showed us a lot of support...
and cheered for us.
I'd like to express my sincerest gratitude.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Before I explain to you about today's race...
- I heard Ryan Reynolds is joining. - Right.
- There were articles about it. - I found out from an article.
- He was in "Deadpool." - I'm so excited today.
He and I are the same age.
- You are? Really? - They are the same age.
- You guys should be friends. - Right.
But he's married and has kids too.
- Right. - But he's married and has kids too.
You should get married too.
- Suk Jin... - Anyway, before we start today,
we'll bring in a guest who will join us.
- There's a guest? - I saw the guest earlier.
All right.
- Hello. - My gosh.
Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - It's great to see you.
What's she doing with the jacket?
- I mean why... - What's she doing with her lips?
What's wrong with her?
Stop it. Cut the music. Cut it.
Bo Ra. Goodness, Bo Ra.
- It was really fun when she joined. - Didn't people tell you that a lot?
- Brave Dancer. - Brave Hwang.
Bo Ra, you're here to interpret for Ryan Reynolds, right?
- Really? - I beg your pardon?
- What? - Yes. She must speak English.
- I can't speak a word of English. - Really?
I can't speak a word of English.
Really?
Actually, people criticized me a lot when I did a show with Paris Hilton.
- Why? - They questioned why I was there...
when I spoke no English at all.
- You're that bad? - I'm awful. What should I do?
I know his wife though. The actress with a mole.
- Blake? - Yes. The woman with the mole.
Actually, you resemble her a bit.
- I see a resemblance. - Right.
Are you here because you're her lookalike?
- That's why she is here. - That must be it.
- That's it. - Give her a round of applause.
- Welcome. - She's his wife's lookalike.
- She's Blake's lookalike. - Right.
- There has to be a reason. - She was here for a reason.
- I should mark my face. - Mark a mole on your face.
Today, you will be meeting with Ryan Reynolds,
Melanie Laurent, and Adria Arjona, the main cast of a new film...
directed by the master of films, Michael Bay.
- Really? - We'll meet all of them?
We'll meet other actresses too?
- Really? All of them? - Melanie...
They will land in Korea this morning and must depart this evening.
They will only spend two hours with us.
- I know it's a bit sad, but... - They are here only for a day.
- Giving us two hours is a lot. - Right.
- They are here only for a day. - Of course.
So you'll meet them at your final mission.
These visiting stars...
will look at your profiles as well as Bo Ra's...
and personally choose three members for their own team.
They will choose 3 members for their teams themselves.
Just by looking at our photos?
- I hope Ryan recognizes me. - Please.
I hope they have a different standard for looks.
- Send the photo? - We have to send it to you?
Let's see.
How about this for Suk Jin?
- Jae Suk. That's... - Is this good?
- That's a terrible photo. - My gosh.
This is Kwang Soo's photo. Goodness, this photo...
- Isn't it nice? - No one can beat this.
- It's good, right? - Yes.
- I'll send a photo of Ji Hyo. - Yes, send it.
- I like photos like this. - Look at her.
- I just sent it to you. - Let me see.
- Let me see. - Gosh, he's...
- Let me see. - good at taking photos.
- Who is it? - Who is this?
- Who is this? - It's Suk Jin.
It's Suk Jin.
That's Suk Jin?
- That's me? - Who is this?
Isn't this a middle-aged woman?
- Who is it? - It's Suk Jin.
- Oh, no. I feel bad. - Poor him.
Goodness.
- I sent you the photo. - You sent me all the photos.
- Okay. - This is just the first 20 minutes.
Okay. Hello.
It's going to start right now.
I see.
We'll start now.
Choose the ones...
- you want to team up with. - So beautiful.
We have...
- A huge transformation... - Here...
first off guys.
Yes.
- Okay. - Who do we choose?
- Do you know who you want? - We're picking three.
- One each. - Okay.
And I'm going to pick...
I'll tell you the rules now.
- It's called the Ghost Hunter Race. - What's that?
Is there a spy?
Among the nine of you,
two of you are ghosts.
- When did you get the mission? - When did you film it?
Do they know that they are ghosts?
Yes, they do.
- They are aware of it? - The other members are hunters...
- who must catch the ghosts. - No way.
Then, you must have filmed this part in advance.
They must've gone to the hotel after filming it.
Right. It must've been after taking the shower.
- And they went back after that. - In their room.
I saw Se Chan and Jae Suk walking around together earlier.
- We had a burger. - We had a burger.
We got ready quickly.
There are three rounds in total.
After each round, depending on the result,
2 slots of 2 name tags each will be attached on the penalty roulette.
After the final mission, Ryan will pick the penalty himself.
After the final mission, when the penalty roulette is spun,
if the chosen slot contains a ghost, the ghosts will win.
All of the hunters...
- will face the penalty. - All of us?
If the chosen slot doesn't have a ghost, the hunters will win.
And two ghosts will face the penalty.
So the ghosts will try to sabotage the games?
The ghosts must have their names on the roulette.
They must be in every slot.
They might be obvious to spot.
I don't get it.
I will never be the ghost.
Bo Ra, stop pretending you don't get it.
- No, I'm not pretending. - She's pretending to not get it.
- Bo Ra. That's a shame. - It's really not me.
- She already got the mission. - We found out from the get-go.
Gosh, what a shame.
- It's really not me. - We found out right away.
If I'm the ghost, I won't star on Running Man.
- That was a hard move. - It's really not me.
- If it's me, I won't come here. - By the way,
why did people criticize you when you starred on a show...
with Paris Hilton?
I was over-the-top.
Why? When did that happen?
I was overly happy.
I said, "Thank you."
You made big reactions.
- You know my reactions are big. - Yes, they are.
I said, "My gosh, thank you."
They said I was pathetic.
Will you...
- take it down a notch today? - "Pathetic".
I'm not going to make any reactions today.
But you're making big reactions right now.
- My gosh. - No, later when they come.
- Bo Ra is so funny. - My gosh.
- Bo Ra. Seriously. - I won't make reactions.
Everyone, let's get moving for the first mission.
- Get on the bus, everyone. - Okay.
So we should try to let the ghosts win the games?
I can see my breath now.
- Where's So Min? - I'm right here.
What are you doing there?
I sat here because I saw a camera here.
Good job.
"What are you doing there?"
- You're running your own channel. - Jong Kook.
Running Man is rated 12.
- It's her online channel. - Her online channel.
- People would like the video. - Bo Ra.
If you could run your own channel, what will you do?
I'm already running my own channel.
- Really? - You walk.
- What do you on the channel? - You told us that you walk.
It's called WalkTalk. I walk in my videos.
- You walk? - I see.
- I took about 100,000 steps. - That's so cool.
Hey, I don't think to watch you walk will be entertaining.
It's so fun, Suk Jin.
Are you kidding me right now?
It's a killer video. I do more than just walking.
- Walking is no fun. - It's crazy.
Do people criticize you on your channel too?
- They don't criticize me there. - I see.
I don't have a lot of subscribers.
- There are no people to begin with. - Bo Ra.
Goodness, her story is really funny today.
- It's nice. - It's entertaining.
Suk Jin has been meeting up...
- with people who are on YouTube. - What do you want to do there?
- You'll start an online channel? - Will you talk about stocks?
They wanted to meet up.
- Suk Jin... - I don't think I can do it.
will talk about how to age beautifully.
He will talk about how to age beautifully.
That's great.
By the way, she must be mentally strong.
Suk Jin, stop talking. We need to play games now.
Nice timing.
Good job.
- That was great. - That hit the spot.
- Let's cut him off. - Nice.
- Cut Suk Jin off. - That was a great line.
As for the first mission, everyone must pass.
- Come on. - Come on.
- We lost this one. - This isn't going to work.
If you complete the mission at least once out of five attempts,
we won't attach your name tags on the roulette.
But if you fail, 4 name tags will be attached on 2 slots.
Will the ghosts sabotage the game? What will they do?
- They'll sabotage the game. - Right? Okay.
All right. As for this mission,
it's an upgrade strawberry game.
It's called Kwang Soo Is Not a Fool.
The name of the game is Kwang Soo Is Not a Fool?
- Kwang Soo is the main character. - Kwang Soo Is Not a Fool.
You'll follow the tempo of the strawberry game...
and listen to the arithmetic expression provided by the staff.
You need to call out his name in order on the beat.
For example, we'll say "Run, Kwang Soo."
"What's 3 plus 2?"
The answer is five.
You'll call out his name only five times.
Once you finish calling out his name five times,
you can say on the next beat, "He's not a fool."
That's so hard.
You came up with such an insulting game.
"He's not a fool." Of course, not. I'm not a fool.
We can make sure that you are not a fool with this game.
What?
Here's the order. Bo Ra, Se Chan,
- Haha, Ji Hyo, and So Min. - Okay.
- Okay. - Start.
Run, Kwang Soo.
What's 3 plus 1?
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo
He's not a fool.
- No, no. - No.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo
He's not a fool
- What? - No, no.
- That's not how you play. - Okay.
- Listen. - Why don't we start first?
- Bo Ra. - Okay.
- Bo Ra, you should keep walking. - Okay.
Okay.
- You should just walk instead. - It's because Bo Ra...
- is on the bus. - It's because she's on the bus.
- You should walk. - She should play it while walking.
- We'll start with Jong Kook. - Okay.
- Se Chan, Ji Hyo, Haha, - We'll show you.
- and So Min. This is the order. - I'll give it a try.
- Run, Kwang Soo. - Slowly.
What's 3 plus 3?
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo
- He's not a fool! - He's not a fool!
- Ji Hyo didn't say the line. - Why?
- Ji Hyo didn't say it. - She said it.
- Didn't you say the line? - I didn't?
No, she said it.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo
You know the title of the game...
- shouldn't have my mine in it. - We should say Ji Hyo's name.
It should be, Run, Ji Hyo.
Shouldn't it be Run, Ji Hyo?
- Or Get a Grip, Ji Hyo. - You should have raised them.
- I raised my hands. - I saw it.
- I saw it. - I won't let you slide from now on.
Ji Hyo isn't a fool!
- Hey, I'm not a fool. - She raised her hands.
It's hard to say that Ji Hyo isn't...
- a fool in this situation. - I agree.
It's hard to say that Ji Hyo isn't a fool in this situation.
- It's a bit iffy. - Right.
- Right. - That's true.
- That's true. - Okay. I'll raise them high.
We should start with Bo Ra.
- Sure. - What do you think?
- Run, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
What's 9 minus 7?
Kwang Soo
- He's not a fool - He's not a fool
Ji Hyo, you raised your hands, right?
- You raised them too soon. - Ji Hyo.
- He's not a fool - He's not a fool
I mean...
You're nagging me for raising them and not raising them.
What am I supposed to do?
Ji Hyo, are you a ghost?
No.
- She might be the ghost. - No.
She has to be.
- It's really not me. - Ji Hyo.
Look Jong Kook in his eye.
- This must be burning. - He'll be watching you.
The fur is burning now.
- It's his laser beam. - This is impossible.
- The back of my head hurts. - Let's do better.
- Are you a ghost or a fool? - Earlier... No.
Are you a fish or what?
- Choose 1 of the 2. Ghost or fish? - Are you oats?
- Are you oats or what? - I'm really not the ghost.
I desperately wish that you are not the ghost,
- but I can't say that you are not. - We can't say that.
- This keeps happening. - Listen.
Let's change the title to Ji Hyo Is Not a Fool.
- Good job. - Okay.
Let's try again.
- Run, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
What's 27 divided by 3?
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo
Goodness.
- Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo - Goodness.
- Just one. - My gosh.
You should have said it once.
- Se Chan isn't a ghost though. - You should've said it once.
I don't think he's a ghost.
Can you think that I'm a ghost?
I got confused. I thought it was an even number.
If we're going to succeed as a team,
- Just 1 time. - let's say it either 1 or 2 times.
- Once or twice is the best. - That's the best.
- All right. Everyone. - I...
It's 1, 2, 3, 4.
Do this. 1, 2. Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo
- I know. - Count to two and say his name.
- Count to two and say his name. - Okay.
- Let's try this, okay? - Stop it, old fart.
Listen. I'm talking right now.
- That old fart. - Okay.
Mr. Producer, let's do this.
This is your last round.
So Min will start first.
We need to get through this last round.
Here we go.
- Run, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
What's 11 plus 6?
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo
- Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo - It's 17.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo We're at 10 now.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo
- Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo - We're at 14.
- Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo - We're at 16.
Kwang Soo
Gosh.
- Hey, you. - He's a ghost!
- You were supposed to say it once. - I said it early.
- We were so close. - It was a mistake. I mean it.
It was my mistake.
- No, it can't be. He's a ghost. - He's a ghost.
- It was my mistake. - He's a ghost.
I mean...
I did well in the beginning of the game.
I did well during the last 5 rounds. I only made 1 mistake.
You made a mistake when it counts the most!
You made a mistake at a critical moment.
- This place is full of old farts! - It was a crucial moment!
Hey, you. Let me say something.
Hey, this feels like a team dinner.
- How many principals do we have? - Let's try one more time.
Okay. Give us one more chance.
"Give us one more chance." He's an old fart.
If we said "He's a fool",
- it would've been over? - Yes.
It's not "He's a fool." It's "He's not a fool."
You need to understand the game properly.
- That wasn't the line? - You must say, "He's not a fool."
- It's not, "He's a fool"? - If you say that, it's wrong.
- All right. We'll wrap up here. - What?
Gosh, we failed this mission.
Four of your names must go on the roulette.
You can decide the names among yourselves.
Put the name tags of people who made the most mistakes.
- No. - But they could be ghosts.
- We should exclude ghosts. - Right.
I haven't gotten a single part wrong so far.
Okay, let's put his name up.
- Me too. - I was never wrong.
- I'm not a ghost. - She's not a ghost either.
- We can put up your name too. - It's not me.
- It's not me. - Let's put her name up.
- It's not me. - Let's do that.
Guys, trust me and put my name up.
- Not him. - Not him.
- We shouldn't trust him. - Not him.
When I say that it's not me, I'm telling the truth.
I can vouch for him.
Bo Ra, this is only your second time here.
Right.
- You don't know him. - We shouldn't put his name up.
- We should never do that. - He's right.
- Not him. - It's really not me.
- Be quiet. - We have no one else to put up.
- Why should I be quiet? - How many times...
have you deceived me?
Several times.
How many times have you deceived me?
- Is he crazy? - Yes, I've lied to you before.
You have, haven't you?
Come on.
- After today's show, - Don't forget that.
Mr. Kim...
- "Mr. Kim"? - Yes.
- If I'm not a ghost... - He's acting like a stranger.
- Are you no longer friends? - He's acting like a stranger.
- He has. - If I'm not a ghost,
you better apologize to me, Mr. Kim.
- What? - Yes, you, Mr. Kim.
Fine, I will.
But you better apologize...
- for all the times you've lied. - Don't address me like that.
- Where are your manners? - Don't address you like that?
Don't address you like that?
- Okay. - I'm a grown man.
I want my share of the restaurant's money...
by tomorrow.
Hurry!
- He's looking down on me! - Hey.
- He's mad at you. - Mr. Kim.
We're almost there. Hang in there.
- Haha, I'll take his spot. - You little...
- He'll take the spot. - He'll take the spot.
Just go home.
- Just go home on time. - I'll take his spot.
- Gosh. - Or how about this?
Since So Min and I are the least suspicious ones,
- should we pick one? - Sure, that'll be better.
- Right, pick one. - We'll pick...
- someone else. - Okay.
- I'll pick Suk Jin. - Okay.
- He's the least likely to be one. - It's really not me. Good choice.
I pick Se Chan.
All right.
- I pick him. - We can trust Se Chan.
It'd be crazy if the ghosts were in this group.
That would be insane.
This is too confusing.
- Me too. - I have no idea.
It's confusing.
What is this?
- It's... - They're velcro balls.
- What are the balls for? - Maybe we need to hit something.
This looks like fun.
We'll be using those cups.
Okay, that's nice.
- I know this. - I really like this game.
If you win, you'll be able to pick a name and get a meal card.
It's called Upgrade Go! Stop!
- Meal card? Nice. - Meal card?
You'll be divided into groups of 4 and 5.
4 and 5?
The Money and Chance Card Zones are on the table.
For the Money Zone,
there are cups ranging from 1 to 5 dollars and 2 duds.
There are duds as well.
After each round,
the winning team can open as many cups as they like.
The losing team has...
- only one chance. - I see.
If you open a cup and there's money,
you'll be given that much money and have the choice to move on.
If you get a dud, all your money will disappear.
For the Chance Zone, there are 10 chance cards.
For every round, each team must open the cups once.
The winning team will be offered...
7 favorable ones and 3 unfavorable ones.
The losing team will be offered...
3 favorable ones and 7 unfavorable ones.
You'll pick out of these choices.
Those are the probabilities.
There will be a total of three rounds.
The team with the highest score will win.
The winning team will pick four names from the losing team...
and attach them to the roulette.
After this game, you will be able to eat with the money you've saved,
so try to save up as much as possible.
Let's split into two teams now.
Your teammates matter.
We should avoid the ghosts.
Let's use spoons.
Take them out.
Here are the rules.
I will tell you the rules...
of Ball Touch Out, the game we'll play beforehand.
- Ball Touch? - Ball Touch Out?
One member from each team will wear a velcro suit.
For one minute, you will throw the balls toward your opponent.
Whoever sticks the most balls on your opponent wins.
You may not remove any balls that are on your body.
Pick a member and wear the suit.
Bo Ra, you should do it.
Then we'll pick So Min.
It's So Min versus Bo Ra.
- I'm curious. - This is...
a match between two crazies.
Why are they taking their clothes off?
- What's with her lips? - What's wrong with them?
Stop the music.
- Look at their gazes. - Good luck!
Look at them.
You must win.
It's a match between the crazies.
- They'll be fighting each other. - They're so weird.
It's a match between the senior crazy...
- and a junior crazy. - You're right.
Look at them.
Why would you do that?
They look like penguins.
Get ready, set, go.
Throw it at her.
Throw it now.
- Good job. - Dodge.
- Hey, don't get them on you! - You shouldn't get them on you!
Don't get the balls on yourself.
Throw!
- Good. - You need to keep throwing.
Keep throwing them.
You need to keep throwing.
- You look cool. - Good.
You look like Spider-Man.
Dodge!
Don't show her your back!
- Bo Ra! - Dodge!
- Dodge! - Why are you so bad at throwing?
Dodge!
She's just full of passion.
- So Min is doing well. - What are you doing?
- What is she doing? - Why are you so bad at this?
What are you doing?
She's doing nothing well!
What have you done?
- Isn't she... - Come on.
a ghost?
- She only has passion. - What were you doing?
You did well.
- Good job. - You did well.
I'm not a ghost.
- I'm really not. - Good work.
You did so well.
So Min wins.
I can't believe I beat someone. It's unbelievable.
Is she dying?
- Are you okay? - Are you okay?
She's exhausted.
I'm too old for this.
So Min's team...
will start with the Money Zone.
Money Zone.
This is important.
We need to eat at all costs.
I hope you get a dud on your first opening.
From 1 to 10.
Choose whichever you want.
- I'll do it. - You do it.
All right.
- Trust your gut. - Choose whichever.
Number nine.
- I doubt it'd be a dud. - Me too.
I hope you get a dud.
- I hope you get a dud. - One dollar.
- 1 dollar. - Do it 1 more time.
- Do it one more time. - Again?
- Go, Ji Hyo, go! - Jae Suk.
- Okay! - That's three dollars in total.
- Pick another cup. - Pick another cup.
- You're such scaredy-cats. - No.
- Come on. - Let me be!
- Don't. - Let's do it again!
- Don't. - Let's do it again.
Go. Let's go.
- Let's do it again. - Do it.
- Jae Suk. - Just trust me.
- Let's go. - Let's go. Don't be scared.
1, 2...
- 1, 2. Okay. - All right.
Six dollars. Okay.
That's six dollars.
- Let's do it again! - No, don't.
No, not this time.
- That one's too dangerous. - I agree.
What can we have for six dollars?
We can have stir-fried rice.
- Do you want to stop or continue? - Let's stop.
Let's just stop here.
Let's eat.
One serving is not enough.
- We got six dollars. - We have the chance cards too.
- Let's go. - Again?
- We have the chance cards too. - Let's go.
- We have the chance cards too. - Let's do it.
- Okay! - Okay!
Let's stop here.
- Let's stop here. - Let's do that.
- Let's try it one more time. - Come on.
- I pick this. - Please!
- Don't be so reckless. - Let's do this!
- What's gotten into him? - Don't do this.
He's a gambler.
Let's go.
- Let's just eat now. - Do it one more time.
- Jae Suk, let's stop. - Let's stop.
- Let's stop. - Okay.
You can have sweet and sour pork if you have one more dollar.
- No, let's move on. - Let's move on.
I'll move on.
- So you've stopped? - Yes.
The losing team can pick only once.
- This is stressful. - Pick from the untouched ones.
Or number three...
- How about this one? - Pick this one.
I agree with Suk Jin.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
- It doesn't feel right. - It doesn't.
- All right, let's go. - Really?
- Go. - Try it.
- I'll get five dollars. - Pick that one.
- 3 dollars. - 3 dollars.
That wasn't too bad.
The winning team will move onto the Chance Card Zone.
- Let's go. - You get the good one.
There are 7 favorable ones and 3 unfavorable ones.
The losing team will get a bad probability...
with 7 unfavorable ones and 3 favorable ones.
Who knows what'll happen?
- All right. - Okay.
- Number 10? - Number 10.
- Why are you so reckless? - Why are you so rash?
- You're scaring me. - Don't worry.
There are 7 favorable ones and 3 unfavorable ones.
"You will obtain the money the other team won this round."
We got it.
They'll be getting our money?
Good work!
They'll get our three dollars?
We can pick a good one too.
- We can pick a good one as well. - You're right.
- We can pick the same one. - Right.
- We can pick the same one. - Then we'll get all the money.
- Right. - The best chance card is...
- switching the amount of money. - Okay!
- I'll pick number one. - Okay, do it.
- Here I go. - Don't hesitate.
We could be extremely lucky and get that card.
1, 2, 3.
- It's a good one. - "Open another money cup."
- That's good too. - That one.
- That's good too. - He's right.
- Let it be a dud. - Let it be a dud.
I think the ones that haven't been touched will have five dollars.
How about this last one?
How about number four?
"Four" also means death, and we will survive.
- Number four. - Let's do it!
- 1, 2, 3. - Let's go!
Who picked this one?
Why did you pick 4 instead of 6?
That's grand.
If we go first next, we can pick from that pile.
Right.
- Exactly. - I can't believe it was a dud.
It's time for the second round. Please get ready.
Haha's representing, right?
- Then it should be me. - Really?
I'll end him.
Aim mostly for his face. Haha, take off your glasses.
You're done for now. Serves you right for being cheeky on the bus.
Jong Kook doesn't even care about the game.
How he can hurt you is his number one focus.
Haha, I guess it's up to you to survive.
There's nothing we can do.
Mr. Kim, wait.
Mr. Kim?
If you want to live, just stayed turned around.
Curl into a ball when the game begins.
- Just stay curled up. - Protect your face.
- It's how you can survive. - Haha, don't let him win.
- Show him what you've got. - Ready,
get set...
This is insane!
- Haha, throw yours too. - Gosh!
Hey!
Jong Kook...
What on earth is this?
He's like a mad man.
- Gosh. - Oh, no!
He won.
- Haha lost. - 4, 3,
2, 1.
It's over.
- Hold on. - You idiot!
- I got hit in the face. - You moron.
Finally, I feel better.
Congratulations.
Jong Kook, you seem at ease now.
- We won. - There's no doubt about it.
- It was terrifying. - You idiot.
- Gosh. - Jong Kook wins.
It really hurt.
- All right, let's do this. - Let's get ourselves some money.
We should start with the dud pile.
Right, we should.
If this one's a dud too, then the rest will be...
- Yes, money. - It'll be money underneath.
Just get a dud and be done with it.
Get another dud.
- Get another dud. - Get another dud.
- But another dud... - I doubt it.
- Let's do it. - Just go for it.
Go for it. It's highly unlikely.
- Of course. - Here we go.
- It won't be another dud. - 1, 2, 3.
- What did you do? - Such mind games!
- We can select that pile now. - Exactly.
- That's our target. - Okay.
- Let's choose that pile. - They'll go for all of this now.
- We only get one try. - Only one.
- I see. - It's our turn now.
- The losing team can choose one. - That pile, Jae Suk.
It already had two duds, so go for it.
Five dollars!
- Five dollars. - No way.
- You now have 21 dollars. - Nice!
I can't believe you stacked them up this way.
You can pick a chance card now.
There's one that'll let us swap our balance.
- That's right. - Let's swap our balance.
Jong Kook, seven of these will benefit us.
Choose the swap. Number eight?
- Do we have 21 dollars? - What is it?
What is it?
You should've thought it over.
- They chose but failed. - They chose a bad one.
"Coin flip. Guess it wrong and you'll lose 10 dollars."
- 10 dollars? - You'll lose 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars? - But we don't have any money.
Will our balance be minus 10 dollars then?
How can you pick a bad chance card?
What's the point in winning the game then?
What's the point when things will get worse for us?
Guess it wrong and you'll lose 10 dollars.
- What's heads? - The one with the crane.
- The number will be tails. - We'll just have to get it right.
- Guess it right and we're good. - Do we begin?
Here we go.
Heads!
- It was kind of obvious. - It's tails.
- I know what it is. - Tails.
- I agree. - Tails?
It twirled three times, so tails.
- The crane is heads, right? - Yes.
I'll let you see then. You called tails.
Tails.
- Tails. - Tails.
Okay.
- What a relief. - It twirled three times.
We still don't have any money though.
You'll now choose a chance card from the bad zone.
- We can pick a good one. - Sure we can.
Choose one.
Please let it be a bad one.
- The chances are low. - A bad one...
I think Jae Suk should choose.
- Me? - You're extremely lucky today.
- But... - I think he's the ghost.
He's been trying to sabotage us, but that's backfiring on him.
- Really? - Makes sense.
He's too lucky today.
All right, here we go.
"Double your money. Multiply your total by two times."
See?
- See what I mean? - Jae Suk!
He must be the ghost.
- He must be. - I think he is too.
He's only picking the good ones...
because he's trying to sabotage them.
They now have 42 dollars.
You two are...
- the ghosts. - What?
- The ghosts. - What?
- Let's do this! - Just do it.
- Go? - Let's go.
- 3 dollars. - 3 dollars.
"Double your money. Multiply your total by two times."
- See what I mean? - Jae Suk!
- He must be the ghost. - He must be.
They now have 42 dollars.
Why aren't you happy?
- You don't seem thrilled. - I'm flustered, that's all.
- But... - 42 dollars?
I can't believe I chose this.
You have 42 dollars.
In the last round, two from each team will compete.
The team with the least number of balls on them wins.
Who will it be this time?
- You should do it. - Me? Okay.
- Kwang Soo, go ahead. - Okay.
Doesn't that side have more balls?
Want some?
That's powerful.
Gosh, this is scary.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
We need to win this time.
- Good luck. - You've got this.
- This will be fun. - Get ready.
- Are you ready? - It's a big match.
Dodge his and then throw yours.
Why not just throw one now?
- Hey. - What are you doing?
Throw them.
- Throw them one at a time. - Hey!
- Don't show your back. - Kwang Soo!
Don't show your back.
- Don't show your back. - Don't show him your back.
- What is this? - Darn!
- Nice. - I can't believe him.
- Kwang Soo, don't show your back. - No!
- He's a ghost. - He is.
You shouldn't show your back.
- He's a ghost. - Your balls are sticking to you.
He has to be the ghost.
- What are you doing? - Stop showing your back.
Are you kidding me?
Unbelievable.
I can't believe this.
- Seriously? - Kwang Soo's a fool.
- Hey. - 10 seconds!
- Why are you being this way? - He's a fool.
Throw them.
Get more on him.
- Hurry. - Get him!
- This is your chance. - Now!
- Hurry. - Okay, that's it.
- Three... - Hurry.
- Two... - This is your last chance.
- One. - That was the last one.
That was the last one. Wait, it's hard to tell.
- He got the hang of it. - You never know.
- At the last second... - We could've won.
It seems close.
- It seems close. - You never know.
Please...
I have four.
1, 2, 3.
That's eight.
There's 25.
- 25. - 25?
- Yes. - 2, 4,
- 6, 8... - You never know.
- It was a close game. - It seems close.
- Here. - There's 21.
Okay!
- Nice. - Why throw them all at once?
What was that?
- Kwang Soo... - Why did you show your back?
- Exactly. - You should've done this instead.
That's right.
Get ready...
- What on earth? - Nice.
Gosh.
Nice. That's it!
- You're doing great. - Good job.
- Dodge her balls. - You're looking sexy.
That much...
She's covered in balls now.
Why are you sticking more balls on yourself?
Look.
5, 4, 3,
2, 1.
You were extremely sexy just now.
Team Jong Kook is the overall winner.
- Okay. - The duds...
- 1 pile had 2 duds. - Which pile is it?
- Was it this one? - The one with 5 dollars.
- Right, this is the one. - Number four.
- Right. - Let's take it all.
- We'll no longer get a dud. - Okay, we've chosen.
- We'll choose. - Here we go.
- Just take them all. - As long as it's not much.
- Gosh. - Two dollars.
- 3 dollars. - 3 dollars.
- 6 dollars. - 6 dollars.
- 4 dollars? That's 10 in total. - 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars? - The total.
- We have 10 dollars in total. - Good.
Pile number four has been depleted.
Number four started with a dud.
I doubt it'll be the same for number five.
Exactly. You're right.
- Really? - It's not possible.
Pile number four started with a dud.
- I'm getting a bad feeling. - Okay?
Let's do this.
- Okay. - We have 11 dollars.
We need more money if we're to beat them.
- Let's keep going. - But if it's a dud...
There won't be a dud under the one dollar.
It'd only show up after five dollars.
- I choose this one. - But...
- I have a bad feeling about this. - It's not possible.
- You're wrong. - I get good hunches, don't I?
I doubt the others will start with a dud now.
- We're nervous because it's you. - How about this one?
- Pile number one? - Yes.
There won't be a pile that starts with a dud now.
- There will be at least two. - Exactly.
- Underneath the five dollars. - I agree.
I agree with Suk Jin.
Isn't it more likely to have a dud?
- It won't be a dud. - No way.
- This one! - Okay, let's do this.
- Okay! - Good job.
One more?
- Let's do one more. - Let's do one more.
Are you sure?
- Which one? - It's the last one.
- It's three dollars. - We did it.
Let's stop now.
- I want to do just one more time. - We have to stop.
I think we'll get five more dollars.
- Keep going. - Let's do just one more.
Okay. Let's do one more.
We might get five more dollars.
You'll lose all your money.
It'll be a dud.
Five dollars!
- Good job! - We've gained 20 dollars.
- We've almost caught up. - Let's stop now.
- Keep going. - Let's stop.
- We'll stop. - We should control ourselves.
- Let's control ourselves. - You will stop at only 20 dollars?
It's the losing team's turn to pick an amount.
- We're still safe, right? - Yes.
Pick a dud.
Is it a dud? I told you.
- It's the first dud. - Yes.
We picked a dud in this round.
We can pick a good chance card.
Chance cards are more important.
Pick a good one. Please.
- It's been going well for us. - It's going well.
- We've gained 20 dollars. - There are two bad ones left.
The rest are all good.
- There are only two bad ones left. - There are only two.
- I'll choose number 4. - Number 4?
- Number four again? - Yes.
Last time, I died. I'm sure I'll live this time.
1, 2, 3.
- Okay! - It's a good one.
"Swap your amount with the other team."
- Let's do that. - Let's swap.
- Let's swap! - Let's swap!
- Let me see. - See what?
- Let me see the card. - Come see then.
Let me see. You're dead meat.
- It's true. - What are you talking about?
Can't you read?
- Can they really swap? - You picked a good one!
Good job!
We should have swapped when we had no money.
Still, their amount is more than double what we have.
Good shot!
We have 20 dollars now.
We might be able to swap again.
- We have a swap card too. - You do.
They do?
- But the chances are slim. - No way.
- That's not going to happen. - It's okay.
We can swap back.
- We'll pick a swap card too. - That's unlikely.
I think I've run out of luck.
- Just try. - You're a ghost, so it'll be fine.
You...
This is frustrating. You're suspecting I'm a ghost.
You can do this.
Number eight?
- You're a ghost, so it'll be fine. - That's unlikely.
They...
- "Swap your amount..." - Seriously?
Seriously?
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
- You did it! - I swear.
Jae Suk...
- I didn't expect this. - This is insane.
What's with you?
- What's with me? - I didn't...
I can't believe it.
A ghost...
I found a ghost.
Jae Suk is a ghost.
This is crazy.
This is unbelievable. How could he pick that?
If Jae Suk really is a ghost, he's so unlucky.
- You're right. - If he really is a ghost...
- Then he is extremely unlucky. - It's the worst.
It's the worst.
I'm shocked.
Out of the five members on the losing team,
- choose 4 for the roulette. - 4?
I think they're all ghosts.
- Didn't you see how hard I worked? - I'm not a ghost.
- You saw it, right? - Hey.
I'm suspecting...
- Jong Kook, Suk Jin, and Bo Ra. - Why me?
- I worked so hard. - You're suspicious.
I kept telling them to stop...
- when we were picking amounts. - Hey.
- Kwang Soo is suspicious. - Why?
- He's been acting strange. - No.
- I was like Jae Suk. - He threw the balls like this.
I was trying to throw as many balls as possible at once.
I don't think Se Chan is a ghost.
Let's choose everyone except Bo Ra.
- Everyone except Bo Ra, okay? - Okay.
Everyone except Bo Ra.
- Why? I'm not a ghost. - Everyone except Bo Ra.
Don't put Suk Jin's name on it.
Kwang Soo...
It's done.
- Please choose a dish. - I'm so happy.
- I choose fried rice. - Jjamppong and fried dumplings.
That sounds good. I want fried rice.
Should I have fried rice? It's been a while.
- I'm craving carbs. - Fried dumplings...
- Jjamppong has carbs too. - Does anyone want jjajangmyeon?
I'm craving rice.
Everything on the menu...
has carbs.
I didn't want to reveal this.
In Vietnam, she said on the street,
"That hotel must be owned by a Korean."
Don't say it.
"It must be owned by Mr. Park Royal."
It was the Park Royal Hotel,
and she thought it was owned by Mr. Park Royal.
It was the Park Royal Hotel.
And she thought it was owned by Mr. Park Royal.
This is the truth.
"Park Royal is a pretty name."
- "His name is unique. Mr. Park..." - Unbelievable.
- Mr. Park Royal... It's so funny. - Mr. Park Royal.
It's unbelievable.
They've chosen their teams, right?
Who would choose me after seeing the picture?
I look like a blue egg.
Adria Arjona.
Melanie Laurent.
Arjona.
What's up? Ryan Reynolds.
Your voice is so nice.
Hi, nice to meet you, and you?
- You're good. - What time is it now?
Fine, thank you, and you?
They're coming down right now.
They're coming down.
Are they really coming?
Where are they? Are they here?
Where are they?
We're no one.
You see that?
Let's do this.
What's up?
Let's go! Let's do this!
- Oh, my gosh! - Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh, Ryan!
Hi, Ryan!
- Get out of his way. - Come here.
- What's with you? - What are you doing?
- Giraffe! - "Giraffe"?
He called me Giraffe.
Gosh.
- He called me Giraffe. - Finally,
Ryan Reynolds, Melanie Laurent,
and Adria Arjona are with us here.
- Shall we sit down? - Sure.
All right, guys. Can I get one more out?
He's so hyped up.
He's full of energy.
He hugged me so tight.
I'd like to ask the three of them...
to introduce themselves to our viewers first.
- Hello, we're excited to be here. - Hi.
We can't wait to be the show's first human sacrifices.
Following Ryan,
let's hear from Adria.
Hi, how are you?
It's so nice to be here. Thank you for having us.
We have Melanie here as well.
I'm so ready to go.
Hi.
All right.
Their movie will be...
released soon.
Can you tell us a bit about your movie?
The movie "6 Underground"...
is a giant spectacle action extravaganza...
for Netflix that we're very excited about.
It's about six people who fake their own deaths to go off-grid...
to right some of the greatest wrongs in the world.
We're especially psyched about it.
- It sounds so fun. - I can't wait.
I'll definitely watch it.
We'll ask each guest...
a few questions.
Let's start with Ryan.
Like he said,
this is his second time in Korea.
- Can he read Korean? - I'm reading this right now.
- It's written in Korean. - No.
Not that one.
Let's do this one.
- Okay. - Let's do this one.
- He's so funny. - He has a sense of humor.
Ryan is so funny.
He has a sense of humor.
Why are you taking off your pants?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I misinterpreted this.
- I misinterpreted this. - Tell him I have a present for him.
I have a present for him.
Ryan.
He knows it.
Hold on a second.
Here...
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- He's eating it. - He's so good at this.
Like he said,
this is his second time in Korea.
And he promised...
he'd gulp down a bottle of soju the next time he's in Korea.
- Really? - Really?
Oh, my gosh.
Yes. No problem.
Sure. I don't mind...
being legally bonused for the rest of the day.
What?
- You're going to drink soju now? - For the rest of the day...
Sure.
No problem. I've never in my life said no to alcohol.
After drinking soju,
he'll take the whole day off.
- Ryan is such a good talker. - Seriously.
- He's so good. - He's so funny.
Give it up for Ryan!
Let's ask some questions...
- to Adria this time. - Yes!
We want you to imagine yourself as a secret agent...
and go with your gut feeling.
Which member looks to be the youngest?
- The youngest. - Yes.
The youngest?
I think... Wait, what's her name?
- Jeon. - Jeon.
Did I win? Yes? Are you the youngest?
- Yes. - Yes?
- Ask how old she thinks So Min is. - How old is she?
Twenty...
Seven.
Really?
- 34. - 34? What?
So Min is excited.
We are going to talk afterward.
You have to tell me some of your secrets.
What about him? The glasses guy.
The glasses?
- 30... - 30?
Six.
Adria is like...
She is like Santa Claus.
- Seriously. - She is the nicest.
42?
54.
- 54? - Yes.
- What? - What?
They are genuinely surprised.
In Korean age, I am 54.
In American age, I am 53. 52.
- Dad? - Yes.
Dad? No dad!
- Dad? - Yes. Dad? No dad!
I am not your dad.
But you are a dad!
You are a dad! You are a dad!
My goodness.
- Ryan has a way with words. - He doesn't take a break.
He is good.
Please interpret this.
He has a way with words.
- Seriously. - Yes.
That's what this gesture means. Ryan.
That's what this gesture means.
The direct translation of this means, "Shut up, Ryan."
"Please, shut up."
Adria, we have another question for you.
- Your father is a musician. - Really?
He traveled around the world.
- Yes. - Really?
He still is a musician.
He still tours the whole world. I was raised in a tour bus.
- Yes. - That's cool.
That's really cool.
Do you know any K-Pop singers or songs?
Show them your BTS tattoo.
- Tattoo? - BTS tattoo?
Am I serious? Am I joking?
- You will never know. - My goodness.
- I thought he was serious. - Ryan has...
a way with words.
I thought he was serious.
I have an EXO tattoo on my lower back.
- It's on my lower back. - An EXO tattoo on your lower back.
I will only show you. You can take a look.
- It's okay. - No?
All right.
He showed me.
A world-class star showed me his flesh.
- I was surprised too. - It was the first time.
He is the best.
Let's ask a question to Melanie.
Melanie!
Melanie Laurent!
- Melanie! - Yes, Melanie!
Melanie!
Melanie, you visited Korea again...
four years after you had a photoshoot here.
The thing is,
there are...
quite a few Korean actors who said Melanie is their ideal type.
Who are they?
Kang Ha Neul.
He is really famous right now in Korea.
He is a really young and hot guy.
Yes? Okay.
I can... My husband is here,
but I am French, so I am kind of like open to whatever.
Let's see what happens.
My goodness. Melanie also has...
- a way with words. - Right?
It's her.
My goodness.
She is funny.
Since we taught you this gesture,
please use it to other people when you go back.
Use it to other people in Hollywood.
This is very Deadpool.
Seriously.
We took some time to get to know...
the three of them.
Now, let's get started in earnest.
Team Running Man and Team Actors will go against each other...
in the final mission, Lucky Six Match.
The three members of Team Actors...
saw the nine profile photos in the morning...
and added three members to their team.
- That's right. - That's right.
- That's right. - How embarrassing!
The three members are...
- Okay. - Who starts?
- You can start. - I think I am going to go with...
Yoo.
Nice. Very wise choice.
Who are you going to go with?
Okay. I love that hair. The red hair.
I am going to go with Ji.
Ji? Okay.
I am going to pick Lee.
So we are going with Yoo, Ji, and Lee.
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, and Suk Jin.
- Okay! - What?
- The three of us? - Okay.
What's up?
- Oh, yes. - Really?
Oh, yes.
Did they really pick the three of us?
- Why? - What was the criterion?
Why?
- Why? Why? - What was the criterion?
- That came out of nowhere. - Why?
- I mean... - Why?
Because. Look at you guys! You are warriors!
- We are? - Oh, my goodness.
- We are warriors? - Warriors.
From those photos, I am the true warrior.
You will play the game...
6 versus 6.
To win the final mission, you must win 2 out of 3 rounds.
You will play...
traditional Korean games as the actors requested.
Each round, the winning team...
will receive Korean snacks.
Okay.
Those snacks are delicious.
Let's play!
- Let's play! - Let's begin the match.
Yes!
Come on, guys. Come on, guys.
- We are going to do this. - Come on.
I am very excited.
- I am going to get really excited. - Yes.
Ryan keeps using this gesture.
Their organization is scaring me.
Look how perfect they are. I feel like they are the winners.
- It's not like that. - I really want to tell them.
- The three of them... - It's not like that.
- I wish I was fluent in English. - I wish I could show them.
How do I say in English, "You basically stepped on poop"?
- Seriously. - I will play with seriousness.
The first game is jegi.
Jegi?
- The teams will take turns. - Okay.
The six members must choose the order from 1st to 6th.
The first player must kick once or more.
The second player must kick twice or more.
The 5th player must kick 5 times or more and so on...
for the team to succeed.
We need time to practice.
We will give you time to practice.
- This is... - Have they played this game before?
You kick with the inside of your foot.
Jegi is hard.
- Don't hurt me. - Melanie.
- This is bad. - I am trying.
- This is... - There you go.
You are good!
That's incredible.
- Are you ready? - What?
- What was that? - My goodness.
We won!
- We are done. - He is so good.
- We win! - I am done.
- He is so good. - What is up with him?
- I think... - How is that possible?
- he is just athletic. - That's sexy.
That's sexy.
Did you play soccer before?
- What? No. - Soccer? No?
- Hacky sack. - Hacky sack.
- Good. - Two.
- Okay. - Two.
- You got it. - 1, 2.
- Perfect. - Are you three?
- Shall we play Race of Wits? - Shall we?
- Let's do that. - Okay.
- Let's play Race of Wits. - It's better to go first.
Let's explain the rules to the three of them.
Let's demonstrate.
I can't believe I will play Race of Wits with them.
I played Race of Wits so many times.
- Watch us. - Watch us.
- Watch. - This game.
- What? - I don't know. We'll see.
- They're going to play this game? - Ryan's Race of Wits.
Start. One.
Two.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 5.
- 3. 4. - 5.
- You got it? - Okay.
- Do you understand, Melanie? - Okay?
Do you get it?
I really love this game,
but I didn't know I'd be playing Race of Wits with these world stars.
This day has come.
- My heart is beating so fast. - This day has come.
He loves this game.
I really love this game.
Can you believe how tall he is?
So tall.
Okay.
Melanie.
No, no.
- No. - Stop.
- Ready... - Okay.
Ready...
- Go. - One.
Two.
- 3. - 3.
- Out. - We're out.
We're out.
He's really bad.
So Mi, why did you go?
Ready, go.
One.
Two.
- 3. - 4.
- 5. - 6.
Seven.
- 8. - 9.
Ten.
I went easy on them.
- You did? - I went easy.
You didn't go easy.
- I really like these actors, - Come with me.
- so I sacrificed myself. - Come.
I went easy on them.
It's really fun seeing them getting nervous...
- and enjoying this game. - This is so much fun.
It's fun.
Ready,
- I'm 1. I'm going to do 1. - go.
- 1. - 2.
Three.
Four.
Five.
- 6. - 6.
- Both out. - My bad.
- Sorry. - What was that?
I didn't mean to.
- Why were you trying to win? - I didn't mean to.
- You were trying to win. - No!
- You're not witty. - No.
- I didn't mean to. - You beat Melanie.
- You were trying to win. - No, it was an instinct.
Sorry, Melanie.
- What? - We said "seven" together.
- Together... - We're out together.
- Okay. Together... - We're out together.
We're out together. It's fine.
- "We're out together." - It's getting exciting.
Stay out of this, Ji Hyo.
"We're out together."
He looks ready. Good.
The elite members.
Good luck.
- Ready, - Go first.
go.
- 1. - 1.
Oh, my.
- 1. - 1. Oh, my.
Come on.
Was it you?
- Him. - What?
- Me? - Ryan called one.
- No, it was Adria. - It was her?
Okay.
- Do rock-paper-scissors. - It's rock-paper-scissors.
This is an honor.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Go, Ryan.
Shoot.
You're so slow-witted. Why would you win?
- Okay! - It's us then.
I'm the guy who beat Ryan.
Do you want to go first or should we go?
They go first.
- Okay. - 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
1, 2, 3.
- Are you ready? - Yes!
Go first, Adria.
- Do I go first? - Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
At least one.
- It touched her foot. - No, wait. No, no.
- She touched it. - At least one.
- No, wait. No, no. - She touched it.
I don't think she did.
- She touched it. - I don't think she did.
No, she touched it.
That doesn't count?
Okay, I'm going to go again though.
- Because... - One more chance?
One more chance.
- Because... - Sides.
- Okay. - One.
- Melanie. - Oh, my gosh.
- 2. - 2.
- Please, Melanie. - Two.
- She must be nervous. - You got this.
- She touched it. - I touched it a little bit.
She just touched it.
- I touched it a little bit. - She touched it.
No.
- It's our turn. - Do we go?
- Next time. - I had another try.
- She gets to have another try. - Okay.
- They're stubborn too. - She's stubborn.
Hollywood stars are stubborn too.
Come on!
- It's not just us. - These are rules.
We can't do this all night.
I guess everybody is stubborn.
- Fine. - Everybody around the world.
Let her go again.
- Okay. - All right.
- Give us 1 more chance too then. - 1 more chance.
Go like this.
Oh, my gosh. So much pressure.
Oh, my gosh.
Kwang Soo.
It's better the more you get.
- This is a traditional game. - More is better.
- I'm really bad at this. - We have to watch Ryan play.
- Kwang Soo, more is better. - You're not that important.
Ryan can do five.
- Keep going. - Great.
- Okay. - Five.
You got it! Beautiful.
There you go.
- There you go. - That's our new dance.
We should do that now.
- Nice! - That's our new dance.
We should do that now. That's our new dance.
- He's so dirty. - What's wrong with him?
Suk Jin.
Say, "Hey, handsome man."
- What? - What?
- What? - Cut out the nonsense.
- Handsome man. - What are you doing?
- Handsome man. - Okay.
Wait, he's not on our team. No.
- He's on our team. - He's on our team.
- He is? You're so... - We're on the same team.
- He's not on our team. No. - He's on our team.
- He's on our team. - Oh, he is!
We're on the same team.
She didn't know he was on our team.
- I mean... - You're so beautiful.
- Handsome man. - She didn't know.
- Come on. - Handsome.
Handsome man.
- Handsome man. - Handsome man.
- Adria is so cute. - That was shocking.
"He's not on our team."
People around the world are rooting for you.
- We can get big worldwide. - I know.
- Go for 4. - At least 4.
1, 2, 3...
Three...
Four!
5, 6, 7.
Yes!
Dance!
Dance.
They are all doing it.
Ryan.
Ryan. Go, Ryan.
- 5. - 5.
- Ryan. - Five?
- No! - Practice. That was practice.
- No, it's over. - That was practice.
- He didn't say he was starting. - It's over.
- It's over. - It's not.
- It's over. - He didn't say he was starting.
What's wrong with Ryan?
It's over.
- What's wrong, Ryan? - That was so random.
- No way. - Fine.
- No way. - Is that necessary?
Fine.
- Next time. - No problem.
- I tried twice. - Your turn.
Now.
- Okay. - Bo Ra.
- Just get 1. - Get 1.
- Do one. - It's easy.
Okay! It's easy.
- All right! - Gosh.
It dropped long before that.
It's fine.
- Bo Ra. - There was lag.
It dropped long before that.
Let's scare her.
If we can't do this...
I'm so nervous.
- You can do it. It's okay. - Touch it twice.
It's okay. Tap, tap.
Okay. Out.
Tap, tap.
- Okay! - Okay!
Why?
You failed. Why would you do this?
I wanted to try it.
Sorry.
- Ryan too. - All right. One.
- Yes! - Yes!
Right.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- I'm okay. - Don't try to be funny.
We have to watch Ryan play.
Come on.
- Okay! - Yes.
I can't do this.
Ryan.
- Let's go, Ryan. - Ryan.
I'll go fifth.
1, 2.
- I'll go 5th. - 1, 2.
Three.
No!
Why does he keep doing that?
- What are you doing? - Stop it.
Why are you doing this, Ryan?
Why is he doing that?
Why do you keep doing that?
- Good job. - Good job.
- Respect. - I truly respect you.
- Big brother. - I don't think this game will end,
so let's just combine everybody's scores.
- All right. - Good.
- I agree. - Guys should go after.
The team that gets more.
- Can I do two then? - Yes, it doesn't matter.
- Okay. - Seven.
- Seven. - Good luck, Dong Hoon.
- 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, - 8, 9, 10, 11, 12...
- Good job. - 13, 14,
13, 14,
15, 16.
14, 15.
- Ryan got hit! - Why did you cheat?
Ryan got hit by the jegi!
16.
- That was good. - All right.
- That was very good though. - All right.
- Are we at 16? - 16.
16.
17, 18.
Get out of town.
Forget about it.
Se Chan is good at jegi.
Finish them off.
- I am afraid right now. - Yes.
Who pushed me?
- Stop it. - Don't push me.
He is in the flow.
- 31. - What?
- 31. - 31.
- 31. - They have an advantage.
- That's too much. - I am going to contribute one.
Adria, go first.
Yes!
I will take it!
I will take it! I will take it!
She has a competitive streak.
Get out there, Laurent. Do it.
How did this dance get started?
- It's Melanie's fault. - Melanie.
We actually have a dance.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
- Melanie. - This is hilarious.
- Oh, yes! - Two!
- 2. - 2.
Come on.
That's good.
- 3. - 4.
- 4. - 4.
I am just going to click the noises.
Ryan should go last.
I should tie that thing to a string.
- Yes! - Yes.
My technique!
- Suk Jin. - You know,
the preexisting rules...
- are... - This jegi resembles Suk Jin.
- It's losing hair. - Suk Jin.
It's suffering from hair loss like Suk Jin.
What is up with you?
- I can kick and go... - Come on.
- I should kick it 10 times. - That's right.
You should kick it that many times.
2, 3, 4...
That's good.
- Oh, no. - Six.
- 7, 8, - That's good.
9, 10.
11, 12.
- Yes! Get it now! - 13, 14,
- 15, 16. - Yes!
15, 16.
17, 18.
- 18. Okay. - Okay!
- It's okay. - Okay. That was good.
- 26. - Okay.
Two people haven't gone yet, right?
Ryan can finish this.
Ryan.
31 to 36.
- Ryan can finish this. - Kick it five times.
Just five!
Just five. Yes.
1, 2, 3,
four...
1, 2, 3, 4...
1, 2, 3,
4, 5, 6.
- Yes! - Five...
Yes!
What?
Come on! Come on!
He is really good.
That was incredible.
Team Actors win.
You will get a snack card.
We will move on to the next game.
There is nothing he can't do.
Ryan...
This isn't an easy game.
He is good at everything.
I love it.
Okay. One more.
- Teach her how to hold it. - Hold it like this.
Kwang Soo is trying so hard to be cast.
Good, good.
- Hey. - Good, good. One more.
- Let's go. - You are transparent.
Seriously.
- He is trying so hard. - My goodness.
He is trying the hardest today.
Team Actors wins...
if more red sides are showing.
Team Running Man wins if more blue sides are showing.
Team Actors wins if more red sides are showing.
We will add up the number of ddakjis in three rounds.
The team that turns over more ddakjis wins.
We... Many orange... Good.
We... Many Blue... Bad.
- Okay. - What are you saying?
- Go, go. - What?
Move out of the way.
Two players will represent the team in each round.
Ready.
- 1 minute. - 1 minute.
- Come on, Melanie. - You got this, Melanie.
- Ready. - Come on!
Go!
- Close. - Almost.
- Go! - Good.
Really close.
I see so many red sides! Get them flipped over.
Get the ones Kwang Soo can't reach. Behind you.
Okay. You are doing great.
Se Chan is good.
Se Chan is really good.
- Okay. - Se Chan is really good.
Okay.
Now, it's sadness.
Sadness is taking over my body.
You are doing great, Mel.
Now, it's sadness.
Sadness is taking over my body.
It's pretty sad.
- Melanie. - That's good.
Come on.
You got this. You got this.
- Look at Se Chan. - He is so good.
Look at Se Chan.
- I see blue everywhere. - Se Chan is so good.
I see blue everywhere.
- 2. - 4.
3, 2, 1.
Okay.
- We won. - We won.
You were like a machine.
- You were like a ddakji factory. - Great job, Mel.
- They killed us. - Yes.
I got three of them.
Go!
- There you go. - She is fast.
Get angry with it!
- Okay. - Get angry!
Suk Jin, you need to do better.
- Awesome! - Adria!
Adria!
Okay. Okay.
- Time's up. - Good job. Good job.
The current score is...
- 25 to 15. - Okay!
- Let's move on to the third round. - Ryan.
- I have a bad feeling. - You are the last.
- Ryan. - Are we going?
- This is the next round. - Let's turn the tables.
Come on, Ryan.
Ready.
Go!
- Come on, Ryan. - We hit the red ones, right?
That's good!
This one. Right here.
Okay!
Who plays the Ddakji Game so desperately?
I have never seen a white man who is so good at this game.
That's good!
Why won't it flip over?
Ryan, Jong Kook is following you.
Where did it go?
The ddakji broke.
Good job. We are winning.
That's good. You are doing great, Ryan.
I see red everywhere.
- Yes! - That's good.
Yes!
10,
- 9, 8. 7, - One more.
- 6, 5, - One more.
- 4, 3, 2, 1. - Okay!
- 2, 1. - Ryan!
One.
Good job. Good job.
But he is not competitive!
Why did he play so hard?
He even broke one of the ddakjis.
- Why did he play so hard? - Most stars don't play so hard.
He broke a ddakji.
- How are you knees? - Why did he play so hard?
I am exhausted.
The final score.
It's 16 to 4.
With the score of 31 to 29, Team Actors won.
We won!
We win!
- We didn't go easy on them. - But it looks that way.
Seriously.
We didn't go easy on them.
Since Team Actor won two rounds,
there won't be more games.
It's time to choose and eat the snacks.
Everything's good, but I recommend the fish-shaped bun.
What about this? Is this good?
Maybe sugar?
Sugar candy.
- Korean candy. - Okay.
- I'm going with this then. - Okay.
- Good choice. - Yes?
- You can only take one. - I want that to swim into my body.
He has to try the fish-shaped bun.
- Fish burger? - Fish burger for the winter.
Fish burger?
- Who said "fish burger?" - Fish.
We'll do fish-shaped bun and the candy.
Try.
- Korean style. - Korean style.
This is good.
- Super good. - I really like this.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- It's warm. - It's lukewarm.
As long as it's good.
I really like fish-shaped buns.
This is like a waffle.
- Super good. - This is so yummy.
Love it.
Actually, no. I don't like it.
- He's good. - He's funny.
Until the end.
I want to eat.
- This is my favorite... - Fish-shaped bun.
winter snack.
It's different, no?
- Is it good? - Use your hand.
It's like something you've never...
- It's so interesting. - had before.
I really like that.
- What are these called? - It's not too sweet.
- Ggultarae. - Ggultarae.
- Yes. Ggultarae. - Ggultarae.
- Right, ggultarae. - Ggultarae.
This is the final game.
The ghosts' names should not go on this roulette...
if the other members don't want the penalty.
Pick four people who are unlikely to be ghosts and put...
- their names on the roulette. - I have no idea.
- Who do you think it is? - You can ask.
Who do you think did bad on purpose?
- He's the ghost. - Ghost?
- Ryan thinks you're the ghost. - 100 percent, guaranteed.
- Me too. - I agree.
- And he's the ghost. - Same here.
- Yes. Do you need any help? - Why?
- This is really frustrating. - That's how you feel?
- Are you the ghost? - No.
I'm human.
Old guy.
- You? - No, no.
- Ghost. - Yes.
- Yes. - Ghost?
He's a bad liar.
- Ghost? - I think...
- Jae Suk and Jong Kook. - Kim and you.
There's somebody on this team too.
Ryan's convinced.
- Let's go with that. - Okay. Go.
Don't do Haha.
- It's not me. - It's not him.
Bring in the penalty cards.
- Pick one. - Pick.
What will he pick?
As long as it's not the water cannon.
That's the worst.
- What is it? - What is it?
- A wig? - With a wig on?
- With a wig on? - Pressure point massage with a wig.
This is doable.
- This is good. - It's doable.
Good job. He's good.
He doesn't just hold it.
He's really good.
I really want Ryan.
You just have to spin the roulette now.
After spinning the roulette, if a ghost is one of the names...
that lands on the penalty spot, the ghosts win.
- Right. - Right.
If there are no ghosts, Running Man wins.
- Yes. - Yes.
For your information, on the roulette,
the ghosts...
- Are there ghosts? - Yes.
- There are? - Really? Who?
Is it Jong Kook?
- Jong Kook. - It's not me.
Should we spin it?
- 1, 2, 3. Go! - 2, 3. Go!
You said there are ghosts on this,
but they're not in every space.
It's pressure point massage wearing a wig.
It's Suk Jin and Haha.
It's Suk Jin, Haha, Kwang Soo, and So Min.
See?
People included are Suk Jin, Haha, Kwang Soo, and So Min.
- People who are included. - I only had one name tag.
That was close.
- Out of the four of them... - I think you're right.
- There are ghosts. - It's you.
- It's you, right? - It's So Min.
You're smiling. Look. You can't hide it. You look happy.
Are there any ghosts?
There are none.
- I told you. It's not me. - Is that good?
- Good. - Don't ever doubt me again.
- Who is it then? - Who is it?
- Today's ghosts are... - He's drinking water.
- It's Jae Suk. - Jae Suk and...
- Jae Suk and Jong Kook. - Right!
- That's what I said. - Me too.
- See? That's what I said. - You were precisely right.
He was really good.
You were precisely right.
- I knew it. - How did you know?
- How did Ryan know? - I just looked at him. You're it.
- How did she know? - I'm a psychic.
You two are...
ghosts today.
- What? - Pardon?
It's been a while since we've been on the same team.
We don't fail when we are on the same team.
We never fail when we are together.
But I feel bad.
Suk Jin lives closest to here.
You have to put it on properly.
Jong Kook,
you're not going to shut our business, right?
That was pretty intense.
- That was really bad. - Mr. Jong Kook.
It was for a short time,
- but they were really involved. - I agree.
We had so much fun.
Please say a few words for us.
- The best. - It was so much fun.
It's going to be very hard to do another TV show.
- We're going to be so bored. - I know.
Every other TV show after this is going to be terrible for us.
- Thank you. - It was so much fun.
Can we invite you again next time you come to Korea?
- Yes. - Of course.
Yes. Heck, yes.
We prepared gifts for them.
- Your name. - It's symbolic.
- This is our sign. - That's nice.
- Name tag. - We always use this.
Adria Arjona.
Melanie Laurent.
- Thank you so much. - I love it.
- Thank you, guys. - This is meaningful.
Set, go.
- Why? - This is really painful.
- This is so painful. - It's just for five seconds.
My hip will break.
- It's a massage. - It's good for your health.
Who becomes healthy like this?
Shut your mouth and just do it!
He doesn't care about our health. He's here to kill us.
- This is not good for your health. - That's not true.
- This is painful. - He's relaxing your muscles.
- Set, go. - I don't think so.
1, 2,
- He has to start again. - three,
- four, - Again.
Ready.
Set, go.
- Doesn't that hurt? - Two,
- He's enduring it. - three,
3, 4...
- He's incredible. - He's determined.
- Jae Suk flopped all over. - Wasn't that painful?
He took it seriously.
He was like a fish out of water.
The Ggannes Film Festival opened in Sangam-dong, Seoul.
- It's a film festival today. - Actors from Korea...
- and around the world are here. - It's Jun Hyo Seong and Yoyomi.
They're so funny.
- I can't get it on. - No!
- That was great acting. - This is a mess.
- Okay. Do it. - I won't lose.
- A blooper on TV? - A broadcasting accident?
Everybody's in danger.
- Why is she making that face? - Why did you do that?
This has to be the producer.
I got goosebumps.