- You're here. - Hey.
- Hello. - Hi.
This way. Go to the end.
- Stop that. - Why do you stand...
- at the end of the line these days? - What do you mean?
You're at the end of the line.
I think that wherever I stand becomes the new middle.
(It doesn't matter where he stands.)
(The center depends on where Jae Seok stands.)
- He's so confident. - "I'm the center."
- I'm confident. - That's nice.
But Haha is always right next to me.
- What? Who's next to you? - Haha is standing next to me.
- Someone is standing there? - Come on. Why did you say that?
(I don't see anyone there.)
- There he goes again. - Why?
- Jong Kook... - Where?
- Did he get started already? - Last week...
- That? He's still holding a grudge? - My gosh.
(Last week, the number of candies determined the rankings.)
(When they had to come together as a team,)
(Haha didn't submit any candies.)
(Without knowing this, Jong Kook gave Haha free candies.)
(Score)
(And Jong Kook had to face the penalty in the end.)
(Jong Kook had to pay for trusting Haha.)
- Who's there? - My gosh.
- You don't see anyone? - I got goosebumps.
- You didn't see him? - I got goosebumps.
He's determined to punish Haha today.
- He made everyone believe him. - Right.
- Luckily... - That's not true, Jong Kook.
I'm glad that he didn't show up this week.
- Jong Kook! - I'm glad that...
(Haha is gone from Jong Kook's heart.)
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook. - He didn't come today.
- Gosh, you're something else. - He's invisible.
- The invisible guy is crazy. - My gosh, seriously.
Jong Kook, there's someone on your left. Don't you see him?
No. Seok Jin, why are you standing so far away?
Come closer. You should come closer.
Haha, come over here. Haha.
- Seriously. - Today is not your day.
- Let's just finish the opening. - I can do it!
If I'm the spy today, I'll be dead.
This means that he will sever ties with me.
By the way, the episode will air on Se Chan's birthday.
- It's Se Chan's birthday? - Really?
- Thank you. - My gosh.
- Happy birthday! - Really? Thank you.
- Happy birthday. - You're celebrating too early.
(It's too early to celebrate your birthday.)
Okay.
- So there are two weeks left... - It's too early.
- until your birthday. - Let's skip this part.
- On TV... - So we don't need to talk about it.
Right. We don't.
- Can't you talk about it? - It's too early.
What's your plan for your birthday? Who will you spend it with?
- Do you have any plans? - Right.
Actually, I think I'll be alone on my birthday this year.
- I doubt it. - Why do you say that?
(Perhaps, you might not be alone on your birthday this year.)
- Spend it with So Min. - So Min won't throw a surprise.
- Right? - No, no.
No, I won't. Don't look at me like that.
- No. - No, I don't expect anything.
Hey, we should all meet up on your birthday.
- When? On my birthday? - Yes.
We should all meet up including So Min.
- Let's meet up. - I won't invite you.
- I'll spend it alone. - Hey.
Do you want to be invisible too?
- No, no. - Do you want to be invisible too?
(Do you want to be gone too?)
- Jong Kook. I'll invite you. - What? I'm right here.
- I saw that coming. - I'm here.
- I'm right here. - You know?
You traitor.
- This is scary. - I'll invite you to my birthday.
- That was hilarious. - That was scary.
You get to enjoy your birthdays when you're a bachelor.
Seok Jin, you should have a party soon.
Party...
- You'll have a party next week. - He'll pile up yakgwa on the side.
(At his birthday party, he'll pile up yakgwa on both sides.)
He ought to have a party.
- He'll have a lot of refreshments. - I'll wear hanbok.
- He'll invite singers. - I should go to his party.
- I can go. I can go as San Seul. - San Seul should come and sing.
- San Seul should come. - San Seul should go.
- He needs a pig's head. - My gosh.
Yu San Seul.
Before you begin your race today,
guests you'll be happy to see are waiting.
- I heard we're having guests. - All right.
First guest, please come on in.
Come on in.
(Who is the first guest?)
(Who is it?)
- It's Han Na. - Han Na.
(She's back after 3 weeks.)
(A beautiful and superb actress who's irreplaceable)
(I stay in bed a lot at home.)
(After revealing what she'd been up to,)
(she left after relaxing her stiff muscles with her unique dance.)
(And Han Na is back only after 3 weeks.)
- My gosh. - We see her every week.
- Han Na. - She's our friend.
- You're part of the show now. - Han Na.
- Han Na. - You're part of the show now.
- Nice to see you. - Isn't she part of the show now?
- Come here. - You look great.
- You look great these days. - Your outfits get nicer every time.
It hasn't been a month since Han Na was on our show.
- Right. - Three weeks.
- Three weeks? - It's only been three weeks.
It's better to be here than staying in bed at home.
(It's better to be here than staying in bed at home.)
(Han Na shared the hardship of lounging around at home.)
It's better to be here.
I used to lie down on my bed in my bedroom.
After that episode,
- I stay in the living room now. - You did? That's great.
- She's making progress. - Great.
Han Na was our first guest.
- Let's bring in the next guest. - Okay.
Sounds good.
Who is it?
(The second guest after Han Na)
(Surprised)
(Who is the guest that made their jaws drop open?)
(Lee Hee Jin of Baby V.O.X)
(This 1st-generation girl group was popular in Korea and abroad.)
(And the lead vocalist, Hee Jin, was in the center of popularity.)
(Now, she's actively performing as an actress in many dramas.)
My gosh, hello.
(Hee Jin who started her Act Two in life as an actress walks in.)
(I'm constantly reminded)
(Summoning "Killer" by Baby V.O.X)
- Baby V.O.X. - That's the song.
My gosh. Hee Jin.
It's so nice to see you.
- Hee Jin. - Hello.
- It's so nice to see you. - This is amazing.
- Hello. - Stand over there.
- It's her first time here. - It's so nice to see you.
I've never seen her in person.
- My gosh, Hee Jin is here. - She was in Baby V.O.X.
All right. This is her first time on Running Man.
- Really? - Yes.
Please say hello to the viewers.
Hello.
I'm Lee Hee Jin.
Hello. I'm Lee Hee Jin.
Her voice.
She feels awkward as it's been a long time.
- Right. I bet. I can understand it. - Right.
I should tell you guys this. Kan Mi Youn got married recently.
- Yes. - Everyone went to her wedding.
I heard you turned down...
- her offer to get the bouquet. - You did?
I wasn't confident that I could get married within six months.
If you don't, you can't get married for three years or something.
- Right. - There's a myth like that.
So you can keep getting the bouquet before your six months are up.
- What? - You can keep getting it.
- Are you renewing the term? - Yes, you are.
- You can renew it? - Don't let that stop you, Hee Jin.
- You can renew it. - Get the bouquet.
- Get another one within six months. - She can get another one.
- You can renew it. - And you can dry the flowers.
And if you burn them, it will be gone.
I'm serious.
(If you burn the dry flowers, the curse will be lifted.)
- I'm serious. - What was that?
- I'm serious. - I didn't know.
- You can do that. - She's spreading...
- a weird spell. - What...
Why would you burn the flowers?
We talked about Mi Youn's wedding briefly.
- There's another guest. - There's one more?
Let's continue with the third guest. Let's bring in the guest.
(It's time to meet the third guest.)
(The guest will enter after Han Na and Hee Jin.)
(Who is this friendly face?)
- It's YooA. - She's in OH MY GIRL.
(OH MY GIRL is beloved for their mystical and innocent themes.)
(And YooA is the lead vocalist in the group.)
(And singing isn't the only thing she excels in.)
(With her groovy moves and intense gaze,)
(she's famous as the main dancer of the group.)
(Unexpected side of this adorable girl)
OH MY GIRL. She's in OH MY GIRL.
Hello.
- She has such a small face. - She's the best.
She's the best dancer.
YooA, is this your first time on our show?
Yes. I'm really nervous right now.
- Really? - I don't know if I'm shaking...
because I'm cold or because I'm nervous.
- She said she's cold, Kwang Soo. - Pardon?
(She said she's cold, Kwang Soo.)
- She's said she's cold. - Right.
He must be colder. He's only wearing this coat.
You used to take off your jackets, but you don't do that nowadays.
I'm coming down with a cold too.
- I'm coming down with a cold. - Seriously.
He said he's coming down with a cold.
- He's firm. - Right.
- But still. - Pardon?
But still.
Will you be happy if I take this off for you?
What are you doing, Kwang Soo? She's cold.
- What are you doing? She's cold. - What?
- She said she's cold. - What are you doing?
I mean...
What about Sun Bin?
(Starting to take off his coat)
- Are you nice to all the women? - Unbelievable.
- When you have a girlfriend? - You guys are jerks.
(You guys are jerks.)
You are so bad.
(These bad guys are laughing.)
Teasing Kwang Soo is so much fun.
- Kwang Soo. - But...
(I'm fine.)
- All right. - It's the best.
Let's bring in the next guest.
- Come on out. - The next guest is a man.
- Really? - My gosh. Ji Hyo.
- So Min. - Both of you look so happy...
- to meet him. - So Min, no pushing back your hair?
She's pushing back her hair again.
(Getting ready to be charming)
Come on out.
(Here's the last guest.)
(The female members of the show are anticipating to meet the guest.)
(Who is the male guest?)
Hello.
- Yoo Byung Jae. - It's Yoo Byung Jae.
(The sure bet on variety shows, Yoo Byung Jae)
(He fearlessly pinched Jong Kook's cheek.)
(I hate getting my cheek pinched the most.)
(He was thoroughly beloved by Jong Kook after that.)
(Hello, I'm here!)
(I see. It was Byung Jae.)
Byung Jae.
- It's been a while. - I haven't seen you for a while.
Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Hey, Byung Jae. - He's hilarious.
He pretended to be cheerful.
He's not cheerful.
He's not that cheerful.
Back then, you were just yourself, but I think you've changed.
Yes. I watched Heo Kyeong Hwan's performance on the show last week.
(Yes. I watched Heo Kyeong Hwan's performance on the show last week.)
(Byung Jae felt the danger of not preparing for a variety show.)
- I wanted to show a new side of me. - That's why.
By the way, you look like a celebrity now.
- What made you say that? - I see NASA written here.
- And you dyed your hair yellow. - Right.
I've had this hair for two years.
Really? I'm sorry.
- Right. - My gosh.
- Everyone here is busy. - That's right.
- That happens, you know. - My gosh.
Shouldn't Byung Jae and YooA stand together?
Right, they should. Kwang Soo, switch your spot with him.
- You should switch spots. - Me and him?
Right.
- Look at the size of their faces. - My gosh.
(A difference between a man who became a celebrity and a natural?)
Come over here.
- He told Byung Jae to move. - That's fascinating.
It's fascinating, right?
On "Star King", they did this CG.
- Enlarging the face? - But...
Seriously. YooA's face...
- is too small. - She has such a small face.
- It's too small. - It's this big.
Her face could disappear.
Let's talk about what they have been up to these days.
- By the way, Han Na was... - Yes.
on our show three weeks ago.
We don't have any updates.
(Nothing new happened yet.)
Moving on, we'll talk about Hee Jin's recent life.
Do you have a boyfriend?
- No. - I see.
Actually,
when you were on variety shows before, people asked this a lot.
If you had an ideal type for men...
- Right. - or who your ideal type was.
When you talked about your ideal types, how did you answer it?
- I only mentioned one person. - Who?
- Who was it? - Go Soo.
(It's Go Soo.)
David Go.
- He's really handsome. - Go Soo.
I guess you cared about men's looks when you were young.
(I did.)
You cared about that.
Even men can agree to that.
- He was everyone's ideal type. - I agree.
Do you have another ideal type?
If you don't have one, you can say so.
- I have an ideal type. - You do?
Can you tell us?
(Who is her current ideal type of men?)
(Go Soo with chiseled facial features was her idea type.)
(She cared about looks before. What is her ideal type now?)
Someone who won't cheat.
(Someone who won't cheat.)
- Someone who won't cheat. - Right. That's so true.
She was burned before.
- Now... - She got cheated on.
- Now, her ideal type is detailed. - She was.
- It's not about looks. - It's detailed now.
It's not about looks now.
- She doesn't care about looks. - Exactly.
- I can tell she was hurt before. - Right. She was hurt.
She was hurt before.
- "Cheat". - That's the first one. No cheating.
- Someone who's hardworking. - A hardworking man.
Also, I don't want him...
to intrude or bother me when I'm working.
All right.
- I don't know who her ex is. - Who is he?
- He bothered her. - Who is that?
- And he cheated on her. - This is hard.
- That was terrible. - That was his ex.
Should we curse him out for you?
Yes.
You scumbag!
(You scumbag!)
Don't cheat on women, you jerk!
You piece of trash.
(That hits the spot.)
- I got into the role. - Was that enough?
(As he watches her, he's reminded of...)
He doesn't cheat.
(Pointing at Se Chan)
You won't bother me.
You work hard at your job.
- Yang Se Chan! - Yang Se Chan!
(The perfect ideal type for realistic women, Yang Se Chan)
- Hey, it might work out for them. - This is crazy.
Hey, I think you really might start dating.
- What's going on between you two? - Stop it. Stop pushing us.
Don't toy with So Min.
(Is this strictly for business? Or do they actually have feelings?)
How could you go along this act?
- I'm tearing up. - That's the worst.
Jae Seok, she should dance about her breakup.
- Should she? Hee Jin. - Yes.
Han Na did this breakup dance three weeks ago on our show.
- She really sent it. - Yes.
This is the dance you do when you went through a breakup.
Demonstrate for her, Han Na.
This is Gook Jin's dance.
She was covering one eye because tears were falling.
- But you show the other side. - Show the other side.
You need to show the pretty side.
- Show your pretty face. - My good side is the left side.
In 1, 2.
(Suddenly dancing)
(Starting her breakup dance)
(Gook Ju's club dance was reinterpreted traditionally.)
- Han Na. - Good job. Nice.
(Dancing stiffly)
Hee Jin can pull it off too.
- She can pull it off. - Nice.
- That's how you dance. - She pulled it off.
- The breakup dance was nice. - Well done.
- Breakup dance. - Breakup dance.
All right.
- I always say this. - This is funny.
I hope you can meet great guys.
- Half of our world are men. - Right.
- That's right! - That's right!
- That's right! I can do it. - You can do it.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
- Yang Se Chan! - Yang Se Chan!
(The man of her new love)
(Showing his teeth)
He won't cheat.
- He works hard. - He works hard.
And he doesn't bother you.
- Yang Se Chan! - Yang Se Chan!
(The ideal type for women who had been hurt, Yang Se Chan)
Don't get the wrong idea.
Se Chan is the only single guy on our show.
- I see. - Great.
- What about me? - Hey, Jong Kook.
- I'm single too. - Is he an old man?
(I've been single for 44 years.)
- Do you want to be invisible? - You...
Hey, make her invisible too.
That was something else.
- Don't try to put me on his list. - Hey.
I can't see you.
Are you doing that on your own?
Let's interview YooA next.
- Did you know this? - What?
She's the main dancer of OH MY GIRL.
- I know that. - Really?
- You didn't know, did you? - She's the main dancer.
- Really? - Isn't your brother a good dancer?
- Really? - Yes, he's a choreographer.
- My gosh. - Really?
YooA.
Can you dance for us?
- Sure. - Really?
- Yes. - Please demonstrate.
- She's really good. She's good. - My goodness.
- I can't wait. - She's very good.
I didn't know she was the main dancer.
(The queen of dancers among idol singers will dance soon.)
(Powerful and energetic)
She's so cool.
This is really cool.
Look at her gaze.
(Taking big strides)
(Surprised)
(Wrapping up with an edgy dance move)
- There's more. - There's more?
(It's not over yet.)
(Wait, this song is...)
- Isn't that Michael Jackson's? - It's Michael Jackson's.
("Smooth Criminal" by Michael Jackson)
I love Michael Jackson.
My gosh, Michael Jackson's song.
(She recreates the genius dancer, Michael Jackson's performance.)
That was so cool.
(Perfect technique)
(Summoning back Michael Jackson to 2019)
(Utterly excited)
(Her legendary performance was good enough to be compared to...)
(the king of pop songs, Michael Jackson's performance.)
(She's indeed the queen of dancers among idol singers.)
Hold on.
- You know what? - You're a great dancer.
I got goosebumps when I was watching this touching performance.
- Why? - I saw it too.
- Did you see it? - Yes.
When we were cheering like crazy, Seok Jin went,
"Hey, what's your name again?"
(Hey, what's your name again?)
- I heard that too. - My gosh.
(It was after when she was done.)
Hey, what's your name again?
- It's YooA. - YooA?
(I need to remember her.)
I wanted to know her name.
- I wanted to remember her name. - YooA.
And she was really nice about it.
"It's YooA."
- YooA. - I'm a huge fan now.
- She's the best. I told you. - So...
- YooA... - Yes.
When she heard that Hee Jin would be on the show with her,
- Baby V.O.X's song? - Really?
- she prepared a performance. - Really?
- I love the song. - Will you join her?
- It's been so long. - Awesome.
- I want to see it. - YooA prepared this performance.
- Let's check it out. - It's this.
- Play the song. - This...
YooA will be performing?
(Anticipating)
("Ya Ya Ya" by Baby V.O.X)
It's "Ya Ya Ya".
(She's happy to hear her song.)
(Looking cheerful and bubbly)
- I really love this song. - This was the song.
(Trying to remember the choreography)
(The original singer dances.)
(She swings her arm just like the old days.)
She's the original singer.
- You remember it. - She's the original singer.
(It was a beloved song back then.)
She's moving forward.
- She's moving forward. - She's moving forward.
(Bringing back the 90s)
This is it!
That was hard.
(Their performance brought them back to the 90s.)
She's really good.
(With the nostalgic performances, her interview ends.)
It's been a while.
All right.
- Byung Jae. - Yes.
I heard that you feel especially intimidated...
when you meet Jong Kook.
Why aren't you standing next to me today?
If he did,
- he'd be in Jong Kook's arms. - Right.
- Jong Kook likes guys like him. - Right.
- I like Byung Jae or Shorry. - Shorry.
- Shorry. - People who fit in his arms.
- Back then, I liked guys like Haha. - Right. Exactly.
(Invisible wall)
- But you don't like him now? - I don't like him now.
(Jong Kook, I'm still here!)
I used to hang out with him.
By the way,
- He never looked at me today. - we...
(I keep seeing something.)
- Yes, that's right. - Did you watch that?
Actually, I have never met Jong Kook...
- in private. - We have never hung out.
And the only time we talked was...
I was talking to DinDin...
- on the phone at night. - Go on.
Jong Kook said...
that DinDin had to hang up because he had to play soccer.
(DinDin has to play soccer now. Hang up the phone now.)
- Soccer. - It was Thursday, right?
- Futsal? - He was talking to Byung Jae...
during our break.
I asked who it was, and he said Byung Jae.
Then I yelled, "Hang up!"
- You heard that. - But it didn't sound like...
DinDin wanted to play soccer.
(Is that so?)
Are you coming this week?
Yes, I'll be there tomorrow.
Yes, I ought to go!
(I'll be there no matter what.)
- You've been absent a lot. - I've come to my senses.
Without Jong Kook,
more than 90 percent of the teammates would leave.
It's unbelievable.
If Jong Kook says that he's not showing up...
in the group chat,
everyone else bails out as well.
If Jong Kook says he's coming,
everyone else says that they are too.
He's like a bell.
That's amazing.
- He's the center of the club. - I know.
If I don't go, they yield the field to another team.
- Right. - If he goes, we all go.
(Everyone shows up if he does.)
They follow him.
It's been a while,
but how about we do an acrostic poem?
That sounds good.
- He's good at them. - Right.
He's amazing.
What should we do?
I'm fine with anything.
- How about Jee Seok Jin? - Sure.
- All right. - I tend...
- to be quick. - All right.
- We need to hurry. - All right.
Let's hurry and do one with his name.
- Jee. - Last week,
- Seok. - I saw his social network.
And he looked like a bachelor.
He watched him on TV.
Let's do Se Chan now.
I'm sure it'll be difficult.
- Yang. - Se Hyeong's brother,
- Se. - Se Chan is...
- Chan. - the fifth wheel on this show.
(It's hurtful, but it's true.)
- He's good. - He really is.
- That didn't take long. - It's because...
all the other members intimidate you.
And Yeong Ja intimidates me "Omniscient Interfering View".
We're both like that.
That's how we work.
When working with seniors, it feels the worst...
- to walk on eggshells. - Right.
For example, if you fail to play along with them...
Right.
- You were like that just now. - Really?
(You were like that too.)
I can't believe you told him that.
You'll only dispirit him.
- He's... - It's better that he did.
- It's better... - I was unsure.
- It's better to tell him. - It's better.
- We're close enough. - Right.
(Byung Jae looks dispirited.)
- All right. - He's good.
That's it.
I've prepared acrostic poems for all of them.
It's over. You can do it again later.
Make one with my name when we're on the bus.
- Do it on the bus? - Yes.
- Do we not have one today? - We're shooting here.
We're not getting on a bus?
Don't be ridiculous.
Let him take the bus by himself.
(He can ride it alone.)
(Jong Kook still has a grudge.)
- That's enough. - That's enough.
That's enough.
- You're killing him. - Do I need to cry?
He wanted to ride one, so I just told him to.
I'm so glad it's not me.
He has a grudge.
(Poor Haha.)
For today's race, you can win if you invest well.
It's called Run to You: Project to Attract Investments Race.
Including the four guests,
it'll be an individual match among the 12 of you.
You each have 10 coins each.
The individual with the most amount of R coins wins.
They will receive a reward.
The individual with the fewest coins...
will receive the water cannon as their penalty.
- It's freezing today. - You'd be dead.
You'd freeze.
(It's a very cold day.)
Four individuals may participate per event.
There will be a total of three rounds.
The rest of you...
may invest as many coins as you wish in one member.
If the member you invested in wins,
you'll receive the amount that was invested.
The rest will lose their coins.
Let's get changed and go inside.
- Okay. - Okay!
(They need to be smart about their investments.)
We'll begin the first round.
Okay.
- It's comfortable. - Do you have a cloth?
It's here.
(The staff has it.)
(Staring)
Thank you.
They all want to give it to him.
What is it?
Why are you jealous again?
- What is it? - My gosh.
- My gosh. - You don't even have lenses.
You should be nice to them all the time.
(Ever since Yu San Seul debuted, Seok Jin has been jealous.)
He's so jealous.
Byung Jae looks like...
- a robot vacuum charging. - Right?
He looks like that.
Aren't you uncomfortable?
I'm not that comfortable.
"I'm not that comfortable."
On our way in here, I asked if he liked soccer.
He said he hated it.
(He defended himself.)
- I see. - He didn't give you a chance.
- No, he didn't. - Well done.
- I really don't like it. - Good job.
Then Jong Kook won't ask you anymore.
- No. - No, he won't.
- I won't force him. - Right.
Let me explain once again.
We surveyed 100 individuals.
For example, if we asked them which one of you...
would jump rope the best, they'd rank you guys.
The first place will be compensated twofold,
The fourth place will be threefold.
- Okay. - So on, so forth.
The last place will be compensated tenfold.
You all have 10 coins each.
Let us begin.
- All right. - What is it?
Let me reveal the members...
who will participate in this match.
- What? Jong Kook came in first. - What?
- What? - Kwang Soo...
- and Haha are there too. - Kwang Soo...
- is fivefold. - He's fivefold.
This definitely has something to do with strength.
- Why am I tenfold? - Kwang Soo is strong too.
Why am I tenfold?
(These 4 will participate.)
Haha is the last.
Does this have to do with something scary?
Maybe it's about trivia.
Trivia?
- Trivia? - It doesn't make sense for him.
- What do you mean? - Don't you think so?
- I'm good with trivia. - Really?
I think it's trivia-related.
Ji Hyo and Se Chan both came in fourth place.
- We were in 4th place? - 4th?
- I don't think this is... - It's not about trivia.
- about trivia. - It's not.
I'll bet all my money on that.
- I'm sure that's not it. - If they're in fourth place...
It's definitely not about trivia.
I was wrong.
- You're right. - Right.
First place was Jong Kook.
Second place was Jae Seok.
- What? - Third place was Byung Jae.
Sixth place was Kwang Soo.
Haha came in eighth place alongside the others.
The others as in?
Hee Jin, Han Na, YooA,
- and Seok Jin. - We all came in eighth place?
(He's upset.)
- Long jumping. - Amount of muscles?
- I think I know. - What is it?
It's... How should I put it?
Maybe it's about masculine strength?
(He's happy to have come 1st place.)
But seeing how I came in second place...
(I think he's right.)
Thigh wrestling?
- Something about masculinity? - Masculine strength.
Hey.
I have three kids.
Stamina.
- My stamina is... - I beat you.
(He cuts him off.)
That's why it's odd.
Oh, that's why?
Although I'm only twofold,
if you invest a lot, you'll get a lot.
What?
(Is he coercing them to invest in him?)
- What was that? - Were you threatening us?
Why did he sound like a gambler?
If you bet a lot...
He talks like Agwi.
Isn't it best for everyone?
(He's the Agwi of Running Man.)
- All right. - I have no idea.
So Min, go first.
The ones who are participating can't bet, right?
- No. - No. But if you win,
you'll get five coins per investor.
(They can't bet, but they can gain more coins if they win.)
- They need to try to win. - Right.
(Will the investors successfully bet and strike gold?)
- Who will you bet on? - One coin for Haha.
(She's very careful.)
- That's fine, right? - Yes.
I'd like to bet on Kwang Soo.
(He trusts Kwang Soo.)
One coin.
- All right. - What is it?
You were a scaredy-cat, weren't you?
Weren't you?
- You bet a coin, right? - One coin?
Ji Hyo.
I bet eight coins on Jong Kook.
I bet nine coins on Jong Kook.
(They bet on Jong Kook who seems the most likely to win.)
(All of them finish betting.)
(Jong Kook, Byung Jae, Kwang Soo, Haha)
I will reveal the event.
For this first round,
Jong Kook, Haha, Byung Jae, and Kwang Soo will participate.
(What is the event?)
Withstanding Pain, King of Thighs.
- No! - Come on!
(Withstanding Pain, King of Thighs)
(The contestants have mixed feelings.)
(Hee Jin betted on Haha.)
- Jong Kook will win for sure. - Come, come, come...
- Come on! - Right.
You can do it.
- You can do it, right? - Did you bet on me?
- Gosh. - Jong Kook will win for sure.
I don't feel pain.
Are we using our hands?
Yes, you are.
Haha's rank is unbelievable.
The survey was precise.
I only received one bet?
I will withstand the pain for that person.
- I'll do that. - You only got one bet?
I'll withstand the pain.
- Let me explain the rules. - Okay.
There will be four chairs.
You'll do rock-paper-scissors to decide on the order.
You'll hit the thigh of the person sitting next to you.
You'll roll a die.
You can only hit them if you get an even number.
Please play rock-paper-scissors to decide on the order.
- The order is important. - It's the most important.
(This game will determine who gets hit by whom.)
- First place will... - They'll sit last.
Okay.
- First place will sit last. - Got it.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo comes 1st place.)
- Okay! - You can do it!
This is all for that one investor!
I'll withstand the pain!
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Haha wins.)
(He is determined to win.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Byung Jae comes last.)
Byung Jae, sit first.
(Byung Jae picks his seat first.)
I'm next, right?
(Jong Kook sits down.)
(What is this?)
(He's trying to grasp the situation.)
- Hold on. - Jong Kook.
- He sat well. - You'll sit last since you won.
- No. - The winner will sit last.
- No, ask them about the direction. - The rules aren't correct.
The one who won...
You volunteered to sit last.
But we already agreed that the winner would sit last.
That's exactly where it's wrong.
Winning rock-paper-scissors is a good thing.
- Then you can go first. - Right.
He can pick first.
- The winner should pick first. - Right.
Pick your seat.
(Kwang Soo picks 1st.)
- Second place. - Are we going this way?
Are we?
(He's meticulous.)
All right.
I should sit here.
No, I should.
(What are they doing?)
Since we're going this way?
What are you three scheming?
What are you talking about?
The order has already been decided.
Jae Seok, what am I supposed to do?
(His fate has been decided.)
What do I need to do so that I won't get hit by him?
Let's do this. Jong Kook can start first.
- 1st place can sit 1st. - Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
I guess you can see Haha now.
- What? - I guess you can see Haha now.
- He's becoming more visible, right? - Yes.
- I can see his form. - His form?
- Yes. - You mean, like a ghost?
I'm starting to see his form.
- So first place is... - How about Kwang Soo decides?
- Do that. - Let the winner decide.
- Let's do that. - Okay.
Okay, let's do that.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Scissors, Rock)
(The winner is chosen.)
- Decide on the order. - Go ahead.
- Are you sure? - I'm going to endure it.
We'll go this way and this is where I'll sit.
- Haha, you can sit here. - Thanks.
- Hold on. - Is this Kwang Soo's seat?
(Jong Kook can sit here.)
- Jong Kook can sit here. - Right.
Who's left will sit next to me.
- You can sit here. - What?
Fine, I'll endure the pain.
Kwang Soo, good luck.
- Good luck. - It's all in the dice anyway.
(Just trust me.)
- It's all in the dice. - Jong Kook, isn't he annoying?
- Right. - Just don't get caught.
Jong Kook answered my question.
(Jong Kook answered my question.)
You can only hit the other person if you roll an even number.
(They must roll an even number to hit the person next to them.)
(Kwang Soo goes first.)
(Drop the dice!)
Four!
(An even number!)
- Haha can't endure this. - You can do it, Haha.
- Good luck. - You're tenfold.
You must endure the pain.
Pork belly will be on me.
He offered pork belly.
Think about it.
[VIU Ver] SBS E480 Running Man
"Run to You: Project to Attract Investments Race"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Kwang Soo adds a twist...)
(and aims for the other leg.)
(Grunt)
Wait, he just grunted.
- He grunted. - I heard a grunt.
Okay!
- A grunt. - You're out.
(Haha is eliminated because of a single grunt.)
Kwang Soo went for the other leg.
- He hit me right here. - A single grunt.
(Forgive me. Next up is Byung Jae.)
Go, Byung Jae.
- An even number! - It's an even number.
(Byung Jae also rolls an even number.)
- Byung Jae used to box, you know. - Good luck!
He might injure his hand while slapping Jong Kook.
- Look at his fragile hand. - You're right.
My eldest son's hand is that size.
- It'll hurt. - His thighs seem firm.
He has no chance.
(Byung Jae slaps him with all his might.)
That was cute.
- He yelped. - Byung Jae made a sound.
- Right. - Next time.
- He should be out. - That's not the rule.
He definitely yelped.
- But I was the one slapping him. - There's no point to this.
I told you it'd hurt your hand more.
That's right.
(The dice has been rolled.)
(Please let it be an odd number.)
Gosh.
- It's an even number. - An even number.
- He's wearing jeans. - Let's hear a loud slap.
- Oh, no. - Make it sound loud.
Oh, dear.
- Let's speed things up. - It's over.
(He'll soon be executed.)
I'm holding onto him.
(Slap!)
Hold on...
(Kwang Soo, breathe!)
He kind of made a sound.
Yes, like this.
Is that so?
- Are you all right? - He's out.
You're out.
Right...
(Hold on a second.)
- Are you all right? - He's out.
- He's out. - Let's continue.
His thigh is throbbing.
He's out.
(The dice is rolled.)
- He needs a taste of it. - Okay, we're done.
(It's another even number.)
I feel so bad for you.
(Byung Jae, stay strong.)
He'll probably scream before Jong Kook raises his hand.
(Something just jolted.)
(Yelling in pain)
Yes. Go, Jong Kook!
- Kim Jong Kook! - Seriously?
- Kim Jong Kook. - Kim Jong Kook.
- Nice. - Okay.
- All right. - What a sweet win.
Did you know?
Investing in Jong Kook meant that you'd win double.
Four people bet on him.
(They each doubled what they invested.)
Meanwhile, Jong Kook wins 5 coins per person which is 20.
Okay, good.
I bet on Kwang Soo for nothing.
It's impossible to endure.
I only bet one though.
(He's not much of a risk-taker.)
Two people bet on Kwang Soo and Haha each,
but no one bet on Byung Jae.
What?
(But no one bet on Byung Jae.)
(Then who did Byung Jae play the game for?)
Really?
Then what did you endure the pain for?
I did it for the people counting on me.
What a shame.
(Current Number of Coins)
(Jong Kook is in the lead with 30 coins.)
(Hee Jin is in last place with 8 coins.)
It's now time for our next game.
We always order from this place when we're in this neighborhood.
- Yes! - The jjamppong!
- It's to die for. - The Chinese restaurant.
- It's truly amazing. - It's the best.
We will order you lunch,
but first, you'll split into two teams...
and play Say Food Name at the End.
(Say Food Name at the End)
- Okay. - The losing team...
will have to pay for their lunch with R coins.
- What? - You'll take our coins?
Yes, you'll pay up 10 coins in total.
- That's a lot. - It's not a small number.
- I only have 10. - So...
Please split into two teams.
- We'll play Race of Wits. - Sure.
We'll play Race of Wits to decide the teams.
How many games will it take though?
- What? - How many games will that take?
He should see a specialist regarding this obsession.
How many are we?
- There are 12 of us. - There are 12 of us.
Then the first six will form a team.
- The first 6? - The first 6 to lose?
Yes, that's right.
- That's not so bad. - Right?
Let's begin then. And go.
(They begin Race of Wits to decide the teams.)
- 1. - 2.
- 3. - 4.
(They quickly reach 4.)
(The others...)
(only glance at one another.)
(Silent...)
- Hold on. - This team...
Is no one standing up because of the current members?
That must be it.
No one's standing up because they don't like this team.
Hold on.
- Is that why? - It really is a game of wits.
We all could tell that it was a sinking ship.
Guys, sit down for a second.
- This is wrong. - Why?
Why? You four are a team.
No one is willing to join us.
Hold on.
The game isn't over yet.
Ji Hyo!
You're the one who suggested the game.
- Fine, have a seat. - You only need two more members.
This is odd.
- How about this instead? - Go on.
- We have to try it first. - The first six to lose are a team.
Okay, sounds good.
The first six to lose will be a team.
Good. Let's begin.
- 1. - 2.
Okay, that's two.
- 3. - 4.
Five.
- Six. - Okay.
- Are they a team? - No.
- The first six to lose. - That's right.
Seven.
- 8. - 8.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo said 8 at the same time.)
- You and Jong Kook. - That's two.
Is it because you wanted to team up with him?
You wanted to be on his team.
- Wait... - It was kind of obvious.
You were slightly late.
It was obvious.
You think I did it on purpose?
(Kwang Soo's eyes are on Jong Kook.)
(He repeated Jong Kook's number and pretended to be upset.)
- You think I did it on purpose? - Was it to be on his team?
- No, I was going to say eight. - Okay, fine.
All right. You two are a team.
- Have a seat then. - Is this how it'll be?
- Get ready... - The losers will be on our team.
Right.
And go!
- 1. - 1.
- And go! - 1.
(Applicants make a rush for it.)
I said it too.
- Really? - Me too.
- I said it too. - Me too.
- Get over here. - This game was a bad idea.
The rest will join me.
We need one more on our team.
Come on!
- We'll send one over. - We need one more.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The one who loses will join our team.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Han Na and Seok Jin lose.)
(Seok Jin loses!)
Nice.
(And so the teams are decided.)
(The teams)
So now you'll play Say Food Name at the End.
The rules are just like that of a word relay.
The last person just has to name a food at the end.
You win if you go around in a circle twice.
Can the words only be in three Korean syllables?
Yes, that's right.
However, the food doesn't have to follow that rule.
- Right. - No words can be repeated.
- Right. - Let's wish us luck!
- Go! - Let's do this.
This is for the jjamppong.
(What?)
(They're constantly reminded of the song.)
- What was that? Gosh. - That came from nowhere.
Why did you suddenly sing that? How about "Get Up"?
You're using up your energy.
Nice.
- We'll begin. - Let's do this!
(She's embarrassed by her song from 20 years ago.)
- We'll give you the first word. - Right.
Let's do a practice round first.
- Kung, kung, kung - Kung, kung, kung
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta - Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Say a food name at the end - Say a food name at the end
Gorilla.
Radio.
(Gorilla, Radio...)
Audio.
(Gorilla, Radio, Audio...)
Arcade.
Laboratory.
(Gorilla, Radio, Audio, Arcade, Laboratory...)
(He has to name a food that starts with "shil" in Korean.)
Struggling soup.
(Gorilla, Radio, Audio, Arcade, Laboratory, Struggling soup)
(What's a struggling soup?)
What on earth is a struggling soup?
Seriously?
Does that exist?
Is it a soup you make while in a struggle?
(It can also be a dialect for "wildcat.")
- In an altercation. - Bring me the soup!
(Arguing)
- A struggle... - What is that?
I think I ate it in Jincheon.
Get up from that seat.
- Come on. - Go again.
Here we go then. Ready, begin.
- Kung, kung, kung - Kung, kung, kung
Stay with basic words.
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta - Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Say a food name at the end - Say a food name at the end
(The first syllable is "bu.")
Like father, like son.
(Like father, like son)
(Like father,)
(like son)
You could've said "parents."
Your turn is over now.
Gosh.
- He's sick, that's why. - Make way.
What do you mean he's sick?
He falters when the camera is only on him.
Anyway, move.
- He's sick, that's all. - Let's sit.
What?
- Are you guys ready? - Yes.
Here we go. Ready, begin.
- Kung, kung, kung - Kung, kung, kung
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta - Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Say a food name at the end - Say a food name at the end
(The first syllable is "jang.")
Jang Su Won.
Monkey.
Barbershop.
Head manager.
Im Chang Jung.
(Jang Su Won, Monkey, Barbershop, Head manager, Im Chang Jung)
(She only needs to name a food that starts with "jung" in Korean.)
A delicious snail.
(Incorrect!)
(A delicious snail.)
Why not?
- What was that? - It makes sense.
It doesn't. It's our turn now.
Why isn't that allowed?
Hold on. Why isn't that allowed?
What if I said, "a snail dish made with love"?
- Sounds good to me. - We should swap seats.
Give us another chance...
because we didn't get a practice round.
No can do.
We never practiced.
- But we... - You're out.
We started right away!
(We started without practice!)
(They're shoved away.)
(Scared)
- We started right away. - You're right.
We started right away.
- Let us try one more time. - We didn't get to practice.
- Hey. - Guys.
We didn't lose.
- It's just that he's persuasive. - Right.
(If you say so.)
- It's not that... - Are you sure?
- we're scared of Jong Kook. - Of course not.
- You're not intimidated, are you? - Are you?
(Never)
Jong Kook has a point.
Start.
- Kung, kung, kung - Kung, kung, kung
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta - Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Say a food name at the end - Say a food name at the end
- One, two... - Jee Seok Jin.
Jeans... Hold on.
(Jeans?)
Qin Shi Huang! You punk!
I'm sorry.
You're out.
You messed up last week, and you make another mistake?
- But it makes him notice me now. - You're happy?
He notices my mistake.
- Start. - Slowly.
- Kung, kung, kung - But it shouldn't be too slow.
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta - Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Say a food name at the end - Say a food name at the end
Jun Ji Hyun.
Hyun Jung Hwa.
Bathroom.
Silmido.
Lunchbox.
"Rak"?
(What's a food name that starts with "rak"?)
You gave her "rak"?
Lock and Lock...
What food name starts with "rak"?
Why did you have to give her "rak"?
- How could you... - Seriously.
Also, after saying that word, he looked so cold.
"It's up to you."
"I'm innocent."
YooA, I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry. - He said,
"Rak, rak, rak."
You must be so hurt.
- I'm sorry. - How could you do this to me?
You guys are out.
Start.
(Thanks to Jae Seok's word choice, Team Jong Kook gets another chance.)
- Kungkungtta, kungkungtta - Kungkungtta, kungkungtta
- Say a food name at the end - Say a food name at the end
Squid.
Fish shop.
Fir tree.
Risky move.
Swimming pool.
Eel soup.
(They've finally finished one round.)
Rice bowl.
"Reut"?
("Reut"?)
(What 3-syllable word starts with "reut"?)
Hey!
I said, "eel soup!"
- That word ends the game. - Are you on our team?
- You could have said, "rice thief." - Thank you.
There are so many words that start with "rice."
So Min saved us with "rice bowl."
Let's play one last round.
- Okay. - One last round.
It's the last round.
(The team that says more words winds.)
(Team Jong Kook said 7 words. How will Team Jae Seok do?)
Mortgage.
Shortcut.
Travel partner.
Knee.
(Pak?)
(Fail)
- Hey. - Pak?
What word starts with "pak"?
Park Chan Ho.
(There is a word.)
Park Ji Sung.
- Pronunciation is key. - Right.
Okay.
Too bad.
You guys got to the fifth word, so team Jong Kook wins.
(R Coin Distribution)
Byung Jae, Hee Jin, and YooA, eat a lot.
- Enjoy. - Enjoy.
Let's eat.
It smells nice and smoky.
(Slurping)
It tastes so good.
- It's delicious. - It tastes so good.
Byung Jae, do you have a girlfriend?
Not at the moment.
When did you break up?
- It's been a few years. - A few years?
Byung Jae is a nice guy.
Byung Jae is amazing.
But no one seems to want to set him up with anyone.
(That's on point.)
- Is that it? - All you say is, "He's amazing."
- What kind of girl do you like? - I like...
Even though I might not be able to meet my type...
- I like the cute type. - The cute type?
- So Min is very cute. - She is.
(So Min is a perfect example of a cute girl.)
- She is, but... - Are you talking about appearances?
I'm not talking about a girl who looks cute...
- or tries to do cute things. - Then?
I like a girl who is a bit clumsy.
So Min is very clumsy.
- She's really clumsy. - I'm very clumsy.
That's not what I mean.
(That's not what I mean.)
I mean...
I like a girl who does her best but still is clumsy.
- That's So Min. - She has food all over her face.
That's not what I mean either.
(Determined)
I like a girl who is cute but doesn't know she is.
- I don't. - She doesn't.
She really doesn't.
You're not my type.
(Straightforward)
(He turns her down.)
I like cute girls.
You're not his type.
I don't like guys who have a beard either.
I'm relieved.
(The lunch break is over.)
Let me announce who will play the second game.
Please look at the board.
It's too hard.
- What? - Ji Hyo?
- Jae Seok is at the top? - Ten times for Se Chan?
Could it be a quiz?
- It's a quiz! No. - It's a quiz.
It can't be a quiz.
- It's not a quiz. - No.
The viewers don't know her well.
Jae Seok came in first place,
- Ji Hyo in fifth place, - Fifth place?
Hee Jin in seventh place,
and Se Chan in 12th place.
- He's at the bottom. - One by one...
Haha, you go first.
(Haha will invest in a member first.)
(How many coins will he invest in who?)
(After thinking for a moment...)
I invest nine coins in Jae Seok.
I invest two coins in Ji Hyo.
(Meanwhile, So Min...)
Hey.
Are you confident?
(She asks Se Chan a question.)
(So Min sounds so bold.)
(It gives Se Chan confidence.)
It's the power of love.
- You can bet on me. - Are you confident?
Yes, bet on me.
Bet one more coin than you originally thought.
I'll go double.
I bet six.
(Unbelievable)
(So Min bets 6 coins on Se Chan.)
Is So Min betting on Se Chan?
I bet five.
(She gets cold feet.)
(She decides to be more realistic.)
Was she lying?
(Did she really bet on me?)
(Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, Hee Jin, Se Chan)
We're done.
Here's the game Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, Se Chan,
and Hee Jin will play.
Please.
The general knowledge quiz, The Quiz King.
(The general knowledge quiz, The Quiz King)
(Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, Hee Jin, Se Chan)
(Survey Result, 100 votes in total)
(It really was a quiz.)
I'm doomed.
(Haha is happy about betting 9 coins on Jae Seok.)
The one who survives the longest becomes the final winner.
But you don't get to answer simply by raising your hand.
We'll play rock-paper-scissors, and the person who plays...
the same thing as me gets to answer.
If you say the wrong answer, you're out for that question.
Two outs eliminate you from the game.
The person who survives the longest wins.
What if there are two people left? Do they both write their answers?
- What happens? - They both get to answer.
- Okay. - Let's do this.
- It's a history question. - Gosh.
I have no idea.
It's an easy one.
- Don't play the same thing as him. - I can't do this.
He was a king of Joseon.
He was the third son of Taejong Yi Bang Won...
and called Grand Prince Chungnyeong. Who is he?
- Pardon? - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Grand Prince Chungnyeong? - Yi Bang Won's third son?
Don't play the same thing as me.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo has to answer.)
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
- Please write your answer. - I managed to escape.
Ji Hyo will reveal herself to the world now.
Did he become the king in the end?
(By any chance...)
Can't you give Ji Hyo some more time to write her answer?
He was the king.
Oh, that's good.
(The person became the king in the end.)
- 1, 2, 3. - The sushi king.
(Seok Jin distracts Ji Hyo.)
- The sushi king? - What's that?
(Yi Bang Won's third son was the sushi king?)
You're not allowed to distract her.
- Leave her alone. - Sejong the Great.
(Ji Hyo says her answer.)
Sejong the Great.
(Is "Sejong the Great" correct?)
and called Grand Prince Chungnyeong. Who is he?
Sejong the Great.
(Is "Sejong the Great" correct?)
It's correct.
(Yi Bang Won's 3rd son, Grand Prince Chungnyeong, became the 4th king.)
(She got it right?)
- She's incredible. - Great job.
Sejong the Great is the only king Ji Hyo has heard of!
(She made use of all the historical knowledge she has.)
- She got lucky. - That's not true.
- She got lucky. - It's not like that.
- That's not true. - She knows only one king,
- and that's Sejong the Great. - No.
- She got lucky. - I know more.
Sejong the Great!
(I'd like to share this joy with Sejong the Great.)
(Let's all shout the name of Sejong the Great!)
- Ji Hyo got it right. - Oh, my.
- I knew it. - Ji Hyo's off the hook now.
I knew it.
- It's a mystery. - Here's the next question.
What do you call a voluntarily childless couple...
where both partners work?
What did you say?
(Ji Hyo drops her head.)
It's easy. It's DINKs.
DINKs.
As in Hiddink.
I'm not sure.
(Hee Jin has no idea.)
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - He can get it right.
- It's easy. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- It's easy. - Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(The person who will solve the second question is...)
(Ji Hyo again.)
- It's Ji Hyo again. - Is it Ji Hyo again?
You know the answer, right?
- I... - You know, right?
- I am sure I saw it somewhere. - Get on People.
(Get on People)
(Working couples who don't have kids are called "Get on People"?)
Orange People.
Queue People.
(Even "Queue People" appears.)
Stop distracting her.
Mohe People. Mohe People.
Mohe People.
Gosh, I heard it somewhere. Hold on.
Ji Hyo, you will get it right if you think hard.
You can do it.
- Hold on. - 3, 2, 1.
(Time's up.)
- The answer is "DINKs." - That's right. DINKs.
The acronym stands for "Double income, no kids."
(Working couples who purposefully don't have kids)
I thought it was "Tofu People."
You should have said something.
- "Tofu People"? - Where did that come from?
Here comes the next one.
"What's the name of the infectious disease..."
"caused by the bacteria Yersinia pestis..."
"that swept over Europe in the 14th century?"
- My goodness. - This one is hard.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok and Hee Jin play the same hand.)
- Okay. - Jae Seok and Hee Jin.
My goodness.
- Does he know the answer? - The previous ones were easy.
You know the answer, right?
(Did Se Chan figure out the answer?)
Does Se Chan know the answer?
I figured it out too.
Write down the answer as a bonus round.
(Se Chan participates as a bonus round.)
Write it down.
(Does Se Chan know the answer?)
- Write it down. - I... Is it wrong?
- Should I erase it? Is it wrong? - One.
Two.
- Three. - I don't know.
- "Bubonic plague" is correct. - Really?
(Jae Seok is correct and Hee Jin is incorrect.)
(Bubonic plague is spread through infected fleas.)
Everyone.
Take a look at Se Chan's answer.
(Se Chan wrote down the answer confidently.)
(Extremely curious)
Eczema.
(Was eczema widespread from the 14th century?)
It is about the skin.
That's why I thought it was eczema.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Jae Seok wins the second game as expected.)
Thus, for Jae Seok...
5 times 3 is 15. So he wins 15 coins.
- 15 coins. That's good. - And...
Jae Seok's investors will get...
- twice the coins they invested. - Okay.
I thought about investing in Jae Seok.
(Current Number of R Coins)
(Only the last round remains!)
Let me announce the members who will play the last game.
- The last game? - There will be a twist this time.
- So far, the top 1 has won. - You must invest in the top 1.
How many members will play?
YooA is in first place?
- I get it. - So Min is in second place.
It must be about dance.
- Dance. - Dance or flexibility.
If YooA is in first place, it must be about dance.
- Of course. - Dance.
YooA is in first place.
Hee Jin is in second place.
- Me? - It must be dance.
- Dance or flexibility. - Dance.
Kwang Soo and Han Na are in seventh place.
- Han NA can do... - She dances like a middle-aged man.
a limited number of dances.
I don't know the most recent dances.
- But I do know a few dances. - Do a dance of S.E.S.
- What? - Do it.
There was a dance I showed you.
(What?)
(Sloppy)
- Something doesn't seem right. - Hey.
- Something doesn't seem right. - The dance moves look strange.
- Are you imitating a worm? - It looks strange.
How could she make simple moves look strange?
- It looks strange. - Are you imitating a tadpole?
- Why are you bobbing your head? - Are you imitating a tadpole?
- What? - Your dance doesn't look right.
- Seriously. - It doesn't look right.
She has Seok Jin's dance skills.
I know the dances for the old K-Pop songs.
It's time for you to choose which member to invest in.
If Seok Jin wins...
and the investors get 10 times the coins...
I will grit my teeth.
(Invest in me!)
Invest in me.
(They suddenly burst out laughing.)
My goodness.
You are so mean.
Jong Kook is ridiculous.
"10 times?"
"He is a grandpa."
10 times?
He is a grandpa.
Seok Jin is...
(Laughing)
(The younger members burst out laughing.)
Why won't you say anything?
- What? Were they talking about me? - Yes.
(This grandpa can't make out words.)
Please make a bet now.
I don't know.
- You should invest in So Min. - Right?
Se Chan, I invested five coins in you earlier.
Right.
Se Chan, I invested five coins in you earlier too.
(Speaking cutely)
- This is driving me crazy. - Se Chan.
I will go first.
(Se Chan goes first.)
You will reveal how many coins I got later, right?
(Since this is the last game, they need to invest carefully!)
(YooA, So Min, Han Na, and Seok Jin)
(How many coins did the members invest?)
I made the best decision possible.
Seok Jin, So Min,
Han Na, and YooA...
- will have... - Let's see what it is.
the dance match, The Dance King.
- All right. - It's dance.
This isn't half bad. I have a chance.
When the dance video pauses,
do the next dance move to succeed.
- Thank goodness. - My goodness.
So Min can do this.
The member who gets the most number of questions wins.
- I think YooA will win. - If the dances are old...
- If the dances are old... - That's right.
Then Seok Jin will have a chance.
Come on out.
Let's decide on the order.
So Min knows many old dances.
I don't know any recent dances.
If everyone gets it wrong,
the one who got it the closest will win.
Okay. Then I will show all the dance moves.
I don't know any dance.
The last two games we played didn't have room...
for an unexpected result, but this one is different.
If Seok Jin wins, the investors get 10 times the coins.
- All right. Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors
I lost.
- Rock-paper-scissors - I won, right?
Is it more advantageous to go first?
What? No, it isn't.
- You are going 1st. - 1st.
- You are going 2nd. - 2nd?
- You are going third. - Does the order change?
I am going fourth.
It could be advantageous for Han Na...
since she can study the others' dances.
- That's right. - I will study them.
It was good for her to win at rock-paper-scissors.
Look at her. She is warming up.
(Flexible)
I will watch and copy YooA.
I will copy her.
I will tie my hair like YooA.
That's right, YooA.
(She is ridiculous.)
Let's begin. Play the video.
Play the video.
(What could be the first song?)
- What is that? - It's H.O.T.
("Candy" has signature dance moves of moving the arms sideways...)
(as well as the Power Racer Dance and Hammer Dance.)
(The song came out when YooA was 2 years old.)
What is she going to do?
(YooA begins to dance.)
She knows the dance!
YooA knows the dance.
When the video pauses...
(If she continues on after the pause, she succeeds!)
She is dancing perfectly.
(Does she know the dance?)
She knows the dance.
That's incredible.
- Let's go. - It starts now.
(Does YooA know the dance of a song that came out when she was 2?)
Let's go!
That's incredible.
- "I just love you". - It starts now.
(She continues on with the dance.)
(Do you remember the dance?)
(The answer)
(H.O.T.'s mega-hit song covered the nation with white balloons.)
(The signature dance move involves swinging the arms sideways.)
(Will YooA be able to do the dance?)
(The investors show different reactions.)
(The signature dance moves are almost the same!)
(She is really good.)
She is really good.
Hey, her dance moves are...
nearly accurate.
(She brings back the memories of the past!)
Her dance moves are nearly perfect.
(YooA's investor is highly satisfied.)
Her dance moves were nearly perfect.
(YooA got the signature dance moves nearly perfectly.)
You know the dance.
So Min, you have a chance.
- You know the dance. - Yes.
- It's Seok Jin's turn. - My goodness.
Seok Jin.
My heart is racing.
(Flailing)
My goodness.
Go with your feeling.
(What kind of "Candy" will he show?)
(My goodness.)
(His struggle makes everyone's heart ache.)
I can't watch this.
- My goodness. - What is that?
I told you he is a grandpa.
- Grandpa! Grandpa! - Grandpa! Grandpa!
(They feel bad for him.)
Please stop.
Seok Jin.
Why are you making the idol group's dance...
look so oily?
- Grandpa! Grandpa! - Grandpa! Grandpa!
So Min is up next.
I know the dance.
- That was different. - I know the dance.
- So Min, let's go! - Let's go!
(So Min runs through the memories of the time she was a fan of H.O.T.)
Let's go! Come on!
(H.O.T., are you watching this?)
(Her dance moves are spot on!)
(The investors are satisfied.)
- That's good. - She is good.
(Having been a fan, her dance is on point!)
She is good.
So Min, let's go!
(Perfect)
All right.
(She even shows the Racer Dance.)
Okay!
- She is good. - You didn't have to do that.
She is good.
- Han Na. - Han Na.
- That's from the earlier part. - Don't go over the top.
- Let's go. - I studied So Min's dance.
Double it. Double it.
Come on. Get the order right.
- She is hilarious. - 1, 2, 3.
She is hilarious.
(She shows a sloppy dance.)
(The investor who is seeing his stocks decline)
(She ignores Kwang Soo...)
(and continues to show her sloppy dance.)
Why is she moving her legs that way?
Her legs...
It's the opposite side!
- What's wrong with her? - Keep going.
She's so funny.
(She reinterpreted "Candy" in her own style.)
- What's wrong with her legs? - She's so funny.
She's so funny.
(Other investors are more than satisfied.)
That was fine.
- How do you do this? - Flimsy legs.
- That was so funny. - That's what she did.
Han Na.
- Doesn't it go like this? - That was indeed Han Na.
She was pointing her arm and leg on the same side.
(She still gets the maximum price for the laugh.)
We went over the results,
and YooA wins and gets first place.
(YooA wins round one.)
She gets first place.
(YooA has 1 point.)
- I knew she was going to win. - She was really good.
But if none of you know the dance perfectly,
the person who dances with most energy wins.
- With energy. - Han Na...
- and Seok Jin, - That's true.
- Try your best. - Good luck.
- Next. - What order would you like to go?
- Order. - Keep it the same.
Who's going first?
- So Min. - So Min's first.
- Then Han Na, - Right.
- and Seok Jin. - All right.
(So Min, Han Na, Seok Jin, and YooA)
I'm in trouble.
Play the music.
So Min is a good dancer too.
("So Cool" by SISTAR was released in 2011.)
(The signature dance move involves flailing movements.)
I don't know. I don't know this.
- I don't know this. - Look at YooA's face.
(The chorus part is the second question.)
(You can almost remember it.)
(Here's the answer for the viewers.)
(The answer)
(You're supposed to rub your neck.)
I don't know this.
What do I do?
Do I start?
Cool.
(What? Does she know it?)
(Was it supposed to be that aggressive?)
- Is that it? - She's correct.
(She's seductive.)
- Who's that? - She's correct.
It's the correct dance.
(She thinks she's sexy,)
She's correct.
(so her mouth opens naturally.)
She's correct. Keep going!
Be bold!
So Min, be bold.
- What's the problem? - Excuse me.
So Min, did you rub dirt off your skin?
(She took a bath thanks to SISTAR's dance.)
- So Min, - Yes?
did you rub dirt off your skin?
Next is Han Na. Han Na, be bold.
Be bold. So Min was close.
(How is Han Na's "So Cool"?)
What's that? Why is she brushing her hair?
(He's almost crying.)
- Oh, gosh. - What is that?
(She washes her hair and spins.)
Who told her to do this? That's "Bruise" by Kim Hyun Jung.
(She keeps on showing off her hair regardless of what he says.)
She's here for the comedy.
She's being flimsy again.
(She doesn't care about winning at all.)
I can't do this.
Han Na.
Where is this dance from?
It's funnier because she looks so normal.
(A man carefully approaches the stage.)
She's the best.
She looks fine.
He's getting nervous.
(He's nervous all alone.)
- Seok Jin. - Are you going to do this?
Of course.
Of course. People invested in me.
Should we skip? Should we just keep going?
- I'm looking forward to this. - I have to dance.
Seok Jin, be bold if you can't dance.
- Okay. - Be energetic.
Seok Jin, be as sexy as possible.
(Be sexy?)
(Like this?)
(Rubbing)
Maybe it's actually this.
(You never know.)
(He expresses his sexiness for 1 percent possibility.)
I hate this.
(I'd rather not look.)
- Are you a fly? - Please stop it.
That's enough.
(Interrupting)
- That's it. - It's my turn.
Let's watch.
- She might not know. - Let's go.
What is this?
She's different.
This is the dance.
There was this move.
(Their eyes are on her.)
- This is right. - Is it?
- I remember. I recognize it. - It goes like this.
- She's right. - Good job.
(Her competitors feel defeated after seeing her sexy dance.)
(Her investor is super satisfied.)
Good job.
So Min got it right.
So Min was pretty close.
So Min, you were close. You never know.
It's possible that SISTAR will do the dance...
like Seok Jin on the video.
Like Seok Jin on the video.
You don't know yet.
(Is this it?)
YooA was good,
but her dances moves were wrong other than the "so cool" part.
- Was she? - Really?
(Original dance, YooA's dance)
We have to go with the energetic dance.
So Min was energetic. She even took it to the floor.
So Min was most energetic for this one.
It was So Min.
Look. My knees are red.
- So Min gets one point. - Yes!
(She got 1 precious point.)
- Good job, So Min. - Good job.
It's okay.
So Min, assign the order.
Seok Jin, YooA, me, and Han Na.
Play the music.
("Adult Ceremony" by Park Ji Yoon was everybody's favorite dance.)
Park Ji Yoon.
So Min is good at this.
(Many people did parodies of this dance.)
(What dance follows this part?)
(I know this!)
I know this.
(Everybody but Seok Jin knows the chorus. Here's the answer.)
(The answer)
(Bounce at the hips.)
(Push sideways like you're playing hard-to-get.)
(1st contestant freezes on the spot.)
This is hard.
Good job.
- Rub your hands. - That's exactly it.
(They don't sound genuine at all.)
(Gosh, my eyes.)
Old man!
(He misbehaves in front of the guests.)
- Good job. That's exactly it. - Goodness.
Can I go?
This question...
is advantageous to So Min.
- Right? - Yes.
- I don't remember it entirely. - So Min.
Watch YooA.
- I think I know this. - I'll copy her.
- YooA's. - It's not that part.
Wait.
Seok Jin just finished. Give him a round of applause.
(Wait. Seok Jin just finished. Give him a round of applause.)
(Cheering)
Good shot!
You're going overboard.
You're the best.
I thought the camera was off.
Play the music.
(She was 6 at the time. Would she remember the song?)
She's right. This is the dance.
This is risky.
So Min, this isn't it. This part is right.
- This is right. - This is it.
She's good.
(It doesn't matter what's right. She already scored 100 percent.)
Awesome!
I don't think that was right, but she was good.
She made it look like it was the correct dance.
- She's good. - But...
- there was something more. - I don't remember.
I think So Min knows.
I don't remember everything though.
There's a good chance for So Min.
So Min, try to remember your days as a trainee.
I'm sure she knows.
I'm sure she does.
(Goodness!)
(This is it!)
(He's amazed.)
(She's copying the dance in her head.)
No, no.
- This part. - Now.
(She made a fatal mistake.)
Han Na said she knew for sure.
She's good.
So Min's good.
This is right.
- She's right. - This is right.
(Her body remembers the end.)
- She's right. - I was right.
- She was right. - She got it.
I hope Han Na takes this. Han Na.
- Han Na! - She said she knew.
I think I know a few more moves.
She learned this dance.
I didn't learn it,
but I know a few more moves.
- You know a few more? - Good luck, Han Na.
Let's start.
- Play... - I know this for sure.
the music.
I know this for sure.
- Bring your foot up. Correct. - She's good.
- She knows. - It's this part.
She knows.
This is it.
She's right.
- What? - This is it.
I thought she almost fell.
- This is it. - She got it.
- The dance moves are correct. - She got it!
(They're excited.)
(This is it!)
- She got it. - She's so right.
She got it.
(She catches the body wave So Min missed.)
She's almost exact.
- She's right. - She's right.
This is it.
- You never know. - Yes!
Han Na wins.
(Han Na wins.)
(The flimsy dancer wins.)
Finally, something I know.
Oh, my.
- Good job, Han Na. - Something I know.
- It's now 1 to 1 to 1. - Was it okay?
This is a tight race.
- It's a tight race. - Seok Jin,
you never know.
Seok Jin, you never know.
- You never know. - Good luck, Seok Jin!
Good luck, Seok Jin!
- Good luck. - You didn't invest in me.
- You didn't invest in me. - Good luck.
Let's lift him.
This is so funny.
- Good luck! - Toss him up in the air.
Seok Jin!
- You didn't invest in me. - That's enough.
This is so funny.
You can do it, Seok Jin. Good luck.
The next song might be in your favor.
That's true.
- Han Na chooses this time. - They should do the final round.
- Han Na. - Final round for three of them.
We have to keep going.
It's tied at one.
It's 1 to 1 to 1, so you might win a point.
- Then... - I doubt it.
(He's serious.)
(That won't happen.)
Let's just go with the three of them.
- Come on. - I doubt it.
It's 1 to 1 to 1,
so you might win a point.
You never know.
It's difficult for me to stand there.
- You never know though. - It's really hard for me...
to stand here by myself.
I can't believe the staff included him in this.
They put me in here.
- He's worth tenfold. - These guys...
- They were trying to be funny. - How mean.
- Why did you put me here? - It's tenfold if he wins.
- How cruel. - It should be more like 50.
- This is too funny. - I can't stop laughing.
- I can't stop laughing. - This is an unusually tight race.
Let's start. Play the music.
("One More Time" by Jewelry was released in 2008.)
(Everyone knows the dance.)
- "Baby one more time." - That's it. Here it comes.
Seok Jin, you got this.
I don't know this dance.
What?
(He does the group dance from the fan-meet.)
What are you doing?
(Lia Kim, I am making good use of the dance I learned.)
Seok Jin.
What was that?
Stop.
(It's painful to watch the struggles of a grandpa dancer.)
I'm starting to forget this dance too.
(The group dance from the fan-meet)
I am forgetting the dance.
He is forgetting it.
Seok Jin.
Seriously.
When Seok Jin did this, he looked so shabby.
- No one helped him. - Stop it.
When he did this, his back looked so bent.
- Stop it. - That was hilarious.
- Who is next? - YooA, let's go.
Cheer for me.
It's a matter of whether or not YooA knows the dance.
Let's go.
(She knows the dance well!)
(YooA's dance makes them want to invest more coins.)
- That's it. - That's it.
Stay focused.
- She knows the dance. - It's perfect.
(He always copies a cool dance move.)
All right.
- That was incredible. - All right.
- I studied everyone's dance. - You are good at copying the dance.
Okay.
With Han Na, you never know. She can copy...
- YooA's dance. - YooA did an amazing job.
Here comes Han Na's dance.
Han Na is scanning.
- Here it comes. - Let's go.
Let's go.
That's it!
What is that?
(After the nice intro,)
(she shows a sloppy dance.)
(Dance is all about moving to the beat.)
You are so courageous.
(Courage)
(Her courageous dance ensures that Kwang Soo will lose his coins.)
- You are so courageous. - You are so courageous.
You are so courageous.
(Her dance is more memorable than YooA's.)
- Her steps are quick. - She is incredible.
Han Na.
Han Na is incredible.
- I did it. - I acknowledge her talent.
All the songs were old, but YooA did splendidly.
The winner is YooA.
(There was unanimous consent.)
(The current score is 2 to 1 to 1 to 0.)
- She deserves the victory. - Her dances were spot on.
Is it over?
- One song remains. - Aren't we done?
- Aren't we done? - Okay. Seok Jin, you never know.
Try your best until the end.
(The match starts now.)
Don't give up like you did earlier.
- Did I upset you somehow, Chul Min? - Seok Jin.
- Why did you put me in this group? - You never know.
Why? Mi Yeon.
Why did you put me in this group? This is so stressful.
It's time to turn the tables.
Seok Jin, there are people who bet on you.
Seok Jin, let's go!
I get it,
but why are you saying "You never know"?
(But why are you saying "You never know"?)
- You never know. - Do you take me for a fool?
- You never know. - Don't give up.
- You never know. - The game isn't over.
Do you want me to believe you and dance diligently?
- The game isn't over. - You are right!
- The game isn't over. - That's right.
- I... - You can do it.
- Do your best until the end. - You can do it.
My stomach hurts from laughing.
- My stomach hurts so much. - Let's begin.
(What could be the last question?)
("SOLO" by Jennie is a song that was released in 2018.)
(It has only been a year since its release.)
(Will Han Na be able to survive with "SOLO"?)
She seems to know the dance.
- She knows the dance. - She seems to know the dance.
(Han Na has the signature dance move down.)
(How will her version of "SOLO" be?)
She knows the dance.
What is that?
- Hey. - What are you doing?
(Her solo dance is explosive.)
That's a different type of the solo dance.
(She welcomes new love.)
- A solo dance. - That's not the right dance.
A solo dance.
(The dance suits "SOLO" perfectly.)
"I am solo."
Her dance suits the song.
- It was a solo dance. - A solo dance.
- It was a solo dance. - That's right.
- A solo dance. - Good job.
I don't know the dance very well.
I don't know the dance at all.
- Shall I play a different song? - Yes.
It was really strange...
because Seok Jin practiced the dance in the back.
(He did it while Han Na was dancing.)
(You never know!)
- Hey. - He hasn't given up.
- It's not over yet. - Seok Jin put his hand...
in the pocket.
- He practiced with seriousness. - I know.
- I was so surprised. - Seok Jin.
You never know.
That's right.
"You never know."
(You never know.)
- This is for you. - "You never know."
- "You never know." - "You never know."
Come here.
(Messages of support pour in.)
- Come here. - I believe in you!
- You never know. - Come here.
- You need to be scolded. - You never know.
You never know.
You must think I am a fool.
- That was funny. - That was funny.
Let's move on to the next song.
Here it comes.
Play.
("Bubble Pop" by HyunA was released in 2011.)
(The signature dance move involves rapid hip movements.)
- "Bubble Pop." - This is good.
Here it comes.
(YooA gets started on the "Bubble Pop" dance.)
(YooA would know a song by her senior singer.)
(The dance comes right away.)
(The answer for "Bubble pop" will be revealed.)
(The answer)
(1. Blow a kiss. 2. Bend the back continuously.)
(She starts off perfectly.)
So Min, watch carefully.
Remember each dance move.
Gosh, she is good.
(YooA remembers each detail.)
- She is really good. - She is good.
(She ends every dance with her own charms.)
Her movements are so light.
To be honest, we don't know if the dance is right.
- But we can tell she is good. - She exudes confidence.
Let's go. Play the song.
So Min, shake your hips.
(Creaking)
That's good. Keep going.
- The dance didn't go that way. - No.
Shake your hips.
Keep going until the end.
- Keep going. - Hang in there.
Go to Se Chan.
(I am here.)
(Knowing that she won't win, she focuses on building love.)
She is good.
- This is embarrassing. - She is good.
She decided to find love instead.
- Good job. - That was hilarious.
I will sit out on this one, so Han Na can go next.
- You should dance, Seok Jin. - No.
You never know.
Listen. You...
It's not over until it is!
- You can do it! - You can do it!
- You never know. - You never know, my foot.
You don't know how it feels to stand here alone.
There are children...
- who see you and dream. - Hey.
I am standing here...
and the song is "Bubble Pop."
Seok Jin.
(At the age of 54, he is competing against a 24-year-old idol singer.)
I...
Try to understand where I am coming from.
How am I supposed to dance here?
Bubble, bubble... I can't do that.
I will leave "Bubble Pop" to you.
My stomach hurts.
- We understand. - My goodness,
- Please understand. - We understand.
(His heart is at ease now.)
- We understand. - It's Han Na's turn.
How will I do the signature dance move?
Han Na, the signature dance move could suit you better.
Do it in your style.
(The outcome depends on Han Na's dance.)
(She gets the hand gesture right.)
Han Na knows the dance.
(Her speed is on another level.)
She is fast.
(The part she knows ends and she begins to dance sloppily.)
(Kwang Soo will lose the coins he invested.)
(Carefree)
This is hilarious.
- Her facial expression is funny. - You are the best.
Her facial expression is funny.
Han Na, move sideways.
(She appeases her fans.)
(Even though she lost, she fought well.)
- Han Na is hilarious. - I love this dance move.
- Moving sideways. - I love this dance move.
The Charlie Chaplin Dance.
I laughed so much today.
Thus,
the winner of this round is...
YooA.
(YooA wins the round again.)
(With 3 points, YooA becomes the final winner.)
It's as expected.
YooA, good job.
- It's over. - I knew you would win.
I acknowledge her talent.
They couldn't win against her.
But they fought well.
- I am glad. - They couldn't win against her.
- I knew this would happen. - Everyone did a good job.
- It was a fierce match. - Everyone is a winner.
The rankings have completely changed.
- Really? - Really?
This is a disaster. I bet a lot of coins.
Me too.
I will announce the one who is in first place.
(1st place)
With this round, the one who is in first place is...
(Who invested wisely and succeeded to rise to the top?)
Byung Jae with 52 coins.
(Byung Jae is in 1st place with 52 coins.)
52 coins?
- 52 coins? - Did you bet all the coins?
- No, no. - He bet many coins on YooA.
- Good job, Byung Jae. - It was a winning move.
Seok Jin used to be at the bottom with four coins.
Now, the one at the bottom is...
(Did the one at the bottom change?)
Hee Jin with zero coins.
Zero coins? Did I hear that right?
(Screaming)
(How is that possible?)
- 0 coins? - 0 coins?
- My goodness. - She went all in.
She bet all of her coins on So Min.
- She bet all of her coins on me. - So Min.
(Hee Jin bet all of her coins on So Min.)
Either Seok Jin or So Min.
(She didn't have a clue.)
I will bet all of my coins on So Min.
(She bet all of her coins on So Min.)
Let's move to the location of the penalty.
(Don't put all your eggs in one basket.)
Today, only one person will receive the penalty.
Everyone,
we are done.
Byung Jae, take the ring.
Byung Jae.
- I haven't seen it in a while. - Today,
Han Na,
- YooA, - It's real gold.
Byung Jae, and Hee Jin worked really hard.
That's right.
- Hee Jin. - Yes?
- Get in position. - My goodness.
(Go for the penalty.)
- Get ready. - Get ready.
- This way. - Stand wherever you want.
Everybody, please count to three,
and the water bomb will be released.
One,
two,
three.
(We wish her the best of luck...)
(like the explosive water bomb.)
Come here.
(We wish her the best of luck like the explosive water bomb.)
(We would like to thank Hee Jin, Han Na, YooA of OH MY GIRL,)
(and Byung Jae for joining us on a cold day.)
She's in danger.
(It all started on the sea train to Incheon.)
(People start shrieking and behaving strangely on the train.)
(There are zombies, and their lives are at danger.)
(The train is locked. They must act with reason.)
(The survival aces gather for an unprecedented incident.)
(Chanmi says she doesn't want to lose.)
(They have to pull themselves together to survive.)
(Hyejeong says she can't beat this.)
(One touch determines who survives.)
(Seolhyun says she's within the territory.)
(Safety zone closes in on them.)
(Yuna says she has to find a box.)
(Are there mysterious boxes hidden in the disaster zone?)
(Jimin says she has to rip the name tags.)
(As soon as they let their guard down,)
(the humans collapse.)
(To Incheon: Catch Me)