(Last week)
(The Teamwork Race will determine the partners of the members.)
(The members were overly motivated before revealing the identities.)
(At last, the artists for the joint performances were revealed.)
(Gummy)
(Code Kunst and Nucksal)
(SORAN and Apink)
(This awesome lineup reminds them of a festival.)
(Current Partners)
(They must win missions to team up with the artist of their choice.)
(Teams in 1st and 2nd places will get cards to switch partners.)
(If all 3 members pick the same card, the team will stay as it is.)
(If one of them picks a different card, they'll switch partners.)
What is this?
I see water.
Goodness, what is this?
(Whipped cream, acupressure mats, a pool, and a karaoke machine)
What's this?
(What is the mission?)
(Before the mission, everyone stands up with their teams.)
(What?)
- This isn't my team. - Over there.
(Why did she suddenly stand next to Se Chan?)
That was so natural. Why did you stand here?
- Right. - She stood right next to me.
- You two had a thing... - But her team is over there.
- a long time ago, right? - Yes.
(Jae Seok said Na Eun belonged the mountain animal family.)
(How could you say that?)
(Na Eun is like Formosan sika deer.)
(He confessed his feelings to her who resembled the beautiful deer.)
She was my lady. Lady Na Eun.
- I stood next to him. - What?
- Lady Na Eun. - But Na Eun lets him believe...
- there's a chance. - Exactly.
(I do?)
When she stood next to me, I almost rekindled our fling.
- You never know. - I thought about it.
- She makes him think he has a shot. - But I thought that wasn't right.
I almost went for it,
- but I'm going to get a grip. - Good job.
- After you thought about it? - Don't toy with him.
Make it clear to him if you don't want him.
By the way, is it a done deal that Kwang Soo will stay there?
Of course.
- Really? - We've gotten close now.
Why aren't you answering?
First of all, we've gotten close.
- But... - What?
- Of course, we got close. - I kept...
- observing each team. - Okay.
Kwang Soo kept hovering around Ji Yeon.
- I'm her shadow. - Really?
- He takes good care of me. - Right.
Is that so? Code Kunst and Nucksal,
it looked like you don't care about Seok Jin at all.
I don't care about them either.
(Acting strong)
No, no. No, no.
- We talked after our meal. - What did you talk about?
I asked him about our team. And he said not to even bring it up.
(Don't even bring it up.)
- He said not to bring it up. - "Don't even bring it up."
Hey, there's always a challenge.
- How could you say that? - After observing him,
he reminds me of a fairy who lives in a closet.
- You mean Dobby? - Right. He resembles Dobby.
- He looks like Dobby. - Dobby...
I resemble Dobby...
- and the groom in "Corpse Bride". - Right.
- He looks just like Dobby. - Dobby.
He looks like a character in horror movies.
He didn't say that?
- You resemble him too. - Who?
(Looking around)
(Me?)
- He resembles Dobby too. - How could you...
You two belong to the same family. You're right. You resemble him.
You will earn a chance to switch the partners with this mission.
This mission will require your teamwork and singing skills.
It's called Athletic Singing Contest.
- Great. - Three people...
from each team will try out the mission.
Each team will pick a song you're confident to sing...
and connect each other's bodies while the song is playing.
And the team with the highest score will win the mission.
We have to connect our bodies.
However, there's a rule you must follow to connect the bodies.
Each person will roll the dice with six body parts written, twice.
Only the selected body parts can touch the floor...
when you connect the bodies.
- What? - What if we get the face?
What about the head?
If a different part of the body touches the floor,
a point will be deducted for every second.
All right. Code Kunst and Nucksal, you can go first.
All right.
(They throw the dice to select body parts that can touch the floor.)
- Head. - Head.
Head. You can roll it one more time.
(It would be easy if we get the back.)
(What is Seok Jin's second body part?)
- Bottom. - Bottom.
How can only his head and bottom touch the floor?
- How is that even possible? - Only my head and bottom can touch?
Isn't that the worst combination?
Only my head and bottom can touch the floor?
- That's really hard. - Ji Hyo.
(They must keep their position during the 1st verse.)
- She got the back. - Back.
- She got a nice one. - That's the best one.
- Back and bottom. Back and head. - That's good.
- You can just lie down. - Go ahead.
- Back. - I'm the only one with bad parts.
Back and feet. Okay.
- That's the best combination. - Back and feet.
(Back and feet, back and head, and head and bottom)
- Start when the song plays. - Okay.
(Staying close to the microphone is advantageous.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Ji Hyo, follow the rules.
I'm following the rules.
- Your feet aren't touching. - They aren't touching.
They aren't touching.
- Feet. - Seok Jin, I can't reach.
Seok Jin, you have to go into the water. You have no choice.
(You have to do that to make your bodies touch.)
- Right. Your bodies must touch. - Let's do it again.
You should take turns since it's hard to connect all at once.
- My back has to be in the water. - Right. Just do it.
You have to go into the water.
I have to go into the water no matter what.
How many times did say you have to go into the water?
How many times did you tell me? Did you tell me dozens of times?
Hey, I thought they were having lovers' quarrel.
Hey.
- My gosh. Unbelievable. - You take my spot then.
You want to switch because you don't want your back to get wet.
- That's right. I don't want that. - Ji Hyo sounds really angry.
No, I don't want to. You go in. You picked back and head.
- You're unbelievable. You... - No, I don't want to.
Darn you.
(He acts out since he can't win the argument.)
- I can't. - Did you throw that?
I can't sing the song.
Take care of Nucksal.
- Hey. - Take care of Nucksal.
- Take care of him. - Please take care of me.
And he said that he's known for his considerate behaviors.
- He said he's an English gentleman. - English gentleman.
He said he's an English gentleman.
We'll start now.
Start.
Connect your bodies first.
(Go away. This is my spot.)
She's set. You're next.
(The song has already started. Only Ji Hyo is in position.)
(Only his bottom and head can touch the floor.)
- There you go. Yes. - They must touch his head. Good.
(He gently lies down as he doesn't want to get wet.)
(I will help you not to fall into the water.)
(Success! All three of their bodies are touching.)
(He starts rapping now.)
(Back and feet, head and bottom, and head and back)
It's cold.
(His diction is excellent.)
(Screaming)
His head is touching.
(He tries his best not to get his hair wet.)
Seok Jin.
(He's trying so hard not to wet his hair.)
Hey, don't pinch my scalp.
Lift your head!
He's struggling.
He doesn't want to get wet.
(Lifting up)
(Ji Hyo kindly lifts up his head to save it from getting wet.)
(Ji Hyo's feet have the strongest hold!)
Hey, don't pinch!
- I'm holding you up. - Why are you doing that?
I'm holding you up.
- Your feet... - Seriously.
(The 1st verse ends in the middle of their argument.)
- Seriously. - Hey.
That was more than the first verse. You kept playing until the bridge.
What's the score?
(His rapping was excellent. What's the score from the machine?)
(The score for Team Nucksal and Code Kunst...)
- My gosh. - 28 points.
We can beat this. We have a shot!
(He was great, but the score was unexpectedly low.)
(He's suddenly feeling confident.)
- We can beat this. Are you ready? - Okay.
- Gosh, 28 points? We can beat it. - What happened?
All right. The score was 28 points.
Nucksal's head touched the floor for 13 seconds. We deduced 13.
And Ji Hyo's bottom touched, so we deducted 10 points.
- The final score is five points. - I...
Five points? That's the worst.
We can win points as long as we keep our postures.
Next up is...
- SORAN, right? - Yes, we'll go next.
- You can do this. - Let's do this.
- Okay. - Tall guys, do the mission.
They are the tallest in our team.
- They are the tallest guys. - They are the tallest.
They aren't funny, but...
- We'll win. We will. - They're not funny, but we'll win.
Let's do this!
(He's feeling enthusiastic too.)
(He's feeling overly enthusiastic than usual.)
What do you think about enthusiastic guys?
He's every girl's ideal type.
(He's every girl's ideal type.)
(The exemplary man of their ideal type)
Great, great!
(His enthusiasm explodes.)
- Do well. - Nice!
We're off to a great start.
(He doesn't stop cheering them on.)
(Glancing)
I just spotted this. Na Eun keeps glancing at you.
Really?
Just now, I asked...
about enthusiastic guys, and she said they are her ideal types.
You are our ideal type.
All right. We're ready. Okay, go, go, go!
(He stays enthusiastic for the beautiful deer.)
Let's go!
(Her heart pounds.)
(I will stay enthusiastic until my body breaks down,)
(my dear lady.)
Gosh, he's so theatrical.
(He throws the dice in the midst of Se Chan's cheer.)
Bottom.
(Feet, bottom, head)
(Back and feet, head and bottom, and stomach and feet)
My gosh, he's amazing.
Se Chan looks like a coach.
You can sit down.
(His passion exudes even from his back.)
- Do you have head and bottom? - Head and bottom.
- He's not talking. - He's not talking.
- He's only mouthing it. - He has no idea what he's doing.
(Mouthing)
Wait, you're not saying anything.
Can you lie down on your side with your head and bottom?
He has leadership skills.
- That's right. - On your side.
- You can do this, right? - Yes!
Let's go!
(His leadership skills explode.)
We can do this!
(Se Chan opened up a new horizon for ideal types.)
- SORAN. - Okay.
That really looked like a team-building trip from a company.
- You can do this! - Where should I go?
- "Love Is". Turbo's song. - "Love Is"?
- Go! Start. - You can do this.
- There you go. - You're doing great.
- Go inside. - Nice!
- There you go! - Head and bottom.
Head... There you go.
Great, great.
- Great. - Great. Sing it!
Your feet have to touch.
(He has to sing now.)
- Not yet. - Not yet.
- It's still the interlude. - The verse still hasn't started.
- They picked a long one. - It's so long.
- Was the interlude this long? - Why did you pick a long one?
- Jump the interlude. - Hey.
Why is the interlude so long?
When will it start?
- Hey. - It's too long.
- Jung Nam didn't sing the song. - Here it goes.
It's starting now.
(The song starts at last.)
(He sings in a stable manner with only his stomach touching.)
He's singing now.
The microphone is picking up his voice.
(The posture is good and so is his voice.)
There you go!
(They are holding perfect postures...)
(while touching only the selected body parts.)
By the way, they played the game by the book.
- They're playing it by the book. - They are indeed.
(They clap to cheer him on for 3 seconds.)
They are even clapping.
(His posture is stable as if he's lying on his bed.)
- There you go. - This part isn't touching!
This is totally by the book.
- I'm serious. - Their postures are perfect.
(He's at ease.)
He's like a master.
- There you go! - Lift your head up!
(These new recruits are putting on a fierce battle of masters.)
(As they hold precise postures from start to finish,)
(he finishes the 1st verse.)
- There you go. - Is it over?
What's the score?
(Their postures were perfect. What's their score?)
(Team SORAN's score is...)
(53 points.)
(It's almost twice higher than Team Nucksal and Code Kunst's.)
- That's a high score. - Well done.
(We did it!)
- They were amazing. - They were perfect.
(Even the other teams approve. They were perfect.)
We'll reveal their final score.
They earned 53 points.
And as for deductions...
(Deductions...)
There are none.
(There are no deductions.)
(The final score is 53.)
- I agree. There were no deductions. - My gosh. They were...
- They played by the book. - Right.
I've never seen people who followed the rules perfectly.
You have to do whatever it takes.
Their teamwork is perfect.
You should have them vet the game before we film.
- Seriously. Incorporated SORAN... - Hey.
makes the perfect team.
- Good job. - Nice!
Sit down.
All right. As for this team,
there are three members which is perfect for this game.
- Right. - Yes.
One of them is trying so hard to cling onto this team.
"Cling"? How could you say that?
- I thought he was their agent. - Agent?
When they say that I'll get kicked out, you should...
- deny that. - I kept denying it. I did.
This team will stay as it is to the end.
- Watch. I'm serious. - Okay.
- Here I go. I'll take it seriously. - Okay.
(As he hopes to stay in the team, he throws the dice.)
- Stomach and feet. - Back and feet.
(Stomach and feet, feet and back, and stomach and feet)
(Everyone is anticipating Team Gummy's song pick.)
It's starting. It started.
"Unreasonable Reason".
We can do this.
I just have to lift my body, right?
- Okay. - Hey, you can grab my feet.
Yes, you can grab my feet.
- She's really close. - My gosh.
- There you go. - She's over the microphone.
- It's because he's tall. - Right.
- She is over the microphone. - Kwang Soo is contributing a lot.
My gosh, she's at the microphone.
Gosh, what is this?
My feet have to touch.
- I'm set. Okay. - She can reach the microphone.
- Kwang Soo is amazing. - This is no joke.
Kwang Soo contributed a lot.
(It's a mix of Athletic Jong Kook, Tall Kwang Soo,)
(and the Queen of Singers, Gummy.)
This is like a concert.
(What an amazing combination!)
(Her scatting is enough to turn this place into a concert venue.)
This is unfair.
(My gosh, Gummy is singing really well!)
Hey, don't shake!
Don't shake me!
(They forget about the mission for the moment...)
(and begin enjoying the performance.)
(Her voice and singing skills give them goosebumps.)
- If you try to leave me - She's incredible.
(When you said you loved me)
(With the complete support from Jong Kook and Kwang Soo,)
(she only focuses on her singing at ease.)
(The song excites everyone.)
(Given her singing skills, we'll definitely win 1st place.)
Gummy, your hands are touching.
(Only her stomach and feet can touch.)
(Her hands are touching the floor.)
(As she's too focused, she can't hear him.)
Your hands!
Gummy, you have to lift your hands!
- Her hands are touching. - You must take off your hands!
They'll get a lot of deductions.
- Ji Yeon, take off your hands! - Your hands!
Ji Yeon, you must take off your hands!
She can't hear you.
Yes, there you go. Lift your hands.
- You can't hold the microphone. - No holding the microphone.
Why not?
Look! She's holding it. She's holding it. Count the seconds!
(She's still holding on to the microphone.)
(Unfortunately, she finishes the 1st verse...)
(while holding onto the microphone to the end.)
What's the score?
(Although her hands were touching...)
That was hard.
(How many points did she get from the karaoke machine?)
(That's amazing! Their jaws drop open.)
(What on earth is her score?)
- Okay! We won. - 84 points.
(Team Gummy gets 84 points.)
(We still have a shot even if we get deductions.)
- You'll lose a lot of points. - But we'll lose points.
- That's all right. - All right.
Your score is 84 points.
Your hands touched for a minute. So the final score is 24 points.
(The final score is 24 points.)
We deducted 60 points.
- Your hands were touching. - You deducted 60 points?
Really? You should have told me.
We kept telling you.
- We kept yelling, - I can't believe this.
- "Hands, hands!" - I'm sorry.
(Yelling at her was harder than getting into the positions.)
You should have looked around.
- We yelled a lot. - I didn't hear anything at all.
Ji Yeon is perfect,
but she's not good at playing games.
- By the way, Ji Yeon, - Yes?
where did you get your slippers? They are so nice.
- They look like traditional socks. - I love your slippers.
- Oh, no. - I do.
- You should've told me sooner. - Great.
Eun Ji, Ha Young, and Na Eun will give it a try.
Eun Ji, do a good job and take me from this team!
- Eun Ji. - Yes?
Win the game and take me to your team!
Okay.
Ha Young, take me from this team!
(Who is that again?)
I'll throw the dice.
Ha Young.
(They throw the dice to select the body parts that can touch.)
- Head. - All right.
(Head, hands, and stomach)
(Back and head, hands and stomach, and stomach and feet)
Let's do this!
(Apink chooses their song.)
(It's "Tears" by So Chan Whee.)
- It's "Tears" by So Chan Whee. - They picked that?
- Is it "Tears"? - That's amazing.
I want to hear them sing.
Hurry up!
Ha Young, go farther.
- More, more, more. - They might succeed.
You can go farther down. Come up.
Come up. Okay, okay.
That's her hair.
(He pulls on her hair.)
(Is this the most comfortable they can be?)
Here we go.
(The microphone is too high.)
(There's a leak.)
If you don't touch it, you'll lose points.
Na Eun doesn't want to grab her foot.
Why not?
- You're doing well. - You're doing well!
Come a bit closer.
Na Eun is hilarious.
(Eun Ji's voice is stable.)
- That's great! - Good work!
(He's impressed.)
The microphone is going down!
(The microphone helps her sing better.)
(The microphone helped her.)
Here we go!
Let's go!
(Let's enjoy this!)
Don't call me
A heartless woman
(She sings well despite the unfavorable circumstances.)
She's really good.
Don't forget
My love
(She sings the high note.)
(They forget that it's a competition and enjoy themselves.)
(Even Code Kunst responds.)
(This is their second time enjoying such a great performance.)
(Her struggling team members...)
(also gain strength through her amazing voice.)
(She ends the song perfectly.)
That was great.
(Gummy approves.)
(How well did they do?)
- That's so amazing! - That's incredible!
Great job!
(Will you sing another song?)
We got 98 points!
That's amazing!
That's incredible! Good job!
- My gosh. - That was excellent.
Ha Young, good job.
- Good job, Ha Young. - Good work.
- You did so well. - Na Eun, gosh!
Here is the final result.
They received 98 points.
But Na Eun's thighs kept touching the ground, so we'll deduct some.
No, they weren't.
We will deduct 30 points.
(They get a 30-point deduction?)
Your score is 68 points. You're still in 1st place.
(Team Apink comes 1st place.)
You guys sang so well.
(The 1st 2 winning teams can switch teammates.)
- Eun Ji! - Yes?
Don't forget!
(Guys, don't forget that I'm here!)
That was incredible.
(We'll keep you in mind.)
(Change One, Change Both)
(If even 1 member picks a different card, they'll switch.)
The winning team will pick their cards.
Here we go.
(The team switching begins.)
1, 2, 3.
- What? - What?
(Jae Seok and Haha both choose Change Both.)
(If Eun Ji also picks that card, the team will be maintained.)
(What's her card?)
(She picks Change One.)
- What? - What?
(Change Both: 2, Change One: 1)
- They're different. - Okay!
- Change One. - Change One.
My gosh.
- Change One? - Do we change one member?
- Are you serious? - Look at Se Chan.
(Apink, are you watching me?)
- Look at him. - He's waiting.
What is this?
Since Eun Ji chose a different one, she'll pick.
There's someone who doesn't look like they belong there.
I see one person.
(Why is everyone looking at me?)
- What? - He realized that it's him.
By the way, Ji Yeon.
Why were you looking at your feet?
I was thinking, "No!"
- Right. - Are you sure about that?
- I mean... - Why didn't you say it?
I said something.
- She's so kind. - That's why I was doing this.
She really is kind.
Then...
(Which one of them will be expelled?)
- I'm fine either way. - Good work, Haha.
- Good work, guys. - Judging by the combination...
- I'm a fan. - Right?
- You know that, right? - Right?
If you're too happy about this,
- we'll bring you back. - I'm not happy.
I like you guys.
If you're being too happy, we'll bring you back.
What's wrong with you?
- Calm down. - Look at her.
She has a temper.
She doesn't know when to back down.
This is a new character.
- She doesn't know when to stop. - Where have you been all along?
Apink, go.
- Over there. - Is it our turn?
- The parasite. - "Parasite"?
(Are you talking about me?)
- She's talking about the movie. - "Parasite"?
- Yes, the movie. - She's talking about the movie.
This is a parasite.
(A group of people living in unsuitable environments)
"Parasite"?
- Come on. - I'm talking about the movie.
Did you seriously call me a parasite?
Apink, pick. 1, 2, 3.
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Lee Kwang Soo.
- Okay. - Gosh.
- Oh, no. - Oh, no.
- Hey. - It's Kwang Soo!
(Welcome)
This is great.
(When will you call my name?)
Team SORAN, please pick your cards.
1, 2...
(Will they switch or maintain?)
Three.
Change One.
(Change Both: 2 Change One: 1)
(Se Chan chooses Change One.)
Who is it? Oh, it's me.
- Hey. - I picked the wrong card. Really.
(You're so mean.)
To be honest,
this team needs someone who'll stick with them.
Hey, if you're talking about me, I refuse.
I pretty much became one with Code Kunst.
- I'm serious. - Don't lie.
Please say something!
- We didn't become one. - Hold on.
Hey, I'm not the only one. There's also Ji Hyo and him.
No, Se Chan. You belong in that team.
If Seok Jin goes over there, they'll be called KORAN.
All right, then. Let's create KORAN.
(He chooses Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin! Code Kunst is loving this.
He's so happy.
(Seok Jin and Se Chan switch places.)
- Hey, aren't you being too happy? - Okay.
- I'm just making it enjoyable. - SORAN!
(He quickly lets go of his former team.)
He didn't even look back.
- We did it! - Let's go.
Look.
If I move to Gummy's team, it'll be a Grand Slam.
- You're right. - I'm going to join that team.
Once I go there, it's game over.
He's right.
- If he comes here, it's all over. - He's hilarious.
(Current Partners)
What is this?
That's deep. I almost slipped.
It looks cool.
It may be hot out, but the water is still cold.
What is this?
We need to fall in. Or maybe we need to stop midway.
- Wait. - It's quite deep.
Look at Code Kunst.
(He shows a V.)
He didn't play around like this with Seok Jin.
- He became brighter. - I think it has finally begun.
This feels like our very first game.
Seok Jin is behind you.
(Staring)
So what? What can he do?
He's hilarious.
- He's so brave. - "What can he do?"
- He can't hold back any longer. - Be patient. I'll come back.
(I'm just kidding.)
By the way, Nucksal and Code Kunst are finally looking stable...
now that Se Chan has joined the group.
- I know. - You're right.
- They changed. - They're finally smiling.
I had no idea...
how mischievous Code Kunst could be.
He shows reactions. He's become so much brighter.
- I did the same before as well. - Did what?
- I joked around. - You joked around?
But he told me to stay put.
(Seok Jin banned him from playing around.)
- Seok Jin said that? - He did?
- Was he lording over him? - How could you do that?
He told me to sit down because everyone else was standing.
(He forced his surviving tips onto him.)
That was funny.
This is your last chance at picking your final partners.
It's called Ride the Conveyor Belt and Answer.
(Ride the Conveyor Belt and Answer)
Two members from each team will participate.
They will sit on this moving conveyor belt.
They must complete the given, random missions.
If they both succeed in making two rounds, they'll succeed.
But if you fail midway,
you will have to start from the beginning once again.
It sounds difficult.
I will tell you what the four random missions are.
First one is Color Game.
- What is that? - What is that?
If I say, "Red, blue, blue,"
you must say, "apple, sea, sky".
(Name things that are of those colors.)
- It sounds difficult. - It won't be easy.
The second one is Lee Kwang Soo Game.
- "Lee Kwang Soo Game"? - He has a game of his own?
If I say, "gimbap," you must pick either "gim" or "bap".
In three seconds,
you must answer what's opposite of mine.
Look. Let's say he said, "a bus".
- 1, 2, bus. - Bus.
- Then you lose. - Got it.
The third one is Speed Acrostic Poem.
If I say, "Yu Jae Seok," you must make a logical poem.
Elegant and fun...
- Man. - Man.
- It just needs to make sense? - If it makes sense, you succeed.
You know Say It Backwards, right?
Yes.
Say it backwards. Piano.
Anopi.
- Noapi. - Noapi.
If it's a wrong answer, please lower your voice.
I was certain.
Which team would like to go first?
- Se Chan and Code Kunst, go. - What do you mean?
- Go. - Se Chan and Code Kunst.
Should we go? Are you ready?
- Should we go first? - Code Kunst, go.
Don't back away.
(He nags and discourages him.)
- Come on. - He got up.
I was going to participate once you left our team.
(He's now determined to win.)
He's holding a grudge against Seok Jin.
Don't try too hard.
They might succeed at one go.
- Right. - There's a chance.
- Please! - All right.
- Let's start with Code Kunst. - You can do it!
- Watch me. - You must succeed!
- He wants you to watch him. - I will. I'll watch you.
Get ready.
(He acts tough but prepares his body for the water.)
Get ready, set, go.
Lee Kwang Soo Game.
Jjamppong. Jjam or ppong.
1, 2, 3.
- Jjam. - Ppong.
Okay!
(1 down, 3 to go.)
Speed Acrostic Poem. Son Na Eun.
Son Na Eun secretly thinks I'm attractive.
Okay!
(Son Na Eun secretly thinks I'm attractive.)
I approve.
(They pass the second round.)
Speed Acrostic Poem with Yu Jae Seok.
(Speed Acrostic Poem: Yu Jae Seok)
Yu Jae Seok isn't as funny as Seok Jin.
(Yu Jae Seok isn't as funny as Seok Jin.)
(Speed Acrostic Poem: Yu Jae Seok)
(Has Code Kunst mastered variety shows?)
(They only have one more game to complete.)
Color Game. Red, red, yellow.
(Color Game: Red, red, yellow)
Kimchi stew, apple, and...
Just keep going!
Color Game. Red, yellow, blue.
Kimchi stew...
(Code Kunst couldn't hold on any longer.)
(He gets the full course variety show treatment.)
(They're laughing their heads off.)
Red, yellow, and... Darn it.
(He takes a bath after grunting at the world.)
(They almost made it though.)
Is it over then?
This is too hard.
It's not easy at all.
You guys were great though.
We almost made it.
We'll go next.
The Tank Sisters. Nam Joo and...
- Cho Rong. - Right.
If you actually do this...
- Hold on. - I can't wait.
We can end it in this round.
- We can win. - It's perfectly doable!
(Pondering)
- Do we play one round each? - Nam Joo, fold your legs.
- What? - Do we play one round each?
- No, twice. - I don't get it.
You have to play two rounds each.
If you get it wrong, you have to start over.
I like how you're out there despite not knowing the rules.
I love it.
Just do as you wish!
You are the Tank Sisters!
- Gosh. - Just drive on.
They don't even know the rules.
- Get ready. - The Tank Sisters.
Ready, go!
Say It Backwards. Scandal.
- "Ladnacs". - Nice.
(1st round complete)
- Nice. - That was great.
Speed Acrostic Poem with Yu Jae Seok.
Yu Jae Seok, Jae Seok...
(Speed Acrostic Poem: Yu Jae Seok)
Hey, you're better looking than Seok Jin!
(Hey, you're better looking than Seok Jin!)
Unbelievable. She's just throwing about words.
Back to the start. Color Game. Red, yellow, blue.
Kimchi, banana, water.
- Nice. - You've got this!
Lee Kwang Soo Game. Pajeon. "Pa" or "jeon".
- Jeon! - 1, 2, 3.
(Why are you saying it first?)
- Jeon! - Jeon!
That's not it!
(She proves that she doesn't know the rules.)
Seriously?
Hey!
- Tank Sisters! - Do you not care about winning?
Speed Acrostic Poem with Kim Jong Kook.
(Falling and screaming!)
(She screams at the top of her lungs.)
(Cho Rong is scared amid of all that.)
Unbelievable.
Gosh, this is scary. Mom!
Are you guys kidding me?
How can she say the word first?
It wasn't even a mind game.
- I know. - What was she getting at?
How can you just say your answer?
Unbelievable.
So next up is SORAN and...
Sure, we'll go next.
My teammates...
Well, these two.
(My teammates...)
(Well, these two.)
Have you forgotten their names?
Really?
(To Seok Jin, he's just a man in glasses.)
- What? - What's his name?
He doesn't know his name?
(CEO Jee doesn't care about his employees' names.)
- Good luck. - Go, go!
Even I feel sorry.
If this team wins, Seok Jin will get the boot.
I don't know to which team, but he'll be kicked out.
Go, "Yang Bae".
- Here we go. - I'm ready.
So Min, good luck.
(Seo Myun Ho, Lee Tae Wook, Pyeon Yu Il)
Ready, go.
Say It Backwards. The Netherlands.
"Sdnal-Nether".
(Incorrect)
Say It Backwards. Shin Saimdang.
"Gnadmias Nihs".
Speed Acrostic Poem with Jee Seok Jin.
Jee Seok Jin truly hates Seok Jin.
(Jee Seok Jin truly hates Seok Jin.)
(They fail the 2nd round.)
- What? - Gosh.
Young Bae, come on.
Say It Backwards. Africa.
"Rica"... "Ricaf"...
(Say It Backwards: Africa)
(Rica!)
(Ricaf!)
(She spits out the incorrect answer as she throws herself.)
(What was that wailing?)
(Team SORAN fails its 1st attempt.)
That was loud and bold.
Four syllable words are difficult.
- Say It Backwards is hard. - It's too difficult.
Next up is Romantic Punch and Ant Man.
- Good luck. - The game is on.
- Okay. - Let's do this.
Ready, go.
Say It Backwards. Frog.
"Gorf".
Say It Backwards. Africa.
(Laughing)
(Africa, did you say?)
Moving on!
Lee Kwang Soo Game. Mushroom. "Mush" or "room". 1, 2, 3.
- Mush. - Room.
(1st round complete)
Lee Kwang Soo Game. Popcorn. "Pop" or "corn". 1, 2, 3.
- Corn. - Corn.
(Fails 2nd round)
(I should've taken Haha's spot.)
Say It Backwards. King Sejong.
(Splash!)
(He laughs when the question is too tricky.)
(He's suddenly doing an impression of King Sejong.)
(Why on earth does he keep on laughing?)
(We're just as doomed.)
Haha wasn't even participating.
All he did was laugh the entire time.
Now we're back to Nucksal and his sister.
The two are so alike.
- Let's go! - You've got this!
Ready, go.
Say It Backwards. South Korea.
"Aerok Hyuos".
(She took too long.)
It's a tricky one.
Lee Kwang Soo Game. Garlic. "Gar" or "lic".
- 1, 2, 3. Lic. - Gar!
That's it.
(She said "lic" first and then shifted to "gar".)
Lee Kwang Soo Game. Japchae. "Jap" or "chae".
- 1, 2, 3. - Chae!
- Jap. - Jap.
(I won't be fooled this time.)
(He tries the trick too.)
(He fails.)
- Nucksal, that's too bad. - It wasn't a bad idea.
- Gosh. - Speed Acrostic Poem.
(Yelping)
(Ji Hyo ends up taking a dive.)
(Speed Acrostic Poem: Yu Jae Seok)
Yu Jae Seok, please...
Kneel in contrition.
(Is he protesting so that he won't have to take a dive?)
Hey, what did I do wrong to kneel in contrition?
(He looks like the one who must apologize.)
- That was charming of you. - I couldn't help it.
- That was bold but friendly. - Shall we get going then?
Seok Jin, it's our turn.
- It's us. - Really?
- It's our turn. - We're Apink.
- It's our turn. - Oh, Apink.
Seok Jin's been participating in every game so far,
but he stays clear of the one that involves a dive.
- He won't participate. - You're the only one...
who's dry up here.
- Dry and dry - Dry and dry
(This is how Seok Jin survived on variety shows.)
All right then.
From our team, it'll be Na Eun and the giant.
- Right. - All right.
- I'll get it done. - Go on.
- I think they'll beat the game. - It's Na Eun and the giant.
We must win first place.
I have a place to be, so let's go.
- A place to be? - Let's do this!
He has a place to be.
- A place to be? - Yes.
Here we go then.
Ready, go.
Say It Backwards. Espana.
(Say It Backwards: Espana)
"Nas"...
How can Kwang Soo get this right?
Speed Acrostic Poem with Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo...
is a manic swimmer.
Nice!
(She made a perfect sentence.)
Speed Acrostic Poem with Son Na Eun.
Son Na Eun is the nation's...
(Kwang Soo, hurry!)
Tinfoil.
(Son Na Eun is the nation's tinfoil?)
(Son Na Eun, the nation's tinfoil)
- What is he saying? - My gosh!
(She ends up falling in anyways.)
My gosh.
(Poor Na Eun)
Say It Backwards. Spain.
"N"... "Niaps".
I can't believe him.
He's good for nothing, isn't he?
What do you mean she's the nation's tinfoil?
Gosh.
Are you that bad at improvisations?
Goodness.
Next up is Corporation SORAN.
Two of them!
(Two from Corporation SORAN!)
(You heard their names a few minutes ago.)
- Two of them! - What are their names?
Call them by their names.
- Go. - Seo Myun Ho and Lee Tae Wook.
- Myun Ho and Tae Wook. - "Myun Heo", cue!
It's Myun Ho, not Myun Heo.
- And Tae Wook. - Myun Ho and Tae Wook.
They look like two robots up there.
They are robots that play games.
The machines...
that do everything by the book.
- All right! - I have a good feeling about this.
I only accept loud voices from my employees.
- Yes, sir! - Got it!
It doesn't matter if we lose.
Lose with dignity!
The company's so old-fashioned.
Okay, here we go.
- Good luck. - Ready, go.
Speed Acrostic Poem with Jeon So Min.
Jeon So Min, let's eat beef.
(Speed Acrostic Poem: Jeon So Min)
Hurry!
Hey!
I can tell that he's nervous.
Color Game. Blue, blue, green.
(It's your turn.)
Hurry.
(Color Game: Blue, blue, green)
What are you doing?
(An error has occurred with Robot Number 2.)
What's going on?
Lee Kwang Soo Game.
Sky. "Sk" or "Y". 1, 2, 3.
- Y. - Y.
(Incorrect!)
(Corporation SORAN is close to bankruptcy.)
Oh, no. I really thought they'd make it.
It was adorable.
(The game's too tricky for variety show rookies.)
I honestly can't tell those two apart.
They seem like twins.
- I... - Twins?
Don't you agree?
Which one is which?
Tae Wook and Myun Ho are true amateurs.
- Amateurs? - True amateurs.
- Right. - Of course.
Say whatever you want, but those two are amateurs.
I haven't seen amateurs like those two before.
Next time get ready. We'll only do three games this time.
- Sure. - Three games?
Ready, go.
Say It Backwards. Ukraine.
"Nei... Ark..."
Lee Kwang Soo Game.
Choose between "Jjam" and "bbong". 1, 2, 3.
- Jjam! - Jjam!
(He failed again.)
Goodness.
Doesn't it look like it got faster?
It's getting faster.
(In return for just three wins to succeed, the belt is moving faster.)
- It's faster. - Why is it going so fast?
What was that? Turn it back again.
- No way! - Turn it back.
Move.
(We'll move if you don't.)
(This is how the pros do it.)
- That's too much. - That's enough.
(Giving a self-advantage without even consulting the staff)
(How far back are you going?)
Lee Kwang Soo Game.
Mathematics. Say "Math" or "matics".
1, 2, 3.
- Math. - Math. What was that?
Why do you keep saying the first syllable only?
(Why do you keep saying the first syllable only?)
(Yelling at junior producers)
- What did the producer do wrong? - Say It Backwards.
Live to look good.
"Good look..."
"to live." This is too fast.
- It's too fast. - Why is it going so fast?
Why is it so fast?
Is this a highway or what?
- Is this a freeway or something? - Why is it going so fast?
(He's using his strength to hold onto the belt.)
It's working.
(It stopped. We're good.)
(This team gets through everything by using force.)
Say It Backwards.
"Anne of Green Gables".
You think I can do that?
(He was going to get it wrong, but he at least dove in nicely.)
Poor guys.
Look at him.
He's giving up again.
This is too hard.
- Let's go. - We have to do good.
Good luck Eun Ji!
- Here comes the king of improv. - It's the king of improv.
The emperor of improv.
- Just watch. - He's incredible.
Watch how good he is at Say It Backwards.
- He beats the game itself. - He's like a rapper.
You know how hip-hop artists play with the beat?
I do that with words.
(I play with words like hip-hop artists play with the beat.)
He's also a master in Say It Backwards.
- I'm serious. - Watch how I improvise.
He even says things backwards in his sleep.
(Mythical stories about Jae Seok are spilling out from everywhere.)
- We'll get started now. - Let's go.
Start.
Say It Backwards. Highlighter pen.
- "Pen highlighter". - Good.
Speed Acrostic Poem.
(It's finally the emperor's turn.)
(It's time for him to show his unbelievable wit...)
(to all the inexperienced rookies.)
Speed Acrostic Poem.
- Jee Seok Jin. - Jee Seok Jin.
Jee Seok Jin.
Seok Jin.
(Jee Seok Jin, Jee Seok Jin, Seok Jin.)
What was that?
(It's too embarrassing to show our guests.)
Who are you trying to imitate?
Lee Kwang Soo Game. Meat pancakes. "Meat" or "pancakes".
- 1, 2, 3. Meat! - Pancakes!
- You got it. - Lee Kwang Soo Game.
Jjajang. "Jja" or "jang". 1, 2, 3.
- Jja. - Jja.
(The emperor fails again.)
Speed Acrostic Poem. Lee Kwang Soo.
(Trying to hold on)
Lee Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo...
is trash.
(Kwang Soo is trash.)
(Kwang Soo is trash!)
She called him trash.
(She left some wise words...)
That was good.
Why is that a fail?
Speed Acrostic Poem. Lee Kwang Soo.
- We need to go again. - Speed Poem. Lee Kwang Soo.
- Who? - Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo you brat!)
(He barely said anything but Kwang Soo feels insulted already.)
(What was that?)
(Jae Seok looked like such an amateur at this game.)
I called him trash.
Trash!
(We had no idea it could get worse than "manic swimmer".)
- Trash. - Trash.
- Kwang Soo the trash. - Kwang Soo the trash.
(Team Apink's third round is over just like that.)
- Let's go. - They understand the game now.
Ready, set, go.
Speed Acrostic Poem. Jee Seok Jin.
Ji Sang Yeol,
Seok Jin isn't nearly as funny as you are.
That's good.
Lee Kwang Soo Game. Seoul.
"Seo" or "ul". 1, 2, 3.
- Seo. - Ul.
- He's good. - They're good.
Just one more to go.
Speed Acrostic Poem. Kim Jong Kook.
(They'll be in the lead if he successfully makes up the poem.)
(Show us, Nucksal.)
Kim Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook...
does not drink soup from a saucer.
(Kim Jong Kook does not drink soup from a saucer.)
That was good.
(I didn't expect us to succeed!)
No way.
We did it!
(They succeeded just in three games, placing first.)
I finally met a good team.
They're so good.
(Code Kunst is all excited now.)
- They're so energetic. - They're full of energy.
They're loud kids like us.
- Good job! - Awesome!
(They can exchange a member and reject an order to exchange.)
Say It Backwards. Fight a hundred battles and win a hundred times.
Times hundred a win and battles hundred a fight.
"Trea" or "sure". 1, 2, 3.
- Trea. - Sure.
- Just one more to go. - Just one more.
Speed Acrostic Poem.
Jeon So Min.
The mighty So Min...
- is embarrassed. - That's right.
(It makes sense though it sounds weird, so they get a point.)
(Team SORAN is guaranteed second place.)
- That was good. - Okay.
So...
Team Nucksal and Code Kunst placed first.
We're in the lead.
Team SORAN is in second place.
(What will the first and the second place teams decide to do?)
Team Nucksal and Code Kunst, please come up first.
(There's no change if all teammates choose the same card.)
Are you all ready?
One.
Two.
(If they choose different cards, whoever chooses the wrong card...)
(receives the team member exchange card.)
Three.
(What did Team Nucksal and Code Kunst choose?)
(They all chose the same card.)
This team is set.
Get in here!
(Nobody can take anyone from this team anymore.)
Nobody can change this team now.
Team SORAN.
What should we do?
Let's all choose "Change Both".
Then we'll stay as we are.
(They've decided to choose the same card and stay together.)
- We're all staying, right? - Yes.
You like this team, right?
- You like us, right? - Of course, I do.
I love this team.
- Are you done discussing? - Yes.
Yes.
One.
(What will this team choose?)
Two.
- Three. - Here!
(Seok Jin and Young Bae chose the same card.)
(But wait.)
Changing one.
(So Min chose the member-changing card alone.)
- I didn't know that I chose this. - Seriously?
I really had no idea.
I seriously just picked the wrong card.
I really didn't know that it was this card.
I had no idea.
- I really didn't know. - No way.
So Min.
- I had no idea. - She planned this.
- She knew all along. - I really didn't know.
- This was her plan. - I had no idea.
(I honestly had no idea.)
(Kneels down)
Are you insane?
(After a long discussion, the Oldie CEO has decided to move.)
So Min, who do you want to bring to your team?
- We... - I can't believe this.
made our decision...
- after our long discussion. - Please.
We voted on this.
(Which team will Seok Jin end up in?)
(Will it be Team Gummy...)
(or Team Apink?)
(Seok Jin for...)
Jae Seok.
(for Jae Seok.)
(You're trading with our team?)
No, please don't.
(Team Gummy is staying as they are.)
Wow.
I didn't know that it was going to end up like this.
- We were the best team. - Now,
I present to you, the new CEO of Team SORAN.
You're here.
(Welcome, CEO Yu.)
Let's just be funny.
(Let's just be funny.)
(They've decided to be the funny team.)
Let's just be funny.
Hey, I released an album before.
Cho Rong, this is so sad.
Let's switch our uniforms now.
I can't even count how many times I've changed my uniforms.
(I've had to change too many times.)
- How many times have you changed? - You changed so many times.
It's amazing, really.
You're the biggest catch.
(Moving from one team to another is my forte.)
I'll try my best.
Great.
Team SORAN.
- Nice to meet you. - There's a frog here.
The frog and the grasshopper meet again.
(After the many exchanges, the teams are finally set.)
(A week later)
- Hello. - It's just as So Min described.
I told him that there were a lot of animals here.
This is Corporation SORAN.
(This is SORAN's place.)
- This is our first meeting. - Yes.
You all look good today.
(You all look good today.)
(They definitely tried harder to dress better this time.)
You're right. He even took his hat off.
I see...
a couple of awkward things here and there.
The awkward feeling in new clothes.
Look at your socks.
Did you match your socks with your guitar?
You're right.
I didn't know I'd be wearing these.
You really tried hard to look good today.
- Yes. - Anyway,
we ended the show off on a really bright note,
so I just didn't say anything,
but why did you have to get me on this team?
(Why did you have to get me on this team?)
Why did you do that?
(Why did you do that?)
I was going to be in a team with Apink.
I didn't complain then because I was busy laughing at Seok Jin.
I watched him go.
We really couldn't be on a team with Seok Jin.
(We really couldn't be on a team with Seok Jin.)
(We couldn't deal with that old-fashioned CEO.)
- Why? - We had a lot of clashes.
Why did you take me away from Apink?
- Do you know "Fake Love" by BTS? - Of course, I do.
Tae Wook played the guitar for that.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
Why didn't you tell me so earlier?
(Why didn't you tell me so earlier?)
Why didn't you?
You should've told me earlier.
This is exactly the type of things you need to tell me.
I told you.
- I'm sorry, but... - This is...
this is the key to my heart.
I'm disappointed in you.
Can you play a bit of "Fake Love" for me?
When I was recording the song,
I made the part so that it can't be played by just one person.
It's such a difficult part that he can't play it live.
The live version is played by someone else.
(What does that mean?)
- Really? - So what is it?
You made the part, but can't play it live?
I've never played it live.
What about the recent song?
- That one... - What about "Boy With Luv"?
- That one... - Did you also play "Boy With Luv"?
Yes.
Can you play it now?
I can't remember how it goes.
(I can't remember how it goes.)
(What do you mean, you can't remember?)
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
You can't play "Fake Love"...
or "Boy With Luv" for us?
(Sorry, Tae Wook is a bit off because he's genius.)
Seriously.
Something sounds fishy.
You can't play at all?
Fine.
For now, let's hear...
a nice song you prepared.
There is a pretty cheerful song,
a medium-tempo ballad song that would have strong music sales,
and a totally cheerful song. There are three songs.
- You prepared different songs. - We prepared the outlines.
You should listen to them.
- Shall we do that? - Yes.
- A pretty cheerful song. - A pretty cheerful song.
It won't be half-bad for a performance.
- That's good. - We will play that first.
- A pretty cheerful song. - A pretty cheerful song.
(Playing the melody)
(He rides the rhythm and gets ready to show good cheer.)
(It feels good.)
(They are good.)
(Their hands and feet move to the rhythm.)
(They have the perfect teamwork.)
(The first song...)
(uplifts their mood with the varied beats and sweet melody.)
- That's how it goes. - It's really nice.
- That's the song. - It's really nice.
It's a bit like pop music.
- You are correct. - Right?
- It's like pop music. - It's like pop music.
It wouldn't be strange if it goes on the Billboard charts.
(He tries to sell the song.)
(The Billboard charts?)
That's right.
Your ambition exceeds your popularity.
(His ambition is big enough for the Billboard.)
(They can't deny it.)
Your ambition...
- I get that a lot. - Seriously.
I have always taken good care of my image...
in case I become a star.
I see that Yu Il can play the drums better than I expected.
- Thank you. - He is cool.
- You didn't expect that. - I thought...
the band was built on friendship.
(He thought SORAN was built on friendship.)
I had never witnessed your talent.
I now see that everyone is quite talented.
What's the song that will top digital music charts?
- That's... - The medium-tempo song.
Are you sure of it?
- It will be a mega-hit. - Really?
You won't be able to walk down the street.
- Is it that good? - If we pick this song,
we will need to form a group.
I am a bit afraid of that.
Has SORAN ever topped digital music charts?
We will do that with this song.
- This is the beginning. - That's right.
- We will top the charts. - This is the beginning.
That's right.
You will take the first step with us.
The newborn on digital music charts.
Let's hear the song that will top...
- digital music charts. - All right.
We will play it.
[VIU Ver] SBS E459 Running Man
"A Collaboration with Artists - Teamwork Race Part 2"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(The mood is quite different from that of the first song.)
I am in tears already.
(He scoffs.)
- Are you in tears? - Yes.
(It's a melody that will captivate women's hearts.)
(This song is nice.)
I am getting ideas for the lyrics.
It could be the theme song for a movie.
I agree.
(The sentimental melody makes you recall a movie scene.)
(SORAN's ballad song that will top the digital music charts)
Gosh, this song...
I already have an idea for the lyrics.
Someone is watching from the sky.
- What? - Who is watching?
- Someone... - Grandpa?
It could be the grandpa, dad, or mom.
They make the rain fall or the sun shine.
I had that idea.
I think it could be a song about love.
That's a good idea.
Out of the songs we have,
I wrote one as I thought about my daughter.
- "Sunshine"? - Yes.
That song...
So Min, how involved are you in this band?
(So Min, how involved are you in this band?)
- She isn't involved. - Hold on.
- She just likes the band. - It seems like...
- My face turned red. - everyone else except for me...
is in the band.
("So Min Is Revealed As the 5th Member of SORAN")
- It looks like... - It's not like that.
the five of you are in the band.
Why did you call me here?
What is going on?
(I knew something wasn't right.)
- You prepared three songs. - Yes.
This song is totally cheerful.
- It's very cheerful. - It's very cheerful.
- It's totally cheerful. - Okay. Let's hear it.
All right.
(The drum sound explodes from the start.)
(This is cheerful.)
(The beat and melody liven up the atmosphere.)
(They are in sync.)
(SORAN's music is lively and cheerful.)
Sing anything.
(Singing)
(I knew you could do it!)
(I can't believe them.)
(Did So Min succeed to make a melody in one go?)
Hold on. Here is what I think.
You had a rehearsal, right?
Of course not.
How could you toss the microphone as if it's the most natural thing?
It's obvious that you had a rehearsal.
- That's not true. - Jeon So Min,
- how are you related to SORAN? - It's not like that.
Jeon SORAN.
("Band SORAN IS Actually Jeon SORAN")
Be quiet. Jae Seok will grow suspicious.
You will name the team Jeon SORAN and kick me out, right?
(Congratulations on forming Jeon SORAN)
For goodness' sake.
- Am I wrong? - Yes, you are.
- You are wrong. - You are wrong.
All right.
So Min, which song did you like?
If you don't like these three songs...
(He becomes a salesman.)
- There's more? - I could make three more songs...
and send them this week.
- That's incredible. - Is there a song factory?
Since we are a band, we can gather and work on songs anytime.
- Can you do that? - Jae Seok.
He doesn't even remember "Fake Love".
(He doesn't even remember "Fake Love".)
Can you really do that?
How can you do that when you don't even remember...
"Fake Love"?
- It's a different matter. - Really?
He can make new songs.
- He follows his feelings. - That's right.
Is there a keyword or a mood...
- Genre. - you want?
You could choose a genre or a part of the lyrics.
So Min, ask them to make a song for your poem.
If you recite your poem,
- we will make a song. - You wrote one at 2am.
Do you have a poem you wrote down?
Yes, I do. I have a lot of poems.
(Yes, I do. I have a lot of poems.)
Do you have a lot of poems?
She is not kidding.
- She has a lot of poems. - Which one should I use?
The nickname Jong Kook gave, Crazy Poet, suits her.
There are so many.
"Nothing to talk about but you."
It's too short.
- "Nothing to talk about but you." - "Nothing to talk about but you."
Yes. I wrote down that line.
"Nothing to talk about but you."
When I have a boyfriend, only my friends know about him.
After a breakup, I have nothing to talk about but him.
- It's only a line. - With your friends,
you talk about your ex.
That's the mood.
"Nothing to talk about but you."
Then it should be a bit melancholy.
The key of B major.
I might cry.
"Nothing to talk about but you."
(The melody is produced right away.)
In 2, 3, 4.
"Nothing to talk about but you."
(The melody is produced right away.)
In 2, 3, 4.
2, 3, 4.
(They produce a ballad song after exchanging a few glances.)
Please turn off the camera so that I can cry.
I can't believe it.
(The melancholy melody suits the poem So Min wrote.)
It's fitting.
At a get-together with friends
There were many things I wanted to say
- This is fascinating. - Seriously.
Today, as always
I have nothing to talk about but you
(I have nothing to talk about but you)
(It's So Min's turn to sing...)
(to Yu Il's beats.)
I have nothing to talk about but you
All right.
(It's cringe-worthy.)
(SORAN's performance suits...)
For goodness' sake.
(the emotions So Min felt when she wrote the poem.)
(Embarrassed)
Stop tucking your hair behind your ear.
You will graze your skin.
(I am a woman with a past.)
Stop tucking your hair behind your ear.
(Poet Jeon So Min and SORAN had a successful jam session.)
So Min.
It's so fascinating.
I know.
I have so many poems right here.
(I have so many poems right here.)
(Poet Jeon and SORAN could have endless collaborations.)
She has so many poems.
I have many poems. "You can call me at night."
That's one.
("You can call me at night"?)
In that case...
She is resolute.
- "You can call me at night." - The lyrics are very resolute.
"You can call me at night."
Here is another one. "I don't remember..."
"which ramyeon I had..."
"with you."
That's a good one.
"I don't remember which ramyeon I had with you".
I will start with that...
- and wrap up... - Okay.
- with "You can call me at night." - Okay.
This is so fascinating.
(The melody comes out right away.)
All right.
It's good. It's good.
(In a flash, they jump to the middle of the night.)
I will tell you this
Since you aren't drinking
It suits the mood.
- It's perfect. - Yes.
I don't remember which ramyeon I had with you
You can call me at night
(You can call me at night)
- How should it go? - Give the microphone to So Min.
(So Min gets the microphone.)
You can call me at night
- I am singing out of tune. - You are doing well.
(Laughing)
It's okay because I am drunk
All right. All right. It seems like...
SORAN and So Min have good teamwork.
She is pretty good. I think she is better than me.
Seriously.
I can't believe you came up with a song right away.
- It's fascinating. - Then why can't you play...
"Fake Love"?
(Then why can't you play "Fake Love"?)
(You can have an impromptu jam session.)
You are talented enough to do this.
Why can't you play "Fake Love"?
He should practice, but...
- He doesn't practice. - He keeps saying he can't do it.
I will play a bit of it.
(I will play a bit of it.)
This is the first time.
- Seriously. - He never plays it.
- It will be really short. - It's okay.
(This melody is...)
(It's the guitar intro of "Fake Love" by BTS.)
(They hear the live performance of the guitar accompaniment...)
He can play it.
(Tae Wook recorded for the song.)
- Then it moves on. - Tae Wook is amazing.
- I heard it for the first time. - SORAN can do anything.
- That's right. - They cover all genres.
They cover all genres.
SORAN and So Min go well together in terms of sentimentality.
I'm the one who doesn't fit.
(That's the problem.)
(Jae Seok got fooled by the 5 members of Jeon SORAN.)
SORAN and So Min go well together, but I don't.
I am the problem.
(Will Jae Seok be able to perform with Jeon SORAN?)
(Meanwhile, a studio in Gangnam)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It has been a while. - It has been a while.
It has been a while.
It's an honor to work with you.
Their voices...
(He stops in the middle of high-fiving everyone...)
(and makes a U-turn.)
Why didn't you high-five me? High-five me.
It's enough that I high-fived half of the group.
(Shortened greetings)
- What? - We don't have much time.
For goodness' sake.
Let's sit down.
A bit later,
we will meet a composer who will help us.
- A composer? - Yes.
We are having a meeting for the theme today.
Are we have a meeting for the theme today?
(Is that what we are doing today?)
What did you think we were doing today?
- I had no idea. - I am so confused right now.
We dance when we are asked to dance.
- I wonder who the composer will be. - Hey!
(Who will be composing the song for Team Apink?)
Gosh, you look like a designer.
(Composer Nang)
(The melody you remember after hearing it only once.)
("LUV" by Apink)
("Bboom Bboom" by MOMOLAND)
("Up and Down" by EXID)
(Every song he composes makes it into the charts.)
Hello, I am Nang of B and N.
It's nice to meet you.
- Nang. - Nang.
I am nervous to meet a big-time composer.
- Really? - I am nervous.
- The two of us... - Seok Jin will realize his dream...
of becoming a singer.
I will put my life on the line for this.
- Seriously. - Really?
Let's hear you sing. I need to do a key check.
- I need to see how well... - What's a key check?
We...
(What kind of a key is he talking about?)
- It's to see your vocal range. - I see.
All right. How about...
- we sing in here? - Okay.
- I will sing "I Miss You". - Please go ahead.
It's his favorite song to sing.
(Will he really sing "I Miss You" by Kim Bum Soo?)
He also likes to sing "Love" by Jo Jang Hyuk.
- I will play the melody. - "The memories..."
(The test begins in earnest.)
(How well can Kwang Soo sing?)
In 2, 3.
The memories
(It's the perfect cacophony.)
Please let me start over.
(He quickly gives up.)
Please give me one more chance.
(He crushes their expectations.)
- Give me one more chance. - All right.
- I will sing properly this time. - Okay.
- You can do this. - Don't be nervous.
Don't be nervous.
- This is great. - You got this.
(He warms up his throat and goes again.)
In 2, 3.
The memories of loving you
Like crazy
(The memories of loving you like crazy)
(He can hit high notes.)
(The recollections)
(Look for you)
(I didn't think his voice would go up.)
(I can no longer)
(It sounds like he is herding cows.)
(He wraps up like a singer.)
You did a good job.
- It's was the original key, right? - Yes.
He sang better than I expected.
All right.
Is there a genre...
- or a concept you have in mind? - Is there?
There used to be a group called Sharp.
That's right.
"Sweety".
I love it. I love it.
This is really nice.
(Cheerful music like Sharp's would go well with Team Apink.)
- It will be fun. - Girl groups need to have...
the right facial expressions on the stage.
(The right facial expressions matter as much as the singing skills.)
- That's right. - Acting skills.
We won't be able to look cute.
Right?
I have never tried it.
(We will give you a demonstration.)
(Such freshness is rare on Running Man.)
That was the facial expression!
(When she dances to the rhythm naturally,)
(her fresh charms explode.)
- That's how you do it. - She is really good.
Their facial expressions are a work of art.
Bo Mi, my goodness.
(She melts men's hearts...)
(with the alluring finale.)
(The epitome of perfection)
That was the facial expression!
We will be an eyesore if we try those facial expressions.
Would you do the chorus?
Their facial expressions changed...
in accordance with the lyrics.
They didn't only smile. They glared as well.
- There was a hint of sadness too. - Yes.
How do they change their facial expressions so fast?
I will play the song.
Let's see how it looks.
(They watched Apink's performance.)
1, 2, 3. Do you remember?
(He moves to the rhythm.)
(Please open the door.)
That's not our dance.
L, O, V, E, love
Are you having a seizure? Are you getting an electric shock?
(Electric shock dance)
An electric shock!
(His unique dance...)
(makes them scream.)
(How do I look?)
(I look refreshing, right?)
(It looks like he is channeling a spirit.)
He is good.
Gosh, I am sweating.
(They have no words.)
This audition is necessary for the performance, right?
(This audition is necessary for the performance, right?)
- I had to ask. - Do we need to act cute?
(What kind of a song will be created?)
- My goodness. - Have you been well?
This is Code Kunst's company,
- You must have made a lot of money. - AOMG.
- That's right. - The building is very big.
- Let's sit down. - Okay.
So, what do you think?
Will things work out?
We have starred in a few audition programs.
Things always work out. Don't worry.
I have recorded rap verses...
a few times.
- Really? - Yes.
- You have never done it, right? - I have done it...
for Gary's...
"Turned off the TV".
- That's right. - I did Yoon Mi Rae's part.
Gary told me not to do it again.
(Gary told me not to do it again.)
(You should stay an actress.)
If Gary said that...
He was like, "Are you singing a children's song?"
Will you be able to fix her part, Code Kunst?
- I will be able to do that. - Really?
- It's the power of digital devices. - Computers are advanced these days.
- Really? - We can use technologies.
You can trust the power of digital devices.
- Really? I see. - The recording will be nice.
But we won't be allowed to lip-sync. We need to sing.
That's right.
There is such a thing as doubling.
- So we just overlap it? - Right.
- With everything in the background. - I just adjust it all.
- Or... - Look at these guys.
- They're like con artists. - For example...
What are you talking about?
- They're con artists. - That's not it.
I want someone else from AOMG.
- Get me someone else. - That's not it.
- That's not what we mean. - I see you're trying to con us.
- We were about to get fooled. - Wait a second.
- Did you do this every time? - No.
- Using tricks... - No, no.
- That's not it. - We don't need that trick.
- Right? - But...
- for amateurs like... - Oh, so you use that technique...
for amateurs.
- And you have to be good. - You have to be good to begin with.
- That's a given. - Right, right.
But even if you do things poorly, these techniques will cover for it.
That's all you need to know.
(Don't worry. Your ability can be boosted at any time.)
Gosh, it's confusing.
Don't you have a lot of songs in your flash drive, Code Kunst?
- You must have many hidden songs. - Right.
I think we still have to make a new song.
Right, based on something that's already been made.
I have one in mind. The kind of rap I want to do.
- In the middle of the performance, - What is it?
the lights would turn off,
and I'd rap like crazy without any accompaniment.
That's like BewhY.
(The way BewhY raps is to do it under the spotlight.)
I'd stand under the spotlight with the sound of heavy breathing.
(He wants the spotlight and the sound of heavy breathing.)
People would wonder what this is about.
- Then I'd start rapping. - With the light shining on you.
(Shooting out his rap)
- Like how BewhY does. - Like BewhY.
(Audience cheering)
Your mouth looks similar to that of BewhY.
- A bit, right? - Yes.
BewhY and Dok2.
(He wants to perform like BewhY and look like Dok2.)
"I'm Dok2."
"I'm Dok2. Get me a building."
(In short, he wants to do everything that's cool.)
I want something with a strong climax.
I'll bring some songs I have. Around three of them.
Let's see what your preference is by listening to them.
Just feel free to choose what you like.
Choose something that's easy to pull tricks.
(Don't be like that.)
Wouldn't that be good for us?
- A song that's easy to pull tricks. - I've brought songs...
- Let's do that. - with that in mind.
- Let's check your preference. - Okay.
Okay.
I've got everything here.
A bad guy, an excited guy,
- A strange guy, a sad guy. - and a sad guy.
What kind of guy do you want to be?
A crazy guy.
"A crazy guy"?
A mad guy.
(He wants to be crazy on stage.)
(It's beyond imagination.)
(His fiery eyes are full of madness.)
(I think his dream has already come true.)
People would cheer.
(Making weird sounds)
- That's wrestling. - No, I mean...
- What is this? - I've got to do it.
I've got to hear my audience shout.
Ji Hyo and I have to hear that.
"Ji Hyo!" Like this.
- I want madness. - Okay.
This would be good for festivals.
(The first beat prepared by Code Kunst)
- It's "Orange". This one's nice. - This is...
This one is really nice.
I'd make an appearance here.
- He's imagining the performance. - I am.
- Like this. - He's a professional.
You'd come up from the bottom of the stage.
I like this.
(It makes them imagine their performance just by listening.)
Then goes the rap.
Oh, yes.
(They love the beat.)
- Good. - This is one.
- This is one. - I love it.
- The second one has a theme. - What is it?
Its title is "Before the Club".
It's about the excitement right before you enter a club.
(She knows how it feels.)
Let's listen to it.
Good.
But the club is a bit classy.
- A high-class club. - With champagne served.
(He knows the feeling.)
(A luxurious champagne party)
This would be played in slow motion.
And I'd do this next to you.
(She'd do this beside him.)
(Showing off her luxurious body wave)
- It's nice. - I like this.
It feels like summer.
(Shall I go in now?)
(The player enters the club.)
Popping champagne.
(Champagne is popped, and the mood goes popping.)
(And her body wave as the finishing touch)
(Nucksal and Code Kunst's luxurious club party)
That looks good, Ji Hyo.
They're good.
(They've fallen in love with the second beat as well.)
This one's incredible too.
- Our fans would love it. - These kinds of mood...
- But... - "But"?
Because it's actually... Ji Hyo.
I'm worried so much to be honest.
What's making you worried?
- What's your biggest concern? - What is it?
- I feel like I have to do well. - I see.
- Just have fun. - That's the hip-hop spirit.
Why don't you...
show us how you do that part, Ji Hyo?
You mentioned you rapped in "Turned off the TV".
Right, I did.
- Do you remember the lyrics? - Yes.
- Did you memorize them? - Of course.
All right.
(They play the song first.)
It's a part that goes, "Why are you turning off the TV when it's hot?"
- It's here. - Why are you drawing the curtains?
I'm watching TV, so why are you turning it off?
Why are you looking at me like that again?
I'm tired, I just want to sleep
(This is why Gary told her never to rap again.)
(Mumbling)
It's so funny, I'll think about it
Go turn the lights off
- I'm so embarrassed - No.
- Ji Hyo. - Turn off the cameras.
- Turn off the cameras. - Goodness.
- Turn off the lights. - Lights off.
- Turn the lights off. - And the TV too.
(Her rapping skills make them want to turn everything off.)
- Turn them off. - Turn off every machine here.
Turn all the machines off.
Turn off your phones. Turn it all off.
Is that enough?
Oh, yes.
(Digital technology is their superpower.)
Are you serious?
As long as you can talk, it's good enough.
As long as we can hear your voice.
I don't think I can trust you guys.
- What's wrong with you? - Is this really a company?
I'm confused. Can I trust really them?
As long as you can stamp your feet and clap your hands,
we can make a song for you.
(Ji Hyo will be a digital rapper in the 21st century.)
We need to hear Se Chan rap properly too.
Me? All right.
- What can you do? - I'll do something I can show off.
Is there any song you enjoy singing at karaoke rooms?
- "Guilty". - "Guilty", okay.
(Rapping clearly)
(He shows an unexpected rapping ability with clear diction.)
(He eventually becomes out of breath.)
I think I have to break up with her today
He's out of breath.
(His rap suffocates the others as they watch.)
- He might end up dying. - I know.
It might kill him.
I can do this much.
- Okay. - What do you think? Is it okay?
These days,
hip-hop has changed a lot.
You shouldn't speak clearly.
- I see. - Oh, really?
People used to go, "Hello, I'm Nucksal."
- But not anymore. - "Hello, I'm Nucksal."
(A difference between old hip-hop and new hip-hop)
- Really? - Isn't that a bit too rude?
- That's... - It's too insincere.
It's too rude. We shouldn't be like that on TV.
You've got to record a song within three minutes after you wake up.
- Are you serious? - When your voice is...
- I can do a good job with that. - still down.
- Ji Hyo is confident. - Ji Hyo,
what you did wasn't bad. It sounded loose.
- My voice was... - It's trendier.
(Ji Hyo's rap is a bit trendier.)
What?
- I'm telling you. - Are you serious?
(Ms. 40, aka Trendy Rapper)
- What she did... - Hey.
- was trendy? - My style is trendier than yours.
- This is upsetting. - Sit back down.
- Sit down. - Her rap is more trendy?
Maybe I should play this for her.
Play what?
I'm playing this for Ji Hyo...
so that she learns from this person's confidence.
He fills the song only with sound words.
(He plays a song for Ji Hyo to regain her confidence.)
(Rapping)
(He catches it.)
(Making sounds)
You're good.
(Speaking sound words)
(Exclaiming)
What you just did...
- comes out in the later part. - What?
Try listening to this.
There.
(Woof, woof)
(Barking)
How was that?
(He's indeed a "want-to-be" crazy guy.)
They rap like this too. And it leads to my point.
You can pull it off if you have confidence.
- You heard the last part. - Don't you agree?
- This is about confidence. - Right.
Let's try doing it while we're at it.
Write what you will say here.
You mean, this?
- Why not? - We're doing this?
Let's give it a go.
This is about confidence. I can do it.
(Her eyes shake.)
- I'll write words for you. - Right, right.
(Nucksal will rap freestyle first, then Ji Hyo will follow.)
Try rapping.
(Amazed)
(Sound words for Ji Hyo are complete too.)
When do I start?
Hold on.
Here it comes. 2, 3, 4.
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - Now.
(Giddy-up)
(Woot, woot)
(There you go.)
(Alright)
(Se Chan takes over.)
Just say it like this.
What is that?
I just wrote random words.
Don't hesitate.
What is that?
It's not bad.
I know.
- You can do it too. - Right.
- He's too hilarious. - Don't worry about backup sounds.
- You don't have to worry either. - It's good.
I have 500 of these.
Various ones.
- You're an artist. - Don't you worry.
- I've got it. - That's improvisation.
Why don't we just record a song now?
- Let's go with it. - You can do it too, Ji Hyo.
- Right, everyone can do it. - I'm telling you.
In my opinion,
we should include what we just listened to.
Then I'll make a group chat for us...
and share three songs with you...
- including what we just listened. - Let's share songs that way.
I'm sorry,
but she can't be in that group chat.
- You don't have the messenger app? - She doesn't have it.
- Then... - She's 40.
(Whispering that she's 40)
(You little...)
So it's illegal from the age of 40.
- Hey. - Right.
What are you talking about?
Then we'll record the songs on a tape and hand it to you, Se Chan.
- You have a cassette player, right? - You've got all these machines.
- She might use a messenger swallow. - "Swallow".
That's centuries ago.
Or a letter.
- Goodness. - We'll share them with you somehow.
(Code Kunst's beat will be delivered via cassette tape.)
- I've been to this studio before. - Oh, really?
Have a seat here.
What do we do?
- Have you been well? - Yes.
- And you? - Did you write any songs?
(Asking out of the blue)
(Flustered)
- Nothing has been decided yet. - Oh, really?
Yes, of course.
Gummy, we have all our trust in you.
- We're depending on you. - Really?
I was depending on you guys.
- I didn't think about anything. - I thought about it,
and even after giving it a lot of thought,
I can't think of anything because Haha is in our group.
(I can't think of anything because Haha is in our group.)
Me too.
Honestly, I don't know how I can fit between you two.
- Honestly, - And it's not like I can sit out.
things were easier when we had Kwang Soo in our group.
I agree.
Things got harder when you joined our team.
- It's puzzling, isn't it? - Yes.
- We have different colors. - You have such a distinct voice...
and color.
Then maybe you should just leave the song preparation to me.
Why don't I make it my style?
- Reggae? - No.
To be honest,
since I'm in this group,
I thought a traditional ballad would be nice.
But what's important...
is that I've never heard you sing a ballad before.
I need to hear you sing...
- seriously. - But...
I get shy when I get put on the spot.
I need to feel comfortable first.
- Get used to the surroundings? - Yes, and then...
maybe we can talk about love.
- What's a good ballad? - Or...
- maybe a Shin Seung Hun song? - What's something recent?
- Sure, a Seung Hun song is good. - Those are high.
What about "Reflection of You in My Smile".
"Reflection of You in My Smile".
- Do you have the lyrics? - Yes.
("Reflection of You in My Smile" by Shin Seung Hun is...)
(one of the legendary songs in the history of Korean ballads.)
(It was a debut album that sold over a million copies.)
(How will a traditional ballad by Haha sound?)
More than a rose
Hold on.
- Hold on. Sorry. - Keep going. You can do it.
(Don't worry. Keep going.)
This is good.
(Continuing on with the song with Gummy's support)
A fragrant stronger than that
Seems like your voice isn't that low, either.
(Haha is surprising everyone with his ballad-singing skills.)
Don't just throw the note into the air.
You are warmer than that
- You're really good. - This is good.
Why did you do that again?
Don't do that.
(Blushing)
Think of it as projecting thinner sounds.
(Think of it as projecting thinner sounds.)
Okay, this is good.
That's all I need to hear.
(Running away)
I can't do this!
(I can't do this at all!)
We're good. I see hope.
- He's... - Let's do a ballad.
You're just very stubborn...
- with the syllables you emphasize. - That's right.
- Let's do a ballad. - This is embarrassing.
You're really good.
- Can I be honest? - Sure.
I was the lead of the alto section in the YMCA choir.
Alto?
Since we've all tested me,
I'm going to test you.
I know you two are good,
- but let's hear it. - A duet?
- Can you do a duet? - I've never done one with a lady.
Can you do a duet?
Do you know "Scars Deeper than Love"?
I know the song.
Do you know "The Blue in You"?
- I need to see the lyrics. - That's fine.
You can read the lyrics as you go. You can sit here.
This is such an honor.
- I've never done this, but... - This is such an honor.
- This is incredible. - Let's do a song that you know.
(How will the best ballad artists of Korea sound together?)
Maybe we should've just met up at a karaoke place.
I close my eyes
The light and the sight of you are fading away
Now in the darkness
(The queen of RnB is ringing through everyone's souls.)
In the deep blue
Why are you slipping away
The world
Is still standing by you
- Although it is not love - Although it is not love
- When we met - When we met
- It lifted the darkness - It lifted the darkness
(The perfect harmonies make it hard to believe that this is an improv.)
(This is how an improvised duet of the two best ballad singers sound.)
- The sight of you in my eyes - In my eyes
(Harmony that heals your soul)
There's no way this is the first time you sang together.
You definitely met up last week.
That's incredible.
- You're being too nice. - There's no place for me here.
No, why don't we try singing this together, the two of us?
(Try singing the song with me.)
Come on.
- It's going to sound funny. - Not at all.
(How will the reggae kid and the queen of ballad sound together?)
I'm dreaming
My time with you has stopped
(It's almost Haha's time to sing.)
This is crazy.
(Rain)
(You're doing fine.)
(He's trying to sing as gently as possible.)
- That's good. - That's it.
Let's sing all together. Jong Kook, sing in unison with Haha.
(Although it isn't love)
You can lower the octave if it's too high for you.
(When we met)
(They sound much more stable, thanks to Gummy's advice.)
(Their different voices actually sound great together.)
The sight of me in your eyes
The sight of you
- In my eyes - In my eyes
(Team Gummy has a very unique blend of voices.)
That's awesome.
I know I sang it, but that was absolutely beautiful.
I got goosebumps.
Honestly, that was just too beautiful.
This was my first time singing in harmony since YMCA.
- First time harmonizing. - You are singing an octave lower...
but still in unison with us...
- that made it sound perfect. - I liked it too.
- Right? - Let's settle with a ballad.
Let's take some time to decide whether we'll go traditional...
- or something different. - This is incredible.
This is unbelievable.
(They're locked inside a building deep inside the mountains?)
(The members are locked inside a building.)
(The only hope is the five exits.)
(Another escapee, Cho Jung Seok, is here.)
(A charming lady, Yoon A)
(Right then, as soon as someone opened the first exit,)
(the other exits began disappearing.)
(In a mess of mysterious things being spotted one by one,)
(will the members be able to escape safely?)
There must be something else.
(Five Exits: Escape to Live)