- My gosh, it's starting now. - Goodness.
It's winter!
This is a perfect place to bring your family. My son will love this.
Gosh, It's so nice to come to a ski resort.
- At nights, they light up candles. - You would book a room here.
- They light them up here? - Yes, the street looks so pretty.
- Is that so? - It's an awesome spot...
- for couples to visit. Yes. - Photos will look so beautiful.
I'll come back here when I get a boyfriend!
You can bring your family here.
- Hey, look at Se Chan's hair. - What?
- Se Chan, what's up with your hair? - He got a cute haircut.
- After my haircut, - My gosh.
- people said... - It looks familiar. Yeom Sang Soo.
(We've definitely seen it somewhere.)
He copied Yeom Sang Soo's hairstyle.
I went to Gangnam for this haircut. They said this was trending now.
- Did you perm your side hair? - This haircut... Yes.
- It's the down perm. - You got the down perm?
- You had the down perm? - I got my front and back permed.
- Why did you get your hair permed? - I mean...
I was told I would look much younger if I kept my side hair down.
You can just use a few grains of rice to keep it down.
(You didn't need the perm.)
Grains of rice? Did you say grains of rice?
- You can mash them, - I'm a celebrity, after all.
filter them in the water, and apply it in the morning. It works well.
- Grains of rice? - Mash some grains of rice.
I thought that was your penalty.
- My hairstylist said it was great. - Exactly. I thought...
if Se Chan lost the race last week or something.
I wondered if the hairstyle was part of his penalty.
It doesn't matter if I get my hair done in Gangnam.
You know that two of your members are missing, right?
- We had no idea. - Me neither.
- I thought they were with us. - What?
- It's the penalty. - What? I see. The penalty.
- They had a penalty to face. - Come on out.
(What happened to Seok Jin and Kwang Soo who dreamed of revenge?)
- Hello. - Hi. Happy New Year.
Hi. Happy New Year.
- You should take off your shirt. - That's not a penalty.
- Hold on. What is that? - Come on.
- Their given penalty... - That was lame.
(A flood of criticisms)
Hey, what's wrong with you? Wearing this doesn't feel rewarding.
- That's too weak to be a penalty. - That's lame.
- Se Chan and I did that once. - This outfit is so embarrassing.
(He feels wronged.)
Hey, Kwang Soo. What is this? My goodness.
I've worn one with roosters. I began from the Year of Monkey.
Oh, right. He's the go-to guy for these kinds of outfits.
All right. You two have lost the race last week.
As a way to celebrate the Year of the Golden Pig,
you must give out every stuffed pig in your sacks...
to join today's opening segment.
I'm all for the penalty.
But wearing this in a ski resort is too much.
(My gosh, I must take a photo of this!)
Gosh, this is...
(Embarrassing 2019)
Come on, it's the start of the New Year.
(Paying for the misfortune of 2019)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Do you want a stuffed pig?
(They start carrying out the penalty.)
- My gosh, your outfit. - Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year. - Thank you.
Hello, kid. Do you want one?
Say hello to him.
Do you want one?
Anthony, do you want a stuffed pig?
(Shaking his head)
- Do you not want it? - Wait.
(Please take one. I want to finish this.)
- He said he doesn't want it. - What?
I have a lot of plushies at home.
- He has a lot at home. - You don't want it?
- I have a lot of plushies at home. - I see.
- What's wrong? - He doesn't want one.
- He doesn't want one? - He has a lot at home.
- He already has a lot. - Gosh, he's so cute.
Bye.
- Happy New Year. - My gosh!
Happy New Year. Goodness.
- Happy New Year. - Thank you.
Bye.
That's lame. Really.
- This isn't funny at all. - They should've laughed.
Hold on. I'm funnier.
- Se Chan's hairstyle is funnier. - My hairstyle is funnier.
I'm serious. His hairstyle is funnier.
My gosh, they're getting criticized even after doing the penalty.
I didn't know, but you looked decent because of your hair.
- Yes, it stands out so much. - My hair made me look good?
- Exactly. - Yes, your hair matters a lot.
You look like a toad with your side hair down like that.
(You look like a toad with your side hair down like that.)
I didn't know about this before.
- Do I look fat? - A big toad?
- Hey, by the way... - I see. I didn't know.
- 2019 has dawned. - Okay.
- We're one year older than before. - Yes.
- Congratulations. - Okay.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
- He's the oldest? He's 54. - Yes.
- 54. - 54.
He kept dropping the number, 54, and now he's finally 54 years old.
- You've been on TV for so long. - My gosh.
He'll be 60 soon.
- Seok Jin is 54. - I'm serious.
And I turned 48 this year.
- 48. - 48.
- And Jong Kook is now... - 44.
- 44. - Double 4.
- We're 34. We're 34. - 44.
- We're 34. - 34.
- 34. - 34.
(The youngest members of the same age)
(Recipient of Top Excellence Award and toad with a failed makeover)
Actually, So Min and Se Chan...
- are 34 years old. - We're not that young.
- They'd be department chiefs. - Yes, that's right.
Chiefs... They are as old as chiefs.
- We are as old as chiefs. - You could be chiefs.
My goodness, you shouldn't be here talking to us.
- Seok Jin. - What?
You shouldn't be doing this in that pig outfit.
(Looking pitiful)
- Let go. Let go of me. - Right now...
- Yes, my friend is a director now. - Right now...
My friend is a director of a conglomerate.
When my friend got promoted to a director, I'm wearing these pigs.
I'm wearing this pig outfit when my friend became a director.
- My gosh. - He's cute.
My role model used to be...
- Gyeong Gyu who has a long career, - Exactly.
but now, you're my role model. It's you.
- Goodness. - You have such a long career.
Anyway, he's my role model. Seok Jin is my role model.
- To celebrate the New Year, 2019, - Let's go now.
to bring good luck, to bring money, and to bring happiness,
- he'll show us the Bring-it Dance. - Bring-it Dance?
Bring it. Move forward.
If you ask me, I'll bring it
(Watch his Bring-it Dance, and bring a lot of good fortune.)
I'll comply even in the Year of the Pig.
- Bring-it Dance. - Look at his shoes.
You're making me cry. I'm crying now.
- Your director-friend is watching. - Come on, fix up your outfit.
- Your director-friend is watching. - My role model.
My role model.
I can't do it anymore. It's embarrassing.
Today, to celebrate the New Year, 2019,
with the wish that you will level up in every aspect,
we have the New Year Project.
Running Man Playing Game, also known as, RPG.
We have prepared Until You Reach the Highest Level Race.
- Until the Highest Level? - The Highest Level?
- RPG is a game. - Okay.
Do we need to level up?
Running Man Playing Game will begin now.
(Running Man Playing Game will begin now.)
To play the RPG,
the players must find quests, scattered all over the site.
They can only acquire the items or level up...
when they complete their quests.
There are different ranks.
Just like games, there are different ranks.
Depending on the quests, players' level may go up or go down.
The moment a player reaches Level 10, the game is over.
The winning player will be given a great prize.
Whatever you imagine, it will be beyond your imagination.
- Really? - Is that so?
- We've prepared great prizes. - How good is it?
All right. It's RPG, the Highest Level Project.
Your first level-up mission is...
It's called Rice Cake Soup in the Sky.
- Rice Cake Soup in the Sky? - Rice Cake Soup in the Sky?
Everyone's current level is one.
You can level up if you can eat a bowl of rice cake soup.
That's simple.
- We need to eat rice cake soup? - That's easy.
Then we'll distribute the badges for Level One.
By the way, what if...
- Jong Kook gets the highest level? - Right, exactly.
That won't happen.
- That can't happen. - Right.
I'm sure it won't be that easy.
I'm sure this will be difficult.
(Everyone starts the race as Level 1.)
All right. Before we start the race,
everyone will ride the gondola lift one by one.
- One by one? - Yes.
Why? What is it? What could this be?
My gosh, there's something else.
(Why are we riding the lift all separately?)
All right. Should we get on it now?
- 54. 54. - 54. 54.
- Everyone will ride it separately. - 54-year-old.
Here I go.
Hello.
Happy New Year.
(Seok Jin has entered.)
Seok Jin, there's your own close-up!
(His own close-up, a splendid feat after 54 years)
54-year-old, okay!
There's your close-up. Come on!
Happy New Year!
He keeps on saying the same thing.
(Is it lagging as soon as he logged in?)
- He doesn't know if it will air. - "Happy New Year."
All right. Let's get going.
(What kind of a quest awaits at the canyon?)
Gosh, what's the mission today? I can't even guess.
My gosh.
Whatever they tell you, try to stay calm.
(People log in one by one.)
(All of 8 players are on the gondola lifts now.)
(They will head over to the Snow Canyon now.)
My gosh.
I haven't been to a ski resort for a while now. It's so nice.
This is great.
(The players have entered.)
Something must be up since everyone took the lift by themselves.
Before you begin the quest,
acquire the ingredients first.
(Before reaching the Snow Canyon, they can obtain the ingredients.)
"Acquire the ingredients for rice cake soup."
"To level up and make the soup, you need eight ingredients."
"Choose one ingredient you need and acquire the chosen ingredient."
"However, if other players choose the same ingredients,"
"they will not be available." My gosh, what will I do?
"They will not be available."
(Choose one ingredient and acquire the ingredient.)
(I knew it. They wouldn't just give us the rice cake soup.)
My gosh, I need all of them.
Seasoning, water,
eggs, and beef.
(Which one must I choose?)
(Seok Jin is choosing his ingredient.)
What do you think is the most important ingredient?
It's the rice cake.
I will...
(Player Seok Jin...)
I will choose the rice cake.
(Player Seok Jin has chosen the rice cake.)
Everyone has chosen their ingredients.
Please check the result.
Everyone.
You all choose an ingredient on your way up here, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
All right. Out of the ingredients you have chosen,
I will remove the ones that no one chose...
and the ingredients that overlapped amongst yourselves.
- It was really hard. - All right.
- Seok Jin, you'll go first. - Okay.
- Please reveal the chosen card. - Okay.
- Gosh, please. - Seok Jin will go first.
You all know what I chose, right?
- You know how I play, right? - Okay, okay. Go ahead.
- Rice cake! - It's rice cake as expected.
- See? - All right.
All right. So Min. It's your turn, So Min.
- I chose the pot. - Yes!
(Player So Min has chosen the pot.)
Okay.
(Since they chose different cards, they have the rice cake and pot.)
- Gosh, you are unbelievable. - Okay.
- Did you choose the pot? - He chose the pot.
Please, no.
- Why did you... - Jae Seok.
(Player Jae Seok has chosen the pot.)
(Both So Min and Jae Seok chose the pot.)
- What a great start. - Come on.
My gosh, I chose the pot.
Jae Seok and I click sometimes at the worst timing.
That was useless. Why...
- My gosh... - Didn't you choose beef?
There was an order we rode the lift.
I was the 3rd one to ride it. Because I was the 3rd one...
There were 8 players and 8 ingredients.
- Which one did you choose? - There are eight of us.
I chose it in order.
- I chose it according to the order. - You chose the rice cake?
- My gosh. - What is this?
- Seriously. - Come on.
- You can't blame this on me. - Fine.
(They have lost the rice cake among the 8 ingredients.)
- That's why I chose beef. - I didn't know at all.
- I also own a barbecue restaurant. - Exactly.
- Beef was the fourth one. - Good job. Well done.
- Great job. - My gosh, beef.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
Since I was the fifth one...
- I thought we'd go in order. - Exactly. My gosh.
- You were thoughtful. - I chose the water.
- Well done. - There you go.
(The ace player has chosen the water.)
- Kwang Soo. - You are indeed awesome.
(They have beef and water for now.)
(The portable burner, eggs, dried lavers, and seasoning remain.)
(If he had chosen 1 of them, they would have 3 ingredients.)
- I chose the rice cake. - That little...
(Giraffe-lover chose the rice cake.)
- You ought to think first. - Come on.
Mr. Pot.
(Look who's talking.)
You should have thought someone would choose the rice cake.
I thought that's why no one would pick this one.
I had no idea that you would choose the pot.
- Did you choose the pot too? - What did you choose?
- I got the pot too. - I thought you wouldn't.
- I got it too. - No.
I got the pot too.
- 3 rice cake and 3 pots. - What is this?
The players have acquired beef and water out of eight ingredients.
Among eight ingredients for the level-up mission,
the pot, portable burner, rice cake, eggs, dried laver,
- and seasoning have disappeared. - A lot of ingredients disappeared.
Find the ingredients that had disappeared.
Find the R spots on your own,
and when you carry out the quests at the spots,
- you can find the ingredients. - Okay.
(Find the R flags and complete the quests.)
How are we supposed to do this?
(The race has begun. Good luck.)
Would it be somewhere over here?
Wouldn't it be inside there?
Let's go check.
(They must find the quests to find the missing ingredients.)
I don't see anything here.
This place is huge. How can I find that?
There should be a better way to find the flags.
I really want to find it. I don't think it's here.
- I need to find the items... - Yes, we need to find them now.
We're supposed to find them as we walk around the whole day.
Is... Is that supposed to be fun then?
I don't know. I don't know that either.
I've never played such a game.
- My gosh, this is... - Let's go.
(As Jong Kook and Ji Hyo move...)
- Jong Kook. - Hey, Jong Kook is going somewhere.
Let's follow him.
Jong Kook is over there.
- Hey, why is this locked? - What's this?
- Here it is. - Look at this.
(He finds the envelope for the quest.)
- Look at this. It's locked. - What's this?
The door is locked, but I found this here.
(They have discovered the quest.)
"Decipher the Code"?
"For the passcode of the locked door,"
"decipher the code or find the code, buried somewhere..."
"in the snow field."
- Jae Seok, come here! - Hey, come here.
Jae Seok!
- We found it. - We found it.
- Look. There's a code. - Look at this.
All right. Look.
- We can either decipher the code... - Here it is.
or the code is hidden somewhere in the snow field.
Where? What did you say?
- In the snow field? - We must crack the code.
- The passcode... - We must get the passcode.
Here's an important part. These are all numbers,
- but it's alphabet here. - These are letters.
(The hint is in numbers, but the code is in letters.)
(How can we connect the numbers with the alphabet?)
- Hey, I got it! - This is...
- A, B, C, D... - Exactly.
- Hold on. - This one corresponds to G.
- All right. G. - G.
(Then the 8th letter is H.)
My gosh, how will we find the code like that?
- What about overlapping letters? - Must we write all of them?
"Find the code, buried somewhere in the snow field."
(Find the code, buried somewhere in the snow field.)
- We should just look for it. - Hey.
- When will we solve the puzzle? - Hey, the puzzle is faster.
- This one is faster. - I'll stick with this one.
- I give up. Okay. - Hey, this is much faster.
- Try to use your brain. - This is way faster.
- I mean... - I know that this isn't easy.
Hey.
(Deciphering the code versus searching for the code)
Don't we need to go down to reach the snow field?
(Which group will be able to open up the door first?)
Should we go down here?
My gosh, how will we find it here?
- Can you see anything, Kwang Soo? - I don't see anything here.
How will we find it here?
The snow field?
(It's equivalent to looking for a needle in a haystack.)
Is it better to decipher the code?
- Seok Jin. - By the way...
(By the way...)
Our group...
We're the dumb ones.
- We're not dumb. - We're the dumb ones.
- 3 rice cakes, and 1 pot. - No.
The people...
who didn't solve the puzzle and came down here from there...
are a bit...
- dense including myself. - No way.
We're just active.
- Let's say that we're active. - I came down right away.
I'm sure there are patterns.
- Patterns? - There has to be a pattern there.
- My gosh, this is... - Hey, take a look at this.
How many letters are there?
- 1, 2, 3, 4, - 1, 2...
- 5. - There are 5 here.
How many are there?
There are eight.
Let's get rid of numbers that overlap.
(The overlapping numbers must be somehow relevant.)
Goodness, this...
My gosh, this is hard.
1, 2, 3, 4...
I don't think that's relevant.
7, 8. These numbers are all the same, aren't they?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. Never mind.
- There are only six. - Right.
(Even the first quest is difficult.)
Goodness, this...
Wait, hold on. Isn't this shape of an E?
- Isn't this shape of an E? - That's an E. E.
- That's E. - This one is L.
(The number, 1, make up the letter, L.)
- 5... - Where's 3?
This is for number five.
- L. - L.
- Number five makes L too. - It's L.
- E-L-E? - L-E-L-E-L-E.
- Should we try it? - Isn't that L-I-E?
- E-L-E-L-E. - Let's try this in order.
I.
In order? But I'm not sure where I should start first.
Let's give it a try first.
- 2, 2, 3. - But there are numbers.
- Number ones make up L. - Yes, it's L.
- Number twos make up E. - You're right!
- Number threes make up V. - It's V. V.
- Hey, hold on. - Number four.
- Number fours make up E. E again. - My gosh.
- Okay, Seok Jin. - You should've been a detective.
- Number fives make up L. - It's L.
- Le... - L.
- Level. - Level.
- "Level" is the code. - Gosh, Jong Kook.
(Will "level" be the right code?)
- It worked. - Did it work?
- Okay. - Amazing.
(No way! It's unlocked!)
- Wait. - We were just...
- Level! - Shouldn't we tell others?
Let them exercise on the field.
(They enter into the Quest Castle with their sharp intellect.)
- Let's go. - This is nice. It's nice.
Let's close the door.
- We can't close the door. - The others have to come in too.
Let's try the next one by ourselves.
(You have completed the quest. Find the next quest.)
There it is.
(He finds something.)
Wait. What's this?
(Haha finds an R flag and tubes.)
Quest.
I found it.
(A quest has been found.)
"Shoot the Tubes".
"Stick your bottom in a tube and shoot it."
"If the eight members' tubes fly more than 10m in total,"
"the location of one ingredient will be revealed."
"If you fail,"
"one member has to go down a level to get another chance."
- Let's start from So Min. - So Min.
Okay.
Me? Okay.
Come here.
Okay.
Kwang Soo, help with the tubes.
- Active ones! - This is... Yes?
So Min.
(She falls from the beginning.)
- Hold on. - What's wrong?
So Min.
So Min, hold me.
Stand behind the line.
So Min.
Bend your body even lower.
(Wobbly)
(She falls again.)
- There you go. - Even lower.
- This looks good. - That's enough.
- You're ready. - You can start.
It's going to shoot...
It's going to shoot so far.
- Watch out. It might hit you. - Come here.
The rest of you, step back.
So Min.
1, 2, 3. Start!
Start! 1, 2, 3.
(She thrusts her bottom out...)
(and falls.)
(Let me lie down for a moment.)
- Hey. - What was that?
- Hey! - So Min!
You shouldn't lie down. Shoot it.
- So Min. - Let me try again.
- You can't. - 22cm.
20cm.
- It was funny at least. - It was funny at least.
Jae Seok, show us.
- Should I? - Yes, please.
- Back in the day... - You're the master.
I was good at it back in the kungkungta days.
That's right.
(I used to shoot some tubes.)
(His bottom-thrusting started already then.)
(He was praised by Kang Ho Dong as the tube ace.)
Push the tube down.
- Push it down. - All the way.
(The tube has to be pushed down all the way.)
- All the way. - Like this?
- Good. - It's all the way down now.
Show us.
- 2, 3. - 2, 3.
(His butt that's been asleep for a long time...)
(finally awakens.)
(So Min, watch me. This is how you shoot a tube.)
Hey.
The tube was too far down.
- What did you do? - It was too far down.
Why...
It was too far down.
- It's hard. - Hold on.
- What did you do? - What's with you?
It was too far down.
- How far down did you mean? - You said all the way down.
- It was too far down. - You said all the way down.
I've never tried this before.
(Jae Seok, are you watching?)
- 54! - 54!
(Here comes the 54-year-old.)
(Let me show you the power of a middle-aged man.)
Bend down even lower.
Even lower.
(Let me show you the power of a middle-aged man.)
- Hold him. - Okay.
- Bend down. - There you go.
(Kwang Soo is almost choking Seok Jin.)
- It's going down. - There you go.
There you go.
Bend your knees.
- Okay. - Good.
- Ready. - Okay.
(Here we go.)
- Ready. - 1, 2, 3.
(With everyone's help, Seok Jin is ready to shoot the tube.)
1, 2, 3.
(How far will it go?)
Gosh.
(It lands right in front of Seok Jin.)
Three.
What is this? It didn't go far.
It's exactly what I expected of him.
(The 3 members managed to shoot only 90cm in total.)
You should bend down low.
(Let me raise the record.)
It was okay.
You have to bend down like this.
That was close.
- Se Chan. - Try it.
- Good. - There you go.
It looks perfect.
How does it feel?
It feels good.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- Okay. - It looks so stable.
1, 2, 3.
- Look at that. - Oh, my.
(Flying)
It went back.
(It flew quite far,)
(but it went back.)
(Se Chan shoots 1m 20cm.)
It went back.
- It's over 2m now? - You did well.
Do your best.
Let's keep going like this.
- Let's do it. - Good.
Done.
He's ready.
Your upper body...
Yes!
Good!
(But)
(It lands at 1m 60cm.)
Why couldn't you do better?
What is this?
Let me try.
(Jong Kook steps up.)
It'd be great if someone can shoot 3m.
Like this?
If it goes too deep, it won't shoot.
Can it go down even further?
There you go.
Let me try.
The angle is important.
Good.
(The tube flies much longer this time.)
- Good! - How far did it go?
(It lands a lot farther away from the line.)
(It lands at 2m 20cm.)
Okay. Is it done?
- 2m 20cm. - Okay.
- 2m 20cm. - Good.
- It wasn't bad. - Haha, please do well.
Haha is good at it.
You have to make it nice and tight.
Are you the last player?
What's the number now?
(Haha and Ji Hyo have to shoot more than 3m 50cm.)
(Do like I did, Haha.)
Haha's legs have become strong.
(He thrusts his bottom.)
Please take us to 5m.
(Haha should take them near 10m.)
It's almost there.
(Flying)
- Good! - Yes!
(Haha shoots 2m 30cm.)
(He is the unexpected master.)
Good!
(Now there is only 1.2m to go.)
Okay. It's Ji Hyo's turn.
- Ji Hyo. - We're almost there.
Let's continue this way.
The tube is all the way down.
Is she the last player?
- Stand up quickly. - Straighten your body.
- Your hands... - Raise your upper body.
- We can do this. - Okay.
Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, let's do it.
1, 2, 3.
Good!
(Powerful)
No!
(The tube is bouncing near 2m.)
(They only have 1m 20cm to go, and the tube is bouncing.)
(This will determine if they will get another ingredient.)
(It lands far back.)
We have to try again.
(It reaches beyond 2m,)
(but it ended up near 1m.)
- We failed? - We didn't make it?
By how much?
It's 9.8m.
(The result is 9m 80cm.)
Jae Seok!
If only So Min and Jae Seok hadn't failed...
Gosh.
Jae Seok shot only 10cm.
To win another chance,
one of you has to go down a level.
(One of them has to go down a level.)
(Everyone is at Level 1 right now.)
Those who shot less than 1m.
(They compete to determine who should go down a level.)
By the way,
why is it the three of us again?
- Wait. - Gosh.
We even went to Hong Kong together.
That's right.
- We failed our mission. - We failed.
(They get back together after 2 weeks.)
I'm on a different level from them.
- I shot 60cm. - I'm the best among us.
- You shot only 10cm, right? - Yes.
- Gosh. - By the way,
he really looks old.
- His pants make him look old. - They do.
Okay.
(Seok Jin is wearing an old man's pants.)
Hold on. Let me...
(They make sure Seok Jin doesn't cheat.)
Let me fix this.
(Let go of me.)
(What?)
(Where is the tube?)
(It lands at 10cm.)
Why were you holding me?
You were moving your arms.
You shouldn't use your arms.
I wasn't going to use them.
Your arms...
So Min. You should...
- So Min is good. - She's good.
Like this.
(She looks more determined this time.)
(The three of them do their best to avoid the penalty.)
Three.
(Will she manage to avoid going down a level?)
Look at that.
What's happening?
(Worried)
(Bouncing)
(It falls right away.)
(Minus 30cm)
No!
This doesn't count!
- Okay. Minus. - This is...
- What is this? - Minus.
So Min is so unlucky.
- Why... - It's So Min.
- You're at level zero. - So Min.
What is this?
Sorry.
(So Min goes down to Level 0.)
In the beginning...
The first five people should finish it.
2m by 5 people.
I don't want to go last.
So Min, that's better.
- Let's go. - Look at the ceiling.
- Look at the ceiling. - Look at the ceiling.
Look at the ceiling.
- 1, 2, 3. - Let's go!
Yes!
(The power of demotion)
See?
- See? - You did it.
- So Min. - She did it.
So Min. See?
- 1m 60cm. - So Min.
- You have to look at the ceiling. - Good job.
- Look up. - Let me go first.
Five people should finish it.
Haha.
(Haha holds the highest record of 2m 30cm.)
- You can do this! - You can do this!
All right.
Start!
(Will he do well this time too?)
(Shooting)
(It flies high.)
- 2m. - Good.
- Nice. - 2m.
It's not bad.
If we fail again, another person has to go down a level.
Focus.
(Let's maintain our levels and eat rice cake soup.)
It's all right.
(Se Chan 2m, Ji Hyo 1m 10cm)
- Nice. - Good.
Good!
- It went quite far. - That was close.
I think we'll succeed.
But...
(Kwang Soo was so confident.)
Seriously.
(He records 0cm.)
- You tried to be funny. - No.
It was real.
(Seok Jin laughed at Kwang Soo.)
- This is strange. - No.
This is strange.
(Embarrassed)
- Who should go down... - What should we do?
It's minus.
Okay. Look at the ceiling.
- He can finish it. - Look at the ceiling.
How much is left?
1.6m.
- It's not much. - We have 1.6m to go.
- Perfect. - Okay.
- Let's go! - It looks perfect.
- Here we go. - It looks perfect.
- Good. - 1, 2, 3.
(He shoots the tube, hoping this will be the last try.)
(In his first try, he shot 2m 20cm.)
(1m 60cm should be no problem for him.)
What's with him?
(What?)
- My goodness. - He's a spy.
(He shoots only 80cm this time.)
- He's a spy. - No.
- He's a spy. - Jong Kook.
- What? - 90cm?
- What did you do? - What's wrong?
- 90cm? - It's not bad.
Are you a spy?
No. There is no spy today.
Just step forward.
- Step forward. - Seriously.
We have no choice.
It has to be you.
Jong Kook and you...
Kwang Soo too.
- The three of them... - No.
- Not me. - You too.
- Seok Jin has to be in too. - It's the three of us.
One of us three will be holding the badge.
Each of you choose one of us.
The one who chooses the person holding the badge will take it.
- Are you okay with that? - Yes.
All right.
(Whispering)
- Turn around. - Turn around.
(One of them is holding the badge.)
Unlucky ones, do you want to choose first?
I want to go later.
I want to go later too.
You go first.
(Jong Kook is going to choose one first.)
(One of them is holding the Level 0 badge.)
Gosh.
(The other two's hands are empty.)
I don't think Haha is holding anything.
(If he chooses the person holding the badge, he will go down a level.)
(Jong Kook approaches Haha.)
- His hands... - It shows.
Two of them have nothing, right?
- That's right. - I think it's Se Chan.
(Whose hands are empty?)
- Two of them have nothing? - Nothing.
(Thinking)
I choose Haha.
(Jong Kook chooses Haha.)
- Haha. - My business partner.
We can relax. I think it's Haha.
- I think so too. - Should he open his hand?
Please open your hand.
I'll open it.
Start.
(Empty)
- Yes! - Yes!
What a relief.
(Jong Kook maintains his level.)
Okay.
(So it's one of us?)
My goodness.
- Look at Se Chan's poker face. - I knew it.
(They have their poker face on.)
- He wanted to go last. - That's right.
- He said that. - Yes.
I choose Jae Seok.
- I'm done. - Okay.
I was chosen by Seok Jin.
Yes.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(We don't care about the tubes anymore. This is our real quest.)
(Who is holding the badge, Jae Seok or Se Chan?)
Congratulations.
(Congratulations, Seok Jin.)
Why...
(Seok Jin is going down a level.)
- He is my role model. - Why...
- Why... - Did you see that?
All the unlucky ones come to me.
Seok Jin and I are to compete.
(Seok Jin goes down to Level 0.)
We have to shoot the tubes again, right?
Let's start from the good ones.
Let's do that.
It's deflated.
(Okay. Let me start.)
Kwang Soo, step aside. Let's start from Jong Kook.
(Let's start from Jong Kook.)
Step aside.
- I'll do better this time. - Okay.
I'll do better.
- I'll do better. - There you go.
- I'll show you. - Okay.
I'm ready.
- Should I go? - Yes.
(In the last round, he was suspected to be a spy.)
(He wants to make up for it.)
1, 2...
(Determined)
(Rolling)
- Oh, my. - It's over.
(The tube rolls...)
(and lands at 2m 90cm.)
That's more like Jong Kook.
Okay. It's over.
- It's over. - It's over.
Why did you do that last time?
The tube didn't sit right last time.
It was okay this time.
(Se Chan shoots 2m.)
- Good! - Yes!
(Jae Seok manages to shoot 1.6m too.)
Not bad.
Fall over.
- Yes! - That's a relief.
(The tube master steps up.)
It's over.
(By Haha shooting 2.7m,)
(they break the 10m barrier.)
- It's over. - Haha.
He's my brother.
(They finally complete the tube quest.)
Unbelievable.
- We should have done this earlier. - Haha is amazing.
We should have done this earlier.
I'm so proud of myself right now.
There.
"Choose 2 people to get the ingredient."
"The ingredient is in sight."
"It is at the end of a cold, difficult road."
(The ingredient is at the end of a cold, difficult road?)
"Choose 2 people to get the ingredient."
(Choose 2 people.)
It's probably going to be hard.
It's at the end of a cold, difficult road.
This...
(2 people have to go on a cold, difficult road.)
- Race of Wits. - Sure.
(In a situation like this, Race of Wits is the best.)
- Race of Wits? - We'll play only one round.
- The last two people lose. - Okay.
- This is the only round. - Okay.
- Do you understand? - Gosh.
- Okay. - I'll say, "two".
- I'm "1". - I'm "1".
- I'm serious. - I'm "2".
- I'll say, "1". - I'm "1".
I'm always "one".
- I'm telling you. - I'm "one".
- Start. - One.
Those two...
(Kwang Soo and So Min lose.)
They are too much of a risk.
I can't trust them.
This will be risky.
- I don't like it. - Just go.
Go now.
I'm worried.
These two can't be trusted.
(Kwang Soo and So Min are getting the ingredient.)
Let's go get the ingredient.
Where is it?
- We're supposed to bring it here? - It's at the end of a cold road.
Cold and difficult.
That sounds suspicious.
(I see something over there.)
Can we ride it?
(A quest flag has been discovered.)
(Go to the end of the cold and difficult road on the sled.)
(So Min gets in.)
Let's go.
- I see it. - Where?
Over there.
- I see ingredients on the table. - Really?
- Let's go. - Is it fast?
No.
It's not too fast. No.
- It's okay. - Here we go.
(Let's go!)
It's fun!
Here we go.
- It's fun. It's so refreshing. - It is.
(Were you scared of the cold, difficult road?)
(It's actually pretty refreshing and exciting.)
- It's fun. - It's so refreshing.
It's so fun.
(They're already at the end of the road.)
It's so fast.
(Are we here?)
(They instinctively start racing.)
(They always compete for no reason.)
Wait for me.
- Can we eat this? - Hold on.
(Stop!)
- You can't eat it. - No?
You can't eat it. Stop.
Isn't it a mission?
- Please read it out loud. - It's a mission.
(A quest has been obtained.)
Make a decision.
You can either bring the ingredients to your team...
or eat the soup in front of you and go up a level by yourself.
"In front of you..."
(Of course, we'll eat the soup.)
(Let us go up a level.)
(Rice cake soup has never tasted this good.)
I have no choice. I'm at level zero.
I have no choice either. I was born this way.
(Self-justification)
(It sounds convincing because it's Kwang Soo.)
How are we going to keep this a secret?
Let's not tell them we had a choice.
(He wants to pretend they had no choice.)
Let's tell them it just happened.
I'm starting to regret my decision.
Why?
I feel bad.
As if.
(I know you too well.)
(Just eat.)
I'm finally back to Level One.
- I'm starting over. I'm happy. - We had no choice.
Anyone would have made the same decision.
Of course.
(They go back to the team.)
"We had to complete a mission."
I feel ashamed of myself.
I can't go back.
How do you deal with all the guilt?
How do you deal with it?
To be honest, I don't feel so much guilt.
Seriously. I don't.
- They're going to question us. - Should we...
(Rubbing)
No.
(So Min catches on.)
What should we tell them? That we fell?
Let's say they threw snow at us.
Make them think it was hard.
- And cold. - Yes.
(The betrayer duo)
(They sprinkle snow on each other.)
Let's go. This should do. It's cold.
Do I look innocent?
Do I look frustrated?
I can't stop smiling.
Smile, and it's over.
- Here they come. - Here they come.
- They're plotting something. - They're whispering.
They're on to something.
They'll say they couldn't find it.
- Welcome back. - Did you find it?
(Did you find the ingredient?)
It was like a penalty.
You two were smiling so big.
We had to complete a mission...
But you won something, right?
(Examining)
- We had to... - Why are you Level Two?
(Why are you Level 2?)
- Really? - Really?
- The thing is... - You ate the rice cake soup?
No.
(You ate the rice cake soup?)
- No. - You did.
- So Min started eating first. - Don't lie.
(So Min started eating first.)
- Seriously. - Why did you...
dirty your hair on purpose?
- Where did you eat the soup? - I didn't eat any.
Then how did your level go up?
I didn't eat it.
You have eggs stuck in your teeth.
(Stop lying.)
I can see the egg yolk.
Isn't it over once you eat rice cake soup?
What's wrong with the two of you?
- What do we do with them? - It's this year's first episode.
That's not it.
It's a war now.
We're going to team up.
Remember that.
Let's block him only.
We understand.
We'll have our eye on you and So Min.
- Stop it. - How could they?
This is wrong.
What's next?
(Peeking)
(Jae Seok finds something.)
(Surprised)
- Is there something more? - Here it is.
What is it?
(He finds a quest.)
"We prepared warm snacks for you."
"Enjoy eight dumplings after determining the order of eating."
(There's a total of 8 dumplings, 1 for each member.)
(Eat them based on the determined order.)
They're dumplings.
They're steaming.
Exclude these two...
and play Race of Wits.
- Let's determine the order. - Okay.
Are you excluding the two of us?
Why?
- We don't have enough. - You stay out.
- Go away. - You two play separately.
- You two play separately. - Go away.
Are you telling us to stay out of the game?
- Go away. - Why?
Two of you play rock-paper-scissors.
- That works. - You'll be 7th and 8th.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors.)
(Kwang Soo loses.)
Yes.
- I'm seventh in place. - Don't lean forward.
Don't lean forward. Stand up straight.
(They play Race of Wits to determine the order.)
- Start. - One.
Two.
- 3. - 4.
- I said four. - How could you?
- 4. - 5.
(Haha says five.)
(Se Chan, Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Jong Kook, and Haha)
No way.
- This is Race of Wits. - No way.
- We got it. - 3 and 4.
- All right. - Go ahead.
I bet it's delicious.
It's over once you put down the chopsticks.
- Okay. - When you put them down.
(He tries the first dumpling.)
Taste it first.
Do you eat it regardless of your level?
(Impressed)
They look delicious.
Steam is rising.
Se Chan is enjoying it so much.
He eats it in a cute way.
- Put them down. - That's enough.
Come on.
- Put them down. - Okay, good job.
- Put them down. - This is wrong, Se Chan.
- Hey, hey. - Can't I eat...
- You know what? - three?
- This can happen as you eat. - Stop it.
- Put them down. - That's enough.
- You can't do this. - Se Chan.
- Okay. - Good job.
- It was the best. - He ate three.
Don't go overboard, Se Chan.
- It's my turn soon. - It's not you.
You aren't third.
You should be conscientious.
Let's see what he does as an MC representative of Korea.
Is it delicious?
It's steamed well.
(He eats the fourth dumpling.)
- They cook well. - All I need is one dumpling.
Jae Seok.
Two?
I know how it tastes.
Goodness.
He eats with gusto.
- Will Haha get to eat any? - Goodness.
It's really delicious.
Once you eat one, you want more.
It's appetizing.
Will Haha get to eat any?
Jong Kook is thinking.
He's like family to me.
Haha's role model is Seok Jin, so just finish them.
Right, he did say that.
Haha kept saying that Seok Jin is his role model.
- Do you want some? - Yes.
Why?
Jong Kook, I really want to eat it.
- Jong Kook. - It's really delicious.
- One won't be enough. - Of course.
- Give it to me. - It isn't enough.
It's so tasty.
I've been good to you for 17 years.
(I've been good to you for 17 years.)
He's making us emotional.
(Do you remember, Jong Kook?)
(For the last 17 years,)
(I have always been your fan, Jong Kook.)
(I'm Haha, your black cat for eternity.)
- He's been his butler. - He has for a long time.
- His butler for 17 years. - This isn't easy.
There's "12 Years A Slave".
- Being his butler for 17 years. - 17 years?
Being his butler for 17 years isn't easy.
- Okay. - Okay.
(The 17 years of trust earned Haha a dumpling.)
He's been a slave for 17 years.
The last comment, "Butler for 17 years" was good.
Leave me half of it, Haha.
How can I leave half?
Remember us in Mapo-gu?
(Remember our time in Mapo-gu.)
- Haha. - Ji Hyo.
Think hard.
(Ji Hyo)
I'm moving.
(There's no more Mapo-gu.)
(Haha finishes the last dumpling.)
He's moving.
He finished the last one.
That was clean.
Isn't it delicious?
These dumplings are excellent.
They're really good.
We finished everything.
(Rice cake soup siblings are hungry.)
- These dumplings are excellent. - There's galbi inside.
- They're so good. - Where are they from?
(Sniffing)
- Look at her. - I'm smelling them.
(I want to smell them at least.)
(Do you want to smell them too?)
- They must be galbi dumplings. - These are good dumplings.
(Are we only eating dumplings?)
Is there something more?
(There must be something now that the quest is over.)
Is there something underneath? Open this up.
- There's nothing. - There's nothing.
(Is there something?)
What is it?
Here it is again.
- What is it? - Really?
"Two people to find rice cake soup ingredients".
[VIU Ver] SBS E433 Running Man
"Running Man Playing Game (RPG)"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Pick two members to find rice cake soup ingredients.)
(The one who had the most dumplings and a member of his choice)
"The one who had the most dumplings"...
"and a member of his choice"?
It's Se Chan.
(Let's go, Se Chan.)
- Se Chan. - Wait.
- Haha is so sly. - Se Chan.
I should have eaten more.
I should have finished all four.
I didn't get to eat rice cake soup or dumplings.
- Look at me. - This is impossible.
There's no way to go.
The one who talked badly about my hair...
during the opening segment can go to the back of the line.
Se Chan, it wasn't me.
Jae Seok started it.
Jong Kook started it first.
Keep down my hair with a few grains of rice?
It was definitely Jae Seok.
Jae Seok said it.
(Goodness)
- I said you looked cute. - I said it looks good on you.
- I said that you looked cute. - I know how to get there.
- You and I are butlers. - Se Chan.
- Let's work together. - Butlers should stick together.
- Look carefully. - Number one.
Why aren't you doing anything?
- Jong Kook. - Aren't you going?
I teased him a lot about his hair during the opening.
Why did you?
Okay, I made my decision.
- Let's go, Se Chan. - I'm going to lose my mind.
- Haha. - That's right.
(He picks Haha.)
- Haha. Ji Hyo, I had no choice. - Let's go.
- Let's go together. - Gosh, Se Chan.
- Haha is a wrong choice. - It's Haha.
- Se Chan. - We can win.
I hope you choose wisely.
We need to find everything before going back home.
- You can't sacrifice the group. - Right.
- Okay. - We have to collect ingredients.
- Let's go. - Se Chan.
You must look far to become a bird.
Don't lose sight of the forest for the trees.
(The butler brothers go find rice cake soup ingredients.)
Where shall we go?
- Thank you, Se Chan. - You're welcome.
Teamwork is important.
You know what to do, right?
- Let's go level up. - We just go level up.
(Forget about finding ingredients.)
- Let's have some rice cake soup. - If I could,
I'd give you my level.
We should advance together.
What's the point of doing it alone?
- Are we searching again? - Goodness.
Let us eat some rice cake soup too.
(They need to find the ingredients in order to level up.)
Hey, there's something.
- What is it? - There's an R flag.
Is it here already?
(Follow the R mark.)
- I think we have to go upstairs. - Is it here?
Go upstairs?
I think we go upstairs.
- Look, there's another R. - Go upstairs.
You're right.
(The members follow the R and go to the second floor.)
- What? - What's going on?
(Jae Seok is startled by something.)
Who is it?
(What is waiting for them?)
(Who are the mysterious women with their backs turned?)
(Quest fairies have been discovered.)
(It's Apink.)
(Quest fairies of charisma return to Running Man.)
What brings them here?
(They attract the crowd with their new song "Percent".)
(They will help the members for their quests.)
Say hello.
What's going on?
Hello, Bo Mi.
What brings you here?
- Hello. - What brings you here?
- Hello. - What brings them here?
I thought there were name tags.
Congratulations.
Your level went up.
(Congratulations, your level went up.)
(Their level went up?)
As you found us,
your level went up.
We leveled up?
- Really? - Is it true?
- Did our level go up? - How?
- Okay. - Congratulations.
I'm Level Three.
I'm Level Two.
(The six members level up.)
Why did we level up?
What about...
- Haha and Se Chan? What about them? - Will they miss it?
(What about Haha and Se Chan?)
(They're excited.)
Level up.
- You two. - Yes?
Among the ingredients, you gained a pot.
Take the pot and return to the restaurant.
Why?
What about the level-up?
Your level...
will not go up.
(Your level will not go up.)
I came here for the level-up.
Those who left were greedy.
So the rest of you will level up.
(The butler brothers fail to raise their level.)
Is that why our level went up?
"Couple up with the quest fairies."
"Only couples may participate in the next quest."
"When couples are determined,"
"you're given a chance to earn ingredients and raise your level."
"Those who left to get ingredients are a couple automatically."
The two of them are a couple.
We choose couples among us.
(The members couple up with the quest fairies.)
- Do we take it? - Yes.
- Go back to the restaurant. - Wait.
(They earn a pot among 8 ingredients.)
This is unfair.
You should have told us.
(The butler brothers earn a pot.)
It's our first time having the entire group...
- of Apink. - It's the first time.
- Right. - We invited members separately.
- We never had the entire group. - Really?
Here's what's more surprising.
I haven't seen Bo Mi sing in a long time.
(Bo Mi sings.)
Every time she came, she gave us low kicks.
(Bo Mi usually gave low kicks.)
(She kicks every time she comes.)
(When Bo Mi kicks, the knees get bent.)
(She's the queen of low kicks.)
Bo Mi, you got leaner.
You surprised me, Bo Mi.
- Is it because she lost weight? - Don't I look weak?
You look out of it.
You should sit, Bo Mi.
- Are you okay? - Sit down for a while.
She looks so weak.
I don't think her low kicks will hurt anymore.
(He provokes her all of a sudden.)
- Is that a challenge? - I bet they won't hurt.
Take a challenge.
- I can handle her low kicks. - I don't think they'll hurt.
Her legs are so thin now.
I'm still strong.
Give it a try, Seok Jin.
I got kicked many times.
(Flinching)
You got kicked before, so you can compare them.
You will know the difference.
I'm sorry, but the top of your foot may hurt.
I got stronger.
(He gets pretentious.)
- Don't strain yourself, Bo Mi. - Shall I kick?
(I'm ready.)
(He's no longer scared of Bo Mi's low kicks.)
(Thud)
(Startled)
That must've hurt a lot.
(The sound is very clear.)
(Groaning in pain)
(He slaps the floor three times.)
Poor Seok Jin.
My gosh, I'm always kicking you.
- Goodness. - How is it?
Has her kick changed?
(Not one bit.)
- Is it the same? - I said I didn't want to.
It hurts more.
Bo Mi's still got it.
(Everyone celebrates.)
We should congratulate her.
(The queen of low kicks is eternal.)
(It's okay.)
I'm okay.
This is great.
- This is great. - It's fun.
(Couples)
(Jae Seok and Cho Rong, Seok Jin and Nam Joo,)
(Jong Kook and Na Eun, Haha and Se Chan)
What's this?
(A quest has been discovered.)
(It's a quest for couples.)
- What is it? - "Feed with the Wind".
"Feed with the Wind".
Seven couples work together on a quest.
When successful, you earn an ingredient.
Couples play in a relay.
One person eats food that swings from the opposite end.
All couples must eat everything in 100 seconds to succeed.
(A quest is successful when they eat all in 100 seconds.)
The one with a hole isn't easy to eat.
It's possible to do it.
- Nam Joo. - Yes?
Don't disappoint me.
(Laughing)
- Haha, we're first. - We'll finish fast.
You must finish under 100 seconds.
We will only take three seconds.
Get ready.
Get ready, set.
(The game starts.)
(Haha fetches the fruit as soon as the game starts.)
(Will they succeed as soon as they get started?)
(What will be the result?)
Set.
(The game starts.)
(Will they succeed
as soon as they get started?)
(Unfortunately they fail.)
It isn't done yet.
No.
(They could have succeeded
in one go.)
- No.
- Haha.
(Catch, Haha.)
(He's so close.)
Come on.
- He got it. - Okay.
(They finally succeed.)
(They succeed in 15 seconds.)
- He got it. - Okay.
That was great.
(Next are Ji Hyo and Ha Young.)
- Send it far. - Move the chairs.
- Send it far. - Far?
(She blows it far.)
- 100 seconds. - Move the chairs.
(It's close to her mouth.)
100 seconds.
Just a little bit more.
- 100 seconds. - Blow.
One more time. Blow.
(She blows lightly.)
(She got it in her mouth.)
(It comes back out.)
100 seconds. That's right.
(Ji Hyo and Ha Young succeed easily.)
- Okay. - They got it.
- Let's go. - Go.
That was great.
Blow it far.
- Make it far. - Blow.
- It's moving. - Hey, hey.
You have to blow it, Kwang Soo.
Blow it.
- You have to blow it. - Kwang Soo.
(Why can't you grab it when you have a big mouth?)
This is a problem.
(His mouth is big.)
(However, the snack is also huge.)
- It's a problem. - Kwang Soo.
(The snack hits his front tooth.)
(We can hear the sound of friction.)
(Poor Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo's tooth got hit.)
He got hit in his tooth.
- Gosh. - Kwang Soo.
- You have to bite, Kwang Soo. - You can do it.
- You can do it. - Blow it.
Eun Ji, blow it for him.
- Blow it hard one more time. - Kwang Soo.
You have to bite, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
(It's about to go in.)
(He barely succeeds by biting with his front teeth.)
(Kwang Soo and Eun Ji succeed.)
- Great. - Okay.
- Go. - Who's next?
- Move. - Who's next?
We got it.
We have 100 seconds.
We got it. This one is difficult.
- No. - Bo Mi.
- She can't even reach it. - Bo Mi.
(She can't reach it.)
Change the position.
- That won't work. - Bo Mi can't do it.
(She can't even get close.)
- Bo Mi. - She can't reach it.
Why are you twisting your back? Straighten your back.
Straighten your back.
- Straighten your back. - Straighten up.
- Bo Mi. - Come on.
Bo Mi.
Straighten your back.
- Sit up. - Straighten your back.
Bo Mi.
So Min, eat it for her.
- Change seats. - Bo Mi.
Change seats, and blow it, Bo Mi.
- Go. - That's better.
She can reach it.
So Min's sitting height is tall.
(Jong Kook is relieved.)
(Her sitting height is as tall as Han Gi Beom's.)
(She's working hard with her tall sitting height.)
Eat it now.
Come on.
- She almost got it. - Come on.
So Min.
(Bo Mi blows it, and So Min opens her mouth.)
Gosh, Bo Mi.
- So Min. - Lower yourself.
You can do it.
It's frustrating to watch.
It's frustrating.
Lower yourself.
So Min.
(It's so frustrating to watch.)
It's frustrating.
You won't make it.
- Move. - Blow it.
So Min.
Blow harder, Bo Mi.
It's over with this couple.
So Min.
- Goodness. - Just give up.
(Time is up.)
What happened?
Why can't you do it?
- My neck hurts. - You couldn't reach it, right?
- No. - You should try with the long one.
The two of them took a difficult one.
Do you want to switch? This one is easier.
So Min and Bo Mi should take the long one.
Who wants to take this one?
- Anything is fine. - Who wants this?
Inevitably, one of us has to level down.
Including Apink members...
Stop it.
(Let's play with Apink members.)
(Stop it.)
That's enough.
He loves wits too much.
Let's play Race of Wits.
- Start. - One.
- 2. - 2.
(Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and So Min)
Please come out.
- 1. - 2.
- 3. - 3.
Let's play again.
Please.
Please let me win once.
I'm almost there.
- Start. - One.
(It's the last round.)
- 2. - 2.
Jae Seok.
Gosh, you have no wits.
- You play rock-paper-scissors. - Right.
- Let's play 1 round. - 1 round.
Get ready.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(The loser in this round gets his level lowered.)
(Will it be Kwang Soo who's currently in the lead?)
(Will Jae Seok be the last with Seok Jin?)
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Gosh, Jae Seok always loses.
(Jae Seok's level is lowered.)
I know.
Your level goes down.
Kwang Soo.
- He's at Level 3. - You're Level 1.
You're the last.
You're the last of the last.
(Jae Seok's level is lowered from 2 to 1.)
Countdown for 100 seconds starts.
Get ready.
Set.
(Will they succeed this time?)
(Their second attempt starts.)
Blow it smoothly.
- You need to hurry. - So Min is good at catching.
We're almost there.
- Hey, suck it in. - Goodness.
This shouldn't take so long.
(They're very slow.)
(Please, So Min.)
(Will they succeed this time?)
So Min, that's it.
(She finally ate it.)
- Okay. - Next couple should sit.
Go.
Suck it like a vacuum.
Eat it in one go.
Grab it first with the lips.
- Use the lips. - Eat it in one go.
(Jong Kook nags and Ha Young blows it.)
(She catches it.)
Okay, that was good.
- Let's go. - Come on, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo's team succeeds immediately.)
(He takes it as Eun Ji blows on it.)
(He ate it right away.)
That was good.
(The fourth one is the most difficult.)
Suck it in.
Haha.
(Flapping)
You must do it quickly.
- Hey. - Grab it first with the lips.
Grab with the lips.
(The snack moves too quickly.)
Goodness.
(Please let me eat it.)
Push it.
(Se Chan does it right away.)
(If you tell me to push it,)
(I'll push it.)
Okay, we got it.
(He takes the problematic snack...)
(and pushes it with his lips.)
(Everyone is shocked.)
We got it. No, my lips didn't touch his.
They didn't touch.
Go.
(Jong Kook and Na Eun try the fifth one.)
- You got it. - That's good.
Okay. Good. All right.
Cho Rong!
We can do it.
(There are only two snacks left.)
Blow it. Hurry.
No, that's too strong.
(She blows too hard.)
(Despite that...)
(He almost had it!)
Put your tongue through it.
(Biting)
All right!
(Thanks to his protruding lips, he gets it.)
We're almost there.
(There's only one left.)
We got it! Last one!
- Last one! - 20 seconds.
(Can they finish on time and obtain the ingredients?)
- Seok Jin. - Come on.
- She can't reach. - Nam Joo.
You have to eat it, Seok Jin! She can't reach.
(Nam Joo can't reach. You have to eat it, Seok Jin!)
- Switch seats. - You have to eat it, Seok Jin!
- Switch seats. - Switch seats.
Nam Joo has to blow it.
There's no time!
Eat it.
It's too strong.
- It's too strong. - Gently.
Smoothly!
You can do it!
(There's no time left. Can they succeed?)
(Biting)
(They complete the quest on time.)
He did it!
(We did it!)
(They obtained a portable burner out of 8 ingredients.)
We did it!
(Portable burner)
A quest has been discovered.
Hoodie Link Between Us.
"This is a couples' match to reach the next level."
"Tie yours and your opponents' hoodies together,"
"and the team that can guess the letter..."
"on the opponents' head first wins."
If you play against Jong Kook, you won't be able to see.
- This... - You won't be able to see.
I want to avoid Jong Kook.
He might not be able to see well.
(He has small eyes.)
There's a team that'll advance by default.
Let's pick one and go ahead.
Is something wrong?
- No. - Are you in a good mood?
Are you in a bad mood because you are Level One?
- Don't get me wrong. - Excuse me.
- Are you getting annoyed? - Are you?
I'm not.
- I know what that's like. - I'm not.
- Is this it? - You're mistaken.
- You're mistaken. - Am I?
It feels like he's annoyed.
- Then... - We'll pick first.
- Pick one. - No, Haha.
- This one. - Are you sure?
- This one. - Okay.
Take it. In 1, 2, 3. Show us.
- I'm 100 percent sure. - Show us right away.
(Is this the default win?)
- In 1, 2, 3. - It's blank.
(It's a blank card.)
All right. Pick one, Cho Rong.
- Please take one. - It's 1 out of 6.
(Jae Seok and Cho Rong are next.)
Isn't it better to go first?
- It is. - That's not possible.
It's not.
(What card did Cho Rong pick?)
(Darn it.)
Here.
(It's not a default win.)
- "Darn it"? - What did you say?
She's competitive.
Pick one, Na Eun.
We already did two teams, so I'll move to the other side.
(He changes the order all of a sudden.)
What are you doing?
That's being annoying.
- I agree. - We did two teams on that side.
- Right? - Yes.
That's being annoying.
(Hold on.)
- No? - No.
- I'm not. - Okay.
- I'll keep an eye on you. - Pick one.
- Which one do you want to pick? - This one.
(This one.)
This one? Then I'll pick something else.
(Kwang Soo is unlucky.)
(What card did she pick?)
Okay. What is it, Eun Ji?
(It's still a blank card.)
Get out.
Okay. Good.
- Please, Bo Mi. - Can we pick at the same time?
Bo Mi. Feel it.
- Can you feel it? - Yes.
(This is it.)
- Please. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Did Bo Mi feel something?)
(The result is...)
(a dud.)
Okay!
(All 4 cards so far were blank. There are 3 cards left.)
That was close. There are three left.
Okay. Come back here.
You did 2 here and 2 there, so you have to come back.
- No, no. - Sir?
- Hold on. - We need a moment, sir.
- Sir. - Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok gets dragged to the corner.)
Where are you going, Jae Seok?
(This is the end of the annoying one.)
Hold on. We can talk, but don't get away from the cameras.
I'm doing that on purpose.
(I'm doing that on purpose.)
(They're already at the end.)
Don't get away from the cameras. Hey!
(What do I do now?)
(He puts up a fight.)
- Get me on the camera! - No...
(Help me.)
- Why are you taking me there? - But why?
- You did 2 and 2, so come back. - Watch.
- Listen to me. - Okay, I will.
Listen. I did 2 and 2, right?
I did 2 and 2, so 1 person from each team...
(There are three teams left.)
- Pick. - We can do that.
- I'll pick. - Okay.
All right. You pick, Na Eun.
I think it's us.
- Right? - Yes.
- I feel that way too. - Right?
- This one. - Show us.
(They picked their cards.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Who's the lucky one with the default win?)
(It's Na Eun.)
It's us.
(Jong Kook and Na Eun advance to the semifinal.)
I told you it's us. All right!
They're so lucky.
Jae Seok, you should have gone in the right order.
Why did you change it?
You can't be annoying all of a sudden.
(The default win has been decided. The list of matches will be given.)
- This is how the world is. - This is how the world is.
Na Eun's got the lucky touch.
(Hoodie Link Between Us)
First contestants, please come on out.
- For the first match... - Then we'll just face Seok Jin.
Okay. Seok Jin versus Haha.
- No. - Seok Jin versus Haha.
Nam Joo as well.
It'll be a sweet win. It'll be sweet.
This might as well be a default win.
- Put this on. - Tie it for each other.
- Do we tie it? - Tie it for each other.
I won't be soft.
- This is a game. - Nam Joo, you have to win.
I think I'll laugh.
What did you say?
What do you mean you'll laugh?
(This will be fun.)
All right.
- It's on the side. - It goes on the side?
(They have to guess the letter on the opponent's head.)
Is it on the left?
- You can't see that. - It goes on the side?
It's harder to see.
- If you know the answer, yell out. - Okay.
- Ready, - Haha, you have to look at mine.
- set... - This is going to be so hard.
I know.
If you pull, you can't see either one.
(They lose their sight.)
Pull and let go.
You have to pull and let go.
- Se Chan can't look at Nam Joo's. - You can't see.
I can't see at all.
(What's that?)
(Floundering)
I can't see.
I can see now.
I can see.
Hold on.
(Peeking)
Mine.
(Haha sees Seok Jin's letter.)
Hey, this is it.
(They have to see Nam Joo's now.)
(He checks hers as well through a small opening.)
Hey. Answer!
- Answer! - "Bang Mok".
- What? - "Bang Mok".
(He's correct.)
- Okay! - Yes!
(Haha and Se Chan advance to the semifinal.)
If you pull on this, you can't see anything.
I saw through a gap.
Next, Ha Young and Ji Hyo...
versus Bo Mi and So Min.
This is hard.
- This is the second match. - Right.
Please put your heads down.
So Min and Ji Hyo.
They haven't faced each other that many times.
I think they're competitive.
("Ah Ram" and "Go Sat")
I think So Min will get dragged around.
I'm curious.
(Staring contest)
(She's intimidated.)
(They had a headbutting match going on.)
(It's fierce.)
Are you sure?
Ha Young is strong, right?
- Right? - It's a close call.
Bo Mi is really strong too.
- Those two are the strongest. - Let's go.
Ready,
set...
(The game starts.)
It's "Ah" here.
(As soon as they start,)
(Ha Young sees her letter.)
It's "Ah" here.
(Ha Young is incredible.)
(Meanwhile, the other ones...)
(Peekaboo)
(They are intense in their own way.)
Ji Hyo, it's "Ah" here.
(She's busy right now.)
- Shall we get up? - Get up?
In 1, 2, 3.
(She faked it.)
(They both collapse.)
What are you guys doing?
(I'm going to pay attention and look.)
- What are you two... - Answer!
- Answer? - Answer.
- Goodness. - Answer.
- What is it? - Say it.
- Don't hold her. - "Ah Ram".
(She's correct.)
How did you see?
- Could you see? - I saw it.
- Gosh. - She got it right away.
I peeked.
Next, it's our turn.
- Yes. - This is going to be dirty.
Here they come.
- What do I do? - Oh, gosh.
(They're very nervous.)
The weather is perfect for a dirty match.
(The two who are known to play dirty meet once again.)
(The original dirty player is Grasshopper.)
Both teams are...
very dirty.
What did you do now?
(A well-matched contest)
I'm looking forward to this.
(Dragon versus Tiger. Who will win?)
- I'm looking forward to this. - Kwang Soo is going to be dirty.
I think Jae Seok will get dragged around.
(Kwang Soo is going to be dirty.)
(Pulling)
- Okay. - Why does he pull his pants up?
(It's all the way up.)
Let's go.
We'll put the letters on. Don't look.
(Dirty meets dirty.)
(The way they are dressed suggests it will be a very dirty match.)
- Why did you pull up your pants? - It feels better like this.
This way, it won't come off.
("Hwi Sae" and "Hal Gi")
Hey, let's show each other.
Let's just show each other.
Let's go. Ready,
set...
(The game starts.)
It's competitive.
This is hard.
(Pulling)
(Her vision is blocked.)
(Eun Ji controls the hoodie as she pleases.)
(She sees Cho Rong's letter.)
Kwang Soo!
What's that?
(She calls for Kwang Soo.)
(There is a face competition going on.)
(Whoever moves their head first loses.)
(They defend with their faces.)
This is short-track speed skating.
(That looks like...)
What's this?
(Finals for face short-track)
(The two players are getting ready to go forward.)
What's that?
(This is the fair dirty play.)
(It's always a tight match. This is no different.)
(None of them is backing down. This is a tight match.)
Are you skating?
Answer!
(Does Eun Ji know the answer?)
(They don't care.)
Answer?
"Hal Gi".
(Eun Ji's answer is "Hal Gi".)
(She's correct.)
(What?)
Jae Seok.
We can see yours.
You're showing it...
to everybody.
(While they were face skating,)
(Eun Ji saw Jae Seok's letter.)
Did you see his?
You saw his?
(Thanks to Eun Ji, they advance to the semifinal.)
Didn't you see it, Cho Rong?
I only saw half a lap of short-track.
We were supposed to watch two laps. That's too bad.
(Let's compliment the dirty players who played a great match.)
I'm so mad.
(The semifinalists have been decided.)
Goodness.
We are ready.
Winners, please come on out.
Ji Hyo and Haha should go first.
Okay.
(Okay, let's do this!)
All right!
(Ji Hyo against Haha, and Ha Young against Se Chan)
Am I facing Ji Hyo?
Please get close.
Haha and Ji Hyo both look like men.
I touched her shoulders,
and she's muscular here.
She is.
(Don't you underestimate her.)
("Deu Re" for Ji Hyo and Ha Young)
("Ki Seu" for Haha and Se Chan)
Where is it for you?
I...
- Left side? - What about you?
- Let's go. - Ready,
(They're around the same build. Who'll be the winners?)
set...
(The game starts.)
(She lies down.)
What are you doing?
It's on the floor.
Where's Haha's?
(It's a competitive game.)
(Haha sees "Re".)
This is uncomfortable, Haha.
Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, "Seu".
(Se Chan sees hers too.)
- "Seu". - It's "Deu".
She's "Deu", Haha.
(He has Se Chan's information.)
Answer.
"Deu Re".
All right!
(He's correct.)
("Deu Re" indicates the weight of one's character.)
- What's "Deu Re"? - How did you know?
I saw yours.
This time...
It's been a while.
(Second round of semifinals)
This will be good to watch.
(Kwang Soo and Eun Ji versus Jong Kook and Na Eun)
- This will be good to watch. - It's been a while.
If Eun Ji beats Na Eun,
you never know what'll happen.
This is my first time, so I'm really nervous.
Don't look.
(Kwang Soo is tall and agile.)
Put on the letters.
This reminds me of Andre Kim's fashion show.
Left or right?
This side, right?
("Wi Re" for Kwang Soo and Eun Ji)
("Gam Da" for Jong Kook and Na Eun)
- Ready, - Come on.
set...
(The game starts.)
(Eun Ji tightens the string as soon as the game starts.)
Hold on.
(She spins it around.)
(Eun Ji sees "Gam".)
- I can't see. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, "Gam".
She sees it so well.
She's so good.
(Eun Ji saw her letter,)
(so it's Kwang Soo's turn.)
(Kwang Soo starts attacking as well.)
(He attacks by going round and round.)
(Keep trying.)
I saw it.
(This won't work.)
"Re".
(While Kwang Soo takes a second, he sees Eun Ji's letter.)
(What is he doing?)
What? "Re"?
Answer. "Wi Re"?
("Wi Re"?)
"Wi Re". Okay.
(He's correct.)
(Sighing)
Goodness.
It was Jong Kook's game anyways.
Hey, why did you take your phone out?
(Why did you take your phone out?)
I was going to take a picture.
- I was going to look at it. - This was his game anyways.
(Jong Kook and Na Eun advance to the finals.)
That was so funny.
(Finals is Haha and Se Chan versus Jong Kook and Na Eun.)
- Who do you want? - Whoever.
You can take Na Eun.
Okay. I won't say no.
I'm envious of you, Se Chan.
Please put the letters on.
- Haha. - Yes.
We came this far, so we have to win.
Of course.
("Gi Yuk" for Haha and Se Chan)
This is our chance.
("Tae Ggal" for Jong Kook and Na Eun)
Se Chan, I think I'm already in pain.
Ready,
(Which team will advance to the next level?)
set...
(The final match starts.)
No.
(Is Se Chan helpless against Na Eun?)
Hold on.
Hey, hold on.
(He goes round and round Na Eun.)
(Na Eun is busy avoiding him.)
(What do I do?)
I can't see.
(He can only see Na Eun.)
- "Gi". Na Eun, yours is "Gi". - "Gi"?
(Jong Kook sees the letter on Se Chan from the other side.)
(He has to look at Haha's to put the letters together.)
- "Gi". - Hold on.
- Go away. - Look at his!
(Hurry up.)
Look at his!
(Lifting)
(Poor Haha.)
- This is over. - Look at his, Na Eun.
Na Eun, it's "Gi". Look at his.
Okay.
I can't see.
(If Na Eun can't see,)
(he can look for himself.)
(What's going on?)
"Gi Yuk".
(He finds the letter "Yuk".)
(He's correct.)
(Jong Kook and Na Eun are the winners.)
What happened, Haha?
Hey, are you all right?
This sweater has no hole!
(Haha and Se Chan lose unfortunately.)
Do you guys always lose?
Yes!
(You know well.)
- It's been like this for 8 years. - Cho Rong said,
"Do you guys always lose?"
(Jong Kook always wins. They advance to the next level.)
(I tried so hard.)
Sadly, it's time to say goodbye to Apink.
(It's time to say goodbye to the quest fairies.)
- Please! - Why?
- A little bit more! - Please!
30 more minutes. Please!
We're just getting started.
Let's do another round.
That was so short.
It was great having them.
Let's give a round of applause for Apink.
Thank you.
Where is it?
Is it around the cameraman's neck?
(Find the next quest.)
- There it is. - Where?
- It's outside. - It's outside.
Ji Hyo, good catch.
Last Party Time.
Out of all the rice cake soup ingredients,
you have earned a pot, beef,
You have not obtained rice cake, seasoning, eggs, and seaweed,
so they're hidden around the resort.
The person who finds the ingredients and makes rice cake soup advances.
However, each person can only find one ingredient.
The sled goes down once you find a partner...
who has a different ingredient.
(You can only find one ingredient each.)
(You must get on the sled with someone who found a different one.)
The clan member you partner up with is very important.
It's about who you come down the hill with.
I have to find it.
Find what?
- Ingredients, Seok Jin. - Ingredients.
- Ingredients for rice cake soup. - I see.
I have to find it fast and leave.
We have to find the ingredients.
What do they look like?
Is it an envelope?
There must be one.
I think there'll be one here.
Is it hanging from here?
Can you tell me once you see one?
I'm not the only one who can't see it, right?
Why can't I find any?
(She becomes suspicious.)
(Is it in the back of your head?)
It can't be in here.
Why is it nowhere to be found?
(I'm suspicious of you.)
Are there mission envelopes?
Give it to me.
(Yelling)
Hurry.
(She's helpless, so she just yells at nobody.)
This is pretty.
Is it here?
Is this the famous candle street?
(Candle street brightens the surrounding.)
There has to be an envelope here.
There has to be one. Oh, dear.
What's this?
(She was looking at the candles and found an ingredient card.)
(Seasoning)
(Jeon So Min earned seasoning.)
Wasn't I so swift?
I was so quick.
Did the others find anything?
I hope there's somebody.
Look at the sun. It's so pretty.
(Who will get the remaining ingredients?)
Look. It's so pretty.
This is a beautiful world.
I guess you found one early.
(He clenches his teeth.)
You don't have a partner, so you can't go.
You're right.
(Finding a clan member is just as important.)
Ji Hyo. Did you find one?
(The other members haven't found any. They're still looking.)
There must be one here.
(Seok Jin spots something!)
This is it!
(He found one in the door crack.)
Seok Jin found it.
Goodness.
It was there?
(Seok Jin finds an ingredient after So Min.)
I found one.
(Eggs)
(Seok Jin obtained eggs.)
What happens now that I found an ingredient?
Who found an ingredient?
It's Seok Jin.
(Why does it have to be Seok Jin?)
Who wants to team up with me?
- I won't team up with Seok Jin. - This is...
He is untrustworthy.
Who wants to team up with me?
(Has anyone found an ingredient?)
You get on the sled with someone who found an ingredient, right?
Someone who found an ingredient?
(She passes by Seok Jin.)
- Haven't you found an ingredient? - No, I haven't.
(Why hasn't anyone found an ingredient?)
I need to go and cook rice cake soup.
I want to team up with Jong Kook...
because he is fair.
(Jong Kook is searching diligently.)
My goodness.
My goodness,
why didn't I see this before?
My goodness.
(Seaweed)
(Jong Kook obtained seaweed.)
With whom should I go? Hold on.
Jong Kook, did you find an ingredient?
So Min.
- You found an ingredient, right? - Yes.
Let's go down the hill.
(Will you join So Min's clan?)
- Let's go. - Okay.
(Yes)
- What are you doing? - Gosh.
- Hey. - Don't be like that.
(So Min brushes him off.)
(Did they form a clan?)
Seok Jin found an ingredient, but I didn't want to team up...
- with him. - Let's hurry up.
It's important...
that we hurry up and go down.
I found my savior!
Okay.
We don't know what's waiting for us.
- You are right. - We have to keep advancing.
There it is.
This is the final quest of Rice Cake Soup in the Sky Race.
(The final quest, Snow tube)
The two players who found an ingredient...
must take a snow tube to the final destination.
(The two players who found an ingredient...)
(must take a snow tube to the final destination.)
I am a bit scared.
Let's go.
(You can reach the final destination by riding this snow tube.)
So Min, let's go.
- It's okay. - Okay.
Should I lie back?
Should I raise my legs?
(She babbles out of fear.)
(She goes down with a scream.)
Mom!
(Here I come to eat rice cake soup!)
(She moves through the wind to level up.)
(This is so much fun.)
(My goodness.)
(It's actually fun.)
This is fun. This is fun.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
(So Min, here I come!)
(Let's level up!)
(He is carefree.)
(He succeeds to land in a cute way.)
(Sexy)
This is great.
This is really fun.
- It's fun, right? - It's great.
How pretty!
- How pretty! - This place is nice.
Will we cook rice cake soup here?
My goodness, this is my first time.
This is my first time. This place is pretty.
- I agree. Do you want a photo? - Yes, please.
Thank you, Jong Kook.
Don't mention it.
(They take a photo.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Cute)
(A photo by Jong Kook)
Thank you.
You must have taken a lot of photos.
- That's not true. - The angle is really nice.
Really?
It's not here.
(While the Tiger Moth Clan is taking photos...)
Haha, did you find an ingredient?
- No, I didn't. - It's nowhere to be found.
Did you find an ingredient?
(At that moment)
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo finds an ingredient that was hidden.)
(Rice cake)
(Lee Kwang Soo obtained rice cake.)
Rice cake! It's the most important ingredient.
Rice cake.
Kwang Soo, did you find an ingredient?
(Will you join Jee Seok Jin's clan?)
Let's go together.
- Did you find an ingredient? - Yes.
If you found an ingredient, sure.
It's important that we go down the hill.
- Let's go. - I don't know what is going on.
- What? - I don't know what is going on.
Oh, we are taking a sled down.
(They arrive at the snow tube quest as well.)
- Hold on. - I don't think I can do this.
(They just need to take a snow tube down the slide.)
I can't do this.
How are we supposed to ride this?
I will run to the final destination.
It doesn't matter how we go down the hill, right?
You must ride a snow tube in order to cook rice cake soup.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Knock me out.
How old do you have to be to ride this?
Push me down the slope while I am sleeping.
(He says anything that comes to mind.)
Let's go. We need to hurry up because people are waiting.
The water is boiling.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(Seok Jin's snow tube goes first.)
(Screaming)
(He is having so much fun that he can't close his mouth.)
That was incredible.
(Seok Jin succeeds to land.)
(Kwang Soo's snow tube goes next.)
(This is so much fun.)
(Screaming)
That was incredible.
(The scaredy-cat succeeds to land as well.)
(His face shows how intense the ride was.)
It was okay, right?
- It was fun. - It was fun, right?
It was really fun once I got on.
It was really fast.
The speed was incredible.
Let's cook rice cake soup.
- Okay. - Shall we cook rice cake soup?
- Let's level up. - Let's level up together.
Is there a bowl?
- Everyone important is here. - You are right.
Seasoning.
Let's add everything.
- Let's add rice cake first. - Rice cake.
- Add rice cake. - Should I add everything?
Isn't that too much?
- Garlic. - That's too much garlic.
That's...
(Add a lot of rice cake and garlic.)
Hey!
- The producer instructed me. - You added...
You added...
- You added too much garlic. - Should we add eggs later?
It will be tasty. It's the taste of Korea.
(The taste of Korea)
(Let's give it a taste.)
(What?)
(She grimaces.)
- What is it? - Hey!
(Her face tells everything.)
This is far from aromatic.
It's really spicy.
You told me to add all of it.
- You told me to add all of it. - You told her to add all of it.
(In any case, they manage to make rice cake soup and level up.)
It's tasty.
There could be...
some people who like this taste. It's not bad.
They already made...
- They look happy. - I know.
(The 4 people who haven't found any ingredients...)
(will form a clan of 2 people and ride a snow tube.)
This is sad.
A clan of two people.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan formed a clan.)
(Giggling)
Here I come!
(We didn't find an ingredient, but we will have fun.)
All right.
(Jae Seok and Haha formed a clan.)
(The timid duo rides a snow tube.)
My goodness.
(Rice Cake Soup in the Sky Race ends.)
The four of you will level up.
- Okay! - Yes!
Okay.
Let's go.
Jae Seok, Haha, and Se Chan are Level One and last in place.
For goodness' sake.
- For goodness' sake. - I can't believe it.
Remember your clan member.
The secret of these clans will be revealed...
- next week. - What?
(The secrets of the clans will be revealed next week?)
These must be teams.
(Which adventures will these clans have next?)
(Attention, members of Running Man!)
(Turn on the camera we gave you right now.)
(Text one of the secrets of your clan to the main producer.)
(You will receive amazing benefits in the order the texts arrive.)
(The benefits will be revealed next week.)