- Hello. - Hello.
- It's hot. - By the way,
the heatwave is really here.
- It's so hot today. - The heatwave has struck.
- Seriously. - I heard...
- it'll be really hot this year. - It's so sunny in the afternoon.
- Jong Kook, nice pink shorts. - Right?
(Attracting attention)
- I wear bright colors in summer. - Your pink shorts look nice.
What happened?
I wear bright-colored outfits in summer. I do.
I was just complimenting you.
I think you were a eunuch in your previous life.
(I think you were a eunuch in your previous life.)
- That's so true. - He was a traitor.
- He had to be a traitor. Traitor. - A traitor.
"Yes, Your Majesty."
Since it's hot today, let's speed things up today.
Okay!
Before we start today, let me tell you...
that we have invited guests who don't star on variety shows often.
- Really? - Yes!
(There are guests that are hard to see on variety shows?)
(We're having guests today!)
Who are these guests?
It will be different today.
All right. Please come on out.
- Where? - Where?
(Who are today's guests?)
Gosh, hey.
- Goodness. - Hello.
(Who are these guests that don't star on variety shows often?)
(Four cast members from the movie, "Metamorphosis")
Hello, sir.
Gosh, hello.
(Cho Yi Hyun, Sung Dong Il, Kim Hye Jun, Bae Seong Woo)
(Welcome, cast of "Metamorphosis".)
They are the main characters of the movie. Gosh, Dong Il.
You haven't changed.
- You're still so causal. - He's wearing a neon color.
- Seong Woo is here. - My gosh.
Please come to the center.
You should stand in the center.
As for Dong Il, a long time ago, he was here...
- for "The Accidental Detective". - Right.
Of course. You were on our show quite a few times now.
- Right. It was because of him. - Exactly.
It was when he filmed the movie with Kwang Soo.
- Right. We had so much fun. - You were here for that.
The movie would have done better if he wasn't in the movie.
(He's being brutally honest all of a sudden.)
(Feeling hurt)
Gosh.
- Goodness. - He was acting just like...
he was filming Running Man for our movie.
Why did you do that?
- I tried to stop the director. - Exactly.
- I told him it's either him or me. - That's why among entertainers,
he's known as my junior comedian.
We've been telling him to focus on just variety shows.
But he's not listening to me.
I guess he gets offers from time to time.
Just don't do anything, Kwang Soo.
I'm meeting two people who can suffocate me the most in my life.
(I'm meeting two people who can suffocate me the most in my life.)
- I'm about to lose it. - Really?
All right. The four of them will be joining us today.
First of all, he's been on our show several times now.
It's Sung Dong Il.
(Cherished national actor, Sung Dong Il)
The movie is called "Metamorphosis". Please tell us about the movie.
The devil is going to take turns possessing the entire family.
You're possessed?
Isn't that obvious? As for horror movies,
when there are beautiful ladies like them, one of them...
- will be in an accident. - Come on.
- That's outdated. - That's not what it's about.
- It's not like that these days. - It's not? I'm sorry.
- First of all... Yes? - Seriously.
He's lasted in this industry too long without any wits.
(Launching his 2nd brutally honest comment)
- Did you hear him? - Why would he say that?
"Without any wits."
He's talking about "Hometown Legends".
I see. That was outdated.
Few years back, he'd rush to me excited saying, "Hey, Dong Il!"
But today, he came crawling over like this.
You should rest now.
(You should rest now.)
Well, you're still working.
How can I rest?
(Well, you're still working. How can I rest?)
You're still working.
Suk Jin is working so hard that he's skinning his knees.
- Right. - Look at his knees.
All right. That was Dong Il's introduction.
Now, let's move onto Bae Seong Woo.
(The next guest, scene-stealer, Bae Seong Woo, is introduced.)
(All kinds of modifiers suit him.)
(He's the actor with 1,000 faces the viewers have acknowledged.)
(He's the sought-after actor in the movie industry...)
(as he slowly stars in masterpiece movies.)
(You'll find out his real charms on Running Man shortly!)
(Look forward to his bromance with his best friend, Kwang Soo.)
By the way, Seong Woo is friends with Kwang Soo too.
- Yes, he is. - Right.
The three of us have been close friends for several years now.
- I see. - It's Seong Woo's interview.
All right. You debuted in a musical first?
- He has a great voice. - He's a good singer.
I didn't know he was good at singing.
- He majored in ballet. - What?
- Ballet? - You did ballet?
- Yes. - He majored in ballet.
- Then... - Why are you staring at me?
Can you show us a little bit?
- I want to see him dance now. - I'm so curious.
You saw "Gisselle".
- You know? - I can do this.
(He gets into position. Is he doing a turn?)
(Looking sloppy)
I'm sorry.
(Oh, my...)
This is grass.
You could've done better without it.
- He's not that talented. - Right.
(He's not that talented.)
- He's not that good. - That's why...
- I'm focusing on another area. - You majored in ballet?
I just majored in theater acting.
- He has ties to SBS too. - Right.
- Right. - Of course, we know.
- Bae Seong Jae is his brother. - Right.
- Watch the World Cup on SBS. - Right.
- That's amazing. - I was hired by SBS first too.
- Oh, right. - Right!
Really?
- SBS hired him as an actor. - Right.
- Really? - The first group of recruits.
- I was the founding member. - Right.
Who are some actors that were hired with you?
Gong Hyung Jin started with me.
- Oh Dae Gyu. - Oh Dae Gyu.
I don't even know what they are up to.
(Making a confession all of a sudden)
- It's been so long. - But they were your colleagues.
- I'm sure they are doing well. - Right.
- I hope they're healthy. - Right.
We had brief introductions of these two guests now.
They are new faces on our show. They'll join us today.
Let me introduce Kim Hye Jun and Cho Yi Hyun to you.
(Rising super rookies)
(Cho Yi Hyun and Kim Hye Jun)
(Kim Hye Jun, a rising new actress in the movie industry)
(Cho Yi Hyun, a real super rookie with a meteorite debut last year)
(They are rising actresses to watch in the movie industry.)
By the way, don't people mistake you two as sisters?
- You look alike. - You resemble each other.
- You two look alike. - Right. We're sisters in the movie.
They resemble each other.
- That's why. Are you related? - They look so much alike.
- No. - No.
- You two resemble each other. - They have a similar image.
Why are you guys chatting so much unlike during our introductions?
(Why are you guys chatting so much unlike during our introductions?)
- We're curious about them. - We're interested.
- It means we're interested. - It's our first time meeting them.
When you were walking down the stairs earlier,
- we were only looking at them. - Right.
I'm sorry.
- Only they will go viral online. - That just means...
- people are interested in them. - I was just stopping by too.
I see.
(Casually strolling his neighborhood)
In today's race,
deities have disguised themselves as humans.
- It's a Metamorphosis Race. - Okay.
Currently, three deities are hiding among you disguised as humans.
(Three deities are disguised as humans.)
It's not me. It's not me.
- Is it you? - It's not me. I swear.
I knew it.
- It's not me. It's really not me. - You, you.
- I bet it's one of them. - There are three?
- I saw this coming. - It's 1 of the 2.
- It's not me. It's not! - Hey, look.
Let me tell you about the deities.
There's Hades, the deity of the afterlife, who was forced...
to the underworld in the beginning of time where he ruled.
He harbored ill feelings toward his brothers Zeus and Poseidon...
and locked them up for eternity in the underworld.
To rule the world of the living, he's disguised himself as a human...
and is hiding among you.
Zeus and Poseidon...
are disguised as humans and are hiding here...
to find Hades to send back to the underworld again.
The three deities are Zeus, Poseidon, and Hades.
Does that mean there's one villain who is Hades?
The villain is Hades.
For the sake of convenience, you'll address...
everyone as brother, not sister.
- Brother. We're all men. - Brother.
Before Zeus and Poseidon get eliminated,
you must help them and eliminate Hades to win.
- There's Hades. - Hades.
However, if Hades finds out who Zeus and Poseidon are...
and eliminates them first, Hades will win the race.
And all of you will be dragged to the underworld.
- Hades. - Hades.
- "Ha"des? - What?
- Haha. - Hades.
- Hades? - I was the spy last week.
Or is Jae Suk Zeus?
- Zeus? - Is Jae Suk Zeus?
He really must be Zeus. He's surprised.
- Do your ad-lib. - Say your ad-lib.
It's not me.
(Shaking like a tree)
- Your ad-lib is impressive. - Ad-lib.
- Did you see that? - He didn't ad-lib.
- It's no joke. - It should go into a factory.
Would Hades deliberately get caught?
- Who? - I don't see why he would do that.
- To end the filming quickly. - To go home early?
- He wants to get off early. - Do you want to go home early?
Well, my wife told me to come home early today.
Is he Hades?
(I have to go home early today.)
Are you Hades?
- My house is not far from here. - Hades.
She asked me why I'd be late.
But I'm sure they already chose Hades.
(It's 1 versus 11.)
By the way, it will be so hard for Hades.
Right.
I think you could be Hades.
- No, that's not true. - I agree.
He might be acting.
(They move to another place for their first mission.)
This is just like "Tray Karaoke".
I came in here because it's too hot outside.
This place is cool.
It's hot. This is "Tray Karaoke".
When did So Min get here?
Why are you here early?
Me? Just because.
- Hey, it's So Min. - She's...
- Okay. - Seriously.
It's just hot.
It's just hot. You don't trust me?
Hey. Se Chan, you don't believe me?
- No. - Hey.
- So Min. - Yes, Haha?
That's not how you seduce men.
(That's not how you seduce men.)
Then how?
Men won't fall for that.
Don't be so aggressive.
What should I do then?
You should come up with an order first.
Choose between Suk Jin and him first.
(In that case, it's Se Chan.)
Se Chan.
What?
("Come here, Se Chan." She starts joking.)
- What? - Come here.
Hurry.
Do I have to call you like this? Se Chan.
(He's sick of her.)
Stop it.
Hey, I think it worked a bit.
(Seeing his reaction)
Se Chan.
(Will this work?)
Haha, what's wrong with her?
Stop it. She went like this, "Se Chan".
How am I supposed to respond to that?
Do I say, "Sure, So Min."
- You should go to her. - Tell her to come to you.
(You come here.)
(Really? Okay, I'll get going now.)
(Feeling the chills)
- She's good. - Yes, she's good.
- That was natural. - She's good.
(Their plot of love no one is interested in is over.)
- Everyone is here, right? - Yes.
Right before the cameras were rolling,
he said it's uncomfortable to hang out with Kwang Soo.
He doesn't get why Kwang Soo wears masks.
- Everyone can recognize it's him. - It's so obvious.
(No matter how much he covers up, it's him.)
Why do you do that, Kwang Soo?
Hey, it's obvious.
I can understand...
- when D.O. does it. - D.O.
Dong Il, do you know what's the funniest?
They went to the airport and both wore masks.
- Right. Right. - Jong Kook.
- He was wearing a sleeveless top. - Yes, we did.
He wore a sleeveless top and a mask.
- Right. - That's funny.
(He can totally relate to it.)
Have you worn a mask before?
- Pardon? - Have you worn one?
No, my respiratory system is weak.
Your respiratory system is weak.
(No, my respiratory system is weak.)
(This manly guy has weak lung power.)
I need to breathe in a lot of oxygen.
We shouldn't laugh at this. It's true.
I need to take in big gulps of oxygen.
His respiratory system is weak.
All right. Here's your first mission.
With this group mission, you can figure out who Hades is.
It's called Stopping Means Death.
You will choose six members to play each round...
in order to complete your mission.
As for your mission, you'll listen to the category we give you...
and name one thing about the category one at a time.
If the category is girl group,
- you'll name girl groups. - Right.
- Everyone will name one. - GFRIEND.
GFRIEND. Did you understand?
- I'm good at this. - I'm good at this.
Hye Jun and Yi Hyun, you understood it, right?
- Of course. - They'll be so good.
(They confidently answered it, but they are worried.)
If you successfully complete three or more rounds,
all 12 of you will receive a hint about Hades.
Everyone will get the hint?
We have to complete the mission.
All right. Here's your category for the first round.
- We'll see who gets it wrong. - We'll see who gets it wrong.
Here's the first keyword.
Stopping Means Death.
Famous figures with four-syllable names.
- King Sejong. - Madame Curie.
- What king? - Four-syllable name...
(He's taking his time.)
(They are surprised.)
- Dong Il, there are a lot. - Gosh.
- Eulji Mundeok. Sunwoo Jae Duk. - Madame Curie?
Sunwoo Jae Duk?
Seonwoo Yong Nyeo.
Jae Duk is alive now.
- Eulji Mundeok. - He's very active now.
That startled me.
Napoleon.
Should we count that as a failed round?
Or should we play another practice round?
- Practice round. - Practice round.
Practice round.
- Let's switch. - Dong Il.
Why don't you sit at the end?
Dong Il, you can go last.
- Or you can go 1st. - Going 1st is fine.
- Dong ll, you can go 1st. - Going 1st would be nice.
- First? - You can have time to prepare.
- Going second would be better. - They will give us enough time.
- Dong Il, you can go last. - Why don't you go first?
Am I that much of an issue?
(Am I that much of an issue?)
It's not that.
- That's not why. - No, no.
- It's a practice round. - You can just try it out.
Why don't you take me out then?
- No. You can play. - No.
Don't be upset. It's not that.
It's our strategy. It's a strategy.
If someone else says first whatever he was preparing to say...
All right. I'll start.
- I'll give you an easy one. - Okay.
Stopping Means Death.
Four-syllable Korean movies.
(Four-syllable Korean movies)
Hold on.
(His time is up.)
(They lose the 1st round.)
- Hey, this one hurt so much. - It really hurt.
- My gosh. - I was so startled.
- What's this? - Look at him.
Hey, Dong Il is angry now!
- Are you all right? - It really hurt.
This one really hurt.
- What was up with that? - Listen.
I think the viewers should know how much it hurts too.
(Anyway, as Seong Woo stalled, they lost the 1st round.)
- Why don't the six of us try next? - We'll try it.
- Seong Woo will play again. - What are some movies?
- Here's the thing. - Let's make him play again.
- He's filmed so many movies. - He'll play again.
- He was the main lead too. - That was a bit fishy.
- That is odd. - I see.
- He was in "Inside Men". - He'll play one more round.
There aren't that many four-syllable movies.
- No, there are a lot. - "Peppermint Candy".
- The six of us will play. - Right.
- "The Unjust". "Inside Men". - "Along with the Gods".
- Right. - "Along with the Gods".
- My movies have four syllables. - There were a lot.
(Was that a mistake? Or did he do it on purpose?)
- In which order should we sit? - Hey, I'll go first.
- Come on. - I want to see him play again.
What do you think?
We'll start now. No practice rounds. We'll start right away.
Hey, you have to ad-lib this.
Jae Suk and his ad-lib.
- He's going to have fun with it. - Watch.
- It's perfect if he goes second. - I'll do it with my ad-lib.
Hey, let's switch places. I'll take your place.
(That was sudden.)
- Why? - Why?
- Have fun with the ad-lib. - Go back to your seat.
- Go sit down. - Magician of language.
Okay.
- Hye Jun. Yi Hyun. Watch me. - Okay.
- Watch, Seong Woo. - We'll watch you.
Here we go.
Stopping Means Death.
Male idol stars.
BTOB.
- Cool. - Kwang Soo.
(It's a mixed group, and his time was up.)
- Hey. - Cool?
- Hey. It's not just two guys. - Cool isn't a male group.
- Cool? - It's a mixed group.
- Hey. Cool? - I didn't do it on purpose.
- Cool? - I mean...
There are BTS and EXO.
- There's Turbo too. - EXO...
- I just couldn't remember it. - Something is off about you.
- BTS. - I'm serious.
- There's no way. It was too easy. - EXO.
- Something's off about him. - I admit that I made a mistake.
- Highlight. - Jae Suk.
Kwang Soo has ties with the guests today.
- It's likely that it's him. - That makes sense.
- That's not it. - He's helping like an assistant.
Before we move on, Kwang Soo will get the tray.
- Why didn't you get hit? - It didn't hit him.
- The tray didn't hit him. - Why?
Okay. I'll do it.
(A while ago, he said Cool.)
(He avoided the tray by lowering his head.)
(And he starts acting like it hurt.)
(He dreamed of the perfect crime.)
- Why didn't he get hit? - It didn't hit him.
- Right. - Why didn't that hit Kwang Soo?
I saw it. He had his head jutted out, so he didn't get it.
No. Lower it. I'll do it for Kwang Soo.
(Stepping in all of a sudden)
- How? - Lower it.
Lower it just as it is.
Lower it.
- How will he... - Lower it more.
- How will he do that? - Lower it more.
- You must lower it more. - Lower it more.
That's good. I'll punish Kwang Soo.
(The righteous man came to punish Kwang Soo for his trickery.)
Here I go.
(Just tray)
(He's totally startled.)
(That hits the spot for everyone.)
Great.
- Kwang Soo, that's how you do it. - Kwang Soo.
Hey, compared to him, I'm such a nice guy.
- Hey, he's... - Let me explain.
Even other female members faced the trays.
But he's the tallest one...
and dodged like this to avoid the tray.
- Right. - It's as if...
he knew that he was going to get it wrong.
(Thinking back, he knew he'd get it wrong.)
(That makes sense.)
It was an honest mistake.
Kwang Soo is usually good at these kinds of games.
- Kwang Soo, you stay. - It was a mistake.
- I think Dong Il should play. - Okay. Come, Dong Il.
But in my opinion, I don't think he's Hades.
He didn't understand them at first.
- Suk Jin, okay. Sit down. - Me?
(He's not even listening to Suk Jin.)
(Me?)
Why aren't you listening to what I have to say?
We're trying to figure out who it is with my sharp reasoning skills.
Here's your category.
- Stopping Means Death. - Stopping Means Death.
A noodle dish.
- Guksu. - Jjajangmyeon.
Jjapaghetti.
(His time runs out.)
That was a strong one.
(Kwang Soo gets it wrong again.)
- Hey... - Gosh.
(Gosh, I'm doomed.)
- There's kalguksu too. - Exactly.
- There are so many noodles dishes. - There are so many.
- Pyeongyang naengmyeon. - Listen.
When Seong Woo said jjajangmyeon, you should say jjamppong.
- I was thinking of jjajangmyeon. - There are more.
- It's not that. I'm not Hades. - Bibimguksu too.
I'm just bad at this game.
Even if you are Hades,
you're ruining the show.
(Even if you are Hades, you're ruining the show.)
- You're ruining it. - I'm not Hades.
- I'm not ruining the show. - No.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said jjajangmyeon.
You were preparing to say that.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
- He's nice. - He's taking care of Kwang Soo.
He's a good guy.
He wants to look cool by himself.
(Unbelievable)
There are more than three Hades in this group.
It's really not me.
- Seong Woo. Kwang Soo, and Dong Il. - Yes.
All right. Everyone, come on out.
- Come on out. - "Come on out."
Here we go.
- Let's complete three rounds. - Okay.
- Stopping Means Death. - Stopping Means Death.
Films with numbers in their titles.
"Seven".
"Eight".
(He says eight after hearing "Seven" without thinking.)
- Eight? - That was awful.
- There's "No. 3". - That was...
- Something is off about him. - There's "Seventeen" too.
- I... - "Ocean's Eleven".
- Hey, hold on. - I mean...
- What's wrong with you? - Wait.
- Hey. - He's terrible.
Do you get nervous when you get the question?
You're the most famous host. Why are you nervous?
The keyword was something I didn't see coming.
I'm so shocked.
Here we go.
- Let's complete three rounds. - Okay.
- Let's not say the same answer. - This group...
Should I go last?
- Why? Are you nervous? - I mean...
Isn't it better for people who aren't good at this to go first?
- That's why you're there. - That's why you're there.
Do you not know why you're going second?
Goodness.
You indeed have the best ad-libs.
- Seong Woo, pay attention now. - Okay.
- He should switch with Ji Hyo. - Okay.
(People who aren't good at this will go first.)
- We'll start now. - If I screw up,
you can think that I'm Hades.
- Okay. - Let's enunciate well.
Stopping Means Death.
Words with the sound for double b's.
- Double b's. - Double b's?
Bread.
"Papillon".
"Mulberry".
(For the 1st time, all 3 of them get it right.)
(Now, there are only 3 more left.)
Honk, honk.
(He gets it wrong.)
(Shouting)
- What was that? - Come on.
(What was that?)
(Dong Il gets it wrong.)
"Honk, honk"?
(What was that?)
That really hurts. I'm dizzy.
- Isn't that okay? - That was a car sound.
- Honk, honk. - Yes.
You can't do that.
- I can't? - Isn't it in the dictionary?
- Right, it is. - Honk, honk.
It's an actual word?
- They have the word. - Yes.
Don't they have it?
- Honk, honk. - Isn't it?
- Isn't it in the dictionary? - Honk, honk.
- All right. - I'm right, right?
If you can tell me the meaning, then I'll understand.
- Are you serious? - Hey.
(It's in the dictionary.)
- It is? - My gosh.
- Tell them the definition. - What?
- I think I know this one. - Isn't this it?
It means you're happy.
- No, it's not that one. - No?
- It's... - He just told him off.
Honk, honk.
(Honk, honk)
Wait, so it's in the dictionary.
- You can give a similar meaning. - Just tell them.
It's related to a government office.
- Honk, honk? - Yes, it's related...
to a government office.
- Right. - A government office?
It's related to government offices.
(He got lucky with the word.)
(Will Dong Il be able to get it right?)
It's wrong?
It means "the honking of a vehicle".
(The honking of a vehicle)
You should've said that!
Why did you say that?
(They tricked him.)
My gosh.
- Why did you say that? - Does his word exist?
He could've just said the honking of a car.
Why did you say that?
It's the sound of a vehicle.
- Everyone. - We were right.
This is your last chance.
Please choose your teammates carefully.
Let's form a competent team.
Okay. Let's pick only the best ones.
- Suk Jin, come out. - Okay.
Hold on. Jae Suk, come here.
- Go. - Don't try to join them.
I'll keep him in check.
Here we go.
Please let it be easy.
All right. This will be an easy one.
Stopping Means Death.
An actor's name.
(An actor's name)
Sung Dong Il.
Bae Seong Woo.
- What are you doing? - Lee Kwang Soo!
She got this wrong?
(She runs out of time.)
- What was that? - Hold on.
- You failed? - This makes no sense.
- She's so strange. - She is...
- She's definitely Hades. - No, wait.
- What is this? - There are many names.
There are many actors.
- There are so many actors. - There's Won Bin.
All right, Yi Hyun.
(She's an actress herself.)
I have my doubts, but we'll move on.
- Goodness. - Did we fail?
I caught you.
You failed round one.
We will not give you a hint regarding Hades.
(They fail to acquire a hint about Hades.)
There are so many actors.
I was too nervous.
Forget it.
We'll have some time to think about this.
Jae Suk, you're the second-most suspicious.
- And you're the third. - You're the third.
I'm seriously innocent.
- Aren't you hungry? - Yes.
For this mission, a hint and a meal card will be given.
(A hint and a meal card will be given.)
- It's called Eat Up. - Eat Up?
(Eat Up)
You'll be divided into 2 teams of 6.
Please split into teams first.
Should we use the spoons?
It's a battle.
I hope we don't get all the weak members.
Please pick one each.
- Here. - Ji Hyo.
Suk Jin.
- I've already made a choice. - Okay.
Please stand with your teammates.
(Team Dong Il, Team Seong Woo)
We have two candidates who are suspicious of being Hades.
Goodness.
- There are 3. - There are 3.
- All of them are there. - You're right.
- They're all here. - My gosh.
All of them are here.
- We need to prove them wrong. - Right.
We'll find out who it is.
All three of them are here.
(However)
I'm glad we can eat.
While eating, the winning team...
can pick which one of you will receive...
a hint about Hades and the brother deities.
But shouldn't the Hades candidates not receive the hints?
- You're right. - And who are they?
You.
And Yi Hyun.
It's really not me.
We have so many candidates on our team.
How about the one with the best leadership receive the hint?
- For example, Jong Kook. - But this is an individual battle.
- I see. - So there's no teamwork.
If you can't pick yet,
since Seong Woo is bored,
we'll play rock-paper-scissors with him.
Whoever plays the same hand as him will be eliminated.
- All right. - The remaining one will...
I haven't eaten yet. Is this necessary?
(What was that?)
Come on, be easy on him.
You should do something productive.
If he does it right,
- give him some food. - I will.
Yes, do so.
(That's great.)
- If you work a bit... - Work a bit?
If you play the same hand as him,
you'll be eliminated.
(Whoever plays the same hand loses.)
Rock-paper-scissors with Bae Seong Woo.
(Seong Woo plays scissors.)
- If you have scissors, you lose. - Okay.
- If you have scissors, you lose. - It's us three.
Yes.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seong Woo plays paper.)
One more time. Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seong Woo plays rock.)
(He's the only survivor.)
(Se Chan is the survivor.)
(Bring the hint to me.)
- Se Chan's Hades. - He is.
No way.
I doubt he is.
But I bet he'll give Hades critical information,
thinking Hades is on his side.
(There's a 200-percent chance of that happening.)
You're right.
- He tends to do that. - You're right.
Here you go.
He can't share it.
(Hades isn't a radio DJ. Suk Jin is excluded.)
(Candidates for Hades)
(Suk Jin is excluded?)
What is it?
It's a married man, right?
- Right? - Is it too broad?
- Is it too broad? - It's not like the hints...
we've always received.
Then?
- It's not broad? - No.
Seriously?
- I should've gotten this. - Oh, no.
I'm disappointed.
I'm glad Se Chan knows though.
(This time, he opens the brother deities hint.)
(The brother deities are brother and sister.)
Read it out loud.
- What? - Read it out loud.
Who are you to order me around?
I can share this one.
- What is it? - What is it?
"The brother deities are brother and sister."
(Resolutely)
(They're brother and sister?)
They're brother and sister.
- They're a female and a male. - Exactly.
- There's one each. - They're brother and sister?
Are you sure you were safe to say that?
Hades shouldn't know.
(Was that okay to say? Hades shouldn't know that.)
I told you he'd help Hades out.
- Hey. - Should you have told us that?
(Will the brother deities be able to catch Hades?)
(They arrive at their third destination.)
- Did you enjoy your meal? - Yes.
This is an individual battle.
Okay.
(This mission will be done individually.)
Suk Jin, your eyes are quite swollen.
Why are they swollen?
They swelled up in such a short time.
After we finished eating, we had a break.
I saw Suk Jin sleeping on a chair.
It made me teary-eyed.
(It made me teary-eyed.)
- It did? - That was what I saw of him...
after not seeing him for a while.
Dong Il is concerned about you a lot.
By the way, I was lying down.
You know those lids they put over dishes?
Who put that over my face?
That's better than a white cloth.
(That's better than a white cloth.)
(Only those over 50 can make such jokes.)
This will be an individual battle regarding movies.
It's called Do You Remember That Scene?
(Do You Remember That Scene?)
After listening to the question,
stand in front of 1 of the 3 choices that are given to you.
The last two surviving members will be rewarded.
The first-place winner will be given...
- both hints. - Okay.
The 2nd place winner will be given only 1.
- Here's the first question. - Let's hear it.
Here it is.
(Which running scene lasts the longest?)
"Which running scene lasts the longest?"
("Marathon")
Oh, that one.
(They need to find out which following scene is the longest.)
- Just this scene? - I think so.
You'll be shown a still.
You can figure it out then.
This is easier for actors.
Not at all.
(The scene stops.)
So it's the scene after this one.
(How long does the character run for?)
Which one of them runs the longest?
Time-wise?
"The Chaser".
Hey, 4885.
- I saw this four times. - It's you, right?
- He was so skinny. - He looked so young.
- Get out. - He was so skinny.
- This one's long. - He runs for a long time.
- I'm pretty sure. - He runs for a long time.
(How long does this character run for?)
(This is the third movie.)
It's "Forrest Gump".
(Is this one the answer?)
He runs for a very long time.
- Doesn't he run for three minutes? - Doesn't he run forever?
- Tom Hanks is in it. - It's him, right?
He wears that hat until he grows a mustache.
He runs until he grows a mustache.
(This is a famous scene. How long does he run for?)
Goodness.
Which one among these...
do the characters run the longest?
- It must be "Forrest Gump". - Let me answer.
- No, you need to stand up. - You need to stand up.
Suk Jin, please wake up.
Doesn't it feel like the most unlikely one is the answer?
Don't you think it's "Forrest Gump"?
I think it's the most unlikely one.
This will be amazing.
Everyone's standing in front of this one.
- You chose "Marathon"? - No one else is coming here?
In "The Chaser", he trips and then runs again.
- Exactly! - That's right.
The protagonist runs longer in "The Chaser" than in "Marathon".
I paused the movie because I was out of breath.
If it's a chase of high-tension,
it doesn't feel as boring.
However, it feels boring if the scene is a touching one.
The protagonist in "Marathon" runs really long.
All right. I'll reveal the answer then.
- Sure. - We'll start with...
"Forrest Gump".
That must be the shortest!
- It must be short. - It must be.
- Okay. - It must be the shortest.
Here he goes.
Is he running now?
This is where he begins to run.
He runs until you can't see him.
The same amount of time...
(Off he goes!)
- He's running. - Gosh.
It's longer than I expected.
- It's going on for a while. - He's featured on the news.
- Yes, the news. - That's right.
- He gets a beard. - People start to follow him.
Yes, they do.
This is already quite long.
- This'll surpass a minute. - For sure.
He's hasn't even changed clothes yet.
You're right.
- There's not a hint of a beard. - Not yet.
He then sports a beard.
We should be on the next scene by now.
Please move on.
Is this for real?
Maybe this is the longest running scene.
(He's worried.)
- It's long. - Was it this long?
(The scene suddenly changes though.)
- Nice! - All right.
This is really short.
- Is this for real? - So "Forrest Gump"...
Is this how the movie goes?
It's 45 seconds.
Yes, this is how the movie goes.
Why are you suddenly frowning?
The scene changed.
"Forrest Gump", 45 seconds.
It has to be the same scene.
The scene in "The Chaser" will be over a minute.
4885. Okay, he's running.
Could it be two minutes?
It's the most important scene in the movie.
No, not yet!
It's only been eight seconds.
- No, not yet! - Wait, it's over!
He only tripped and he's still running.
But...
- Up he goes the stairs. - The stairs.
- Run! - Run harder.
- Run! - Keep running!
Trip!
- No, not yet. - Keep running.
- Keep going. - He needs to run some more.
- That's right. - Run some more!
Yes!
- 47 seconds. - Keep running!
- Keep going. - He stopped running.
No, not yet. He'll run again.
That's it!
Is he running some more?
No way.
- Go, go! - No, stop.
- Go! - He's a running man.
Look at him run.
No, please stop.
I think it's a perfect win.
Please run some more.
This is unfair.
He finally stopped.
- It's over. - All right.
- A minute and... - A minute and 33 seconds.
- Yes! - Nice!
It's not bad. It's actually quite good.
Last but not least, let's check "Marathon".
The song is quite long in this movie.
The scene could change after six seconds.
- Here he goes. - He's running.
(To the sentimental music,)
(the protagonist starts to run.)
He's in the finals, so the run is very long.
No, you never know.
He might not actually run the whole marathon.
- That's right. - This is a variety show, isn't it?
- Look. - He's holding a chocolate pie.
Drop it.
- There. - Goodness. Pick it up!
It's over. He's not running.
The scene hasn't exactly changed.
- Seriously? - This shouldn't count.
But that was the case for us.
He'll now run while enjoying the scenery.
- That's right. - He'll enjoy the wind.
He greets the people in the neighborhood.
How long was "The Chaser" again?
A minute and 33 seconds.
It's almost over. He's at the finish line!
- He's almost there. - Run past the finish line!
I see the finish line.
Run a little more!
- Please cut it short. - Please.
Even I'm rooting for Cho Seung Woo now.
(It's almost at a minute and 30 seconds.)
It's easier to run in the rain.
(A minute and 30 seconds passed on "Marathon".)
He runs until he reaches the finish line.
How is this any fun if "Marathon" has the longest scene?
(Which team won?)
(He ran longer than the protagonist in "The Chaser".)
("Marathon" has the longest running scene.)
- No way. - This movie...
has the longest running scene at 4 minutes and 33 seconds.
But...
(The protagonist went on...)
(to run through...)
(a supermarket, a swimming pool, and a subway station.)
(Even a zebra joined him.)
(He crosses the finish line after 4 minutes and 33 seconds.)
I didn't choose it because I thought it was obvious.
So Min, Dong Il, and Jae Suk win a point each.
So here's the next question.
(Which line from the movie lasts the longest?)
("A Promise")
- This scene. - It's a long one.
- I cried during this scene. - Me too.
("Assassination")
Gosh, this one.
Go on and take a look.
Good one.
The line that follows?
(How long does his testimony go on for?)
("The Attorney")
(How long did the protagonist's line last?)
This is a hard choice.
Which of the following scenes...
takes the longest to wrap up?
(This is a tough one.)
Me too.
I think it's "The Attorney".
I think it's "Assassination".
"Assassination"?
Every actor has a different speed...
of which they speak in when delivering lines.
Song Kang Ho delivers his line quite fast...
and so does Park Shin Yang.
They spit out their lines.
- But it'll be only one page... - Right.
- Three... - It could be short.
- Two. - Hold on.
- What's up with you all? - What Dong Il said...
Hold on a second.
- I could be wrong, you know. - One.
Time's up. Your decision is final.
Just like last time, we'll start with the third movie.
Then it must not be the longest.
Are we starting with "The Attorney"?
- Yes. - Then it's not the longest.
- This is where it starts. - Right.
(He begins his dialogue.)
According to Article 1, Section 2 of the Constitution...
Kang Ho...
- His speech is fast. - Sovereignty resides in the people,
and all state authority shall emanate from the people.
The nation is its people!
(Just like Dong Il said...)
- He talks fast. - You're right.
- Right? - He talks fast.
It's what I noticed over the years.
Counsel is badgering the witness!
- Have you... - Counsel!
Is there more?
- Do you admit to torture? - No.
(His dialogue is over.)
- It ended. - That was 40 seconds.
It's short.
That can't be the longest dialogue.
- Please let it be "A Promise" next. - It has to be over a minute.
Here we go.
(The accused begins his dialogue.)
Six of them!
- There are six. - In 1912,
I was hit during the assassination of the governor.
See the two holes?
- Here we go. - I got this one in 1922...
and this one in 1927 in Khabarovsk.
He's talking quite fast. What's going on?
- It's fast. - You said he talks slowly.
- He does. - Let's keep watching.
We might have a chance.
(This speed might give us a chance.)
(The dialogue lasted 40 seconds in "The Attorney".)
Please.
- Okay! - There's more.
It's over.
You don't know...
what I felt when I lost all of them!
(His dialogue is longer than that from "The Attorney".)
You never know. He should talk some more.
Please keep going.
They'd fight to their deaths!
- Here it goes. - He slowed down.
(His speech finally slows down.)
- No, gosh, no. - Please, no.
- Say some more. - Come on!
- He'll turn around and keep going. - Go on!
Say your lines!
(If it ends here, it'll only be 58 seconds.)
Your Honor, please interrupt him.
(A minute isn't enough to guarantee their win.)
(Will the protagonist say more?)
(That's all.)
- He ended it. - 59 seconds.
(The dialogue ends at 59 seconds.)
("Assassination" is currently in 1st place.)
- It's shorter than I expected. - Exactly.
The speech in "A Promise" is very long.
(All that's left is "A Promise".)
Is it "A Promise" then?
(Park Shin Yang begins his lines.)
Here we go.
(She's already on the verge of tears.)
The background music isn't a good sign.
This will at least be a minute.
Only long lines get background music.
(The same happened in "Marathon".)
She's a fine doctor too.
- I think we've lost. - Already?
- He has a lot of lines left. - It's already been...
- Already... - I feel like we've already lost.
He didn't say much but 20 seconds passed.
How long of a break is he taking?
Gosh.
He stopped for five seconds after "I."
Go on with your line!
He's right.
- Oh, dear. - Oh, no.
He's not even at the climax.
No way.
He's still at this line.
Game over.
He's not even at his main line.
- If you... - If you...
(He begins the climax after 50 seconds.)
"If you ask what I did wrong..."
"If you ask me my sin..."
("Assassination" was 59 seconds.)
"If you ask me why..."
"All I did was love her."
- "All I did was love her." - "I loved her."
All I did was love her.
"I loved her."
(What's he doing?)
(It doesn't take much to go from a great actor to a fool.)
"My biggest sin is that I'm leaving her behind."
I'm getting sad all over again.
(Almost in tears)
- Game over. - Just so you know,
his lines continue until a minute and 52 seconds.
(So Min and Ji Hyo win a point each.)
Hit someone from the second team.
Did only you two win points?
- Ji Hyo? - I'll...
- Bae Seong Woo? - I'll hit his behind.
(She choose to hit Bae Seong Woo's behind.)
Seong Woo's bottom naturally sticks out,
so it already provides a lot of cushion.
See? Look at that.
He has great posture.
Swing up from the bottom.
- Like this? - Don't aim too low though.
- What? - Hold on.
Too low?
(Don't aim too low though.)
- Too low? - It'll be a disaster.
- Well... - If you do...
He'll have to sing the national anthem.
(The national anthem...)
- One... - Look at him.
Why did you suddenly tuck in your tailbone?
- Stick it out like before. - But that's not my bottom.
Is that why?
She'll hit your bottom anyway.
There you go. Be a man.
Let's do this.
(He tries to focus but fails.)
(Smack)
(The sound was quite loud.)
His bottom beat the squeaky hammer.
- The hammer bounced off his bottom. - His bottom...
Why didn't it squeak?
- It just bounced off his bottom. - That's incredible.
You guys do it. I already hit Kwang Soo.
- I'm done. - Suk Jin, you can do it.
Jae Suk, come here.
- Jae Suk. Good. - I'll flick his forehead.
Suk Jin's flick is really strong.
- You can't hold my head. - I won't.
(Suk Jin gets ready to flick, frowning.)
(With this flick,)
(I'll teach you a lesson.)
(It's too weak.)
- Gosh. - He missed it.
- Oh, my. - You're too weak.
Suk Jin.
- He missed it. - But...
you have to do it again.
I saw it.
But you have to do it again.
When Suk Jin was flicking his forehead,
- Jae Suk moved forward. - No.
- You can't do that. - I didn't.
If you let me flick you, I'll let you flick me again.
What are you talking about?
You're being ridiculous.
- Suk Jin, let me flick you. - That doesn't make sense.
Okay, try it.
Are you letting him flick you?
For him to flick me, I should flick him too.
That sounds surprisingly convincing.
(It's surprisingly convincing.)
Your nose or forehead?
- Eyes... - Nose is better.
Nose is better.
Nose is better, definitely.
- I'll flick your nose too. - Okay.
- Take off your glasses. - It's better on the nose?
His nose must be heavy.
- I'll catch it over here. - Okay.
Just in case.
- I can't wait. - But...
This is fair, right?
(Flicked)
(His nose swings.)
(Shocked)
(Angry)
That really hurts.
Like when you ate horseradish.
(Is he okay?)
Let me take your glasses.
- Come here. - Aim well.
Take off your glasses.
I want to flick your mouth.
All right.
(It's too weak again.)
(Suk Jin missed it.)
He missed it.
What's wrong?
(In addition to his punch, his flick is weak too.)
- Did he miss it? - Suk Jin.
Let Jae Suk flick you again.
- What's with you? - That was so close.
Seriously.
- I'm so angry. - Let's do it again.
You have to flick him properly once.
(Is that really necessary?)
(He's flicked again.)
(It's strong.)
(The sound was unbelievably loud.)
(Is this really necessary on a variety show?)
(It's time for Suk Jin to take revenge.)
- It hurts just watching it. - It has to be at least that strong.
- This is annoying. - It has to be.
This is your last chance.
Right.
(He won't get any more chances.)
(This is the last chance he has.)
(Will Suk Jin be able to take revenge?)
(Flick)
(It was a proper flick this time.)
(It sounded like the clang of a bell.)
(Everyone congratulates Suk Jin.)
It hurt a lot, right?
(Unbelievable)
That was nice.
- It was proper. - It was.
It was proper.
His nose went around and hit his ear.
All right. Four people survived.
The four of them will play rock-paper-scissors...
to decide 1st and 2nd places.
(They play rock-paper-scissors to decide 1st place.)
(Ji Hyo wins.)
Ji Hyo.
I keep losing at rock-paper-scissors today.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min wins.)
(So Min gets to pick the hint she wants.)
- Let's sit down. - Okay.
Let's just sit down.
(Dong Il wraps up the situation.)
First place, come here.
(Ji Hyo receives a hint first.)
(The hint is about the brother deities.)
(The brother deities are not in their 20s.)
(Moments before...)
(The hint given after the meal mission said...)
(the deities are brother and sister.)
(Among the 4 female candidates, those not in their 20s are...)
(So Min and Ji Hyo.)
That hint is about the other two deities, right?
Exactly.
Poseidon and Zeus.
(Now, Ji Hyo will receive a hint about Hades.)
(Hades is not in his or her 20s.)
(Yi Hyun and Hye Jun are excluded.)
Do you want a hint about Zeus and Poseidon...
or about Hades?
(So Min, in 2nd place, can choose the hint she wants.)
Hades can actually be one of us.
What do you mean?
- Among those who get a hint. - Among us?
(If So Min is Hades, she'd choose a hint about the brother deities.)
(But she chose a hint about Hades.)
Did it give you any ideas? Was it too general?
No, it wasn't that general.
It actually gave me an idea.
- It's not general? - Not much.
We'll begin the race now,
during which, you'll have to protect Zeus and Poseidon...
and eliminate Hades for good.
It's called The Otherworld.
(Final Mission: The Otherworld)
The race will take place...
at a place filled with spirits Hades brought from the Otherworld.
(The place is filled with spirits Hades brought from the Otherworld.)
(Welcome to the Otherworld.)
What is this?
Hidden in that building are hints about Hades,
the brother deities,
and how to eliminate...
Hades.
We have to find them?
Before Hades eliminate Zeus and Poseidon,
find and eliminate Hades, and Team Human will win.
But if Hades eliminate his or her brothers first,
Hades will win alone.
- Are we playing individually? - Alone?
Also, there's a special photo studio in the Otherworld.
(The Otherworld has a special photo studio.)
The photo studio opens at certain times.
The two who find the tickets can choose a person...
of their choice to enter the studio.
When the four of them take a photo together,
depending on whether the photo includes the brothers or Hades,
- the photo will look different. - That's creepy.
Photos with the brother deities in them will look bright.
Photos with Hades in them will look dark.
If both the brothers and Hades are in the same picture,
the people in the photo will look hairy.
(Hairy?)
- They'll look hairy. - All right.
Move to your positions,
- and the final race will start. - Let's go!
(They enter Hades' Otherworld.)
This is creepy.
I'm stressed out.
Give me a second. I'm too scared.
(How am I going to go in?)
(She notices something.)
(An ugly toad ghost?)
(They don't care about Hades anymore.)
What is this?
(Everyone is on edge.)
- What is this? - Lee Kwang Soo.
(There's no one else in the hallway, but someone calls his name.)
Haha.
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Gosh.
(Lee Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo swears at Se Chan.)
- Sorry. - Why are you so scared?
- Sorry. - I just called your name.
- I thought we've started. - Not yet.
(The toad ghost disappears.)
(It's a frog ghost this time.)
When others make that sound, they really sound like ghosts.
But when So Min does it,
she sounds like a crazy person.
It's even scarier.
He's saying something bad about me.
He is, right?
I think Hades...
(Hades is still veiled in mystery.)
It's either Kwang Soo...
or Dong Il.
(Suk Jin thinks it's either Kwang Soo or Dong Il.)
Dong Il keeps pretending...
he doesn't know the rules.
It's a little unnatural.
Seong Woo is a little suspicious.
Something about him doesn't feel right.
(Something about him doesn't feel right.)
I think it's Seong Woo.
(Seong Woo is suspect number 3 for Hades.)
It's either Dong Il or Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk is also being suspected to be Hades.)
I don't care about Hades. This is way too creepy.
Gosh, this is not good.
It's driving me crazy.
All right.
I'm Poseidon.
So I can do this.
(What? Is Ji Hyo Poseidon?)
(Right before today's shoot)
You two are deities disguised as humans.
(You two are deities disguised as humans.)
Ji Hyo, you are Poseidon, the deity of the sea.
(Ji Hyo is Poseidon, who works with Zeus to find Hades.)
I have too many candidates for Hades.
Dong Il, Seong Woo,
Jae Suk, and Kwang Soo.
(Dong Il, Seong Woo, Jae Suk, Kwang Soo)
This is driving me crazy.
(Who on earth is Hades?)
Five,
four,
three,
two.
The race starts.
(The race starts.)
(In this place are the hints that will be the key of this race.)
(However,)
(no one is coming out.)
This place is so red.
(Ji Hyo is Poseidon, a target of Hades.)
My goodness.
(She gathers up her courage and begins to look for the hints.)
Gosh, I really don't want to go in.
(This place definitely looks haunted.)
I really don't want to go in.
(Bang)
(Tiny bang sounds are enough to make her scared.)
Is this how it's going to be?
(Why is she scolding the cameraman?)
(She approaches the suspicious well.)
(She gets startled by herself.)
What?
(Is there a ghost inside?)
(The is a ghost over here.)
(Screaming)
(Running)
(The deity of the sea gets scared very easily.)
I might die...
before I catch Hades.
(Another coward is on the search.)
My goodness.
I know you are going to get up.
Hurry up and get up.
(It's a strange night-duty room.)
(There is a suspicious cabinet...)
(and an even more suspicious looking security guard.)
(I will stay far from that man.)
(Shouting)
Dong Il.
(It's me.)
Gosh!
(Screaming)
(Please save me.)
(What did So Min see inside the cabinet?)
Dong Il, look at that.
That was so scary.
(Crying)
Dong Il, look at that.
I was so startled.
This is too much.
This is...
(Screaming)
(How can I help you?)
(He is excited by So Min's reaction.)
I was so startled.
I guess these days...
- I was so scared. - ghosts carry cellphones.
(Embarrassed)
Your eyes must hurt.
Hold on.
- There must be an envelope. - I don't think it's here.
This isn't the room.
I don't think it's here.
(Where are the hints on Hades?)
My goodness.
(This person is busy looking for the hints.)
(Hye Jun looks around and opens the door carefully.)
(There are various items scattered around the room.)
(She enters cautiously to find a hint.)
(She reckons there is a hint inside a box.)
(She opens all the boxes in the room.)
(Peek-a-boo)
(Don't touch my boxes.)
(She forgets about the hints...)
(and runs away.)
I am so scared.
(Her legs give out.)
(She collects herself.)
Hold on.
Did she go back inside?
(There is one box she hasn't opened yet.)
Don't come out.
Excuse me.
(She enters the room again to check the last box.)
The hint...
(Peek-a-boo)
(She gets the box.)
(I found a hint.)
(She almost fell by in her attempt to tease the ghost.)
(Be careful.)
(She leaves the room happily after receiving a hint.)
(Which hint did Hye Jun receive after the struggle?)
(Hades uses his or her own name.)
(The hint rules out Haha since he doesn't use his own name.)
It rules out Haha.
(Seven candidates for Hades remain.)
We need to enter every room, right?
(He is touring every room.)
It's scary in a strange way.
(He approaches the cabinet with his eyes on the ghost.)
For goodness' sake.
(He pretends to be strong as he runs away.)
Someone is in here.
(Who was startled just now?)
Was that you, Seong Woo?
My goodness.
- Hold on. - There was a loud bang.
(He pretends to be calm.)
A hint must be where the ghost is.
That's how it usually is.
(Ji Hyo goes towards the ghost instead of Seong Woo.)
This is driving me crazy.
(What?)
(She finds a hint near the ghost like Jong Kook said.)
Did you find something?
Let's go.
Seong Woo is a fool.
I think...
(He gets startled by the door.)
(He is playing by himself as he searches the room.)
- Let's see it. - Jong Kook.
(The hint they found behind Seong Woo's back says,)
(Hades is a man.)
(The hint rules out So Min from the candidates for Hades.)
The ghosts in this room...
aren't very scary.
I guess we should jump rope.
(Two ghosts are turning the rope.)
Do we jump rope?
I guess we should do this.
- Go, Se Chan. - You should go first.
How many times should I jump?
Go.
Go and jump rope.
(Se Chan tries jump roping.)
(Little child, little child, turn around)
Turn around.
Turn around, turn around, and touch the ground
Touch the ground, touch the ground
Put your arms up
Put your arms up, put your arms up, and leave
- Leave. - He did it.
(Se Chan did as the ghosts asked.)
- It's a hint. - He gets a hint.
(It's a hint!)
Come here. Bring it over here.
We are a team.
(Se Chan checks the hint first.)
(What is this?)
(Why is he so startled?)
Share it with us. Don't be like that.
(He shares the hint with the other cowards.)
What is this?
(If you are a deity, beware of April 5.)
(It's a hint about all 3 deities.)
- April fifth? - What is it?
- What is it? - Is it someone's birthday?
- It's someone's birthday, right? - No, no. April fifth is...
- Arbor Day. - Arbor Day.
It's when you plant trees.
(A deity should beware of Arbor day?)
What about Arbor Day?
When is Dong Il's birthday?
I think it's in April.
The red light must indicate something.
I think there is something inside the room.
- This room? - What should we do?
What should we do?
- My goodness. - This room...
It's a station for a bus that goes to the Otherworld.
(The Grim Reaper waits at the bus station.)
(Otherworld, Human World, Heavens)
- What? - Lee Kwang Soo.
Song Ji Hyo.
- He called your name. - Why me?
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Why did he call my name?)
To the Otherworld.
- My goodness. - Seong Woo.
(As soon as the Grim Reaper finishes talking...)
(Is that another Grim Reaper?)
I just followed the crowd.
Seong Woo, are you carrying that arm as a weapon?
It puts my heart at ease.
There must be a hint inside the bus.
(There must be a hint inside the bus.)
- Seong Woo. - Jong Kook, there might be a hint.
(Ji Hyo suddenly comes over.)
(Swiping)
(While Seong Woo is focused on the bus,)
(she gets a hint from the Grim Reaper.)
There's nothing here.
(Seong Woo doesn't realize that Ji Hyo found a hint.)
(He focuses on the bus.)
He is still looking for a hint.
(He is so funny.)
He's the first to enter and the first to search the room,
but he still can't find a hint.
He can't find a hint.
Why is he so clueless?
Seong Woo.
(He walks towards Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.)
Is this a hint?
Let's go.
- What should we do? - "Information Protection Act".
"Entry number 12,504".
(This can't be about Hades.)
Where are the hints?
(He finds a bag this time.)
This must be it.
(It's a staff member's sock.)
(I was wrong.)
(The hint they found behind Seong Woo's back says...)
Those are Chinese words...
- for "Human" and "10". - 10?
(If you are a deity, beware of 'Human' plus '10'.)
(What does the hint that starts with "If you are a deity" mean?)
(Haha has been ruled out from the candidates for Hades.)
I am sorry.
(He leaves the 3 cowards and looks for the hints by himself.)
It's here.
(He finds a hint.)
Thank you.
Leave!
(The ghost is annoyed.)
(He calms his heart and checks the hint again.)
(Find Hades' 'Blank' chair, put a deity's name tag on it,)
(and burn it to eliminate that deity.)
"Find Hades' 'Blank' chair, put a deity's name tag on it..."
(Do they need to find Hades' "Blank" chair?)
This is...
(What could be the thing Ji Hyo, a deity, should beware of?)
What is April fifth?
April fifth is Arbor Day.
(Confused)
(Then what do other hints mean?)
Right?
April fifth is Arbor Day.
(If you are a deity, beware of April 5th.)
(If you are a deity, beware of 'Human' plus '10'.)
(Jong Kook knows the two hints that go, "If you are a deity...")
This is driving me crazy. Hold on.
"Beware of April fifth."
(He begins to solve the meaning of April 5th.)
April?
(Did Jong Kook figure it out?)
(April 5)
Arbor Day. It equals "Wood".
(Arbor Day, Wood)
(Wood)
(Wooden)
What should I do now?
(That's why the deities should beware of wooden chairs.)
"Find Hades' 'Blank' chair, put a deity's name tag on it..."
(Putting a deity's name tag on Hades' wooden chair...)
(and burning it eliminates the deity.)
(Haha figured out how to eliminate a deity.)
(He shares the information with other members.)
That's incredible.
"Hades' wooden chair".
"Burn it to eliminate that deity."
Where did you find these hints?
My goodness.
(Find Hades' wooden chair and the incinerator.)
We need to find the wooden chair.
These aren't wooden chairs.
(There are too many wooden chairs inside the building.)
No way.
(Which one is Hades' wooden chair?)
- Isn't that the incinerator? - Gosh, you startled me.
Maybe we have to take the chair over there.
Wait. We need to find a wooden chair we can stick a name tag on.
(Put Hades' name tag on the chair and burn it to eliminate Hades.)
Since we need to burn it, the chair won't be that big.
(After sharing the hints,)
(Haha begins to look for Hades' chair.)
(At that moment,)
(someone quietly chases after Haha.)
(When he looks back, it's too late!)
What? What?
(Ripping)
Hades?
A human, Haha, is out.
(A human, Haha, is out.)
(Is Haha out?)
What?
No way. I promised to protect him.
Haha is out.
- Haha? - Yes.
Haha knows too much.
- Hold on. - Who took him out?
(Who could be Hades, the deity who eliminated Haha?)
There must be something in here.
(Hades' identity is still a mystery.)
(The candidates for Hades meet during their search for hints.)
Gosh, that startled me.
What is this?
(Everything is upside down in this room.)
I am reminded of a movie I was in.
There must be something in here.
(Crouching)
For goodness' sake.
(That startled me.)
(Thanks to Seong Woo's prank, he finds a hint.)
You need to share that.
Let me read it first.
If this is a hint about Poseidon or Zeus...
You might be Hades.
(Find Hades' 'Blank' chair, put a deity's name tag on it,)
(and burn it to eliminate that deity.)
What is it?
(Kwang Soo figured out how to eliminate a deity.)
This is a useful one.
I showed you a useful one earlier!
- Hey! - This is...
You don't know much about the rules of Running Man, right?
I will share them with you.
(He says it to Kwang Soo.)
(He is the one who is visiting Running Man for the first time.)
- I have done this for 10 years. - All right. I was joking.
What's the hint?
(Pressuring)
- Come on. - Hades'...
(Hades'...)
A pause means...
- You are lying. - you are making things up.
- Hades' name tag must be removed. - What?
Hades' name tag must be removed.
They said it's not about taking name tags.
Yes, it is.
They said it's not about that.
Are you saying the production crew lied to me?
Hades'...
(Kwang Soo is flustered.)
- Come here. - Come here.
(They explode.)
(Are you going to keep lying?)
- I am telling the truth. - You will be filming...
a movie with me, right?
We will also work together for "The Accidental Detective".
I will tell you.
Hades supposedly has a wooden chair.
- What? - Hades' chair.
Chair.
We need to find that chair.
- Is that the hint? - We need to put...
Hades' name tag...
on that chair.
We can put a name tag on that chair, right?
- That's right. - Then it must be made of velcro.
(Upon learning how to eliminate Hades,)
(Seong Woo suddenly heads somewhere.)
(The room Seong Woo entered upon learning the hint is...)
(the room of dolls with Annabelle.)
Do you want to play a game with me?
Yes.
Really? Press the doorbell.
If the door opens, you lose.
You can press once or many times.
It's a game of chance anyway.
- I will go first. - Sure.
(Seong Woo goes first.)
(Ringing)
(The door of the haunted house opens.)
I lost.
Yes.
(Since Seong Woo won,)
(Annabelle gives him a gift.)
Pick one.
(There are members' name tags on the tray.)
(It's a chance to obtain a name tag without ripping it off the person.)
(Put a deity's name tag on the chair and burn it...)
(to take the deity out.)
(Find Hades' 'Blank' chair, put a deity's name tag on it,)
(and burn it to eliminate that deity.)
(Which name tag will Seong Woo choose?)
(After much consideration,)
(he picks Jong Kook's name tag.)
Can I take a look at them?
(He wants to take a look at the name tags.)
Please let me take a look.
Came back in 10 minutes.
10 minutes?
(Stealing)
(He steals in front of the ghost.)
(Grabbing)
I will come back in 10 minutes.
(He steals a second name tag while distracting the ghost.)
Seong Woo.
Put down the name tags.
(Put down the name tags.)
(He returns the two name tags.)
I will come back.
(He leaves the room with one name tag.)
(Hesitant)
(The lobby is empty...)
(except for someone who is moving suspiciously.)
(Who is that?)
(It's Dong Il!)
(He approaches someone without a word.)
(He surprises a ghost that was hiding.)
(Dong Il isn't afraid of ghosts.)
(What is Dong Il doing?)
(It's the side effect of a scary experience.)
(A human turns into a ghost.)
(Jae Suk didn't find many hints.)
What is this?
(In front of the keys,)
(he finds a hint!)
(Zeus has a 4 in his or her birthday.)
(Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, Dong Il, Jong Kook, and So Min)
(One of them is Zeus!)
(Jae Suk is the first person to find a hint about Zeus.)
(The race ends if Hades eliminates Zeus and Poseidon.)
(What?)
(He finds Dong Il, a candidate for Zeus.)
(Soon after Dong Il enters the room,)
(Jae Suk enters the same room.)
(Ripping)
(What?)
A human, Sung Dong Il, is out.
Really?
(Dong Il is out?)
A human?
A human, Sung Dong Il, is out.
Okay.
(Seong Woo heads somewhere upon hearing the news.)
Is this for real?
- Seong Woo, where have you been? - Seong Woo.
I was going to revisit Annabelle's room.
I am fairly certain Hades is 1 of the 3.
Who?
(Who does he think Hades is?)
It's not Dong Il.
- Why not? - Did you find a hint?
He passed away just now.
- What? - What?
(Dong Il passed away just now.)
- Is he out? - Oh, is "out" the proper term?
What?
(He is out.)
- I was so startled! - Seong Woo!
- I am sorry. - I was so startled!
- That came out wrong. - I almost cried.
You can't say something like that about people...
like Dong Il and Suk Jin.
I wouldn't like it either.
- I was so startled. - I am sorry.
What are you?
- What are you? - What?
He is... Excuse me. You should sit down.
(The security ghost is standing inside a small cabinet.)
I am sorry. All along...
Should I shut the door? What should I do?
- Maybe I should shut the door. - Then he will be too hot.
- He will be too hot. - What should I do?
- Please sit here. - Come on out.
- All of us have seen you. - Please sit here.
I was so surprised.
- He was still doing that. - Please sit here.
- It's okay. - He is like a mannequin.
It's okay.
- It's really okay. - You should take a break.
Gosh, I had no idea.
Please lie down straight. You don't need to do that.
(Please lie down straight.)
- Please lie down straight. - You don't need to do that.
- Take a break. - He must be hot.
- It must have been hard. - Lie down.
- Seriously. - That's right.
I am sorry. We were so absorbed in the conversation.
Everyone, please pause.
(Everyone, please pause.)
(What is going on?)
Pause?
The photo studio is open.
(The photo studio is open.)
(The photo studio is finally open.)
(There is a special photo studio in the Otherworld?)
(The photo studio will open at when the time is right.)
(The 2 people who find the ticket can choose 1 other person each...)
(and enter the photo studio. Four people can enter.)
(When the 4 people get their photo taken,)
(it will look bright if one brother deity is among them.)
(The photo with Hades will look dark.)
(If both Hades and a brother deity are in the photo,)
(the people in the photo will look hairy.)
(Photo Studio)
Only those with the tickets can enter.
For goodness' sake.
Who found the tickets?
(Who found the tickets?)
I don't have a ticket.
Who has a ticket?
- Who has a ticket? - I will choose a person.
- Do you have a ticket? - Do you have a ticket?
- Do you have a ticket? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo has 1 ticket.)
(He was looking for a hint in the hallway earlier...)
(when he came across a ticket.)
You need to include a human.
Include me since I'm human.
- I'm definitely human. - Seong Woo.
How about this? Seong Woo is definitely coming.
I'll go with Seong Woo...
and two humans.
Two humans?
You can only take one person.
Aren't there four people?
- Someone else found the ticket. - Really?
I can take one person. I'll go with Seong Woo.
(He picks Seong Woo who's a candidate for Hades.)
- Seong Woo. I should watch. - Okay. Right.
- Bae Seong Woo. - Yes?
Someone who has a photo printing ticket picked you.
- Really? Okay. - Please go to the photo studio.
It'll be creepy if it's really him.
(He picks Seong Woo to go with to the photo studio.)
- Jae Suk, you have been called. - Really?
(Jae Suk is chosen to go to the photo studio.)
(Who picked Jae Suk?)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes, Jae Suk?
- Did you call me? - No.
(Jae Suk arrives without knowing why.)
Who called me?
I don't know who.
- I'll go inside first. - Go ahead.
(Who picked Jae Suk?)
This is great.
(3 people enter the photo studio.)
- You came. - What?
I called you.
Did you call me?
(The one who called Jae Suk is...)
I called you, Jae Suk.
(A moment ago in the ghost room)
(He obtains a photo printing ticket.)
People are suspicious of him.
I'll take Jae Suk with me.
(He picks Jae Suk, a candidate for Hades.)
- Okay. - Let me tell you again.
If one of you is a brother deity, the photo will turn bright.
If one of you is Hades, the photo will turn dark.
If Hades and brother deities are among you,
- you'll have beards in your photo. - Okay.
- If there's a brother deity? - If there is at least once,
Here we go. Smile.
1, 2, 3.
(The photo of these 4)
(How will it turn out?)
Okay.
(An important hint will be given in their photo.)
Please wait for the result.
- It'll be an important hint. - Definitely.
- Overall, - Definitely.
all of us are men.
- Right. - We're all candidates.
- All four of us are candidates. - Right.
- Your photo is printed. - Okay.
(Your photo is printed.)
- Please take it. - Okay.
- Check it. - This is very...
- crucial hint. - Let's see.
We just have to flip it.
This is crucial.
(Members are surprised by the photo.)
(What kind of photo is it?)
(They have beards in the photo.)
(Beards means Hades and brother deities are among them.)
Wait, wait a minute.
(Hades and Zeus are among them.)
Wait.
- Is everyone here? - Everyone is here.
(Zeus and Hades exist among the 4 of them.)
- Hades and... - There are Hades and Zeus.
It's either Zeus or Poseidon.
One of them is a woman.
(Candidates for Hades and Zeus are narrowed down.)
We...
The people who need to be here are here.
- We shouldn't move. Wait. - The person who's left...
- Why? - Okay, I have to go.
- Wait. - Jae Suk, why are you leaving?
- Okay, I'm leaving. - Wait.
Jae Suk, why are you leaving?
- I have to go. - Wait.
- Wait. - What's wrong?
- Do you have something to do? - Wait, listen.
- It's dangerous here. - Wait, listen.
Isn't everyone here?
- Let me talk. - It's dangerous.
- I can't stay here. - Right?
- I am... - It's not what you think.
- I'm leaving. - Right here...
I'm leaving.
(Jae Suk leaves without analyzing.)
(What's wrong with him all of a sudden?)
Where are you going, Jae Suk?
(Is Jae Suk Hades?)
Where did he go? We found out everything.
Where is he going? Everyone is here.
It's so strange that he left.
(He acts suspicious.)
Hey.
- Hey. - What happened?
- He's out. - Did the photo come out?
- Which photo was it? - One of them is Hades.
- Really? - Who are inside?
I don't know yet.
- Who are inside? - Which photo was it?
- The one with beards. - In that case...
- there are also deities. - There are also deities.
- I told you. - Hold on.
Come here for a minute.
(He gathers the members carefully.)
I'm Zeus.
(I'm Zeus.)
- Really? - I'm Zeus.
- In that case... - Really?
She thinks Jong Kook is Zeus.
(Yi Hyun thinks that Jong Kook is Zeus.)
(Is Jong Kook Zeus?)
Why?
He told me himself.
Someone also told me.
(Both Jae Suk and Jong Kook claim that they're Zeus.)
They told me to keep it a secret.
I'm Zeus.
Jong Kook is Hades.
(Jong Kook is Hades.)
I think Jong Kook is Hades.
(Is Jong Kook Hades all of a sudden?)
(As rumors say, is Jong Kook Zeus?)
- I think Jong Kook is Hades. - What?
- I have a feeling. - Then...
- it's confusing again. - I suspected Seong Woo.
- Me too. - Me too.
Suddenly, Jong Wook said...
- Hades found out about the chair? - Be quiet.
How would he know right now?
What did it mean?
They gathered around.
Wait, be quiet.
Wait, so he's saying he's Zeus?
Don't tell them.
(Who is telling the truth?)
(Jae Suk moves quickly to the doll room.)
Hello, aren't you tired?
Can we do it again?
(By playing the haunted room game,)
(he obtains Jong Kook's name tag.)
I'll take Jong Kook's.
- Thank you. - Bye.
Bye. I'm Zeus.
(Jae Suk claims that he's Zeus. Who is he?)
So Min, did you go to the photo room?
No, but I heard that it's the photo with beards.
(Ji Hyo hears about the hint later.)
Ji Hyo.
We took a photo.
(Jong Kook shares the hint directly with Ji Hyo.)
It was the one with beards.
- Who was inside? - Here's the photo.
- Come here, Ji Hyo. - I told you already.
Four people.
It was the photo with beards, and I was one of them.
It's one of the three.
- Is it one of the three? - Yes.
You aren't it, are you?
- No. - You aren't.
- You aren't it. - You found out everything about me.
- I'm not it. - We could tell them.
- Can't we tell them? - We can.
We can tell them now.
(What do they want to tell us?)
Jae Suk claims that he's Zeus.
He said that he's Zeus.
Jae Suk did?
What were the hints again?
- Jae Suk said that he's Zeus? - He told me.
Then it's him.
- Suk Jin believes him. - Jae Suk?
Be quiet. Don't tell anyone.
I'm Poseidon.
- Are you Zeus? - Yes.
(If Ji Hyo is Poseidon)
- We got the mission this morning. - We did.
(We got the mission this morning.)
(If they received the mission together...)
Today's Metamorphosis Race will have deities disguised as humans.
The two of you are the deities who are disguised as humans.
Have you heard of Zeus, Poseidon, and Hades from...
- Greek and Roman mythology? - Yes.
Kicked out to the underworld, Hades became vengeful.
To take Zeus and Poseidon to the underworld with him,
he's is hiding as a human.
To make Hades return to the underworld,
Zeus and Poseidon are also disguised as humans.
Is she Poseidon?
Am I Zeus, and is he Poseidon?
Ji Hyo, you're Poseidon, the deity of the sea.
Okay.
You're Poseidon. How dare you try to be Zeus?
- Two of you are deities. - Okay.
If the brother deities find Hades and eliminate him first,
Team Deity and Human win.
If Hades finds Zeus and Poseidon...
and eliminates the brother deities first,
- Hades will win. - Okay.
(Two deities heard the rules in advance.)
No wonder I thought you two made a good couple today.
I thought you two made a good couple today.
Then is it Jae Suk?
(Is Jae Suk Hades?)
(Jae Suk has been watching everything.)
We have to kill Hades now.
We should get the name tag...
from Annabelle's room.
(Jae Suk claimed to be Zeus. Is he Hades?)
- Let's go and take it. - Okay.
Goodness.
I now know who Poseidon is.
(Ji Hyo heads to the doll room to find Hades' name tag.)
(At that moment)
(Jae Suk follows Ji Hyo and enters the room.)
(Screaming)
(Tearing)
Ji Hyo, who is Poseidon,
was eliminated a moment ago.
Ji Hyo, who is Poseidon was eliminated a moment ago.
Who is it?
- Ji Hyo just left a moment ago. - What?
- Jae Suk. - We can't tell you when it was.
Did Jae Suk...
(Was it Jae Suk who eliminated Ji Hyo?)
(Is Jae Suk Hades?)
Did you find the name tag?
You mean Jae Suk's?
- Who? - Jae Suk's.
(Jae Suk's name tag)
- Did you find the wooden chair? - Wooden chair?
- What? - Did you find the wooden chair?
- No. - We have to find it.
We have to find the chair.
- Right. - The chair.
(To eliminate Hades, they must find his wooden chair.)
Hades?
Does it say it's Hades' chair?
(There are many chairs in the building.)
No way.
How can we find it when there are so many chairs?
(Which one is Hades' wooden chair?)
Goodness.
(At that time,)
(Kwang Soo spots a suspicious-looking chair.)
(Burn Hades' chair with the name tag of a deity to eliminate that deity.)
(There's a label on the chair.)
Is this a wooden chair?
Is this it?
(It's Hades' wooden chair.)
(All he has to do is find Hades' name tag.)
Is this the chair?
This one has to be it.
- Jong Kook, isn't this it? - What?
This one has to it.
It's also the right size.
That's not it.
- That's not it. - I don't think that's it.
Isn't this it?
What are you going to do?
(Jae Suk appears.)
This is the chair.
(This is Hades' wooden chair.)
(Jae Suk approaches Hades' wooden chair.)
Who is Hades?
- I don't think that's it. - I think this is it.
Who do you think it is? Isn't it Jong Kook?
(Isn't it Jong Kook?)
(Is Jong Kook Hades?)
I think so.
I thought about it carefully.
(Moments ago, Jae Suk left the photo studio quickly.)
I thought it was Seong Woo.
(They're narrowing down candidates for Hades.)
Wait.
Seong Woo doesn't know anything.
(Kwang Soo hears Jae Suk by chance.)
(Jae Suk was narrowing down candidates for Hades.)
Hey, you aren't it, are you?
You aren't Hades.
Of course not.
Since you're saying that, you aren't Hades.
Come here, Kwang Soo.
Hurry, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
Hurry.
(It's not clear who Hades is.)
- Hurry, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
We need to stop him now.
- Let's take this. - Seriously. Come here.
I'm telling the truth. Come now.
See? He's burning it.
Come here now.
- Is it him? - Come here now.
Is it him?
Kwang Soo!
(Jong Kook tries to stop Kwang Soo.)
Seriously.
No.
Put it in here right now.
(Who is the real Hades?)
(It goes into the fire.)
Did you put a name tag on? Did you put mine?
- Jae Suk put it on. - Did you put the name on?
Jong Kook.
- I don't think it's him. - Isn't it him?
- It isn't him. - Is that the right chair?
- That's not the right chair. - It is.
That chair is Hades' chair.
Is that right?
- That's the right chair? - Is this the chair?
(It is Hades' wooden chair.)
Goodness.
Jong Kook is...
(The race result changes depending on who Jong Kook is.)
(Who is Jong Kook?)
Jong Kook is...
(He is...)
Hades.
(Unbelievable)
(The real Hades is Jong Kook.)
You brat.
- Why you... - Goodness.
Jong Kook, you're one of the three deities.
You're Hades, the deity of the underworld.
(It suits him somehow.)
The deity of the underworld suits me.
When the guests arrive,
it'll be an unfair fight of 1 against 11.
Right.
That's why we'll give you an advantage.
One of the brother deities who is after Hades is...
Poseidon, and it's Ji Hyo.
(He's given who Poseidon is.)
We will share this with you.
It's Ji Hyo.
Since you're Hades,
you cannot lie to anyone that you're Zeus.
(He's not allowed to lie about being Zeus.)
I understand. Leave it up to me.
- Please do well. - Okay.
You know why we called you separately, right?
Yes, can you not make us do things like this?
Please I beg you.
- To do it with her... - It makes me uncomfortable.
Two of you are deities disguised as humans.
- What? - Okay.
Is she Poseidon?
- Am I Zeus, and is he Poseidon? - Is Ji Hyo Poseidon?
Ji Hyo, you're Poseidon, the deity of the sea.
Okay, you're Poseidon.
How dare you try to be Zeus?
- Two of you are deities. - Okay.
(Jong Kook finishes the shoot after fooling Ji Hyo completely.)
- We got the mission this morning. - We did.
(Jong Kook's acting fooled everyone.)
(Haha was the first to figure out how to eliminate deities.)
(Tearing)
(Haha is eliminated.)
You're Hades.
(Tearing)
(Dong Il is also eliminated.)
I'm sorry.
(He was a candidate for Zeus.)
Let's see. Come here.
Come here.
"Zeus was born on an even number day."
(Zeus was born on an even number day.)
(Jong Kook isn't included.)
- What? - Wait.
Is it a hint for Zeus?
(Tearing)
(Jong Kook eliminates Ji Hyo.)
What?
(What's this?)
(Completely fooled Ji Hyo is eliminated.)
It has to be Jae Suk after seeing this.
The winners of the summer special Metamorphosis Race...
are Team Brother Deities and Team Human.
(Team Brother Deities and Team Human are final winners.)
It could be have been dangerous.
- I'm glad that we won. - By the way...
Zeus.
(She's ashamed.)
- We won. - Poseidon.
- Zeus. - Poseidon.
You worked so closely with Jong Kook.
She thought that I was Zeus.
- It couldn't be helped. - The two of them stayed together.
I know.
To Team Brother Deities and Team Human who won the race,
we'll give high-quality nutritional supplements to fight the summer.
Nutritional supplements? I like them.
It's Vitamin C.
(Thank you.)
Please tell us what you thought.
It was very thrilling.
It was a good game.
You don't know the rules.
I saw many ghosts.
I'll keep it as a good memory.
Thank you for the nutritional supplements.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We thank our guests and all the ghosts.)
(Members are desperately looking for one person.)
(Father)
(Emergency money of 6,000 dollars disappeared.)
(Father took the family's emergency money.)
(The children are angry at their father who is in hiding.)
Okay, I don't know.
(It's war.)
(Disappeared Emergency Money Race starts.)
(Members on the suspect list)
(A mystery that awaits the members)
What kind of riddle is this?
(Deciphering the mystery is not easy.)
(Who is the father in hiding?)
(Find the Father)