(The biting wind makes the day
feel like a winter day.)
(Due to the sudden strong wind,
they can't do the opening outdoors.)
(They head indoors
to avoid the wind.)
- It's gotten very cold.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Is this a subway station?
- Hi.
- The subway runs here?
- My gosh.
"Wolmi Sea Station".
It must be a new subway station.
- I guess we're going to get on it.
- Is this a real subway station?
This isn't the subway.
This is the Wolmi Sea Train.
- This is interesting.
- Sea Train?
- Yes.
- What's the Sea Train? Gosh.
(You can get on a monorail that goes
around Wolmi Island and the sea.)
This is a station.
There's good seafood here.
I don't have any pockets.
Hold my phone for me.
Sure.
I have to hold his phone now.
- Are you his secretary?
- He's using my pockets too.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Kwang Soo has pockets too.
Why did you ask him?
It's more comfortable to ask him.
- Jong Kook, how could you say that?
- Is that so?
- Don't be like that.
- What?
- He's uncomfortable with you now.
- Be nicer to him.
My phone might mess up
your outfit.
Your coat might droop down.
Nonsense. If it's yours,
I'll even put it in my underwear.
(Nonsense. If it's yours,
I'll even put it in my underwear.)
- Jong Kook.
- Why would he say that?
You feel closer to Se Chan
than Kwang Soo, right?
It's not that. It won't show
since he's wearing a mustang jacket.
- Kwang Soo was his go-to guy.
- Right.
- It's so disappointing. Se Chan...
- By the way,
to tell you the truth, he and
Jong Kook grew apart after 2017.
What?
(His detailed recollection
is groundless.)
- What? It's true.
- What happened two years ago?
My gosh.
- That's true.
I could even guess the timeline.
- That's not true.
- What?
Kwang Soo, aren't you disappointed?
Put this in.
What is this?
(I'm already upset as it is.)
(Throwing away his phone)
(What have I done wrong?)
What is he doing?
- He seemed disappointed.
- Great job.
Seriously. Oh, right.
Let's congratulate Kwang Soo.
- Why?
- He won an award.
- He won the Popularity Award.
- Right. I knew that.
- Popular Star Award.
The Chungjungone's
Popular Star Award goes to...
(He won the Popular Star Award
among countless actors.)
(Is this really happening?)
(This is all thanks to you guys.)
- It sounds like Chungjungone.
- "Chungjungone".
- Is it Chungjungone Award?
- It's the Popular Star Award.
- No.
Did they create a new award
named Gochujang Award?
- That's not the name.
- That's not it.
- Hey.
- So it's from Chungjungone, right?
- Right.
- Chungjungone and the film award...
- It's all...
- It's the Popular Star Award!
- You should...
(Exploding with annoyance)
It's Chungjungone's
Popular Star Award.
So the company, Chungjungone,
gave you the award.
- Did they give you gochujang?
- Right.
No, they didn't.
- Or cooking oil?
- I got a trophy instead.
- Congratulations on your award.
- Right.
- Actually, when we were young,
- It's Blue Dragon Awards.
- it was the most respected awards.
- That's right. I'm proud of him.
- Thank you.
- He won an award at a film awards.
In "One-Eyed Jacks"...
- "One-Eyed Jacks".
- The scene with his back.
- Right.
- He won the award with that scene.
- I think that's why he won.
- His back.
- That scene was very popular.
- A lot of people liked that scene.
I won the award for my role
in "Inseparable Bros."
- You should have asked me. You...
- Well...
- Congratulations.
- Don't say it if you don't know.
- Thank you.
- Award from Chungjungone.
- This is...
- You won the award as a film actor.
- By the way,
he was nominated
for the Supporting Actor too.
- Right.
- Yes.
- That's impressive.
- He was nominated.
Goodness. This is why I feel
uncomfortable around him.
(This is why he feels uncomfortable
about Kwang Soo lately.)
- That's not my fault.
- Jong Kook.
- At the Blue Dragon Awards...
- I have your phone in my pocket.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- At the Blue Dragon Awards...
- My gosh, stop it.
This is impressive.
- What's happening?
- So Min is in a one-episode drama.
They sent you the coffee truck
to your location for the drama.
Yes. I was very surprised.
I really had no idea.
The truck showed up out of the blue.
They sent the truck together
because if he sends it by himself,
- we'll find out about his feelings.
- No.
- He did it with Haha and Jong Kook.
- That's right.
Se Chan got it all started.
His photo was in the middle.
I saw that his photo
was all the way on top.
- He chose that photo.
- They sent me the truck.
He told me that he didn't do
much for the surprise.
He said that the other guys
came up with everything.
I really didn't know
they used my photo.
No. Se Chan insisted
on sending you the coffee truck.
(What? Did you suggest the idea?)
- You're acting all indifferent.
- Come on.
- Seriously.
- You act cold on the outside.
I was just standing here,
but I should've known better.
(He was between them.)
Come over here.
- Stay here.
- By the way...
- Well, this is about Jae Suk.
- Yes?
He's the number one celebrity
beloved by the people.
- My gosh.
- Gosh.
- You know what?
- This is...
Winning an award at the Blue Dragon
Awards is impressive,
but this is really impressive.
- And we're doing a show with him.
- He's always ranked number one.
We didn't know how famous he was
because we work with him.
Even I was really surprised.
- Thank you again.
- Suzy was in fifth place.
- BTS was in sixth place.
- BTS.
What's Suk Jin's ranking?
- He's not in the rankings?
- Hey, let's talk about good things.
(Hey, let's talk about good things.)
- Just in case.
- Congratulating him...
- was hard for Suk Jin.
- I thought he might be ranked too.
He was the only one who clapped
for Jae Suk while feeling bitter.
Ji Hyo, any news from the past week?
(Well...)
Well...
- The drama?
- No.
- What did you do?
- I stayed at home.
(I stayed at home.)
- She stayed at home.
- You should go out, Ji Hyo.
She's been staying home
for 10 years.
You should walk around.
You always stay at home.
You should come to my restaurant
and grill some meat...
or babysit my children.
I should call you.
You need a change of scenery.
Ji Hyo...
Before we start today's race,
some guests came to our show.
We have guests.
(The door of the train
suddenly opens.)
Ha Neul?
What's this?
- Gosh.
- Goodness!
- My gosh.
- It's AOA.
It's AOA. Goodness!
(Today's guest is AOA.)
It's "Heart Attack."
- AOA!
- The whole group is here.
Gosh, you guys are here.
It's AOA.
We missed you!
It's nice to see you.
- They are dancing in the morning.
- She's going to copy them.
- It's only 10:30 a.m. now.
- It's morning now.
It's 10:30 a.m.
(AOA performs their new song,
"Come See Me.")
My gosh, that's so cool.
- I want to dance like them.
- My gosh.
I want to dance like them too.
They told us to come see them.
(I'll go see you.)
- Nice!
- That's nice.
(Exclaiming)
(Their intense performance
continues.)
(What is this white thing?)
(AOA's refreshing performance
makes them want to go see them.)
- Come see me
- See me
(All of a sudden,
it turns into a village festival.)
(Please listen
to "Come See Me" a lot.)
AOA!
(They give them a warm welcome
for their performance.)
(The whole group has joined!)
We've never had the whole group
on our show.
The whole group is here.
- In 2, 3. Hello.
- Hello.
- We're ace of angels, AOA.
(Especially welcoming
them zealously)
- Great.
- Hyejeong.
- Is that a hot pack on your belly?
- Yes.
- I wanted to do my best today.
- She dressed warmly.
- You know what I think?
- That's what I put it on.
I don't think she would've done that
when she debuted.
But AOA is laid-back now.
Your attitude changed a lot.
By the way,
during their performance,
- we cheered them on.
- They were good.
- And our cheers were outdated.
- They were outdated.
The one that stood out
the most for me was...
"Let's do it" stood out too.
There was an unintelligible cheer.
That's ancient.
Majors in the army would say
something like that.
- Or the commanders.
- Right.
Great.
Today, you'll taste signature
regional dishes in Incheon.
It's Tasty Road in Incheon.
It's called Ace of Ace Race.
(Tasty Road in Incheon:
Ace of Ace Race)
Tasty food!
(Feeling happy)
There will be three rounds.
You'll split into 3 teams of 4, 4,
and 5 and compete.
Meal tickets will be disturbed
based on the result of the match.
Each dish costs a certain number
of meal tickets to eat it.
You will be given a meal ticket
you can use in your first mission.
A team with 4 members will get 4.
And a team with 5 members, 5.
However, the members
who fail to eat...
- will get a penalty badge.
- There's a penalty again?
The member with the most badges and
the member of his or her choice...
- will face the penalty.
- The member will choose someone.
- Again?
- I'm doomed.
- My gosh, it's that again.
A team with five members
may have an advantage,
but if the team doesn't win,
it might be disadvantageous.
Before you start your missions,
you'll split into teams first.
This is important. Yes.
Here's how you'll form your teams.
You will come up with an order
and take turns to pick someone.
When you say his or her lookalike,
anyone who laughs will be out.
(Anyone who laughs at the lookalike
will be out.)
The last member to survive
will win the game.
- This is hard.
- The winner will have the chance...
to form all of the three teams
however he or she likes.
- The winner decides everything?
- The winner decides the teams.
- Don't take it personally.
- No holding grudges.
- We're supposed to make this funny.
- We'll go this way.
- Sure.
Ready, set, go.
Noh Joo Hyun.
(Copy and paste)
- That doesn't matter.
- The member on the left starts?
- You can pick anyone.
- That doesn't matter.
Jong Kook, it's your turn.
My neighbor.
(Pointing at Suk Jin)
(He faces a small crisis...)
(as Jong Kook comes up
with a believable lookalike.)
Kwang Soo.
Hippo's poop.
(Kwang Soo said
Se Chan resembles hippo's poop.)
(He hasn't seen it, but strangely,
it might resemble Se Chan.)
(Imagining a hippo, pooping out
Se Chan in Savannah)
Next.
Jimin.
Jang Dong Gun.
(Jimin says Suk Jin
resembles Jang Dong Gun.)
(He can't believe his ears.)
(They do share
the same nationality.)
Jang Dong Gun.
(Laughing)
That was funny.
- Ji Hyo, you can't lower your head.
- I almost laughed.
- You're out.
- She laughed.
- Ji Hyo, you're out.
- I'm out?
- Go.
- You can't lower your head.
Seolhyun.
Rat.
(Summoning a rodent
all of a sudden...)
(makes him burst into laughter.)
- You're out.
(I almost laughed.)
She didn't say much,
- but isn't "rat" so funny.
- I almost laughed.
My gosh. I shouldn't have laughed.
(Rat: rodent, resembles Se Chan)
Suk Jin.
Chanmi.
Yoo Ah In.
(Suk Jin says Chanmi
resembles Yoo Ah In.)
- I think she's mad.
- Yoo Ah In.
Kwang Soo.
- Are you crying?
- A long piece of poop.
(Haha says Kwang Soo
resembles a long piece of poop.)
(Kwang Soo is tall, but...)
(This long piece of poop won
the Popular Star Award.)
- A long piece of poop.
(The laughter alert is issued.)
A long piece of poop.
- Dragon poop.
- You're out.
(Some of them are eliminated
at his answer.)
- Seolhyun. Yuna. You're out.
- Why did you laugh?
Seolhyun, you're out.
- Why are you laughing?
- That was...
That was a ridiculous answer.
Why did you laugh?
Why was it a long piece? Why?
That answer eliminated
almost everyone.
- It was so funny.
- Nice try.
It was so funny. Even the color
of his coat reminds me of poop.
- Next up is Se Chan.
- Jimin.
Colonel Fury.
(Se Chan says
Jimin resembles Colonel Fury.)
(The level of resemblance
is very high.)
(Laughing)
Colonel Fury.
- Colonel Fury.
- That was so mean.
- I wasn't going to say that.
- He's no joke.
- That was so mean.
- Why?
- No, this is just a game.
- My gosh.
- This is just a game.
- Next.
- Kwang Soo.
- Se Chan.
Punched clay.
(Kwang Soo says Se Chan
resembles punched clay.)
Punched clay.
(Slamming)
(How to make Se Chan,
eyes, nose, mouth)
That was a nice answer.
"Punched clay."
- That was hurtful.
- It's all right.
- This is just a game.
This is just a game.
I'm glad I got eliminated early on.
- Jimin.
- Kwang Soo.
Tumbling leaf.
(Jimin says
Kwang Soo is a tumbling leaf.)
- Jimin.
- Kwang Soo.
A tumbling leaf.
(How does a tumbling leaf look?)
I think he smiled.
(Strangely, we might have seen him
tumble on the ground.)
- That was funny.
- Next.
- "Tumbling leaf".
- They are all inanimate.
All right. That was hilarious.
Next up is Hyejeong.
Suk Jin.
Grandpa.
(Hyejeong says
Suk Jin resembles a grandpa.)
Suk Jin. Grandpa.
(Grandpa)
(Se Chan and Jong Kook laugh
at her brutally honest answer.)
That was brutally honest.
- That was brutally honest.
- Hey.
(Being with youth hurts.)
- You're all out.
- That was hilarious.
Next up is Jimin.
(It's Jimin's turn again.)
Kwang Soo.
(She goes after Kwang Soo again.)
- An envelope.
- "Envelope".
Envelope.
(This is long too.)
Hyejeong is out.
(The remaining members are out
as she continues to name objects.)
- It's impossible not to laugh.
- Hyejeong is out.
- Jimin wins.
- What was that? Envelope?
- Envelope.
- But he does look like an envelope.
- That was funny.
- But he looks like it.
- Right.
- Envelope.
I can't believe she said envelope.
That was a funny answer.
- Poop envelope.
- Right.
- I know. The yellow one, right?
- The long one.
Right.
(He only got hurt
by trying to stay to the end.)
Jimin, you can divide them
into three teams.
- Teams of 4, 4, and 5.
- Teams of 4, 4, and 5?
I'll go with the Envelope Guy.
Okay.
- Haha.
- Great!
(Jimin picks Kwang Soo and Haha.)
And So Min.
This is the best team.
You chose only the sly members.
(Colonel Jimin formed
the Avengers with sly members.)
- She only chose the good ones.
- My gosh.
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
(Jimin can choose
teams for others.)
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
(Don't look at her eyes.)
(Instinctively avoiding her eyes)
(As Suk Jin's name is called,
they all look away.)
No one is looking at her.
- Hey.
- No one is looking at her.
(Everyone felt a sense of danger.)
- Hey.
- No one is looking at her.
- Everyone stopped breathing.
- You're looking at the floor.
- Why did you pick me first?
- Right now...
I couldn't breathe.
- For the first time today,
- I thought we were playing...
- I looked at the floor.
- a game of silence.
- It was a game of silence.
- I looked at the floor.
- Pick him at the end.
- At the end?
- Okay.
- I'll pick your team last.
- You need to separate them well.
- Okay.
(Teams)
- Come on.
- Nice.
Wait and see.
- It's gotten cold suddenly.
- Yes.
(Heading to the first mission
after forming their teams)
- Se Chan.
- Yes.
You could have taken my seat.
Why did you wait for me
and sit there instead?
- Me?
- Yes.
- Is she making you self-conscious?
- Who is?
(Peekaboo)
(It's So Min.)
- That was awkward.
- So Min is there.
Keep a distance for the time being.
- Yes. I will.
- Last week,
I called Se Chan a few times.
But he tried to hang up
the phone quickly.
- Why do you feel awkward?
- No.
Se Chan might be confused
because we keep...
- mentioning this on TV.
- You're keeping your distance.
Is she his love interest?
- Yes.
- Who said that?
(Are they
each other's love interest?)
- That's not true, Hyejeong.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- No.
- Not yet.
- Is it just a fling?
It didn't happen yet.
- Is it a fling?
- There's something between them.
Hey.
When your mind is made up,
call me in front of my house.
(So Min's blunt comment toward him)
- Did you hear that?
- Make your decision.
So Min keeps leading him on.
It'll happen tonight. "So Min."
"Did you mean that earlier or not?"
- Why are you doing this to me?
- What?
- Chanmi is the youngest, right?
- Yes.
- How old are you?
- I'm 24.
- Really?
- You're so young!
- What about you, Seolhyun?
- They are older.
I'm 25.
- What?
- I see.
- You started from middle school.
- She's still young.
I thought you were 21.
- 21?
- So Min isn't happy.
Why not?
(Don't talk about other women.)
- Look at her face.
- No, no.
- Look at her.
- She hates it.
- Not at all.
- So Min, how old are you?
- How old are you?
- I'm 34.
(I may be 34,
but I still want to be cute.)
34? What was that?
(As So Min became cuter and cuter,)
(they finally arrive
at their first destination.)
This is Chinatown.
We had a great time last time.
- The place became more beautiful.
- You're right.
They decorated the place.
For the first mission,
you'll have jjajangmyeon, jjamppong,
and tangsuyuk.
(It's a Chinese special.)
- Chinese cuisine.
- Let's do this!
Each of you will get
a meal ticket.
Each dish will need
a specific number of meal tickets.
Jjajangmyeon and jjamppong need
two tickets each.
For 2 servings
of tangsuyuk, you need 5 tickets.
Five?
Those who cannot eat...
will be given penalty badges.
- But not if we eat?
- So we need to eat.
(They need to eat in order
not to get one.)
Let's start with jjajangmyeon.
- I'm going to have this.
- Me too.
Your first mission is called...
Trick or True Yut.
- What?
- Yut?
(Trick or True Yut)
The rules are simple.
You'll move according to the result
of the thrown yut-sticks.
The 1st to get 2 of their pieces
across the board wins.
Okay!
The winning team will be given
10 meal tickets.
(1st place will be given
10 meal tickets.)
The 2nd team will be given 5.
The third team won't be given any.
Five tickets aren't bad either.
There are four of us.
Here's the catch.
You will play the game in order.
The other two teams may not see
the result.
The playing team will play
in secret.
The actual result of the game
doesn't matter.
You may move according
to the result or lie.
We can lie?
For example, you got a gae
but lie and say you got a yut.
If the other two teams think
that you are lying,
they can raise the red X card
in the given minute...
and say, "Trick!"
If it truly turns out to be a lie,
their piece will be eliminated,
and the team that caught them
will replace it with theirs.
If it turns out that the team
has told the truth,
the other team will remove
one of their own pieces.
If there are no pieces available,
they'll have to give
one of their meal tickets.
If you've run out of tickets
as well,
I'll be handing you penalty badges.
(The penalty badges will be given.)
We shouldn't say trick whenever
we want.
- Right?
- We should discuss first.
- You're right.
- Don't worry.
- We're a team.
Now, we will decide on the order.
- Let's play the Race of Wits.
- That's good.
Don't you know how many of us
are here today?
- There are 12.
- I see.
- No, there are 13.
Let's begin.
Start.
- 1.
- You're out.
- Se Chan.
(As soon as the game begins,
So Min and Se Chan are eliminated.)
What was that?
- What was that?
(Her heart is fluttering as well.)
You're eliminated.
- So Min, we're eliminated.
- You are.
- Step back.
- You're out.
Go.
Start.
One.
- Two.
- No.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
- 6.
- 7.
(Their teamwork is amazing.)
- 6.
- 7.
Good job.
You're out.
- It's okay.
- There are only three of us.
- You're out?
Yes.
- Start.
- Me too?
- Not you.
- It shouldn't overlap.
- You shouldn't.
- I got it.
You're not out.
- You're not out.
- Get in.
- Seolhyun is out, right?
- She said seven.
- Right?
- No.
- We heard you loud and clear.
- Hold on.
- She's not out.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I mean...
- She said seven.
- Hold on.
- No, she's not out.
- Tell us.
- Are you out?
- No.
See?
(She's so brazen.)
- See?
- I'm not out.
- She's not out?
- No.
She's out.
- Guys.
- Our other team member...
- was out.
- Do you know...
Do you know what Chanmi said?
- What?
- It was so shocking.
"Seolhyun is a good liar."
(Chanmi tattles on her.)
(They're fair and square.)
See?
- See?
- Seolhyun is a good liar.
(She was a whistleblower.)
Guys.
Chanmi...
has changed a lot.
- She's a good liar.
- What is she doing?
- She's so brazen.
- She really is.
Seolhyun was doing well.
I'm so dumbfounded.
Chanmi.
If you lose this round,
your team will be in third place.
Jong Kook will say two.
Don't forget that.
There's no doubt.
- We can make a sacrifice.
- Jong Kook.
One of us needs to say two as well.
Start.
- 1.
(Chanmi, Kwang Soo,
and Jimin are out.)
(That's it.)
I'm the winner.
We won!
- I didn't say it.
- You did.
No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
- No, I...
- I really didn't.
- Come on, Jimin.
- Why have you become so brazen?
- I really didn't.
- I didn't, though.
- You did.
- Stop it.
- Jimin.
Let's play fair and square.
- I'm serious.
- Come on.
This is not fair.
Hold on. Chanmi said something
once again.
- Chanmi told me something.
- What?
- "Jimin is close with Seolhyun."
- Wait.
- So don't lie.
- I didn't say a thing.
- Hey.
- Come on.
- Exactly. I was getting ready.
- She knows everything.
Jong Kook's team will decide.
All right. We get to pick.
What should we do?
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- We shouldn't be greedy.
- You're right.
All right.
- This is...
- It's only the beginning.
- This is hard.
- Isn't it?
- I'll go.
- Okay.
Here she goes.
(What is the outcome?)
Okay, then.
You need to move it.
(She looks suspicious.)
Don't I get another toss?
(Is she telling the truth or not?)
(Is this the truth?)
We already heard
you're a good liar.
- She's really good.
- It's a habit now.
It really is.
- A habit?
- It is.
I bet this is a geol.
It's geol. One of the sticks
looked like this.
I'm not good at lying.
- Please turn around.
- I can't believe this.
- What is it?
- We get another shot anyway.
- What did you get?
- We caught yours.
- You did?
- Yes.
- Whose?
- Ours.
(Will they doubt him?)
Jong Kook's not the type...
- to risk from the beginning.
- This is for sure.
Of course.
But since Seolhyun's
on the team, it could be a lie.
- Not at all.
- I heard she's a good liar.
Gae comes out the most often.
Right. Either gae or geol.
- Shall we pass?
- Sure.
- Let's do that.
- We give this a pass.
Let's give it a pass.
- A pass?
- Let's suspect them.
Let's try that.
- Just this once.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Just this once.
- 1, 2, 3. Trick.
- Trick.
(They trust Kwang Soo.)
Were they telling the truth?
(Did Team Green really get a gae,
or are they lying?)
- Yes. Give us a meal ticket.
- See?
- I was right.
- Right.
(Seolhyun did get a gae.)
- That was amazing.
- Gae is easy to get.
- You see...
- Gae and geol come out the most.
- Right.
- You're right.
One of you should hand over
a ticket.
You two can pick.
1, 2, 3. You.
(They choose Kwang Soo.)
- You instigated it.
- You did.
- Right.
- Exactly.
- I told you it was right.
- You know what?
You guys look like amateurs.
- An amateur?
They do.
Turn around.
We're going to throw it.
(He's at a loss for words.)
Didn't it feel like a lie, though?
Did you throw it yet?
- Yes.
- Chanmi, you can throw it.
- Go first.
- Go.
- I haven't done this before.
- So...
- There's beginner's luck.
- You can do it.
- Right.
- All right.
I'm fine with either gae or geol.
- Both of them are fine.
- I tried this when I was little.
I can determine by the sound.
Don't look.
If it's a good toss, let's shout.
- Shout?
- Yes.
Yes, let's do that.
Here we go.
Whatever we get will be nice.
Good luck!
(After discussing how to react,
she throws the sticks.)
(Will Chanmi experience
beginner's luck?)
Good luck!
- Mo!
(They scream.)
- Are you kidding me?
- This is crazy!
- What did they get?
- No way.
- This is insane.
- Mo is possible.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
- Turn around.
- This is it.
- You guys were being loud.
- What happened?
- You got a mo?
(Team Red puts forth a new piece.)
- We did get it.
- They're baiting us.
- We got it.
- They're telling the truth.
- You really got a mo?
- Really?
- Mo?
- We'll take the shortcut.
- Right.
- We did get a mo.
- That is possible.
- We got it.
- Okay.
Who threw the sticks?
- Chanmi.
- Chanmi?
- Trust me.
I'll put my meal ticket on the line
and say that they're lying.
- What?
Trust me.
(She doesn't think
they're telling the truth.)
- No, look at them.
- Chanmi isn't a good liar.
They're not lying.
They're just trying to trick us.
- Do whatever you wish.
- Five.
- Four.
- I won't look.
- Three.
- It'll be your meal ticket.
- Two.
- Okay.
- One.
- I'll put mine on the line.
For this round...
(Team Blue thinks they're lying.)
(Did they really get a mo or not?)
(What's the result.)
They told the truth.
(Team Red did get a mo.)
I told you.
It's beginner's luck.
That was great.
See? It's beginner's luck.
- Jimin...
You don't need to hand over
your meal ticket.
Just remove your team's piece.
- You need to remove your piece.
- What?
- Really? Not the meal ticket?
- It's the piece?
You'll hand over the ticket
if you have no pieces left.
You need to start
from the beginning.
We'll hand over our ticket
and keep the piece.
- I didn't know.
- Me neither.
He told us before.
- Get rid of it.
- I'm sorry.
We're too impulsive.
(She's the most impulsive.)
- Let's go on.
- Chanmi.
- Get a do, gae, geol, or yut.
- I feel pressured.
Yut. It's the best.
- Yut.
- Hold on.
No, gae and geol are both good
as well.
- Geol is better.
- They're all good.
- I feel pressured.
- Chanmi.
- They're all good. Don't be.
- Chanmi, you can do it.
- I can get anything, right?
- Hey.
- Yes.
- Chanmi.
Beginner's luck really does exist.
That's right. You can do it!
No way.
- They're acting strange.
- They are.
How strange.
They're being so awkward.
You're right.
- That was so weird.
- It sounded awkward.
Let's forget about
advancing the normal way...
and move our pieces
by catching their lies.
(A new strategy)
Advancing the normal way...
- So...
- If you had listened to me,
- we would've been fine.
- But you...
I let you because
you didn't want to.
Please turn around.
You won't believe
what Chanmi just did.
- She threw a back-do.
- A back-do.
- What?
We captured Team Green's piece.
Hold on. Who has a meal ticket left?
- I have one.
- You're going that way?
- I have some left.
- Seriously?
- That's impossible.
- You'll be left with nothing.
Show us how you moved
your piece again.
Can you not get so emotional?
What? When did we get emotional?
- You're awful at games.
- It's for real.
We're awful at this game?
- Yes, am I wrong?
- Pay attention to our pieces.
He really is a fuddy-duddy...
because he keeps acting
like a leader among us.
(He keeps acting
like a leader among us.)
(Haha is proven to be
a fuddy-duddy.)
What did I even say?
I mean you three...
The trick...
- He tells us off.
- You guys insisted.
- He acts like Jong Kook here.
- He nags us.
- From what I see...
- They agree.
- Unbelievable.
- Bet a meal ticket.
I'll bet mine. You're lying.
- We call the lie.
- They're lying.
- The back-do...
- So what Team Red got...
(Did Team Red
really throw a back-do?)
(Team Blue's meal ticket
is on the line.)
They're telling the truth.
Nice!
Chanmi, good job.
No way.
- Chanmi...
- You're the best.
They're telling the truth.
Please give up your meal ticket.
She threw a back-do?
(Team Blue must forfeit
another meal ticket.)
Why do you keep giving up
your meal tickets?
- You don't have many left.
- She threw a back-do...
so we captured Team Green's piece.
- Don't you get it?
- At this rate,
you'll be asked
to leave the restaurant.
What are you going to do?
- Let's go crazy now.
- Sure thing.
I just don't care anymore.
I bet you're thinking
about lying next.
Gosh.
Is this about the right timing?
They're backed into a corner,
so the timing fits.
- We don't have any pieces on.
- let's do this.
It's a perfect time to lie.
(What they get will be important.)
(Team Blue gets a gae.)
Okay!
(The forced reaction
makes them burst into laughter.)
We got this.
- He was too conscious of it.
- Exactly.
- This is a lie.
- You were too late.
I'm sure you all heard it too,
but he yelled just from his throat.
No way!
Let's just turn around.
- Don't react in any way.
- Are we good?
- Please turn around.
- We placed our piece.
He only yelled from his throat.
Unbelievable.
They caught Team Green's piece.
- Ours?
- All right.
- Let's call their lie.
- We don't need to though.
- There's no need to risk it.
- We don't have to step forward.
- It's up to Team Green.
- They already seem grim.
- Look at them.
- Only one team should call the lie.
They don't seem to be at ease.
It's easy to get a geol.
Isn't Jimin acting
like she's nervous?
- Right.
- Right?
- Geol...
- Hold on a second.
- We don't need to...
- Give us some time.
We have nothing to lose.
You don't need to take our spot...
- because you're ahead of us.
- He's stopping us.
(Kwang Soo's reaction
only makes them suspect him more.)
(Busted?)
- All right. "Trick!"
- "Trick!"
(It's a trick!)
- Trick...
- Team Blue...
was lying.
(It was a trick.)
(Team Blue never got a geol.)
- I knew it.
- It was too obvious.
Why did you have to talk so much?
- Seriously?
- You should've kept quiet.
He talked too much.
- Too much.
- I was nervous.
Kwang Soo tried to stop us.
- Why talk at all?
- He talks too much.
We could tell by your face.
Remove Team Blue's piece
and move any of your pieces.
- We're off to paradise.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Paradise.
- Nice!
(Team Red's piece
moves three spaces.)
Let's go!
- We're on a roll.
- Do, gae, geol...
Do, gae, geol, yut.
We only need a yut.
Do we need a yut now?
- But if we get a gae...
- We'll be in trouble.
We won't be able
to avoid the fire pit.
Then that's all we have to avoid.
Hold on. Why are you guys arguing?
(Why are you guys arguing?)
I'd rather play this game alone.
Same here.
- I'd...
- I want you all to shut it.
If you hadn't yelled,
- we wouldn't have been caught.
- Exactly.
You talked too much though.
- I was shocked.
- It's all because of you.
Want to know
the expression you had?
I...
- We're not on the same page.
- Not at all.
Let's each toss one
of the yut-sticks.
- We won't take turns.
- Good idea.
Don't react in any way.
- No.
- Don't.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo, you especially.
Watch it.
(He's upset.)
- You're the problem though.
- Okay, fine.
The problematic Team Blue is up.
- You seem grim.
- Everybody, sit.
Look at them.
- Wait.
- They're throwing one each.
One each?
- We'll give it a go.
- It'll be confusing.
- They're a mess.
- Tell me about it.
1, 2, 3.
- Wait.
- Aren't we tossing all at once?
- Are you done?
- Not yet.
Are you done?
(The second yut-stick
is also facing up.)
(Even Jimin's yut-stick is
facing up.)
(Last but not least,
Kwang Soo throws his.)
(Kwang Soo's stick
is also facing up.)
(Team Blue throws a yut!)
(Nice!)
(They keep quiet
just like they agreed.)
They must've messed up.
They're lying for sure,
so let's call them out.
- Please turn around.
- Sure.
- What is it?
- They say they got a yut.
(They all laugh at the news.)
- What?
- We'll call them out.
So Min's shoulder is cramping.
- Let's do this.
- Stop talking.
It's a trick.
Shall we call their lie too?
- Right.
- Let's call it.
- It's a trick.
- Shall we?
- It's a lie.
- Go ahead, guys.
Okay, we'll call it.
- A trick?
- It's a trick.
(The two teams will counter.)
(Just call it.)
- It's a trick.
- They're lying.
Team Blue is telling the truth.
(The truth!)
(Team Blue really did get a yut.)
(I'm glad we didn't call them out.)
Nice!
(Team Blue finally comes together.)
No way.
Good job, guys. Nice.
It's all about that
one lucky punch. Yes!
I can't believe we did it.
- You all did great.
- Anyway,
the image we built
played a huge part.
- You're right.
- Exactly.
- We can catch them with a geol.
- Right.
We can catch Team Red's piece
resting in paradise.
- You only need a geol.
- A geol.
- We need a geol.
- Yut, mo, geol is fine.
Just don't let it be do or gae.
- Don't feel pressured.
- We'll go ahead.
We won't blame you.
Throw them up high.
(What did he throw?)
They must've decided
not to react in any way.
I heard something though.
Me too.
- Right?
- Please turn around.
- They didn't get anything good.
- They've already set the bait.
- You caught us?
- What?
(Startled)
(Team Blue is claiming...)
(that they caught
Team Red's piece in paradise.)
We got a geol,
went to paradise and...
- Who threw the sticks?
- Haha did.
- Haha?
- Yes.
- Haha did.
I think they're telling the truth.
The bait they've set up so far
is working.
Team Red is the victim,
so let's wait and see.
I'm sure they'll take action.
If this is a trick though,
we'll have to start from zero.
- We can't ever catch up with them.
- Five.
- Four.
- We have to take the risk.
- We have to.
- But they're telling the truth.
- It's the truth.
- They're telling the truth.
- Two.
- I'm sure of it.
- One. No one's calling them out?
- They're slightly smiling.
Team Blue is telling...
(Team Blue is telling...)
It's the truth.
Nice.
I can't believe they're in the lead.
Okay, good.
We shook up the entire game.
- We turned it upside down.
- Exactly.
The balance has been tilted.
- Tilted?
- We're almost there.
Double or nothing, guys?
- Go for it.
- Nice.
- Get lost if you're scared.
- We need them to get a gae...
and drop into the pit.
(Will they take a step closer
to win the game...)
(or will they plummet
into the fire pit?)
(What did they throw?)
They promised not to react
in any way.
- Right...
- And that's more confusing.
It's about time you're scared now.
Please turn around.
- What did you get?
- A do.
(They're claiming that
they avoided the fire pit.)
- A do?
- Then that's probably true.
There's a high possibility
that they got a gae.
- Right.
- Because that means the fire pit.
You're right!
(Did they claim to have gotten a do
to escape the fire pit?)
- If they had gotten a gae...
- We'd add a new piece.
- We would've added a new piece.
- Right.
But then they could
easily be caught.
- Hold on.
- No.
- If they got a gae...
- They're telling the truth.
- Right.
- I agree.
- Do is hard to get.
- It's not easy to get a do.
- 5, 4...
- They've set the bait so well.
- Three...
- What do you say?
(Glancing)
- Call it.
- It's a "trick."
- "Trick!"
(Let's call it.)
- Really?
- Are you sure?
- I don't think so.
- It's a trick.
(They claimed it a trick even though
their teammates are doubtful.)
(Is Team Blue telling the truth?)
- It's the truth.
- What did I tell you?
(Team Blue dramatically
gets a do which saved them.)
(Bitter...)
Right, of course.
We're only confident
when we're not lying.
It's all about having
nothing to lose.
This could've gone south.
Are you kidding me?
- Exactly.
- We're in the lead now.
How dramatic is this?
Yutnori is so much fun.
- Being confident is the key.
- Our team...
- You're right.
- The situation is bad.
- Let's catch that piece.
- Why am I nervous?
(Team Red is cornered,
but what did they throw?)
Darn it. I can't believe it.
Talk about a disappointment.
This is disappointing.
(Team Red places a new piece
with geol.)
Geol? We'll let them have that one.
Right. Is it our turn then?
We'll catch Team Red's piece.
- This is so disappointing.
- Well...
Let them have it.
Is no one calling them out?
Well, Team Red...
lied.
(They lied!)
(Team Red lied about
getting a geol.)
What did you throw?
- A gae.
It was a gae.
Right, we'll be as sly as we can.
You take no chances at all, do you?
(You take no chances at all,
do you?)
- Cowards.
- Go, team!
- We'll be as sly as possible.
- All right.
You lied just to advance
one more step?
That's what you lied for?
Okay!
We must get a geol and catch it.
If they do, call their lie.
Oh, no...
Okay.
(Hyejeong aims to get a geol.)
(But she throws a gae.)
(It's a gae.)
(It should've been a geol.)
They can't have caught us.
(It's Team Green's turn
to move their piece.)
Are you done?
(Will they be honest
and advance two steps?)
- We're done.
- Okay.
You didn't catch us, did you?
You did?
Team Green said they got a geol
and caught Team Red's piece.
- Guys.
- Unbelievable.
- We should catch them out.
- You really threw a geol?
We did.
Seolhyun, did you get a geol?
Yes.
- The thing is...
- We don't have to be there.
We have two pieces on the board.
We can leave them there.
- It doesn't matter.
- Right.
Kwang Soo.
We'll pass.
You guys can call them out.
- No, we don't want to.
- We can't.
- You're not as stupid as I thought.
- We don't want to.
(You're not as stupid as I thought.)
Why do you look down on him?
I thought he'd fall for it,
but he didn't.
Kwang Soo is not stupid!
I thought he'd fall for it,
but he didn't.
(Kwang Soo is not stupid.)
Too bad.
- No objection?
- No.
What they said was...
- a trick.
- What?
(What they said was a lie.)
(Team Green
didn't really get a geol.)
- I knew it.
- It was a lie?
Everyone seems to trust us.
- Are you guys getting impatient?
- Yes.
Did you have to catch that piece?
Finally, the dirty game has started!
This is our chance!
(The dirty game begins.)
- Double or nothing!
Let's turn this around.
Double or nothing!
Hyejeong.
- It's okay.
- Hyejeong.
Let's not show any reaction.
Okay!
(The yut-sticks are thrown.)
(They look surprised
but keep quiet.)
(What's the result?)
Their reaction is genuine now.
(They're not showing any reaction.)
- We're done.
- Please wait.
It has to be true. What did they do?
They say they threw a mo.
- A mo?
(Are you sure you got a mo?)
Put it up.
- Hold on.
- Maybe not.
- Wait.
- No. It's too risky.
- I'm positive.
Let them be there.
We have...
- nothing to lose.
- We...
Bring it on!
- Double or nothing!
- Bring it on!
- Let's do this!
- Let's take a vote.
- Hold on.
Do they really have the guts?
They don't.
They got a do
but are calling it a gae.
What are you saying?
We're not timid people.
- But they couldn't lie about a mo.
- We're not timid people.
- Should we?
- Yes, call them out.
- Let's do it.
- This time...
I think they're telling the truth.
- Three,
- Hurry up.
- two,
- Director, hurry up!
- one.
- Hurry up!
Time's up. No objection?
No objection.
What they said was...
(Did Team Red really get a mo?)
- true.
- Yes!
Good job.
(Team Red did throw a mo.)
Why didn't you object?
I didn't want to!
I was getting anxious!
- Why are you blaming me?
- Suk Jin.
You didn't look anxious at all.
You looked like a con man
asking for an investment.
Your eyes were shining.
- It's so hard to resist.
- Hold back.
- You shouldn't.
- Let's...
Let's imagine we don't have this
until our piece is finished.
- I'll put this away.
- Okay.
I'll put it here.
- Until our piece is finished.
- We can't use it.
Let's start. Let's go.
Turn around.
(Team Red gets to throw again.)
(What did they get this time?)
(Silent)
(They look more careful than ever.)
They're deciding
whether they should turn.
- We have to stop them.
- Please trust me.
- Wait!
- Be quiet!
Why are you doing this?
You fools!
- This is not okay.
- Let's hear him out.
- They're lying.
- They're up to something.
Suk Jin wants to lie,
- but the others are stopping him.
- Right.
Suk Jin sounds exaggerated.
- Okay.
- Turn around.
- What happened?
- This is crazy.
- You got a yut?
- What?
You got a yut?
- We were surprised too.
- I can't stand it.
I can't stand it anymore.
- I think it's false too.
- It's false.
- I can't stand it anymore.
- Suk Jin definitely...
- Come on.
- We were shocked too.
- We were.
I thought Hyejeong was crazy.
- I didn't know she'd be so good.
- We heard you guys argue.
If you're Tazza,
she's Yutzza.
- Is that a thing?
- She's Yutzza.
Yes, she's Yutzza.
- We were shocked.
- They're tricking us.
- I was so surprised.
- Let's speed up.
- How could you get a yut again?
- It's impossible.
You threw a mo and then a yut?
- Can we do it?
- One.
- Let's do it!
- "Trick!"
Team Blue thinks you're lying.
(Team Blue thinks it's a lie
and makes Jae Suk smile.)
- I'm positive.
- It's just impossible.
I'm sure Suk Jin pushed it.
- Everyone else was against it.
- We heard them argue.
Let's speed up.
- You think I pushed it?
- It's a trick.
It was true.
(It was true.)
Take Team Blue's piece away.
(No way.)
(Haha faints.)
- This is crazy.
- Hold on.
- The blue piece?
- You're crazy.
(The blue piece was about to finish
but has to start over now.)
Why did you have to bring this?
- Did they buy any items?
- I mean...
Do you have items?
- They got a mo and a yut?
- Go, Hyejeong!
- Move.
- Get out of the way.
Here comes Hyejeong!
Hyejeong is on fire today.
Go, Hyejeong!
- Why won't you listen to me?
- I couldn't resist.
You thought it was false too.
I wanted to hold back.
- So did I.
- Ji Hyo's team should've called it.
- But they won't listen.
- Exactly.
- Anything is fine.
- Just toss anything.
- A gae is fine too.
- Anything is fine.
Hyejeong is a yutnori genius.
(This time,)
(she throws a do.)
(Silent)
Unbelievable.
(They don't need to think too much.)
(They move their leading piece
one step forward.)
Let's move one step forward.
- Turn around.
- What happened?
They threw a do
and advanced one step.
- All right.
- That's...
But there's a chance...
they got a gae or a geol
and didn't want to take a risk.
- Take the risk then.
- They might have wanted to...
- Call them out.
- Call them out. You have one left.
- Five,
- Should I? Hold on.
- four...
- They have a problem.
- It's no big deal.
- They need help.
- Let's do it!
- You should pass this time.
- It's no big deal.
- Let's pass this time.
- Let's do it!
- Let's pass.
- It's a lie.
They're lying.
- 1, 2, 3. "Trick!"
- "Trick!"
(They all say it's a lie.)
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- It was...
- true.
- Darn it.
(True)
(This is the consequence
of gambling.)
- Why did you do that?
With a gae, we would have
caught the green piece.
- They would have caught us.
- Why did you do that?
Can you shred this?
- Seriously.
- Please.
- We shouldn't have this.
- Gambling is a scary thing.
(Gambling Addiction Hotline: 1336)
- Destroy it.
- No.
(They have second thoughts.)
(They put it high up instead.)
Don't use it.
(Team Blue has
only one meal ticket left.)
It'd be perfect
if we land on paradise.
Let's do this, guys.
We need a do, yut, or mo.
We have three options.
(Their goal is to throw a do.)
(They get a do.)
(They can't believe
they really threw a do.)
(They move their piece
onto paradise.)
- Turn around, everyone.
- Okay.
They threw a do
and landed on paradise.
(They got a do?)
We have to object.
- Get the sign.
- We have to object.
- Get the sign!
- Let's do this!
- We object to this.
- It's impossible.
- Are you kidding us?
- We're going to risk it.
- They went too far.
- It's a lie.
- We're calling them out.
- This is unacceptable.
- They went way too far.
- It's impossible.
- It's a lie.
- We're objecting to this.
It was...
true.
- Darn it!
(They lose all
of their meal tickets.)
- Shred it!
- Please shred it.
(They don't want the sign.)
(Shredded)
(Celebrating)
You guys are broke now.
- They can't resist it.
- Unbelievable.
These guys...
Can we take a loan?
Loan us some meal tickets.
You'll be getting
penalty badges now.
Let us visit a nearby pawnshop
for a moment.
(They'd go on all night.)
We can do this. We can overcome it.
Let's change the rule.
Bring one piece home to win.
We'll overcome it.
If we get a gae, we can catch them.
- It's easy to get a gae.
- A gae?
- You haven't thrown yet, right?
- Us?
- I have.
- We all have.
- Someone lucky should do it.
- You do it.
- No.
Hyejeong would throw a yut or a mo.
- You'd throw a gae.
- Okay.
(You'd get a gae.)
- You're perfect.
- Okay.
- I'd throw a gae?
- He'd get a gae.
I'd get a gae.
- Take it easy.
- I'm a gae hunter.
Take it easy. You can do this!
- We need a gae.
- Relax.
(What did the gae hunter toss?)
(What?)
What's this?
- What did he do?
- I'm sure.
Turn around.
- They probably caught it.
- They caught it?
- No.
- No, they didn't.
(The red piece...)
(has advanced five steps.)
They got a mo
and advanced five steps.
- What did they get?
- They threw a mo.
- It's a trick.
- It's definitely a trick.
- They didn't get a gae.
- It's impossible.
If you're not using it,
please let me borrow it.
- We call "trick."
- "Trick".
- I mean...
- It's impossible.
They threw a mo
and advanced five steps?
- We got a mo.
- Come on.
- Who are you trying to fool?
- It's a trick.
- You thought we wouldn't object.
- You thought we wouldn't.
- Exactly.
Do you want the chance?
I'm serious this time.
- We were disappointed.
- Do you want it?
Jae Suk threw the sticks.
- Jae Suk did?
- He did...
and got a mo.
- I...
- We have to object.
I threw a mo.
It's a trick.
If it really is a trick,
- you'll move to their position.
- We'll move to their position?
- Fine, let's do it.
- Let's do it.
- We have nothing to lose.
We have nothing to lose anyway.
- Let's do it.
- We have to catch them once.
- Let's go.
- "Trick!"
- It was...
(Was it true or false?)
- true.
- It's true!
(Jae Suk did get a mo.)
- It's true?
- It's true!
(Team Blue gets a penalty badge.)
We'll decide later.
Let's finish.
- Anything but a do is fine.
We might get a do or a back-do.
There's a chance.
- Take it easy.
- Relax.
(They need to avoid
a do or a back-do.)
(It's a do.)
(Unfortunately, they get a do.)
It's so quiet.
- Did they get a do?
- In any case,
there's no winner yet.
- Please turn around.
- The game didn't end.
- My goodness.
- This team claims...
- they threw a do.
- I can't believe it.
(They stayed honest
and advanced one step.)
So what happened?
- They are at the starting point.
- The starting point.
- We got a do.
- Okay.
It's plausible.
Let them off.
- Let them off. Let's move on.
- Excuse me?
(The tiger moths decide
to let them off.)
- Excuse me?
- We really got a do.
We really got a do.
Don't do that again.
I know you will say
you really got it, but...
They might have gotten a back-do,
but we have no reason...
- to say they are lying.
- Let's focus on ourselves.
- Let's go.
If we throw a yut,
we will catch their piece.
If we get a mo, we will get out.
(Jong Kook throws the yut sticks
and gets...)
(a geol.)
(They honestly advance three steps
and neither team objects.)
We are done.
You didn't get a yut or a mo, right?
Did you get a geol?
- Then it must be true.
- They didn't play a trick.
Team Blue, toss the sticks.
(Kwang Soo unfolds something.)
(It reads,)
("Please react
as if we got a mo or a yut.")
(They ask the staff to lie.)
This is meaningless.
That team doesn't scare me at all.
- Here we go.
- Okay. Let's go.
Good luck.
(I believe in you, staff.)
(Gae)
(So Min asks for a false reaction.)
(Silent)
(I can't believe
this lousy production crew.)
(We asked you for a favor!)
(Why won't you react?)
(Didn't you read this?)
- Everyone is laughing.
- Seriously.
- Did they get a back-do?
- A back-do...
or a do.
- We're throwing the yut-sticks.
- Let's go.
- We will do it now.
- You already did!
- No, we didn't.
- Let's go.
(They are the rule-breakers.)
(They ask for a reaction.)
(The nice staff members cheer.)
My goodness.
- This is incredible.
- This is insane.
- All right.
- What did they throw?
(How many steps will they advance?)
Please turn around.
Did you get a mo?
- Mo?
- You are ridiculous.
We can't do anything about it.
They are going all in.
If I were a member of this team,
I would lie...
since this is the last chance.
Suk Jin, let's see what they get
the second time.
- Let them go again.
- Okay.
Let's see what they get
the second time.
This time, it was a lie.
Okay!
It's meaningless.
It's okay.
Hey, don't say it's meaningless!
It's meaningful!
(Annoyed)
(Emotional)
- We can do this!
- It's meaningful.
We can do this!
It's not over until it is!
- Toss the sticks carefully.
- Seriously.
Please turn around.
Stay calm.
(Kwang Soo comes up to the front.)
We will throw the sticks.
(He begins to write
something down again.)
(What will he write this time?)
(This time, Kwang Soo asks...)
(the staff members to react
as if they threw a do.)
(I am begging you.)
Please throw the yut-sticks.
(What are they playing at?)
Two.
(They got a mo!)
(It's a miracle.)
(They can't believe they got a mo.)
(This time,
the reaction is authentic.)
- Did they get a good one?
- It's a trick.
- It's a lie.
- I am 100 percent certain.
- Hey, don't help them.
- What was that?
- Don't be like that.
- Don't react.
- What was that?
- They stayed silent at first.
They stayed silent at first.
(We are so happy.)
(Good job, Jimin!)
It's a lie.
(They are certain it's a lie.)
It's a lie. We caught them.
It was so obvious this time.
Turn around.
This team claims they threw a do
and advanced to there.
- "Trick!"
(This team claims they threw a do
and advanced to there.)
(Trick!)
- It's a lie.
- We are 100 percent certain.
- It's a trick.
- If you are right,
it will be over for Team Blue.
- Okay.
- We are 100 percent certain.
It was true.
(It was true!)
(Sad)
(Happy)
- It was true?
- We will lose the other piece.
- We have two pieces.
- We can lose this piece.
- Yes!
- I love you guys!
- We can do this!
It's not over until it is!
- "One-Eyed..."
- "Jacks!"
(In tears)
We are going next.
- We are going next.
- It's okay.
- But if they...
- If they get a mo again...
- Seriously.
- If they get a mo or a yut,
- we would lose.
- That won't happen.
- Let's call out their lie...
even if they are in last place.
- I am so annoyed.
- Okay.
- A yut will put it in the fire pit.
If we get a yut,
we will start a new piece.
- That's right.
- We won't get a yut.
- Come on.
- Let's see how it goes.
If we lose at this point...
- I can't believe it.
- How did that happen?
We have to do well.
This is our last chance.
I will give you my spirits.
(Cheering)
(No way.)
Their reaction was late.
I should have made
that piece take an exit.
- You shouldn't have gotten a do.
- All right.
- Turn around.
- Seriously.
- What?
- They claim they got a yut...
- and advanced a new piece.
- Okay.
(Could it be true?)
A new piece?
I think it's true.
This lets them take another turn.
Oh, you are right.
(Is it a ploy to have another turn?)
- That's right.
- Let's call them out.
- No, no.
- Hold on.
- It's their only chance to win.
- No, no.
It's their only chance to win.
There is no way
they got a yut after a mo.
- 10...
- No, no.
They advanced a new piece
to avoid the fire pit.
Nine.
If we take a chance, we could win.
They advanced a new piece
to avoid the fire pit.
- We need to call them out.
- I don't think...
- I don't think we should.
- Eight.
(If Team Blue is lying,)
(the team that calls them out 1st
will win.)
(But if they are not,
calling them out will cost a piece.)
- "Trick!"
- It isn't.
(Team Red shouted it out first.)
We are taking a risk.
- We are taking a risk.
- We have to take a risk.
- Otherwise, they would win.
- That's right.
It was...
We will give you one more chance.
- No.
- They are lying.
(Is it the truth or a trick?)
- It was...
- A trick.
(This is the objection
that will decide the winner.)
A trick.
(Team Blue got a gae,
but acted like they got a yut.)
I knew it.
Jong Kook, had you stayed quiet,
we would have gone down.
- You gave us a hint.
- A hint about another turn.
(We should have objected.)
Nice! We placed first!
- Thank you.
- We got them.
Thank you.
(Team Red places 1st!)
We got them.
That was incredible.
- It's our turn to throw the sticks.
- It will end the game.
They could get a back-do.
- They could get a back-do.
- That's right.
If miracles exist,
they will get a back-do.
Even if we get a do,
- the game won't end.
- A do won't do.
We would get stuck on the last step.
Please.
It was cool. It was a miracle...
- when you threw that mo, Jimin.
- Seriously.
- It was cool.
- I was so surprised.
(Let's get a gae
or something better.)
- We are done.
- All right.
Turn around.
(It seems like the game is over.)
- We are done.
I think...
- I think...
- What did they get?
- they got a do.
They claim they got something better
than a do and took an exit.
Had they gotten a do,
they wouldn't have taken an exit.
This is our last chance.
- It's a trick.
- Let's go. "Trick!"
- We have to object. Do you agree?
- It's a trick.
- We have to object.
- You could get a penalty badge.
Give us a penalty badge!
They are irredeemable.
We have to object.
- It's your call.
- It was...
(The last objection will decide
which team places 2nd.)
(Was it the truth or a lie?)
It was...
a trick.
(Trick!)
(They are overjoyed.)
(What did Team Green get
to use a trick?)
(Seolhyun threw the yut-sticks.)
(A back-do)
(For goodness' sake!)
(How could this happen?)
(They had to use a trick
to avoid the fire pit.)
- We got a back-do.
- A back-do.
(They had to use a trick
to avoid the fire pit.)
- We got a back-do.
- A back-do.
Did you get a back-do?
That would have put the piece
on the fire pit.
That was unbelievable.
That was insane. That was insane.
It was a miracle.
- See?
- A miracle occurred.
- Seriously.
Thus, the winner is...
We are so cool.
(Team Red got 15 meal tickets,)
(Team Blue got 5 meal tickets
and 3 penalty badges,)
(and Team Green got 4 meal tickets
and 2 penalty badges.)
- Thank you for the food.
That team is having a feast.
- Of course.
- It's so tasty.
- We placed first.
- I wish I could give you some.
I'm so jealous.
(Jjajangmyeon after a good match
tastes incredible.)
(Seolhyun has a spoonful
of jjamppong soup.)
(It's so tasty.)
How is it? Is it good?
- Seolhyun, is it good?
- Yes.
How did you get a back-do
in that critical moment?
(He holds grudges.)
I don't know.
I can't believe you got a back-do.
Seolhyun, he is being nice
because it's you.
If it was Haha or one of us,
he wouldn't have sat still.
Had Haha done it,
I would have held grudges
for two weeks.
Is he still mad at Haha?
- Is he?
- Is he still mad at Haha?
Yondu?
Be quiet.
(The meal ends on a pleasant note.)
Is that crunchy fried chicken?
- It looks delicious.
- It's chicken!
Incheon is well-known
for its crunchy fried chicken.
I really want egg bread.
- I want this.
- What's jjajang bingsu?
- I want egg bread.
- Is that bingsu?
I guess that's ice cream.
It looks like jjajangmyeon,
but it's ice cream.
The prizes on this mission...
are the desserts
that represent Incheon.
The second mission is
Come and Find Me Like a Cat.
(The second mission,
Come and Find Me Like a Cat)
Come and Find Me Like a Cat.
(They like the name.)
This game will be played
while the train goes around once.
Pick one person as an attacker
on your team,
and we'll take turns attacking.
Everybody
but the person attacking...
has to run away
in the designated train.
(Everybody but the attacker
has to run away in the train.)
The attacker wears the blindfold,
- and uses this plush toy.
- That sounds fun.
If you hit your opponents,
you earn a point.
If you hit your own team or staff,
you lose two points.
You can't just attack.
The people running away
can't talk...
but can make animal sounds.
Like "woof, woof?"
- Right.
- Meow
For example,
if my team is trying to hit me,
then I can't say your name,
but I can say, "woof, woof"...
- or "cock-a-doodle-doo."
- Meow
1st place team gets 10 meal tickets,
2nd place team gets 5,
- and 3rd place team gets 1.
- This is difficult.
(Which team will win this game?)
You can't make any sound
but animal sounds.
Is it this train
or can we go to the next one?
- Should we get started?
- It's just this train.
- It's just this?
- That's so hard.
(This is too tight for 12 people.)
- It's small.
- It's so tight.
- We can't run away here.
- Is it "meow?"
- Ours is "meow."
- Should we move around?
You can move around now.
We have to walk around.
Team Green, let's stay together.
We'll get hit together.
- First team,
- Do we go first?
please have your attacker come up.
Put on the blindfold.
- We have to make a lot of sounds.
- Woof, woof
I won't go there then.
Kwang Soo, woof, woof.
Hey, you can't do that.
Not here, woof.
It's a full blindfold
with swim goggles.
We'll start once I blow the whistle.
Please move around.
- I don't think he can see at all.
- Right? He can't see.
- This is the plush toy.
- Ready...
Ready, set...
(How many points
will Team Blue earn?)
(Game starts.)
Behind you, woof.
Woof, woof, me.
Woof
(Somebody is here.)
(Chanmi and Jae Suk are
cornered already.)
Woof, woof
(Hit them!)
(Hitting)
Woof!
(Slapping)
(He confirms that
it's a guy's voice.)
(I got you, punk.)
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo's knee
is not coming down.)
Hey.
Woof, woof, behind you.
- We'll see about this.
- Woof, woof
We'll see.
(Team Blue gains a point
if they get Jae Suk.)
- They're here, woof.
- Woof!
- Woof, woof
- Can he see?
(Kwang Soo loses track.)
Dong Hoon.
(I'm So Min.)
(He approaches So Min
who's barking.)
(What?)
(A shoe camera?)
(Hitting)
(His body responds
to the smell of the shoe.)
- Good job.
- Who was it?
- Se Chan.
- You're going to swing that hard?
(Is there another person behind?)
(Hyejeong is about to get caught.)
(He goes behind the camera
following Haha's voice.)
(I got you, punk.)
- Minus two for staff.
- No, no.
(Director Kang Chan Hee,
oldest staff member of Running Man)
(He's the 1st celebrity
who hit Producer Kang.)
Minus two for staff.
- It's Chan Hee.
- I'm sorry.
- You hit his cheek.
I'm sorry, sir!
- You hit his cheek!
- I'm sorry.
Last chance.
- Woof, woof
- So Min.
- She's on our team. Come here.
(There's tension in the air
with one chance left.)
(Their legs shake.)
Good.
(Yuna gets away.)
(He chases after her.)
(Producer Jung Chul Min)
(He swings full force.)
(As soon as he detects movement,)
(he swings full force.)
(He attacks the producer too.)
What was that?
- It's Chul Min.
- I'm sorry!
- Who did you think it was?
- I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry. I had no idea.
Chul Min!
- I'm sorry.
- Why would you hit him?
I'm sorry.
- Is it over?
- It's over.
- He grabbed my hair.
- That was so funny.
(There are other victims.)
- He grabbed my hair.
- Are you all right?
- Right? My bad.
- No, it's okay.
You have to make the animal sounds.
Team Red, please come up.
- Se Chan.
- Yes.
- Direct me.
- Good luck.
Go forward is "meow."
"Meow"?
Go back is "meow!"
- Is this for everybody?
- "Meow!"
(Everybody can hear.)
- Suk Jin.
- Is this for all of us?
- What are you doing?
- Go forward is "meow."
- Did you hear him?
Go back is "woof?"
Go forward is "meow."
Go back is "woof."
- All right.
- Meow
I'll communicate
with animal sounds, okay?
Okay.
- Woof, woof
- Jae Suk's voice.
That's go forward.
No. Kwang Soo
- He said Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo
(Hold on.)
- What was that?
- Kwang Soo!
How does a dog speak?
- I didn't speak.
- The dog said, "Kwang Soo."
Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo.
- Do Haha.
Haha!
- Only animal sounds count.
- These are animal sounds.
Look at the sea.
It's pretty.
This is nice.
- This is great.
- This is amazing.
- Look at that.
- This is so nice.
- Let's get started. Ready...
- Woof, woof
(Se Chan is the attacker.
How many points will he earn?)
Set...
(Game starts.)
Woof, woof
Meow, it's me.
(Hit him!)
- Kwang Soo.
- Woof, woof
(Why is he hanging from there?)
Woof, woof
(That's the signal to attack.)
(Hitting)
Woof, woof
(Collapsing)
What now?
- Who was it?
- Kwang Soo.
(What kind of strategy was that?)
(Oh, my.)
- Woof, woof
(Se Chan is on a roll
after catching Kwang Soo.)
(He advances boldly.)
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook are
in front of him,)
(but he gets flung.)
- No.
- Woof, woof
(It's us!)
(Is this an animal sound?)
Go back!
(Hitting)
(I don't know anymore.)
(Calm down.)
(He shows no mercy.)
Meow, meow
(Be quiet, everybody.)
Hey.
- Are you out of your mind?
- Woof, woof
- Goodness.
(He doesn't care about the strategy
anymore. He just goes for it.)
(Who's that?)
- Woof, woof
- Good job.
(What's he doing?)
Meow, meow
That's it.
That was so funny.
Do you have a grudge?
- That was so funny.
- Why?
- Why did you hit Jae Suk?
- Why did you hit my eye?
- My bad.
- Why did you hit him?
I got the animal sounds confused.
- Goodness.
- Okay.
- That was so funny.
- Let's get started. Ready...
(It's Team Green's turn.
Yuna is the attacker.)
Set...
(Game starts.)
I don't know where I am.
(Her team dashes away.)
Meow
(It's us.)
(What?)
(We're on the same team.)
(It's us!)
(Hit them!)
(Hitting)
She hit them.
(It's obviously Seolhyun's voice.)
(She swings without hesitation.)
- Ji Hyo got hit.
- They both got hit.
- It's minus two points.
- She can't hit us again.
- She hit her own team, so minus 2.
- Minus 2.
Oh, gosh.
(Jong Kook feels threatened,
so he uses force.)
What?
(She attacks him.)
(She eliminates Suk Jin who was
making a weird chimpanzee sound.)
- Did I get hit?
- Suk Jin is out.
(She's searching for
her next target.)
(It's me, Yuna.)
Woof, woof
(Jong Kook sounded urgent.)
(She replies with an attack.)
- You can't hit our team.
- Woof, woof
He's on our team.
- Is this over?
- That's it.
- All right.
This is round two.
That was round one.
How many are there?
- You go.
- This is the last one.
I'll go this time.
Is it just two rounds?
- Yes, it's just two.
- Come here.
Hyejeong, do you want to try?
- Can you do it?
- Go, Hyejeong.
- Hyejeong can do it.
- Okay.
We need signals.
"Woof" is to hit.
"Crow" is to hold.
(Suk Jin's secret strategy)
Okay.
That was so obvious.
Suk Jin, why are you talking
in front of other people?
- No, they didn't hear.
- Chanmi, what's this?
Got it? "Crow" is to hold.
"Crow" is to hold.
Once I blow the whistle, we start.
Please move around.
We moved around.
Okay.
- You moved back a lot.
- Ready,
set...
(Round 2 starts.)
I'm scared.
(She feels anxious
from the beginning.)
(They're relaxed.)
(It's me. I'm here.)
(Hitting)
Meow, meow
How many times did I meow?
(Goodness)
I was the only one meowing.
Everybody else was quiet.
Were you listening?
Hey.
Go that way.
(Chanmi meows.)
- Nice, nice.
- Woof, woof
Nice. Good.
We're on the same team.
(Jong Kook starts cheating again.)
- Go.
- Meow
Meow, meow!
(Don't you hear us meowing?)
(She hears her teammates meowing
and swings.)
- Meow
- Hey, wait.
- Move.
Hyejeong.
(Team Red's strategy failed.)
(She swung at Suk Jin's meows.)
How many times did we meow?
Hyejeong is a mess.
- This is a mess.
- Why did you hit...
when we meowed?
I have the result.
- I hope we're not in last place.
- Please.
Team Green...
earned two points,
- so they're first place.
- Our team.
They're first place?
We were the best.
We're second place then.
One team has minus 4 points,
and the other team has minus 5.
- That's right.
- It's close.
We're pretty close.
You never know.
The team in second
with minus 4 points is...
(The team in second
with minus 4 points is...)
Team Red.
(Team Red is the 2nd place.)
- Really?
- Thank goodness.
- We are the second place.
That was incredible.
We hit a lot.
There was a difference
of minus one point.
Thank goodness.
It was impossible to place first.
- It's a good result.
- That was incredible.
- Seriously.
- Okay. Good job.
Thus, we have
the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd places.
The 3rd place gets 1 meal ticket.
How beautiful!
It's the perfect place to visit
with the family.
(They enjoy the view of the sea
from the sea train.)
I will make sure I return.
Men and women of all ages
would like this place.
- It's the perfect spot for a date.
- Seriously.
You can sightsee
and eat delicious food here!
(He keeps overdoing it.)
The winter sea is pretty.
The winter sea is the best.
The winter sea is so pretty.
(The winter sea is so pretty.)
(So Min is an actress
who specializes in commercials.)
The winter sea!
Would you stand with Se Chan
and repeat what you said?
- Seriously.
- Stand in the middle.
Honey, the winter sea is so pretty.
Let's visit the next time.
You are already here!
What you said makes no sense.
Let's come back here.
Come back without the cameras.
Se Chan seems like
he is in his late 40s.
"Let's visit sometime."
Now, order the snacks
using your meal tickets.
Here you go.
- I want egg bread.
- How about one jjajang bingsu...
and three egg bread?
Then the person who can't eat
will receive a penalty badge.
- Oh, we can't share.
- No.
- Let's have one egg bread each.
- Okay.
- Egg bread is tasty.
- We will have one egg bread each.
One egg bread, please.
- One egg bread.
- Five egg breads,
one crunchy fried chicken,
and one jjajang bingsu.
We are rich.
They need to compete.
Let's decide who will eat.
That's right.
(Tapping)
(Let's play scissors.)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo also tells Jimin
to play scissors.)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(Don't let Haha know, okay?)
- One winner.
- That's right.
One person will avoid getting
a penalty badge.
- Rock...
- Who will get a penalty badge?
Who will get a penalty badge?
(What?)
(Is Haha signaling Kwang Soo
to play scissors?)
- Everyone else will get it.
Everyone else will get it.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(What will be the result?)
(Jimin plays scissors by herself.)
(The three of them agreed
to play scissors.)
(All of them play rock.)
- How did this happen?
- They are the worst.
(Didn't we agree to play scissors?)
- Jimin has the worst luck.
(Jimin suffers alone
amidst a bunch of tricksters.)
- Why didn't you play scissors?
- My goodness.
For goodness' sake.
You are the absolute worst!
Hey.
- You are irredeemable.
- Hey.
- Kwang Soo is the worst.
- You are irredeemable.
You are the worst.
- I am disappointed in you, So Min.
- You get exhausted...
when you are stuck with them.
- They are too...
- You pass out when you go home.
- They betrayed each other just now.
- They play dirty.
Who will eat the egg bread?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
For goodness' sake.
I am so upset.
Jimin, when you chose them
as your team members,
I wondered if you knew
what you were doing.
You chose the dirtiest ones
among us.
The three of them are the worst.
Rock-paper-scissors
Okay. Gosh.
(The three of them think alike.)
You guys are unbelievable.
For goodness' sake.
- For goodness' sake.
One person.
There is nothing beautiful about
the way they act.
I...
You lose if you don't play,
rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo wins in the end.)
Okay!
Rock-paper-scissors
(Okay!)
(Panting)
Kwang Soo won.
(He goes to get the egg bread
without looking back.)
He is the worst.
I will eat the egg bread.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
- The bingsu looks incredible.
That bingsu looks delicious.
Crunchy fried chicken is tasty
even when it's cold.
Mix it with chopsticks.
It looks delicious.
I wanted to eat ice cream.
Gosh, there is fruit.
It's really tasty.
(Delicious food impresses them.)
(The last dish)
It smells nice. I love egg bread.
Thank you for the food.
- It's tasty.
- It's so tasty.
It's warm.
- One is mine.
- How many is yours?
- One.
- You got it earlier.
- Kwang Soo, this is yours.
- Don't lie. You got it earlier.
Ji Hyo gave it to me.
(As she delivers the egg bread,)
(she takes her share.)
If you are going to do that,
what use are the rules?
- You care about the rules?
- I learned from you.
If you are going to eat
like an animal...
(Kwang Soo should think back
to how he was.)
I learned from you.
It's so tasty.
Kwang Soo has a lot.
(Let me take this!)
(She eats a piece
that flew towards her.)
Kwang Soo got betrayed.
(My hands move faster
than your eyes can see.)
(It's delicious.)
Peck at the food like a pigeon.
(So these are my team members.)
How tasty!
It's delicious.
- Let's move on to the last race.
- Okay!
(With zero trust for each other,
they move on to the last mission.)
- What are these?
- Grilled Spanish mackerel?
I want the twisted donut.
These are the last dishes
of Tasty Road in Incheon.
Grilled Spanish mackerel became
famous in Incheon 40 years ago...
because it perfectly suited
makgeolli that was produced nearby.
- Okay.
- There is a story.
There is also
the sweet and sour crab...
which is a dish
of fried soft-shelled crab.
Then there is
the bean powder twisted donut...
which is made in
1 of the top 5 bakeries in Incheon.
- It looks delicious.
- We must eat it.
- 1 of the top 5 bakeries.
The last mission you will do
to win these dishes is...
Heart Attack Survival.
(The last mission,
Heart Attack Survival)
At this place,
weapons are hidden.
Weapons?
If you find a weapon...
and touch another member,
a battle will take place.
If you win,
the other will be eliminated.
If you don't win,
the other will be given 10 seconds
to run away and find a weapon.
We need to find the weapons.
- This is a team battle, right?
- That's right.
Like earlier,
1st place gets 10 meal tickets,
2nd place gets 5 meal tickets,
and 3rd place gets 1 meal ticket.
We will have our fill today.
- You understood the rules, right?
- Yes.
- Move to your respective locations.
- Okay.
Take a hat each.
What will happen?
The race starts now.
- You are on your own.
- This is a team battle.
- Let's go!
- Firstly,
- We need to find the weapons.
- let's look for boxes.
- Yes.
I don't see the weapons.
I don't think they are here.
(Searching thoroughly)
It's here.
(It's here!)
(He finds a weapon box
behind a pavilion!)
(What's the first weapon
Jae Suk found?)
"Make the other laugh
in 30 seconds."
It's too hard.
"Make the other laugh
in 30 seconds" is too hard.
(Make the other laugh
in 30 seconds?)
When the battle begins, slap me.
(He asks his cameraman.)
I can't slap you!
This is for the mission.
Okay?
(He gets roped into it.)
(He spots someone!)
Haha!
I think he is going to attack me.
What?
(He touches Haha!)
- Come on.
- What's the weapon?
(What's the weapon?)
Let's go.
I need to make you laugh
in 30 seconds.
(I just need to suppress laughter
in 30 seconds.)
Okay? Get ready.
- Get ready.
- 30 seconds.
I feel like laughing already.
Hold on.
Get ready. Set, go.
Do it.
(Slapping)
(He stifles his laughter.)
One more time.
Hold on.
He laughed!
It doesn't matter if I laugh.
Do it one more time. Come on.
(He asks to get slapped again.)
Come here and slap me.
(Today, slapping Jae Suk
is his job.)
Slap me.
(Now, he slaps
even when he isn't asked.)
(Haha is barely suppressing
his laughter.)
(The angle becomes shaky.)
(His identity as a cameraman
becomes shaky as well.)
(Right now,
he is Jae Suk's assistant.)
How many times
do you have to slap me?
- Haha succeeded to defend himself.
- Okay!
- Run away.
For goodness' sake. Kwon Ryeol.
You should have slapped me,
not pushed me.
(I can't do that.)
You should have slapped hard
to make him laugh.
I would have laughed
if he slapped hard.
For goodness' sake.
(Another member is looking
for a weapon.)
What is this?
Who put this box upside down?
(He finds a box!)
My goodness.
I could really use a weapon.
(Have a ssireum match.)
"Make the other fall down first
during a ssireum match to win."
It's about ssireum.
That must be why
the box was upside down.
I knew I would find a weapon here.
Who should I take out?
(Now that he has a strong weapon,
he roams confidently.)
I see someone.
(He sees someone in the distance.)
(The back
of an unsuspecting member)
All right.
(Tapping)
He touched you.
(Me?)
- Go.
What is it?
Let's have a ssireum match.
(Would you like to have
a ssireum match with me?)
There is a ssireum field.
- Will you pick me?
- What?
I just touched you.
Let's move to the ssireum field.
Let's go and watch
the ssireum match.
I will die in vain.
It would be nice
to take Kwang Soo out.
He used to be
a professional ssireum player!
I have a bad knee.
(He used to be
a professional ssireum player.)
So which knee is it?
- You don't need to know.
- What?
You don't need to know.
It's this knee!
- He grabbed this knee.
- Stop it.
Kwang Soo, you never know.
- Ssireum is...
- Jong Kook.
not about force.
I don't even know
how to tie the thigh band.
Like this.
(He helps Jong Kook first.)
Hey.
(He pulls with his might.)
(This is playing hard to get
with the thigh band.)
- Are you in pain?
- Yes.
Are you in pain?
Please bow.
Play fair.
(Running Man supports fair plays.)
Don't put too much force.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Set, go.
(The match of the century starts,
but it has an obvious ending.)
He's done.
(This is actually a close match.)
Hey, gosh. Hey!
You can't do that
with the thigh band.
You can't do this
(The thigh band is too loose.)
Spread your legs out.
Spread your legs out by a lot.
- He'll lean back once you attack.
- You can do it.
All right.
- Hey.
- Good job.
(He pretends to do a major inner
reaping throw and hits Jong Kook.)
The major inner reaping throw
was not successful.
Wouldn't Jong Kook obviously win?
- Jong Kook!
I'm going to kill you.
(His beastly instinct has awoken.)
(He fixes his grasp
on the loose thigh band.)
Really?
Kwang Soo, this is not about force.
There you go.
(Jong Kook attacks,)
(but Kwang Soo defends.)
We have to win today, Kwang Soo.
I think he almost won.
(Kwang Soo attacks suddenly.)
(Ssireum is about skills!)
Oh, my!
(Jong Kook is a former wrestler.
Will he go down?)
(Kwang Soo collapses.)
(It was meaningless
to advance forward.)
(He got pinned down.)
Oh, my.
(That was exactly as predicted.)
Let's go.
- Good try.
- Great effort.
(That was a pathetic loss.)
- I did it.
- She did it.
- Push with your tongue.
- Up. Good job.
Her shoes are tight.
Oh, my.
Sorry.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
This is so good.
This is really good too.
The person
with most penalty badges...
and another person they pick
will get the penalty.
I really don't want it.
Currently...
(Who has
the most number of penalty badges?)
Jimin and So Min have
two penalty badges each.
(Jimin and So Min have
two penalty badges each.)
Everybody else has one each.
Last place has two?
Last place has two.
We have to decide the loser
between So Min and Jimin.
- Then...
- Should we do something?
- How about O-X?
- A lottery?
Let's do that.
That look was hurtful.
I'm curious.
1, 2, 3.
(The person with X gets the penalty.
Who will it be?)
(Jimin gets last place.)
This is unbelievable.
This is unbelievable. I'm upset now.
Jimin worked so hard today.
She worked the hardest.
Today's penalty is
colored whipped cream.
We added some coloring to it.
- There's coloring?
- What color is it?
Goodness, Jimin.
- Why are you being fussy?
- Are you the same age?
- No.
- She's older.
- She's younger.
- We call each other by name.
- We use names.
It's American style.
- That's cool.
- Like "Jimin" and "Yuna".
Dong Hoon.
So Min.
Suk Jin.
We should do that too.
This is not beneficial
to you either.
Jimin, pick one person...
- to receive the penalty with you.
- One person?
Jimin, who upset you?
Weren't you most upset
with rock-paper-scissors?
They agreed on it,
- but somebody changed their mind.
- Right.
You can go behind
and push one person's back.
- Shall I?
- Jimin.
- Why?
(Be quiet.)
- I got goosebumps.
- The person who gets pushed...
Oh, dear.
- What was that?
- You startled me.
Suk Jin, were you surprised?
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, were you surprised?
Hey!
Jae Suk,
Suk Jin was really surprised.
(His heart dropped.)
(He gets startled by little things
at his age.)
"Suk Jin was really surprised."
- Suk Jin, were you surprised?
- Jae Suk, don't do that.
- Suk Jin was really surprised.
- Suk Jin.
- Were you?
Those two can't laugh.
It's just them two.
while everybody else can.
- She won't pick her own team.
- There's no need to.
Will she pick us?
(Let's see.)
(Are we trembling?)
(She goes on her knees.)
So Min.
- I wish you a healthy life.
- You're not going on your knees.
- I'll go with Kwang Soo.
- No!
You're not going on your knees.
I'll go with Kwang Soo.
(I was going on my knees!)
I was going on my knees!
I was just going on my knees! Hey!
I'm so relieved.
Good thing I went on my knees.
So Jimin and Kwang Soo
will get the penalty.
- Jimin.
- Yes?
- Please say a few words.
- I had a lot of fun.
I'm happy all of us from AOA
was on Running Man.
That's true.
Please listen to "Come See Me."
- "Come See Me"!
- "Come See Me."
Here's the penalty. 1, 2, 3.
(With green whipped cream,)
(they become green monsters.)
- What is that?
- Hold on.
What is it?
What's this?
Is it Lady Yondu?
Look at this.
What is this?
(We have to take pictures of this.)
It's artificial grass.
- Leave, all of you!
- Artificial grass.
- Let's conclude. 1, 2, 3.
- You're a soccer field.
(The unparalleled top agents
are here.)
(World star Ryan Reynolds)
(Female action warrior
Melanie Laurent)
(Rising action star
Adria Arjona)
(They'll select Running Man members
who'll join the top agents.)
(They must stand out...)
(and join the top agent team.)
(Only confident candidates
should apply.)
(Some attack each other
to get recruited...)
(while some defend.)
(Which Running Man members
will become the top agents?)
(While they were having fun,)
(laughter turned into screams.)
I have to avoid the ghost.
(A dangerous ghost is
hiding among them.)
(The identities of the top agents
get revealed.)
(What secrets do these
suspicious top agents have?)
(Ghost Hunter Race)