Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
"The Don't Walk, Run Team " @Viki
[The landmarks central to the city]
[And]
[The unfamiliar landmark at night!]
[Now in the city at night, running man in action!]
Running Man's new rule. Once the entrance and exits close the mission begins.
Only the team that has managed to obtain a greater amount of prize money
by the next morning can escape.
There are two ways of earning prize money:
Win the game with prize money of ₩500,000
Find the golden pigs hidden in various places.
But they can only check how much is inside the pigs when they get to the escape gate.
Which team will collect a lot of prize money and escape?
[Mission start!]
[Running Man second landmark]
[Gross area of 420,000 square meters and 44,000 bleachers!]
[Extra large complex space: Suwon World Cup Stadium!]
[The amount of golden piggy banks they've acquired last week]
[The amount of piggy banks as of now]
[Another round to win golden piggy banks worth 500,000 won starts now, and the super express diving mission will also start]
Why do you keep taking off your clothes?
If you can't do that, you are not a man!
I am not a man~
[Haha (barely) succeeds diving 3.5m]
- It's ok, you can do it!
[One after another they appear. And now Running Man's official private investigator Joong Ki]
[Running Man, Fighting!]
[Home team: Song Joong Ki succeeds diving 5m]
Wait, if this happens, it's 3.5m vs 5.0m
Ji Hyo! We'll be so grateful even if you only dive 5m!
Let's go home early today!
Ji Hyo!
[Song Ji Hyo, with the dedication to escape succeeds in diving 5 meters]
- Hara doesn't have any fear!
[And now the competitive Hara]
[To win and escape, throw away your fears]
[Hara succeeds for 5m]
- Is it Gary's turn next now?
- It's Gary's turn.
[Locked in for 7 hours]
Is it Gary's turn now?
Yes, it's Gary.
Jump 5 meters!
[Gasp]
He looks so much like an old man.
I thought he was a staff.
[You can't tell what he is thinking, but]
[Still wears a peaceful expression]
[He needs to go for a lower diving point for our team to win]
Gary hyung!
[To 3.5m? Higher?!]
- It's dangerous.
- You shouldn't do that.
Gary, gary. Don't go up!
- Hyung, that's dangerous.
- That's not an easy height. That's difficult.
- So noisy!
[Gary arrives at the 5m diving board!]
You shouldn't do that.
You need to come off there.
I know your feeling.
- Gary you have to jump off from there.
- Is this scary?
Hey... how do you jump off here?
[But if it's for our team's success and escape!]
I just need to go one step forward, right?
Just one step!
[But taking one step forward off a cliff...]
Okay~
Good, good, good!
Hwaiting!
I'm on top of this world~
[Why a song all of a sudden?!]
And those who love me~
[Gary's people?]
- What are you doing, Gary?
I want to walk my PATH!
[Crooked?]
[While diving, he's heading into the surface of the water...?!]
[Gary 5m success!]
[His expression is always...]
[Calm~]
[Score right now: Home has 10m, Away has 13.5m]
We have to go even higher.
Go hyung!
[This time it's the home team's Ji Suk Jin]
Let's go hyung!
We'll win if we jump 5 meters or more.
Of course. Why are you stating the obvious, Hyung?
- I'll go for it.
- See, there's nothing to be afraid of.
[Diving 5 meters to get the 50,000 won!]
[No way...]
[Anticipating~]
[How high is he going?]
[Oh my! 7.5m?]
- Hyung! Come down from there!
- This is crazy.
[This is on another level...]
It's too high up, really.
Hold on!
I can't jump off...
[After he nobly comes up here, he becomes a coward(?)]
[Then to 5 meters?]
[Huh? Is he going lower?!]
[Surprised]
- Ah hyung!
It's 3.5m.
[If he dives 3.5 meters, then they'll be tied with the other team]
Oppa, 3.5 meters isn't right!
That's not it, that's not it!
3.5m! 3.5m!
Hyung! You have to jump at least 5m!
Jong Kook! I will trust you!
Jump 5m!
We believe in you hyung!
I want to just jump off this one!
Jump off 5m one!
Why get off 5m?
[Taken Back vs. Welcomed]
So cool.
Ji Suk Jin!
Ji Suk Jin! Ji Suk Jin!
[Cheering for the other team!]
- You have to jump the 5 meter one.
- No, this one is fine.
Hyung, didn't you see Haha jump? You're going to lose face.
No you won't, you won't lose face. Don't worry and just jump there.
It'll make us a tie.
- Go easy, hyungnim.
- Now, blue team.
- Blue team?
- Yes?
I am sorry.
[I am... sorry?]
[Oh my]
- I am sorry.
[Suk Jin, really?]
[Plop]
[Splash]
[Suk Jin succeeds with 3.5 meters]
[We're screwed vs. We did it]
[Already a victorious atmosphere]
[Incompetent...]
[Disappointed]
We're tied!
It's ok, we're tied! It's all thanks to Suk Jin.
That's a relief.
[What are you telling us to do...]
[Current score: Home team 13.5m vs. Away team 13.5m]
[Repositioning the chair for Big Hyung]
Ji Suk Jin! Ji Suk Jin!
Ji Suk Jin!
Loosen up.
[Glares]
[Chun Hee and Jung Kook VS. Jae Suk and Kwang Soo]
It's really, really scary.
[Jae Suk challenges it as both teams are tied]
[The perfect chance to widen the gap]
[Going to the dangerous diving board]
It's really scary...
[Beating heart]
[Kept going up]
[Jaesuk, arrives at 5m!]
Oh, this is no joke!
That's the 5 meter one!
Think about jumping off that, and go to 7.5m!
[Doesn't hear anything]
Oppa, do you have a freer(?) of heights?
What's a freer?
- Yes, I'm scared of heights.
[Embarrassed]
- 5m?
- 7.5m!
I said I can't!
[The scaredy cat MC Yoo can't help but flop down...]
The look on his face!
What's the difference between 5m and 3.5m?
7.5m is too high!
5m is okay, right? 5m?
[For vs. Against]
- What?
- It's fine but Jong Kook hyung is laughing.
I'm not laughing! What's up with you?
[Turns~]
Hold on, I will try going up just once more.
That's right!
[On their feet cheering]
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
Yoo Jae Suk!
[He arrived at the 7.5 meter platform but...]
- But 5 meters is too high, really.
It's too high up.
[Distant]
[Slowly, slowly]
[This is 7.5m!]
[In the end: U turn]
[Lost his mind]
- My mind, seriously...
[Relaxed opponent]
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
Why are you putting me in a difficult situation?
Hyungnim! Sing a song!
[Finally made up his mind]
- Oppa, fighting!
- Don't come.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Fighting!
[Focus of attention]
[What in the world. Jae Suk is challenging the 7.5 meter one?]
I'm really scared. I'm really scared but
- Hyung!
- Oppa! Do well!
That's not the image of you, hyung.
[If you want to escape here, you need to jump]
[7.5m that no one had challenged]
[Having two hands in a fist]
[Will he jump off?]
[Ah...]
[Failed 1st attempt]
Hyung, don't be pressured.
I will jump myself.
Hyung, you don't have to jump off there.
[Diving board height + Depth of the water= Height of 12.5 m]
Hyung! Not yet!
[Will he really jump off?]
Jae Suk, do 5m!
[Closes his eyes...]
[And thinking about it...]
[Flashback to 10 hours ago]
[Because of me, we lost a precious piggy bank...]
[The ambition he displayed in front of his teammates..]
[10 hours since they were captured inside...]
[I...]
[You guys...]
[I'll let you get out]
[I am coming]
[Escape the fear!]
[MC Yoo horray!]
[As soon as the two feet were let go, ]
[the fear and the tense feeling also went.]
[Jae Suk succeeds with 7.5 meters]
[Burden is on the last two members of the Home team]
Amazing. Amazing.
[They can never seem to understand the cool image
of their most scaredy cat member]
[Huh?]
[Your lips are going to rip apart~]
[Chun Hee's are also going to rip apart~]
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by " The Don't Walk, Run Team " @Viki
Oh, it's so scary. So scary.
[Like a grasshopper who died and came back to life]
He's so cool.
[Gold welcome]
[Takes back his glasses]
Go to the back!
[Those who jumped at a lower height are sent to the back!]
[He's calming down after sitting]
That was so scary.
[Current scores: Home: 13.5 meters. Away: 21 meters.]
[Home Team: Must jump more than 7.5 meters]
We're 7.5 meters behind now.
- You may all be surprised but Chun Hee will be challenging the 10 meter platform.
- What?!
[Next to start, Lee Chun Hee, 10 meter challenge?!]
Chun Hee!
I didn't say that I was going to jump from 7.5 meters.
[What are you telling me to do...]
Chun Hee, just go up first and take a look. After that jump at least 7.5m.
[The klutzy Chun Hee of the past, what will be his decision?]
[Shows his wrath for nothing]
[If he jumps from 7.5 meters, they will be tied. If he challenges 10 meters, it is possible for them to win]
One more! One more! That's right.
[10 meters in one shot?]
[He arrived at the 10 meter diving platform]
Just start from there! Run!
[Right here... Like this...]
Lee Chun Hee!
[It's high]
[Leaning flat]
[Peek~]
It doesn't make sense.
[Extremely high up]
Oppa. You're the first to go up 10 meters.
Hyung! It's like you can touch the roof!
If you jump from 10 meters, we will win.
- Do I have to jump from 10 meters for us to win?
- Yes~
But you have Jong Kook. Kwang Soo won't be able to jump from 10 meters.
If you jump from there, I'll give up.
- Chun Hee!
- Hold on!
I'll head down to check out 7.5 meters! I'm only going to check it out!
- Just go check it out.
[I know how 10 meters will be]
It's really high.
[Descending to 7.5 meters]
[Disappointed...]
[Arrived at 7.5 meters]
[Careful]
[It's not easy here either...]
Come down, come down!
Hyung, to make your drama a hit-
Chun Hee, come down...
Come down...
- Come down...
- Stay there!
You have to jump 10 meters. If you want to win, you have to jump 10 meters.
[Shu~]
[Chun Hee's fate(?)]
Confidently!
- It doesn't make sense that he comes down.
- Jong Kook hyung, I can't jump 10 meters.
[Burden on the last challenger]
[Home Team: Chun Hee -7.5 meters challenge]
- He's going.
- What do to about him?
He just needs to take one more step.
[There's nothing for me to back down on!]
[Jump]
[A new leap that will surpass myself!]
[A clean dive]
[Forget the Chun Hee of the past!]
[Dizzy~]
[Chun Hee succeeds with 7.5 meters]
- I should've jumped from the 10 meters one!
- We told you!
[The two teams are back to being tied]
- This is the last round, right?
[The people left are Kwang Soo VS Jong Kook]
- Say anything you want.
- Say anything and go up.
[His expression looks like he's about to cry]
- Say what you want and go up.
Kwang Soo, your mouth has opened too much.
Your mouth has opened too much.
[Go in the water...]
[Will the 500,000 won golden piggy bank go to the very nervous Kwang Soo?]
[The last player's huge burden]
Kwang Soo, that's not right!
That's not the platform!
[7.5 meters arrival!]
- That's not where you should jump.
- Now.
Kwang Soo, if it's not going to work,
it's not going to work!
If it's not going to work, then it's not going to work!
Jong Kook Hyung, why are you suddenly becoming talkative!
[Jong Kook has to jump more than Kwang Soo does to win!]
- If Kwang Soo jumps from there, Jong Kook will have to jump from the 10 meter platform.
- Let's think about it while talking.
- Wait a minute, Kwang Soo!
- It doesn't have to be like this.
- My bones are weak!
Kwang Soo, stay there!
[Delicate silhouette]
- Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo, that's not it. No, no, it's not it.
[Darkness before his eyes]
-That isn't right.
-Kwang Soo, you can do this!
- Kwang Soo you have to jump from there.
- You can do this, Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, don't jump from there!
[He went back...?!]
[It'll be a disadvantage for us if you go down...]
- Kwang Soo come down. That's right, Kwang Soo.
[Relief~]
- Kwang Soo, don't stay there. Kwang Soo!
[Wow!! He's going to the 10 meter platform?!]
[Surprise]
[Away Team: Powerful standing]
- Kwang Soo, no!
- Kwang Soo, don't give up!
[Kwang Soo arrives to the 10 meter platform]
[Stride by stride he goes to the front...]
- How can he jump from there?
Wow, it's really high up.
- Even I'm not going to jump from there, Kwang Soo.
[In order to escape he must jump 15m!]
Try stopping him!
Yeah, stop him and lose?
[Serious]
- Do you have confidence?
- Let's just cheer him on for now.
Fighting! Lee Kwang Soo, fighting!
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Will the timid Kwang Soo... gather the courage... for his team!]
If you're going to do it, do it with confidence!
[ No, please... ]
[At this time]
[Kwang Soo leaves without saying anything]
- That's right, just come down.
Kwang Soo!
[At this point, the jumping team apologizes]
We, I thought you were very good at swimming.
We thought it would be good to save you for last.
[Protecting the player before caring about winning or losing]
- We thought wrong. It's not your fault, so just come down for now.
It's not your fault.
[After going to the 10m platform on impulse]
[He arrives at the 7.5 platform again!]
[He still has a flushed appearance]
Kwang Soo, is the... is the 7.5 platform alright?
[That's... that...]
Why is he scratching his head?
[Agony]
[Kwang Soo also drops his hat]
[Shu~]
[Absent mindedly falls]
- Fighting!
Kwang Soo, it's impressive if you jump from the 5 meter one too. You can also jump from the 5 meter one.
Not there!
Kwang Soo, don't look in that direction. Don't look there.
[Nonetheless, his leftover feelings for the 10 meter platform...]
- Kwang Soo, don't look there. Don't look there.
Hey. Kwang Soo, don't look there.
[Both teams flustered]
[The leftover feelings keep...]
- We can lose this!
[Constantly obsessed]
[Can reach out and touch it]
Leave, Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo's confusing thoughts]
- Kwang Soo, don't even look in that direction.
- You still wanna do it?
[His heart sinks every time he looks at the 10m]
[Takes a look again]
[Should I jump... from 10 meters...]
- Kwang Soo, don't look there!
Kwang Soo! Don't look there!
- Don't look there!
Kwang Soo, don't even look there!
What exactly is he thinking about?
If you're not going to jump from there, just come down! Come down.
Come down, Kwang Soo.
[He's looking at it again...]
- Kwang Soo, don't look there! Come down.
[I want to win, but it's too high up there]
- Kwang Soo, don't look there!
Kwang Soo!
Don't look! Don't look there!
[Should I go up? Or should I just jump from here...?]
[To the timid me, someone give me an answer...]
- Camera, camera.
It's ok Kwang Soo!
- My ears hurt.
- But Kwang Soo, just know this.
Jong Kook Hyung felt scared a little just now!
- Kwang Soo, come down!
- After he looked at the 10m!
His heart just sank!
Kwang Soo, come down!
No, Kwang Soo!
[If that's so...]
- No, Kwang Soo!
- Come down, don't look there!
[Should I go to 10 meters...?]
- Don't, Kwang Soo!
[Kim Jong Kook Hyung...]
Kwang Soo, the camera. The camera is filming you.
Kwang Soo, come down!
Come down!
[Without a word, troubled for a long time]
- Kwang Soo.
-No, no.
[He's finally made up his mind]
- That's right. Just stay there.
You can come down more from there. Kwang Soo, you can come down.
- You can do the 5 meter one, we won't say anything to you.
- Of course, of course.
Earlier...
- I was going to tell you...
- Come down, Kwang Soo. You can come down.
Yes, yes.
[I got cut off again...]
Don't do it, Kwang Soo!
[Away Team: Kwang Soo, 7.5 meters challenge!]
- For me-
- There's no time.
Just looking at him is funny, right?
5...
4... 3... 2...
[Kwang Soo, let's go!]
- 1...
[It's okay even if it's not 10 meters]
[Frightened]
[Swept away all the conflict as to where he should dive]
[In the end... no one knows what he was thinking about from above...]
Kwang Soo...
You're cool.
[Aigoo]
- You were cool.
My friend, Kwang Soo!
[ 7.5m: Success ]
Are you alright?
Kwang Soo, I feel so touched.
It's 28.5 meters VS 21 meters now.
Whoa, seriously.
[Home team: Last starter, Jong Kook]
[He's going in the direction of the golden piggy bank with 500,000 won]
[100 times the burden]
[He has to jump from 10 meters to win!]
[Casually warms up]
[Dignified]
[The look of determination to win]
[Is he going directly to the 10 meter one?]
[Through 5 meters, to 7.5 meters...]
It's a really big problem! Really!
[Distressed Kwang Soo giving fear]
Hyung, for real, it's no joke. You'll get hurt.
[He arrives at the summit of 10m]
[It seems like he's on top of the world]
[Jong Kook and Joong Ki, who came out to support him]
[After really getting a look]
[Jong Kook is also on his hands and knees]
Should I come up?
[Welcome...]
- Hyung, it's really no joke up there.
[His image is dropping]
[Even after looking several times]
Hyung, it's really no joke up there!
Hey this is really a problem.
[The only person that went up when everyone else couldn't]
[Oh~ Slowly to the front!]
He's coming.
Kim Jong Kook!
[Never less, not an easy challenge]
Jong Kook!
You're Kim Jong Kook!
Hyung, I got it.
- You're a man, Kim Jong Kook.
- It's really high.
[It must be high up...]
Kim Jong Kook!
Oppa you can do this!
You can do it Jong Kook!
[Both of the teams forget about winning and offer support]
[He was seized with fear]
[However...]
- Let's go!
[In this moment]
[forget about escaping or winning]
[Forget about winning or losing]
[Just jump!]
[Vertical drop]
[Not an inch of disturbance]
[A perfect dive]
[Home Team: Jong Kook -Best result, 10 meters success!]
[He did it...!]
Kim Jong Kook!
[A real man, Kim Jong Kook]
The water also didn't splash a lot!
Your score is 9.9, Jong Kook! 9.9!
[Hyungnim, you're the best!]
This kind of thing is worth 9 points.
The water didn't splash at all when he went in.
[Luxurious diving: Like a national athlete ]
[Relaxed]
[What is up with that person...]
[Final results: Home: 31 meters. Away: 28.5 meters]
- Fighting, fighting, fighting!
If you were going to do this, you should've told me earlier.
[Ah... 10 meters...]
Daebak! You were really cool!
For this game, home team wins!
[Home Team: Wins! Gains ₩500,000]
[Up to now, count of the collected golden pigs]
[Locked in for 10 hours]
Everyone, it is from now.
- Everyone has slowly used up all their energy.
[After entering the water, everyone's faces looks exhaused]
Everyone, it's nearing 12 hours since you left your home.
It's been a bit rough on you guys.
[Facial expression in the morning when going back home! Right behind?!]
You know, the facial expression for when we go home is right behind there.
- Yes, really.
- It's right there.
I think it'll be a very delightful moment.
I hope it's our team!
What is it this time?
[Mission 6: Find the 5 golden pigs in the stadium!]
This time, you have to find the hidden golden pigs.
Do we start when you say go?
Hara, look here, not there.
Hara, you're on our side.
[A clue to find the piggy banks arrives]
[Go towards the place that was written by a citizen Lee Kwang Soo]
There are the names of Suwon citizens written underneath the seats of the stadium.
Oh!
Seat! Seat! Seat!
How can we find this?
Let's go out there.
We have to find the seat.
How can we find this?
[But... we have to rummage through all of this?]
- We have to have to search all this?
- It can't be helped. We have to find it.
[We have to rummage through 44,000 seats?]
Run up there!
Run! Run!
They say in running man you don't need just fast legs,
- you need to be able to think quickly as well.
- That's true.
There's also a possibility that it might not be in here.
[It's too huge! ]
- Jong Kook hyung and I will try searching.
- Okay.
[The home team splits up to search]
[Seat locations where the citizen's name is Lee Kwang Soo ]
[3 in the North, 1 in the South and 1 in the East]
[Underneath the chair with the name "Lee Kwang Soo"]
[Is the golden piggy bank!]
Look at all of the corners!
[Looking for 5 seats among 44,000! It's like searching for a needle in a haystack!]
How do we find "Lee Kwang Soo"?
How can you find "Lee Kwang Soo"... You would have to be familiar with this place to find it.
[You have to check the name on all of the 44,000 seats!]
It's not here.
[It hurts just looking at his back.]
How do you find it?
Did you find it?
You said that you found it?
No, I couldn't find it.
It was a lie!
Hold on. Is this Suk Jin hyung?
Yeah, it's me Suk Jin.
Why are you contacting our team?
Are you Jae Suk?
- Hyung, why are you contacting mine?
- It was a mistake.
[Slowly moving up north]
How do we find it?
That piggy bank will be wherever there is a Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Cho Su.
- I was taken by surprise.
[So close!]
[Gets lonely as he goes around]
Over there.
[The location of the first golden piggy bank]
[HaHa is approaching it!]
[It's a golden piggy bank!]
[Bingo!]
[He moves in for it right away!]
[Running]
What!
[HaHa acquires one golden piggy bank!]
He found it!
[Already 1! The away team is off to a good start]
You got one?
There's still 4 left!
Hey! The way I see this, why are we looking for the name? Just look for the piggy!
We can just look for the pig!
Pig! The pig!
[Now there are only 4 golden piggies left]
[Jae Suk and HaHa are moving towards the East side!]
[Chun Hee and Jong Kook are also following]
[The location of the second pig is on the second floor]
You couldn't find any on that side?
- You're Jae Suk!
- Hyung, who are you?
Why do you keep contacting me?
[Because I changed walkie-talkies earlier]
[Both teams are searching in the same area!]
HaHa!
- The second floor!
- Okay.
- Let's go up.
- The second floor.
Hyung! It could be upstairs!
[The home team also moves towards the second floor!]
[They searched all of the first floor and discovered one!]
When can we find all of this?
[The second floor is even more vast than the first floor]
[Joong Ki is also on the second floor]
[Panting]
[They've been at this since 3AM]
[Jae Suk is approaching the closest pig!]
[Huh? Did he give up?!]
[If Jae Suk just moves up a bit more, he can see it!]
- Huh?
[Panting]
[On the other side, Joong Ki is going even higher!]
[Huh?]
Come here.
What's up with him?
[What do you think...]
- He found it!
[Golden Pig]
[Those who missed it even though it was right in front of their eyes: Jae Suk and HaHa]
[Joong Ki acquires one piggy bank!]
[Home Team 1:1 Away Team]
[So close!]
You should have told me!
[You were tired so you sat down...]
[The location of the third piggy bank]
[Meanwhile, Ji Hyo is moving in towards the South]
[She discovers a piggy bank!]
I found it!
[Ji Hyo gets the third piggy bank!]
- She said she found it~
- Who?
- Ji Hyo noona.
- Really?
[At this rate...]
[The only place they didn't search is the second floor of the north section!]
[The remaining 2 pigs are on the second floor of the north section!]
- Here! Here!
- It should be around here.
[Phew~]
Haha.
Hyung, I'll try and go up.
[It's a matter of time as to when both teams will go to the second floor of the north section!]
[Chun Hee and Joong Ki arrive on the second floor!]
[Jae Suk gathers his strength once again and goes up the stairs!]
[The location of the closest piggy bank!]
[Chun Hee and Joong Ki are close]
[But still, if Jae Suk goes up higher he could also be the first one to see it]
[Who will get to it first?]
[Jae Suk is diligently at work]
[Again plunking himself down/!]
[Low stamina]
[Panting]
[Even the VJ responsible for Jae Suk is panting]
Chun Hee! Over here! Come over here!
- Over there! To the left!
[It seems like Joong Ki has discovered something]
The left!
[He discovers the 4th golden pig!]
AH!
We found it!
[Chun Hee and Joong Ki get the 4th golden pig!]
[And Jae Suk who was left behind missed it again]
We found it!
[Panting...]
[Even the VJ responsible for Jae Suk is panting!]
What am I supposed to do if you arrive this late?
[What a dream combination...]
Hyung!
Hyung! There's only one left now.
We're 2:2.
[The last piggy bank is on the second floor of the north section]
I feel like I'm dying!
[Jae Suk leaves the close piggy bank and goes far to search for it again]
[It could also be on this side]
We can clearly see it from up there.
[Both teams are almost near the piggy bank]
[ Oh? ]
[Ah!]
[The last golden pig]
Hyung!
[Runs]
[Kwang Soo runs at the speed of light]
[Heavens!]
[Kwang Soo overtakes him]
[ Ah~ ]
[Who will get to the pig first?]
[Grabs]
[Kwang Soo gets the last piggy bank]
[Blank...]
Yeah!
[The away team gets 3 out of the 5 piggy banks]
[ Race Over ]
[Jae Suk doesn't know the situation inside and keeps running]
Exercise!
We have to exercise!
They said they found them all~
They said they found them all.
You like it more than I do. They found them all but why do you like it more than I do?
Huh?
Why do you like the fact that they found them all more than I do?
[A dream combination! Now a sigh~]
You like it so much.
[A never ending moonlit race]
Whoo~
[Home team 2: 3 Away Team]
[The daybreak ends like that...]
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Everyone
ran well but
But the stamina of the VJ's and directors...
- are too weak.
- The thing is after I was going up,
He just stayed at the bottom and started filming a full shot!
And this person who ran around with me!
After a while
We should run till the end! But then he said
'Hyung! They said they found them all!"
And where is that audio director who went around with me? Yes, that person.
You're the audio director.
His audio and mine are overlapped.
Huk Huk Huk Huk!
I'm not even sure if we can use that footage!
- Everyone we have to do another game!
- Another one?
Let's go!
Cut!
[Even the filming has temporarily stopped, one man's difficult time is yet to be over]
- What the heck?
- How could you run so bad?
You can't even breathe properly right now. What are you going to do?
Are you going to the health club or not?
It could have been a problem! This can't happen. I'll take you to the health club.
- It's good to train your body.
- Look, you didn't even capture me on camera just now!
What are you doing? Look at this!
I'll take a look at this.
Is it ok to end it? The others are shooting right now!
[Uncomfortable]
You have to film these things well.
I know it's a difficult job.
It started to get exciting around the 20 minute mark.
Up until here his breathing is alright.
Why are you filming Lee Kwang Soo?
Why did you film Lee Kwang Soo after filming me?
Kwang Soo!
[The VJ who is tired of running after Jae Suk]
[Just starts filming Kwang Soo who is next to him!]
He's filming another person!
Look at this! This is when I appear!
Look at all of this.
We went up to there.
This is when things start getting weird.
Why are you filming Chun Hee too?
You should film me!
Seems like he's following Chun Hee.
Where am I?
[Damn! Almost all of it is of the ground]
[Jae Suk]
[Because I couldn't follow you, I zoomed in!]
Jong Kook! It was difficult because of this friend.
This is where his comment comes out. Because he was so tired.
They said they found them all, Hyung
Huk Huk Huk
"They said they found them all hyung"
- It wasn't me, it was him.
- This person!
- Really?
[That time was so tiring]
Anyway, I'll take you to a health club.
Let's go to a health club.
[To our staff as well! Don't walk, run! Running Man!]
[The amount of golden pigs collected so far]
[Locked up for 11 hours]
[Now another game in which they can win ₩500,00 ]
Hello, viewers!
I'm Yoo Jae Sook from telepathy studio.
Hello, I'm Ji Suk Jin.
Today we're going to talk about the break door outdoor variety.
For the second time, Ji Suk Jin.
Hello.
- Hello.
This is your second time filming this show. How is it?
- After the first recording, I passed out when I got home.
- Yes.
But now, I can endure it.
- Okay.
- If you don't like that answer then please tell me!
- Can I really say it?
- Sure.
- Just a little!
- Okay.
What kind of game are we playing today? Why don't our telepathy guest of the day Ji Suk Jin explain?
First off, you have to wear headphones.
- We already have ours on.
- Right.
-You wear these
- You will be able to hear really loud music.
- Right.
When you're listening to the music, one person has the question sheet.
And one person has the answer sheet.
Choose one question from the question sheet and one answer from the answer sheet.
If they don't match then you lose
If they don't match, then you would lose.
- The prize is ₩500,000, correct?
- Yes, ₩500,000.
That's good. Can both teams enter?
Come in!
They're coming in here so chic.
Go hara, Chun Hee, Jong Kook and Joong Ki.
Did you take a look at their expressions?
Ji Hyo, HaHa, Gary and Lee Kwang Soo are also here.
And our telepathy show will be broadcasted all over the world.
- Yes.
- Let's give this a try.
Let's start with Kwang Soo.
- Fighting!
Let's begin.
[There is music already coming out from the headphones]
- Jae Suk, can you hear?
- I'm ready!
Start!
[The question sheet and answer sheet]
What were Napoleon's most famous words?
[This is the answer]
Lend me 4,000 won!
- Napoleon's famous words?
- Lend me 4,000 won!
Do you remember the catchphrase Nan Da Kim had on a comedy show?
In the name of justice, I can't forgive you!
Do you remember the catch phrase Nan Da Kim had on a comedy show?
Can you recite with strong feelings, one of the lines from hamlet, one of the tragedies written by Shakespeare?
Eureka!
What do ginseng seekers say when they find ginseng?
I'm still hungry.
Please tell us the chorus from Song of Cheongsan that was written in the Goryeo dynasty.
Quit acting cool! You're not even good looking!
The words they say in Sailor Moon when they transform?
Yalala Yalala Shong Yala Yala
[When Sailor Moon transforms]
In the fairytale "The Sun and the Moon" what does the tiger say to the mother when she sells rice cakes?
To be, or not to be. That is the question.
To be or not to be. That is the question.
A line from one of Shakespeare's tragedies?
If you give me one rice cake I won't eat you!
- Your name is?
- Eureka!
[Time Out]
Wow! This is!
[Since they couldn't hear each other, they don't know if they got it right or wrong]
- We didn't even get one?
- You didn't even get one.
It was really fun!
- It was really fun!
- Then that's fine, I guess.
- Ah so funny.
- We didn't even get one?
Kwang Soo, you were hilarious.
"Your name is eureka!"
Ok, now it's Hara and me.
Fighting.
[Putting on the headphones with the loud music]
Start!
What are you feeling right now?
My insides are gonna explode!
[It makes sense but unfortunately it's not the right answewr]
What do you think when you drink too much alcohol?
I want to throw up!
What would you feel if you pulled an all-nighter?
Ah, I'm tired.
[They already have two questions correct!]
- How would you feel if you got into a scandal with no proof?
- I stepped in poop!
I stepped in poop!
You just ate a lot of good food! What would you say?
My stomach is going to burst!
If someone is abusing someone in a public place, what do you think?
Ah so cute! I want to bite you!
What would you say to the person who farted in the elevator?
Awesome!
[Time out]
[They've answered four questions correctly]
Wow!
You got 4 right!
Woah.
Gary says the answers.
[Kwang Soo and Gary]
And Kwang Soo will read the question. We'll do it one more time.
Fighting!
- Gary! Say it with a loud voice.
- Okay.
Gary I have more faith in you than I have in Kwang Soo.
[Because it's dawn, he's stuttering]
- I have a feeling this is going to be really funny.
[They can't hear each other. They decide on a sign beforehand]
Let's do this.
Okay, Ready... Start!
What are you going to say to your friend when you need to borrow money?
Give me back my leg!
[Saying "Give me back my leg" when you want to borrow money...]
- In Song Dae Kwan's "Popular Song" what is the popular verse?
- So noisy!
- When you're arguing with someone and you're really mad, what would you say?
- Prosecute him!
What is the most famous congratulatory greeting for a wedding?
Hang up! If you find it, it's one for 10 won!
If you find it, it's one for 10 won!
- In the drama "The Trap of Youth" what did Shim Eun Ha say when she was getting revenge?
- Kungkungdari kungkungdda
Kungkungdari kungkungdda
Shock!
What do you want to say to people who talk a lot like Yoo Jae Suk Ssi?
Give me some money.
- When you're arguing with someone and extremely mad, what would you say?
- I will destroy you!
- In hometown legends, which lines come out the most?
- So noisy!
- What do the policemen say when they've captures a criminal?
- I curse you!
- In Song Dae Kwan's "Popular song" what is the popular lyrics?
- Because of you I can't accomplish anything!
- In college times in the street alleys what do the scary sunbaes say the most?
- Give me back my leg!
[Time out.]
[Away team, zero points]
So the most popular phrase among college these days is "give me back my leg."
No wonder I heard it so many times.
You should say it in a loud voice.
[Dumbfounded]
- Let's do well!
- I think we work well together.
-I[Home Team: Joong Ki and Jong Kook]
- Yeah, that's right Joong Ki.
- Jong Kook, your shoulders are too narrow.
It's not like this originally. What's up with this?
Do it in a loud voice! Loud voice!
So you can't hear?
Ready... Start!
What do you want to say to the person you hate?
Constipation!
- What do you want to say to the person you hate?
- Constipation!
[To the person you hate... constipation?]
What do you call it when your face is red and crumples up due to your inability to poop?
Cow!
Hyung, this is a very famous proverb.
What are you deprived of and need to fix the stable?
A Mongolian spot!
[You are deprived of a Mongolian spot and you should fix the stable!]
- It's a proverb saying that we need to be careful about everything.
What do we need to tap on to cross over?
Rice cake!
- They didn't even get one right.
- What is the reason for Jong Kook's crazy workout routine?
Fart!
[Jong Kook has been hiding it all this time...]
[But he works out so hard because of farts...?]
You meet someone after a long time but you forgot their name. What would you say in place of their name?
Muscle!
When your insides aren't good,
what is the gas that your body lets out?
A stone bridge!
- We did it!
- What are the spots that appear on new born babies?
Constipation!
[Time out]
- That's good!
- Hey!
Hey! How could you be deprived of a Mongolian spot and fix the barn?
You didn't get any of them correct.
So for this telepathy game,
the home team wins!
[The home team wins and gets ₩500,000]
- Whoa.
[The amount of golden piggy banks acquires so far]
Entrances and exits are locked.
- I found it!
[The amount of piggy banks the team has acquired so far ]
[The amount of money they've collected from the piggy banks: Home team: ₩150,000 and ₩100,000]
[In order to escape, they've been fiercely running for 13 hours!
[And finally, the ₩500,000 final mission!]
[Been locked up for 13 hours]
[Both teams enter the interior]
Come in. Come in.
[The last game will be spread out in this place?]
- Put it here.
- Please be careful.
But indoors is much better than outdoors.
- So they come in here to warm up.
[This is a warm up room. The players come in here to warm up before every match.]
The athletes need to warm up before any competition or practice.
But we already warmed up a little outside, why are we here to sweat in here?
Hara has been having a lot of schedules in Japan. You must be really tired right now.
- No.
- Though there isn't any one of us who has had a busy schedule like Hara.
[Mr. Suk Jin] What are you doing tomorrow?
I'm resting.
[A very productive(?) schedule of Suk Jin.]
Hara really hasn't looked at Suk Jin not once.
- She doesn't even take one glance at you.
- That was hilarious.
Hey, I can draw the back of your skull.
I can draw the back of your skull.
- Hey, you seriously.
[Suk Jin is looking at the back of Hara's head.]
One team will have a goal keeper hanging from the pole, the other team will try to score.
Each member needs to try to make a goal. Who ever has the most goals wins.
So, this game is simple isn't it?
[The goal keeper is extremely important.]
Haha wont be able to block anything under it.
- How much longer are you going to poke fun at my height?
[Very sensitive talking about his height.]
Then shall we talk about your girlfriend?
Then do you not have a girlfriend?
- While I know everything.
[Haha vs: Jong Kook. Which an unseasonable heated battle]
You have a girlfriend too!
- Hey!
[In a fit of rage]
- Am I wrong?
- Just stop it.
Seems like you had a bad break up?
Even though two people keep going back and forth at it,
We know what we need to know. It's not something we don't know.
But, Haha are you really okay?
Are you annoyed?
- Your tone of voice...
[An annoyed tone]
Why? This is originally how I talk!
[Who was Jong Kook's girlfriend?]
[I don't know.]
Suk Jin, just said. "Excuse me but who was his girlfriend?"
- Why did you say that to Hara?
- Well.. Because she's an idol.
[The man in his 40's is curious about celebrity talk!]
- Jong Kook
- I thought Hara would know.
The first round is for a minute.
We'll count how many goals we get in. We really have to win this time.
[Which ever team makes the most points wins.]
So does your team
- want to block first?
- No, we're going to kick first.
[He's not being fooled]
- We want to kick first.
- You think really quickly.
Your friend over there doesn't seem to know.
[The friend who doesn't know.]
Suk Jin wasn't fooled.
He's a person that came out on Sparta season 2.
[SpartaKook?]
He came out on Sparta season 2.
Okay, we have chosen our first goal keeper. It's Lee Kwang Soo.
[Away team's goal keeper Lee Kwang Soo.]
This is a hard ball.
Hey, Kwang Soo
Kwang Soo block it! Fighting!
[So long...]
Kwang Soo, fighting!
[The dignity of a 190 cm person]
Ready, go!
[Home team round one start!]
[Blocked it!]
That's good!
Ah!
[Even the second player Joong Ki fails]
Come out! Run!
[They've been overpowered by his height? They still haven't made one goal yet!]
They haven't even made it one goal!
[They're running about in confusion]
[Did he block it?]
[Goal!]
[Finally, this is Jong Kook's first goal!]
[Did he catch it?[
[The good blocker Kwang Soo!]
It's blocked!
[Hits.]
[Hits him.]
Ah what?
Catch the ball!
[Hits.]
Hey what?
Just a minute.
[Hara makes the next goal for the home team!]
- That's good.
[This time SukJin makes the third goal!]
- Hyung, this is so hard.
- I know.
[Home team has succeeded, making three goals.]
How much was that?
- That team kicks really lousy, don't they?
- Yeah.
[Home team's goal keeper is JoongKi.]
We shouldn't kick like that.
- One by one.
- How are you going to kick?
- We're going to kick one by one.
- Really?
- We're going for it!
- The bottom.
We're going for it!
- The bottom is too empty.
- Start!
- One by one.
- Slowly.
[Did he block it?]
Wow!
[Goal!]
[Short! Just passed through~]
[Gary also shoots in the same way]
[KwangSoo's legs are bottomless so he could prevent goals.]
[Flower boy JoongKi's humiliation.]
[The size difference.]
We won!
[Away team has successfully made 4 goals.]
[Home team 0, away team 1.]
- How about we go for a total?
- What kind?
The total points. Anyway, if we win we'll have to do it one more time.
- [In informal speech] We have to do it one more time.
- Excuse me
- We should speak more formally.
- Okay
[You spoke too informally]
- It's ok, it's nothing.
[Suk Jin quickly acknowledges it]
- It's because I'm a bit impatient.
- Yes, even though you're a hyung.
Although in variety shows these days we do speak comfortably, it was a bit weird when you did it.
I always feel this. That you guys are really close.
Besides me, you all look really close.
So what do you think we should do?
Let's kick ten balls.
- 10.
- Let's go with 10.
If both teams end up in a tie,
then Joong Ki and HaHa will go at it(as a goal keeper) one more time.
- Hyung, I'm tall.
- I know.
[The excited flower boy Joong Ki]
- I'm taller than this hyung!
- I know.
[He doesn't like the thought that he's a same height as HaHa]
Joong Ki, you're not that tall.
Go and compete Joong Ki.
[Round 2 start!]
- Ready..
- KwangSoo Fighting!
[This time again KwangSoo is the goal keeper.]
[The first kicker is Jong Kook]
Start!
[As expected, a jam packed goal post]
- 10?
The direction. Think about it.
There's also speed.
[Kim Jong Kook fails.]
Kwang Soo fighting!
- His legs are longer than we expected
- Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, I like what you're doing.
[The next kicker is Song Joong Ki.]
Kwang Soo is good.
Okay!
[He powerfully gets a goal!]
[Just wait and see...]
Look at where he got it in.
To get a goal from there is hard.
[The fact that he was able to make it in between his two arms makes it even more fascinating]
How many is that?
Fighting!
[The course where he can block it?]
[Suk Jin gets a clean goal!]
Wasn't that cool?
[That was funny...]
[This time it's Hara's turn.]
- That's it! That's it!
- Ah!
[Ah! It could've been a goal...]
That's it! That's it!
[Extremely fortunate]
Now, the last one.
[The last runner: Chun Hee]
Do it slowly.
[Take this!]
[I can block it!]
[It went in!]
-3 of them didn't go in!
- That's okay.
[The second round is complete. The Home Team succeeds in getting 7 goals]
- Wow, a lot of it went in.
- It's okay.
Cheon Hee fighting!
[This time Cheon Hee is the goal keeper for the home team.]
[Chun Hee dangling on there is also imposing]
It looks like Lee Chun Hee is just a little bit shorter.
- He's just a little bit short.
[Narrowly doesn't touch the bottom]
[Away team, round two start!]
[This time Haha starts first.]
Ah!
[He shoots with his strong right leg!]
- Gary
- Gary fighting.
[Up next is the trendy rapper Gary]
[This time it's mainstream rapper Gary.]
[Gary also succeeds.]
That was good!
[That's strange]
[Delicate two legs, small hearted, Lee KwangSoo.]
- Kwang Soo, you can do it.
- You can do it.
[I'm just going to block you!]
[Oh!]
[He blocked it!]
[The Klutz wins!]
[This time it's MC Yoo.]
Don't do it.
[First his body, then the goal post. No goal!]
[The shining star goal keeper CheonHee.]
- Wow.
- Yay!
[However in a while...]
Chun Hee is losing his strength.
Chun Hee lost his strength.
Isn't this even more difficult?
[Tearing scissors?]
He's out of it already.
Gary! This is your chance!
The last kicker is going to be Ji Hyo.
[He coolly succeeds]
[Floundering]
[Hot on their trail!]
- Chun Hee!
- Just block one!
All you have to do is just block one.
I have been blocking it.
- If Ji Hyo gets it in we have a tie..
[If Ji Hyo succeeds then it will be a tie.]
If Ji Hyo gets it in then we'll have a tie.
- Fighting!
- Let's do this.
[The Away Team's fate is up to Ji Hyo's feet]
[Chun Hee is also turning over a new leaf... Huh?]
[Klutz]
Can't we change the goal keeper?
We all have the same circumstances.
I'm going in like this!
It can't be helped.
We have the same circumstances!
- Was it slippery earlier?
- I also did it like that, hyung.
- It could be slippery.
- Good.
[Slips~]
- It could be slippery.
- Good.
[It's been a while... Chun Hee's signature body gag!]
[Can the game end...]
- Good.
- This seems slippery.
[He did grab on to it...]
- The last ball.
- That's it!
[Surprised]
That's good Ji Hyo.
[You're doing well Ji Hyo]
That's it!
[Argh!]
[Shoots right away]
[5 goals in a row? If she succeeds it's a tie!]
[Legs! I'm believing in you!]
[Did he block it?]
[Song Ji Hyo makes a goal!]
- You could have just blocked one!
[A dramatic tie]
[Breakdown]
[The home team who won all the games lost because of Chun Hee]
- That's great.
- No way.
Bravo.
- Since we have a tie
[The revival of the away team]
Both teams will be kicking five balls.
[Both teams kick 5 balls and whoever gets the most balls in wins]
You just have to kick it.
- See how many goes inside.
- If it comes out then it doesn't count. Right?
- It just has to stay inside.
- It just has to stay inside?
-Of course.
- For example
- Why are you saying an example?
- Let's quickly get this started.
[Embarrassed]
- It's so hot.
- Show it by lifting it up.
Lift it up. Ok?
[As expected from the king of adlib]
- Okay? Lift it up.
- We got it.
[Hyung, I respect you]
- HaHa and Joong Ki.
- Joong Ki?
- Just once.
- Yes, just once.
-Why do I feel like we'll lose?
He's at least a thousand times better than HaHa.
- Seriously.
- Hyung!
So is Jong Shin hyung a point?
- Am I a point?
[In banmal: A point?]
You guys look very close.
You guys are fighting so you guys must be really close.
- Can I be on friendly terms with you too?
- Let's get on with it!
- Come out secretly.
Hurry and go.
It's important if it goes inside or not.
Hey!
Control! Control the balls that are going inside!
[I will block them all!]
[Out of the 5 balls, how many will go inside?]
- That's it!
[Oh...?]
[Away team gets 4 balls in]
- That's it!
[They all almost hit the bulls eye underneath his legs]
[It looks like the Away team will win!]
- Joong Ki.
[Mom's friend's son: Joong Ki's humiliation]
Comparing you to HaHa makes you sad, right?
Start from here and kick like this. Practice.
- No, we're good. We can do this.
- Try this.
Try this. Practice.
- Just go forward!
[It's high]
Don't worry about HaHa. Just think about it as vacant!
[It is very much vacant...]
Look there's no one there.
- HaHa is right there!
[Where did you go...]
Don't you see him?
HaHa, raise your hands!
- He's right here!
- It seems as if no one is there.
He's in there right now.
- Is it capable of CG?
- Get it in.
- 1,2
- Slowly.
3!
[4 people shoot at the same time!]
[I'm here!]
[Even with his shoes]
[One of them hits the goal post and comes out]
[Joong Ki shoots a step late]
[If his shot gets in then it's a tie!]
[Can HaHa defend well!]
[The goal that will determine the home team's fate!]
[Hits]
[Home team only get 2 balls in!]
[HaHa! We won!]
[Third round over: The away team wins]
[Devastated]
We won! We won!
[MVP is HaHa]
No way.
- There was HaHa!
[Home team is feeling so frustrated that they can't even move]
- There was Haha!
- I thought about it as no one was there!
[Words of the Day: There was HaHa]
Away team wins!
[Home team 4:3 Away Team]
[Breaks down into tears]
Is it Park Ji Seong and Guus Hiddink?
Get down.
You don't have to go that far.
I know you're happy but you don't have to go that far.
I'm so happy.
[It's been 17 hours since Running Man has been confined in Suwon World Cup Stadium]
[The morning is bright]
[However, there is only one team that can get out from this place!]
- It's time.
- It's time. It's morning.
[The last moment]
There's a team that will stay and a team that can escape.
Didn't forget, right?
I really want to win.
- I want to get out of here.
- I'm so desperate to win.
- That's what everyone wants, right?
- Yes.
[The Sun has already risen]
[The citizens have also started their morning]
The prize money is the same.
Yes, the starting money is the same. ₩ 1,500,000
₩ 150,000,000
This is good. I see hope.
[The first piggy bank contains ₩500 coins]
₩ 1,800,000!
[Another piggy bank contains ₩100 coins]
₩ 1,9000,000!
Wow, these are ₩100 coins.
[Their piggy bank has ₩100 coins]
They get ₩100,000!
[This time it's ₩500 coins!]
[They get ₩320,000!]
[They get ₩10,000]
[If that's the case]
There is a ₩30,000 difference!
This is our last piggy bank.
Please be ₩500 coins.
They're ₩50 coins.
[Their last piggy bank has ₩50 coins...]
[Are they a step closer to escaping?]
There's fairly a lot going in there!
[It keeps pouring out!]
Wow, that's really a lot.
[₩100,000!]
[Their total is ₩2,000,000!]
Wow. ₩2,000,000.
Please!
- Let's just leave it like this.
- I have a good feeling.
Hold on.
Yay!
[Their last piggy bank contains ₩100 coins!]
- Let's try it. [But they don't know how how many coins are in there]
[Can they overcome the ₩70,000 difference?]
To get ₩70,000 how many do we need?
[They need to get 700 ₩500 coins to surpass them]
[There's 500 of them!]
[680!]
[Oh?]
[They get 700!]
[The home team makes a last minute turn around!]
[They get a total of ₩2,030,000]
[The joy and sorrow of a ₩30,000 difference]
[The home team succeeds in escaping!]
[Surprised]
- I'm going.
[The gates that have been locked are now being opened.]
You did a good job.
[Go...]
[Since they're left, they have a penalty!]
[Going to the outside world they haven't seen in 17 hours!]
Wow fresh air.
[The escape ceremony]
[Yeah~]
[Free from all thoughts]
[A little while later]
[Today's penalty: Giving away free coffee]
[Filthy]
[Couldn't wash for 17 hours]
- Hello. -Please have some.
- Coffee. [Found their first person going to work.]
- I'm sorry...
[Struggling]
I'm sorry...
We've been up all night.
- Have a wonderful day.
- Fighting.
You should say "Have a nice day" a bit brighter.
"Have a nice day."
[A bright greeting with a ragged look.]
- Hello.
- Please have a cup of coffee.
Please have a cup of coffee.
We aren't asking for money.
[Timid Kwang Soo kindly follows her]
[To the employees that are going to work]
[Now moving the stand to the office!]
- Would you like a cup of coffee?
- Please enjoy it.
Oh.. Please send me home.
Oh, you're left here.
[Who is left?]
[It's the low stamina VJ responsible for filming Jae Suk]
[Next Land Mark!]
[The museum is alive!]
[The national science museum]
[They'll wake up the sleeping museum with Jessica and Nickhun]
Oppa! Oppa!
[The hurdles are getting upgraded more and more!]
[What happened to them?]
[The museum is really alive!]
[August 1st at 5:20 PM]