Timing and Subtitles brought to you
by the Don't Walk, Run! Team @ Viki
City Center
Landmark
[ And ]
[ The unfamiliar landmark at night! ]
Now in the city at night
Running Man in action!
A new concept action variety show!
You can't imagine
Their night...
Will be revealed now!
Running Man
Some night on June 2010
A car approaching SBS
and one person coming out from the car
Kyaaaa!
What is this?
Yoo Jae Suk
Opening Mission: Find the newly
reconstructed rooftop garden
Yoo Jae Suk's current location: 8th floor
Rooftop Garden: 9th Floor
The rooftop garden is located on the 9th floor...
but Yoo Jae Suk got off on the 8th floor
Hello!
The security guard on patrol
Where is the rooftop garden?
How do you get there?
Nervous
If you could please tell me
how to get there...
I heard there's a variety show...
That's right.
Nice to meet you!
I have to get back to work.
Are you just going to leave without
telling me how to get there?
Will I appear on the show by any chance?
Will it come on screen?
If it's not interesting,
it'll be edited out.
At this time, two cars arrive
Haha
Kim Jong Kook
Hello, long time no see!
Cars continue to arrive.
These guys are...?
Their first meeting...
Their first meeting
Will they be able to find it?
[Heliport]
I think it's here... it's here.
Rooftop garden?
Ah, it's right here.
Jae Suk finally succeeds
in finding the rooftop garden
Jae Suk slowly enters!
Why is it like this?
Lost
Eh? It's like this again...
Here at SBS's 9th floor, the rooftop garden
Do I just stand here
until everyone gets here?
I said, do I just stand here
There they are, they're here!
Running Man's Kim Jong Kook & Haha
Ah! Jong Kook and Haha!
Come here quickly.
A sudden formal greeting...
Don't do that!
Haha, I said, don't be like this!
It's embarrassing...
That friend?
Kwang Soo...?
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
He's tall
- Please move over...
Haha hurriedly moves away from his spot.
No, no move back.
My leg hurts...
Please get up.
He bends over to greet him...
mannered Kwang Soo.
[If his legs are apart, their heights will match.]
First of all, the title of this show is...
Running Man
Don't walk, Run. This is something very...
- Isn't it Health Man?
- No, it's not.
A handsome silhouette never seen before!
Firstly... Oh... Song Joong Ki.
Actor Song Joong Ki
Drama: Obstetrics and Gynecology Doctors Newcomer
who have been attracting a lot of attention lately.
Hello.
The pretty boy with a beautiful smile.
He's even wearing
a flower brooch for the opening.
Ah, for the opening.
Flower... brooch?
Charisma
- Someone else is coming...!
Ah! Joong Ki.
Oh, Gary!
Hip-Hop Musician LeeSsang's Gary
Gary...
The star behind many hit songs,
LeeSsang's Gary
Aren't you Jung Dae Sae?
Soccer Star Jung Dae Sae
Hip-Hop Star Gary
Aren't you looking good? Jung Dae Sae.
Ah, yes.
He looks good but funny some how
Yo~ What's up?
The rappers and
their hip-hop style of greeting
Oh!
Your breast is too big, man!
His breast is too big.
Pants, pants.
Firstly, Gary, also, Joong Ki and Kwang Soo,
nice to meet you guys.
However, it's raining.
We can't help but continue to get wet.
Are you alright?
[Again, who is this...? Walking in the rain!]
I'm alright.
[Again, who is this...? Walking confidently in the rain!]
Oh!
Hello, Hyungnim.
[20 years of variety, Ji Suk Jin]
Hello.
I know Suk Jin hyung very well.
[Very forthright, like a big brother...]
This hyung is very nervous now!
[He feels extremely nervous because
he is coming on an outdoor variety show?]
Although he seems very natural,
he is actually very nervous right now.
- Yes, its been a long time since I've been out of the studios.
- Is this your first time meeting...
[Since 2003, this is his first time in an outdoor variety show]
- Joong Ki today?
- Yes.
[This time, it's a female figure?]
Ah someone's coming.
Oh.
[Confident
[Confident, sexily walking towards us
with her head up high...]
[Her first sentence is...?]
Give me an umbrella, umbrella!
Ah, Hyori!
Ah, seriously.
I was told that I'm the special invited guest,
how can you let me get wet?
Tonight's main character.
Ah, is that so?
[Tonight's main character]
I'm the main character for today?
[Running Man First Guest, The invincible, Lee Hyori!]
Please wait.
My mascara is dripping.
Where? How?
- Where is it that you don't want to get wet? Your shoulders, or?
- My eyes.
- Ah, eyes.
- Yes.
To begin a show, this way isn't bad.
- I especially drew my eyeliner thicker today.
- Ah, yes.
[Again, another back view of a lady...?]
Coming, someone is coming!
[She who came here
listening to the little rain...?]
Aiyooo~
Hello.
- Aiyoo, Jung Eum!
- Jae Suk oppa!
[Running Man First Guest
The refreshing Hwang Jung Eum!]
It's seems like it's been a while
since meeting with an audience.
Don't walk, run! Running Man! Hello everyone!
[Sunday night, New Variety Show!]
We'll start one by one.
[Beginning with a simple self-introduction]
Since this is the first show, please do a brief self-introduction and greeting.
Starting with Ji Suk Jin.
Hello.
You all know me right? I'm Ji Suk Jin.
[Hm? The rain starts to pour...!]
Ah, it's raining hard!
Why did it start when I'm talking?
I've done many variety shows, but I've never
had openings where it rained like this.
They say it's rainy season!
Bad luck rain!
[It's been fine all day
and suddenly it rains]
This won't really do!
Hyungnim!
[Suk Jin walked over to get a raincoat...]
Hyung, you can't do that.
No hyung, you can't do this outside...
What are you wearing that for?!
Ah, I really haven't been
outside for a long time.
[So no raincoats?]
We'll finish this quickly from now on.
- Joong Ki.
- Yes.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello. I'm Song Joong Ki. I was born in 1985 and I'm 26 years old this year.
[Like a blooming flower, Song Joong Ki]
[Cute] Here it seems like Kwang Soo
and myself are the maknaes (the youngest).
I'll work hard with the hyungs (what boys call older boys).
Fighting!
Next up, our Kwang Soo!
Hello.
[Soaked]
I'm Lee Kwang Soo.
[Suddenly, the rain pours]
Why did it get so bad from the start!
[I can't see...]
I...
I... am a sprout!
[Ignoring, Messy~]
Oppa, Jung Eum's tears are flowing.
- Are you okay?
- Put this on.
[I'm not done with my introduction]
[I still have a lot to say...]
[Everyone is distracted by the rain...]
Hello!
[Due to the rain, no one hears him]
I was born in 1985!
Wait a moment! Kwang Soo is introducing himself.
Listen to him.
Yes, I am Lee Kwang Soo.
I'm 26 years old.
Kwang Soo is crying!
You're filming a drama right?
Ah yes, together with Jung Eum.
Smile, smile.
Right now, we're filming Dong Yi.
- He's become very popular. He's someone to look forward to.
- Thank you.
Please tell us about your plans.
I will strive hard!
[A newbie Kwang Soo, under the spotlight recently. He'll attract you with his unique charms...!]
What about Gary?
You've come on a variety show again.
Hello, I'm Kang Gary who live in Jamsil.
Your surname is Kang, oppa?
Kang Gary.
Although I don't know Gary very well,
I heard he's an incredible friend.
Gil oppa can move aside.
I heard he's at least
10 times of Gil's power.
I'm a witness. There are many other witnesses as well.
[We look forward to your effort, Mr.Kang Gary!]
Then we will work hard! Please anticipate!
- Don't walk, run!
- Ra...
Running Man!
[The sudden weird pose that came out!]
Since it's the first time, just use this.
Okay. Hyori says use this.
[What's Suk Jin doing again...?]
Running Man, Bang!
Bang!
What is this?!
[Old fashioned!]
[Seems to fit Suk Jin well...]
Running Man, Bang!
[Just like that...]
[Running Man's first episode starts]
[Running Man's First Landmark]
[Seoul's Yong Dong Po Gu's T Shopping Mall!]
[With a total of 37,000 square meters,
and 10,000 people visit every day!]
[The largest shopping mall
with about 200 stores!]
[New concept variety show, Running Man]
[Once the exits are sealed,
the game starts!]
[Search for the secret tube
that holds the secret code to exit!]
[The device given to the two teams
to receive instructions!]
[The unimaginable through race and game]
[Collect the secret code
to escape before the mall opens!]
[Awaiting the losing team is
an unexpected punishment]
[Running Man]
[According to their shopping characteristics,
they're divided into the Cheap Team and the Expensive Team]
[Expensive Team] You've all finished changing, right?
When the instructions come, just head over will do.
[Message arrived]
[First Landmark: 'T' Shopping Mall]
Ah, it's near.
Just head there will do.
Let's go!
Hurry, get in!
[Expensive Team sets off]
But what are we going to do when we get there?
Nowadays, the producers don't reveal such things anymore.
Jung Eum, today we might film overnight.
Is that alright with you?
Oh, I slept the whole day today.
- Previously, when we filmed High Kick Through the Roof...
- Ah yes, the both of you.
Towards the overnight filming,
she really isn't tired at all...
- To me, overnight filming is nothing.
- Ah, it wasn't easy for Kwang Soo to say something~
[Oops!]
[Kwang Soo is a very reserved person...]
[Hmm...]
Kwang Soo keeps everything in his heart.
He remembers them.
I was thinking if it was because
what I said was boring so...
[Kwang Soo...
Will he hang in there well...?]
[At the same time...]
[The other vehicle in transit]
No matter what, Hyori has quick eyes.
I can quickly sense what's going on,
and Oppa can use your brain.
Actually, mu IQ is quite high...
When was the last time you ran?
How many years ago?
I don't run!
You should since this is Running Man.
Don't worry.
I grew out my nails to scratch people.
And grabbing people by the hair.
[Just like that...
traveling into the changing city night...]
[Finally reached
Yong Dong Po's 'T' Shopping Mall!]
[Cheap Team arrives]
[The empty mall with nothing
[The empty mall with nothing,
finally enters!]
This is the start.
No, this is really... This is huge!
[Take a look, the interior is huge]
[It's beautiful...]
Ah really,
we will be stuck here today.
They're here!
They're here.
[Expensive Team arrives]
[Blank]
Is this where they want us to be running?
They want us to not walk but run.
Wow, this is too much.
[The time now is 10:50 PM. When the shops are all closed!]
Now is when the shops are all closed.
You guys haven't been to a mall where the shops are all closed, have you?
- It's what every female dreams of!
- Just like a scene in a drama.
The kind where you'd come in
and just shop as you wish.
[I feel happy imagining it!]
[Nods]
Both teams have heard right?
From now until the stores open.
The team that loses the game
will not be let out.
From now on,
we are enemies.
And also this name tag behind...
If you get caught, this comes off.
Is that so?
If that happens, Oppa won't be able
to participate in the game.
That... Can you see that?
- What's that?
[Surprised]
[Exits Sealed]
[ In the middle of sealing the exits ]
This is totally like a movie!
[ Blank~ ]
[ Once all the exits are locked,
no one can leave ]
[ West Entrance is sealed ]
[ East Entrance is sealed ]
[ South Entrance is sealed ]
[ Main Entrance is sealed,
the sealing is complete! ]
First, from this point,
we can't go anywhere.
The wining Team can just leave?
Nothing else?
We can just go home like that?
Regardless of the time?
Now, Cheap Team
Please move to the 3rd floor immediately.
Wow~ This really is like a movie.
Cheap Team, Lets go.
Hyo-ri! Do well!
Lets Go!
[ The search for the first code
has finally begun ]
[ Cheap Team is first heading to the 3rd floor ]
From now on, there is no one who is going to give us hints on where to go.
Where is the third floor?
This is second floor.
- Your is stamina is pretty good.
- I'm getting tired already
[ Right from the start,
An overexcited 43-year old Suk Jin? ]
Wait a second, Let's come up with a plan.
Because Hyo-ri is known for foul play,
Let's come up with a plan.
That's alright.
[ In order to keep in touch with other
members, they are given walkie-talkies. ]
Hello, Hello. 1, 2, 3
Grasshopper, come out. Over.
Grasshopper is out!
Nice! Nice! Nice!
Where should we head to?
There should be a message.
[ Waiting for the message
to the first code location ]
It's here.
[ The Message has arrived ]
Go to the most expensive place in the mall.
[ The first code is at the most
expensive place in the mall ]
Wait, No. If were talking about expensive,
shouldn't it be jewelry and stuff like that.
That's right. No matter how expensive the bags are,
they can't be as expensive as jewelry.
- Isn't it going to be designer items?
- No, no.
Go to the most expensive place in the mall.
- I know, I know where it is?
- Where? Where?
- Where is it?
- In most shopping malls,
the first floor has the
most expensive stores.
Let's stay calm!
Let's start moving and have a look around.
Okay, Lets go!
[ First, Let's start searching randomly ]
We aren't going shopping!
Even though, I'm still happy.
[ Urgent ]
- I need to go use the restroom first.
- No, No Hold it in.
- Hold it in
- It's really urgent
Let's move together, first.
It doesn't seem to be here.
[ Ah ~ ]
[ Jung-eum, What exactly did
she see that surprised her ]
[ No other than...
Shoes that attract ladies ]
[ These shoes look like
they've been waiting for her ]
[ As if attracted by a magnetic force ]
Get her.
Hold her! Hold her!
[ Jung-eum is a shopaholic ]
- No, It's not there
- But, those are expensive things too.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Beauty, fancy, art ..
- It's not the food court, young sports, casual ..
- Should we try going towards beauty?
- I don't think It'll be beauty, more of make up and stuff.
Let's try going over there.
[ Looks around ]
I don't think It's there, Oppa.
I've shopped before, So I know.
[ The shopping world is difficult for guys ]
To be honest, I'm not familiar with these things.
[ In the middle
of the many shops in the hall ]
[ Where exactly is the shop
that sells the most expensive item ]
[ 3F seems to be filled
with accessories and apparels ]
- It doesn't seem to be here
- Yeah, It doesn't.
- Lets go the jewelry area
- Let's go up first, since no one is there.
Jewelry is normally...
On the first level?
You have to think carefully!
Cheap Team started on the 3rd floor.
- We have to move accordingly.
- There is a big possibility that it's on the 2nd floor!
Go upstairs!
Don't walk, run!
Go find a bathroom, please!
Being able to run
like this in a shopping mall is...
This program seems so fun!
While she running, without even knowing it,
Jung-eum keeps giggling.
Why are you so happy, Jung-eum?
It feels like I went back
to being a little kid~
I actually really need
to go to the bathroom.
Someone go find a bathroom.
[Really... I feel like I'm going to die.]
I think Jae Suk Hyung has
to go to the bathroom first.
Oh there it is!
[Finally they find a bathroom!]
I'll go the the bathroom for a second.
Hyung, you have to keep
the walkie talkie on even in the bathroom.
What kind of camera would
follow us even in here...
Go to the shop with the most
expensive merchandise in this building.
[In this shopping mall, where would
the most expensive item be located?]
[Is the item a bag? Necklace?
Make up? Clothing? Shoes?]
[The answer is this crystal brand shop]
[Expensive crystal products!]
[Magnificent and valuable products too!]
[Even among those,
the most expensive product is...]
[This 200 million Won watch right here!]
[Right behind it,
there lays the first pass code!]
[On one team, there is Jae Suk
who is still in the bathroom.]
Jae Suk Oppa, does it feel nice?
Jung-eum, you shouldn't be like this!
Call Jong Kook!
Jong Kook Oppa, does it feel nice?
Don't ask!
[ On the opposite side,
the hardworking Cheap Team ]
Let's go to the Jewelry area.
- Let's go and have a look around since it's not here.
- Jewelry is usually...
on the first floor.
[ Jewelry is not on the top floor ]
- We have to head down
[ Slow foot steps
that gradually become faster ]
Oppa, check the 1st floor
and see if they have jewelry shops.
Over there!
[ Seemed to have notice something ]
What?
Isn't that it?
[ Correct! They found the place
that sells the most expensive item ]
That's expensive.
- Is it?
- Of course, It should be there
Jong Kook, does it feel good?
Don't ask.
You shouldn't be
asking those questions!
Hide! Hide!
[ Surprised! ]
Catch them, don't move!
Gary, get them!
[ Expensive team,
that is wasting time at the toilet. ]
[ RM Rule - If you pull the other
team's name tag, that member can't move ]
Oppa! Let's search! Hurry!
[ Why is it so loud? ]
Hyung! Hyung!
[ Rapper Gary, right in front of them
in a split second ]
Tear the name tag!
[ Gary is attacking Kwang Soo's name tag ]
[ Kwang Soo Out! ]
[ If this continues,
Jung-eum is in danger as well ]
[ If they are ousted, the situation will be a disadvantage for them ]
- No!
[ Taking a looking at
the situation from behind... ]
[ First, Expensive Team's Joong Ki goes in ]
[ Behind Joong Ki is... ]
[ Kim Jong Kook ]
[ Save me~ ]
[ Hiding from Kim Jong Kook comes first. ]
[ Sprinter Joong Ki,
turning the situation around with his speed ]
[ Surprisingly, Suk Jin is also fast! ]
[ Avoided Joong Ki very well. ]
Oh, Where are you Hyo-Ri?
[ She is... ]
[ Seizing the moment in the chaos to go to the Jewelry shop ]
- Where did they go?
I'm all alone, where are they?
[ Luxurious ]
Oppa! Gary Oppa!
- Where are you, Hyo-ri?
- Come to the Jewelry shop.
Come to the Jewelry shop.
Okay! I'm coming.
[The Expensive Team
starts to hurry at a late start]
[That's why I said
that it's better to control..]
Where is it?
[Has a feeling that it's here...]
- Where are you Hyo-ri?
- Come to the Jewelry shop.
It seems to be here...
This is...
Wait a second...
[ Hyo-ri noticed something ]
I found it! This is . . Oppa!
Gary, I found it!
[ The first Password is? ]
[ Number of people = 6 ]
- 1,2,3,4,5,6
Okay! Okay!
What is this?
[First race over!]
I found it!
I found it! I found it!
[ First Password race,
Cheap Team Victory ]
[On the other hand... The man who is the only person out,
sitting next to the bathrooms]
When do I have to stay here until?
[ After 25 minutes... ]
Have you found the password?
Oh, Yeah, We found it.
Hyori has, as expected of Hyori.
One person.
Then we have to reveal it.
Why reveal the number?
- Jung-eum, ask her.
What's the password?
- Look her in the eyes and say it.
She opened her eyes wider.
[Scared!]
Jung eum!
Hyori Unni is so scary.
No, I can't have that kind of image!
What do we have to do?
[What do they have to do now?]
[The producer is passing the game]
[??]
First of all, this
Ok, it's done.
[Ok! It's done!]
- Oh!
[Immediately got the feeling]
Let me explain the game. Just look.
This race is a clothes hanger competition.
Right now, on the clothes rack, there are four pieces of clothes
hanging on that side and five on this side, right?
In the state of wearing the clothes,
move forward, in a relay format.
[Unable to believe
if he is telling the truth...]
It's written there like that!
You must have read it wrong!
Hyori, would I lie to you?
Would I lie? I -It's true!
I means four people
have to form a line. I -Exactly.
And this is important, you have to win to
start moving first.
[Rule - You have to win first and then you can start to find the password]
Now looking at it,
You have to go quickly and find it quickly.
It's my first time talking so much
in a shopping mall.
It's nice since there's no people.
We're starting. Please turn on the camera.
[They're already nervous,
variety newbies, Joong Ki & Gary]
Cue! [For the camera]
- Wait! Wait!
That's not it!
Wait wait! That's not it.
Wait wait!
Gary, it's not yet.
[He misunderstood the camera cue
as the start of the game!]
[They're both variety newbies...]
Wait, it's my first time saying this
[Education for the variety newbies]
Cue means the camera is going to start rolling!
'Start' is for the game to start!
Do you understand?
[A kind variety teacher MC Yoo~]
Everyone fighting!
Let's clap!
[Livening up the atmosphere]
Wa~it!
[Ok! Ok!]
Ready!
[Finally - 1 Round]
[The variety newbies are nervous again]
Start!
[Speed]
[Joong Ki's fast too]
[Dress quickly and run with the hanger...!]
Joong Ki's wearing something cool!
Joong Ki's first!
[Woo~sh]
[The way he is running is a little...]
[Gary starts]
[Finally turning!
As Joong Ki has a sharp turn...]
[Urgent situation!]
[Towards the two variety newbies,
compared to laughter, winning is more important!]
[Hit!]
[At the turning point~the camera~what...]
[Joong Ki reached
the start-off point first!]
You have to wear
the clothes with the hanger!
Joong Ki fighting!
[Expensive team, starts first!]
[Straight after the cheap team goes]
[Right leg!]
What are we doing in the early morning
[Really sincere]
[Happily experiencing the human hanger!]
[The onlookers are embarrassed]
[Cheap Team leads by a little!]
Calm down!
Cheap Team: Third person is Haha
Expensive Team: Third person is Jae Suk.
Ready? Go!
[Haha hasn't even put on
the clothes properly...]
Go! Go! Just go!
Right, right, right, right.
[Only Jae Suk's footing is wrong]
[Still, Jae Suk is shouting the right foot]
[Suddenly... ]
Jae Suk, just stand on top!
[Cheap Team seized the chance to lead!]
[Turning around the halfway point]
[Now going to fetch the last member!]
[Jae Suk who has
the wrong footing again...]
Hurry! Hurry!
[Last person Hyori]
[Last people Jung Eum and Kwang Soo]
1, 2, 1, 2
[Expensive team starts too!]
Right leg!
[...Huh? Stands still...]
Why didn't you wear it Jung Eum?!
Oh!
[Just like that, the gap widened again]
[Jung Eum just stands
on the rack due to her nervousness]
[But the gap seems to have gotten large]
[Conflict~]
[Pinch!]
[Hyori is holding tightly on
to Jae Suk's hair!]
[When did the gap become so small?]
[Right now, the Cheap Team
still leads just slightly...]
[Will they win like this?]
[A big reversal win?!]
[...At this moment...!]
[Speedy~]
[Kim Jong Kook is on full power!]
[What happened...?]
[They are all standing on the rack,
while Jong Kook and Kwang Soo go!]
[Expensive Team reached
the finish line first!]
[Drama-like reverse]
Isn't pulling hair a foul?
Isn't it?!
[Outdoor variety newbie lost his soul]
Gary, take this off.
[Variety newbie, Knock Down]
The last round is the deciding battle.
Hyori and Jung Eum, the both of you
should go against each other.
Good, good, good!
You can do it! You can do it!
You haven't told Jung Eum my nickname, right?
I -She should know.
You know it right?
I hope you don't get hurt.
It's really not like that,
but due to the game,
it will turn out this way.
You must try really hard.
[Smirk~]
You start to focus
That expression shows that Hyori
thought of a good way to cheat.
[Sweats]
I've done these a lot with Hyori.
If Hyori smiles with her eyes then
[That girl's eye smile means... a fun cheat sign]
she's thought of a good way to cheat.
Be careful.
Hyori fighting!
[Must be a win!]
Show us some cheating!
Start!
[Heading that way...]
[She's grabbed her]
Hey! Lee Hyori!
[A scary scene!]
[What is this.. between women]
[Throw!]
[What?]
[Speeding towards Jung Eum]
[Even with Jung Eum in the lead...]
[Hyori grabs her again!]
[Excited!]
Ahhh!
[How long is she going to hold on?]
[Is Hyori going to...]
[Oh my!]
[The threatening hair pull!]
Jung Eum! You grab her too!
[This time it's Jung Eum!]
[I'm scared]
[The hair pull once again!]
[Perhaps?]
[Retaliation!]
[Late-night fight at the shopping mall]
[They're doing it right.
Women's Boxing tournament]
[I will not lose!]
[Dizzy]
[Zoom~]
[I'm scared! I'm scared!]
[Expensive Team Jung Eum wins!]
[A mess!]
Let's reconcile.
[Hyori, the first time
she's been cheated on!]
Hyori, stay calm!
Come out! Where is she?!
[Begging for forgiveness]
Sorry!
[Surprisingly, a strong girl, Jung Eum!]
Jung Eum is not normal either!
I -Jung Eum, with her innocent face!
Everyone, please don't misunderstand.
They get along well. The game was just too wild.
How about shaking hands?
[Slap!]
So cool.
[So cool~]
[Well known cool sister, Hyori!]
It's been a long time
since I saw Hyori scared.
It showed a little.
The winning team will receive
the clue to the secret code first,
and the losing team will receive
a penalty before they proceed.
It's okay! It's okay!
Are you okay?
Really?
For the Cheap Team, the four of you have
to finish drinking this before you get the clue
And we don't have a penalty, right?
Aren't we supposed
to continue running later?
Throughout, we need to go to the bathroom too!
I -Yes. That's why you would run to the bathroom.
[I can't believe it!]
After you start, we'll go.
Don't breathe in the middle.
[Start!]
The clue is here... It's coming...
It's here! Hello! This is SBS Running Man. Hint. In times of expensive oil prices,
we solve air conditioning/heating problems by 0000. Go to 0000.
Hello! This is SBS Running Man. Hint. In times of expensive oil prices,
[Race Start!]
[Difficulty level: 3]
[In times of expensive oil prices, we solve air conditioning/heating problems by 0000. Go to 0000.]
[In times of expensive oil prices,
we solve air conditioning/heating problems by 0000. Go to 0000.]
Meanwhile, the Cheap Team is...
I hate sucking on this!
[??]
[Everyone generously
giving theirs to Suk Jin]
[You're probably thirsty
from all the running, drink up]
What are you guys doing?
Kwang Soo, think of a 4 letter word.
Joong Ki! Jung Eum! Jong Kook!
Let's all think of a 4 letter word!
[Hybrid?]
That's five words.
[That's 4 syllables...]
[The hint is air conditioning/heating!]
[Where is the second secret code?]
What is the 4 words? Look up there.
[What?]
Hey! Stop it!
OKay. Geez.
[They do anything since no one's around]
Let's see. What is there?
Jung Eum! Regardless of what it is,
just say something with four words.
This is so tiring...
You were so bright and enthusiastic.
You had fun.
But the question is hard...
Let's think while sitting down.
It's not like we can figure it out
by walking around.
Think of something with four words.
Isn't heating and
cooling powered by electricity?
Oil.
Electricity. I -Wind power!
No. Does that even make sense?
Why not? This place is so tall.
I -Should I look at the message again?
[Ignoring]
[Kwang Soo, he tried so hard
to say something]
That doesn't make sense.
[Again]
There might be another clue in the message.
[Ugh.]
Kwang Soo, what did you say?
Kwang Soo just tell me.
Jong Kook kept on talking.
You guys... So... I'm kind of upset...
It's not that we don't want to listen to you.
It's because this side...
Okay, Kwang Soo, tell us.
[Out of nowhere]
What? It's okay. Tell us.
Can it be related to clothing?
[Hansa Moshi?]
[Oh my God]
[Kwang Soo is giving up on his idea...]
[The city's air conditioning
was done by clothing?]
[Cheap Team is still doing
their punishment]
Gary is the man!
Give us the clue please.
In times of expensive oil prices,
we solve air conditioning/heating problems by 0000. Go to 0000.
Central Heating Room!
Solar energy?
Can solar energy provide cooling?
Do we have to go to the roof?
It seems like the roof.
I -Let's talk while we walk.
It's not oil or gas.
Let's just go up.
[Startled!]
[That team doesn't know either!]
[Discovered each other!]
They saw us.
Since they're hiding like that, does it mean that
they already know the answer? I -No. They don't know.
They are just trying
to take off your name tag.
[Kwang Soo experienced it before]
Let's take a took upstairs.
[The Expensive Team is on the 4th floor
while the Cheap Team is on the 5th floor]
The roof! The roof!
[Cheap Team's opinions
lead them towards the roof]
The roof is right.
[Can the secret code
be located at the rooftop?]
It is rooftop!
We'll win if we get there first! Hurry!
Guys. Be quiet. Try not to make loud steps.
Can you lock the door?
You can't?
Wait, isn't it the rooftop?
Those guys are running!
Let's go to the roof!
Where? Isn't it there?
[This way and that]
Hurry and film us! Film us!
Oh my God!
Run! Run! Run!
[Cheap Team is already at the rooftop]
[Is the secret code at the rooftop?]
Roof park.
There is a sign here.
[Sky Park]
Guys run! They're coming!
Run!
[The gap in between is getting shorter!]
Guys! Catch up with them!
Run faster!
[The secret code isn't easily visible]
[The person who gets it first
is the keeper]
I found it! I found it!
Here!
[The second secret clue!]
[The secret clue is
placed on top of the sculpture!]
Its here!
[Get the secret code
that is hanging in the air]
Bend down!
[Gary gets down after hearing Hyori]
[Is the secret code
going to be in Hyori's hands?!]
[No!]
[It's mine!]
[Missed!]
[Hyori was off by a little]
[In which hands will
the secret bottle go into...]
[Fighting for the bottle
is these two teams]
[Meet up]
[Haha takes this as an opportunity]
[If only Haha gets it with his hands!]
[But at this time!]
[Grab]
[Kwang Soo easily gets it and succeeds!]
[Second Round, RACE OVER]
[Second Round, the Expensive Team wins!]
[We were really
disadvantaged in this game.]
[The second secret number = 3
(Number of people)]
[Proud]
[Three hours of lock-down]
Because we need to finish filming before the mall opens,
let's hurry this and make this funny for people.
Kwang Soo... are you okay?
I'm oka...
[Why is the radio suddenly...]
Joong Ki... after I do the interview...
Tell us, tell us.
I'm okay,
[...He is interrupted again...]
Yes.
[Rule: You must win the game in order to start the race!]
- Now, the game we will be playing is Chicken Fight.
They say that the first team
to go first has more of an advantage.
So let's play a game
to decide who will go first.
It will be Lips Rock, Paper, and Scissors.
Rock... Scissors... Paper.
Do you understand now?
Let's begin with Suk Jin Hyung and I.
I look forward to it.
Oppa, men can also be cute.
Oppa, take your glasses off!
Why?!
[Flustered]
- Why do I have to take my glasses off for this game?
Why do I need to take them off
for this game?
No, why...?
There's no need.
Hey...
[Oh my...]
I have to take them off?
Get close to one another
and open your hearts to each other.
[Use this chance to say what has been hidden in your heart.]
- Talk about things you haven't been able to say to each other.
- To be honest, I do have something to say.
- What is it?
10 years ago
- You introduced me to my wife, right.
- Of course, I thought that you two would match really well.
Why did you do that?!
[Haha]
[What is he saying!?]
Were you serious?
Why did you do it?
[Your wife would be looking at
this at home though...]
It's not like that. I was just curious.
Hyung, I'm sorry.
You know me. I felt like we are compatible.
[Seems like a long story]
- I am just grateful.
- Like I said before.
When I set you and your wife up...
- Your wife called me...
- What did she say?
- She didn't want to continue meeting you.
[Feeling dizzy]
I am serious.
- But you guys are living well off.
- Is it real?
- Really, tell me.
- Yes, your wife said it.
- It's things from the past.
- Yeah. It's been a long time.
[It was exactly on the day of match-making]
- She said on the day of the match -making.
She said that you didn't seem like
the type to keep wanting to meet.
- Also...
- Did she say that?
She really said it.
I really worked hard to make you both meet.
You know that right?
I wanted to meet her, truthfully.
[Suk Jin's wife, the one he fell in love with at first sight!]
- But she didn't really like me.
- Yeah she didn't.
[Jae Suk worked hard to connect the two until the end.]
So you kept putting us together and connecting us, that's how my wife and I got married.
Yeah, so why did you do that?
[About to cry]
Why did you do that?
Hyung! You still love her though, right?
I love her a lot!
The end!
[Now, let's start
the Lip Rock Paper Scissors]
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Paper, rock.]
[Scissors and Rock]
[Laughs]
[Sticks out tongue]
Why?
No...
Hyung, your nostrils were different sizes.
A long time ago,
he had surgery to reduce the size.
So what?
His nostrils were like this.
[His nostrils were flaring]
When I first began being a comedian,
my nostrils could've been mistaken for my fists.
But
the doctor helped me fix it.
The doctor helped me fix it.
[Game start.]
[Rock.]
[Paper.]
[Paper. Scissors.]
[Now it's Jae Suk's turn to attack]
[Rock.]
[Rock]
[Jae Suk wins!]
No!
Why did you do that 10 years ago?
[Cheap team: 0 Expensive Team: 1]
Next up from our team will be Joong Ki.
And this team will be... Gary.
Yes, I'll do it.
I don't know whose team is who now.
Look at them!
He looks like military guards!
Gary really has a face that can be
commonly seen in any neighborhood.
Military guard.
Let's start off by saying some words
to each other about our looks.
You're handsome but...
[Free from distraction]
You're handsome!
[Gary saying these words are somewhat...]
- That's right, you're handsome.
I have no words.
[Now it's time for Joong Ki to speak...]
- Stop...!
[Shh!]
[Gary, what are you doing right now...?]
He blocked his lip right now, right.
The gesture he just did
was a gesture to get girls.
He just made that gesture.
[Scary]
[Let's begin the game now~]
[Rock.]
[Paper.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Scissors.]
- What are you two doing?
[Have you two connected...?]
- This isn't that kind of game.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Scissors.]
[Haha]
This isn't a couple game.
You both have to be careful.
Ready.
[Rock, scissors... Paper!]
[Rock. Scissors.]
[Paper.]
[Scissors]
[Gary wins!]
Let's have Jung Eum and Hyo Ri go now.
[Hyo Ri vs. Jung Eum]
Both are beauties..
They both are beauties.
How about you both say some words
to each other up close?
So you are young!
Relax and talk!
What are you saying?
[Kicking people from early morning!]
- Why are you being like this, seriously.
[Your personality is the same as before.]
I don't know about anything else,
but you're older than me right.
Your nose, the line between
your nose and your lips
is the best in Korea, to be truthful!
No, not your eyes... but here...
Come here...
What did you say...
[Grab]
[Why did you talk about her age.]
- You said to be truthful.
Why are you holding my hands?
In case you'll pull her hair!
Here, here. Let's begin.
Rock, scissors..
[Scissors. Rock.]
[Scissors. Rock]
[Paper. Scissors.]
[Rock. Paper.]
[Cute. Cute.]
Are you going
to keep pretending to be cute?
[Angry]
It's just a game.
It is just a game.
Do you know how she did it?
Just try to do it too.
Do you want to see me try to be cute once?
Try it.
[Again, kicks]
Just stay still!
It's because I can't see.
Kwang Soo! Are you having fun watching us?!
[It's interesting for the comedy newbies]
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
[Terrifying]
[Something very daring]
Hyo Ri, this is a warning.
You can't do that.
You're the cutest!
Scissors.
[They're both doing the same thing?]
Unni, that's my move!
[Again!]
[Again]
You can't look.
We don't know who's going to win yet.
Let's start again.
[Scissors. Paper.]
[Rock.]
[Hyo Ri wins!]
We don't need cuteness
or anything like that!
[Cheap Team gets to go first]
Because your team won,
you guys get to go first.
Let's do this for real.
What do we do, then?
There's someone coming from the back!
What? Who is it?
[Someone...]
[Is coming...?]
[Their identities are...]
[50 people citizen's corps]
This makes no sense! Absolutely no sense!
How did they...
Where did you guys come from?
Come this way.
- Come here.
- Where did they find these people...?
- This is nonsense!
- We're screwed.
In place!
[Imposing]
How many people do you think there are?
[Now revealing game rules!]
The game will continue until
you knock down all these people.
[Until they knock them all down!]
[Only laughter comes out
because it is so unbelievable...]
- Unbelievable.
- There are this many people right now!
No matter how we look at it,
it looks like a large army!
If you knock down one citizen, you win.
[A chicken fight that requires strategy!]
[It does't matter how many citizens each team knocks down.
The team that knocks down the last citizen will win. ]
We just have to hold out.
Everyone! We will now try our hardest,
and play Chicken Fight now.
Please take care of us.
So that we won't get hurt.
Thank you.
The sound of their applause is...
Wow this kind of chicken fight...
Leave me in the back!
You're our ace.
They're telling Hyo Ri to stand in front!
Even we won't do that.
Ugh, seriously.
Get ready!
[They shout a cheer]
[Flustered]
Okay. Start!
You guys can to go to them.
[Scarily rushing in]
[The sound too]
[Invincible Hyori is eliminated]
This doesn't make sense.
[However!]
[They attack an unsuspecting Suk Jin!]
[Falling down here and there]
You guys are really bad
at playing this game!
[Suk Jin even managed
to knock down two people.]
[Those that have been
disqualified go to the back.]
They're really strong.
[But..]
[The mood in front of
the human wave strategy...]
[Currently surrounding HaHa!]
[And in the end, he is disqualified
because he didn't have power.]
[This time they concentrate on Suk Jin!]
[Eliminated without a pulse]
[The last person remaining is Gary!]
[Completely surrounded]
[They're coming all at once!]
[Ok! I'm the rapper Gary!]
[Going head to head like a man]
[He's stuck!]
[The crushed rapper]
The people who fell, please go to the back.
Let's take a count of the people.
Oppa! They're no joke.
[11 members of the Citizen Team have been disqualified.]
The ones that have been disqualified are over there.
But the people remaining are going "woo"
[Expensive Team challenges!]
[Nervous.]
- Even if there's Jong Kook, we're..
[Now there are 39 members of
the Citizen Team left.]
[They're coming again!]
[Spearhead! They fierce fully attack
the muscle chicken]
[Offense and defense in the front line]
[Without even a nod, a concentrated attack]
[You are amazing, Kim Jong Kook!]
- Oppa!
- It's ok!
[Jae Suk is out!]
[Jae Suk is Jae Suk but...]
[How did Kwang Soo...?]
[Since running everywhere by himself]
[Just running back and he's eliminated]
Don't step on me! Don't step on me!
[Extreme sadness]
[What are you doing instead of coming out?]
[He narrowly escapes!]
That really hurt.
Ugh, seriously!
[After Joong Ki was disqualified]
[Jung Eum was disqualified.]
[Now the only one left
is the muscle chicken!]
Win this, Oppa!
[If you're going to throw yourself at me,
then come and throw all of yourselfs at once!]
[I can not back down like this!]
[Jong Kook's fierce bent attack!]
[Jong Kook eventually was disqualified.]
- It really hurt.
You suffered a lot hyungnim!
[Still, they were able
to get rid of 5 cizitens]
Jong Kook is not a human, he's a machine.
[Chicken fight machine]
- They hit here, and here.
- They're no joke, oppa!
Let's try and change our strategy.
How about fighting one on one?
Shall we try and fighting one on one?
The citizens should pick out
a member they wanna go up against.
- If you guys choose a member, then we'll...
- I want to compete with Jong Kook Hyungnim!
- Whoa!
- Do you think you'll be ok?
I was part of those
who remained from the game before.
[That chicken(?)
won't be easy to defeat though.]
Fighting!
[Now, who will be the winner...?]
- Show him with one move!
[Flying in mid air?]
Next person! Next person!
[Choi Kang Ja from
the Citizen Team has been KO-ed.]
Will the next person come out.
[The next challenger.]
They're citizens!
Watch yourself!
[This person also seems strong...]
[Oh my god..]
Are you okay?
Wait, wait.
[Even his shoulders]
Is it difficult?
What are we gonna do about his shoulders?
Leave!
[Don't go, Mr. Jae Suk...]
[The last player from
the Expensive Team, Kwang Soo.]
[Within seconds, one member has fallen!]
[Kwang speed! Chicken legs]
He's going for it! He's going for it!
Why are his legs so thin!
[Actively using his long legs!]
[Kwang Soo wo... Huh?]
[He just wins]
[And he just falls down]
[Discharged]
Ah, what should we do?
Ok the cheap team!
Let's do a one on one too!
[The first opponent from
the Citizens Team is?]
I'd like to play with Mr. Suk Jin!
[Oh come on...]
It seems as if you don't know me well.
Take your hands out, Hyungnim!
I'm going to defeat you.
Bang!
[Wanted to forget but...]
[A greasy Bbang~!]
[Me too, Bbang!]
Okay, get ready... Start!
[With good vigor]
[With one move...]
[What is this...]
- Hyori! What do you think about Hyori?
- I'm a fan.
Please be gentle~
[Gently]
[Unmatched! Hyori's aegyo strategy]
No, we can fight like this and then-
She does it so naturally.
[Leg seems rusty]
[Hyori's Aegyo strategy is very useful]
[Public humiliation]
You lost too easily!
Come on!
Don't get fooled by this!
Don't be concerned
about these kinds of things.
[Attacks fairly but...]
It hurts!
Ah, it hurts!
[Shocking.]
- Wow, THAT hurts?
[Unbelievable]
- This is cheating!
- It hurts right here!
It started to hurt right here!
[Bursting into rage!]
[Lethal]
[Melting~]
Why are you being like this, really?
Do it gently!
Whoa!
[Hyo Ri is disqualified.]
You have won.
You're amazing!
[This is too much!]
You had to win against Hyo Ri!
You've done well.
He did a good job! Good job.
Now it's a team event.
Just until one person is left.
Why do you stubbornly want to win?
We all have to win.
We really have to win. We have to win this.
Go!
- Whoa!
- They're coming! They're coming!
[It immediately turns into chaos!]
[Still, all they do is try!
The battle excessively becomes fierce!]
[The muscle chicken
is gathering up his strength]
[Joong Ki also tries his best!]
[I should get rid of all of them!]
[Joong Ki does suicide bombing
and is eliminated]
[The citizens are too separated
for you to see all of them!]
[Bump!]
[The grasshopper chicken is eliminated]
[Ah... Camera...]
[Cry baby]
It hurts so much!
[Embarrassed]
[Now there are only 7 citizens remaining!]
In the back! In the back!
[Jeong Eum is also eliminated]
[Stabs]
[Muscle chicken, Jongkook
is heroically eliminated!]
[Now only Kwangsoo
is the only person left!]
[Excited]
Kwangsoo! You have to beat three people!
[Finally, there are only 3 citizens left]
[Nervous]
One at a time?
[They attack from here and there]
[Please...]
Please!
[Now Kwangsoo...]
[Is on his knees...]
[Now just 3 people!
The chance goes to the cheap team]
Hyung!
It's 4 against 3.
Just 3 people.
Why are you coming towards me?
[First, the cute chicken Hyori
is eliminated]
They got this! They got this!
[Attractive spectacle]
We didn't lose?
What are you doing?!
Hold on. Hold on!
Hey, even if it's just one person-
We got this! We got this!
There's only two people left!
Just one more person!
Win! You have to win!
Please win!
[Park Young Ho: 23 years old]
Win!
Woah!
Good! Please! Please!
Please don't lose.
[Don't really know who will win!]
[Bumps into him]
[Sinks]
[Suk Jin is eliminated]
[Goes straight to Gary?]
[All the members of the cheap team
are eliminated]
[The expensive team is cheering]
[An amazing person!]
- Hold on.
- What happened?
Why did I fall down
like this in a chicken fight?
I'm sorry. We have no choice but to win.
A game is a game so please understand.
Yes, we're sorry.
Let's do a cheer!
1,2,3 fighting!
Fighting!
This is the last set!
[5 versus 1]
[Goes straight for Jong Kook!]
[From the start he aims
for the ace, Jong Kook!]
[In the midst of it all,
Joong Ki is eliminated]
[4 versus 1]
[Kwang soo and Jae Suk's tag team attack!]
[Hits]
[Jae Suk is fatally eliminated]
[Jae Suk is dead]
[This is an angle we've seen
many times today...]
Yeah!
Aigoo!
[Now there's only two people left on the team!
Jong Kook and Jeong Eum]
[Confrontation]
Oppa, be careful!
[Taps]
So gentle.
Wow, this is no joke.
[Well matched]
No!
[Then]
[The chicken fight
machine's offensive attack!]
[If he misses this attack...]
[Falls down with a thud]
[Kim Jong Kook wins]
Awesome job!
You're awesome.
Good job!
You gave us a really fun game.
You really worked hard. Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
You can go home now!
Be safe!
Thank you!
Wow they did a really good job.
This is a first.
This is really difficult.
Where is it?
I feel like this is the place
that sells the cheapest things.
This place is really big!
Run! Run!
- Yeah, you have to use your head.
- It's over here.
Jeong Eum!
[Jeong Eum, what's making you so excited?]
[The pretty things she's been waiting for]
[She can't help but be excited]
- Here it is! Here it is!
- Don't look for that.
You're finding the things you want.
In my opinion,
they would probably use an offical thing as a marker.
Don't you think?
Earlier they used something...
- Sticker?
- Yeah something like that.
Usually what floor is it on?
The third floor.
We have to find the cheapest so one team,
one team has to distract them.
Me and Gary.
You and Suk Jin. Fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
Oh yeah~
[Who will find it first?]
[While Haha and Gary
are trying to find the expensive team]
[The two are trying to find the store]
Not that way.
[Will the cheap item be
at the place they're headed?]
- Oh, I'm going crazy.
- I think this is the right way.
What's over there?
This is killer.
[Careful]
[Becoming the hyena's target...]
[Thirsting for his close friend
Jeong Eum the sheep]
What would be the cheap thing?
Where did she go?
They give discounts here.
I can't see anything here.
[You're caught...]
There's nothing here.
[Not aware of anything and
just wanders off here and there]
[At that moment]
[Astonished]
[Afraid]
Jong Kook hyung!
[Jong Kook is on the move to help!]
Jong Kook hyung! Hyung!
What should I do?
[If he gets his nametag
ripped off he's out]
Jong Kook hyung!
Hyung!
[Jong Kook hyung]
[Save me]
Hyung! Hyung!
[Jong Kook is moving in!]
[First, Kwangsoo is out of the race]
[At this moment,
Haha who was waiting this whole time!]
[Crash!]
[In the end: Jong Kook, Gary and Kwangsoo
are out of the race]
You grabbed me so be careful!
[Meanwhile, these members
of the cheap team are on the move]
When did they...?
[They discover the convenience store!]
Yes!
We have to find it.
Find the cheapest thing!
There will be probably
something worth ten cents.
- How much are these?
- They're expensive.
- Oh, they're expensive?
500 won?
Try and find something.
[Find the item~]
Oppa! Look at this!
- Here.
- What's that?
- There was only one.
- How much is this?
- Oh, this is cheap. It's chocolate.
Yes, it's here.
Oppa I'll keep a look out
so try and find it.
- There's something big here right?
- In the inside.
There's something inside?
I think there could be something inside.
- Wow this is...
Haha, where are you?
Come to the convinience store.
Come in, come in.
Haha is at the convenience store!
[Overheard the radio]
[They get a tip off!]
Let's talk a bit! Let's talk!
[They move towards the convenience store!]
[And Haha who is still alive is running]
You're not even on the same team
and you're helping them out.
[I'm crazy aren't I...]
Mart. Okay.
Mart! There's also a mart.
Over there! Over there!
Hyung, go hide.
[At this rate, it seems like they'll meet up
with the other team at the convenience store]
[I won't lose you~]
It's here. I'm certain it's here.
There's nowhere else but here.
- It's in there so you have to find it.
- It's in here so...
[Can't help but look on the floor]
They're coming!
[Expensive team is right
in front of the convenience store!]
What do we do?
[This is the cheapest candy
in the building at only 100 won!]
[And in here is the password]
They're coming.
[Oh?!]
[Hyori discovers it?]
[We have to go there quickly!]
[Can't let that happen!]
[It should be here...]
[Hyori]
[Discovers it!]
[Hyori also discovers the third password!]
[The expensive team finally arrives
at the convenience store!]
[Suk Jin and Hyori hide]
[Comes in]
[Suk Jin has been discovered!]
- It's not on the bottom.
- Where is it?
Huh?
[Now is the time!]
[Hyori takes the password]
[They acquire the third password!]
[The third password= one]
Ugh, this much effort.
[Third race is over!]
You found the convenience store?
She's a genius!
[The night before at 11 PM.
Entrance blockade]
[The first password]
[The cheap team acquires it!
It's the number 6]
[The expensive team acquires
the second password Number 3. ]
[And the third password goes
to the cheap team. It's number 1]
[And the fourth password goes
to the expensive team! It's the number 5]
[Now there is only one password left!]
[Win the last game and acquire it!]
[1 Hour and 30 minutes until opening]
[Today's last stage,
Shopping Mall wedding hall A]
We met a few days ago at 6:30 PM didn't we?
Over these 12 hours,
it's right about time we fall asleep.
Suk Jin seems to be thinking a lot.
I'm sleeping.
It's time to be sleeping.
What time is it Jongki?
Mr.Jong.
[ Mr. Jong? Who? ]
- Hyung!
[This is all because of the time!]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yes, I made a mistake.
It's 6:45 AM.
From 6PM to 6:45 AM.
This game is really simple.
If you look here, there's a background.
[Yawning]
[Surprised]
[She must be embarrassed...]
Let's take into consideration
our beautiful hyori's image.
And if bringing up her hand was too much,
[Haaa]
It's simple! It's a team effort.
You go up there. And whoever gets
the most people in the shot wins.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
That's good.
[Ten seconds after saying
'I'll take a picture' a wedding photoshoot!]
I'll show you.
I'll take a picture, please head up there.
[Moving towards the photo zone!]
[As expected of Hyori!
Even if she's tired she's the first one up.]
[They're going!]
Please move your hand.
She's a girl. Why are you like that?
[Move a bit!]
[You have no business
being in front of Hyori!]
I'll be taking the photo!
10,9!
[Put your face forward!]
[Move!]
[It's you again...]
[Click!]
[Which team will have a lot of them
showing in the photo?]
[Jae Suk's face won't be in the photo
because it has been captured]
[And it seems like
we have to check the rest]
[Checking to see which team has more]
We won!
We won! We won!
- We won!
- Why?
Kwangsoo's hand is covering up his face!
- I'm sorry.
- We're on the same team!
It can get better.
[We see hope!]
Kwangsoo look at your innocent expression.
[Smile]
Wow Hyori at that moment...
It's amazing isn't it?
[Perfect smile]
The expression is almost similar, right?
[Cheap 1:0 Expensive]
Let's get this started.
I'll be taking the photo after 10 seconds.
Let's win! Let's do a cheer!
1,2,3! Fighting!
I'm taking the photo!
[After 10 seconds, a wedding photoshoot]
[Jae Suk gets the spot he had earlier]
[The guests are
keeping each other in check]
[The frivolous guest, Haha]
[Summoning rapper Gary!]
[Why must this hardship
have to happen to Kwangsoo]
[Interrupt Hyori's photoshoot!]
[Concentration mark]
[Will Hyori be able
to appear in the photo?]
Hey!
[My photo was taken]
[Was Hyori in the shot?]
Hey! I'm disappointed in you!
How can Hyori get in the shot!
[You did it Hyori!]
[Hmmph! It's nothing]
[Even this time, you can see her gums]
If we do it all night
then I'll come out more!
Gary! Gary!
That's awesome!
[What about Gary?]
[It's a face people can't recognize]
[Everyone is in the shot]
[They have to do a rematch]
[Only counts if you look straight
at the camera]
- Wow, they're so awesome.
- 5 seconds!
I'll be taking the photo!
[We have to stop Hyori this time!]
[I'll definitely show up
in the picture again]
[Even if they just blocked Hyori?]
Good!
We covered Hyori~
[The expensive team
is only concerned about Hyori]
Lee Hyori came out again!
[In bloom]
Gary hyung! Gary hyung!
[What about Gary?]
Gary!
That's so unbelievable.
How could you have
such a tranquil expression?
[Peaceful]
That's the first time
I'm seeing something like that!
- Wow this...
- This is funny.
[After falling down!]
- Let's make it a tie.
- Let us win. Gary's expression is funny.
And Hyori's expression is nice. Let us win.
Your eyes are closed here!
I was smiling!
[Cheap team has 2, expensive team has
3 so the expensive team wins!]
You're going to get up there and jump.
You jump and try
to get into the angle and win.
Let's do this!
- Ok!
- I'm going to take the photo!
[Jumping]
Jump oppa!
Hey!
[You have to go high
to get in the wedding photo!]
[What kind of jump picture will come out?]
- Good!
- Hey
[This time... Hyori?]
[Can that happen...?]
[Hyori is in the picture!]
[Ugh, seriously!]
How can she come into the picture again!
Isn't it photoshop?
I didn't know I would come out either.
[Right at the moment the photo was taken]
Take a look at this!
Look at this expression.
[In bloom]
[As expected she is in bloom!]
You're the best!
And the next photo!
[Blooming again!]
[Gary is peaceful]
Look at this.
[Different photos, same expression!]
[Cheap team 1:2 Expensive team]
[The expensive team
acquires the last password]
[Last password is 2]
Now all we need to do
is figure out the password.
We're going. Go!
[The expensive team
what won at the game leaves first!]
[Don't walk, run!]
[The cheap team departs]
They're coming!
Hurry!
Hurry, hurry!
Hurry hurry!
[They have to enter the password]
[The cheap team also arrives!]
If you get the password right,
it'll happen in a flash.
So you have to do it quickly.
It's 6!
6!
[You have to make sure they don't know]
The next is 3! 3!
Hurry!
Try number 5
[Jong Kook remembers exactly!]
[Flustered]
[Now all that's left is one number!]
We're almost there.
Press it, press it.
[The last number the expensive team got]
[Expensive team: 2]
[Cheap team: 1]
[Expensive team succeeds!]
[They can leave!]
[Disappointed]
[They solved the password puzzle!]
Hyori!
[The entrance opens]
[Finally!]
[More thrilling than Shawshank prison]
[Current time: 8:30 AM.
Now it's time to go to work!]
The sunlight is getting to my eyes.
We should of had sunglasses ready.
You know...
we'll decide who gets to leave and
who has to get the punishment by playing rock paper scissors.
Deciding who gets the punishment!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh yeah!
[Suk Jin is chosen!]
Rock paper scissors!
[Haha is also chosen!]
[A while later...]
[In the middle of the shopping mall]
[A strange woman?]
Hello! Nice to meet you!
Going down to the first floor!
Going down!
I'm carrying out my punishment right now.
[Embarrassed]
I think I'm going to go nuts.
What's up with this?
Nice to meet you.
Which floor?
[Very kind hearted]
Good...
Say hoooo
- Say ho~
- Ho~
South Korea!
People going to the 4th floor scream!
May I shake your hand?
Come on~
No, just a handshake!
If you need help
finding something I'll help you.
No matter what it is, I'll help you.
This is a restaurant.
Hello~
- You can ask anything.
- Is this the front gate?
Is this the front gate?
This is the front gate~
Hello!
Let's say Running Man and Bang
Don't walk, run! Running Man!
[The second landmark
is Suwon world cup stadium]
[Running Man's unstoppable instincts!]
[In order to escape,
extraordinary hurdles!]
[And...]
[And Jae Suk who
only makes dangerous choices]
[What is going to drive him till the end?]