Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by KJK Global
In the
middle of Seoul city ...
A place full of
dreams and adventures
A magical
night
is coming
A place where there's no people
became the stage for Running Man
Your heart just shrivels up.
Extraordinary missions
Run.
Let's go.
Run freely within
the dream land
Enjoy watching with
Bongsun ~
Running Man~
You're really an amazing woman.
Where will Running Man have to run today?
A place that gifted us
with memories and dreams for over 20 years
Over 90 million visitors in total
Representative of Korea
L Theme-Park
* L theme park = Lotte World
Like a dream
Late at night at a theme park
This is for you.
with nobody else around
There's songs playing.
They are more excited than ever
We'd have to wait in line
for everything here ...
Memories of childhood faintly appearing
... ﻿like for 40 minutes or so.
I haven't been here in 10 years.
It's been so long.
I've actually never been here for pleasure.
This place filled with dreams will be
Really?
It's awkward since no one's here.
the stage for only Running Man today
It kind of feels like we are
in a movie or a drama ...
... since we're in a theme
park after opening hours.
A theme park after it's closed
everyone has dreamed about it
You're dressed all colorful
for this theme park.
This is my neighborhood.
Proud
My house is just next to here.
Gary Kang who lives in Jamsil.
* Jamsil-dog = Neighborhood in
Songpa-Du district is Seoul
He earned his pocket money
here when he was a kid.
The stage here is where Gary
performed his dance moves.
The dance competition.
Gary won in a dance competition here
Oh really?
Just in case you didn't believe me.
What's that?
This is evidence from
15 years ago, hyungnim.
15 years old
newspaper
"I want to be a good son and give
the prize money to my parents".
"﻿A high-school dancing trio, JS".
Guess what JS stands for.
Trio JS?
JS means ...
Jae...suk.
Jam...sil.
Jam...sil...?
Yes.
You lived here since you were a kid.
15 years ago
Gary in the last year of high school
So it is true.
Now
Here comes today's Running Man guests
Returned as a Quiz King
Game devil
Kim Sooro
Bubbly girl
Shin Bongsun
The best rock idol
Lee Hongki
Today's guests
Kim Sooro
Shin Bongsun
Hyungnim ...
After Family Outing ...
Sooro and Jaesuk meet again
Ah, isn't this Yoo Jaesuk?
Hongki ...
Bongsun ...
Oppa ...
Oppa!
Bongsun storming to someone
Surprised
Oppa ~
Unexpected situation
Hugs~
Thoughtlessly storming to her ideal type Jongkook
Bongsun ~
Whether her direct senior greets her or not
Hey.
I'm your comedian senior.
Nice to meet you sunbaenim.
Come here ~
Rather than senior
Love comes first
It feels like oppa has rented
this whole place just for me.
Bongsun's ideal type Jongkook
rented this whole theme park?
I'm sweating all over my body
after carrying Bongsun.
I just broke out in a cold sweat.
That means he's nervous when I'm around.
That's right.
You are starting straight away
from the opening, aren't you?
What?
I told you to stop starting
up love-lines in programs.
* Referring to Jongkook's love-lines in X-man (with Yoon
Eunhye) and Family Outing (with Lee Hyori & Park Yejin)
Ah, really.
He changed his character
when he came here ...
... so he talks so much now.
MC M(uscle) has become a chatterbox
He's not the one man
you knew in the past.
* Referring to Jongkook's hit song from his 2nd album
He's not the One Man
Bongsun had liked?
He's not as serious anymore,
you should know that Bongsun.
I still like you no matter what.
Yes, Bongsun.
Oppa, this is our first night together.
* In Korea your 'first night together' has
the connotation of being your wedding night
What do you mean tonight
is our first night together ?
First
night
together
Panic
It's the first time I've come to a
theme park with my boyfriend.
Jongkook and Bongsun's
first night
Strange and stingy
A bitter-sweet late night date
You're an ...
... amazing woman.
An amazing woman...
You really give your all to a man.
Today...
The most powerful love story will begin
Jihyo, you have to do
something like Bongsun.
No, she doesn't.
What are these two doing?
No, but Jihyo ...
Hyungnim and Hongki come back here.
Just continue with Bongsun.
Pissed
No, it's not that.
Ah hyung, you never change.
They're not even
talking about me
So the rumors were right.
He gets annoyed so easily.
He still complains about
the side dishes in his 40s.
42 years old this year Complaining Mr Kim Sooro
Hongki, ﻿I heard you're a hot issue in Japan.
New confident hallyu star
FT Island Lee Hongki
He's a hallyu star now.
I saw Hongki two years
ago on "Family Outing".
But he has become a young man now.
Two years ago, because he was a
teenager, he talked a lot but ...
Since I haven't been on a Korean
TV show for more than a year ...
... I feel nervous.
Don't worry.
We must take care of you.
Annoyed
I came as a guest ...
I am not family anymore,
I'm here as a guest today!
Bongsun and then Hongki...
Sooro is annoyed
Didn't you wear this in Family Outing?
You really do love me, don't you?
A little attention and
he's already fine
He used to wear that when
we filmed Family Outing.
Now or the past...
Sooro's still a cutie in his 40s
We have Sooro with us today ...
And his movie ...
What is it?
I heard he called up and asked us to
mention a lot about his upcoming movie.
Extremely embarrassed
So you shot a film, what's it about?
To say that so directly...
You don't need to say it that way ...
... everyone will know about it
through their own way nowadays.
You're Quiz Man, aren't you?
Quiz King.
Angry
Why do you sound angry?
It's not a big thing to get angry about
He keeps saying its Quiz
Man, when it's Quiz King.
I told you not to point at me.
Don't point.
Isn't Jongkook so manly?
Bongsun is really into him
She says he's manly when
he points at his hyungs.
Bongsun talked to me about you privately.
Bongsun also talks about Jongkook privately
I really can't focus today.
If she gets married with Jongkook oppa ...
... ﻿she said she won't make you work.
She said she'll take care of everything.
Oppa, you just work out.
No, strangely ...
An unanticipated proposal
I really envy him, oppa
only needs to exercise.
Are you going to get me a gym?
Of course.
What will be the name of the gym?
Bong-Kook.
Bong-Kook gym
It'll be Bong-Kook.
Bong from my name and
Kook from your name.
Derived from their names Bongsun and Jongkook
The name of the gym is Bong-Kook.
Head of Bong-Kook gym Jongkook
Whose name will it be under?
Just in-case oppa runs away,
I will put it under my name.
Good for you, you're smart.
Everything under Bongsun's name
The secret of a wise wife
She's clever no doubt
Bongsun over there ...
Jihyo, Kwangsoo, Sukjin
and Sooro on this team.
Blue Team
Red Team
Wow, that team is ...
In that team, I think Hongki
will take Song Jihyo's role.
Red Team
Hongki takes care of the beauty role
I rank 14 on "Heroes", among 14 people.
* "Heroes" is a funny reality show
In HEROES Bongsun's
beauty ranking is 14 among 14
You are also going to be
on Heroes after our show?
She'll be active full time on Good Sunday today
Yes, for the second half as well.
Wow, you're amazing.
You take care of Sunday's SBS.
SBS ... Shin BongSun.
Shin
Bong
Sun
First we should decide what
the punishment will be.
What will today's punishment be?
Let's do hot pants.
We won last week.
The biggest embarrassment
Hot Pants
We had to go home in hot pants
because we lost last week.
Really?
Last week
Hot pants embarrassing moment
From what happened last week,
I think we kind of smell bad.
I sat next to a lady on the bus and ...
Okay ...
Then ...
Cuts off
I'm talking here.
Then ...
Crying
Hey, I'm about to hit the climax.
Explodes
The complaints against MC M(uscle) since last week exceeds
He's really getting me angry.
I'm sorry.
You've changed a lot.
The hyungs endless jeering
I didn't do it on purpose.
Why?
It's because he has no presence.
Hey, why you ...
Bongsun, aren't you going
to see me on Thursday?
For Jongkook she'll stand up
against her senior
Aren't you going to do the show with me?
That's then, but today ...
Bongsun is unstoppable
Pretends~
Kidding
Why you~
How can you do that to a woman.
It's okay oppa, I'm fine
even if I get hit here.
* Plastic surgery on her nose
I can get back up again.
Love makes Bongsun stronger
Right ~
You have to wear hot pants if you lose.
Okay.
Since we're at a theme park ...
Hot pants has been decided for punishment
... ﻿let's add hair bands and the balloons.
Adding
The theme park's hair band & balloons
Of course.
Hair bands, holding balloons
and the hot pants.
Okay, that's fine.
Which team will wear hot pants and hair band?
I can't walk like this.
Appearance of
smooth legs in Jamsil
Walk faster.
Get ready for a rare clip
that can't be seen anywhere else
Let's see what happens.
The mission starts now
Let's get changed and get started.
After getting changed
the missions will start
Oppa, let's go.
We have to get changed separately.
No ~
I came under the condition
we'll change together.
Running Man's ...
Good, Bong Sun.
We have two leaders.
first romantic(?) night will begin
Are you happy that we're here?
Yes, did you really rent this place?
Told them to get ready for filming
but Bongkook couple is dating(?) ♥
Oppa ...
This is the first time I went to a
theme park with my boyfriend.
Nasal sound
This is the first time for me too, to
go to place like this with a woman.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Oppa, I think you'll look handsome
if you ride those white horses.
Muscle prince riding a white horse?
I'm ...
Oppa, there's no one here.
We have to move quickly.
Just hug me once.
No one is here.
I'll keep this as a secret.
We have to go. There's a camera here.
There are cameras everywhere
so how can it be a secret?
Just once.
Hug me once, there's no one here.
Just hug me once.
Okay ~
Succeeds
A hug celebrating the visit to a theme park
More beautiful than an afternoon
Bongkook couple's first night(?)
We'll get on to it straight away.
The most popular ride in a theme park
Roller Coaster
You know what this is right?
Yes.
I can't ride these.
Roller coaster ~
Really can't ride these.
Who's good at riding roller coasters?
Bongsun, do you like roller coasters?
I'll be fine if I'm with oppa.
If it's with him
it's okay
Really?
Yes.
On the way here just now ...
... he kept trying to drag me ﻿to
places where there was no one else.
When did I?
Bongsun are spreading rumors
so Jongkook can't get away from her
I saw it.
Really?
I saw you two.
It's simple, for the first game ...
... we have to sing while
we're on the roller coaster?
First mission
Roller coaster duet karaoke
You want us to sing on this?
Sing?
It's hard enough to ride the roller
coaster, so how can we sing?
Sing while riding the roller coaster.
Those with highest karaoke score wins
The result depends on the karaoke score?
This has got nothing to do
with your singing abilities.
We already decided on
the song "Blue In You".
Bongkook couple gets a typical duet song
<Blue in you>
Let's just choose a dance song.
No, "Blue in you".
Just sing "Blue in you".
Whines
Usually couples kiss while
they're on the rides, right?
What to do?
Don't know
Glares
You two are going first?
Yes ~
Red Team
Bongkook couple
<Blue in you>
Kim Hyunchul & Lee Sora
Then get on.
"Blue in you".
Sighs~
The couple singing the duet
will sit at the front
The front seats are the scariest.
I never thought I would ride a
roller coaster this late at night.
Yeah, this is going to be no joke.
Honestly, I'm not good at riding these.
Hang on, my stomach ...
It will start as soon I push this.
It won't be an easy mission
Fighting ~
What to do?
Bongsun, you go first.
♪ I close my eyes ... ♪
So it's just like that.
Sister-in-law, come back safely.
Oh, you're doing well.
She's really closing her eyes.
Bongsun is really dating.
What to do?
Jihyo, isn't this romantic?
♪ ﻿Now the darkness ... ♪
What do I do?
The roller coaster heads towards the top
Oh my god ...
... my earphones fell out.
Good for us, her earphones fell out
Big disaster without earphones
she can't hear the music
What do I do?
Let's go.
Tight...
He holds her hand first
It may not be for love ...
but at least her fears go away
Bongsun and Jongkook ♥
♪ Our meeting and the darkness ... ♪
Aaahhh ...
Here it goes
Hard to sing
It falls straight like this, right?
♪ ﻿The time stains within the  ♪
♪ light. ﻿It starts flowing again. ♪
Mine is falling out.
Now's the start
a 360 degree turn
A places where the voice exceeds its limit
Hey, look at Jongkook singing.
His vibratos are great.
Without much effort
automatic vibrato
Thinking that the hard part is gone
♪ Now the darkness ... ♪
♪ ... comes!!! ♪
I love you?
The law of centrifugal force
Full speed turning part
You have to sing.
Faints
How can she sing in a situation like this?
Finally
Already arrived but ...
... their love song continues
Tight...
This is really ...
burning with just one song
Love extensively
Jongkook really loves someone
like that in a program.
A beautiful finish~
The score ~
Red Team
What will
Bongkook couple's score be?
Remember that there
was a singer in this team.
77 is better than expected
Not bad ~
We ...
got close ♥
"﻿One and a half", we'll sing "One and a half".
Blue Team
Jaesuk-Jihyo couple
<1 and 1/2>
Tutu
You're going to get a score
that's 1 and 1/2 of our score.
We have to get over 77, Jihyo.
There's a strategy for this
You have to keep saying something
and no matter what just shout, okay?
I understand.
Strategy to get a high score
Keep making noise
Jihyo, got it?
Yes.
Fighting.
Let's go.
Grooving since the music starts~
Mic test.
Hope they do the same when the ride starts
We'll get over 77.
Make big noises, okay?
Answer me.
Can't hear
Annoyed
2, 3, 4.
♪ ﻿When I saw you from afar, ﻿I  ♪
♪ thought of going the other way ♪
Make sure to go over 77.
I think they're going to get a high score.
Worried
♪ ﻿I want to see the changed you. ♪
♪ ﻿Hoping that you would  ♪
♪ greet me even if its shortly. ♪
♪ One step forward with a beating heart. ♪
Shakes
They can sing so happily now.
How is it where they are now?
You can sing with no worries ...
Comfortably.
... and even dance.
Still on a comfortable stage to sing
Oh my god.
Now...
When they pass this point...
It's dark!
I can't see ~
Cries
Speed up
♪ So I ... ♪
♪ We're able to become ... ♪
♪ Aaaaarrrrggg .... ♪
Gives up on singing
What is this?
I think he can't even scream.
Jihyo swallowed the mic already.
What's Jaesuk doing?
Is Jihyo there alone?
This person is also on it
It's too scary.
♪ From afar I saw ... ♪
♪ ... aaaaahhhhh. ♪
Automatic voice gain section
360 degree turn
Already gave up on singing
Right, we won.
We don't know the score yet.
... we won.
Better to just enjoy then.
Enjoy.
Told you to sing...
Arrive as if they were beaten to a pulp
Blue Team
Sang a dance song
Jaesuk-Jihyo coupleTheir score is?
Jaesuk-Jihyo scores 74
Bongkook couple had 3 point more
Yes, we won.
Still Blue Team scored 74 because they screamed so much
Hey, how come you didn't sing?
We won oppa
You were like Aaaaahhh.
What was that?
And the safety bar keeps hitting your face.
Because of the safety bar Worst condition to sing
It hurts so much.
You should've sang Jihyo.
Total darkness, we couldn't see anything.
You try singing oppa.
Angry
See if you can do it like
what you would expect.
How dare you shout
when you only scored 74.
You're keep provoking her.
Anyway Red Team
has the highest score
Only 74.
Ah, only 3 points difference.
Let's go, Sooro.
Sukjin-Sooro couple goes
Fighting.
Expecting over 90 points from Game Devil
Hyung you have to score over 90, okay?
Put my theme song on.
What I'm worried about is that ...
... ﻿Sooro doesn't care about
being funny for the program.
Victory rather than laughs
Game devil Sooro
You know right?
In Family Outing ...
In 'Family Outing' days
He used to win most of the games he played
Hey, let's score 100, let's go
Think about your age hyungnim.
An rather old song
<Last Night s Story> Fire Engine 87
♪ ﻿Last night, I came to dislike you. ♪
♪ ﻿Last night I came to hate you. ♪
Assa ...
Non-stop music
Spinning around
It's a duet but they are
singing different lyrics
I was ...
... depressed.
... heart broken.
Sooro will score 80, no doubt.
Look at that.
Predicts
Sooro will sing no matter what
whether he's scared or not
He's still fine.
Sooro hyung doesn’t have any fear of these rides
Let's go.
Fear
Wow, it's starting.
♪ My wound ... ♪
♪ My heart ... ♪
♪ Why couldn't you see ... ♪
♪ Why can't you see ... ♪
♪ Last niiiiiigth ... ♪
It's going down
♪ ﻿Last night's party was so lonesome. ♪
♪ ﻿I can't swap you for something  ♪
♪ else even if it's the whole world. ♪
Opens wide
♪ How come you don't know. ♪
♪ Pa ... Soo ... Swa ... Pa. ♪
Only getting this part right
We can't even hear them screaming.
Don't worry, I'm sure they
will be singing perfectly.
Aigoo, you two are so close together.
Yeah, we just got married.
Looks like your husband has been working out a lot
Yeah ...
I just make him work out.
Oh, really?
Getting into the automatic voice gain zone
Sukjin gives up on singing
On the other hand Game Devil Sooro goes solo
Look, Sooro is still singing.
Look.
Loud
Now the full speed section
At least making some noises
Finally
The roller coaster arrives
Alive
Dead
No lyrics in this part.
I told you no lyrics.
Bara Ba Ba Ba ...
Look at their hair.
Have to sing here if they want more points
Hey, it's not there.
Fights
Quarrels
♪ ﻿My friends ... ♪
So far the highest score is
Bongkook couple's 77
77.
Sadly equal to the Red Team
You know you're so mean.
Why?
What are you doing to my husband?
Standing up for her husband
The queen of housewives Bongsun
This woman ...
You turned the music off because
you thought ﻿it'd be too risky.
Complaining that he turned the music off
to make the score lower
How could you do that?
What?
The song had already ended and ...
I heard you say ...
We turned it off because
they sucked at singing.
You were like "I have to turn
this off quickly" and you went.
Now
Blue Team
Red Team
are equal
Next up
Red Team
HaHa-Hongki
<Wrongful meeting>
Kim Gunmo
Unable to sing high notes
Sub-vocal HaHa
Stable main vocal
Hongki
Hongki's enjoying it
Everyone talking about Hongki's singing abilities
Can you hear Hongki singing?
Wow, Hongki's so good at singing.
Hongki's so good.
His singing abilities, as expected.
♪ ﻿I had to give up my love and friendship ♪
HaHa already gave up
What will
the score be for HaHa-Hongki couple?
Scoring the highest so far
It's okay ~
Kwangsoo ...
What’s the highest score right now?
Kwangsoo is attempting a solo challenge
HaHa and Hongki's ﻿78 is
the highest score for now.
Have to get over 78 points to win
Kwangsoo ...
It's okay, it’ll be hard to get over 78.
I think you have to ...
... ﻿start screaming from the beginning.
I understand.
Kwangsoo ...
Yes.
... you're good at singing, right?
I'm confident.
Kwangsoo is full of confidence
Kwangsoo fighting.
Fighting.
Coughs
Kwangsoo, are you okay?
I'm okay ...
You're not okay.
How can he sing when he's coughing?
Why are you so weak?
No, I'm not.
Get this locked.
It's just my appearance that looks weak.
Your face looks like Hongchul
the more and more I see you.
Kwangsoo, it all depends on you.
Blue Team
Last hope
What song did Kwangsoo choose?
Why did you choose such a hard song.
<Faint memories of you>
Hyun Jinyoung
1,2,3,4, start.
♪ Foggy mist ... ♪
That's it, we won.
We lost ~
confident with skills like this?
He said he was
Totally into it
We won.
Let's not waste time, just give us the ball.
We lost ~
The more they hear it
depressing
You told us you were good at singing.
First of all ...
He's totally into singing
no matter what everyone says
... he has no sense of rhythm.
Ignoring pitch and rhythm
Only singing with his feeling
Louder.
Jump ~
Getting into
the groove
Say ho ...
Ho ~
Say ho ho ho ...
Ho ho ho ~
Say ho ...
Everyone shout.
Shout yourself.
♪ ﻿Hazy cigarette smoke, ﻿flashy  ♪
♪ outfit reflected on the mirror. ♪
Hit it.
He just needs to be loud.
For the karaoke machine you need to be loud
You never know.
I rather not hear him singing.
Red Team is relieved
You never know, we might win.
Kwangsoo there's no one to ride with him
I can't see anything.
Jaesuk, I can't see anything.
Roller coaster speed up
Already lost his pitch, rhythm and lyrics
At least his voice is loud
I think he'll do fine since
he has a loud voice.
It's okay ~
I guarantee we’ll get over 80 points.
Anticipates
Of course, he making
loud noises non stop.
His thunderous voice makes them anticipate
Now the roller coaster's highlight section
Can't tell if it's a rap or a wail
Lucky he is still sane
Kwangsoo's roller coaster arrives
Keeps dancing and making additional chorus Not singing
Block them, otherwise
they'll turn the song off.
Trying until last minute
to raise the score
Red Team tries to stop Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo tries to sing
regardless of Red Team's distraction
♪ Full of sadness ... ♪
A late night mass fight in the theme park
The song finally finishes
Red Team is leading with 78 points
Please ~
Blue Team's last hope
Kwangsoo
What will Kwangsoo's score be?
A shocking score
Last place
Red Team
Secure their win
What's 52 points? 52 points.
We could've got 60 if we had a turn.
Bang
52?
Can't look up at them
What are you doing in front of a pole?
Kwangsoo, 52 points.
What can you do with 52 ... 52.
They had all their hopes on him
I'm going crazy ... 52 points.
We would have lost
even if we sang more.
Gloomy
It would've been more than
52 even if you just screamed.
Jihyo is not this kind of
person, but even she said ...
Even kind Jihyo
doesn't understand 52
... "Hey, really, 52".
So the Red Team wins the first game.
Red Team
Gets the first Running Ball
You are going to race.
2nd mission
Bell hide and seek
Same as last time.
We'll decide on the hide
team and the seek team.
The hiding team has
to carry out a mission.
Wait, my stomach ...
Seeking team will have bells on
their shoes while chasing them.
Seeking is too difficult.
Huh?
Where is Jaesuk going?
Jongkook, do you want to hide this time?
Where are you going?
My stomach hurts so much.
Jaesuk oppa has a stomachache
right after he hears the word bells.
Is it because of the bells?
Is it really because of the bells?
Real situation
Jaesuk have a hysteria for the sound of the bells
He runs off right away after
he hears the word bells.
I'm not kidding, my stomach really hurts.
There's a restroom upstairs.
Why is our team like this today?
If you want to find Jaesuk, just use
the bells and search in the restroom.
Since Jaesuk is hiding already,
let us be the hide team again.
No ~
Wants to be the hide-team again
Blue Team
Because hiding is a bit easier.
Since it's quite dark around here,
I think it will be easier to hide.
Actually, we wanted to be the seeking team ...
Red Team
Also wants to be the hiding team
But my condition isn't at the best, so ...
Don't lie oppa you, just want
to date with Bongsun unnie.
Is it really...
because he wants to hide and date?
Oh, oppa we got caught.
Let's leave them to date then.
Oppa let's run far away.
Far away where there's nobody.
Sorry to interrupt, but Bongsun
are you here to shoot a drama?
Since next scene is a kissing
scene, I'm a bit nervous.
You're not letting go of each other's hands.
Holding so tightly.
You're bleeding.
Disregarding who started it Now it's so natural
She keeps holding my hand.
They don't even hold hands
like that in "We Got Married".
An over-affectionate love that you
wouldn't even see in <We Got Married>
You are really great.
The show is called Running Man,
so why are you holding hands?
We got running.
* Pun on the show "We got married"
We Got Running
We have to find Jongkook
and Bongsun quickly.
Catch Jongkook.
Kim Jongkook
Shin Bongsun
We're the only ones left now
They only have one mission left.
The best chaser
Kim Sooro
Oppa ...
You are an amazing woman.
Starting now
A scene you can't watch without tears
Now the love race begins
Hongki, come here.
As always...
Yes, I got it.
The hiding team
is relaxing while waiting for their mission
Where?
Here ...
Really?
They said the mission is in here.
Ah, really?
Take a photo of the bar-code and
mission will be revealed
Yes ~
The newest technology.
Click
"Hello this is Running Man".
Find the tickets from three places
Oh, it's here.
Children's ride Happy Picnic ...
[Tickets are hidden here]
(1) Ticket booth
(2) Children's ride
[Happy picnic]
(3) 2nd floor water fountain
Children's ride ...
Hang on, so ...
Close~
Do you really have to put
your face here, like this?
I just feel a bit dizzy.
Is that so?
From what I've seen in past episodes ...
... we'll get caught 100%
if we run as a group.
Hongki's opinion
"If we flock together, we'll get caught"
That's right ~
Getting caught.
In a group we definitely ...
... get caught 100%.
So let's all separate.
Can Jongkook finally run away from Bongsun?
No, I can't because I'm bad with directions.
No, you have to be with Jongkook.
That's right.
Read Team
Starts to do their mission
Separate ~
Fighting.
First
HaHa and Gary go their own way
I'll go.
Yeah.
Fast Hongki also takes off
Hongki fighting.
What someone intended(?)
All have gone separate ways
So now only Bongkook couple remains as two
Let's go.
Let's go where there's no one else.
Where's a place like that?
Somewhere dark.
Bongsun wait.
Bongsun wants to go behind a stall
We have to play this game.
Think about what we have to find.
We have to find our love.
Love comes before the mission ♥
Let's hide first.
Oppa you want to hide as well?
Meanwhile the seekers
Blue Team
Do we put these on our shoes?
Putting bells on their shoes
Yes, we have to put these on our shoes.
You don't know how scary it is to
hear these bells when you're chased.
The chased team's frightened to death
by this sound
Oh?
Did you get the text?
Instructions arrive
Rip off all 5 name-tags from opposing team
Get all 5 name tags off the
opposing team within an hour.
Chasing team, you can start now.
Blue Team
The chase
Are we starting?
Let's catch them all.
Jongkook ~
Hey, Sooro.
Full of confidence because of Game Devil Sooro
Fighting.
I feel more at ease having the bell.
Memories of hearing the bell
More confident now
There's no reason to be nervous.
This is also your first time right?
They usually hide so they're enjoying it now
I've always ...
You'll lose weight.
... ﻿wanted to walk proudly with ease.
Time remaining
Position of the 3 treasures Red Team needs to find
Game Devil
Sooro
chase started
Searching every area at a fast speed
Scanning every single place
Eyes like a hawk
Armed with the bell
Game Devil
The epitome of fear
Kwangsoo ...
Yes?
If you get separated from me, we
have to meet back as soon as possible.
Teaching
Devil's advice to variety newcomer Kwangsoo
If I see them somewhere, just run.
At this moment
Target found
Game Devil
Already spotted Red Team's Gary
Instead of approaching silently
Direct
charge
Jingle~
Game
Devil
Sooro?
Quickly
Gary escaping immediately~!
Raa ~ awwr
Full round pursuit in such a huge place
started only 5 minutes ago
Hide-n-seek game
Game Devil
Will he already catch one person?
Gary barely escapes up a staircase
Due to Game Devil's pursuit
Physical strength reduced to Zero
Game Devil immediately scans the surroundings
This is crazy.
Kwangsoo is still loitering near the stair
Game Devil's disciple
Still hawk-eyed ...
Game Devil
Surrounded
Clang!!
Gary moved and touched the chain
Game Devil's disciple Kwangsoo Heard that sound
If Gary just runs like this ...
Again
Escapes with all his strength
Kim Sooro teacher ...
Game Devil rushed upon hearing his disciple
He's here.
Because of previous escape attempt
Gary is physically drained
Isn't that Gary's voice?
Big Nose also joins the hunt
Catch him ~
Suddenly
Stuck in the middle
Gary
Blue Team
totally surrounded
What is this...?
Hide-n-seek started
only 5 minutes ago
Tear it off
Got it.
Gary is caught ~
Gary
Meanwhile
Bongkook couple
Hold on.
Confirm the surrounding
Heading toward the water fountain
on the 2nd floor that has the ticket
But ...
A bell sound
Somewhere at the stairs...!
Jihyo is close to the stairs
Suddenly
Bongkook couple Returning to 1st floor in a panic
Jongkook spotted
Oppa ~
I found them.
Oppa, they're here.
Bongkook couple
Hides in a storeroom next to the stairs
Did she see us?
Oppa, they're here.
Total crisis
They're here ~
Where?
Where are they?
Blue Team
Gather after receiving the news
Bongkook couple hides behind this door
Where did they go?
Are they near here?
Nervous
Sukjin...
is slowly...
approaching...?!
Thump
You'll also get scared hearing the bells.
Threatening
Sukjin, he left
Luckily He didn't look behind the wood door
You better hide properly.
Blue Team left after finding nothing
Bongkook couple relieved from their biggest crisis
Run.
Running back to
2 layered fountain just now
Again scanning for the Blue Team~
The fountain must be somewhere here
The 2nd floor fountain
Somewhere here
The ticket must definitely be hidden
HaHa also found the fountain Everybody gathered
Don't know when the Blue Team will appear
Ticket hidden inside the lion's mouth?
Found it, let's go.
Found 1 of the 3 tickets
Remaining time
Still has 2 more tickets to find
Ah, my back hurts.
Oppa your back hurts?
Startled
It's okay.
Bongsun worries for Jongkook all the time
What shall we do?
Is this your back oppa?
Then... is it Bongsun's?
At this moment
Hey, the bells.
Bongkook couple escapes once again Without a moment of rest
But Bongsun
can't keep up with Jongkook
Sukjin today's tough seeker
Bongsun is hiding behind the shop
Here ...
Meanwhile Sukjin is chasing Jongkook
They're here.
What will Jongkook oppa do?
Jongkook is on the 1st floor.
Jongkook hides in a staircase that's hard to see
Looking around
Jongkook oppa ...
Separated Bongkook couple
What will their destiny be...?
I think he's been caught.
Oppa ...
Meanwhile...
Blue Team
Seeker Yooruce Willis ...
Spotted Gary who has already been caught
Talking to teammates
through walkie-talkie
A chance to eavesdrop on Red Teams whereabouts
Crawls
Yooruce Willis got 3 meters away
Jingle...
But hyungnim ...
Why are you behaving like a child?
Yooruce Willis pretends nothing happened
Red Team
Relaying some important information
Yooruce Willis
Can't leave just yet
Slip~
Yooruce Willis
Took off the shoe with the bell?
Really...
Had thought there was no bell sound
This is against the rules.
How is this against the rules?
You're already so old that
you can't behave like this.
My shoes are too big,
so I took them off.
Thick skinned
We didn't do that last time.
I won't break rules again.
Be careful, Jaesuk is walking barefooted.
Time remaining
Hongki arrives near the merry-go-round that has a ticket
It's here.
Tickets place according to the instructions
"Happy picnic"
It should be somewhere here
It's there
To take the ticket from that height ...
No choice but to take the ride
Gasp...!
The fearful
bell sound
Hongki might get caught once he gets off
Just a little bit more
Snatch
Hongki got the 2nd ticket
He needs to get down and escape
The bell sounds are getting louder
Hongki finally escapes the battle
Game Devil
Why is the
strongest seeker here?
Game Devil
Making a dash after spotting Hongki
Run.
Let's go~
Threaten
Aaahhh!
Catch him.
Even walkie-talkie is redundant
with Game Devil's loud voice
2nd floor?
The whole team is coming
At his call...
Hongki escapes very fast but ...
Blue Team forms a circle
Game Devil
Giving commands at the back
last attempt to escape
Hongki's
However...!
Caught
Sooro's final attack
Red Team
Hongki
Red Team's agile Hongki is already out
As expected from Game Devil
Time remaining
HaHa goes to the ticket booth
where the last ticket is hidden
After hearing the bell sound
HaHa went to a sticker photo-booth
Thump
Yooruce Willis is approaching
Go faster...
Yooruce Willis is just beside it
Eh?
He is there
ha ha ha ha
He didn't see me, right?
Phew...
He's going
Jaesuk pretending to walk away
VJ, move over here
Jingle~
Stopped
Now...
Why don't you try to escape?
Gone...
Is he really gone?
Geez !!
Tricked
Chaser Yooruce Willis
making a full dash
HaHa is here.
The Yooruce Willis who was always being chased
Finally...!!
Pant...
Exhausted
I am Hrad Pitt.
And I am ...
... Yoobocop.
Not Robocop but Yoobocop...?
I'm Haminator.
Playing the Hero Game again
30 year old school kids
I caught HaHa.
Haminator
Bongsun has been separated from Jongkook
Oppa...?
Even while escaping and being chased ...
Jongkook oppa where are you?
Totally devoted to him
Even in times of danger ...
Did Jongkook oppa get caught?
Worried for Jongkook
Pacing back and forth
Earlier he said he hurt.
Where is the one man
she wants to meet?
Jongkook oppa where are you?
Squeak
Footsteps...
Someone...
is approaching
The return of One Man
The one whom she
wanted to see ...
... is back again
Bongkook couple an emotional re-encounter
But the happy moment is short lived
Oppa ...
Where is the ticket booth?
Looking for the ticket booth
with the last hidden ticket
Oppa, I think I saw it just now.
Where?
It's near the merry-go-round.
Really?
It's downstairs.
Red Team's last survivors Bongkook couple
Going to the ticket booth where the last ticket is
Remaining time
Blue Team's getting anxious
We need to find Jongkook and Bongsun quickly.
They said they only have one left.
You two
I will catch you
One ticket
Who will be the winners?
Two survivors
Sparkling hawk-eyed
We're the only ones left now.
We have to go over there.
The power of love is really strong.
The bell sound
The only survivors must be careful
The lights.
Camera lights also
Okay ~
Oppa here ...
...Feels~ weird
It's safe here.
Secretly
It's because I'm tired.
I see.
Are you scared?
Why are you holding that.
Weapon
To protect you.
I'll protect oppa if they come.
Boong
Compared to others, you
are more dependable.
Heart beating
Oppa ...
Kiss...
No one's here.
Nose, my nose ...
... silicon.
Bongkook couple gathered courage
Bongsun ...
Jongkook oppa is leading
Bongsun carries the weapon
Arrives near the merry-go-round
It's just up in front.
Did you see it?
If they move together It'll be dangerous
Oppa, then I'll go out there alone.
You're really ...
... an amazing woman.
You're an amazing woman.
In that case, please give
me a kiss on my forehead.
I can't go out for free.
Bongsun's forehead kiss
Will her dream come true
I'll pretend to hide, pretend to be clumsy.
Opportunity and crisis ...
... comes at the same time
Can't get caught now...!
See you later
Jongkook-Bongsun Going separate ways
Oppa I found them.
Over here.
Found them, over here.
You found them?
Where?
Blue Team
Success over here
Where?
Last mission
Can't let them succeed
Where?
I found them, here.
Over here, 2nd floor.
Jongkook escaping alone
Oppa, 2nd floor.
... 2nd floor.
Blue Team
Everyone runs after Jongkook
Gasp...
Hiding in an inner corner
They're all chasing after oppa.
Bongsun going towards the ticket booth
Over here ~
Discovered by Yooruce Willis
...Maybe not...?!!
Slam!
Bongsun's individual VJ got hit
Bongsun's hitting with the broomstick
Bongsun, this is oppa.
Bongsun ...
Both seniors got hit by her
Trying to
calm her down first
It's oppa.
My mission is to ...
... gain more time for him
Love
Bodyguard
Bongsun ~
Bongsun is fighting for Jongkook
Bongsun calm down, it's us.
Grab!
In front of her full force the 2 men are helpless
Bongsun calm down, it's us.
Bongsun, do you want to commit a crime?
In the end ...
Rips~
You are the best.
Bongsun used this.
Two seniors humiliated
I did it ...
Jongkook oppa ...
Let's go.
I managed to delay time with the broom.
I hope oppa used this time to find it.
Shining self-sacrificed spirit till the end
Time remaining
During this time Jongkook is
approaching the ticket booth
Where is it?
It's...
over there!!
Ah... Missed that
He's too anxious and missed it
I'm going crazy.
Blue Team is standing around the ticket booth
Jihyo
She saw me.
What should I do?
Once Jihyo inform the rest
Run down the stairs
if Jihyo comes, got it?
Strategy
Make use of VJ to disguise himself?
Still discovered by Jihyo
Jihyo was startled so she's easy to avoid
Jongkook's final escape
Getting pass Sukjin
and Game Devil as well
full force
To capture Jongkook
Blue Team
Will he get caught
or find the last ticket?
Although they surrounded him Can't catch him
Yooruce Willis in action
Pursuer
This time...
I'll catch you
Over there is
the ticket booth
Reincarnated Yooruce Willis persistent chase
Finally...?
Yooruce Willis
Catches Jongkook
Jongkook
Victory.
Red Team's 5 members all
Blue Team
Bell hide-n-seek
Victory
Hey, Kim Jongkook ...
... after the movie "Chawu", ﻿this is
the first time I have been so scared.
* In the 2009 movie "Chawu" a man-eating boar goes on a rampage
Mission clear, Blue Team victory.
Chawu
Jongkook
A leisurely cup of tea.
3rd mission
A leisurely cup of tea
When all burdens disappear
Happy(?) tea time
Kim Jongkook, you were
being chased by us ...
When they were chasing Jongkook
No, that's not it.
I thought it was the movie "Chawu".
Seemed like a scene from the movie <Chawu>
How could it be Chawu?
Jongkook was running toward me ...
How scared must he have been ...
... ﻿I'm not in a theme park
... but on a highway.
... to think he's on a highway
Felt like I was on a highway.
You know, that sound when a truck comes.
It felt like this is a highway.
Human truck
Sooro hyung was there and I trusted him ...
At that moment reliable Sooro appeared
... but Sooro just pretended to chase.
And wait a minute ...
... this is the first time I have seen
someone hit someone with a broom.
Shin Bongsun broom incident(!)
I was hit on the back of my head.
The first time, it was funny, hey a broom.
I didn't think she's hit us for real.
But
Targeting the seniors with the broom
Can't even recognize the comedian seniors
Scary strength of love(?!)
Even during the game ...
... she said she would fight til the end.
Is that so?
How could you leave Bongsun
and run away by yourself?
I told you before, it's no
use treating him so well.
No use to treat Jongkook well?
He said if I used myself as bait, he
would give me a kiss on my forehead.
One man, in this case ...
No ...
Kiss ~
The atmosphere is getting hotter ~
He said he'll give you a kiss on
forehead if he uses you as bait?
Kim Jongkook, do you know
what happened in this place?
In the drama "Stairways to Heaven".
Stairways to heaven
Kwang Sangwoo and Choi Jiwoo
did the forehead kiss here.
Forehead kiss
Oh really?
This actual merry-go-round
No wonder I wanted a forehead kiss.
Displaying ﻿pure white love
Affectionate forehead kiss
You are wearing a hairpin because of this?
Oh, that’s right.
Princess Jiwoo preparation done
In that case, give us
the boomerang as well.
... give us the boomerang as well.
Stairways to Heaven
Lead actor must have a boomerang
So I can throw it.
To hit the target?
Do the forehead kiss and
throw the boomerang.
Say 'Love is a feeling that
comes back' and do it.
Famous line
Wasn't it '﻿Love make someone crazy'?
If you do it, I’ll do it too.
Hyungnim, why?
Huh?
Slyly inserting himself
The foolish hyung
Hyung, you're really weird.
What is this?
He didn't want to do, so our team will too.
Even insisting ...
Why would our team do it?
I can do with Kwangsoo, is
there any problem with that?
Why would you do that?
Don't worry, I won't do with you.
Oh, I understand.
Your forehead is shiny, so I don't want to.
Hyung, that was so cheap of you.
Like in primary school, when
children after a fight say ...
Brilliantly
immature
... "﻿I don’t like you too".
The level of an immature elementary school kid
What I meant is ...
... if you do, I'll do too.
Still not admitting defeat
Okay, I'll do it.
It's my team, but aren't
his comments too much?
Cheap characters are the best.
1, 2 ...
40 years old
The best at being cheap
At last Jongkook♥Bongsun forehead kiss
Touch
1, 2 ...
He isn't running away?
Look she's making sure I'm still here.
Why are you doing this?
How do I look, if you have
to make sure that I'm here?
Scared One Man
Anxious One Woman
Bongsun, don't you have any pride?
You're a woman.
Earnest
You have to get it this way?
Okay ~
1, 2, 3.
Closing her eyes once more~
Love ...
... ﻿is a feeling that comes back.
Hard earned(?)
returning love
One woman's waiting
And
Finally...
Eh?
What are you doing?
A kiss.
Didn't you say a forehead kiss?
Do you want me to kiss
her on the forehead?
That was what it was about?
A real forehead kiss
Lead actor understanding the scene now
You were only going to do that?
Do you think so many
cameras film just for that?
An unhappy audience
Are you asking me to kiss her forehead?
Kiss ...
Anyone can do this.
You thought I would use
the broom just for this?
For the embarrassed male lead
Just like this ~
Bad demonstration
Hyung, what are you doing?
Two forehead kisses
Hyung, "I Swear".
♪ I swear ... ♪
Disqusting~
This time...
Closing eyes Showing feeling?
First time I met Kim Jongkook oppa ...
Had a crush on
Jongkook for a long time
... I was so nervous, I thought I
wouldn't be able to do anything.
That's why Bongsun has been
looking forward to this
Love is a feeling that returns
You did it?
Time they spent
running together
The time she
denounced others for him
All that for
this moment...
It's done ~
And
a teary One Man
* One Man is referring to his solo hit "One Man" from 2004
Oppa, are you crying?
Don't cry.
Did you enjoy it?
It's a beautiful night ~
Today's leisurely cup of tea ...
What is it?
Today's tea
Good for fatigue relief
Ssanghwacha
Ah ...
Today we're going to put the
ssanghwacha power in first.
Select a number for a corresponding
spoon to add ssanghwacha with
We'll be adding it first.
Wow, there's a big ladle there.
The appearance of various sized spoons
Hey, that one's used in a Chinese restaurant
Starting with ... Kim Jongkook.
Sure ~
I'll, hmm ...
... number 4.
Number 4.
Flat ladle
What is that?
Can't I know what that is first?
Absurd
What is that?
For you who will live 200 years, here it is.
For the one who'll live for 200 years
A ladle full of ssanghwacha
Please get rid of a bit.
Just take it.
You should add more.
After sweating a lot, just sitting
like this makes me really sleepy.
Right?
Yeah.
Next, because you said
you were sleepy, Bongsun.
Sleepy Bongsun's choice is...?
Which one?
Number 3 ~
Ah, number 3.
Wooden spoon
It's favorable ~
Comparatively a favorable size?
Number 3 is okay.
But why did you pour so much?
Since she said she's sleepy Especially more...
This one and that one ...
Poured with spoon or ladle No difference
How could that and this be the same?
Stands up
Oh, is that it?
Are you taking her side?
It's not that.
You're taking her side
No I'm not.
The instant he
meets her eyes
I'm happy because you took my side.
You shouldn't do this
while conducting the show.
What did I do wrong?
Next, Gary.
Number 5 ~
Gary's choice
Mega sized ladle
Number 5 ~
Shocked
Definitely no. 5
Wait, everything in the bowl isn't enough.
No, the game should be possible.
What is with that?
Dazed...
Please sit, I'll pour it out.
Accurately one scoop
Then please add water to this.
It won't even fit, just
add water to the ladle.
Insisting
Will drink from the ladle
All right, I’ll give it to you moderately
Poured moderately but still almost full
You have to fill the cup.
We can't do that.
It looks like you are going to
drink ssanghwacha powder.
Full
Oh my god.
It's good for your health.
No, I can't give it to you like this.
It looks so impolite.
To be polite
using the cup
There's still some left.
Please take this home.
How do you expect me to drink this?
There's no room left for the eggs
Abundant
HaHa, which number?
Number 4.
The ladle.
Hey, Gary.
Again
The mega sized
ladle
Wait ...
Look for yourself.
Good gracious
The numbers were switched but still ...
They lost.
Why is your luck that bad?
We're sorry we were
born without any luck.
Why do these guys have no luck?
Well, since you can't do anything about it ...
The unlucky two boys
... both of you, this is good for health.
Same huge ladle-full of ssanghwacha
Because there are two
people who are unlucky ...
* Bongsun uses a slightly derogatory term for unlucky
... ﻿will we be able to win?
Right?
How unlucky.
Bongsun is even more mad than Jongkook
Why are these two like this?
Let me change team next
week, I really can't do well.
This really ...
If we do Muscle 28, we're done for.
* Referring to an act in Gag Concert that
had been proposed as punishment
These two, really.
The two boys A careful indication of revolt?
You guys have no luck.
Sit down, quickly.
I'll go now.
It's time for Blue Team to make their choices
All right.
Number 3.
Don't trick us.
Yes, number 3.
Oh, this is okay.
Flat ladle
That now looks small.
Scoop as much as you can.
A comparatively easy amount
You can't do that.
Number 2 ~
It's now Jihyo's turn...
Follows Sukjin's recommendation No. 2
Number 2?
A huge ladle
You told me to pick number 2.
Resentful
You should trust someone more trustworthy
Wait, I'd like to pour it for her.
For a lady customer the lady of the house will...
Liberal
You're a 'katsa' with me, right?
* Katsa = Kateun (same) + samoshil (management company)
What's a katsa?
Gasp
The same management company.
Hey, we're all katsa.
Does that make sense?
What is that, unnie?
You swindlers.
You poured using this,
but it's the same as this.
The same quantity as the
mega sized ladle
This one even has more.
That's how it's supposed to be.
I was being easy because it's Jihyo.
Taking her side
If it was someone else,
I would have had no mercy.
Most certain
a swindling couple
Anyway, you drink it ...
... Jihyo.
Now it's Sukjin's turn.
Which number should I choose?
Number 4.
Jihyo recommends no. 4
4? I'll choose number 1.
I'll choose number 1.
Glare
Number 1 ~
Congratulations.
He choose the mega sized ladle
It really is, look for yourself.
He wants
to check
See number 1.
He should have listened to Jihyo
The generous lady of the house
Pouring straight from the bowl
Hello, wait ...
Why?
Is it Arbor Day? Are you
going to plant a tree?
Why?
I said, "Is it Arbor Day?"
Why? It's fine.
Which number?
It's me, right?
Yes, try a number we haven't said yet.
Blue Team
Lastly Jaesuk
Number 2 ~
Really number 2?
Would you like to choose
number 2 or 3, 1 or 3?
MC M(uscle) is trying to divert him
Are you choosing 2 or 3?
I'm giving you a chance here.
Number 2 or 3.
I won't be tricked
Number 2.
It's really number 2?
Why are you doing this?
Wavering...
It's because I'm thinking
about our long friendship.
Even bringing up their friendship
Number 3.
Number 3?
You're for real, right?
You are going to feel
how much I love you.
Ear swab
I said number 2.
Regretting
You really want number 2?
Fine, take number 2.
Huge ladle
It's the big or the small one.
Ear swab
Small or large
Huge ladle
But this is just drinking hot water.
That's why I said it was
the big or the small one.
I'll make sure to pour you a full scoop.
A full scoop from the ear swab
In the end
Then this isn't ssanghwacha.
Tea ssanghwa.
That's a toothpick?
An ear swab.
Oh an ear swab, I thought it was a toothpick.
Added a spoon very deliberately, but ...
The size of earwax
A different worry from other people
This is okay ~
Perfect team
Bongkook the swindling couple
This game is flipping a coin on a
book using the palm of your hand.
Hanging the number off egg
yolks added on a coin flip
What?
If all 5 in your team consecutively
succeed, then your team wins.
Hongki seems to do this well,
not that I get what it is.
Confident Hongki
Oh it's this, ﻿we're going to flip a coin?
It's panchiki ~
During Junior High School I bet
on my school fees with this.
There's a method?
Without touching the coin,
flip the coin a half turn
Really?
Yes.
But to win, everyone has to do this well.
You have to do it all together?
Then would your side like to go first?
Yes.
Go ahead.
The red side on top.
Red Team
Flip it from the red side
to the blue side
Don't touch me.
Jongkook
success
Ah Jongkook is ...
Bongsun
Good.
Hongki
success
This ...
Ah Joongki, oh you're not Joongki.
Very nervous
Good luck.
Gary
success
Donghoon ~
You're the joy in life.
Now only HaHa is left to succeed
Donghoon ~
You're the joy in life.
HaHa ~
You're the best.
He hit it
It must flip to the blue side
You re the best.
What happens?
failure
Red Team
... the best.
You're the best.
What's even scarier than failure is ...
It's our chance now.
Now it's our team's turn.
Oh, he's now ...
The two boys keep having no luck
Seethe
Starting.
Starting from me.
The chance goes to blue team
We ...
Fighting ~
Flip it from the blue side
to the red side
Jaesuk success
Sukjin
success
Fighting.
Don't you think it will ...
Jihyo ...
Success
Kwangsoo ...
Even Kwangsoo
success
Game Devil
Only Sooro is remaining
Sooro ...
It's over.
You really ...
Already feeling like they won
Game Devil
This level can't be hard for him
No, it's okay.
Anxious
Restless
Relaxed
100% certain
Game Devil
You know this, right?
With a snap?
Hit it with a snap.
Relaxed~
You don't need to hit it hard.
Of course
Success?
Gasp
You don't have to hit it hard.
Blue Team
Failure
I did well, didn't I?
You try it, without pressure.
Enraged
The chance goes back to the red team
Start with Jongkook.
Why doesn't it work?
Okay.
Jongkook success
Easily
Bongsun success
Always accurate
Hongki success
Hongki does it so well,
hereally is good at this.
Only the two unlucky boys remain
Gary ...
Please stay seated.
Composed
Okay.
I'll do it on my own.
Gary tries to find tranquility
Okay I got it.
Boooo ...
Slap
Surprised
I'm sorry.
Automatic apology
Dazed
I think everyone got
sensitive since it's dawn.
But we just saw him hit your hand.
Sorry
Sukjin spur him to fight
Jaesuk, doesn't it anger you?
No ~
Provoking
Jaesuk, just get angry.
Kim Jongkooknim ...
* Gary is talking extra respectful to Jongkook
Why'd I do that...
Kim Jongkooknim, I'll go now.
Calm
His hand is weak.
Shaking
It must flip to the blue side
Please...
Failure
Gasp!
Why do the boys in that team always
seem like ﻿they're walking on eggshells?
A fit of rage
Why doesn't it go to HaHa?
Definitely the unlucky two boys
No, I mean, if I can't do it,
it's okay since I'm the first.
So if I don't succeed,
there's no expectations.
Jongkook in a foul temper
But we always get to the end and
these two are always problems.
What...?
Slap
Then let's do it backwards.
A timid revenge for before?
So you don't point.
Then let's do it backwards.
HaHa suggests that they change the order
Okay let's go again.
Starting from us.
Backwards
He wants to start backwards?
HaHa Success
I did it.
He did it.
Red Team continues to succeed
I did it.
She did it.
Only Jongkook is left
If you don't succeed ...
If you don't, what...?
Agitated two boys
If you don't succeed,
give her another kiss.
Awkward
Let's see if you fail.
Repeat what you said.
If he doesn't succeed, he has
to give you another kiss.
Crisis might disband
Jongkook and the Two Boys
I like it.
Major revolt
Will eat him alive if he fails
Jongkook, go quickly.
Okay, wait up.
Just watch it if you fail.
Boooo ...
Curse
Slowly feeling pressured
You hand isn't a hand.
Immature
Then what is my hand?
Foot ~
Amazed...
Because the hand may be
sensitive but the foot is not.
I know you sit next to me
hyung, but ... I'm sorry.
In the end Jaesuk apologizes
Still...
I'll just finish it up now.
Okay.
Please ...
Chicken feet.
* Pun on please
Please succeed
Do you want it?
Yes we do.
Confident
We want it ~
This doesn't happen on your own will.
Hyung, I did it.
Want it?
If he fails in this atmosphere it'll be real bad
We do ~
Okay I'll start.
During our time.
He hit it
What will
happen?
Failure
The collapsing charisma of the leader
What are you doing after
working out for 20 years?
The 20 years old muscles shameful failure
Your arms are that big,
but you can't do that?
Hyung, why do you even exercise?
You're just helpless.
Use your brain.
Angry
No, not me ...
You shouldn't have gone that far
You see how much pressure it is.
Because it's a relay the last person is under a lot of pressure
Okay, it's fine.
I'll go.
I'd prostrate myself.
Hurry up.
The chance goes back to the blue team
I'll go now.
Sooro, you really have to ...
I did it.
Sooro Success
Now everyone succeeds easily but ...
Now
Sukjin's turn
Success
Jaesuk ...
Jaesuk, be confident.
The last player
If Jaesuk succeeds the team will win
Pressure
Boooo ~
Boooo is the best sound ever.
Hit
And this is a grasshopper's hand
Again
A timid revenge for being hit earlier
This is my table.
Please remove your foot.
It's my table.
Jongkook refuses to move his arm
Just move a bit.
Mister...!
Mister?
Mister to you too.
Jaesuk
Concentrating
Hey-ya!
It's now!
I got it.
Blue Team wins
Blue Team
Exempted from adding yolk
Please throw it.
Losing team has to add as many
yolks as the dice is showing
Throw it well.
A small number has to come out
5 egg yolks added
Oh no!
Your hand isn't a hand, but a foot.
Unwelcomed
But this ... ?
How will we add water?
To add nutrition
5 high-protein yolks are added
But from last week ...
... we're in danger here.
Having eggs is more advantageous.
It's like 5 people's worth of ssanghwacha
It looks like an eclipse.
Clear egg level
Okay, we're done.
Ssanghwacha and ...
With a light heart also Blue Team
adds one yolk each
It's a perfect combination.
It's perfect
But what is this for me?
The problem is Jaesuk's ear swab ssanghwacha
The team who drinks it the fastest wins
Kookjong is just not benevolent, isn't he?
Let's go.
Start.
First Blue Team
It's delicious.
Game Devil's
first experience of hot ssanghwacha
Shake
Completely waking up
Jongkook, you really grew up a lot.
Blue Team has more hot water
Hyung it's all like that.
Huff Puff ~
Ah, it's hot.
Frantic
Hot ~
Why is he like
that by himself?
He drank it all.
Next ...
Sooro barely succeeds
I can't wear hot pants.
2nd player
Kwangsoo
Shall I help you?
Please help me once.
Sooro offering Kwangsoo some help
Sooro is giving what kind of help?
You're spilling.
Stop...
Should I hit you harder.
I'm anticipating when Jaesuk's turn.
Gasp!
Game Devil's
expert shock therapy
Kwangsoo, go.
Misunderstanding
I'll hit you harder here.
So that you don't think about ..
It's okay, I'll drink.
Urgent
Is it okay?
He urgently wants to drink without help
Don't let it touch your tongue.
All at once
Swallow~
Good ~
With Sooro's help(?) Kwangsoo easily succeeds
Please, Jihyo.
Don't let it touch your tongue?
Then what about the throat?
Blue Team's only lady
Jihyo
Make it go straight to the Adam’s apple.
It's a full cup of ssanghwacha powder
Jaesuk is the captain.
She still drinks it well
I think it'll taste bad.
She's doing well.
Jihyo ...
Now it's almost over
Jihyo, let's go.
It's near the end.
Let's go.
Good ~
Jihyo at the speed of light
Succeeds
A expected
Sukjin with a full cup of ssanghwacha goes
Good.
Only his lips are moving.
It's because he has a lot of powder.
So much powder there was no place for water
Jaesuk hyung ...
Sukjin succeeds rather easily
In one gulp ~
Blue Team only has Jaesuk left
He wants him to drink it in one gulp.
In one gulp, let's go.
As if you're drinking 500cc of water.
Only one egg The rest is hot water
That's right.
One sip and his reaction is ...
Wiggle
It's okay.
It tastes bad.
Let's go ~
It's not that it's hot
but that it's just not tasty
Ah, it tastes bad.
I can't wear hot pants, really.
I can't wear hot pants.
This is just hot water and egg.
There's no taste.
Can't imagine
What an egg tea tastes like
Doing well.
Out of all the days ﻿I've seen
you, you're the best today.
To the Adam’s apple, don't
let it touch ﻿your tongue.
Because it tastes bad
Don't let it touch the tongue
Think of it as giving it to your stomach.
Devil's advice
If it tastes bad let it go straight to the stomach
You have to accept this hot stuff, stomach.
It's okay.
That's it.
Following Devil's advice
Jaesuk succeeds
That's it.
We won't check the time
until both teams finished.
Ready ... go.
HaHa has powder from a mega sized ladle + 5 yolks
Oh, you're doing well.
What is this?
Aoh~
I understand
that feeling
This is really hot.
Gary, cool it down.
Huff~
Puff~
Cool it down.
What are you doing?
Must take care of everything
for the two boys
HaHa ...
Stir and cool it down, stir.
You need to eat the
sediment with a spoon.
HaHa barely succeeds
Ours is hot starting from here.
Also powder from a mega sized ladle + 5 yolks
But this really wakes you up.
Gary, drink it up.
Since it has so little water it's hard to drink fast
Oppa, more threatening.
Just drink it quickly.
Drink it!
Drink it
Concentrating
I said drink it.
See it's possible.
Straight.
Bongkook couple's joint pressure
Who cares if it's powder, eat it.
Swallow ~
Sharp!
Try to swallow it.
That's it, yes you're done.
Okay, Hongki ...
Refreshingly, drink up.
Hallyu star Hongki starts
One gulp ~
That's right.
A clean success
Okay, Bongsun ...
Bongsun ...
Bongsun starts
How is it?
You okay?
Don't worry about your face.
It's okay.
It's coming.
With love's power...
If you can't drink it now,
you can never drink it.
Breathing
deeply
Hey ...
Swallow.
Bongsun ...
How is she drinking it like that ?
In one shot~
The last Jongkook will?
You're amazing.
Hyung, you'll be burned.
You're suppressing your pain?
Do you have muscles
in your throat as well?
Jongkook also has muscles in his throat?
Is this something to hold back?
The six pack in the throat.
Is this the kind of image
you want to show us.
Are they... the same team...
If it hurts, just say it hurts.
If it hurts, just say it.
Yes, we know you re the captain.
To the end
You need to say when it's hot.
You re not a robot.
Will Jongkook be able
to drink to the end?
Of course, you re not a robot.
Wow, he's stubborn.
In one shot
He's really not human.
Captain Jongkook a strong success
I think we won.
Which team was fastest?
Red Team
4 minutes
Blue Team
4 minutes 15 seconds
Red Team wins with a narrow difference
It was only a 15 second difference.
It could've been dangerous.
Please give it to us.
No hot pants ... yeah.
Last mission
Red Team wins the Running Ball
Current time
I'm trembling.
We're at a disadvantage.
Finally
Time to choose the team that can leave
2 to 1 is rather, truthfully, disadvantageous.
Red Team
Running Balls
Blue Team
Let's put them in.
Okay, two, add them.
Putting the Running Balls in
The team with less balls kept winning.
The team with less balls usually wins
We have to see the other
team with hot pants.
Today's punishment
Wearing hot-pants + the theme
park's hair band and balloons
It's so embarrassing, hot pants.
Hot pants, I really ...
It's really embarrassing.
Blue Team lost and wore hot pants last week
Everyone, let's get started.
Please ...
This makes me crazy.
The team with the same color as the ball
can go straight home
Don't look at it.
Look forward.
The theme park's gods
and the hot pants
What will
happen?
Who will stay?
And who will leave?
The decisive moment
Blue ball
Huge twist
Only one ball but Blue Team
will leave
Shocked
Unbelievable.
The hot pants.
Jihyo even starts to cry
How happy she must be
But is this something to cry over?
Exempt from punishment
It's because I'm deeply moved.
Hot pants F4 appears
* F4 = Flower 4 (refers to the drama "Boys before flowers")
Embarrassing(?) bare legs
Tight fit
Now
it's the outside world
For some reason a lot of people today
Sticking out
Short... and fancily dressed..
Let's walk fast.
Walk quickly.
Oh my, Jongkook oppa
I can't flex my legs at all.
A fast walk, ~
Popping out muscles
Anyone would agree that they definitely stand out
Completely get everyone's attention
If I don't get coffee, then
I can't start my morning.
Giving a huge laugh to the people in the morning
If I were a resident I wouldn't run to you.
You look really scary right now.
You're really scary
You look scarier today than ever.
Isn't this scary?
The muscled hot pants
Hey, I'm completely relaxing my legs.
What happens when you flex them?
Try it once.
Huge
muscle
After seeing his muscles ...
Shy
I really like you, I went to
your concert last summer.
... came straight to him
Jongkook fan
Really? Thank you.
It seems she's a Jongkook fan
Celebratory photo
Oh, do a full shot.
Once more
Of course.
Hey ...
You're telling him to take another photo?
1, 2, 3.
Happy HaHa
Making sure the muscled hot pants completely show
Even then he's still smiling.
Immediately punished
Next week they must win
National Museum of Contemporary Art