Original hardsubs by iSUB
Transcribed by HapB
Color and alignment by SamFive
Today's
landmark
Boramae Safety Experience center
Experiencing disaster and learn
effect methods to cope with it
Out of the ordinary
singing mission
Today it will be another 1:8 match
Jongkook!
To fool the members!
Jongkook
is today's
hunted!
Chase at all costs just to
catch Sparta Kook
Starts now
Today's activity location is at the
Boramae Safety Experience Center.
Boramae Safety Experience Center
It's also a place to experience
fires, earthquakes, typhoons ...
... road accidents and other
disasters in our everyday life.
It's a place where we can
learn to cope with disasters.
Ah right, hold on.
But who is this?
We haven't introduced
the honored guest.
She came last week.
Lizzy came to perform
continuously for two weeks.
Yes, they asked me to come again.
I'm here.
This time the oppas also have
an overwhelming response
I'm here.
Experienced the passion that wasn't
there when Jihyo was around.
Call me oppa.
Oppa ~
Applause and gasp in admiration
This is the first time we meet.
Yes, our Running Man's vitamin.
Yes, I heard that Joongki oppa
was coming, so I'm here again.
A very strong "I am here".
Gary, you purposely let
Jihyo get away last week.
Gary let the
opposing team's Jihyo go
That is not allowed.
I have my reasons.
What reasons?
During the show Jihyo said
that she's attracted to me.
I said you're handsome, not
that I was attracted to you.
Doesn't handsome and attracted
to  have a similar meaning?
So every Monday, the two
of you will be dating.
* Running Man is recorded on Mondays
Monday Couple.
The Monday Couple is born
Yes?
During my break, I go
swimming sometimes.
Uneasy
I met Jihyo noona there.
Really?
Yes, she was fighting with someone.
With whom?
With the swimming coach ...
... his haircut is exactly
the same as Gary hyung.
Really?
We have to be more low-profile.
Like me?
What does
that mean?
Our Kwangsoo is the rising star
when it comes to sabotaging.
From what I see ...
Whichever country of the Three Kingdoms
that has Kwangsoo's sabotaging skills ...
... will be able to rule the world.
Liu Bei of Shu
Cao Cao of Wei
Sun Quan of Wu
Liu Bei of Shu
Able to rule the world through sabotage
Strategist Kwangsoo
This time ...
Be quiet.
Stopping Kwangsoo
a source of slander
This time when I was performing,
I met Jongkook hyung.
What did you say?
I saw him painting his nails.
Not bad, I saw that too.
Nail's color for today is very ideal~
That was not bad.
No boundaries Even dares to make fun of Jongkook
We don't need to get manipulated
by Jongkook hyung anymore.
His back ache shows that he
is not as powerful as before.
These two kids have a plan of betraying?
There are times when it is impossible
to communicate with Jongkook hyung.
Unsatisfied
Hmm ...
We shall see
Everybody saw it, right?
Last week Jongkook didn't
get any Running Man Ball.
All of his partners and
friends blame it on him.
Even...
being chased...
still able to escape...
At the end...
lost to Jaesuk...
It doesn't mater with or without the drawing.
I will have to do the punishment for sure.
I realized the important meaning of hope.
So even till the last game ...
Stop pretending to be at ease.
Everybody saw it last week.
Trapped in
the hopeless state of last week
But ...
Jongkook's attack has already begun
One week earlier at
SBS broadcasting center
This time I didn't get even one.
He is really affected by it...
So I have ...
... a proposal to offer.
Proposal?!
Doing a 1:8 game.
Reversed game?
Yes, a reversed game.
Planning at the confidential meeting
Together remember the lyrics and ...
... make mistakes on purpose when singing.
Will Jongkook's
1:8 reverse succeed?
Everybody, let us step
into the Experience Center.
The other members
don't know anything
Okay, let's go in.
HaHa who betrays
in public
Jongkook will try to
fool the other 8 members
Steal other's ideas
The reverse 1:8 game will begin now
What is today's first game?
Knows everything but pretends not to
It's a song challenge.
A song
challenge
Fake mission
st
What song?
You will be working as a team.
A song will be split to nine small portions.
Yeah.
If all of you can finish the song completely,
all nine members will get a Running Ball.
If someone fails, then no one
will get a Running Man Ball.
Do we all know this song?
Truth is
Jongkook
Remainder
So everybody has to get it correct?
It's not a hidden camera trap this time?
... hidden camera trap this time?
Huh!
Failed from the start?
Ah, it won't be.
Joongki's too sensitive.
Life decreased
by
10 years
It's not.
It isn't?
Because Joongki was fooled before.
Still hasn't
found out
Now even if it is a trap, we have
our strongest reserve candidate ...
... our blank Jihyo.
Most likely to be fooled
Blank~ Jihyo
With Jihyo, we predict
that we won't succeed.
The friend that is easily predicted.
Jihyo, honestly today you were
the one who set the trap, correct?
Glance
No.
Look at her expression.
Really?
How many chances do we get?
You have ten chances
to complete the mission.
10?
Everybody please look at the fire
engine behind, it is Fire Engine's song.
* Fire Engine (SoBangCha) was a K-pop trio in the 80's
Ah it's Fire Engine's song we ...
We know it.
Does Lizzy know?
Lizzy was born in 1992
Does she know Fire Engine's song?
I know.
Lizzy you know?
Which songs do you know?
That one ... "Apartment".
Ah, that's Yoon Sooil's song.
Truth is...
Last week Jongkook received
Fire Engine's song list from the production team
Ah, Fire Engine's "About Last Night".
When it was really popular
the best 5 of Sobangcha songs
In addition...
To fool the members
Jongkook started practicing
The younger ones might not know the songs.
Strategy
Take down those not knowing the
songs: Kwangsoo, Joongki, Lizzy etc
Strategy
From "Not coordinated" to "Very
coordinated", make detailed mistakes.
Strategy
So he can sing and make mistakes
naturally, memorizes all the songs.
Mighty Mouth
Shorry
Strategy
Even if mistakes are made, don't
make panic. Have to stay calm.
Preparing for combat
Simulation is essential
To fool the Running Man members
Jongkook's close friends were called to help
To get rid of Jongkook's
No Running Ball
nightmare
To be the only person
getting a Running Ball
These containers have the song names.
Containers with
the song titles
Choose one from the five.
This might actually be a disadvantage.
We might choose a song that we don't know.
Pretending
So who will be the one to choose?
Jihyo ~
In unison
blank~
Jihyo
will choose
Why is your arm injured?
Because she is Blank Jihyo.
Silly Jihyo...
So that's why she is Blank Jihyo.
Oh very good.
Our Blank Jihyo drew this out.
What is it?
Let's look at which Fire Engine
song Jihyo did choose.
The song that Jihyo chose is?
Today's song
to challenge is
Top
Secret
Korea's 80s idols(?)
Dance group
Fire
Engine
And this glorious ballad
was no. 1 for 5 weeks in a row
Fire Engine's hit song "Top Secret"
But it is also a song that's
not easy to remember
It would be really good if there
is a break in the lyrics here.
This song is not easy, it's really difficult.
The song Jongkook wanted the most
was picked by Blank Jihyo
♪ I really don't know ♪
Isn't that how you sing it?
What are we going to do?
Everyone...
Doesn't know...
If it's this way
he will be able to
complete the mission
Looking at the other tubes
Checking which is the easiest song
"About Last Night".
Fire Engine's most famous song
<About Last Night>
Ah, Jihyo.
Burst out
dissatisfied
I also know that song.
Blames herself
"White Wind".
♪ Blow, blow white wind ♪
"Tell Her".
Blank ~
How can you be so dumb?
Lizzy do you know how to sing this?
Even Lizzy knows
<Tell Her>
19 years old
Not bad.
She knows.
Crying without tears
This is so easy.
♪ I want to be in love ♪
We got the most difficult song.
Jihyo ...
Why did you choose
the most difficult one?
Not her intention to
help Jongkook
Blank~ Jihyo
Everybody listen to it first.
Listen to <Top Secret>
This melody seems very familiar
It is not easy remember the
lyrics after listening only once
Excited Jongkook
The more you listen...
Anxiety...
It's hard to stop yourself
from singing such a happy song
Yeah.
Yeah~
Overzealous
Passion
Increase in confidence the more he listens
Is there a period given
to memorize the lyrics?
Yes.
Oh, it is given?
Starting from now, 5 minutes
for you to memorize the lyrics.
Any given order to sing?
The order can be changed anytime.
Thank goodness.
I'm going crazy.
I like Fire Engine's songs very much,
so I should be able to memorize it.
Really?
Of course.
Jongkook snatches Jaesuk's song sheet
Stopping him from memorizing
This is hard.
Jihyo ...
... aren't you and Joongki
good at memorizing scripts?
* Since Joongki and Jihyo are actors
and usually memorizes scripts.
Memorize these first.
Is this even the same
as memorizing scripts?
Then who can memorize quickly?
It's impossible for
one person to
memorize it...
Brain Joongki
in the midst of repetitive learning
Actress
Jihyo
also starts to memorize
the script seriously
Hyung, the moment I make a
mistake, the beat will be off.
Is that so?
Brain Joongki continues to share his knowledge
♪ I'm always ... ♪
Correct
♪ You are my ... ♪
Wrong
♪ I'm always ... ♪
♪ You are my ... ♪
Stubborn
♪ I'm always ... ♪
Joongki corrects him immediately
the moment he sings wrong
Number one challenger
is still Brain Joongki
Temporarily avoids Joongki and disturbs others
♪ Who is the one you love? ♪
New target HaHa
The dark cloud
still remains
HaHa and Gary are easy to deal with.
Purposely injecting the wrong lyrics
into weak HaHa and Gary's singing
2nd target
Continually spreading wrong lyrics
Brain Joongki is still correcting his mistakes
It's really not an easy task
Let's begin, we're starting to sing.
Jongkook
Remaining
8 members
1st attempt
Start the music.
♪ Closing your eyes is useless ♪
♪ Closing your ears is useless ♪
Closing your ears?
Fail at the first try
The shocking results Air blast punishment
Why?
The fool who doesn't know
where his mistake is HaHa
Jongkook acting in his usual manner
And naturally lecturing HaHa
Hey come here.
Come over to get hit.
Can't you wait for us
to close our mouths?
Punish us only when
our mouths are closed.
Air blast teeth cleaning
Bad timing
Even my glasses were blown off.
Continuing
injuries
Do you know what
your hair looks like?
I know.
Your hair looks like its been permed.
Why was HaHa wrong?
Should have been "covering
ears" and not "closing ears".
Thank you
HaHa ...
Let's go.
2nd attempt
♪ You are my ... ♪
Why are you
like this today?
His gaze means he
discovered something?
Not likely
What are you doing?
Jaesuk is becoming confused
♪ She's standing in front of me ... ♪
♪ ... like she's got something to say ♪
♪ Thinking of your sad look ... ♪
♪ ... I walk on unfamiliar street ♪
♪ You don't understand my heart ... ♪
♪ Your looks ... ♪
2nd taste of failure
Ah really now, Jongkook.
Jongkook was wrong.
But it's really hard.
A singer can't even remember lyrics.
I will intentionally make 2 or 3 mistakes.
Like getting the beat wrong.
Do push-ups.
It's really too difficult.
Didn't I correct your lyrics just now?
Something
is fishy?
If the mistakes continue in this manner
it doesn’t look good for Jongkook
But...
Thanks to his friend's memory
they continually make errors
Why?
Taste of failure 5 times
If that's the case...
Jongkook doesn't even have to
try to win the Running Ball
Because it turned out to be
worse than we planned ...
... we will only sing a
small part of the song.
... we'll only do a small part of the song.
What?
Only singing until "Who do I love".
But ...
We need to change your places.
Change places?
Thank goodness~
Are the both of us changing?
Okay.
I'm telling you, I often forget the lyrics.
So that's the problem.
With shorted song it's more difficult
for Jongkook's 1:8 challenge
Music.
They only have 10 attempts
6th attempt
Starting from here.
It's starting, start singing.
Starting
even without accompaniment
Okay I understand.
Why do you look so unfocused?
Where should I start?
Music please.
♪ ...osing my eyes... ♪
Sukjin slowing the tempo again
Hold on.
I'll do it.
You?
Changing places with Sukjin
Of course.
I'll do it.
Why is he always
good to him?
You?
Of course.
I used to manage
a karaoke lounge.
I really can't do this.
You try it once.
The not-so-easily fooled
Sukjin is next to him
Feels
discomfort
What kind of lyrics are these?
♪ Closing my eyes is useless ... ♪
♪ covering my mouth ... ♪
It's not "covering mouth"
but "covering ears".
Hyung, you're so weird.
Give me a moment.
"Covering my eyes ... Covering my ears..."
Suspicious
♪ Its useless. ♪
Hyung, you're acting weird.
It's cant be that I'm
discovered too easily
Music ...
It's the 6th try again
... please.
Gamado Soyong Eobseo
Gwireul Magado Soyong Eobseo
Jigeum Geunyeoga Naeapeseo
Museun Mareul Hae Julgeonman Gateunde
Seulpeun Nungireul Tteoollimyeo
Natseon Georireul Georeobwado
Geudae Maeumeul Moreugesseo
Nareul Jakku Waemyeon Eotteotkke Ha-myeon
Life shortened
by 10 years
Geudaejinjeong Saranghaneun Sarameun Nugu
Najimaki Soksagineun Sarameun Nugu
Urijunge Joahaneun Sarameun Nugu
Eotteok...
Wait a moment.
It's a mistake but ...
Acted like he forgot the lyrics
Is it wrong?
I got it wrong, I'm sorry.
Nobody knows
I really didn't know, I'm really sorry.
Why are you being like this?
Not a thread of suspicion
I'll go to a different spot
Change with me change with me.
What's yours?
I'll come here then, here.
Now, this is the 7th time.
Only 3 chances remaining.
Music please.
Jaesuk leaving the lyrics behind
What? Seriously now.
I'm sorry please give me some time.
Do you know how hard that spot it?
You have to focus, understand?
I understand..
What should we do if
you mess up in the start?
But I'm okay at the back.
You made a mistake before.
Out of 6 tries
Jongkook made 2 mistakes
That part was hard.
But no one is suspicious
That's true.
Everyone thinks it's difficult
No one suspects anything
Okay, music ... please.
7th try
♪ Closing my ears is useless ♪
♪ Covering my mouth ... ♪
Failure on the 7th try too
Why do you keep saying "mouth".
It's "ear".
Because I am the first,
that's why I got nervous.
It's "ear".
Change ~
Sorry ~
Hyung ~
Hyung ...
I'm really sorry.
Why don't you try it once again?
Sorry.
Just once more.
Because Jaesuk is bad at it
he gives a another chance
No ~
I'll do it.
In the end Jaesuk changes spot
I really have no confidence.
Hyung, that's really hard.
So what if it's hard.
What is this here.
Still acting confused~
You can't be like that.
His greatest ally
Coming to his side to advise him
Joongki...
must be careful
Okay music, lets go.
8th try
Nuneul Gamado Soyong Eobseo
Gwireul Magado Soyong Eobseo
Jigeum Geunyeoga Naeapeseo
Museun Mareul Hae Julgeonman Gateunde
Seulpeun Nungireul Tteoollimyeo
Natseon Georireul Georeobwado
Geudae Maeumeul Moreugesseo
Nareul Jakku Waemyeon Ha-myeon Eotteotkke
Okay, good good.
Geudaejinjeong Saranghaneun Sarameun Nugu
Najimaki Soksagideon Sarameun Nugu
Urijunge Joahaneun Sarameun Nugu
Eotteokedeun Algo Sipeo
Moreuneunge Neomu Mana
Naneun Modeungeol Teoronakgo
Geudae Bimiri Neomu Mana
Ilgeup Bimireul Sipeo Algo
Geudae Nugul ninho...
One more line and they
will succeed Restless
Will Jongkook just fail like this?
And the other 8 members will win?
- 8 Members: Sarang Hago Inneunji ~
- Jongkook: Sarang hago  Isseulkka ~
Other members irritation showing through
Have they found out?
What should I do...?
Suspicion?
This laugh is...?
What a pity.
They're completely fooled
Who sang it wrong just now?
In the end we slipped up.
They really don't know?
As expected
Jongkook is relieved ...
Jaesuk also doesn't know
If he successfully tricked Joongki too...
Then the Running Ball
belongs to Jongkook
Music please.
9th attempt
Nuneul Gamado Soyong Eobseo
Gwireul Magado Soyong Eobseo
Jigeum Geunyeoga Naeapeseo
Museun Mareul Hae Julgeonman Gateunde
Geudaejinjeong Saranghaneun Sarameun Nugu
Najimaki Soksagi  neun
Sarameun Nugu
Why?
Pretending to
be unaware
Very strange...
It's not it?
Seriously... you.
Did they find out the plan?
Are you an idiot?
They didn't find out
Yes, that's the correct one.
You have one chance left.
Let's practice first.
Checking everyone's part one by one
If they get this right...
Jongkook will not succeed
Naneun  Bimireul Teoronakgo
Modeungeol ~
Again
Mistakenly
saying "secret"
Now it seems like Jaesuk
is doing the 1:8
You guys really did a great job.
What are you doing?
Fake outburst
The sad Jongkook is so
thankful to Jaesuk
They have to sing the last part together
Geudae Nugu...saranghago iss~eulkka~
issneun-ljji.. issneun-jii ..
Unsuspecting till the very end
Is there someone you don't know?
This time it's really important, the
deal breaker for the Running Ball.
Let's not waste time and start.
But shouldn't we sing
this part like the climax?
Let's do that then.
Just like that.
Because it's the end.
Last round
10th attempt
It's last round, music please.
Nuneul Gamado Soyong Eobseo
Gwireul Magado Soyong Eobseo
Nervous~
Jigeum Geunyeoga Naeapeseo
Museun Mareul Hae Julgeonman Gateunde
Seulpeun Nungireul Tteoollimyeo
Natseon Georireul Georeobwado
Geudae Maeumeul Moreugesseo
Nareul Jakku Waemyeon Eotteotkke
Geudaejinjeong Saranghaneun Sarameun Nugu
Najimaki Soksagideon Sarameun Nugu
Urijunge Joahaneun Sarameun Nugu
Eotteokedeun Algo Sipeo
Don't go off tone.
Moreuneunge Neomu Mana
1, 2, 3, 4.
Being a disturbance at the last spot
Naneun Modeungeol Teoronakgo
Geudae Bimiri Neomu Mana
Ilgeup Bimireul Sipeo Algo
They can feel success
Geudae Nugul Sarang Hago Inneun...
Finally
The last verse
Indeed..
- 8 Members: Sarang Hago Inneunji ~
- Jong Kook: Sarang Hago Inneunkka ~
Mission failure
Who got it wrong?
Direct
punishment
Assaulted
Exhausted
Yah, pull him up.
Kim Jongkook ...
How can you do this?
Still not aware of being fooled by Jongkook
We were at the end already.
We already emphasized that part
so much and you still got it wrong.
Yah, Kim Jongkook come here.
Stupid.
Kim Jongkook, come here.
Why did you sing 'kka' instead?
Why?
Because if I say 'kka'
I'd get the ball so ...
Blank~
You failed this challenge.
Kim Jongkook gets the Running Ball.
What?
The Running Ball goes to Jongkook?
1:8 Jongkook Success
What?
Oh that was close, finally.
How can this be?
Jongkook successfully tricked all members
This can't be, really.
Absurd
Ah really.
Outrageous
Can't accept the reality
before their eyes
I spent one whole week
practicing this song.
I can not get it wrong.
We all got it right, only he got
it wrong and he gets the ball?
That's right.
Then he got it just like that for free?
If you had exposed him, then you
would have gotten balls instead.
How could we have
seen through this?
Jongkook got it wrong 5 times of 10
The others helped with the rest
Wait, you messed up on purpose?
Of course, how can I get it wrong ...
... when I've been practicing for a week.
We have to add one.
Why? What is it?
Give me my Running Ball please.
Give me one
give me one
Trying to say that he also messed up on purpose
Why did you think I missed
the rhythm just now?
I learned this song from
when I first got into school.
Why did we sing wrong together?
Hey you kids.
In the end
making their own paper balls
Running ball.
So cunning, that was totally unexpected.
Look at how despicable
those muscles are.
You can even do that now.
I got it.
Got a Running Ball through
much love and hate
Current Time
Why do you keep putting
the ball in front of you?
I just want to look at it.
I heard you practiced for a week.
Yes.
This week was very busy for me.
How exhilarating that must be.
Ah, I'm a little sad, really.
No one has a ball
except Jongkook
This time if you become the thief ...
... there is a 100% chance
you will be punished.
Two missions left
The one becoming the thief
100% chance of punishment?
Because if you become the
thief and lose the game ...
... you won't even have one Running Ball.
But if Kim Jongkook becomes the
thief, he will be the same as us.
For a fair(?) hide-n-seek
Sukjin will make Jongkook the thief
But that won't happen.
Are you exercising?
What are you doing?
Don't cross this line.
The childish elders
I went to Jongkook's car just
now and he was knitting.
Framer Kwangsoo's power
can give people a splash
2nd mission
Catch the thief
Postcard will be given to 9
members of Running Man
One of it will be a thief-card
Members will exchange cards
with the people beside them
At the end, everyone except the person who
gets the thief-card, will get a Running Ball
Definitely can't get the thief card.
It's the thief-card, oh it has
the same background color.
They changed it.
An upgrade to prevent cheating
the thief-card
Now all the postcards have
the same background color.
Big Nose hyung
deals the cards
Game
start
Who will get the thief-card...?
Please don't let it be me, please.
Card confirmation
Kwangsoo
Running Man card
Song Jihyo also
What about the card distributor Big Nose?
Phew~
Running Man card
Lizzy, you're the thief right?
Noooo~
This is the first time hearing this
type of tone and expression ...
... after graduating from elementary school.
Noooo~
Stealthy~
Found it...
Unnatural.
HaHa
found that thief card
HaHa hasn't it.
He is not the thief.
Someone must have the thief-card.
All the cards have been seen.
That person must be careful now.
I'm the thief ~
I'm the real thief ~
The stiff-faced real thief
What about HaHa?
No comment.
What?
Isn't that a comment?
No matter what
There's no suspicion over HaHa
The game is called bibo-bibo.
What is that?
Every time 3, 6 or 9 appears, call out
bibo-bibo instead of the number.
Is there an action?
That means we must call out
bibo-bibo for the number 33?
If there is no hand movement, you're out.
Lets start then, from Kwangsoo.
3, 6, 9. 3, 6, 9...
A succession of ZERO mistakes
Reached 20 fast
25.
20 ... bi-Bo.
20... bibo....
26 contains a 6 so Gary
should've said bibo-bibo
Ahh, I'm really bad at this.
Gary
out
Goodbye.
No matter who's out
they are are happy
Goodbye ~
Get disqualified, you
already have a ball.
Why are you still working so hard?.
Making such movements
with your thick hands.
I still want one more.
Not saying bibo but clapping on 3
Celebration?
Everyone's wish
Jongkook is out
Goodbye.
Don't touch this.
Why are you touching
other people's stuff?
Guarding the running ball like gold
Okay.
I was thinking of something
and clapped, that's all.
Oh.... really now...
Kwangsoo * Joongki * Jaesuk * HaHa
are the only ones left
5.
Bibo.
6.
Should have said 7 not 6?
Jaesuk
out
Goodbye.
What a pity.
Please be merciful for once.
Aigoo, what a pity.
Drive him out.
Kwangsoo always survives to the last 3.
The remaining 3
A fast speed
Really good.
Instantaneously breaking 20
Entering the hard 30-39 range
A situation that confuses
the onlookers
We're all confused.
Right ~
Everyone gets distressed from this game
Big Nose hyung sighing
No compromise game war
A long battle of stamina
Can't we just use rock paper
scissors to decide the winner?
Pockets of dissatisfaction
erupting here and there
When is this going to end?
Are they even correct now?
They are in a league of their own
Breaking 80
Haaah ...
Even the thief is drained out
by their thirst for victory
HaHa
quits
Finally down to 2 people.
That's a lot of bibos.
What will happen when 2 play this?
Hurry up and no stopping.
Whoever hesitates is out.
The winner gets a running ball?
That's right.
The winner gets
a Running Ball
A battle between same-age friends.
The last time ... Pygmalion.
2 weeks ago Kwangsoo
completely fooled Joongki
In the end I told the right answer, right?
Pydmallion?
No, it's not.
Kwangsoo ... Pygmalion.
Joongki ... Pygmalion effect.
I haven't finished my sentence...
The Pygmalion effect.
Kwangsoo averting disaster
with his unchanging expression
Pygmalion effect ... correct.
Joongki's fans, around 100 of
them, gave me small notes.
Telling me to not live like that.
Really.
Really?
Kwangsoo is really sensitive about such things.
Joongki and I are same-age friends ...
... but the notes read "At your age still you..."
But there's an even worse insult ...
... and the sender's name was Song Jihyo.
To: Kwangsoo
XXXXX ...
ID: Song Jihyo
Jihyo, so you're actually Joongki's fan.
Feeling so unhappy.
Joongki's fans have no bad intentions.
It is also because the fans like
Kwangsoo that the notes are given.
But that's not very persuasive.
The logic of the fans is liking
Kwangsoo and giving him notes.
Because of liking me so I
was given insulting notes?
Isn't it like that when you're close?
No man, you're saying something weird.
I originally wanted to
package the ending nicely.
Of course, anything weird
must be pointed out.
A dangerous 20 year companion
Do you know how many
secrets of yours I know?
Even sister-in-law doesn't know.
If you dare say anything you're finished too.
Are you really treating me like this?
Aren't I always tight-lipped?
Hyung, the moment I open
my mouth you're done for.
Yah.
I know that too.
That's why I dare not say anything.
The 2 of you continue.
One of you will become the
owner of the Running Ball.
From Kwangsoo ...
Fast
If you hesitate
you're immediately out
Tension
Kwangsoo
victory
Kwangsoo ...
This time you're going to get 200 notes.
Now I just need to give away my card?
Sukjin hyung should talk some more.
I really wish my kids could be like you.
Pass.
This is really the thief-card, Jaesuk hyung.
I already started noticing you when
you started off as a fashion model.
Since that day, I've always
wanted to meet you.
I'm honored.
Pass.
Noona as well.
You know that whatever I said
before was not from the heart.
What words?
What do you feel my forte is?
Be quiet.
Giving timid Kwangsoo a dagger stab
"You be quite"
Did you ask me to
be quiet at that time?
That phrase is so hurtful.
No matter what, you shouldn't have ...
Oppa, you said it too.
I originally didn't want to say this but ...
That day when I went
home I couldn't sleep.
He says he didn't sleep that day
You wanted someone to keep
quiet on a variety show.
Let me do it.
Really good acting, his
eyes are really teary.
Takes the opportunity
to praise his acting
Kwangsoo your acting is really good.
Kwangsoo's variety skills is very good
I scold people too, you know?
Kwangsoo said it well.
How brave.
Why don't you tell me?
I really sincerely apologize to you.
Let's save it first and listen to the others.
Save.
You don't look that old.
You're the last.
Today Kwangsoo wants to release
all the accumulated dissatisfaction
Next is Lizzy.
I really want a boyfriend like you.
Because of Lizzy's flirting
instantaneous melt of Kwangsoo's dissatisfaction
Really?
Then start a relationship.
Can't do it now because of my
company's contract restrictions.
Immediate seriousness?
They can be persuaded.
Right now the company has a restriction.
Really smart, because of
the company restriction.
Pass.
Still passes because of the flirting
And then ...
Nervous
Previously we had this ambiance too.
Kwangsoo, hyung feels that ...
Sincerity
Fail.
A fail with no sympathy
Oh Kwangsoo, really clean and neat.
Kwangsoo's card
Jongkook
Kwangsoo's clean finish
Really clean and neat.
The sin brought on by
a mere Running Ball
Musical Chair Game
A chance to change seats
Now is the time to not
seat on the thief's chair.
The bright-eyes current thief
I'm gonna blow the whistle.
Follow the area in a circle when you
hear the whistle, grab a seat fast.
Start.
Hey wait everyone, we must look happier.
Looks like it's not everyone's forte.
Happily
The other way.
Current seat
of the thief
Doesn't want to go back to
his original seat the thief HaHa
Hold hands.
Who will be
sitting on HaHa's thief chair?
Dance.
Trying their best~
Bodily fight
A deep breath
HaHa
Guarding
his seat
Who will end up sitting on
the seat with the thief card
The seat with
the thief-card
Gary, who changed places in the end?
Is it Jihyo?
Or Gary?
In the end it's Jihyo
After a roundabout exchange
The exchange seats is completed
Everyone, please check.
Excuse me for interrupting, but ...
... how can there only
be 2 people just sitting?
Just stop being such a busy-body.
Just leave us be.
Jihyo ran there to sit.
While going around in circles,
Jihyo was opposite of me.
It feels like she was secretly following him.
What do you mean by this?
I don't want to live~
Big Nose
Checking his card
Exaggerated
Isn't that your original place?
I don't know.
What's 'I don't know'.
It is your original place.
We have to observe Jihyo carefully.
We can see it from her expression.
Intense expression
I know it already.
It's not Jihyo.
Pretending not
to be the thief...
Lips tightly
closed
The first round winner Kwangsoo, will MC.
Congratulations! Debut)?)
MC Kwangsoo
2.
2 people came.
3.
3 people came.
Stand up if MC Kwangsoo
shouts out your number
A person
came
Those after us continue please.
The corresponding number
of people should stand up
Okay, "1 person came" game starts.
No memorable debut(?)
Garnering
applause
Zero level of impact
Two.
2 people came.
Four.
4 people came.
Wobble
You're wrong.
No, my body just wobbled.
Out ~
Jongkook in a wave of accusations
Everyone is united in eliminating him
Jongkook hyung eliminated.
Eliminated
It wasn't.
Good Job MC.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Whatever the MC says counts.
In order to let the game carry on
smoothly please leave quickly.
Force dismissal
You shouldn't have kept a
Running Man ball for yourself.
Stand aside.
cause explosion
of pettiness
1:8 face-off
I'll see how you guys will play.
Have a pleasant time watching.
Of course.
3.
3 people came.
4.
4 people came.
What's wrong?
Jihyo's wrong.
Blank ~
I'm sorry it's because of the mic.
You don't have to apologize, just leave.
She's eliminated.
Blank Jihyo
out
3.
3 people came.
2.
2 people came.
4.
4 people came.
You didn't stand up.
Big Nose who couldn't adapt
Totally clueless
about the situation
Out
You're eliminated.
Sukjin is eliminated.
1.
1 person came.
2.
2 people came.
4.
4 people came.
2.
2 people came.
3.
3 people came.
4.
4 people came.
The one who was supposed
to stand up didn't and ...
... the one who wasn't
supposed to stand did.
HaHa
Lizzy
out
You're eliminated, bye.
Bye ~
This is so difficult, but
Joongki can play it well.
There're 3 people left
and it feels like a trio.
You guys should work
hard to get one of these.
The more tiring
the more meaningful it will be
It's so tiring.
I really want to win.
I'm starting.
2.
2 people came.
1.
1 person came.
3.
3 people came.
2.
2 people came.
It's 2...why'd
he stand up?
Eliminated.
Jaesuk
out
Joongki is so serious.
Joongki gets to the finals again
It's because his fans are a bit scary.
Did you come alone?
What are you doing?
She had a boyfriend?
On Mondays, I'm the boyfriend.
Gary and Jihyo's relationship on Mondays
Nobody can obstruct it
You can come on Tuesdays to take over.
It's me on Mondays.
Come and inquire on Tuesdays.
Starting the game.
Gary
Final
Joongki
Strong lower body
Joongki the short-track athlete
Firm lower-body strength
Gary born as a dancer for the stage
2.
2 people came.
1.
1 person came.
2.
2 people came.
A high-nervous air suitable
for the atmosphere of a final
1.
1 person came.
2.
2 people came.
But somehow the game unknowingly
seems to have changed into an exercise
1.
1 person came.
2 ~
2 people came ~
Kwangsoo calmly
shouting
Flaring up
Being ordered to sit and stand repeatedly
will cause even a famous pretty boy to flare up
Shocked ~
This is much harder
than we imagined.
Pretty Boy running out of stamina
On the other hand a meticulous
youth starting to feel petty
What exactly did they see?
MC Kwangsoo
transforming into
a physical trainer
What...is this?
If anyone pisses me off...
The Safety Experience Center that suddenly
becomes a physical training ground
No eye contact with your officer.
A unique character whose eyes can't be seen even
if other tried to make eye contact
What a character, just look
at his pants and you'd know.
He should be living on an uninhabited island.
Stand up shouting "we are".
Sit back down shouting "a team".
1.
We are ...
2.
... a team.
What are you doing?
Are you idiots, why are you
shouting what he says?
The game is starting.
1.
1 person came.
2.
2 people came.
Make your voices louder.
Enraged
Louder
1.
1 person came.
2.
2 people came.
Is it starting all over?
No arguing.
I'm sorry
What did you say just now?
Don't know what you're talking about.
This officer is not bad person.
You just listen carefully to
my words and you can.
Kwangsoo good job, that's great.
Failure to obey me ...
... then this will then become hell.
Let's start quickly.
1.
1 person came.
2.
2 people came.
1.
1 person came.
Song Joongki eliminated.
Thank you ~
Gary
wins
Joongki's lost the final again.
What's with me.
Help me say that I'm your friend.
A concerned worry that came late
No.
I think you went way overboard.
You can't go back now.
Dear Joongki fans~
Today everyone will show lots of concert right?
Gary is going to give out another card.
I gave it already.
Should've given it to Jongkook.
Approaching Jihyo's side
What are you doing?
There's no table.
2nd round of choosing cards
What wrong?
Hurry up, don't act cute.
Monday Boyfriend Extremely irritated?
When did I act cute?
That's right.
It's not acting cute.
For Jihyo who has the thief-card
all this is just chatter
Just look at it yourself.
It's finally Jihyo's turn to transfer a card
Ultimately Lizzy's choice is?
Jihyo's cards
Running Card
Thief-card
You have to pick based on expression.
Thank you.
The flick of the eyes are?
So curious.
Lizzy's silly(?) expression
Look at that expression
she can act already.
The reason for
Jihyo's vague smile is?
What does that expression mean?
Lizzy, laughed?
Did the thief-card go to HaHa?
His expression is unnatural.
Or to Big Nose?
At a glance it seems there are 3 cards
Totally identical.
Choosing of cards is over
Where is the thief-card now?
Finally the roundabout.
Okay, let's do it.
Hmm?
Cooly accepting?
When the music stops just
immediately sit down.
We're not allowed to push?
There has to be so it's meaningful.
He said no.
In variety shows it's a must.
You can even wrestle
someone to the ground.
How can we wrestle someone?
Hooking of the leg and
other wrestling moves.
Start.
Round and round ~
Final roundabout
Change of seats
Only 1 person wants to
change seats
Curious, who will it be?
The final choice in order to receive
the Running Man ball
Even indecisive Sukjin has finished
the change of seats
Now only the thief knows, right?
Everyone has changed their seat, right?
Only the thief knows the location of the thief-card
Everyone has changed their seat
Only the thief knows.
I'll reveal.
It's coming 1, 2, 3.
At Jihyo's previous place
is a Running Man card
Jihyo's position had a Running Man card.
This is originally Lizzy's position.
Please trust in me.
1, 2, 3.
Jaesuk also has
a Running Man card
Oh, it's a Running Man card
This is Donghoon's position.
* Donghoon is HaHa's real name
Can I trust you, HaHa?
1, 2, 3.
Sukjin
got the thief-card
The thief's card was on HaHa's seat
Truth
I was very close to getting the card.
I should have pushed you.
You were the one distributing the cards.
So it was my fault I got the thief-card?
That's right?
It is so scary to be the
one giving out the cards.
If you give out the cards at the start
you would definitely become the thief.
Unbelievable
Does the one handing out the cards ends up as the thief?
I definitely won't do it again.
I definitely won't give out
the cards in the future.
Till now this has been the law of catch the thief
I won't do it either ~
Me neither.
So let's play a game to decide
who'll distribute them.
Yeah true, rules of
the giving out game.
Playing the giving-out-cards game.
Running Ball.
except Sukjin got a Running Ball
Everyone
5-person Mission Team
4-Person Chasing Team
For Jaesuk who
used to run away every single time
You scared me.
Sparta Kook
will always be there...
Kim Jongkook ...
Now I finally to start having a change in role.
The tables
have turned today
Where are you running to, Kim Jongkook?
Chase Jongkook
Catch Kim Jongkook.
You still don't want to stop?.
Must catch him
Yoo Jaesuk, just you wait.
The exchange of fate between the two
I won't let you off.
Begins now
We will set off first.
Mission
Team
Meeting
Let us split into different
levels to complete the task.
I've got confidence.
You are always the easiest to catch.
You are very tall, everyone can see you.
Here it is.
Find 4 public telephones, then ...
... call this number to know the secret code.
It is saying that in this center
there are 4 public phones ...
Hidden in the building is 4 public phones
... here in this building.
Yes ~
So we must go towards this and call the
number then the secret code will be said?
Yes.
One by one.
Combine the numbers to find
the lockers where the Running Balls are hidden
But how do we get the Running Balls?
Should be in the lockers ~
Don't write 010.
Write it down so they won't forget the number
It is to prevent them from
guessing it's a phone number.
Write the whole string of numbers.
But hyung, I have a request.
Last week I was bullied by
Jaesuk over and over again.
If you and Jaesuk hyung
meet one to one ...
If both of you meet ...
Please grab his head
and spin him in mid air.
Throw him a few times.
Okay, time to go.
Fighting ~
1, 2, 3 ... fighting.
Meanwhile
Chasing
Team
Haven't seen these in a long time.
When having these bells on,
your heart is more relaxed.
Time to go.
When? Now?
Let's go ~
Fighting ~
Yooruce Willis.
Nose Cruise.
Gae Travolta.
Fighting ~
Time remaining
Chasing Team moving into the elevator
Why is it so small in here?
Really no shame, taking
the elevator together.
If Jaesuk wasn’t here
Two of them would be alone together
If it was someone else, I
would have walked away.
Testing
Why are you using the
walkie-talkie all of a sudden?
The person is next to you
Why use the walkie-talkie?
The walkie talkie doesn't seem to work.
The approaching
bell sounds
Panting
From the 3rd floor
Gary * Jihyo
This is made of glass.
Jihyo ...
Why are you trying to
run away from oppa.
You are leaving me so quickly?
Mission
Team
Spotted
It's Kim Jongkook ~
Leaving me so quickly?
Where?
Kim Jongkook.
Mission
Team
Everyone split up
Aigoo, Kwangsoo ...
HaHa * Kwangsoo
Close to a dead end
Wait ~
HaHa taking the opportunity to run~!!
Come here.
Kwangsoo ...
Will the previous Mission Team
let him escape like that?
Yah, run quickly. Yooruce Wills, run quickly.
Even if I got caught, why must I
be caught by Jaesuk and Sukjin?
Aren't you suppose to be on our team?
Hyung wait, let me breathe for a while.
Kwangsoo what is that?
Hyung, look at what's written.
That couldn't be the
clue or is it the mission?
A number written
on his wrist
This is the mission.
Hyung, wait.
If you didn't want them to see it
you should've written it on a paper
Wait for a while and I'll give it to you.
This code ...
It's a code? I didn't know.
Kwangsoo ...
Noona ...
Noona, I can't communicate
now with the hyungs.
Jihyo, remember this ... 4021.
It was kind Jihyo who came
Maybe she let go off Kwangsoo?
Jihyo, help me get the name-tag off.
The friendship of four
Usually hiding together
Noona, wait a minute.
Help me persuade the
hyungs, please talk to them.
How can there be ...
What friendship...
Ah, Jaesuk hyung ...
You did well Jihyo.
They are...
heartless...
Kwangsoo
Time left
Sparta Kooks goes toward
1 st floor
Civil Defense Center
Here you can imagine
the country's Civil Defense History
Over there
Found a public phone
Careful
Dropping the coin in
then dials the numbers on his palm
I am the Running Man.
Code ... quickly.
The 4th number is 8.
Mission Team Using the walkie-talkie to confirm numbers
Joongki at the Earthquake Simulator
Once someone enters
Earthquake immediately starts
Seems like this is the Earthquake Simulation Center.
Please escape from the building.
That scared me.
After the earthquake
Escaping from the simulation
The simulation seems real.
Public phone spotted
Public telephone.
2 out of 4
Public phones found
Shaky
The floor is going through
Richter Scale 5.0 tremor~
The 3rd number is 2.
Thanks for the info.
Mission Team confirms the next number
Time left
Hyung, where are you?
I see Lizzy, 3rd floor ~
Lizzy is at the 3rd floor.
Yooruce Willis starts chasing
I saw Lizzy on the 3rd floor.
Went up, Lizzy went up.
Sparta Kook
What?
Wait for a while, slow down.
Hyung, Jongkook is here.
Jongkook ~
Jaesuk capturing
or Jong Kook capturing?
Yah, you ...
What?
You wait.
Wait
judging from this...
If you and Jaesuk meet one on one ...
What HaHa had said
If 1:1
against Yooruce Willis
Please grab his head
and spin him in mid air.
And throw him a few times.
Originally just laugh
at the idea like that
I beg of you.
Yooruce Willis
Sparta Kooks
It's happening in reality
I'm coming up.
3rd floor ~
Wait, I can rip off your name tag.
Tear it off ~
Say it is easy...
Jongkook is at the 3rd floor ~
Hyung come faster,
Jongkook is at the 3rd floor.
Yah ~
What you doing, wait ...
Jongkook is at the 3rd floor ~
He went down ~
Walking towards the 2nd floor.
Now he's staring directly at me.
Jongkook in the 3rd floor.
Help needed.
Jongkook hyung?
Jihyo ...
Catching someone isn't that important.
Oppa, it's very important.
Gary feels that everything
is better with Jihyo
Very important.
VJ, please help me take this.
Isn't she pulling me right now.
Oh, I'm very happy.
I'm gonna fly up already.
Running very fast, Jihyo ...
Jihyo
Runs to help Jaesuk at 3rd floor
Currently staring at me.
Backup Blank Jihyo arrived
Jongkook ~
Oppa, catch him.
Come here now, Kim Jongkook.
Kim Jongkook ...
Sparta Kook
Managed to run towards
Basement 1's corridor
Blank~
Jihyo
actually chased to here
Yooruce Willis joins
2:1 situation
Oppa ~
Yah, you all ...
But... Til now...
Who is the
Mission Team
Chasing Team
What?
Jaesuk and Jihyo from Chasing
Team are unable to move
Oppa, it hurts.
It's really painful.
Blank~ Jihyo's killer move
Hugging his leg and not budging
Hurry up come.
Capture Kim Jongkook.
Gary ...
Kim Jongkook, I caught you.
Jongkook snatches Jaesuk's walkie-talkie
3rd floor ~
At the 3rd floor.
Jongkook told lies to stop the
Chasing Team from coming
Kim Jongkook.
Gary ...
We still have Jihyo.
Jongkook hyung ...
In Jongkook's pocket is
Mission Team's walkie talkie...?
But...
Jihyo steals the walkie talkie...
Will become the
determining factor of this match...
But why are these two so easily controlled
Hold on to Kim Jongkook.
Poke
Hurry up and hold on.
Yooruce Willis
can't stand it
Yah, Jihyo ...
First, give me the walkie-talkie.
Why?
That's mine.
Oppa.
Get his name
tag off ...
Shuup~
Oppa.
If this goes on it'll
stretch til' morning
This moment
Help me hold him.
What the ...
Joongki Mission Team help arrives
Jihyo ...
This time the shoe!!!
Jongkook losing a shoe
to Jihyo this time
Jihyo... Joongki's...
Rip off his name-tag.
The current target is Joongki
Originally fighting Sparta Kook
Now it's Joongki
Yooruce Willis
Blank~Jihyo
Partnered up
It's done.
Catching Joongki
Success
Jihyo, where're you going?
Jihyo ...
Zero energy
Jongkook hyung ...
I didn't know you'd
run away like that.
Joongki
Remaining time
The one who lost a shoe
Sparta Kook
Where's the telephone?
Allowing the tired body to rest a bit
What should I do about my shoe?
This isn't ours.
Where's my walkie-talkie?
My walkie talkie's missing.
This is the other team's.
Unconsciously holding onto
Jaesuk's walkie-talkie
Jihyo, where are you now
and what are you doing?
Gary:
Jaesuk:
Gary ...
My walkie-talkie has been snatched.
Jongkook can clearly
hear our wireless comms.
Sukjin:
How can you be robbed so easily.
Yoo Jaesuk, just you wait.
I won't let you off so easily.
I won't let you off ...
Meanwhile
Hiding everywhere
Mission
Team
Lizzy
Gary sees her...
Ggakung.
You're caught?
Yes, I'm already caught.
Yeah, I am
Still wearing her name-tag
Lizzy calmly says she's caught
Who caught her?
Lizzy exaggerated acting avoid the danger
Lizzy
2nd floor Traffic accident
experience room
Here ...
should be a public phone too
This experience room is built exactly
like an underground railway
Hello ...
I'm the operator. What's the the matter?
What is the password?
I'm the operator.
Yes?
Is anything the matter?
Stop asking me the same thing.
What is the password? Password.
I'm the operator, is anything the matter?
I'm asking you what the password is.
How can you not answer me?
Asking a machine questions,
what are we going to do...?
The 3rd public telephone found
This is Running Man.
Yes, this is Lizzy. What's the password?
The first number is 0.
The locker number
But...
This fact...
Sparta Kook
who swapped his walkie-talkie didn't hear it
Time left
One remaining number
that is needed
Mission
Team
HaHa
Moving stealthily to
the Earthquake hall
But Joongki already found the public phone here
Only telling each other the numbers
but not saying where they found them
Ding Ling ~
The ringing sound
is already nearby
Coming here after being
harassed by Jongkook
Yooruce Willis
I see HaHa.
Tsk tsk...
If you wanted to hide, find a good spot...
Sukjin hyung ...
Big Nose joining in
It’s our HaHa.
You, come out.
Jongkook
save me
HaHa, are you looking for Jongkook?
Open up.
HaHa, looking for Jongkook?
HaHa, are you looking for Jongkook?
Why is Jaesuk holding
our walkie-talkie?
Wonder why Jongkook's
walkie-talkie is with me?
Irritating
Jongkook hyung
what's happening...
Why is this with me?
That walkie-talkie
got stolen by Jihyo..
From then on...
The victory puzzle got more complicated
Jongkook hyung...
Doesn't know the numbers we found...
Relaxed
Is it enough to have Yooruce Willis guarding?
You go over.
Go over.
Get in
What?
I'm letting hyung in.
Okay.
Open the door.
HaHa gives up ...
Open it.
No way!
HaHa runs for his life
You're done for.
Didn't I say you're done for?.
NooOooOO...
Like the last time
Yooruce Willis catches HaHa
Finished.
HaHa uses all his strength, but ...
HaHa
Jongkook hyung ...
Kwangsoo:
Your Jongkook hyung's walkie-talkie
is right here, you *censored*.
You're speaking vulgarities now.
Hearing Jihyo saying dangerous(?) words
You heard it, right?
Flustered
You're now spouting vulgarities.
What Kwangsoo says is true.
It's not wrong.
Kwangsoo's claims
are not sabotage?!
When did I? I did not.
You’re saying it exactly now.
I did not.
Time left
Over on
this side
Mission
Team's
Lizzy...
The last public phone
They only need to know
one more number of the locker
Hello, this is Running Man.
This is Lizzy, can I have
the password please?
The 2nd number is 1.
Okay, I got it ... 1.
The 2nd number of the password is 1.
I only have to reach the locker and I win
Because of her nervousness
the innocent 19 year old look
Lizzy
Only has to reach the locker to win
But...
Lizzy
Jihyo
Blank~
Unwittingly
ambushing...
If Lizzy is caught it'll be a big problem
Wait up.
Lizzy ...
From the moment she stole the walkie-talkie
Today's heavily active Jihyo
Lizzy, I'm sorry.
Crocodile's tears?
NooOOOoo..
Lizzy
Oppa, I caught Lizzy.
Changing the tide of battle...
She's like a warrior woman
I caught Lizzy.
Only the un-contactable Jongkook survives...
Jongkook can't make it
without a walkie-talkie.
Doesn't Jongkook have a walkie-talkie?
Yeah ...
Then there is no way
he'll know the password.
No way to convey
the locker password
Wait, where's our VJ?
Mission
Team
The last resort?
We can't meet directly..?
Because Jongkook doesn't
have a walkie-talkie ...
We can connect privately with his VJ.
That's it ~
It's okay if you don't have this
Tell our password to the VJ so he
can communicate it across for us.
What we know now is 012...
Are you sure?
I'm not very sure ...
It's 8, that last one.
0128 ~
Tell him it's 0128.
Tell Jongkook's VJ.
The last chance to
change the ending
The people who were caught
already have the 2nd number.
Ah, is that so?
Kim Jongkook receives
the locker's password
The worry has disappeared
now for the last rush
Yah, the chasers have less stress.
The two peaceful men who
doesn't know the situation
There's no feeling of stress.
Although there was this slight feeling
when I bumped into Jongkook.
It's a lot.
Chasing
Team
Last objective
is to capture Jongkook
Searching here and there
If only I could reach basement
Intended to take the escalator
but the alarm sounds
Oh?
The escalator is moving.
The escalator moved?
Trying to ditch the 4 chasers
Emergency situation...!
Big Nose Hyung who didn't manage to catch
anyone today is also in the midst of searching
Where is he?
Oh, Kim Jong Kook is here.
Found
Kim Jong Kook is on the 3rd floor.
Discovered
Kim Jongkook 3rd floor.
Carrying on like this...
I must reach the locker
Suddenly
Yah, it's Kim Jongkook.
Kim Jongkook 1st floor.
They're everywhere
Chasing
Team
Over there ~
Mission
Jong
kook
Chasing
4 hunters
All running to basement
Kim Jongkook is at 1st floor.
Everyone to 1st floor.
Slip~
Got his shoe snatched by Jihyo so he slipped
In the end in front of Jihyo
Walkie-talkie, shoe
The girl who turned the tide of victory
As expected, ended by that girl
All victories will be
completed by her...!
Without a pair of shoes
Jongkook is unable to go full speed
There are the lockers
The end goal is in sight...
It ends like this
Hold them ~
Jihyo * Gary
catches him together
Rip ~
Oh my gosh...!
Jihyo ends the game
Blank ~
You've worked hard, friend.
Hyung, you should express
thanks to our team, right?
Let catch people every week from now on.
You're making it sound nice.
Feeling good about himself Jaesuk who chased
We might as well do
it like this next week.
Chasing
Team
Sukjin Jaesuk Gary Jihyo
Win Running Balls
Okay, there's a change in rules today.
Jaesuk Jongkook Gary Jihyo
balls
Sukjin HaHa Joongki Kwangsoo Lizzy
ball
Shin Lim Dong is a famous place right?
24-hour open for business soondae place.
Today's
punishment
Wearing hot pants and
do a review of ShinLimDong sausage town
Even at this time, there's
still a lot of people around.
There will be plenty of people.
Really a lot.
How many balls?
It's 5, 5 right?
Okay, I'll put it in.
Let Song Jihyo's not come out.
I only have one, even if it's a miracle ...
A miracle ...
The hope-to-escape kiss
Let's start the balls rolling.
Let's start.
Please ...
Kang Gary.
Sincere
1, 2, 3.
The first person to escape is?
As expected
Jihyo
Confirmed
escape
Song Jihyo.
That's unbelievable.
Escaped today too
The Goddess of Luck Song Jihyo
Really now ...
Envious
1, 2, 3.
And the next escapee is?
Please!
Sukjin
Confirmed
escape
Woah ~
Celebratory
gesture
Woo Sa~
Really sincere
shouting ...
Who will be the 3rd to escape?
Please
Kwang
soo
Confirmed
escape
In the pit...
Will Jongkook be punished again today?
Its really left with only 2.
2 chances remaining
1, 2, 3.
Who will be the next escapee?
Lizzy
Confirmed
escape
The escapees are
overjoyed ~
That's great.
This is really ...
Getting closer and closer to the hot pants
The lottery actually picked
3 people owning only 1 ball?
Miracle
3 of the escapees owned only 1 ball
I have 2
1 ... 2 ... 3.
There's only once last chance
... 3.
The last escapee is?
The ball is out
Let's have a look.
Please ~
Please let it be me
Please ...
Kim Jongkook.
Really?
Aiy, stop Joking.
Stop being like that.
Let's have a look at it.
Anticipation
HaHa ... !
HaHa
Confirmed
escape
An exuberant
victory move
The 1:8
Running Ball...
This
is
really
great
The nightmare of wearing hot pants again
I had two balls, but in the end ...
You're requested to wear this.
Hold this.
This is autumn.
Reaching Shin Lim Dong Soondae Town
Ah, really now ...
If we follow the dressing norm,
these should have been pants.
They'll be thinking that
4 weirdos have arrived.
Wah~
And I thought there
wasn't anyone around.
They're all inside.
It's okay, just stay inside.
Hey guys.
I'm very famous in Shin Lim Dong.
I've found my pride in Shin Lim Dong.
Of course.
Hello ~
Running Man suddenly appears
Confused
Please eat well ~
Isn't that
Yoo Jaesuk?
I haven't eaten pan-fried
soondaes for so long.
Huh?
The moment the soondae
and dressings are hooked
I better put this down.
Why aren't we starting?
Everybody seems to be coming over.
Delivering lots of laughter
in the early morning
This is good.
Ah, hot.
What are you doing, acting like this?
Because he's wearing hot pants
the hot sauce drips on his white thigh
Unknowingly, a surge of people...
Food's so good forgets about the punishment
Oh, it's good.
It's cleared.
Ah, this is really tasty.
We ate well ~
See you ~
Original hardsubs by iSUB
Transcribed by HapB
Color and alignment by SamFive