Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Mostly based on hardsubs by iSUBS
Today our Running Man
members got together again.
In front of the large 'L' mart
Today is actually the Christmas
Special for Running Man.
Yeah ~
Christmas Special
Merry Christmas.
How great if it was
really a white Christmas
Stop it.
Kwangsoo, do something
that matches your age.
Kwangsoo!
Gets excited alone
Our cameramen are already freezing.
Don't you feel ﻿bad acting like
this in front of the cameras?
It's not only cold
but also have to fight the artificial snow
Oh, I am sorry.
Kwangsoo acted like this because he
wanted to show his entertaining talent.
I did this to get
praised
Hyung, isn't today the Christmas Special?
Exactly.
I prepared present for everyone.
On the other hand
Honest Joongki prepared presents
What presents?
Startled
What did you get for us, JoongKi?
Excited
This is for HaHa hyung.
Thanks.
Not right, HaHa's present should be placed
beside his pillow on Christmas eve.
Because
he's a child
This is for Gary hyung.
Mine is the biggest, I got the biggest.
This is for Lizzy.
Aigoo, Lizzy's present is small.
This is for Kwangsoo.
Yiah, it's Pororo.
Really lovely ~
Today Joongki became the Santa Claus
I really like it.
I'm embarrassed about my snow spraying.
Self reflection
If we knew about this, we would
have prepared presents too.
That's right.
Young Joongki is indeed
thoughtful
I like it very much.
Today we will be filming in
the huge toy store L Mart.
Today's landmark
The whopping toy store
L-Mart
Children will love today's episode.
Dreams of our childhood
A toy kingdom
Feels warm right?
It's a toy store.
It's the largest toy store here.
A landmark that fits Christmas
Today we are going to film here.
And again, we ﻿have invited
guests for our Christmas Special.
Today's exclusive invited guests
In 2010, the greatest drama
which we highly anticipated.
The two heroes from the drama
"Athena: the Goddess of war" ...
... Kim Minjong and Choi Siwon.
Next generation
versatile entertainer
Choi Siwon
The pioneer of
versatile entertainer
Kim Minjong
Extremely extravagant casting
The hottest topic ever since it's broadcast
Blockbuster drama
Ex-North Korean secret agent
Minjong
Elite rookie agent
Siwon
Oh, Siwon ...
Hello.
Only greeting Siwon?
Minjong has stealthy
being pushed to the back
Minjong is being put down.
Bitter
The greatest drama in 2010
which we are highly anticipating.
You acted very well in Athena.
So the ﻿same applies for Running Man, right?
It didn't broadcast yet, right?
It already came out.
Please make sure you know
the schedule before saying it.
But right now, isn't it
yet to be broadcasted?
'Athena' had been aired when this episode was
broadcasted but not when it was recorded
It's been aired.
I see.
So how's the response for Episode 1?
Hypocrisy
Embarrassed
Didn't you say it has
already been aired?
Smack
The consequence of
chattering is punishment
Personally I really like Minjong.
We also have Siwon from Super Junior.
He acts as an elite in the drama.
Elite rookie agent played by
Siwon
What kind of character do you play?
Me?
Yes.
I act as someone who
escaped from North Korea.
Lives a secret life after
escaping from North Korea
Minjong
Even though I was having fun
when I was in North Korea ...
I know lots of secrets
and confidential issues.
Is that so?
So what kind of character would
you like to play in Running Man?
It has been a while since I
participate in a variety show.
Moreover, today I'm here with Siwon ...
... so it would ﻿be great if I am
assigned to an interesting team.
While playing bells hide-n-seek, do
you ﻿want to seek people or hide.
Of course I want to catch people.
Quick
answer
If you don't want to be
worn, you have to seek.
Somehow I have the feeling
you would be sought after.
Jaesuk's forecast
Minjong might be chased
And we will wear hot pants together?
Plus booking for hot pants?
Minjong with flaming determination
How many Running Balls do you want?
Later on...
Wow, this is really spacious.
Displaying more than 8000 toys
Largest in the nation Heaven for children
First mission is called Christmas Present.
First mission
Christmas Presents
Are the presents for us?
You just received a present.
Jihyo keeps wanting presents.
She seems to be unsatisfied
with the present just now.
I'm going to announce the theme now.
You guys have to shop
based on the theme given.
Based on the theme?
There are 3 rounds.
Yes?
You guys will be divided into 3 teams.
White Team
Siwon - Sukjin
Jaesuk - Minjong
Green Team
Jongkook - Lizzy
Joongki - Kwangsoo
Red Team
Gary - Jihyo
HaHa
The theme for round 1 is to
find the Best 5 presents ...
... that children wish to
receive during Christmas.
Choose 5?
Why make me the
main character here?
It's enough to have me here, fools.
The leader for little kids
Haroro
Among the items in this store ...
... there are hot sale items
that you should bring back.
And among them, choose the Best 5.
The team which gets the
Best 5 items will win.
Don't I have a kid?
Right, so hyung should know about this.
Advantageous for Sukjin who has a 9 year-old son
Don't you have a kid too?
Yes, but I don't know much.
Just ask me.
Full of
confidence
Let's go.
Let's go. Aja aja.
* Aja means similar to fighting
Grab the hot sales item before the others
Let's go. Aja aja.
Is this the one?
Go to where Pororo is.
No, toy car.
Run.
Christmas presents children wish to get
Find the BEST 5
Wow, I'm so happy.
Yah, this one.
Hey children ...
However
In this spacious place
Sukjin has a kid.
No, that's not one of them.
A gun should be one of them.
Over here, that's is it.
Hot sale
item
Toy train set
Not right, this is too expensive.
Can't buy it It's to expensive
Daddy's heart
I say this from a father's perspective.
I want to have this so much
You want to have, but can't buy.
Siwon, isn't this the right one?
That's why this is a Christmas present
Children's heart
Right, I really want to own this.
Daddy's heart
Too expensive
Children's heart
That's why
it's expensive
I want to have it too, but ...
Hyung, let's take one.
Isn't this very good?
No, no.
I said this is too expensive,
people can't afford it, really.
The triumph of 3 children
Toy train set is chosen
It feels like I'm holding a present for real.
We have to use common sense.
Ah, really.
Minjong, isn't it right?
It's the right one.
But this one must cost 2 million won.
Is this right choice?
Yes, this one.
This is too expensive.
I said this is not a
hot sale item, seriously.
Must be right.
Best selling ones.
What is it?
He keeps wanting us to tell him.
I'm sure this is one of them.
I said this is not.
I said people won't buy
because it's too expensive.
Daddy's heart
Minjong ...
They have Running Man's motor here.
Where is it?
Oh, that is really my favourite.
Hot
sale
item
Assembly toy
I love this a lot.
Why keep choosing what you like?
They must be the children's favorite.
Has to be among children's BEST 5
Not their own favorites
You like it, right?
Yes, I really like it.
Is the assembly toy among
the BEST 5...?
Hyung, I really want to buy this.
We have to take this.
This one?
Hold.
Minjong
Let's take this~ Go
Each team can only take 5 items
Must consider carefully
Not right?
No.
Hyung!
What?
Which one?
Siwon is like, "Hyung, this one".
Excitement and flowery hand style
No, this is really not right.
I think it's a right choice,
the children will like it
Daddy Sukjin keeps eliminating expensive stuff
It's too expensive.
Parents hearts
Too expensive~
Hyung ...
... it's not an ordinary
one, this is Star Wars.
Reassures
Look at what you chose,
and now this this one.
Looking at it
They chose two largest ones
Hyung, they have this too.
Just choose two, two is enough.
I really came here to shop.
I'm not in this team, really.
Angsty dad
Siwon found a big-sized toy again
Hyung ~
Hot sale
item
Kiddy electro-car
It's too expensive, people won't buy it.
Again
Christmas presents are supposed
to be lightly more expensive.
Isnt this a hot sale item?
Siwon & Jaesuk are totally convinced
Running Man.
How many have you guys chosen?
I liked it very much
since I was young.
Take it ~
Seriously why are
you guys like this?
We have to take this
one no matter what.
But how many toys
are you going to take?
Even have a hard time putting it in the cart
I'm not in this team.
I don't care anymore.
In the toy store
Understand the heart of anxious parent
Meanwhile
Red
Team
Jihyo & the two kids
What can it be?
It's doll ~
Wow, it's Pororo.
Hey, I am Haroro.
Hyung ...
... Pororo, the friend of our family.
Swoosh~
... friend of our family.
In a hurry
Not much time left...!
Move faster.
Why take this?
Pororo is the best.
Putting you into the cart.
No, putting him will do.
Why no Running Man tags?
Jihyo is anxious to death
Don't be so worried.
Jihyo, want to try putting this on?
Wow, that looks great.
Seriously ...
We have to search faster.
Pick presents faster, my
two kids aren't helping.
Quarrel
Wrangling
Why so anxious?
Let's just have fun.
Be more cheerful.
Don't speak in an ordering tone.
Don't do this.
Bothersome.
You are no different from Jongkook
He's right, relax instead.
Right.
Oppa ...
Jihyo discovered something?
Where is it?
Hot sale
item
Doll
Might be the present young girls
wish to receive the most
Take this no matter what.
Assurance
Barbie doll. Confirmed?
Yes, confirmed.
Oppa ...
Hot sale
item
Doll's house
Wait a minute.
Gary is also assured on this
It has two floors.
Since Jihyo is here
2 items for girls are chosen
Hey there, aunt.
You are here shopping
with your two sons?
It's tiring, these kids
are so disobedient.
My life~
They have things like this too.
Meanwhile moving hastily
Green
Team
Will children like this?
I think so, but ...
Hurry up and find a game.
Game is definitely one of them.
Hyung, this one.
Hot sale
item
Game CD
Hot sale
item
But next to it is
the portable gaming console
Also this ...
This might be used often too
If it's for kids, then take it.
Finally the gaming console is
chosen
Hyung, this one has
no Running Man tag.
Kwangsoo is suspicious
Also, all these have to be
placed more naturally.
Please listen to me once.
Ignore
Let's go.
Compared to the gaming console
Kwangsoo prefers the game CD
We don't know whether
this is the right one.
It's the right one.
We said it's the right one.
Hyung, this is not right.
Come over!
At this time
It's now the closing sale.
Suddenly
Closing sales?
Closing sale ~
Again
Jongkook's manager Kim Gabin
Huh?
Startled
Closing
sale?
Over there.
If it' a sale item then
Hurry ~
chance it's among BEST 5 is high
At the start of the sale
anonymous costumers are rushing in
Bang
A sudden wave of customers
Jihyo ...
Only one for sale
Popular
item
Robot
Siwon, grab it.
Swish~
White
Team
Siwon
wasted
Who'll
be the owner of the only robot...?
Jumps
Green
Team
Joongki also fails
Kwangsoo lifts Joongki
Oh~!
Now there might be a chance...!
No way...
Joongki
Sale item robot
obtained
If it' on sudden sale
it will definitely get into the BEST 5
Jongkook hyung ...
Brings happiness to Jongkook
You got it?
Good, you have done well.
No matter what
Kwangsoo lifting Joongki was the decisive move
Hyung ...
I lifted Joongki on my ﻿
shoulders, so we got it.
It was Joongki who did well.
I lifted Joongki.
It was Joongki.
There is 1 minute left.
Jongkook hyung, over here.
Popular
item
Toy piano
This seems like right.
Wait.
Popular
item
Spinning top
This is the best.
Confident
Most popular toy among children lately
It's this, not any others.
There's not much time left
We have been here already.
Put that in.
Red
Team
Jihyo and the two kids choose Lego
It's not that, we got the right.
Hyung, the remote.
Stay quiet.
Jongkook hyung ...
Towards the final point
Stay quiet, really.
Shopping ended
You don't know how solid this is.
Each team's idea of the BEST 5 toys
For Christmas
Joongki, you want this right?
Kids should really like this.
I want it too.
We are starting now?
The toys children like, in 5th place ...
Pororo ~
In 5th place of the toys children
want most for Christmas is?
Block game.
Block game
White
Team
Red
Correct
White and Red Team get 1 point
Kids really like this a lot.
We will now reveal the 4th place.
Pororo.
In 4th place ...
4th place ...
Game CD.
Game CD
Red
Team
Correct
2 points now
Game CD.
That's really a waste.
The game CD Kwangsoo wanted to choose
Unbelievable.
Now revealing the 3rd place.
Robot.
Doll.
3rd place ...
Train set.
Train set
White
Team
Correct
2 points now
it's too expensive
The toy Sukjin objected to because
I really wanted this toy badly.
I apologize.
This is what I really want now.
Kids wish about the same
regardless of now or then
No, who will buy so many?
If there are two of these, it
will be a year full of warmth.
We have got them.
White
Team
points
Green
Team
points
Red
Team
points
It's 2 to 2 now.
Announcing the 2nd place.
The latest Spinning Top.
Spinning Top
White
Team
Correct
3 points now
White
Team
Leading with 3 points
It's this.
Cheers
Really.
Bitter...
White
Team
Green
Red
Team
Announcing the 1st place..
Pororo ~
If only Red Team gets the 1st place
right, it will be a tie with White Team.
Ultimately
what children want for Christmas
The first place is?
Robot.
Robot
Green Team gets a meaningless point
We won ~
3 out of 5 correct
White
Team
wins 1st round
Bitter...
Pororo robot.
It's a Pororo robot.
Is Pororo actually a robot?
Can even play by himself
Jongkook doesn't play
with toys that's why ...
Are you giving us Running Balls just like that?
No, you have won the 1st round.
Oh, so this is just one round.
This was just the first round.
Bang
We will now reveal the
theme for the 2nd round.
Find the best 3 presents children
would want to receive in the 70s.
Ya, we even have a 60's child.
70's was when Big Nose was a child
Sukjin-Minjong-Jaesuk
Advantage of age
White
Team
I was still a kid in the 70's.
Already counting back to the 70's
Children at that time
during Christmas ...
What presents
did they wish for?
Honestly, this game is to our
advantage to a certain level.
Just now it was and this time again.
In the mart, there are 15
kinds of toys from the past.
Each team has to pick out 3 items.
Go ...
Only 5 minutes to shop
Group style.
Assembly
Happily
Siwon knows what it is
Swish
In the 70's?
This ~
Where should I look?
Siwon immediately brought a model
Since it's brought here, put it in the cart
Siwon, was there a Running
Man sign stuck onto this?
There wasn't.
If there isn't then it can't be.
A cookie box with a Running Man sign
This ~
Struggle
Cookie box set from the 70s.
The bigger hand actions the better
Hyung ~
Prince
Siwon spotted roller skates this time
Swish!
Naive Prince Siwon's reaction
has a good feeling to it
As if they already won
The old men and the Prince
It can't not have
the Running Man sign
Just need to find one more
Hyung ~
Just get it first, hurry.
Old fashion mini car?
Rush~
Jongkook who
reached it first
Immediately
Snatched away by Jongkook
Green
Team
Got the mini car
Jongkook hyung.
What?
Puts the stolen(?) mini car in the cart
God!
Hyung, found it.
Old generation toy telephone
Nods
Right now ...
... did you see Siwon's pose?
The toy telephone
was very popular in the 70's
What is that?
I have memories of playing with
a toy telephone when I was young.
There is no female toys from
what we have picked just now.
Affirmed
I haven't lived in the 60's
and 70's, I know nothing.
Doesn't matter, just find
the toys from the past first.
Jongkook, lets go together.
Kwangsoo:
Jongkook hyung ...
Argh, stop calling me.
Right now, we only can
follow Jongkook hyung.
Hyung, I was wrong.
You guys have not
found anything yet?
Crayons?
Hurry look for it.
Spotted Prince Crayons from the past
Prince crayons.
Kwangsoo ...
Hyung, isn't there also a song for
when the father buys the crayons?
That's right.
Little Man book from the old days
It's here.
Finally found it.
Green Team found the storybook
Mini car * Crayons * Little Man book
Chosen
Shopping time's up
We might win.
The song where the
father buys the crayon.
Prince Crayons, really ...
Crayons is etched in their memories
The things you guys found
seems to be from the 60's.
Those are all from the 60's, right?
Green Team chose humble items
We will reveal one by one.
Presents most wanted by 70's kids
1st of the BEST 3 will be revealed
Starting from 1st place?
Yes.
The 3 most wanted presents are...?
Cookie box set.
Cookie box set
Prince Siwon's big moment celebration
White
Team
Correct
Gets 1 point
The era with lack of cookies
a gift all kids would want
That one should've been ours.
Second place is ...
... Crayon box.
Crayon box
Green Team receives 1 point
Now we win.
Prince Crayon.
Was there really a Prince Crayon?
The first era on that I've ever
used was the Prince Crayons.
Mom buying the Prince Crayon
for Jaesuk's elementary school entry
You don't know how
much it cost back then.
Even the smell is ancient
Ah this smell.
The smell of history.
Hurry up and announce the 3rd one.
Ah, yeah ~
She's angry.
All these talk about
Prince Crayon and stuff.
Red Team hasn't found a single correct one
Ah Jihyo, seriously.
I'm announcing the 3rd one.
Will the White Team win?
Or tie with the green team?
Or will it be the Red Team's bike?
Mini car.
Mini car
2 out of the BEST 3
Green
Team
Wins
Total score of rounds won
White
Team
Green
Red
Team
Look at how regretful
Minjong's expression is.
If only the mini
car didn't get
snatched away
What's the next round?
Please hurry and tell us.
Next round is ...
Choose toys and the team ﻿with the
total sum closest to 50,000 won wins.
Ah the closest to 50,000?
If you have the same value, the
team with the most toys wins.
Like that? Okay.
Then we shouldn't just pick 1 toy
that we think is worth 50,000 won.
Are we going now?
Yes, let's go.
White and Green Teams have won one round each
Go.
Haroro has an upset stomach
Hurry, go to the washroom and come back.
Sorry
Hurry up and come back.
Gary and Jihyo shop alone
Shall we pick toys that
I have bought before?
White
Team's
Strategy
Choosing toys
Sukjin has bought before
That's a good idea.
How about this spinning top?
This should be 10,000 won.
How much is this?
30,000 won.
What?
That's 30,000 won?
This isn't worth 30,000 won
because it's a robot sword.
Should be around 20,000 to 25,000 won.
20,000 to 25,000 won.
Estimated total now
30,000
Those are almost the same,
but this one will be cheaper.
Let's take this then.
Follow the experienced father
Sukjin's estimate with trust
Everyone else is picking small
toys, so let's choose a big one.
Without Haroro present
Romantic atmosphere
Monday
Couple
Right, that's what I was thinking.
Strategy
Choose one
that costs close to 50.000
Let's search for one and
choose just that one.
Oppa, I think this one is okay.
Shopping harmony
Monday
Couple
This one or is this one better?
Jihyo chooses a house set
Looks like there's a bit of a difference.
Looks like that one is better.
Is it? Then I'll take this.
That one.
♥ Sweet
You're just taking that one?
Only needs one kitchen house set?
Want to play with this
together on Christmas?
Okay.
Really?
Then should we take this one?
If this doesn't work then we'll
have to take today's punishment.
That's fine, we'll just take the punishment.
Okay, we'll take the punishment together.
Without any worries
Even taking the punishment together is good
Those two look like newly weds.
What did you say?
Surprised
Siwon ...
... thanks.
Siwon, I love you.
They look like
newly weds shopping together after work
You two really look like a couple.
Aiyo, thank you.
* Pronounce thanks by using seumdwa
Together
we pick toys
Browsing together
It'll be good if everyday was a Monday?
Kang Gary lives the moment
White
Team
Each team tries to buy
toys of a total of 50,000
Green
Team
Red
Please tell the price of
the products one by one.
Seriously, Jongkook took so many things.
The team closest to 50,000 wins
Exactly.
We'll start revealing the
price for the White Team.
Is that a transforming ball?
Yes, this one.
10,000 won
13,600 won.
It's within the estimates.
Within Sukjin's estimate
Blue mini car.
This is the one Minjong wanted,
although I said, "Don't bring it".
How is this one?
30,000 won?
2000 ﻿won.
6,000 won.
See I told you, it's not only 2,000 won.
3 times the estimate
The spinning top, this one should
be over 5,000 won or 8,000 won.
Electronic product.
8,400 won.
You see, I told you, I was right.
The father with experience is more accurate
I told you I've bought it before.
And there's one more mini car.
2000, 10000, 2000, 5000.
1,990.
It's okay.
Right now, what is our total?
Your current total is 29,990 won.
If the last toy is costs 20,000 it'll be
close to 50,000 won
Then this one will be 20,010 won.
But it must be around 35,000 won.
Lastly, we'll reveal the
biggest Robot Sword.
20,000 won ~
21,000 won.
Hyunwoo's dad Sukjin's confident choice
The price of the Robot Sword is?
59,200 won.
Don't worry
59,200 won
59,200 won.
Way over 50,000 won
How can the price be inflated this much?
Had a lot of confidence before
Kim Minjong ~
The price was inflated too much.
White Team's
Running Ball dreams flies away
Is this one so expensive?
White Team total price is 89,190 won.
Completely down
When I bought it I only spent 20,000,
why is it so expensive now?
Next ~
We'll reveal the Red Team now.
We only have one.
That one should be over 50,000 won.
39,900 won.
We have a chance of winning
They are missing around 10,000 won.
We should just have
taken the Robot Sword.
Next we'll reveal Green Team's total.
Pencil case.
3,150 won.
They only revealed one price,
why are you so happy?
Next one is ruler.
Ruler ~
1,200 won, no I mean 800 won.
540 won.
It's okay, that's cheap.
Stationery pro Lizzy's estimates are all correct
Coloring pen.
4,000.
2,900 won.
It's okay ~
What do you mean it's okay?
It's way off the estimate.
It's okay, we still have a bear and this.
We estimated the Frisbee to be 14,000 won.
I estimate that one to be 89,000 won
When I was young, I used
20,000 won to buy that.
9,600 won.
Oh, it's okay.
What is okay?
It's getting further and further
away from your estimate.
How much does the last one
have to cost in order to win?
Current total is 16,190 won
The bear needs to cost more than 23,710.
To win the bear must cost  23,710 won
I have seen that at the
mart outside my house.
It should be around 16,000 won.
20 thousand and ...
20,000?
Only needs to be over 23,710 to win
It's less than 30,000?
29,800 won.
Green
Team
Wins 2nd and 3rd round
Wins at the end
Green Team's total is 45,990 won.
Jongkook Joongki Kwangsoo Lizzy
receives Running Balls
No way this is over 50,000 won?
Disbelieve
From the first mission
Minjong failed to get a Running Ball
But there are still games
that'll make him more surprised
Meeting before the opening
This is going to be a 1:10
battle against Minjong.
Today's 2nd mission is
tricking Kim Minjong
How do we trick him?
Sweaters?
The size is on the back.
I've gotten fatter lately
What is this?
Today's fake mission topic will
be Kim Minjong's classic dramas.
During the judging of Kim Minjong's critics ...
... don't let him figure out that
you all have changed sweaters.
Real mission
Change sweaters
without Minjong noticing
You start with red bags
on your sweaters then ...
Change from red to
green colored bag
... change into sweaters
with green bags.
What if we get discovered?
If Minjong discovers anyone
changing, then it is a fail.
That's hard.
Without Minjong knowing
Change to sweaters with green bags
Guest that's tricking
Guest that's being tricked(?)
Kim Minjong's classic titles.
Revealing the fake game
Happy
There are too many.
With the exception of Minjong ...
... you'll form groups with 2 members each
and challenge Kim Minjong's classic titles.
Minjong will become the judge then?
Yes, Minjong will decide
which team to eliminate.
Really seems like normal game instructions
Will the members
be able to change without being noticed?
Oops
Pay attention
on the sweater
We've prepared a VCR to show
you, what skits you have to act.
Fake mission
Minjong's
<Classic dramas>
Happiness
does not come
in grades
<Happiness doesn't come in grades>
Minjong (19 years old)
So good looking.
Shy
Acting with  the most
popular young stars then
I really liked Minyeon
noona back then.
Kim Bosung.
Feelings!
<Feelings!>
Ah, "Feelings!"
Still a classic drama after so many years
Maybe it'll be me in that spot next time, right?
Son Jichang - Lee Jungjae
Top stars
Also
Woo Heejin
Wow, Woo Heejin.
And young Kim Minjong
Face turning red(?)
Was an idol star back then
Isn't that our punishment, hot pants?
Hot pants?
Ah, this one ...
Pose that belongs to
Minjong
Feeling only you
Son Jichang+Kim Minjong
Hot topic of the time
Jichang - Minjong's
<The Blue>
<Feeling only you>
Topped the charts for 3 weeks
"The Blue".
They were very influential back then.
<Mr. Q>
SBS drama special
Mister Q
Minjong won the best actor prize for this film
Hello, I'm the new employee, Lee Kangto.
I ﻿never missed a single episode of this.
This was the best.
Does Minjong still remember those times?
A famous scene with Kim Heesun
Became a hot topic
I don't care if Haewon sues me.
The kiss scene at the bus stop
Delighted
Innocent Minjong
feeling helpless
I'll sue you.
I'll definitely sue you.
Famous line
Ah~~
Havoc
Shivering embarrassment
But it's really cool
Hyung, then what about your
Bangbae-dong slapping incident?
Don't mention it
Ah, yes.
The hot topic during his
<Lie Detection Test> previously
It was twice, he got slapped twice.
Helping
Minjong's kiss Yoohyuk's slap?
Why do you keep bringing it up?
But isn't it too much, slapping you?
Don't say that about noona.
I got slapped because I did
something wrong of course.
What do you know about my love life?
Then let's start re-enacting
Minjong's classic dramas.
Lets start with, "Happiness
Does Not Come In Grades".
We have to do it well.
HaHa
(as Lee Deokhwa)
Minjong's immortal dramas
Happiness
doesn't come
in grades
Kim Jongkook
(as Kim Minjong)
At this moment ...
... our relationship is not that
of a teacher and his disciple.
It's a fight between two men.
This is HaHa and Jongkook.
Teacher
HaHa
Disciple
Jongkook
will re-enact it
The important thing is his eyes.
Whether we get to stay in the
school or not depends on this.
Already
practicing?
My eyes are not even
half the size of his.
The highlight
of the scene
Look at his eyes.
Eyes show different emotions
every time he gets hit
This embarrassing scene
Minjong unable to watch any longer
Last scene
Decisive final punch
The key point is his eyes.
My eyes aren't even
half the size of his.
I can't stare like that.
Before even starting
Difficulty because of Jongkook's small eyes
Jongkook, the eyes are important.
Whisper
Re-enacting and
changing sweater at the same time?
Already focusing on judging
innocent Minjong
So Haroro and Jongkook will start first.
What are they
discussing?
Listen up.
So HaHa is the teacher
and Jongkook is Minjong.
Gary suddenly takes off his jacket?
Also ...
Observing
Siwon came up with an idea so
that you can become Minjong.
Do you have tape?
The person who started this touching
the nose thing is HOT's Moon Heejun.
Not because the eyes are too close.
We know.
It is better to express
emotions through our eyes.
Eyes too close together,
that is Shin Dongyup.
At this moment
Gary took off his sweater
Lizzy helping
to block
You still have to use the tape.
It's going to be interesting.
I hit you twice right?
Minjong only thinks about judging
In a flash
Gary changes his sweater
Success
Ready?
Everyone, please stand
behind Director Minjong.
Changed to
green sweater
Yes.
Hu~
Eh?
Did he spot Gary's sweater?
If he notice then
the 1:10 challenge will be a failure
Siwon, who usually shouts 'Action'
these days can be assistant director.
Still thinking about judging
Lucky...
Standby, get ready.
Peaceful Gary's excited since
he is the first to succeed
Ready?
Yes.
Ready ... Action.
Ready
Action
HaHa as the teacher
Passionate action acting
Serious
Why are there no lines?
Pro wre... wrestling?
Their plan?
Take off their top
Jongkook also takes off his top
Get up.
He's already up.
From this moment onwards ...
... our relationship is ﻿no longer
that of a teacher and his disciple.
As they are acting
they also have to change their sweaters
Wide open
Satisfied judge Minjong?
Your expression has to keep changing.
Minjong's emotions keep changing
You have to change.
Perfect re-enactment?
Ha ha
Great job?
According to the original scene
It's time for Jongkook to retaliate
Wait, please ...
Indeed
How will he change his sweater?
Taking off his sweater?
Is it necessary
to take it off?
What a plan
Huh!
I did well,
right?
The sweater he has
to change into
Jongkook's retaliation
Teacher.
Teacher(?)
Their acting is so bad.
Even so judge Minjong
is still serious
Is our Jongkook satisfied now?
Only his voice is a perfect
re-enactment Haroro
Come here.
It's only the start.
You still haven't
taken your shirt off
No, you're mine.
Jongkook helping HaHa with his shirt
Ah That's their plan?
gets hit at the same time
Loses his shirt and
have seen something?
Could he
Daeng
Why?
Innocent Minjong is still only judging
It's because you hit me
too much at the start.
Siwon picket up
the shirts with red bags
Let's listen to what
the director has to say.
Hyung, you
are the best
But...
Lizzy's sweater?
How can you be so good at fighting?
When Minjong was focusing on judging
Lizzy changed her
shirt at that moment
Watching and naturally
changing her shirt
Complete
His body is already NG.
* NG = Not Good = Blooper
Reason for the fail?
The drama we saw just now isn't called
"Happiness does not come ﻿in grades".
It's called "Happiness is not muscles".
Gary and Lizzy
have already changed their shirts
Jongkook and HaHa
also changing their shirts
This is interesting.
Is it?
Naive
Is It?
HaHa
Succeeds
Also
Jongkook
Succeeds
You've worked hard ~
Changing sweater
is hard work indeed
This is the 1:10 challenge
Now we might be asked to act in dramas.
Innocent Minjong still doesn't know the truth
Next is Yoo Jaesuk's team.
Song Jihyo
(as Woo Heejin)
Feelings
Yoo Jaesuk
(as Kim Minjong)
Kim Minjong immortal masterpiece
Oppa ...
Can you do something for me?
What is it?
Can you take off your glasses?
Huh?
Do we really have to watch
Jaesuk without glasses?
I can't see anything
with my glasses off.
Even so ...
Just this once.
Jaesuk has to re-enact this
melancholic expression
Oppa looks better
without your glasses on.
Really?
A mission that'll
upset the audience
How can you hide your handsome
face behind those glasses?
Should I wear contact lenses in future?
Can they really change their sweaters
while re-enacting this scene?
Yes.
Oppa, you'll be even more popular then.
Shocked
Jaesuk's deep gaze
Startled
Holding in
his laughter
Minjong hyung's eyes are really deep.
I ﻿will try my best to
show a gaze like yours.
Big nose glasses?
Re-enactment of <Feelings> starts
... but can't do it
Really, why are you still
not getting into the act?
The female lead Jihyo
can't get into the act
Jihyo, you must not laugh.
The difficult part for Jihyo is
not being allowed to laugh
Are you ready? We're starting.
Ready ...
Holding back
her laughter
... action.
Who are you?
Oppa ...
I have a favor to ask.
Keeping quiet
Turns~
Puft~
You can't laugh.
I can't help it.
Pure Minjong is also dying laughing
Director you can't laugh.
They are acting very seriously.
Even if it's hard to watch,
you have to do it seriously
Oh...
Minjong turned around?
Huk!
These four people
have already changed their sweaters
Did Minjong see through it?
Totally
didn't realize
It's you who didn't act well.
Your laughter was the loudest.
There's no other reason ...
I just want to act out
Minjong's deep gaze.
I got it, I'm sorry.
Ready ... action.
Ready
Action
Oppa, I have a favor to ask.
Deep gaze
* BGM = "Sincere Love" by Kim Minjong
Big Burden
But if I take them off, I won't
be able to see anything.
Huh?
She didn't ask him to take off his glasses?
If I take them off, I won't
be able to see anything.
Daeng
Criticism from all sides
But we haven't reached that line yet.
Sorry Jihyo.
I only remembered my own lines.
Because of you, this
segment is destroyed.
Go ~
Jihyo and Jaesuk
failed their attempts
Is "The Blue" the next?
Then we need to change our outfit.
Ah that's right, we need to be ...
... dancers.
Modified strategy?
Suddenly becoming dancers
Jaesuk Jihyo
Dancers?
Fighting.
Should we change our
clothes to a different color?
Why is he saying
such a thing?
Just go out like that will do.
What is this...?
What's this?
Highest point of absurdness
The profound skinny fashion
What's this?
It's too skimpy.
You can't be like this.
Hurry up and wear this..
Why?
Excessive act?
Is it the plan...
or reality?
Please wear it quickly.
The best
operation?
I beg you.
Okay ~
Pure Minjong
with a kind smile
It's better if you wear it.
Pure Minjong is absorbed in the operation
Like this
Also
Jaesuk
succeeds
Yes, better
wearing it
Kim Minjong's immortal masterpieces
Lee Kwangsoo
(as Kim Minjong)
Feeling
Only You
Ji Sukjin
(as Son Jichang)
Continuing with Sukjin and Kwangsoo's
<The Blue>
challenge
Change places.
Move back.
Over!
Mission begins?
Taking off clothes while turning
Take it off.
Whispers
Why are they
all taking their
clothes off?
To divert Minjong's attention
the dancers move forward
Jihyo, lift your legs higher.
In the end got it wrong
Still
Ding dong daeng
You're too generous,
it is so easy to pass.
Thank you.
Because I saw how Sukjin
was acting with a hard time.
Huk!
Big Nose positions to take off his sweater
Why are you suddenly
taking off your clothes?
Of course
Imposing awkward acting again?
Regardless, it's a pass.
Am I too generous?
It was easy.
Whose turn is it next?
Meanwhile Jihyo quickly changes her sweater
It's the last scene already.
Last scene.
People that haven't succeeded yet
Sukjin
Joongki
Kwang
soo
Siwon
There's no time
Actors are you ready?
Doesn't have anything under his sweater
Kwangsoo How embarrassing
Are your emotions ready?
Yes.
We are acting as gangsters.
Get into the act well.
Hello ...
Big Nose is frustrated and
fiercely takes off Kwangsoo's sweater
Minjong can't see what's behind
His attention is on the team mates
Pure Minjong only looks in front
In no time
Kwangsoo
succeeds
Minjong's immortal masterpiece
Gary
(as gangster 1)
Kim Jongkook
(as gangster 2)
You know
it's a secret
Song Joongki
(as Kim Minjong)
Song Jihyo
(as Ha Heera)
Ready ... action
Last enactment
<You know, it's a secret>
Oh, how blinding ...
Real(?) evil act
Dazzling beautiful lady,
where're you going?
Don't you dare to touch me.
Come play with us.
Don't touch me.
There's a saying that "touching
shoulders" is a form of fate.
I touched it already.
I touched it.
Wants to touch it himself and
using passing by as an excuse
Interesting
What should I do?
Come play with us.
Hyung ...
... what do you think
about this chick?
Joongki who's casted as Minjong appears
Situation getting more interesting
Who are you?
What are you?
Big Nose is also swift
Don't bother her anymore, just let her go.
Pure Minjong is fully immersed in their acting
Perhaps this?...
Minjong impressed with the impromptu act
What are you doing now?
Do you want to be like him too?
What exactly do you want?
Where did you come from?
Let her go.
Okay I will first release her.
You tell me what do we do about
the touched shoulders fate?
Just like after drinking
Realistic evil acting
@#$/oA... seum dwa.
* He's speaking gibberish
Joongki said you talk too much.
This again?
Fireworks-like impromptu acting
Are you okay?
Quietly making an ending
I'm okay.
But when is he going to change his sweater?
Thank you Joongki.
I see you in a different light now.
We are ...
Monday Boyfriend disrupts her acting
Let's start all over again.
Are you talking about dating?
Yes.
To commemorate our new beginning,
let us wear a couple-T together.
* Couple-T = Couple T-shirt
Good operation
Immersed
I'm envious
Once we wear the couple-T's ...
When Joongki puts it on ...
only Siwon is left to wear it
... are we dating?
Once we have worn it, we are dating
The lovers act as natural
as drinking water
This fake drama
whose opponent is innocent Minjong
Joongki
Succeeds
Daeng
Not satisfied with the lovers act?
I thought there would be
something for the ending.
Certainly the ending was a little ...
They acted very seriously.
There was a little something.
What about it?
Ha ha
Changing clothes
was a success
I don't know about this ...
What is this?
Fake mission
Minjong's
<Classic titles>
Everybody please move to the center.
Finished
That's really a pity.
What a pity.
Who gets the Running ball?
Acting
At least we all changed
our clothes already.
How about Running ball?
HaHa and Jongkook's team didn't pass.
You think you'll get our share?
Yes ~
Siwon ...
Yes?
... are you done changing?
It's so hot.
Siwon's shirt is inside?
What is this?
It's a green bag sweater
Didn't you feel anything?
Don't you find our acting weird?
Still doesn't understand the situation
Pure Minjong
What is this?
That's ...
Minjong only starts to understand now?
What exactly is this?
We changed our clothes, right?
We all changed our clothes, so we won.
What is this?
Now we'll get our Running
Balls, except Minjong.
Except Kim Minjong
they all get a Running Ball
To HaHa ...
To Gary ...
Burning
Sukjin ...
How can there be such a thing.
Didn't you feel anything
weird in the middle?
Totally nothing.
Pure and innocent Minjong
Ah, really ...
Sorry hyung
First mission 1:10, Running Man wins.
I came wanting to get a Running Ball.
Loyal viewer
Ah, really?
Yes, Running Ball.
My entertainment senses decreased.
My mistake
It's alright
There's still a chance
Uncomfortable
There's an activity.
Currently, only Kim Minjong
doesn't have a Running Ball.
Chasing
Team
Santa outfit
Minjong
Jaesuk
Gary
HaHa
Siwon
Anyway ...
I will treat you very well.
When Jongkook appears on TV ...
Loyal viewer Siwon
Deeply impressed when Jongkook appears
... there's a tiger-like roar "Sparta!".
Jongkook's appearance sound effect
Sparta!
Minjong's appearance sound effect could be ...
... ♪ It's you ♪
Minjong's song
'Sincere love' from 1998
♪ It's you ♪
I haven't worn clothes like this in a long time.
Exquisite
Pajama wearing
Mission
Team
Today's main focus is the socks.
Like sleeping kids Get eliminated
if the socks get taken off
We have protect our socks.
The message is here ~
Find the 4 hidden Running Man
Christmas ﻿decorations ...
... and complete the Christmas tree.
Mission
Team's
instruction
Find 4 Running Man decorations
and complete the Christmas tree
Christmas
a child's dream
Let's go ~
A the empty shopping mall
playing bells hide-n-seek
The mission ...
Quickly splitting up
Mission
Team
Sukjin Jongkook Kwangsoo
Goes to basement toy store
Jihyo Joongki Lizzy
Goes to 1st floor food store
No matter where the sound is shocking
Santa
Chasing
Team
Arrives on
the 1st floor
Siwon and Minjong head to the 2nd floor.
Siwon and I ...
We'll search the 1st floor first.
I think Jongkook is eating chicken
breast meat over there right now.
At the glasses department ...
Athena Team
Pinpoint locations like in a drama
... nothing unusual for now.
Wait for us
Mission Team
We will catch
all of you...!
How do I adjust the sound on this thing?
Already chasing Joongki on the 1st floor
Immediately Joongki has an elimination crisis
Yooruce and the 2 kids skillfully catch Joongki
♪ It's you ♪
Minjong
Slightly late Minjong
I'll tell you where Jongkook is.
Say it ...
Where?
Disclosing Commanders position Will it get him free?
Where is Jongkook?
Jongkook will be walking
around at the basement.
Okay, we got it.
No, but I told you.
♪ It's you ♪ Minjong
Still taking Joongki's sock
I really need a
Running Ball
♪ It's you ♪ Minjong
Coolly ﻿takes off Joongki's sock
Joongki ...
Everyone else was letting Joongki go
We were going to let you go, but ...
... Minjong took your sock off.
♪ It's you ♪ Minjong
Made Joongki OUT even after getting information
Collapse
We wanted to free you but ...
... Minjong thought otherwise.
I'm going to be killed by Jongkook.
Minjong hyung's really calm.
Mission
Team
Joongki
Time left
Basement toy store
Sukjin Jongkook Kwangsoo
Looks like there's one here.
Running Man tree decoration
1 out of 4
Running Man decoration
Found
However bell sounds coming closer
Running Man mania
Prince
Siwon enters
Deeply engrossed in the fun hide-n-seek
No matter
how spacious it's here
His gaze
No one can hide from it
Of all guests
He knows Running Man the most
His existence alone
makes Mission Team nervous
Of course
Attacking upon hearing voices
Gary's chasing Jongkook & Kwangsoo
Gary
captures Kwangsoo
Success
Siwon ~
Jongkook ~
Jongkook escapes
At last Prince Siwon arrives
To the point
Quickly takes Kwangsoo's sock
I know where Jongkook is.
Everyone who's caught uses Jongkook's position as a trade for freedom
Siwon isn't interested in such deals
Athena
Worthy NTS elite member
Prince
Siwon
Good job.
And then late again
♪ It's you ♪
Minjong
Hyung why are you always
slower than us by one step?
Cough cough...
I can't see anything.
Kwang
soo
The boy whose
socks got taken off
is asleep on the bed
On Christmas Eve
there's no sad souls around
Everyone on earth is having
blissful dreams of Santa
...Huh?
Santa intrudes?
Tok
nightmare
Christmas
Peach.
Santa doesn't exist.
Santa grandpa is right behind you.
No matter what
Merry Christmas ~
Meanwhile
Searching the 2nd floor
Jihyo Lizzy
Right before their
eyes
Beautiful items that
make hearts beat faster
Christmas and
an empty store
Girls' romantic getaway
Jihyo tries the latest skateboard model
Teenage Lizzy looks at pretty children clothes
But out of nowhere
came sound of bells
Close!!
Prince
Siwon
Suddenly comes~!
Ace Jihyo got caught
I caught Song Jihyo, 2nd floor.
Oppa, help me please.
Oppa has arrived.
Oppa arrived
Jihyo ...
Wanted Jongkook oppa Why this oppa?
You worked hard.
It's Lizzy, wait ...
Yooruce Willis
found the hiding Lizzy~
The two women were alone.
If it's done right it's possible to catch 2 girls
Evil Jihyo descends
Quickly get away.
Yooruce Willis
bravely hangs onto Jihyo
Where are you going.
Poke
To Jihyo Yooruce Willis is just ...
Come to the 2nd floor.
Totally suppressed
Meanwhile Siwon catches Lizzy
Lizzy
Jihyo escapes towards the basement
Leisurely
I just checked here not long ago.
Seems like HaHa is close by
I checked this area not long ago.
Heading towards Jihyo
I've just checked this area.
Discovers Jihyo
Is she still in Evil Jihyo mode?
My stomach's still not feeling well.
Not looking good after stomachache
HaHa
Right, lend me the walkie-talkie.
What do you want the talkie for?
You run away, it's better.
I'm tired
Not feeling well...
and afraid of Jihyo
You're a ghost, so I can't see you.
It's a fact that ...
.... there's nobody here right?
Innocent
Looking
I don't think there's anything over here
HaHa
can't see Jihyo
If it was me, I wouldn't hide here either.
Thanks.
Anyway
Also in the electronics store there's bell sounds
HaHa
discovers Jihyo again
Aish, where are they?
Just
Swo~sh
Aish, where are they?
Ha
ha
Now at ease to run to the toy store
Again
HaHa
Pretending not to see again?
Do you know where Jihyo is?
Huk!
Yooruce Willis is nearby...?
Looks at her
Awkward
There's nothing at all.
HaHa extremely awkward
Now say
you can't see...
Jihyo, I didn't say anything.
HaHa is definitely acting weird
It's possible to get rid of them and escape
♪ It's you ♪
Minjong
As usual
He's one step behind
Hyung ...
The calm person is here.
The
cold
blooded(?)
Three men surround Jihyo
Evil~
Ah, Jihyo wait ...
Separate your legs.
Fidget
Jihyo, why are you doing this?
Panicking because of Bad Jihyo's resistance
Song Jihyo ...
Why are you like this?
Ah Song Jihyo, you're really ...
Ev~il!
Forcefully got
Jihyo's sock
Jihyo
Remaining time
Siwon, where are you?
He's here pursuing ...
the sounds on the upper level
Isn't the walkie-talkie working?
Why isn't Siwon answering, this kid.
Frustrated
Because it's not
the time for leisurely answers
Sukjin
Their strongest
hide-n-seek guest
Prince
Siwon
You sit down first sit down ...
Out of 4
finally found a decoration
The stockings on that side
are all black, just one is red.
Seem's like there's
a tree decoration just beside the jail...!
Telling it to the Commander
2 out of 4
Tree decoration
Found
That kid runs really fast.
The Commander is their only hope
I thought that kid was a machine.
Instead of rice, does
he just eat gasoline?
Clang
Hey you ...
Jaesuk ...
Yooruce Willis
Hanging onto the strength of the bells
What?
Just one left to catch?
That's right.
Yah, you've changed.
Why?
About this time you're
usually already in jail.
Sukjin Kwangsoo Jaesuk
are usually the first ones in jail
What?
Aren't you being too much like this.
Sukjin Kwangsoo
Feeling betrayed
Do you know how long
we waited for you?
Hurry up and sit down.
You come over.
Arrogant
Come in hyung.
That fellow, Mr. Yoo.
What Mr. Yoo?
Sit down.
Forgive~
Forgive everything since it's Christmas
HaHa quietly joined in
The jail that became one body
because of Christmas carols~
Oppa, it's not right
for you to do this.
Is something wrong with your senses.
Trying to make Yooruce Willis come back
This team isn't fooling around.
The miracle of Christmas?
Both teams singing together
Merry Christmas
What're we going to do after this?
Ah, hyung ...
You know it right?
Is HaHa on the Mission Team now?
Three decorations remain
Meanwhile
♪ It's you ♪
Minjong
Running
Keeps running while looking everywhere
But not once has he found someone
Stamina used up
Jaesuk ...
I'm going to die of exhaustion.
That's the only way to get a Running Ball.
Only survivor Commander
Mission
Team's
3 out of 4
Running Man decorations
Found
The Commander has two
If he can find one more!
Like the quietness before a storm
Ring
Where's the sound coming from?
♪ It's you ♪
Minjong
Ya, he's here.
First time finding Mission Team
2nd level, hurry ...
His first find is
Commander
Jongkook
2nd level, hurry ...
Prince
Siwon is holding his position
The whole Chasing Team is attacking
Amidst all this ...
Finally all four
tree decorations
Found
Really good~~Brilliant...
He is here.
All decorations found
Need to hang them on the tree for
Victory
But Chasing Team's catching up
Be careful.
They're all found ~
Let's sing a song.
As expected
Christmas carols for stabilization
Please...
Everyone is hoping for
a Christmas miracle
But a miracle
isn't given just like that
Hopefully praying
Can the wish for victory come true?
But...
♪ It's you ♪
Minjong wishing even stronger
Miracle
♪ It's you ♪
Minjong caught the Commander
All members of Chasing Team pounce
Puts Commander in headlock
♪ It's you ♪
Minjong
Ah, the strength of his leg.
Ah, wait awhile.
Hurry up.
Finally they got Commander's sock
Mission
Team
Everyone OUT
Chasing
Team
Wins
Hard-earned Christmas emotions
Finally...
The long-awaited
Running Ball he'd hoped for
Now Minjong is smiling.
Result of drawing balls
Sukjin Kwangsoo Jihyo Lizzy
get punished
On a freezing day
Bare legs like this
Today's
punishment
Wearing hot pants and
Give out gifts at the train station
How do you do?
Oh my god
This is a Christmas present.
Wishing everyone
a happy and blessed Christmas