Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by iSUBS
Today's
landmark
Where Seoul Design Fair is held
Worldwide designs have all came here
to be part of the exhibit
Here comes Running Man
Extraordinary event
The brain Joongki gets deceived
Can the Running Man members
deceive Joongki til the end?
In the midst of pelting raindrops
They must dismantle a bomb
Action version
Running Man
Starts now
1 hour
before recording...
Today is Joongki's birthday.
Seoul Design Fair
Somewhere near Olympic Stadium
Really?
Ah, that's right ~
Today is Joongki's birthday, right?
Hello hyung ~
Jongkook is the last to stand up.
Nagging
Hyung, don't you have a lot to say?
Holding a grudge
Whats there to talk about?
What?
Acts dumb
Rock, paper, scissors?
Oh, seriously.
If it's 'Rock Paper Scissors'
Rock, paper, scissors ~
During last week's filming
Scissors
Rock
I won.
I didn't show scissors.
I showed rock and
you showed scissors.
I was clearly paper.
Can't you remember?
The most immature debate
in the history of variety
Rewind, show us the tape.
Seriously, you two ... ?
If it shows that I won when this
is aired, then you're done for.
I'm being serious.
Does it hurt?
I was just saying my opinion.
Shy...
What kind of opinion ?
It was Jongkook who won
Exactly.
I bet you're acting like ﻿this because
you really thought you did win.
I really thought I've won.
Stubborn 40 year old man
Seriously, you drive me crazy.
What are we gonna do?
Because Joongki wasn't here last week ...
... we've decided to trick Joongki for once.
We re going to do a 1 against 7 battle.
Running Ball battle
Showdown
There'll be balls as reward?
Yes and Joongki has already arrived.
Right now he's somewhere
else, getting a fake interview.
Then he'll be over here.
An interview that will never air?
We're secretly tricking him.
Really?
How seriously will he take it?
Joongki probably takes
the interview very serious.
Can you tell us about the playboy character ...
As predicted
The interview
was done seriously
... that you are portraying ﻿in the drama.
Yes, nice to meet you too.
Let's start with a greeting to our audience.
Running Man crew that
Joongki haven't met before
Yes ...
Couldn't imagine it was a fake interview
giving all his efforts
Midnight Interview watchers, hello.
* There's a segment on SBS Daily News that's called Midnight Interview
This is my first time greeting you
on this TV show, nice to meet you.
Let me explain the plan.
Meanwhile
The rest of the members...
After the interview ends ...
... the first game will ﻿be something
called "Running Man Q&A".
Fake segment
Running Man Q&A
And so?
Normally Joongki's image is being
someone with high intelligence.
Publicly acknowledged
Running Man's brain
Joongki
Joongki has been in a intelligence show,
representing Korea and getting 2nd place.
Before Joongki debuted
Successfully participated in a Q&A show
Seriously?
I choose Indus civilizations.
The answer is correct.
Joongki can now successfully
advance into the 3rd round.
Joongki
Enters 3rd round
Q&A shows have a standard format, right?
A million agreements on the
intelligent
Joongki
That's why the format is going to be 7 versus 1.
If you win the game, then
you will get a Running Ball.
If Song Joongki gets the answer right,
the Running Ball goes to him instead.
It's impossible for him to lose.
Flaw
Joongki is super smart, but
the others are much weaker
Look at us, all of us here.
That is why we already have ...
... prepared the questions for you.
Advance
preparation
Before the game
the questions are given to the others
We still won't know the answers.
Hopeless
We can't show you everything.
But we'll ask questions within this criteria.
If everyone can get these
questions correct and ...
... get ﻿away with this, then
the plan will be a success.
We get a chance to learn something new.
Flaw
These seven people haven't
studied anything in a long time
This is my first time studying in 10 years.
Yah, isn't this too much?
I'll try to test you.
First
Looking at the 'predicted questions'
This noun refers to a temporary structure
housing a public event or exhibition and ...
... at the same time used to mean the large tent
used ﻿for events like outdoor or sporting activities.
It also refers to 'a mobile mini-structure'.
The origin of this noun is
the Latin word for 'tent'.
This word is ... ?
Shocked~
"﻿Partition".
Like what it said
Wrong.
"Container"?
Mentioned before
Flaw
They have a abnormal and
huge lack of common sense
What container are you talking about?
Seriously, you guys are to naive.
Sports events in a container?
Pavilion, how can we know that?
But even If we did get it right,
won't Joongki be suspicious?
Worried
If we casually answer 'Pygmalion', like that.
Flaw
If they answer the questions
too easy, suspicions will arise
If they do that suspicions will be at 100%
The Latin word origin of tent is ...
It's too suspicious.
It will definitely be seen through.
The first question will
be about the pavilion.
After Jaesuk gets it right, then
you'll come out to be the host.
For it to run smoothly
First question will be answered by Jaesuk
Ah okay, I understand
It's pavilion, hyung.
Emphasizes
Pavilion.
If you say something else, it would be weird.
Do you think I can't remember?﻿ Pavilion.
Reinforcing the answer
I think Sukjin will get the 1st question right.
Suspicious
He'll be out  before Jaesuk.
Flaw
Temptation to answer
the question to quick
"Pavilion".
Ah, this guy ...
Then he should be the host.
Checking the
answer again
First, let's split up the topics.
Short-term strategy
Split up to study different areas
Divide the questions, one by one.
They must make Joongki lose
I'll remember the first question.
Donghoon, except for pavilion,
you have to remember 4 more.
HaHa's strategy is
cheating?
Except for pavilion, there's still others.
Huh?
Jihyo as well?
Want to be a cheater?
Yeah...
Jiho, frankly, many people have
asked if you really like to scold people.
No.1 keyword search
Talk of the town
Song JiYok
* Yok = To curse or scold
How can that be?
There's already a rumor like that.
Framer Kwangsoo
In the past, there was a rumor that
she tried to get a tougher image ...
Framed
... by having a beard.
Latest gossip
Jihyo with beard?
Jihyo...
I couldn't protect you
This is very important ...
If Joongki gets one question right ...
If Joongki gets one question right
he alone claims victory
... then we're doomed.
Let me tell you how to you can win.
Those who answered a question
correctly can pass the game.
You only need to get 1 question
correct then you have passed?
But this can be a problem.
We have 4 questions each.
If I'm already out and one
of my questions comes ...
... you'll be in trouble.
Oh, that's true.
Of course.
Ah seriously, how much time does
this thing waste, Jongkook ah ...
The more they think
the more complicated it gets
It isn't that bad, who knows.
We're only memorizing 4 questions each.
Within this chaos...
Hurry, Joongki's interview ends soon.
Joongki's
interview has ended
With only one strategy left
I'll do question 2.
Butterflies
in
the
stomach
Hopefully we'll have fun recording in the future.
At that time The interview ended
And I ask all of the 'Midnight Interview'
audience to cheer us on, fighting.
Who'll be the 1:7 showdown winner?
Open
ceremony
is drawing
near
Pellets of rain shower the
colossal Olympic Stadium
Ah, this place ...
Today Running Man's destination is...
The Seoul Design Fair
This is the 'Seoul Design Fair.
Hosted in Seoul
Worldwide celebratory event of design
Filled with beautifully crafted artworks
Today this is their stage
Running Man runs through the night
So this is the 'Seoul Design Fair'.
23 countries and
The stadium has already been
furnished into a fair exhibit.
200 designers participate
There's about 23 countries joining
this festive ceremony and ...
... ﻿200 designers participating in this
internationally recognized designing fair.
Last year there were
3 million who witnessed this event
Not only Seoul joined, but last year there were
about ﻿3 million people who came to participate.
Joongki, we haven't seen you in a long time.
Isn't your drama a big hit?
Pure
Naive
Because Joongki is now filming
a drama, he's quite amazing.
Because I've always came once every
two weeks, I have been dying to run.
If he only knew what's going to happen
Pureness
So film your drama,
your television drama.
Same situation different thoughts
The audience's reaction was really enthusiastic.
I'll do my best.
Yeah, us too
Let's change our place to over there.
Then we'll start, lets go.
This is my first time standing
on a grass paved stadium.
Can we walk on the grass?
An evening
with autumn rain
It's a bit moist.
Only Joongki is unaware of the plot
A nerve-wrecking game
of Q&A starts now
Current time
Joongki might not be clear about this game.
We have ﻿the changed game
format into individual battles.
Since last week
Now there's individual battles on the show
You've heard heard about it?
Yes, I've heard.
Earlier the balls were distributed
to the to red or blue team.
In every game you can
a ball with your name.
Collect Running balls
by winning different games
If it doesn't come out in the end it
has nothing to do with your team.
If it's a ball with your name
you avoid punishment
You have to accept the punishment.
I got it.
Aisssh, this is seriously ...
I don't know if it'll work or not, this.
(Tricking Joongki)
I don't know it'll work
Exactly.
Eh?
Sgussh
What's the first thing we shall do?
We're gonna have a 'Design Q&A' game.
Questions and answers?
You just need to be able to answer
the questions related to design.
We're not familiar with design at all.
All together
Acting ignorant
How would we know anything?
Deceiving Joongki
They've already memorized the answers
Answer before Joongki and win
battle
How?
You only need to answer 1 question, then
you've successfully passed the game.
Acting shocked with all their efforts
Only the last one won't get a Running ball.
Just don't be last, don't be the remaining one
This is a must-win.
Since we have Gary and HaHa
here, I don't think I'll be last.
I think that Joongki is very
good at these Q&A games.
Pretending
Why?
I've seen the TV show.
He's been on 'Korea's Q&A'
show and won 2nd place.
Embarrassed
In 2006 University Year 1
Brilliantly performed in <Korea's Q&A>
Was that you?
Exaggeration
It was "Q&A Korea"?
Oh, that good looking guy was ...
You're too noisy.
You're way
too obvious
Scolded again
Alright, this is the first question.
What is a temporary, free-standing used at
a public event, such as fairs and sports events?
It's also used outdoors and
at sport events as well.
Answer, Sukjin.
Huh...?
I was supposed to
answer the first question
I think Sukjin Hyung will
answer the first question.
At the strategy meeting
He'll pass the game before Jaesuk.
"Pavilion" ~
Correct
He'll be able to host by doing that.
Surely not...
Answer, Sukjin.
a betrayal
Does Sukjin really want to
answer correct and be the MC?
Tent.
Deng
Phew...
Suspecting a 20 year old
friendship during that moment
If it has to do with designing ...
... can it be Model House?
Naive
The tent used for such event...
... it's a noun used to describe
a small mobile structure.
HaHa ~
You...
What's it again...?
Pa ...
It was
your words
If betrayal happens, what do we do?
That can be me as well.
A soon as it starts ... pavilion!
Pavilion
Betrayal
Pa ...
was something
that HaHa has mentioned before
Pa ...
Pa
... tition.
rtition
Partition?
The naive Joongki
How could it be partition?
It isn't right?
Life shortened
by 10 years
The word comes from a Latin origin.
Latin ~
It means tent and
has a Latin origin
It's Latin?
It's so hard.
Yes, Latin.
This is too hard.
Kang Gary ~
Container
All kinds of answers
This standard is something
that Joongki can't imagine
Container, what kind of Latin word is that?
Latin?
Seriously.
Isn't there a hint?
What letter does it start with?
It has already been mentioned.
Already mentioned?
Pa ~
Jaesuk ...
Pa...vilion?
Answering pavilion confidently is a risky.
We must think it through carefully.
Just raise the final syllable .
Pavilion?
Don't tell me
Pa..vilion?
Correct as planned
First to answer correctly
escapes
Wow~
How did you know?
It's correct
Ow~
I was right.
It's really correct?
Pavilion ... ah.
It was right?
It's awkward
Really?
Yeah,
awkward
Pavilion is the Latin word for tent.
I suddenly thought of the newspaper.
Currently filming at a
pavilion built on the sports complex
I've seen the word on the newspaper before
There was a hint.
I was wondering if it was
possible, so I just said it.
But anyway that means
that I have succeeded.
The first
Jaesuk
Success
Running Ball.
Finally
6 more people need to
succeed to get the balls
This is so ridiculous.
Next ...
Yeah?
... move towards this side.
Answer the first question correct
has to continue as MC
Yes.
Decide on the next question.
So I get to choose the question?
Jaesuk got the answer right?
To avoid suspicions
the others are pretending
You knew the answer long ago, didn't you?
No one knew and yet you knew
No, I saw it on the newspaper.
Yah, how can it be like that?
What is the difficulty
level of the questions?
They are all logic questions.
What logic?
Burst of unhappiness
What logical questions?
Only Joongki doesn't know
It's too difficult.
Everyone has been very cooperative
I managed to guess it correctly.
I ﻿have never heard of the
word "pavilion" until today.
I've never heard it before.
If you told me it's a type of
food, I would've believed it.
Okay ...
... the next question.
He is the designer of one of
the architectural exhibits here.
He designed the newest addition to the scene
of the 911 terrorism attacks, Ground Zero.
I know this.
He revamped the entire
plan of World Trade Center.
Hold on ~
Wow, this is too difficult.
The name of the main architect?
Wait, I saw it in the news.
Seen the news?
If Joongki answers correctly
it will end the 1:7 battle
I saw it in the newspapers.
Answer ... HaHa.
Anxiety
HaHa.
Steven Jobs.
Calling out a
random name
Deng
Steve Jobs
is the CEO of Apple
It's not Steven, it's Steve Jobs.
The name is long, right?
Yes.
Jongkook.
Give me a sec.
Recalling the name
Daniel Libeskind.
Correct answer is
Daniel Libeskind
Although
the answer is discussed
Daniel.
Daniel is correct.
Daniel is correct, right?
How did you know that?
Wow~
I heard of the name Daniel
Daniel Lie ...
Hint
Lie ... ?
Sukjin ~
How would I know the
name of the architect ...
... ﻿who rebuilt the World Trade Center?
Remembers because it was so ridiculous
Daniel Libeskind.
Daniel Nicholas.
Deng
It start's with Li, not Ni.
What? Is
it wrong?
Answer.
Daniel Libes ...
Libes ~
Time's up.
Answer
Time's up
Deng
Libes... is correct.
Answer ~
It's Daniel Libeskind.
Libeskind ...
... is correct.
Correct
Totally surprised
How did you?
I just knew this.
When I went there ...
I've been there before,
in front of Ground Zero.
It's the first time I hear this.
Ground Zero
Term used for the of collapsed WTC
building due to the event 9.11.2001
I only know it's not totally zero.
Jongkook please get to the back.
Jongkook 2nd member to escape
Now, we're left with only six people.
Joongki really doesn't know about the quiz.
It's too difficult.
This question has something
to do with designing ...
... so it is not difficult.
Because of that, questions
regarding designing aren't hard.
Everyone should be brave to answer.
To facilitate the atmosphere
everyone should shout their name loudly
HaHa.
Gary.
There's only one for Joongki
Joongki.
Although we are sorry
everyone should answer before Joongki
Jihyo.
Sukjin.
Kwangsoo.
Let's do it backwards.
Again
Kwangsoo.
Sukjin.
Jihyo.
Joongki.
Gary.
HaHa.
Thank you.
Sukjin, Nose King.
The King of Lies is more like it.
Still holding a grudge
because of the scissor-stone-paper incident
The very popular comic, Ninja Turtle.
The main characters have artists' names.
That's right ~
Ah?
Joongki
seems to know the answer...!?
Joongki might get
the answer right this time
We must answer the questions
that Joongki will know quicker.
That's right.
HaHa ... Raphaelo.
No, it isn't.
Leonardo ...
DiCaprio.
Giving a
random answer
No, it isn't.
Michelangelo.
Correct
Donatello
Raphael, Michaelangelo, Leonardo,
the name of the 4th character is?
Sukjin ~
Smack
Bad
luck
Are you okay?
Why did you put
your face so close.
Sukjin?
Do...
3, 2, 1.
Dolatalo?
It's wrong.
Answer
HaHa.
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
Looks
Doriet.
It isn't.
Leonardo, Raphael, Michelangelo ...
One more name to get it right
There's one more, but I just can't recall.
There's even a song for it.
Donatello
What?
Okay ...
... the first syllable is Do.
Kang Gary ~
Donatello.
Donatello?
Kang Gary, how did you know.
I'm Kang Gary, that's why.
Kang Gary
How did you know the name?
Donatello, Nichelangelo ...
My family ~
Gary's family are turtles
What?
All my family.
No.
Nervous to the point of rapping in different languages
Wait, I was so surprised.
Acting as if he's surprised
But it's correct.
You don't know Michelangelo
but you know N ichelangelo.
Of course it's Leonardo
Interesting
What kind of person is Donatello?
Straightforward
Isn't he just one of the four?
No, it's a name of an artist?
Holding twin sai-daggers.
* Daggers with 3 prongs
Donatello ~
The daggers, I remember.
Actually
Raphael is the one using daggers
and Donatello is the one with a Bo-staff
No not that, what does
the artist Donatello do?
Sculptor
Isn't he a sculptor?
Acting
Yes, how did you know?
Donatello ~
Embarrassing performance but still a rap
Gary is
too funny
Gary really surprised me.
Correct answer.
Gary's the 3rd to answer correctly
It's really too surprising.
Gary is already out ...
... so now there's danger.
Joongki must now pull up his socks.
Not safe
This is ridiculous.
Joongki would think it's too weird ...
... especially if HaHa ﻿and
Gary answer correctly.
He'll think that's really weird.
Why do you think that?
Gary is unhappy
with the truth
You have nothing else to say, right?
It is so unbelievable that
Gary got the answer right.
I was also shocked.
You actually got Donatello correct.
Donatello ~
Joongki, sorry
Okay ...
... next question.
Based on the idea of combining
design and economics ...
... what so you call the strategy used to
further the economic influence of design?
What is this?
A design is a design.
The business major Joongki
Use the English word for economics.
Hint
Joongki ~
Desi...
The correct answer is
Design and Economics
Desinomics.
Design + Economics = Designomics
Will Joongki win
against 7 opponents?
Desinomics.
It's not desinomics.
It is close, but it's wrong.
Phew
Sukjin ~
Designmics.
Deng
It isn't designmics.
HaHa is cheating
Designomics?
HaHa ~
Designermics.
It's not designermics.
The answer is designomics
Then what exactly is it?
Memorizing in the last minute
makes them confuse
5 ...
Sukjin, designeconomics.
It isn't designeconomics.
Deng
HaHa, designomics.
Designo ...
... mics
Designomics.
Designomics?
Is it Designo-mics or Desig-nomics?
What's this?
This old man
wants a beating
Revenging
Don't you already
do that just now...
Designo-mics.
At this moment
Song Jihyo ~
Desig-nomics.
Don't be funny and
repeat what I said.
Why?
Not losing to you
Jihyo also wants to live.
Jihyo is normally nice
but plays dirty to get out
The stress from getting closer to the answer
Joongki's oblivious to what's happening
Why?
Okay ..
Haha, design...
...nomics.
Interrupting halfway
Designomics
Correct ~
HaHa is the 4th to answer correctly
Such a waste
Was it designomics?
Designomics.
Our Joongki ...
Such a pity.
Joongki who answered designomics  first
Joongki basically got it correct.
Truthfully it was because of
Joongki that he got it correct.
was taken by HaHa
Joongki's answer
Joongki got it correct.
HaHa didn't get it right
because he knew the answer.
Jihyo, I'm a little disappointed In you
Embarrassed
Now we're left with 4 people.
4 people are left
3 more quiz questions
To win over Joongki
the other 3 have to get it right
Joongki, honestly ...
Who do you think will be
the last one in this Quiz?
Looks like it will be me.
You think so?
Yes.
What does Jihyo think?
You ~
Looks like it will be me.
Me too.
I think it will Joongki.
As long as
3 more people succeed
The next question ...
This means ...
... how others treat me.
Excuse me, if you keep doing that ...
... I'm not able to tell you the answers.
Lying Big Nose who does small actions
just to get the answer
You can't keep doing that.
During that time, my image
is to be very clever.
Original clever image is now
a total mess
I'm afraid my son gets disappointed.
You're son might get disappointed.
My child will be disappointed.
Here's the hint ...
Someone respects me and
has high expectations of me.
I change myself and work hard to avoid
disappointing ﻿other's expectation of me.
Because of expectations or concern ...
... efficacy increases and the ﻿
result changes for the better.
What is the name of this effect?
Kwangsoo ...
Stuttering and can't really remember
I know ...
5, 4 ...
Py...
Wrong.
Sukjin ...
What is the Pygmalion effect?
The Pygmalion effect is ...
... becoming ﻿more hardworking
due to high expectations.
Jaesuk completely understands
the Pygmalion effect
Have to be careful later.
Sukjin ...
Pydmalion?
Deng
No.
Kwangsoo ...
Pygmalion.
The right answer is Pymalion effect
This one I know, Song Joongki.
Pygmalion effect.
Huh
Correct answer...!
Pygmalion effect.
If Joongki manages to guess it ...
... then it will be over.
If Joongki gets it correct ...
... Joongki will win the 1:7 battle
Biggest
crisis
Just like that...?
I haven't finished answering though.
Hurrying
to change
Pygmalion ...
... effect?
Pygmalion effect?
Serious...
Pygmalion effect.
He hadn't finished saying it.
Joongki, he hadn't finished answering yet.
Pygmalion effect, correct answer.
Correct answer.
Kwangsoo's dramatic escape
Basically guessed it correctly.
Nothing to say
Kwangsoo, how did you know that?
Normally... this...
Stuttering
Do you mind explaining
the Pygmalion effect again?
Pygmalion...
Normally, I'm concerned
about this kind of things.
Oh, is that so?
Please explain what it means.
Stubborn Jaesuk attacks with questions
I heard a lot of this mentioned ...
Talk about
this and that
... this Pygmalion effect.
You did a good job.
Ah, really irritating.
Ah, Gary ...
Earlier what was your correct answer?
What was the answer that
you answered correctly?
Donatella.
Donatella ?
Donataylu ?
Donatello ~
What does he do?
Sculptor.
Michelangelo.
Doesn't know anything
Joongki only finds this funny
HaHa, what was your correct answer?
What was your correct answer?
Just get it
over with
Designorimics.
Forgot completely
after it ended
Such interesting friends.
Joongkook, what was your correct answer?
What was your correct answer?
Don't ask
Just continue
They get uneasy after answering
Daniel...
This is enough ~
A scenario that's funny even to them
Ah, really frustrating.
But...
Really frustrating...
Professional pretty boy quiz king
Jaesuk.
Pavilion?
These people...
They can also win at this level of quiz
Daniel Libeskind?
Donatello.
Designomics.
Correct answer.
But...
Joongki didn't know
30 mins of preparations
Even Jongkook and the two kids can answer
Hurry guess.
Only 3 members left
2 more questions left
Next question.
Okay, next question.
Sukjin, fighting.
Using design to change
the quality of city life
Building a stable design
for the future of the city.
In 2010 Seoul became WDC,
what does WDC stands for?
World Design
You have to shout out your name.
Song Jihyo.
Song Jihyo?
You have to show your face
in front of the camera.
Due to anxiousness she
blocked her own face
Song Jihyo ...
World Design ...
Capital
Little Master memorized it seriously
Deng ~
Capital ~
Joongki.
World Design Capital.
Feel wronged
World ...
... Design Capital.
WDC.
I also wanted to say capital,
but Jihyo said it first.
Very reasonable.
World Design City.
World Design City, sounds correct too.
World Discount.
Jihyo, World Design Capital, correct.
Jihyo escaped at the 6th question
Can't...
Currently 2 people left
Sukjin and Joongki
Let's count down to 1.
Let's give an applause
to Joongki and Sukjin.
If Sukjin wins the 7 persons
will all get a Running Ball
Pygmallion.
The few remaining survivors... But then?
Donatello.
Daniel.
... ﻿mics.
Here comes the question.
Fighting ~
Joongki still hasn't
realized anything
Let's start.
Here it is.
This exhibition is very
significant and recognised.
Originally manufacture clothes for
the royal family or the royalties.
Currently it's held held in
Paris twice every year.
It signifies fashion trends ﻿worldwide,
what is the name of the show?
Sukjin.
Hold the cushion and talk.
Sukjin ~
3, 2 ...
Shout his name first
but can't remember
Ah it is very famous, isn't it?
Yes ~
It is very famous, isn't it?
If Joongki knows the answer ...
... he will win
the 1:7 battle
As expected
Will Joongki win...?!
Actually, there is no need to
memorize the difficult question.
If it is really difficult, Joongki will
not possibly know the answer.
What if Joongki knows?
How would we possibly
know Haute Couture?
* Haute Couture (French) = High fashion
(usually refers to high class fashion houses
Haute Couture ~
Difficult to pronounce
Haute Couture
Hau...
Does ...
... he know?
Hoti dekute.
Sounds similar but it's wrong
Luckily
Ah, what was it?
Sukjin.
Haute Couture.
Yes, it is.
Haute Couture ~
Haute Couture?
7 people have been waiting ...
... for this moment
Sukjin ... correct.
Correct.
Mission to make Joongki last
Big success
He knows he's last
All hopes disappear
Following this event ...
... our Joongki becomes the last.
Ah, Joongki ...
We will follow the arrangements.
There comes the running ball.
Only Joongki
doesn't get a ball
But Joongki, I thought
you would do really well.
No, how would we know all these?
The questions were a bit difficult.
But how did you know that, Sukjin?
How did you know?
I knew since it was
written in the script.
Happy birthday, Joongki.
Happy birthday.
Joongki, happy birthday.
What's happening?
Joongki, last week I also got tricked.
Something's fishy
What are you talking about?
It was a 7 to 1 game.
Joongki only realised now
Only I didn't know?
HaHa's palm is filled with
all the answers
Hyung, were you lying when you
said you had been to New York?
I've been to New York.
Jongkook has been to New York
But he don't know about the architect
But why would I care about
the name of a designer?
What's Daniel's last name?
I only know Daniel Henney.
Hyung also doesn't know?
How would I know that?
Jaesuk
Doesn't even know how to put up a tent
None of us knew about
that Pygmalion effect.
But most importantly, you
accepted the interview, right?
That was our staff.
Fake interview
At that time we were busy
memorizing the answers.
How did this happen?
Whatever ...
Night's special edition, hello everyone.
At this time the quiz show had already begun
Jaesuk is very funny.
Hosting and tricking at the same time
Funny hosting to victory
Jaesuk
With Gary I feel comfortable
and he's hilarious.
Donatello.
Laughter at
Joongki's ignorance
Gary
Jongkook has a lot to say.
But today's winner is someone
that seldom tricks Joongki
Jongkook
Sukjin sunbae ...
The skillful senior were able to fool
quick-witted Joongki
... ﻿is clever and I really respect him.
1:7 battle
The 7 members
Victory
Who made you most suspicious?
Daniel Robin ... something.
Naturally
It's Daniel Libeskind
Who would know that?
I didn't answer that
with much difficulty.
Still Jongkook managed to answer it
That 'designomics', Joongki almost guessed it.
There were many crises when
Joongki got it right
Revolving around
HaHa's suggestion
Design + Economics
The Pygmalion effect ~
Blocked by Kwangsoo
Pygmalion effect
Ah, really.
The moment Py was mentioned
Just now, Gary ...
Donatello.
Whatever, the first round of game ...
It's a pity for Joongki, but
we got the Running Ball.
Now it's really
Joongki's birthday party
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Our Joongki is so busy.
Leaving memories behind of
Joongki's 26th birthday
Current time
Since Joongki didn't answer
the questions correctly ...
Gary, you look like you're tired.
After the first mission
an exhausted Gary
Yes, you asked so many
questions I do not know.
Who is Donatello?
Checking
straightaway
Scultor.
Hesitating
What about Jihyo?
World Design Capital.
Jihyo remembers clearly
Kwangsoo?
Pygmalion ~
At this moment
Naturally
Joongki's gentle hand
What are you doing?
Alert
Gary is very tensed
Joongki, when you're not around
the love line here is not bad.
I'm sorry.
It was really good.
I tried everything, but
things still end up this way.
I tried everything
Sour...
Even though love is good ...
... what's not meant to
be is not meant to be.
Jumbled
feelings
Despite trying to make
oneself look better ...
... ﻿there will still be
things that won't work.
Giving up now is a bit early.
Determined
Gary's love for Jihyo won't lessen ♥
Expressing himself in this way ...
... it would be good if both
of them were together.
On the sidelines we will be
thinking, can this child make it.
I ﻿was just asking causally.
Actually, instead of a love-line
both of you look better in ...
... a comedy-line.
Comedy couple(?) Still embarrassed
What does Kwangsoo think of Jihyo?
I heard a lot from people around me
Uneasy
Last time, there was a
sister who bought a bag.
Jihyo said she exchanged
bags with the girl, but  ...
... but the girl said the
bag had been stolen.
The expression that never change
When he talks, his
expression doesn't change.
Really a level of misconception
He doesn't even smile
Looking at Jihyo's face now,
looks like there is a beard.
Like using the beard as a whip.
There's really no expression when he talks.
Master who frames Jihyo until
the very end is still very sincere
When we tell jokes, he doesn't laugh.
Framer Kwangsoo
Okay, what are we doing now?
The 2nd mission is?
Now we play Catch the Thief.
Ah, this game again
Catching
thief
Cards given to them
One of the cards is the thief
Exchange cards with
the one beside you
The person who has the thief-card
at the end won't get a Running Ball
The cards from the previous
game have been used up.
So this time we will use
Jongkook's designed card.
What?
The drawings of Jaesuk
that Jongkook made
When did I design it?
Yah, it's not similar
Doesn't it looks like Jaesuk?
Hyung, let's compare
Isn't It the same expression?
Keeps denying it
No, it isn't.
Exactly
the
same
Then I will distribute the cards.
It's alright to look at it from behind.
First
Kwangsoo isn't
Joongki ...
isn't
Big Nose...?
Running Man card
Checking Jaesuk's card
He's the
thief
Okay.
Trying to control his expression
Peek
Everybody has checked their cards
First, lets exchange cards.
Alright, Haha and Gary.
Who will be the thief?
HaHa's card is given to Gary
Troubled thief Jaesuk
Now Jongkook will choose.
Acting as if he has the thief-card
Joongki, when you weren't
around, he changed a lot.
This looks tensed.
There is the thief, Jongkook got it.
The thief is this person
Oppa, why is it so weird?
Acting like the thief card is right in front of him
This one.
This one ~
Now the thief is with Jongkook.
Definitely is.
The thief is in Jaesuk's hands
That's wrong
Carefully
Jaesuk ...
Yes?
I'm your hyung, so tell me
if you have the thief or not.
What?
Is there a thief?
There is ~
Sukjin's unease at the
straightforward answer
Looks like it's true.
Please...
take it away
The thief
Success
Insides getting nervous
Close your eyes.
Hyung, we can all see from here.
How are we going to
play the game like that.
It's no fun at all.
You guys look forward.
Sensitivity that comes with Running Man
Since when did you
gain interest in me?
Pull your chair back.
One mistake leads to a load of complaints
None of us should know.
I strongly recommend this
Ah, how meaningless.
Because of you, this show is finished.
I strongly recommend this.
Even so Stubbornly
Except HaHa
All members cards are confirmed
Current thief has mixed feelings
The one who wins the game
will be able ﻿to escape ...
... and to give his card to anybody.
Understood.
Thief Jaesuk wants the first place
Design ladder
All of you know ladders game, right?
Starting from the top downwards ...
Yes?
... the person who lands at the
Running Ball gets the first place.
There's no need for substance, just luck.
Okay.
Even I have a chance to win.
Full of
confidence
I really can chooser route well
Jaesuk needs to win
to give away his thief card
If it's based on today's luck, I can do it.
I want to play a
strength game
Kwangsoo starts the designing
Making it look like he's very good
Engrossed
If you do it like this what is
the next person going to do?
It's my first time drawing this.
I got it
Do we write it like that?
It needs to start at the bottom
in order to have a twist.
Joongki is focused on twisted endings
How should I continue?
The ladder got confusing
How will this turn out?
This will take up 3 weeks
worth of screen time.
A design that will take
3 weeks of screen time
There's the Running Ball.
I'm starting.
Thief Jaesuk is showing his top notch skill
No ... That's right.
No way
Now the messy crossed line
Oh, here...?
If he goes down he'll get
the Running Ball
Down, chu.
No way ~
Running Ball.
Cheers
Again ~
Running Ball.
Confirming the process fairly
Like this.
Like this ~
The problematic crossed line
You have to go up.
You cheater.
Repeatedly rewinding
The dream of getting first flew away
It's Kwangsoo's turn.
Ah, this feels good.
Unpredictable from the start
Going down, on the left.
Oh, good.
Please...
Left side ~
Left side, right side.
Go down.
Ah, it's Kwangsoo.
Yes!
Winner Kwangsoo gets a ball
Choosing like that.
Should have added more lines at the bottom
Should have been below.
Stairs designer
Kwangsoo
wins
Stairs designer
Me ~
Sukjin gets a Running Ball
Envy...
We'll follow the arrangement.
Kwangsoo and Sukjin can give
their cards to whoever they want.
Kwangsoo give his to Jongkook
Relieved
To one of them.
Nervous
You should keep this.
Also gave to his nemesis Jongkook
Ah, jealous.
These two became owners of Running Balls.
Jonghook now have 3 cards.
Both of you look very
comfortable with a ball.
I really had the thief-card.
Lying
So there are two thieves now?
Another liar
I was the thief too.
Are there 3 thieves?
More lies
Everyone says they are the thief
I'm also the thief.
Me too.
The one laughing
to himself
Fast breathing
I think it's with Jaesuk.
He looks nervous now.
Oh!
Control expression...
2nd round
of choosing cards
It's nerve-wrecking and driving me crazy.
Jaesuk has
Thief-card
Running Man
It's not with Jaesuk.
It's obviously with Joongki.
Have to choose one.
This one.
The middle card?
The 3 cards(?) look exactly the same
What does this mean?
I was holding 2 cards and
she actually took this one.
Why not?
Choosing naturally with talent
Wisdom, full marks to her wisdom.
Jealous ...
Want her to touch
his face too
Looks like there's something.
Did Jihyo chose the thief-card?
Jaesuk's facial expression is really weird.
A poker face
It's really weird.
There's one.
Excellent acting skills?
Or really depressed?
It's really weird.
Have to choose one.
Where is the thief-card now?
Next game is to try to express
emotions through your eyes.
Have to be faster than others to see
where the numbers are appearing
The person reaching 6 will lose.
We'll be eliminated one by one?
The last person who have not
shout out the number will lose
The numbers also have to be right.
If we stand up together,
will we lose straightaway?
Standing together will be eliminated
I think I'll be the first to stand.
I will stand up, I admit.
What to do if everyone
stands up together and get eliminated?
Stand up.
I'm not lying, I'm serious.
Ready ... start.
Also last person gets eliminated
Who'll be the first to shout?
One ~
Gary
Jihyo
HaHa
Eliminated
3 people got eliminated ~
You have to endure to the very end.
Irritated
Now it's Joongki, me and Jongkook.
Ready ...
You have to endure to
the end, that's the truth.
I can't keep it in anymore.
Hurry.
Endure to the end.
One.
Two.
I endured
One.
Two.
stupidly
Jaesuk didn't shout
a number till the end
Depressed
Why did you tell me to endure?
You have to endure in the beginning, but
when it's different when only 3 are left.
That's why I lost.
Final round
Joongki
Jongkook
The game is starting.
Say something to each other.
You have a backache, so don't stand up.
Yes, Joongki is the child
who needs a ball the most.
So I'll continue sitting.
Ready ...
Intends to continue sitting?
Are you really not going to stand up?
Then give him the Running Ball.
Compared to giving in, I will ...
Fast correction
... start.
One ~
If he starts it's scary
Really put others at a spot.
That's how it is
When we were talking ...
Said he wanted Joongki who
hasn't got a ball to get one
Joongki really doesn't have a single Running Ball.
Too much ...
Battle of giving in?
Jongkook gets a ball
I won't look at my cards
before I give them.
Are you going to give it out now?
Yes, of course.
Giving one person 3 cards?
Yes, one person gets all my cards.
Give them to Jaesuk.
Jaesuk hyung ...
Are you telling him
to give them to me?
I'll give them to you.
Happy
Now HaHa has 4 cards
Have to shift positions.
The three who won can
change the others seats.
Ah, really ...
Why do we have
to change sets?
Why?
So you don't have the thief?
That's not it.
Are you alright with it?
HaHa's seat has 4 cards
high probability the thief card is there
I have 4 cards.
You have 4 cards.
What do you think of my fashion?
It's good.
Is it fashionable?
Usually gets criticized
for his wrinkled fashion
You don't know?
I don't know, what do you think?
Blaming others
This is because of my codi.
That's it.
Give it a kiss.
Automatically
The left side too
Continuously pandering
Today even I have influential power.
You should stay quiet.
That person ...
Noona, what do you think my strength is?
Stay quiet.
This noona ...
You talk too much.
Influential power dropped to zero
"Talk too much".
This is really hilarious
This position is just nice.
Only HaHa and Gary change seats
The thief-card is in whose hand?
Are we going to see it now?
I'll open the cards one by one.
Yeah.
Originally HaHa's seat
Running Man.
Gary has 4 of the 8 cards
High probability of having the thief-card
You didn't look at them yet?
I didn't look at them.
1, 2, 3.
Please ~
All cards are
Running Man
Is it?
Gary is the first to pass
Joongki doesn't looks like he has it.
Is it between these two?
Either Joongki or Jihyo?
Or has Jaesuk been holding
the thief-card all the time?
Wait, let me reveal my card.
Fine, it's me.
Can't stand it
Admitting
Seriously.
This is too much
How can this be?
Exchanging cards and seats
But he still have the thief
Ah, this is really ...
Jaesuk had the thief-card
from the start to the end
This is really too much.
The thief never changed hands.
First Sukjin chose Running Man
2nd Jihyo also chose Running Man
No matter how they choose
they won't get the thief-card
From the start
always the thief
Running Ball.
Except for Jaesuk
everyone gets a Running Ball
Within an hour
stop a bomb from detonating
Battle of the bitter
chase in the rain
5 persons against 3 battle
will begin now
5 from the mission team
3 from the chasing team
It's raining today.
Chasing
Team
Strategy meeting
Start chasing from the pavilion.
Should check if there
is any movement ...
... then 2 people will go in.
1 investigate 2 do a surprise attack
Who will investigate?
Jongkook should do it.
If they see Jongkook they'll
try to escape by all means.
Yes, recently Jongkook's
expression is really good.
From the elevator, when
they were coming up ...
... and they saw you, the
expression were good.
Jongkook's
rising chasing skill
The expression is good.
Rip off the opponents name-tags
within an hour
Mission
Team
Strategy meeting
Joongki is going to try out
the running team today.
Because Joongki is here, I feel very calm.
Feels like Joongki belongs here.
With Joongki's wisdom
everyone feels at ease
Joongki is usually on the other team.
I've been on the Chasing
Team many times before.
Try taking a picture.
Instructions
Use the hand phone
to take a picture
It has to be closer.
Beep
Kwangsoo pressed the exit button
Before taking the picture
Being the most sloppy in their team
Kwangsoo, why did you do that?
Ting ling ~ ♫
Why are you so surprised?
Stop the detonation of the time bomb
Find 4 silver hidden tubes, cut the colored
wires in sequence to dismantle the bomb
It is in the exhibition room
with the sacred flame display.
We must know the order
of the four colors first.
The tubes reveal
the sequence for defusing
The time bomb is placed beside
the Olympic flame platform.
Cut the lines in the
right sequence
We have to know the sequence and ...
... cut the lines after finding the bomb.
I've been in the opposite team for awhile.
Usually Joongki gives ideas
Normally ﻿it's Jongkook
who gives the orders.
But Jongkook always makes the decisions
How is it usually done?
Block different directions
and charge in together.
Attacking the unknowingly
prey from all directions.
Their counter-strategy will be ...
How to counter that?
Even when they know this it doesn't help
We will only get trapped when surrounded.
We'll get trapped.
Giving up
Countdown
Joongki, do it properly.
Trust me today.
Wait ...
In the current situation ...
... there must be one at the
lawn or the city design pavilion.
Lawn
City Design Pavilion
Seoul Design Pavilion
Culture design hub
Even if we only find two ...
... we still must try to defuse it.
Even if someone is captured, never mind.
We're like the master
in the movie Shiri.
* Shiri (aka Swiri) is a Korean movie from 1999
which is the basis for the drama series Iris
Just like the movie 'Shiri'
Same scene, same mission
Let's search the lawn first, quickly.
Running Man shape on the lawn
1. Lawn
2. Cultural design pavilion
3. City design pavilion
4. Seoul design pavilion
But if we start here first, it
would be too dangerous.
Let's try look for it over here first.
They're on their way, let's look here.
There's one under one of these
Big trouble is brewing
Once they give up all is lost
Kwangsoo ~
Sukjin * Jaesuk
Running toward City Design Pavilion
Joongki * Kwangsoo
Running towards Seoul Design Pavilion
Jihyo runs alone toward Cultural Design Pavilion
Jongkook and the two kids
Chasing starts
The rain is pouring, we
have to fight in the rain.
Okay.
Heavy rain
Both in the City Design Pavilion
Jaesuk * Sukjin
Ran quickly
They're looking.
Shocked
1. Lawn
2. Cultural design pavilion
3. City design pavilion
4. Seoul design pavilion
Behind the frame
What's happening, I actually found it.
Touched
Sukjin
Found the first clue
Green wire is the 2nd to be cut
Caught her?
Gary is having a celebration.
How can you let Gary catch Jihyo?
Moving toward the pavilion
where Jaesuk and Sukjin is
HaHa*Jongkook
Unsafe
Hyung, they are currently at the lawn.
Bell sounds
getting closer
Sparta Kook
Sparta.
The backdoor is hopeless
charge towards the front
Yaya, come here.
HaHa waiting at the front door to attack
Yooruce Willis escapes
Big Nose is also running for his life
Sukjin and Joongki reunites
Go there.
1. Lawn
2. Cultural design pavilion
3. City design pavilion (clear)
4. Seoul design pavilion
There's a clue somewhere here
Oppa, did you find any?
We already found one.
Jihyo, you found any
or are you caught?
Under the lighting...?!
It's you, found you
Yooruce Willis
Found one clue
Red wire is the 3rd to be cut
Gary, have you caught Jihyo?
She ran too fast.
Perfectly fine
You said Jihyo ran too fast, I'm speechless.
Jihyo is too fast.
You have to catch her.
Commander orders the orderly
Could it be that you let her go?
It's not that I didn't try to catch her.
She runs faster then you expect.
Can't be like that.
Need to catch her.
Commander
Sparta Kook personally attacks
It's Jongkook.
Sparta Kook in just one breath
What's with your face?
Face after the rain
I already let Gary catch you, I won't do it.
Relaxed
Gary, come here.
Hold on tightly to those you catch.
Being scolded and not saying anything
Other people still have things to do.
She is too fast
Quickly take over.
How am I suppose to take over?
Once you're done here, you have to go.
Dilemma
Joongki ~
Finds Joongki
HaHa*Jongkook Trying to catch Joongki
Here ~
We must catch him.
Leaving
two people
Jihyo is giving up
Stand up.
Where?
For no reason
Unhappy
Where?
Get up.
Don't you trust oppa?
I don't trust ...
Is Gary trying to trick her?
Holds tightly
Please let me live once more.
A girl begs for survival
but a man who is unwilling
* BGM = "Woman who can't break up,
man who can't leave" by Leessang
Jihyo, don't be like that.
Ridiculous
Crazily
Trust oppa.
Lies.
Really?
She trusts him
and stands up
Awkward
Never expected me to be in
the rain with you like this?
Jihyo ...
... is there something that
I can trust you with?
Gary's ransom?
When I let you go, you can't
tell leader Jongkook about it.
Keep this a secret from Jongkook
I won't tell.
We have to keep this a secret, understood?
Is this for real?
Later, if your team wins ...
... you must tell me how to
contact you, understood?
You can't back off now.
A small price to pay
for being released
Contact
Number
Okay, I will.
Promise
Honestly...
Contact number is an excuse
It's only...
to comfort the heart of this man
Hurry and leave.
Why are you so fast?
Just release her like that
Run! Run further...!
A man acting like he can't catch up
There are times when
a man has to let go of the woman
Meanwhile Joongki is being chased
But still rather slow
Joongki runs out
Jongkook
behind
HaHa turns
around
Chasing
Team
Becomes more united day by day
Can Joongki escape?
HaHa suddenly appears
Old team mate Joongki's fate
Mission
Team
Joongki
1. Lawn
2. Cultural design pavilion (clear)
3. City design pavilion (clear)
4. Seoul design pavilion
Gary
Eh?
Why must it be there?
Hiding like that?
Not playing
with you
Silently~
Gary
Starts to attack
Kwangsoo is running for his life
Don't come here.
Go there.
Kwangsoo why did you run towards Jihyo?
Ah, Kim Jongkook.
Falls!!
He saw Jongkook and got shocked
This is the
Sparta Kooks effect
Suddenly appearing in front of you
Sparta Kooks
You fool.
Kwangsoo's life shortened by 100 years
Gary, go and catch her.
Mission
Team
Kwangsoo
Yooruce Willis is in the underpass
Where would they hide.
Keep quiet.
Commander Sparta Kook
Attack starts
Yooruce Willis desperately runs away
His VJ couldn't catch up with his speed
Please escape.
Already ran past half of the stadium
Teamwork attack
Immediately meeting
Come here quickly.
Sparta Kook follows in
Gaecholas Cage goes in from the side door
Hmm? What did he see?
Gary come over here.
What's so nice over there
that I have to see it?
Yooruce Willis
Gary come over here.
Who told you to hide like that
He ran to that side.
Easy to find
but hard to catch
Gary block the other side.
Cooperating
Gary blocks the opposite side
If you run to that side
It's Jongkook again
Huh?
Backstage again?
Gary, he's going to the other side.
Block the other side.
Block him.
Good job
our Gary
The man with 9 lives Yooruce Willis
Hey, why can't you just catch him?
He escaped again because of you.
Agitated
But Harad Pitt
is responsible for patrolling outside
Target
Unable to escape the shadow of the Chasing Team
Harad Pitt
accelerates
Yooruce Willis
last escape in the rain
Fierce
Big
slam
Panting
Chasing
Team
Surround tactic
Success
Mission
Team
Jaesuk
1. Lawn
2. Cultural design pavilion (clear)
3. City design pavilion (clear)
4. Seoul design pavilion
Jongkook * HaHa
Enter the Seoul Design Pavilion
Why are we here again?
We have to come here again.
There's always somebody here all the time.
Bingo
Both Sukjin and Jihyo are here
Look everywhere.
We couldn't catch them earlier.
That team always run to and from here.
You stand guard here.
Keep guarding this place.
This passage, come here.
Guard duty is Harad Pitt's destiny
Alone?
Uneasy
You do it alone.
Worried
Gary come here, come with me.
Unable to capture Jihyo(?)
Gary waits for strategy
Why didn't you catch Jihyo.
Hey, do it well first before talking.
Too fast again.
What too fast ?
I caught her and gave her to you.
Agitated
Gary sorry
You follow me.
You stay here and guard this passage.
They are definitely here.
Let me be the vice-captain.
Okay, you come over here.
Let's get out.
Hey, guard this place properly.
I already caught a few of them, but
he still tells me to do this and that.
Shouldn't do ...
Anxious
Alert
Oh~
Sukjin is very brave
Silently
This place contains
clues that have to be found
Tremendous courage
for a middle-aged man
Harad Pitt is totally unaware
Why do I have to listen to him ...
Whine
... and guard this passage?
He hasn't caught anyone yet.
I ... I already caught Joongki and Jaesuk.
Where are you?
Yes, hyungnim.
Immediately gave himself away
Yes?
That scared me.
How come I'm scared
when I hear his voice?
Yes, hyungnim.
Sukjin is searching
What?
I'm right here, blocking
the 3-way passage now.
Honest
Making sure Harad Pitt went out
The area that I'm standing at ...
... ﻿flim the entire area along with me.
Why do I suddenly feel alert
Again
Playing the lead in a movie
Not caring about any interference
Lonely little devil
Harad Pitt
Where are they
the Mission Team
Not bad, right?
Sukjin is still searching
Light coming out
from the snow
Sukjin
Found a front line clue
What happened?
Today Big Nose found 2 by himself
Heads back to the pavilion
Harad Pitt stops messing around
Blue wire is the first to be cut
Ring
Major emergency
What? Oh!
Sukjin made use
of the wonderful opportunity
HaHa is chasing around the back
Jongkook.
Hints
1st wire to be cut BLUE
2nd wire to be cut GREEN
3rd wire to be cut RED
What is the 4th?
There's now a chance
to dismantle the bomb
Jihyo going towards the bomb
Sukjin should be able to
dismantle the bomb now
But ...
Sukjin is completely surrounded
Hey, there's no where to retreat.
Mission
Team
Sukjin
I thought he escaped, gave me a scare.
The others don't know
the first is blue
What happened to Jihyo noona?
Jihyo noona, come over to the torch.
Those in prison says
2nd wire is green 3rd wire is red
Jihyo is sprinting towards the bomb
Oh, Jihyo noona appears.
Noona.
There's Jihyo.
Hurry, run, cut it.
Green second, red third.
Only Sukjin
knows the 1st clue
Harad Pitt is racing forward
Which is the first one?
Green second and red third.
Yellow or blue?
Must guess the first one correctly
Hey, blue is number one.
Sukjin's voice is too far away
It can't be heard through the rain
Hurry up and cut it.
It all ends if Jihyo is captured
Hey, blue is number one.
Jihyo is confused
Blue? Yellow?
Mission Team's sign of failure?
Ah... Jihyo
She cut yellow first
Mission
Team
Fail
What happened?
Hyung, we won.
Ah... Jihyo lost
her walkie-talkie
There was a 50:50 chance
Fool, you should have waited a little longer.
Ah, really.
Sorry
How to do it?
If you knew blue was number
one we would have made it.
Oppa, it was you who came too late.
Blaming each other
If I waited longer they would
have ripped off my name-tag.
Continue to be
drenched in rain
Warfare in the rain
Chasing
Team
Victory
Jongkook Gary HaHa
get Running Balls
Jongkook alone caught everyone of us.
Current time
Running Ball count
Jongkook Gary HaHa 3 balls each
Sukjin Jihyo Kwangsoo 2
Joongki Jaesuk 1 ball
What is our punishment?
As punishment you have to wear
hot pants and walk to SBS Center.
No way.
Put the balls in first, then talk.
Please.
Please come out once.
Final selection of escapees
Time for luck
It's not 4 people, it's 4 chances instead.
Who'll be the first to escape?
Let my Running Ball come out
Who is it?
HaHa
escapes
Dream comes true
Who'll be the next?
Only 4 chances.
If HaHa comes out again?
Then the rest of us only
have two more chances.
It won't happen.
Denial
Please ~
Who'll be the 2nd to escape?
HaHa again!
Unbelievable
Speechless
Out of his 3 balls 2 came out
Shouts from a lucky man
At a loss
Does it make sense?
Dissatisfied
It's really HaHaHAHa.
HaHa was picked twice
Only 2 chances left
Who'll be next to escape?
Gary
2 happy kids
Jongkook also had 3 balls but
none came out
Please, let there be a miracle this time.
Now it's the last chance
Please ...
Sorrow and joy in one moment
... a miracle.
Anticipating a miracle
Jaesuk with only one ball
Last ball
who'll be the
lucky owner?
Jihyo
Earning dramatic exemptions
since last week Jihyo
Whoa, it's really me.
Unhappy
Shall I give everyone another chance?
Charity
Yes.
Interested
Gift?
HaHa ~
Everybody wants
to get a last chance
Enthusiastic
Seuk ~
You don't like it?
For the chance to be exempted from the punishment
Ask with both hands.
Endure
Hurry, just do it.
Say please give it.
Please give me.
Jongkook, do it
for all of us
Hesitate
Please give it.
Endure
Utter humiliation
Another chance
thanks to Jongkook
One more time ~
1, 2, 3.
Thanks to Jongkook's sacrifice
who'll be the miracle's owner?
Everyone
praying for their own miracle
Eh?
Kim Jongkook ~
Jongkook
Unscripted TV drama
I envy you
Endured humiliation for another chance
for his own success
Doomed
Weren't you a little too much?
Sudden change
I'm sorry.
What idea this idea  that ... ?
Back to rightful position
Jongkook and the 2 kids
Collect them by color.
Wear hot pants to SBS tomorrow
I'll really go crazy.
I already have a pink one at home.
Imagine the color now
the punishment's rumour
Okay, then yellow for you.
Continuing
the punishment
The next night
near SBS broadcast station
One car stops by the road
Members arrive
Costumes on top Hot pants below
Even more humiliating
Micky Yoochun
Pak Minyoung
Joongki did it at the set of
Sungkyunkwan Scandal
Yoo Ahin
Chuseok holidays so there's a lot of people
3 bare-legged men heads toward SBS building
Many spectators
All attention toward them
There's many people here.
Next time they see hot pants
they'll think of Running Man.
The hot pants have a Running Man logo
Enter a nearby coffee house
It's Yoo Jaesuk.
Surprised
Which is the fastest to make?
Iced Americano Coffee.
Three Iced Americano.
In chorus
Brings laughter to the citizens
More citizens have gathered outside
Shy
More disasters It's now raining
Raining, iced coffee and hot pants.
Perfect punishment
Raining
Iced coffee
Hot pants
It's becoming competitive.
Heavy
Scrambling
Sprint
Punishment completed
Arrived at SBS building
Next landmark
SBS broadcast center
Unique perspective with colleagues
who stay up late to work
Forget
past competitions
October 3rd 5:20 PM