Original hardsubs by iSUB
Transcribed by HapB
Color and alignment by SamFive
2018 Pyongyang Winter Olympics Candidate City
Special!
Running
Man
Pyongyang
Gangwon province
A-class resort
Snowy scenery in front of your eyes
Running Man's
big battle!
God of comedy
Shim
Hyungrae
Running Man's
Yeongu
* Yeongu is a role Hyungrae played in a film
The everlasting
Heart of slapstick comedy
It will begin
right now!
A snowy winter
A place you want
to visit during winter
Today Running Man has come
to a wonderful place again.
Running Man gathered at the ski resort
Welcoming
them with snow...
Our two kids here ...
The three
excited ...
Woosh~
The dongsaeng who always
looks after ignorant hyungs
You look so handsome
throwing that snowball.
To Joongki, you guys
don't dare to say anything.
Joongki just threw a snowball, Kwangsoo ...
But...
When done by Kwangsoo...
Woo hoo.
Hwak~
Backs off~
Joongki, Kwangsoo...
Same actions, different responses
How could you treat him like that?
Joongki and Kwangsoo
are same age friends.
Both are born in 1985
You must treat them equally.
For Kwangsoo, subtract at
least 3 years off his age.
Joongki and Kwangsoo ...
... me and Bae Yongjoon,
we are the same age.
Born in 1972
Yoo Jaesuk
Same age~
Bae Yongjun
Can this be used for comparison?
Yongjun we are friends, right?
Plead~
Hyung, So Jisub.
So Jisub?
Gary & So Jisub
Same age friends
Really?
This is
absurd
The place we are at now is ...
... 2018 Winter Olympics candidate city
Pyongyang, in the Gangwon province.
Wishing Pyongyang would
be able to succeed in their bid.
Fighting ~
Pyongyang
Winter
Olympics
We will be rooting for the 2018
Pyongyang Winter Olympics.
Pyongyang fighting
Say it together ... seumdwa.
Seumdwa ~
Pyongyang will win, right?
Everyone, 2010 is coming to an end.
Yes.
Let's take this chance to say
a few words to each other.
I will first say something to Mr. Jaesuk
Why address me as Mr Jaesuk?
Let's call it that way.
Okay, I understand.
I really wish that we could become close
like before, going to the sauna together.
It's a very simple thought.
Don't go and workout with
Jongkook everyday ...
... go out with me as well.
Joongki, who would you
like to say something to?
Me? ... to Jihyo noona.
Oh, you want to say something to Jihyo?
Why aren't you starting?
Who's this?
Why are you saying so
much meaningless stuff?
Someone is suddenly yelling
Please wait a moment.
This person's face will
be revealed shortly
Make it faster.
We will be done soon, please
wait a moment hyung-nim.
During 2011 ...
Yes?
... don't be with Gary hyung.
Be together with me, let's have a
love as pure as this white snow.
Ah really Joongki, why are you like that?
Are you saying that our love is dirty?
Explodes
Is our love dirty?
Jongkook, now it's your turn.
Me? ... I have something to
say to my two lovable kids.
Ah, for the two loveable kids.
What's wrong with you all?
Same person appearing again
♪ Dashing through he snow,  ♪
♪ in a one horse open sleigh. ♪
♪ Run, don't run ~ ♪
Slowing getting the feel...
The two kids always have
all kinds of weird thoughts.
Yes ~
Let's work together in 2011 and
create five new catch phrases.
Ah, I like it.
Let us create "all of" as catch phrases.
* Like "seumdwa" "ssakda" is "all of" pronounced weirdly.
What?
Only HaHa is creating phrases himself
What is ssakda ssakda?
Disregarding Jongkook's
objection of Ssakda Ssakda
Jaesuk ...
Yes?
Sorry to interrupt, but ...
... you look especially close to them
towards the end of the year.
Why are you always like that?
Sukjin's jealousy has no boundaries
Stop trying to come in, hyung.
Why can't I come in, I
was close to him first.
King of childishness
I knew him first.
Both...
...arguing
Suddenly
♪ Dashing through he snow,  ♪
♪ in a one horse open sleigh ♪
This person! Arrived!
The father of comedy!!
♪ Run, don't run ~ ♪
Today the guest is none
other than Shim Hyungrae.
Officially welcoming today's guest
Welcoming
Korea's greatest and eldest comedian
Today's guest
Eternal Yeongu
Shim
Hyungrae
Our big senior, comedy
director Shim Hyungrae.
First greet everyone.
Hello ~
Just now, I was at the side watching.
Smack
Already starting his slapstick comedy
... at the side watching.
Indeed the comedy king Letting us laugh
You should have fallen down.
We don't fall down right at the start.
Using his hand to block
I've just finished a new movie.
And coming to Running Man is an honor.
The new movie <The Last Godfather>
Came immediately after the premier ended
Director Shim is the kids' favorite director.
First is General Yi Sunsin,
second is Shim Hyungrae.
I'm in third place.
In second place is King Sejong.
You really hit me.
You must be sure about things
before you can say it aloud.
Slapstick should appear naturally,
it's not suppose to be that way.
This
way!!
Seems like Jaesuk...
will have a day of suffering...
So it like that, so it's
funny without hurting.
So it won't hurt.
Of course.
Not inflicting pain, but make it funny.
The show Running Man requires
you to keep running and ...
... is your body alright?
Yes it's not a problem.
If it's alright, why did you keep asking
the PD what time it will end today?
It's not that, but why is the opening so long?
This opening is relatively short already.
It's short?
Yes.
I was still thinking, why is it so long?
Bang
Pow
Jihyo
Always blank~ and getting punished
Regardless of age and gender,
everyone is treated equally.
It doesn't hurt, right?
Ah, yeah.
Behind
Pow
This is a strong slapstick
You have to look at it.
Let us welcome director Shim
Hyungrae once again for coming.
Indeed the comedy god
Together with Hyungrae In the world of slapstick
Running Man will begin now.
Pow
Bang
Starting now
slapstick comedy unfolds
The extraordinary
Starting the filming in a moment
It will begin soon ~
Dong
Flower boy Joongki's
embarrassing moment
Are you alright?
When there's a target in front
It doesn't matter whether
it's a junior or senior.
Once he picks his target,
no one can stop him.
But just doing it like that ...
... isn't enough.
After that, for the ending.
Sniff
It's this expression
You must do that as well.
Teacher, I would like to try as well.
Pow
If the ending is like this ...
Bang
Suddenly the Evil Jihyo appears
JiHyo never treats others like that ...
... But she even kicks Kwangsoo.
Why is it like that?
No, I just ...
Calmly playing tricks
I'm sorry.
Slowly
drifting aside
Okay, let's continue.
Today we are dividing into 3 groups.
Should this be done by you?
Since hyung is here, I'll
let you do the MCing.
You do it.
It's too thoughtful.
Okay then ...
We still have a game to play.
The snow is drifting at a nice time as well.
Like this, the air would be better.
The ski resort
is in good condition for games
Oppa ...
Jihyo is learning from HaHa and
is wearing the same kind of hat.
Oh, what's that?
Couple
hat?
Hey, do you love me?
What did you say?
Who learned from whom?
Psychological battle
Running ball ...
When doing the opening, don't talk.
Smock
Why...
Why me...?
Hyung-nim ...
She said she loves me.
It wasn't me who said that hyung-nim.
Backs off
Pow
I really shouldn't
have stood there
Today we are split into
three teams to compete.
So what game are we playing?
It's a lift quiz.
Lift quiz?
There are already 3 groups ...
I am quite unsatisfied with you,
the others are standing, but ...
... you're the only one who is sitting.
Hyungrae doesn't care if you
are the PD or the cameraman.
If you're not careful, you
will be in danger today.
Today's Running Man staff
are in for a period of suffering
Please continue with the rules.
Each time will send out 1 member.
Where are the chisels?
* He misheard
Representative ~
Hyung-nim representative.
Each group will send one member
to take the resort's cable car up.
The remaining members will run uphill.
As the member gives out questions,
you must run uphill to answer.
So now, wouldn't we know which
member would be sent out?
We already know who'll be the
representative from our team.
We can't possibly let
Hyungrae hyung run?
Look at my legs.
Really quite short legs
No matter how I see it, they
resembles those of penguins.
I'm quite unhappy with my legs too.
Are those legs or arms?
This team doesn't need to worry.
Why hyung?
There's me.
That's right.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Hyungrae's team sure to lose?
Ah~
You guys just need
to worry endlessly.
Panic
You need to give the questions well.
Don't trust me.
No confidence
You have to ask the questions well
so we can get the Running Ball.
If not we will get the punishment.
Just accept the punishment then.
Angry
Why must we play this game?
Isn't there me?
Fighting.
Lift Quiz
Blue
Team's
Challenge
starts
Fighting, seumdwa ~
Are they holding their breaths?
* Breath (soom) sounds like seumdwa
It's a trendy word they
created themselves.
But it's still not the trend yet.
That won't work.
So hyung is there anything
left to give to them?
Give them?
Yes.
Running Man ...
Yes?
... we can do it.
I don't know either ~
It must be of standard to be a trendy word
I don't know either.
Besides this, is there another one?
Yeongu has disappeared.
Yeongu has disappeared ~
The earliest trend that
all citizens followed
Later when hyung gives
us the questions ...
... we have to accurately
answer as many as possible.
Who?
We are.
Why?
To get the Running Ball.
Is that thing very expensive?
No, we must get it to be
exempt from punishment.
I think today's game have ended.
Don't worry, there's me.
That's why we're calm
We ...
Let's shout a slogan together.
... can't win.
Team representative is
taking the lift to give the questions
These kids' energy can't make it.
Blue
Team's
representative
is of course(?)
Jong
kook
How worrying.
I have to do well.
Representative must use their
loudest voice to ask the questions
He's our team-mate.
Because of Kwangsoo, I'm uneasy now.
I'm pretty steady.
He's coming ~
I can hear Jongkook oppa's voice.
I heard it.
Jongkook must be very serious.
Jongkook slowly
coming up
Yes.
When Kim Jongkook talks
loudly, he has no charm.
Ha Donghoon ...
... Kang Gary, get ready.
Can you do it well?
Seumdwa ~
Okay.
The representative's throat will hurt
The other members' legs will hurt
In the Olympics ...
... when we get first place
... we hang it on our neck.
Gold medal.
Gold Medal
That's it.
Correct
Hyung louder, slower.
Yah, this is like this.
Seems like an action hint
Horizontal bar?
Ski jump.
Ski Jump
Okay.
Correct
Oppa, slower please!
They are starting to lag behind
Lizzy's leg strength is diminishing
That's it, she's exhausted.
In a little while it's their turn
You can't be like that.
Yes ~
If we get the gold medal,
this thing will be raised up.
Money!
Why will money be raised up?
Flag.
National flag
That's it.
Correct
Lagging behind more and more
Where is this?
Ski field.
No ~
Winter Olympics bidding place.
Pyongyang
Pyongyang.
That's it.
Correct
Ah!!! What are you saying?
How many questions have
they gotten correct?
Lizzy is really ...
What did you say?
Yah, not speed skating.
Fallen
Jongkook hyung ...
Not speed skating, short one.
Our country does it very well.
Even if they heard the question,
they can't answer it.
Figure skating.
Speed skating.
Short one.
Short one!
Aigoo, sorry.
Also ending a snow
fight with slapstick
Short one ~
Hot pants.
Ha ha
Correct
answer
Short Track
Short one.
With short one~
Blue
Team
Totally drained
Why is his voice so soft?
Yah ...
Anger
... it's short track, how
can you guess hot pants ?
In Running Man short one equals hot pants
Aren't they short?
I said not speed skating but the
short one, isn't that short track?
As soon as the game ended
the 4 people explode
How can it be short pants?
We couldn't hear you at all!
I already said it.
We couldn't even hear your voice.
The answer was short track.
I couldn't hear your voice, hyung.
Short track.
I'm sorry I didn't hear your voice.
Poff
Not wanting to be scolded
HaHa starts his Hollywood action
Blue
Team
Answered 4
questions correct
Next is
Yellow
Team
Let's go, Joongki and Jihyo.
Using this short break for a celebration(?)
♪ Dashing through he snow,  ♪
♪ in a one horse open sleigh ♪
* Jongkook makes a pun on the words
Commander charisma frenzy
Yeongu who can't look on
Back of
the head
Zock
Where did such a half hearted
performance come from?
This time towards Lizzy
Doesn't show
when it'll come
Worrying~
Pow
Can't be off guard
Slapstick world
Commander's
satisfying everyone
Bang~
bang~
explosion
Stumble~
Good job.
Yeongu caught hold of the Commander
Hurray
Wow, feels good.
He's coming ~
Sukjin slowly gets to the start point
Oppa, fighting.
We can hear you.
He's coming.
Pyol ~
It's snowing ~
One word.
Snow
Snow ~
Okay.
Correct
♪ White snow falling down from sky ♪
♪ Let's follow the snow ♪
Has to answer correctly according to the question
It's that song.
Winter story ~
Winter Story
Correct
Fast
pace
Already answered
two questions
Memory ~
Memory
That's it.
Correct
They're doing well.
Worrying
Red
Team
Look at this.
But it's already more than half way
Dang ~
Don't cry.
Don't cry
Wow, that's it.
Correct
Don't cry ~
Eh? But ...
Jihyo's strength is dissipating
Two hands holding tightly
In the white snow...
Song Song couple
Huh?
Are they playing games or ...
... dating?
I can...
only sigh...
Yah, love ...
Sukjin only thinks about the game
Jihyo ...
SongSong couple
caught up
Kim Jongseo's song, what rain?
Winter rain.
Winter Rain
Correct
That's right.
Ah, it's tiring.
Listen carefully.
Joongki also exhausted
Yellow
Team
Falling~
At the moment
Leading in
1st place
Yellow
Team
5 correct answers
1, 2, 3, fighting.
Red
Team
Must answer 6 questions
or more to be 1st
Why must we do this?
Don't worry, there's me.
Can they...
really not be worried?
Looking at it, the team
just now was really good
Red
Team's
Hyungrae got on the lift
How does my brain think like this?
The other people kind of worry me.
But Kwangsoo is not so bad.
Kwangsoo seems more relaxed
I'm more worried about Jaesuk.
When he was still a freshman, his
performance really couldn't make it.
Uneasy
Under performing junior's
worrying for the senior
Letting hyung give all the
questions is really worrisome.
He's coming ~
Hyung fighting ~
Now they're shouting like that,
their life is really depressing.
All because they met someone like me.
We will definitely do it well.
Depressing life(?) of two men
We're ready ~
Not knowing anything
Full of spirit
Hyung, give the questions with a loud voice!
Fighting.
Why say fighting, what's the use?
Didn't even prepare the questions
Ignores~
Panic
Now the game
Hyung, give us the question.
It has started.
Hyungrae hyung!
No matter how I give the
questions, we still can't win.
Also busy running...
Sunbae ~
Sunbaenim ...
Hyung ...
The very first... no... from our country.
...What's he saying?...
I can't hear your clearly.
Please speak louder.
Pass ~
Already passing a question
It is already impossible to
answer 6 questions or more
We've won.
It's already more than half way
New year's menu
Describe dumpling soup...
During new year... No Chuseok.
Urging it's Chuseok
The soup we drink during Chuseok.
Deok soup.
Is there only ddeok soup?
Yes?
Then
Dumpling
soup
Dumpling soup.
Correct
Right.
Dumpling soup.
Answering the question
correctly like this...!
Hyung, hurry up.
But they're already exhausted
During winter, how nice
is it to eat this hot dish.
To make
things worse
Obstructing of the challenge
Crash
Bun that we eat during winter.
Hobbang.
Hobbang
Correct
Smock
Hit on the spot
Wait ...
Just let me answer two questions.
Those answering
are far behind...
Sort the seafood... then we eat it.
Pow
This time it's Jaesuk
Spot on!
Ah~ This is all
because of Hyungrae
hyung, seriously!
And there are a lot of
these in the east sea.
Red
Team
Worse than running up is
letting him shout out the questions
Jaesuk ...
Still asking the question
A lot of these in the east sea.
I don't understand your questions.
Kwangsoo ~
Kwangsoo
is not here
When you asked the questions ...
... "This..." and  "That..."
took up 90% of the question.
That was to let you have
a better understanding.
Alright! This... Ah...
This is what took up most of it
That's it, too much of that.
Alright, this... Ah...
Red
Team
Answered 2 questions
Winners got five
questions correct
Yellow
Team
We won!
Sukjin * Jihyo * Joongki
Get Running Balls
There will also be surprising sights
to see in Running Man...
Pyongyang is
getting darker
Wow~
In front of your eyes
is the giant Ski Jump Platform
Here they filmed the movie <Take Off>
Nation's only international
standard ski jumping platform
A ski jumping platform carrying
Republic of Korea's dreams
That's seriously awesome.
If we're chosen to host the
2018 Winter Olympics ...
... then this place will be hosting the events.
Touched
There's also a 160m tall one, that
is around 30 stories of a building.
Height reaches to 160m
The next mission's location will
be at this tall platform's top.
To the top
Taking the monorail
Ah, this is the place.
This is the route that the contestant takes.
Heart warming
Welcome.
Hello.
Welcome ~
That's where they jump.
In front of their eyes
The ski jumping platform
Flying out like a bird here you can always see
the shadow's of the cool ski jump sportsman
Because we're Running Man ...
... let's all jump once.
Hurriedly, this place will hurt
your stomach with a funny mission
We're shooting.
Huk!
Yeongu
Jihyo?
Please look over here.
That's not bad?
1, 2, 3.
Today, a big director has come to join us.
Changed to Yeongu outfits
Yes.
Are you the new year's magpie?
* Magpie = An increasingly talkative bird
The opening is taking too long again.
You made the opening too long.
God of Comedy starts lecturing
... opening too long.
Today we'll do
acting until we satisfy the Sunbae
Hurry ~
There's a Yeongu here.
It's really crazy.
Birth of Yeongu?
ZERO dress up
all natural
If we're filming a comedy
according to the original ...
... then this is good.
A guaranteed 100% funny body
the Calm Original
I really can't see anything.
This is as good example
to play in a comedy
The cast are the most basic in comedy film.
Actually Sukjin you need a dot here.
Take off your glasses.
Yes.
That was on purpose.
And this ...
Because of comedy
takes off the fashion glasses
that protects the eyes
... the pants, all of it.
This can't do.
Basic fashion for Yeongu
tuck the shirt inside
Tuck it inside your pants.
Tuck in everything.
Teacher, if I tuck this all
in, then it is kind of ...
Gary is slowly
becoming more and more like Yeongu
One Yeongu that talks too much
Alright, right now ...
... only fundamentals are no good.
The God of Comedy starts judging
But he dressed up the best.
Only satisfied with Gary
But I didn't dress up.
Doesn't need make-up
Reborn Yeongu(?)
Come here.
Anticipation
Master Hyungrae doing the make-up himself
He got favored without
even saying a word.
Envy~
Teacher ...
It's perfect.
In middle of recreating Yeongu...
Gary seriously looks like
a resurrection of Yeongu.
Happy Yeongu arrives
Smile that show your teeth.
Right on?
Gary, all of a sudden
I envy you a lot today.
That's straight up Yeongu resurrected.
Needing the Yeongu scholarship
a prediction of the super candidate
The anticipated actress
Jihyo's transformation
That's cute.
Cute
You're no exception.
Flower Boy NO exception
Oh, that's pretty.
He's handsome.
That's cute.
Result?
Joongki looks cute like that.
He looks cute no matter what.
Come here.
Before ...
It's the anticipated Jaesuk's turn
Be quiet.
Put a lot on.
Give him a complete make over.
I'll give you the special version.
The black eyed Yeongu when he
tried to steal from another kitchen.
Even Yeongu has a lot of different versions.
Unique
Bang exploding Jaesuk Yeongu ver.
With only make up
causing an uproar
Everybody ...
I went over there for awhile and my
life has changed when I came back.
Straightly Yeongu haunts
This is great.
How about our directors
do a little make up too.
They even want the staff
to have make-up
Try it.
Chanhui hyung, please come out.
It'll be finished quickly.
Hyung, it won't even take one minute.
Of course he objects..
Just try it.
Result
Gets taken by the golden hand
Director please take off your headphones.
Do you know what was sad just now?
What?
Sukjin hyung has this angry
make-up, but no one's filming.
The left alone Big Nose's
exaggerating make-up
Why are we giving the
air-time to the director?
Big Nose hyung being
pushed aside by the director
Job complete
Doing this with us is not bad.
Today is Yeongu day.
Everyone becomes Yeongu
Yeongu DAY
Frightened
Hyojin should give it a try too.
Even dragging the PD into this
You need to try this.
Hyojin PD-nim, come try this.
Come on, hurry.
It's an honor having Hyungrae doing this.
Forcefully dragged into
the make up room(?)
Takes off your glasses.
Ha ha
Let's have a look.
Yeongu PD...?
He's really angry.
You two come here, come here.
This scene seriously ...
Filming location becomes
a warm place with Yeongu
Looks like there is so much harmony.
Such harmony.
Let's take a picture.
Alright let's go.
Today is seriously Yeongu day.
Okay.
1, 2, 3.
Today is
Yeongu DAY
Thank you Running Man.
This is not my camera.
Can't find his own camera(?)
Camera director Kang Chanhee
He's too out of it, can't see anything.
Yeongu DAY will bring
astonishing acts
It's suppose to be here,
but he ran else where.
Oh this, wait.
Ah, this is not my camera.
Magical Yeongu make-up
Alright, what's today's slap stick comedy?
A male and female act.
We're going to destroy our images a bit.
But in return, we will
receive other's laughter.
Today I will give everyone the
real traditional slap stick comedy.
Which is also today's mission.
Ah, is that so?
That's right.
Then let the producer tell us.
What kind of mission is it?
Today will be 1 vs 9.
Let's win against Shim Hyungrae
Using Yeongu's 6 acts of slapstick.
Yes.
It seriously can't be done.
Actually Hyungrae's Yeongu is really ...
Not everyone can learn that.
Will there be practice time?
You will receive 1 on 1
lessons with Hyungrae.
Ah, first divide you
up and come 2 by 2.
1:9 rules
6 stages of comedy. If the 9 members
challenge without an NG, they'll win
1st stage
Drum sound
from afar
These rascals, I have to wake up
early in order to wake them up.
Drum sound from afar
(1986 Sept~1987
That rascal.
A program with laughter
hinted to mock society
That weird rascal, seriously.
Was I seeing things?
Hyungrae's drumming wake up part
will be the 1st stage's question
Hey!
Expressions & movements
Ah I get it, there's no one here.
Can the Running Yeongus act out
Hyungrae's comedy skills?
I was imagining things and I
thought someone was here.
Then ...
Practice of Drum Sound From Afar
Ready ... action.
Those rascals.
I have to get up early in
order to wake them up.
Let me beat the drum to let you
guys know what time it is now.
Expecting
... know what time it is now.
Stiff
It's too fast.
Reaction comes too fast?
It is not like it's a scolding.
Forward this way, so when I swing
back it just nicely hits my head.
So you should be able to feel something.
Director Hyungrae seems like he
is dealing with a comedian newbie
This is not a scolding, try it again.
The National MC seems to have
become smaller in front of him
Hit him harder next time.
You just stay still and be quiet.
Ready, action.
Wow, everyone here is Yeongu.
When you look to this
side, they are all Yeongu.
Okay enough .... ready, action.
An additional Yeongu over here...
Ah, those guys.
To wake them up I myself
have to wake up early too.
Practice seriously
to succeed later at the challenge
Let me beat the drum to let you
guys know what time it is now.
Seems too fast again...?
Who was it?
As expected
I thought I told you ...
... to feel something first.
I thought I told you to
feel something first.
Pow, it's like this.
Giving a neat demonstration
Do you understand?
As expected
Be quiet.
Without warning Bamboo sword attack
This is not an insult.
Ready ... action.
Ah, those guys.
To wake them up I myself
have to wake up early too.
Let me beat the drum to let you
guys know what time it is now.
Seriously, I told you
to have more feeling.
Wasn't the feeling enough this time?
Only by sacrificing your body
can you achieve true slapstick comedy
You must hit harder this time around.
You can't predict the direction of
Hyungrae's bamboo sword attack
You're aiming here, why
did you hit down there?
The head is for people to use.
Ready, action.
Comedy god?
Slapstick in real life
Are you okay?
It really is a case of the
head is for people to use.
You go over there ... Ready, action.
Of course, the head is for people to use.
Are you really okay?
I'm okay, still very handsome.
Whenever something happens,
all the nine Yeongus will gather.
You still have to remember the feeling.
Look at the sweat on my palm.
Now you know why the director
doesn't let you do anything much.
You talk too much, just start acting.
The merciless teaching methods
The cameras are all waiting for you.
I understand.
You shut up too.
All got hit on the head.
Ah those guys, to ...
Dialogue NG
Puft
What are you doing?
Exploded
Come over here, do it properly.
Do you know how expensive
the tapes are these days?
The veteran director Hyungrae even
takes production costs into consideration
Why can't you even remember the script?
Hyung, the Running Ball is at stake here.
Why are you staring at me?
The staff has to be alert too
He has been staring at me with
one eye since the beginning.
You have to
open two eyes today to film
Let Joongki try, his acting skills are very good.
Let Joongki have a go.
I had long wanted to try this.
Then have a go at it, he
should be quite good at it.
Start.
Ah those guys, to wake them up
I myself have to wake up early too.
Let me beat the drum ...
Is he doing well?
...to let you guys know
what time it is now?
What's
wrong...?
As usual, coming over ...
You, from the moment you started
I haven't been feeling very well.
In fact, unhappy since the beginning
What were you doing when
you started walking in?
I'm too nervous.
If Hyungrae hyung hadn't been
here, I would have done better.
Then, Joongki ...
Joongki challenges once again
Ready, action.
Ah those guys, to wake them up
I myself have to get up early too.
Twist slightly a bit more.
Let me ... Uh?
Spirit of Yeongu is implanted
Ah, as I said before.
Embarrassed
Say it, just talk.
Let me beat the drum to let you
guys know what time it is now.
Huh?
Using the head to beat the stick?
This is really weird.
Really weird.
Seems that he is really nervous
I give up ~
Joongki is done ~
Joongki
Gives up
Cute.
This is scary.
He must have been very nervous.
So nervous that he beat himself.
Totally lost control of himself.
You settle yourself first.
Settle yourself first.
Oh?
That's it, that's the way.
Learning how to defend himself
after suffering several hits
A few more times and he will be better.
Good job, next one.
Huh?
Why didn't you defend yourself?
I don't block.
I thought he would block it.
Why didn't you block?
I'm really sorry, but why didn't you block?
Urgent apology
Because this is my concept.
Original style NO defense
I seriously thought you will
block it, I'm really sorry.
How can you look at a senior and hit him?
Dented
It's okay.
Finally......
Stage 2
Drum sound from afar II
A scene where instead of hitting the drum,
the character crash head into it instead
Like this ~
Now we are entering into stage 2.
Kwangsoo stage 2 practice
Ready, action.
Do a good job Kwangsoo.
It is like this ~
Not Yeongu ...
But close to acting like an idiot
But ...
Directly crash headfirst
Yah, but ...
Falls backward~
Sorry, I'll do better next time.
Should have moved back
before hitting the drum
Do it again, Kwangsoo.
Kwangsoo attempting it again
This time...
Forgot to say the lines
Over here.
Sorry.
How can you just quietly walk over?
Reflecting is Kwangsoo's specialty
I'll do my best next time.
A bamboo sword stimulation
to wake up the senses
Do a good job.
I will do my best.
You start from over there ...
... then you slowly walk over here.
After you estimated the distance ...
Before turning around, estimate the
distance to the drum before crashing in it
... you turn around.
This is how you do it.
You must be accurate in your estimation.
Ah, very good.
Remember to never look behind you.
Nervous
Why aren't you saying your lines?
What are you doing there?
Too focused on the timing to turn around
that the lines are forgotten
As you walk over from there
you must say your lines.
Today's 1 vs 9 challenge...
is a worrying sight
Yeongu and Daengchiri I
1989 blockbuster
Yeongu and Daengchiri
The solo scene of
Yeongu's
big formality
Okay, ready ... action.
Father, your inferior son has ...
Yeongu's father
Joongki
Yeongu
Jongkook
... come to pay you respect.
You have to say something too.
In the midst of it Joongki receives
the teaching of the bamboo sword
What are you doing?
Do a good job.
Ready, action.
Father.
Yes?
Your son is now giving you a bow.
Huh?
No matter what, you must remain healthy.
Yah, quickly finish your lines.
The bamboo sword of love that does
not even spare the Commander
Continue saying your own lines quickly.
Shim Hyungrae ~
Enthusiasm
Even though we may be comedians, but we
still have to finish saying our lines quickly.
It will not do if you say it too slowly.
You must also show some expressions.
Yeongu, your father's health
has not been good recently.
Okay
The bamboo sword.
Makes a loud 'jang jang' sound.
It just makes loud sounds,
it doesn't hurt anyone.
Candidate selection day
Practicing the coach scene
It's like a Yeongu academy.
Yeongu and Daengchiri II
Yeongu using his rubber slippers
to fight off the bad guys scene
And the last stage is...?
Drum sound from afar III
Bamboo up, turn left.
(1) Turn left and walk forward
Forward ~
Ah, wait a minute.
(2) It hurts so a request
to change places
I want to go behind.
You don't want to be hit?
Now turn to your right.
(3) After which there is a turn
to the right and again forward
This is how you do it.
We got it.
What am I going to say if
you can't even get this right.
Hit lightly.
Whisper
Right, lift up your bamboo sword.
You'll only meet Hyungrae
hyung once, but me ...
Awkward
Turn left ... Ready, action.
Hit ~
Kwangsoo is obviously not hitting
Flinch
Playing mind tricks...
Sukjin's sprayed with water
You have to hit properly.
Get out.
Give less, gain more
Big Nose's threat towards Kwangsoo
You have to hit properly.
Let me do it.
You must perform well
and show the others.
Sauce-nim, I shall take over.
* In Korean sauce and supervisor sounds similar
Not sauce, but supervisor.
Supervisor.
Supervisor, I'm over at this side, right?
Big Nose request to change roles
I'll be at this side.
Okay, then you shall stand over there.
Yes, I understand.
Okay, pick up your
bamboo swords ...
... and turn right.
That's right...
Hit ~
Doesn't matter which side
the bamboo sword depends on fate
I said the wrong thing, I'm
standing on the other side.
Supervisor, he moved to the other side.
Turn around.
Hit ~
I understand, I totally understand.
The brain needs to know
how to use a person.
From first act to sixth act, the
time restriction is 3 minutes.
Finally
challenge
time
You get 5 chances.
They must succeed within 5 tries
in 3 minutes from act 1 to 6
If we succeed, we get Running Balls.
If in 5 chances we cannot
finish within 3 minutes ...
... then it's sunbae who gets a Running Ball.
Okay.
Okay, fighting.
Catching up with Hyungrae
First attempt
Actor microphone testing ... Ah ah.
Ready, action.
Challenger: Jaesuk
Drum sound from afar I
All these rascals, not
even one of them are up.
I should hit the drum
to make them wake up.
Too fast, he's nervous again.
Impatient as well as being nervous?
He seems like a rookie.
Again, more power.
Who was it?
Good, continue.
Seems like Director
Hyungrae's satisfied?
What are you doing now?
Looks like he forgot...
Why aren't you doing it?
Why did you stop?
Right now, there are so
many cameras filming.
Once again attacks the
innocent cameramen
Please start again.
Has he become a
master of defense?
Wow, you're good at defending.
Of course it doesn't work...
a 2nd time
Seriously.
1st challenge
Fail
Catching up with Hyungrae
Second attempt
Ready, action.
These little ones, you sleep on
whenever I don't wake you up.
I shall hit the drum several
times so they will wake up.
Improved acting?
Who was it?
He'll pass after looking
back one more time
Looks so scary.
If I do it slowly then I will know
who is hitting me from behind.
I know, my angle must be lower.
Good ~
First act
What am I?
My eyes are in front of my face.
Drum sound from afar II
Challenger: Kwangsoo
Didn't find the drum...
Disoriented
What am I? It was right in front of him.
Sorry ~
Sorry.
Do it well.
I'll do it well this time.
Catching up with Hyungrae
Third attempt
Jaesuk
succeeds
Stage 2 ~
Kwangsoo
Extremely nervous
Where is
the drum
Silent
Crashes Success
Oh, he did well.
Stage 2
pass
Yeongu and Daengchiri
Challengers: Joongki & Jongkook
No matter what, please be healthy.
Cut ~
NG because of
Joongki's acting?
You said it too fluently.
I thought it was Jang Dongun's acting.
You must act as stupid.
You can't pretend to be handsome.
I wasn't trying to act handsome.
Again ~
2 more chances left
Fighting ~
We're really dead if we can't do it this time.
We will succeed, hyung.
Catching up with Hyungrae
Fourth attempt
Joongki & Jongkook tries again
Father ...
What's it, Yeongu?
Development?
A father who really does
seem more stupid than before
Your son will bow to you.
Okay, continue.
Please remain healthy no matter what.
Whether giving ...
... or receiving
Your son will bow to you now.
Wobble
Perfect?
Yeongu father and son ritual
We're the seeds of tomorrow
Challengers: HaHa & Jihyo
Let me teach you what
fighting really is today.
Doing well
The best out of all the
challengers
I won't take a beating.
Not treasuring their bodies
Stage 4 challengers Jihyo, HaHa
With all her might
You did well.
Like they were taught Good comedy
Clean cut stage 4
Success
Sorry~
Okay, next.
Sign of success?
It's already stage 5
Yeongu and Daengchiri
Challengers: Gary & Lizzy
I am leaving.
The key point is to catch
the shoe in one try
Caught it
Finally
stage 6
Drum sound from afar III
Challengers: Jaesuk & Sukjin
Pick up sword, turn left.
Forward ~
I'll go to the back, alright?
Say it clearer, clearer.
I only wanted to speak
a bit more Yeongu-like.
Unclear pronunciation
Just say your lines properly.
Sunbae has said this before.
I swear I'm not lying.
Do it again, I'll let you go this time.
Ah, we're nearly succeeding.
Pick you sword up.
Turn left.
Clear
Forward ~
This time you were too clear.
NG, NG again.
Sign of success
slow fading away...
Why NG?
Turn left ...
Then what?
Pick up the sword and then say
"Turn left", it should be like that.
Turn left, like that?
Turn left, just say it like this.
Turn left and turn left,
what is the difference?
I don't see the difference.
It's a subtle difference.
I say it like this.
Don't talk so much, just act.
Now hurry up.
Ah, seriously.
We had almost succeeded.
...because of subtle(?)
pronunciation
Fail
It's our last try.
It's your last chance, just try your best.
Do well ~
Consciously touched by a shoe(?)
1, 2, 3, fighting.
Last chance to obtain Running Balls
Do well this time.
We've come so far, so if we don't
get Running balls we're all dead.
Success depends on this round
then 9 of them can get Running Balls
If they fail
only Shim Hyungrae gets it
Catching up
with Hyungrae
Last challenge
Okay, do it well.
Ah these guys, it's already so
late and they're still sleeping.
Let me hit the drum to wake them up.
Nearly automatic
He seems to be doing better then me.
Who was it?
Who?
Unrelaxed facial expression
Wait a minute ...
If I stand up while hitting the drum
then the person hit me from behind.
I shall try bending my
knees while hitting it.
Please just
this one time
Dangerously
Stage 1
Pass
Let me off I got hit 6 times.
I've suffered from beatings
throughout my whole life.
Kwangsoo
Now he only needs to find the drum
Oh, not bad.
Faster.
Stage 2
Pass
Do it in a breath.
Father.
Yes, Yeongu.
I'm here to say goodbye.
The two have become Yeongu's spin-offs
Please live well.
Totally
immersed
Live ... a long life.
Totally excited
Stage 3
Pass
Good ~
I'll teach you how to fight.
Jihyo & HaHa
Ah, good.
Starting to get on well
Blank Jihyo and fighting master Haroro
I won't take a beating.
Not bad
Pow
Bang
Zock
Good ~
Stage 4
Pass
You villain ...
Lizzy & Gary
Really Yeongu's student?
Hold it in ~
Oh, good ~
Stage 5
Pass
Do this part well.
Last challenge
Last stage 6
Pick up your sword.
Pronouncing 'Turn left' properly is the key
Turn left ...
Forward ~
Half of it done...
I want to go to the back.
Okay, you'll be behind.
Will they really succeed
if they do it like this?
Turn to the right.
Forward ~
Wait a moment.
What's wrong?
Don't you know where you're wrong?
Which part is wrong?
Here ...
It's not so unclear like this.
Take a good look at
what Jaesuk's doing.
What is this?
Take a good look.
Hold the bamboo sword.
Excuse me ...
Sunbaenim, which part did I do wrong?
Fierce protest
Shim sunbae ~
Tap
Also comical inside here
Which is the part was done differently?
Director Shim ...
You keep criticizing me from the start.
The camera director
also suffers for nothing
Which part did I do wrong? Wasn't it the same?
Not listening at all
Did they fail?
No, just that part. Try again.
If you feel it's not awkward
after watching it then clap.
If you feel it's awkward, don't clap.
I won't be the judge.
However, the decision is still ...
So noisy ~
Teachings even the PD can't avoid
He's been sitting there nagging
the whole time since the start.
Hyung is just like the chief now.
St-tart ...
The non-stop body gags that
is incorporated into his life
Give the Running Ball to him.
Giving up
First time in history
The Running Men who always
fight to the end are giving up?
Really, I can't live anymore.
Give it to him.
Just give it to him like that.
I don't want it.
No way ~
I'm begging you,
please accept it.
I'm begging you, accept it.
Pleading
Smile~
<1:9 challenge>
Shim Hyungrae
Wins
I'm taking the Running Ball~
diririr diririr~
Come, let's set a plan of attack.
If you don't want to be caught
then go to Yong Pyeong.
That...
that sort of strategy...
Then, I'll hide in Daegwanryeon.
Oh ... it's here.
Instructions arrive
Mission Team's
Find the four snowmen with gold
medals hidden within the ski resort
On the other side...
On one side of the vast ski resort...
Opening their eyes wide
All of them ~
The Commander coolly snowboards down
Who wouldn't escape from this imposing figure
Haroro and Kwangsoo treat
the snowboard as bobsled...
We're finished ~
Hit the brakes.
Crash
Mission Start
Comes out from building
Mission
Team
Bear with it for awhile and
look for the gold medals.
There ~
HaHa:
What's this...
just came out...!
Stop right there!
Commander
Jongkook
Stop right there!
Scared out of their minds
Jongkook's coming.
Yooruce Willis and Lizzy
Returning to the building
How can it be when we
just came out and ...
Bell sounds...
Thump
If they're discovered now...
they don't have anywhere to escape
Zoom~!
Why did Big Nose come here
too suddenly of all places...!
Sit down ~
Why must you come here?
It's me
Just laughing at
each other like this
I was following Sukjin and
suddenly there's 3 people.
Why must you lead Jongkook here?
Really ...
How would I know?
Jaesuk and Lizzy
you two leave
Really?
Then we'll just go first, thank you.
We could originally have
hidden perfectly well.
I know ~
This is not allowed originally.
You stay there quietly.
Yooruce Willis and Lizzy
Leave here together happily
Hyunwoo ...
* Hyunwoo = Sukjin's son
... today dad has nothing to say.
Since it's like this, I will give you a
chance at something like wrestling.
To give father Sukjin a cool image
since his son is watching at home
You give me a push.
This punk.
Hyunwoo's tough father...!
Where are you going?
Big Nose hyung
wants to escape stealthily
In front of the Commander...
there's no way out...
Rip !!!
Only 2 minutes have passed, 2 minutes.
Sukjin
What is Hyungrae doing
with the staff's clothes?
Kwangsoo just happens to be in front...
Just passed like this...!
Kwangsoo just ran past and
didn't even notice I'm here.
Proud
The perfect dress-up act.
Praising himself
The helicopter, helicam, is flying really well.
Steadily admiring the helicam
The camera in the helicopter
model is a filming equipment
That, I've also operated it before.
It's not an easy thing to do, helicam.
Roughly how many years operating
experience must you have for that?
Didn't hear
How many years of operating
experience must you have for it?
Even laughing after getting hit
by Hyungrae's amazing bamboo sword
How do you do?
Meanwhile in the building...
HaHa starting the movie game early
...But what is this...?
Scene from the movie <Minority Report>?
Must definitely show a similar scene...?
That's settled, this is it.
No matter what Haroro sets out
Lend me the helicopter for awhile.
Completely absorbed
I want to fly.
You're too heavy, it won't do.
Why is it like this?
Kwangsoo, hurry up and
get onto the helicopter.
Not listening at all
Kwangsoo looks expectant
The two men who are suspended
from the helicopter that's taking off
I'll catch hold of you.
Kwangsoo, don't let go.
Hyung, you can't give up.
Kwangsoo ...
I just knew it'd be like this
so I prepared a parachute.
Both of them landed safely(?)
Kwangsoo, continue going straight.
Continue to move forward,
I will give you instructions.
Kwangsoo who is going
according to the instructions
Kwangsoo, continue move forward.
Yah!
The perfect dress-up act(?)
Is it hyung? It can't be.
Chasing Team being chased
Isn't that Hyungrae hyung?
Other than him who
else would be like this
Hit a few more times.
Haroro
hid from Hyungrae and runs back
Left behind
Don't leave me behind
Don't leave me.
Hyungrae hyung's chasing me now
Noooo ...
Shocked
What are you
doing now?
When he's holding the bamboo sword
Even the Commander can't catch him
That, someone's going to come up.
Chasing Team gave up on catching Hyungrae
All three of them are outdoors.
The people indoors can
relax and search boldly.
Where are the four gold medals?
As expected
Mission
Team's
ace is Jihyo
1 out of 4
Gold medal found
Lizzy walks into the ski rental shop
Over here a gold medal
2 out of 4
Gold medals found
Hyung-nim
What?
You can't be like this.
Why?
I wanted you to try to catch me earlier.
Do you want to work with me?
A sudden alliance?
Let's work together.
Work with me?
Yeah.
Haroro wants Hyungrae to betray
We work together and betray our own teams.
Must I reveal my team members' positions?
Then I will gather them all to where I am.
Huh!
So...
So easily tricked...!
Really?
Then to make it more fun ...
... shall we change name-tags?
Scheming
That's not bad too.
Okay ~
Innocent
...Aigoo...
Let's exchange our name-tags.
Yah ... !!!
Let's exchange name-tags.
Back-stabbed
Hyungrae
Time left
Yooruce Willis
heading to the tip of the slop
Ah, so tiring.
Gary comes along
Yah, Kang Gary.
Commander
Jongkook
Kang Gary!
What?
Kim Jongkook.
The Commander
following exclusively...
The two of you, wait up.
This is not good.
Uneasy
Yah, faster.
You wait.
Hey, Kim Jongkook ...
... don't catch us already.
Don't you ever get tired?
Hey Jongkook ...
... this is the first time in 10
years that I've come to ski.
I can't ski properly if
you keep chasing me.
I will definitely catch you.
Nowhere to escape
Let's just go together
before reaching the summit
Cable car
finally reaches the summit
He's getting down.
Yooruce Willis and Gary
gets off first in front of him
Wait for me.
To find the gold medals
they have to get down
Due to anxiety the sky shoes
are no able to get a fixed grip
Wait ~
Gary
escapes successfully
Commander  finally arrives
Yooruce Willis
heads out in panic mood
Calm down, Jongkook calm down.
Why is it coming off?
Suddenly~
Ski shoes sizes weren't right in the first place
Good thing ~
Yooruce Willis
heads out after putting them on again
Yoo Jaesuk ...
Commander
is coming
Yoo Jaesuk ...
Yooruce Willis
Such a frightening skiing experience
Everlasting moment...
on the ski slope...
Wait ...
Both of them are speeding down fast
From the looks of it Yooruce Willis
has a high chance of escaping
Kyaaa~!
Already waiting(?) Kwangsoo...!
You ~
Startled
HaHa in front of the cable cars
3 way siege
Chasing Team had the whole area surrounded
Absurd
Tightly~
How on earth can I be caught by
the two of you, this is injustice.
Jaesuk
Time left
Joongki has been hiding well all this time
Arrives at the outdoor slide
Hmm??
Noona ...
Third gold medal
Yes, found it.
3 out of 4
Gold medals found
They only need to find one more to win
Ring~
Crashes
Flat on
the ground
Ace Jihyo just like that Useless?
How did you fall?
You run first, I'll distract him.
Haroro chases Joongki
Run away quickly.
Donghoon hyung ...
Who are you always looking for help.
Evil Jihyo appears
Donghoon hyung ...
No use crying for help, there's nobody.
Meeting Evil Jihyo
Fighting against her isn't easy
Evil Jihyo
using such a method at her pleasure
Fighting spirit that turns the tables
How can there be such a person.
You are from the mission team,
I'm the one on the chasing team.
Suddenly...!
I'm going to be serious now.
First target is
Same-age Joongki
Weak-looking Kwangsoo
suddenly chases til his death
Kwangsoo ...
After Kwangsoo's capture
Commander puts it to an end
It's really not easy at all today.
Under Kwangsoo's whirlwind chasing
Caught by Kwangsoo Goes to prison
Joongki
Might be something inside?
On the steering wheel The last gold medal
Gary hyung, I found the last gold medal.
There's a red tractor up front.
Transmission received
Okay ...
Ring~
Of all the times now Chasing Team
Today's great leap in activity
Kwangsoo & Haroro from this side
No choice but to sit on
the cable car to escape
Hurry up ~
How many rounds do you have to turn?
Haroro leisurely takes the
car behind and chases
Gary hyung ...
I can't hear you.
Today's movie without Jongkook...
The kids are meeting as enemies
When did it start? Getting sick of our team.
Who ditched who to lead to such a situation?
Our relationship is that of eating
from the same bowl, hyung.
I only get to eat the rice
from the bottom of the bowl.
You always get to eat the rice that is warm.
Because of you ...
... the tip of my mouth became rugged.
Hyung, let's end it here.
Towards hyung, I also shared everything.
Became enemies like that
deep down in their hearts
Kim Jongkook and the kids
he cares about the 2 more than anyone else
The kids who believe that
they'll be together forever
But scars started to develop
because of one lady...
Jihyo run.
Words of jealousy and misunderstanding...
separated the kids...
Hyung, go to Hawaii.
You just go like that, go back down.
Haroro ...
Affectionate verse...
Haroro, turn back now.
Highest level of scripting is utlising the verse
Two Kids reached the summit
Don't continue this anymore.
Spilled out all their
misunderstandings but...
Hyung, how can you do this to me.
This is a showdown between men
Pow
I'm so hurt and it's cold, very cold.
So cold ~
Frozen
It's better if you give me the
name-tag or I won't be nice.
Showdown between men
before one of them faints...!
It won't end until he
humbly kneels down or the final surrender...!
Gary oppa is running towards here.
Hurry ~
Final showdown arrives...
I, know too...
From the looks of it
the whole chasing team will run towards here
However...
That lady is watching, I can't get caught...!
Inside the tractor...
The last gold medal in sight
The Commander is hunting for prey
Nooooo ... !!!
This is the ending of the
showdown between men
We used to have such
good times together.
We are seumdwa.
Let me go first.
Two kids reunite under the arms of Jongkook
We used to be so good together.
How did we end up like
that? It's all Jihyo's fault.
It's because you were
always protecting Jihyo.
Because of a woman
friendship between men is torn apart
But Jihyo she loves you.
That is something we
can't do anything about.
You little rascals do you have
to do this all for one woman!
No, hyung it's not like that.
Do the both of you want a teaching from me?
Grip
Commander Kook removed
all the misunderstandings
Is family or women more important?
Then what about me?
What am I to all of you?
You're nothing.
Bang
What am I to all of you?
You're nothing
I did really well...
why only to the kids...!
Both of you stop fighting, don't ~
quarrel because of a woman.
Getting dizzy
All of you are the same.
Nobody cares about my feelings.
Mission Team's
all members
Chasing Team wins
Jaesuk * Gary * Lizzy
Has 0 Running Balls Punishment confirmed
Today's
punishment
In hope for 2018 Pyongyang Winter Olympic
Skiing in hot pants
Wishing Pyongyang’s bidding of
2018 Winter Olympics a success.
Waddle~
Set off
Bare legs feeling the
harsh winter cold
For Pyongyang Winter Olympics ... Ahhh ...
Not fearing the cold
and wishing for
Pyongyang Winter Olympics
Running
Man
Ah, so cold.
It's Jaesuk oppa.
Pyongyang Winter Olympic Wash Flag
Jaesuk firmly holding it in his
hand while coming down
Moved
Pyongyang fighting ~
With bare legs
skiing on the snow field
At such a time
he can't feel the cold
Running Man
2018 Pyongyang Winter Olympics
Fighting