Timing and Subtitles brought to you by the Don't Walk, Run team @ Viki
Hello Running Man! This is Kim Yuna.
[Today's Landmark! Guided by the Queen of the Ice Rink, Kim Yuna]
I will be cheering for everyone so please do your best! Fighting!
[The No.1 Landmark that symbolizes Seoul]
[Namsan Seoul Tower]
[This time the whole Seoul Tower has become the stage!]
[Taking place at the highest place in Seoul will be a]
[breathtaking game and chase!]
[Today the master of Seoul Tower will be born!]
[God has helped me...]
[Yoowillis's Die Hard 2 starts right now]
-Ah~ we have gathered again today. [The Running Man Team have gathered today at Seoul Tower's fountain]
Are you wearing a wig?
Looks like you are wearing a wig.
-I'm really feeling betrayed right now [The new hair style looks like a wig...]
Before we started recording he told me "your hair style suits you" and now as soon as we get here he says
that it looks like a wig. [As soon the recording starts he changes]
Hey Gary, is your hair not going to grow?
I only go to the salon when I have a recording
But what's surprising is that a lot of kids kept on chanting 'Gary Gary'.
[Rising Star Gary] Gary must be really hot now~
A lot of people are encouraging us that we are finding our groove
We need to work hard. We want to hear that we're fun to watch.
Yes~ Sukjin always says that your own shows are boring.
I saw it three times.
I skip the parts that I come out in
Why?
[Someone is walking towards them...]
[expectant]
[Seems short]
[The Gag world's jack of all trades, Kim Shin Young]
[Welcome]
Are you joining us again today?
-Yes! -Have you seen the show before?
It looks really hard.
After looking around, the most beautiful person here is Song Joong Ki.
[As expected, Flower Joong Ki]
-Even though a woman guest came today...-But our Shin Young looks so nice today!
Ah, for today in order to raise the number of viewers I've boldly worn shorts.
[Proud Showcasing]
[While they are laughing and chatting...]
[Long legs are coming...]
[The girl who without fail shakes the hearts of the guys]
[Queen of the Music world, Son Dam Bi]
[Welcome]
[The reaction is different~]
[a totally different atmosphere than before]
Nice to meet you.
What are you doing? Why are you like that?
-We need to welcome her! -Well, you can do that with words too.
These days everyone is calling her the queen.
[Her popularity as the queen is outstanding]
Kwangsoo have you met Son Dam Bi?
- Nice to meet you. -We've met each other before do you remember?
[She doesn't know...] - When did we?
I see... I will work hard to show you a good side of myself.
All of a sudden, he says he will do his best. [Today from the start hardworking, Kwangsoo]
[Their walk is not typical...]
[After 3 years, he's back!]
[Worldstar Se7en]
Se7en!! When did you come back?
[Suddenly acting close]
You should have given us a call!
Why would he contact you?
No~ I used to be so close with Se7en in the days~
[After 3 years, his first appearance on Variety Show] Hello, it's been a really long time that I'm greeting everyone again. I've come back with my new album Digital Bounce. My name is Se7en, it's very nice to meet you.
Wow~ [New- Hitting the chart's #1 spot right after being released- Digital Bounce]
123456, It's Se7en
[Old style Name gag...]
Was it too out dated?
The sides have already been split naturally.
-Do you want to split up the teams like we did last week? [Just like last week? Winners vs. Losers]
-Okay, let's do that. -We were so close last time.
[Jongkook, Haha, Joongki, Gary vs. Jaesuk, Sukjin, Kwangsoo]
[On the other hand this team looks too weak]
[Regret. I must have been out of my mind when I said that]
This team is too weak!
I'm sorry but...
Give Se7en to our team.
Because over there you have Joongki.
You need to give us Dongwook (Se7en).
Does my opinion not count?
Then, let's go with Se7en's decision.
This time, since this team said that it lost last week.
I'm going to try and become your team's strength.
[Giving strength to the weaker team, Se7en]  -12345 Se7en
[Now they have to go up to Seoul Tower]
One team has to use the stairs.
-The stairs? - How many stairs are there?
About 1km of stairs.
And the other team will take a bus to the top!
I feel like if we ride the bus, it'll be weird... let's take the stairs.
-We have to choose well from the beginning -We might not be riding the bus, but pushing the bus up.
It could happen.
Mission~ Find the Running Man. The Team who does first will win a big prize. While you are on your way to today's mission place Seoul Tower find the Running Man. They are wearing Running Man tennis shoes and the code phrase is "Hambaya~~ Hambaya~~ RU RM?"
See, if you ride the bus you can't find them.
[You can see Seoul's scenery in one look, Seoul Tower landmark]
[A green space within the city.]
[Where citizens go to rest]
[Today Runningman is visiting Seoul Tower]
[Soin Team is riding the bus without suspicion...]
[It's going and going~]
[In the blink of an eye, they have arrived at Seoul Tower]
Wow, it's the tower!
It's my first time seeing it up close!
Lots of things have been filmed here. [Now they are hunkering down to find the Runningman]
-Hello~! [As soon as the running man arrive...]
[Crowded full of citizens]
Everybody, all together.
[They are welcomed heartily]
What about that place? [Finally they've arrived at the PalKakjung]
-Find them, find them! [Will Runningman really be in this place?]
They are wearing tennis shoes!
[Search Search! The one wearing tennis shoes...]
-Hello -It's really hard to find them!
[A lot of people are here tonight at Seoul Tower]
[This place is where the Runningman is at!]
[But their only hint is that they are wearing tennis shoes!]
That person might be running around somewhere, is there a place to do that here?
Huh?
-Hello [A citizen who keeps on staring at the Soin Team]
[Trying the Mission Straightaway] -Are you the runningman?
No, I'm not!
Can you give me some of your snack behind your back?
Why are you taking away the crackers from a citizen?
[After walking, she's hungry Shin Young] -I'll buy you some, let's go. Hold on.
I'm sorry sir.
[Citizens are flocking more and more to the PalKookJung, is the runningman citizen here somewhere?]
- Let's find someone who isn't staring at us. -That's right, we need to find someone who is avoiding us.
[Everyone is staring] -We need to move around.
Hyung, you keep all these people captive here.
I think they're here somewhere.
Everyone, Kim Jong Kook is going to sing a song for us!
[We will do anythign to find the Runningman!] [Passionate!]
[Excited.]
Find them, find them!
Please sing quickly!
Hold on, at least one of you guys need to stay by my side. Joongki come here.
Start~~
There was a man,
who loved you so much
Let's wave together.
There is a man who couldn't say that he loved you.
By your side~
-Running man? -No~
[Where could the running man be?]
They are definitely somewhere close!
- I am there~ -Wow! So cool!
Please love runningman a lot!
We are looking for the runningman
I don't think that they are in this crowd, but probably close by! Could you guys look for them with us?
[Will runningman be amongst them?]
That you are curious?
Inside of their t-shirt,
there should be something that says they are the runningman
Thank you!
[We will find them for you quickly!]
The Daein team has just arrived]
-See I said let's ride the bus~
[As usual, nagging and talking]
-Oh! they must be looking overthere.
Hey let's go, let's go!
Oh they're here! [The other team has sighted the arrival of the Daein team]
Here, here!
[They are rushed and looking straightaway]
let's find them!
Hello, hello!
Ah, there's so much more poeple than we expected
Yoo Jae Suk just took all the people with him
Hello~! [Ooorooroo~ following]
Hello! Hello!
[What is this... He is like a politician...]
Mother, Hambaya~ Hambaya~
Are you the runningman, mother?
You are not?
[it's even hard to move in this situation] -Ah, I am looking for the runningman right now, mother!
Ah, hello!!
[But...]
[The one person who is moving around so freely during this time...]
[No body has realized who he is...]
[Myself, alone...]
[While it seems crazy around the others...]
I alone am free
Who am I? Where is this?
The only person who recognizes Kang Gary who lives in Jamshil
is light of the Seoul Tower
Hambaya~~ Hambaya~~~ [They are still searching for runningman]
Are you the runningman?
Running man?
[Frustrated]
[Is it this person who is wearing sneakers?]
Hambaya~ Hambaya~ are you runningman?
[where are they?]
is the running man not here?
Please spread your light over here, just towards their feet!
He's wearing tennis shoes is their only hint!
They are focused and searching, but...
Still, there is one person who is so relaxed amongst the citizens
First, we need to find people who are avoiding us or aren't greeting us. [Brain Joongki and Muscle Jongkook's Tracking Point]
they are either sitting or~
[Overwhelmed]
Then!!! One person who is trying to avoid them while passing by
Then!!! One person who is trying to avoid them while passing by.
[Now run!]
Excuse me, hold on a second please.
Start. Hambaya~ Hambaya~ are you the running man?
Are you the running man?
[What will the conclusion be?]
Yes I am!
[They found the Runningman!]
Thank you so much!
[They hand a Running ball to the runningman members] We found it!!!
Donghoon (Haha)!! We found it!
Where? Where?
Elated vs. Defeated
What will we do?!
[Regret...]
I told you we needed to find it fast!
They said they found it already!
[The first reveal of the runningball~!]
Running Man Ball.
-1 2 3! We found it!
[The team that wins the mission will receive a Running Ball.]
[Inside contains a ball that is the color of the winning team]
[Collect the Running Balls that are won after every mission in order to escape]
[What is the escape secret that the Running Balls are hiding?].
[Entering like a general back from a battle.]
[Jaesuk is again suddenly at Gary's side]
-Ahhh! Why are you doin this?
My colleague has found it, so I'm just celebrating as well
Please let me know before hand please!
They found something great.
It's the runningman ball.
[Soin team has got 1 Runningball]
Is there something inside? -I don't know. -Try opening it.
What's wrong?
-Oh, this is pretty heavy.
[Inside there is a ball that is the same color as the winning team]
Is it cream?
Is it cream? - No, it's a ball!
-I think it's our team's ball. [If you succeed at the mission, you will be given a ball of your team's color
Even though there were lots of balls, you just took this one that's your color?
[Surprise!]
-What's going on?
[Entrance Blocked]
Hello, Runningman! It's Kim Yuna
Hello, Runningman! It's Kim Yuna.
Figure Queen, Kim Yuna
Everyone, before you complete all of the missions you are not allowed to leave this place.
[Even if possible, you can not black Miss Yuna. Careful careful.]
Runningman members, I'm cheering you on! Please run hard!
[Sucked in]
YooJaesuk obba fighting!
[touched] Fighting!
[Why did the figure queen only cheer for YJS?!]
I personally know her~
She did a commercial with me twice.
yes? -I'm jealous~
I'm jealous~
We are all running hard, but why did she say that only to you? -Yes, we all are! But
she is just saying that she has great expectations for me today. So I need to win!
[Exactly what are you trying to say?]
I saw the punishment a little bit earlier today. Did you see it?
The losing team
[worried] I will let you know beforehand
no brushing your teeth,
no showering,
in your sweat just as you are
you need to take public transportation for your ride home
but my house... is in Anyang...
How many times do you need to change buses from Namsan to Anyang?!
I definitely have to win today!!
Where is your house Kwangsoo?
I'm in NamYangJoo...
[A distance that is not too far from Anyang!]
We can just go like this... Also let's also add another things on the line.
Let's paint on each other's faces.
Sounds good!
Just a litte
no waterpainting
[then something that won't erase?!]
[Forget all of the punishments before[
[Riding public transportation with something drawn on your face]
[The citizens are staring]
-Are you really a celebrity/
[which team will be the one who has to do the punishment tomorrow morning?]
Anywho, everyone has agreed to the punishment right?
Let's say next week that our team loses. Then I'm going to go to your team Jongkook.
I have a punishment I want to give to you.
Biceps 28
This?!
[Totally suits him]
While wearing that costume
Oh really?! Then me too I have one for you.
What? -I'm going to think of one and come.
I'm just saying that if we do win...
[worried] I really do want to lose once to see that.
No, we need to win!
There's the next one. Terminator
when he's kneeling
[Terminator's final pose[
If it's the terminator then...
this pose?!?!
...
I have so many ideas!
If he has to do the terminator pose, all the way to his house
in that pose!
you...
[In a while, don't miss the arrival of Judgement Day...]
This is the first mission.
Can tower race! -Alright then.
Everyone, let's start the first mission.
[they are rearing togo]
since the punishment is fresh in our minds we have a lot of strength.
Let me explain the game quickly
today, we are at the Seoul Tower
since it's very tall
We need to put those cans on your feet
and you need to cross these barriers, pick up the Seoul Tower and then return
Kwansoo vs. Haha
It's okay~ Have a go! [Shortest vs. Tallest]
[After he gets on top of the cans, their heights are similar]
It's similar!
-you are still not taller than him!
[First they have to secure the can to their shoes]
Make it tight, tight!
Yes will do!
Kwangsoo we trust yoU!
Okay, let's go!
[1, 2, 1, 2]
[Haha, the difference in leg length is a bit...]
Ready, set...
why does he look so awkward no matter what he does?
Ready, set, go.
Fighting! [Start]
[Cheating, going around the hurdles]
Where are you going?!
[In that time, Haha has already cleared the two barriers]
[Calmly collecting the Cans]
[Now all he has to do is pick up the tower] -hold on, hold on, go slowly
[Huh?]
[Too Short!]
[Kwangsoo, can he do it?]
[No matter what he does, he can't reach it]
kwangsoo, it's okay! You can just go and do it!
[The short kid Donghoonieeee]
[A tall little kid]
[He always is energetic, but
because of his height he will lose some battles]
[Today he's facing the tallest kwangsoo]
[His arms and legs won't keep up with his own mind]
[Then!]
Kwangsoo starts going again
[In a second he's past the barriers!]
Spread your legs!
[Haha, got the tower!]
[Now Haha has the advantage]
[Kwangsoo has got the tower too]
[Danger] [Falls!!]Go around it! Go around it!
[Clench! Could this be...?!]
[haha easily makes his way tot he finish line]
[no giving up!]
[Running.]
Your pants are falling off!
[It is his underwear?!]
His pants all came off!
Heyyy what are you doing??
All of a sudden it makes one awake!
Why are you enjoying this so much?
Shinyoung's sleep all flew away!
[Can't breathe]
His panties are showing, so you should have turned your head away!
Ahhh his panty!
What is this?
His but is like a peach! It just came out.
[embarrassed]
Thanks to Kwangsoo, all sleep is chased away.
SondamBi vs. Kim Shinyoung
Oops, you're not on our team!
I'm not just a guy who is hosting the games!
hehe, I thought we were on the same side for a sec
The back must be stable.[The two teams are getting ready]
[Jae Suk, is pranking around again~]
[Target...?! Gary of course.]
[Using the tape as a bucket tail.]
[Gary, completely focused on the game.]Wow, this is the best.
I quit![I had it!]
What is the meaning of this Jae Suk?
[I won't stop until I get caught~]
-Joong Ki-Yeah?-Don't be so good to me.
Do you want to make flowers bloom?[Joong Ki, is the only one who treats Shin Young well.]
Joong Ki, you have to be responsible until the very end.
- Actually, I am your fan, Noona.  - Oh, really?
What are you doing? [Why Jae Suk kneels in front of Shin Young?!]
Confession?!
-It's a misunderstanding, a misunderstanding.-Even though we are not on the same team, you have to treat the other team well too.
[Bends down.]I'm looking forwards to this.
Ah, what's up with today? Dam Bi, I am popular.
[...]There is no use of just having a pretty face.
Later, later.
Okay, I understand.  [Accident(?) Extremely Popular, Shin Young.]
Is everything ready?
Set, Start.
Woah! Good job! Good! [Oh~ Dam Bi accelerates forwards.]
Joong Ki, you can't help her.[Joong Ki, hold's Shin Young's hand?]
Take it slow! Take it slow![Dam Bi already reached the turning point.]
What are you doing? [Shin Young suddenly going toward Dam Bi?!]
You're doing it on purpose!
Hold on it! That's right, just like that![So close!]
[Shin Young shamelessly steal from Dam Bi!]
Bite her! Bite her! [Bite her! Can you bite!(?)]
[Shin Young got a grip on Dam Bi's tower!]
It's against the rule! [The brutal community!]
- She really bite me.  - Bite her harder!
[Shine Young really bites!!]
Dam Bi, don't give up! Don't give up![Does Shin Young thought Dam Bi's arm is her midnight feast?!]
You can't do that!
[Shin Young throws away Dam Bi's tower.]
[It's all start over again!]
-Push her! -No![Variety shows are scary...]
She got me!
[She got her?... Where...?]My belly!
[Belly!?]
[The battle between the two same-age friends.]
[Dam Bi got the tower again.] Let go, let go.
[After she let go, Run away!]
Slow down!
So tired. [Dam Bi is back from the battle]
It's enough, Shin Young![Shin Young's fate is to lose the game...]
My stomach hurts.[Joong Ki is helping, even thought they're already lost.]
It's my first time seeing Shin Young's stomach got squeezed.
My stomach hurts.[2nd Round: Dam Bi wins, Adult Team 1:1 Child Team]
Dam Bi...
This is the important of the game. [Playing game under this circumstance...]
Because of the steel tower! [The tower made out of steel...!]
This is the spirit of the game.
Not a bad game! My arms aren't long enough![Shin Young imitates Mo Pal Mo.]
So tall!
- You should try to wear high heels sometime.- This is Number 28. [Introducing Muscle Number 28!]
[shove]
Are you---
- I'm still alive. - He's still alive.
My stomach hurts from laughing.
The atmosphere was the same as when Hyori and Jung Eum were fighting.
Good job![In the end, both team got the same point!]
Next, we have Seven and Joong Ki! [The last battle between the Aces: Seven vs Joong Ki]
- I will do my best.- Don't be too confident.
What are you guys doing over there?
Dam Bi, what are you guys doing?
Dam Bi, what are you doing?[Trying to pull off the bucket.]
- How did you do that?  - Oh, I'm sorry.
[The other one too...]
- Is this magic trick?- No, it's not.
It hurts. [Pull! Pull!]
[The bucket stuck deep inside...]One, two, three
It's not there.[She's just lying down.]
[Everyone is helping... Pop!]
[huh?]
[Chaos Bruce]
- Why do you always wear those type of underwear?- I can see his panties!
[Watch out for your pink panties, Kwang Soo]
This is too funny. [Ha!]
[Kwang Soo is helping Jae Suk, but his foot...]
[Kwang Soo, today is not your day.]
I'm so sorry.
But... Seven hyung just made his comeback after 3 years, is it okay for me to win?
- I can win as well, right?  - Of course.
- Ready...  - Song Joong Ki, have fun! Fighting!
I will have fun.
[Start]
[A battle between the Aces! Both members are extremely fast!]
[Seven and Joong Ki are equally doing good!]
Joong Ki!
[They collect the cans at the same time!]
[He stops after trying to go faster]
We won we won.
-We won.-We definitely won.
Joong Ki grab him!
Bite him! Bite him! Bite him!
Bite him! Bite him! Bite him! [...Huh?]
[It's like they are waltzing?]
[Don't be like this...]
[Just one song...]
[In front of a large audience, one song~]
Joong Ki!
This is not what I wanted. Wait a moment.
Wait a moment.
[Now at the finishing line...]
[Seven's two feet did not pass the line yet]
[He has not won yet!]
He didn't make it yet.
[Now Joong Ki is dragging Seven]
Good job good job!
Didn't we win yet?Where are you going?
[Now is the time to win!]
[Seven leaves Joongki and runs~]
Ah!
That's it! That's it!
[Joong Ki runs after him with all his strength]
[Daein team Seven wins!]
[Final results:Daein team 2 : 1 Soin team]
We won!
[There is a blue ball for the winning team]
Good show! There is no punishment.
This game is not fun!
This is the second mission.  [Mission #2]
[Mission 2, Find the Running Man Globes hidden within the Seoul's Tower!]
It's already 2 in the morning.
2:44 [The time is now 2:44 AM]
You are tired? [Your face looks very pale.]
But--You also look tired.
Compared to them, we look really tired.
Why that? [Instructions have arrive]
It's here?
[If you rip off two name tags from the opposing team, you will gain two hints!]
Two? From anyone?
[Hello! This is SBS Running Man! Once you rip the name tags of two people from the opposing team, there will be a hint there.]
Just any random two person? [Any two member's name tags?]
You don't who it is? [We don't know which two it is.]
[By ripping off two name tags from the opposing team, a hint about where the running balls are hidden will be given]
This location is where the opposing team has to go to.
So they're going to have to look at this.
They're going to have to see it and we're going to hide it on our backs.
Whose back should we put it on?
[Both teams don't know which members of the opposing team have the hints.]
We're here, we are finally here. Don't feel burdened hyung.
[Soin's team receives a message]
This is Running Man.
We have to choose two people.
We have to choose?
It's better for Joong Ki and I to run around so you and Shin Young can hide.
They might not think that we would put it on Shin Young's back.
And for you, I'll protect you.
I understand.
The two of your work together.
This is like a drama where you say something like "hyung you go first"
It'll be like a drama.
Touch Hyung's name tag... Like Hyung, go first! Like that.
Let'd do that next time.
-Next time?  -Next time.
I think the other team will have Seven hide the hint
because he is fast.
From what I think, it's going to be on Seven and Kwangsoo.
Then...Lets put this on Dam Bi and go with her.
They won't think that we would have put it on Dam Bi.
I will put this one on me.
Let's have a team that hides and another team that searches.
I will hide with Kwangsoo.
They will not think that Dam Bi will have the hint.
- Let's do this well. We have to win.  - Ah~ What should we do~
-You seem to like these kind of things.-It's fun~
One, two, three, fighting!
[Let's go home comfortably, Fighting!!]
[There is a number on T2 Love's Tile.]
There's a T2 Love's Tile. That's right.
-There's a phone number.-Wow, our team is so smart!
[Shin Young's hint: there is a number]
[Catch the other team and get the hint]
[Race start!]
- Doesn't this seem like we're filming a spy movie?  - It's been a long time since I've filmed a survival clip.
This is real.
This is real at 3am.
They're going up there right now.
[Soin team. Joong Ki, Gary, and Shin Young]
[In order to hide]
[Daein team moves to the 2nd floor cafe]
[Soin team follows right after them]
[In a rushed mind, they head over to the women's restroom]
I found them!
Come here.
Oh!What? What?
[They don't know who has the hint among themselves...]
Hey Seven.
Son Dam Bi has the hint!
Where are you Seven?
You're dead!
[A mess]
[Seven comes to support!]  -Ah! There's a fire! A fire!
[If Dambi gets out, the hint is taken away]
[Dambi gives her name tag to Suk Jin]
[Suk Jin runs away after taking Dambi's name tag]
Should I turn mine off?[Meanwhile, Daein team Jaesuk and Kwangsoo is...]
Turn one off, turn one off.
[They first go towards the elevator]
The observatory! The observatory!
If we get there, we'll be sure to win.
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo are going to the observatory]
- I'm so nervous now that I have to hide.  - I watched the last episode and you were pretty good at hiding though.
When I played hide and go seek when I was little,
I continued to hide even though everyone was found.
You can say that I was like a "spier" (spy + er).
[They arrive at the top of the building]
Wow...it's so pretty.
It's so pretty.
[Seoul's view is like a painting]
It's so beautiful, really. But if we really hide here, the game's over.
Kwang Soo, there's nowhere to hide.
This place won't do it.
- But if you go down and bump into them, we're over.  - It's really dangerous here.
Just in case we bump into them, don't run immediately.
Because we're the aggressive type, if I run, they're going to follow us.
As long as it's not Jong Kook, do that.
[But surprisingly...]
[Jong Kook and Jae Suk passed each other]
[He comes to the basement floor where the arcade is located]
[They find a photo booth to hide in]
Lets stay here for the time being.
If you think someone is coming,
When there's a feeling of someone coming, go ahead and run away.
I got it hyung.
-Ah, so they'll think I'm hiding here alone and run after me.-That's right.
It's quiet outside.
[They are more anxious because it is so quiet]
[It's more unsettling now that it's quiet...]  - Suk Jin Hyung.
Kwang Soo, if we're both here it's strange so...
Do you want to go up and look? Contact me too.
-What about hyung? -I'll hide here for now.
Ok, I got it... but... ok.
What?
Hyung, to be honest,
I thought that you were a true spy,
but you kind of seem a little cowardly.
It's not that.
[Still, in the end]
[To not look cowardly, they both head outside]
That surprised me.
[peek]
[They're coming!]
[What was that sound?]
[Super nervous]
[Gary and Joong Ki enters the arcade]
[Worried]
[Thump thump]
[Discovered!]  - Excuse me!
What is it?
- Why are you being like this?  - Let's fight it out, Hyung!
If you feel like someone is coming, just run away.
I got it hyung.
Go Kwangsoo! Go!
[He pretends to not have the hint]
[Will Gary and Joong Ki fall for it...?]
It's Jaesuk hyung!]
[They were not fooled]
[What the? They didn't fall for it]
[In danger]
[No!]
What's happening to me?
It's not him! It's not him! Kwang Soo!
[Jaesuk's name tag should have the hint...?]
[Jaesuk picks up his name tag]
[Joong Ki ripped off the whole thing instead of just the name tag]
Go Kwangsoo! I told you to go!]
I told you to go!
Go quickly!
Go fast!
I'm alive.
[This truth must be hidden!]
I'm alive!
I'm alive. He pulled off the clothes too.
He tore off the whole thing so he didn't see this.
[What a relief]
I'm alive.
God has helped me.
And this is how Yooris Willis survives in Die Hard 2.
[Die Hard 2. Yooris Willis survives...]
Ah, wait! Jaesuk!
Wait, wait a min!
- Wait a minute!  - It's done!
What the, he tricked us.
[What happened, Hyung-nim?]
Hyungnim, hyungnim.
I'm not just any spy.
What's happened?
[Elsewhere...]
My ears are plugged.[Shinyoung has fallen behind in the race.]
[Left behind alone]
[Heading to the top floor restaurant alone]
Oppa, you're coming to look for me, right?
[Not a single person to be with me in Seoul's wide open sky...]
Please answer me.
[I'm alone...]
[I'll hide behind the chairs...]
[Cushion...?]
[Going to sleep...]
[Shinyoungs comrades are targeting Dambi now]
No one's left but Seven.
No, no, we---
[Sukjin, Dambi, running back to the Floor 2 cafe]
[This approach!]
[If you run in a circle...of course you'll be back where you started...]
[Of course this happens..]
[Dambis moment of crisis!]
[Will Sukjin be able to protect Dambi on his own?]
I'll show you where the nametag is
We'll show you, we'll show you.
We'll show you, don't rip it.
[Sukjin grabs Dambi's nametag and bolts!]
- I'll show you. - Alright.
But this time...
Please!
[DaeIn team finds their members at the critical moment!]
[It's urgent!]
It can't be!
[Gary got it!]
[SoIn's Team has gained Dambis nametag!]
[The nametag is in JoongKi's hands.]
[SoIn team has gained 1 out of the 2 hints]
I've taken it from them
What is on the lock of love?
Who's is this? [Sukjin found SoIn teams radio!]
This is the opposing team's!
Hey, Jaesuk, get ready
He ripped mine off, but he made a mistake.
So instead of like this, he ripped it like this. He didn't see anything so he threw it away.
Shh, it's the other teams radio!
[Sabotage is possible]
Hyung, didn't we hide "we have the number"?
Do we just need the number?No, yours isn't important.
That means you know the location.
That means they've gone to the padlocks of love area
[It's right next to them]
It's here?
Love's padlock... I told you this is it.It is?
[Blue team waits in front of the padlock]
[They meet!]
[They need to gain at least one hint here]
Come over here! Haha, you've got it, don't you.
[Rip Haha's name tag!] - Long time no see, Hyung.
[Bodyguard Jong Kook protects Haha with his entire body]
[Protecting Haha with his life]
[SoIn's team is in grave danger]
[DaeIn has gained Haha's name tag]
[One of the two hinds: "At T2 Love's Tile"]
- What does it mean?  - We can just go, let's go.
What is this?-Lee Joong Ki...
They said that they had "there is a number".W
It seems like it's on Shin Young's back!
Let's just go to the T2 floor, let's go!
It's fine, it's fine!
It's going to take them a long time to find it anyway! They don't even know where it is.
[They are searching with just the hint "Love's Lock"]
It's not here.
Wait a moment.
What are we supposed to find?
It's done! It's done!
[They've arrive at T2 floor]
[What will be on the tile of love?]
The tiles of love are where you leave a message with your loved one.
It'll be a tile with a number.
[The phone # will definitely be here...]
[This place definitely has a number...]
But there has to be another hint that it's from Running Man.
It's here!
[They've found the number!]
[If they call the number, the hint regarding the Running Ball]  - Did I really just find it?
I'll memorize the 4783, the 4783
[yes, this is running man]
Search for the Running Ball at the top floor restaurant
The highest restaurant? We need to go up.
Is it this way?
They'll probably have written 'Running Man' on it. Look for a shiny new one!
I'm so glad that we met.
I love you Ami
What is it? What is it?
[They found the number!]
Phone, phone![Connecting by Phone]
It's going through
Yes this is running manYes, so are we
We are also running man.
Go to the highest restaurant and search for the Running Man Ball
What are we supposed to? She said go to the highest restaurant
[DaeIn have reached the restaurant]
[If they find it first, they win!]
Timing and Segments brought to you by The Don't Walk, Run! Team @ Viki
Hyung! Shin Young Noona is here!
- You scared me!  - We don't need her now.
No, she might have the ball.
[Shinyoung was napping from loneliness]
[They make it to the restaurant one step behind!]
[Both teams are at the restaurant? What will happen?]
[The place where the ball is hidden]
[The business card lottery box]
[The Running man ball is hidden within the business cards]
[Sliding over]
[Checking the surroundings first...]
[SoIn's team got to the running ball]
[We were here first though...]
Dambi is seriously mad right now
We couldn't find it.[On the verge of tears]
What if we end up punished at this rate?[The terror of punishment that comes with each defeat]
This will be the 3rd mission
The sun is coming up [It's getting brighter]
[Some citizens are up early to exercise]
Now there isn't much left until the punishment, everyone.
We don't know which team will be safe.
By now, we are all starting to fight against sleepiness
We can't sleep right now.[Your eyes close nonetheless]
[You need to gather your wits][
We get something to eat?The comfort of a cup of tea [That's why we've prepared something!]
Let's have a little teatime,
while we move to the next game.
We'll complete it and finish the second game after.
Is this coffee?
It's coffee. Let's start with Kim Jong Kook.
I don't know how to drink coffee.
How many spoons of coffee do you drink?
- Just one!  - Just one? Okay.
Okay, which number?
- What?  - What number would you like?
Even the ladle is here.
- Wait this is...  - So it's number 5.
- Don't be like that, don't look at it.  - Okay, okay.
- Why are you looking at it?  - I also don't know which number is which.
Number one, number one.
What number would you like?
Number two.
Okay, okay. Just wait a second.
Oh, so this was number two.
- I told you that it is number two.  - Really?
[It's incredibly funny, but Jong Kook, who's never had coffee is having all of it today]  - I'll scoop an edible amount.
What number would you like for sugar?
- Do I have to choose for sugar too?  - Of course you do.
They're all doing it? But they all know what number two is.
I'm going to change the numbers again.
[A somehow disappointed look]  - Oh, really?
- Do number five.  - Number five?
- Yeah, it's what I recommend.  - Why do you keep recommending five?
Then choose another number.
- I'll just do number five.  - Number five? Okay.
[What in the world is number five?]
[What is this?]
[An ear-picker!]  - What are you doing?
[Flustered]
It's an ear picker, an ear picker.
Seriously... Hyung.
This is like Korean medicine.
[Almost as concentrated as Korean medicine]
Okay. Shin Young, what number would you like?
- Me too?  - Of course.
- Number three.  - Okay, number three.
Number three!
This is a normal size.
- How many spoonful?  - Just one.
This is a decent size.
Okay, now for the sugar.
Number one.
[Heok! A spatula!]
[I'm done for...]
It tastes good sweet, it's fine.
Okay, now for Joong Ki, which number?
Number three.
- What is number three?  - Here itis.
This is the same as last time! You said you'd change it!
I got too into it and forgot.
He can use it, there's no time. The sun is rising.
- Gary, which number?  - Number two.
You're doing this on purpose, right?
This is really number two!
- Hurry and come!  - What do you mean?
Gary, give it to me. You said you'd do it.
- I won't be too crazy about it.  - This is just like mine.
- I got it.  - Fill it up.
[Are you on his side..?!]  - Hyung why are you doing this to me?
Okay, Haha, hurry and do it, we don't have time.Which number?
- Three, and four.  - Three and four?
[The ladle again!]  - Why are you...?
We don't have time, hurry and do it.
This is awesome.
Okay, number four?
This is four. It's true.
I'm not lying about it.
Why are you being like this?
- This coffee shop is pretty good!  - That's enough.
You're playing a game with us right now.
Okay, so can we start now?   - Go ahead.
Number three.
[The large spoon that kept appearing since earlier]
It isn't number three.
It is number three.
[ Jaeseok who kept giving his opinion from the back ]-Be reasonable.
[ Jong Gook gives a generous scoop ]
Do you want sugar?
Ah yes sugar.  Number 5.
Number five-Oh! You picked well.
Didn't you say you changed the positions?
It's number five!
That's good, that's enough.
[ Adding the sugar wouldn't make a difference ]
Okay, next Dam Bi.  -Number 4
Number 4?
[ It came out again the big ladle ]
[ It no longer has to do with the numbers ]
[ Is she going to curse again? ]  Do you want me to die?
Excuse me, Shin Young. We're at a cafe right now.
[ Seems she hasn't gotten over the trauma from the last game ] Don't be so harsh.
Are you happy with that much?
You can't drink it yet.
I don't want to drink it.
Okay, Suk Jin.
I'll choose number six.
[ The first time this number has been chosen ]
[ But it's the rice scooper again ]
You can't drink it yet.
Okay now, sugar -Number four.
[ Again... number 4? ]
[ The large ladle appears again ]
Let me see if it's actually number four!
It says it right here, number four!
I'm so tired I don't know what's going on.
What is that?!
How many servings is that?!
I'll change the numbers around.
Okay, Seven!
Excuse me, this will eventually melt at least, right?
Yes, it will melt[It's filling the cup up to here]
- It has to melt though!  - It's going to melt.
[It's going to melt some day...]  - Okay, Kwang Soo!
Please solve this for us.
What is this anyways?
[Let's get down to starting the game]
[The team that drinks fastest wins!]Maybe..whoever finishes it fastest...
[How can we chug this?!]
How can we possibly chug this?!
If I chug this...will we get a running ball?
Of course[Since there's a running ball on the line..You must finish the whole cup]
Okay let's start from Haha.
Okay, st...start!
- Hurry, hurry, hurry! - No way!
He's really drinking it...
- Put it down, put it down!  - Wow, he really drank it.
He really drank it.
He's really drinking it.
Hurry up and drink it.
Hurry up and drink it!
You're done drinking?
Is that executioners poison?
How many seconds?[Jaesuk checks that it is clean]
49 seconds!Wow we can win that!
Jae Suk, let's just say we lost.
Be sure to win, please do.
Then, it's our turn.
Start!
[Struggling]
Just what did you put in here?
[A major accident!]
What did he add in it?
38.3 seconds.
Since we complained about being sleepy and tired they feed us this kind of stuff
You could be a funny dancing ahjumma[When you're tired, you gotta move your body]
[Flustered]Even though it's 6am?
Just pretend that you just woke up...give us a cute dance![This is all to wake you up]
1,2,3,4[High Expectations]
[A impactful finish!]
[Lady of 10,000 talents, Shin Young]
There was something like this that existed?
Isn't that Yang Hyun Suk?
What are you planning on doing?
Wait, wait, Seven. Wait, just let me do it once.
- I already did it before!  - Seven hasn't seen it yet!
To do it like Hyun Suk Hyung's style, the basics of hip hop...
you have to think that there's a door in front of you. Think that you're walking out of the door.
The door...
We'll ask Se7en to show us now[Now it's Se7ens turn!]
No music, right?
- Hyun Suk Hyung does this, right?  - That's right.
That's right, that's right.
That's the way![Flowing body movements]
[With barely any effort...a luxurious wave comes out]
That's right, That's how you do it Se7en!
Show us some more!
1,2,3,4,...5,6,7!
Wow, as expected of Se7en![Definitely meeting their dance expectations]
Se7en...5,6,7...Wow
- Are you fine with it?  - Yes.
I'll do singing technique
Can't it Be~e~
They really sing like that!
It's too difficu~t~
It's funny!
[There's always one person like that at Karaoke]
It's so bri~~ight
Everyone's awake, right?
Since everyone's awake now, let's look at the sun[With the coffee and dancing, they've woken up a bit]
No matter what I'm still sleepy
Good work, Running Man.
This is the last mission.
[Final mission: One Mind One Body Badminton]
Everyone, finally we're at the last mission.
Now with this last mission,we will have our winner.
I understand everyone's stayed up all night, but you all look angry.
Everyone, it's morning. With a refreshing feeling,
and since we've come to Namsan, we have to play badminton.
What does it mean to be "one mind, one body"
- Is it like this?  So for example, if Suk Jin Hyung is next to him, his hand is placed here.
It won't come off, it won't.
Do rock paper scissors with Dambi!
No, let's do Joongki
Rock paper...
[Stutter]With Ba--Bambi?
It's not Bambi, its Dambi!
[Queen of the Singing World, Son Bambi?]
[Straight face]Night rain is something that comes at night!
It's not? It's not Bambi?[Worked up]
Bambi? Bambi? Is this morning?
Dambi! Dambi!
[Overboard]Where are you hitting me?
[Everyone's sensitive after staying up all night]
Why did you touch me?
Why are you provoking me?!
Are you crazy?[The punishment dangling in front of them is fearsome, it seems]
Dambi, watch it.
Let's get started![Start of the 1st Set]
[Kwangsoo's Serve]
That's it!
Ah!
[They took a hit!]
- Do it, just do it!  - Don't stop me, wait a second!
Stop stalling time, let's do it!
Let's finish this![What kind of badminton has no rallying?]
Go, go do it!
- Seven, hit it hard.  - It's 1 vs 0, right?
Start
Okay
That's right!
Out!
[DaeIn team hit it back but it went out of bounds]
It's only 1 vs 1, you don't have to do this.
What is that?
How can badminton be this intense?
Oy, to the healthy one over there!
What?
Let's just start!
[Regardless, no one wants the punishment!]
We can win this. [Currently at 1:1 tie]
That's it![The shuttlecock is barely in play...And again Gary goes...!]
[Daein barely returned it?]
[Far away~ ]
[Out]
[Up to 5 points - Daein 1: SoIn 2. A twist!]
[Ignore]
[Dang it.]
Let's go get the shuttlecock.What Dambi, come at me!
You can't hit me?[Well yes, as our hands are tied]
Here, do it, do it.
[Threatening]I could absolutely bite someone right now.
[Stepping back]Don't make me untie these wrists!
[Horror] Anything but that...I'll untie it, I swear!
[Tension]
[Out...?]
[IN! The score is counted!]
This isn't right!
This really isn't right!
That's just luck!
Oh... Hey!
[Surprised]
What should we do?!
Fighting!
Good!
Where do you think you're hitting?
I can't do this~
It's not what you think!
It's not like that.
I'm sad!I'm sorry, it's not like that.
[Again]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but you got hit near your neck.
What?!
Do I need to show you exactly where you hit me with my hands?
You got hit at your stomach.
Ah I'm going crazy.
Do you want to try getting hit too?
We're serving.
That friend, sigh!
This is the last.Let's have fun!If we win it's over right?
If we win it's over.I will serve.
I'm serving.
[After hitting the net, it goes over!]
[YEAH!]
If this hits over we win.  We really have to win.
[They are talking but...]
[The ball that barely crossed the net]
[WOW!]
[SoIn's team gets caught in the net; FAIL]
It got caught, yes! Match point!
[Will SoIn fall apart like this?]
Is this the end? If we end it here, it's really over.If they gain one more point, they can escape!
[It's not over yet!]
[You could say their fates are tied to this last round...]
Time! Just a moment.[Everyone holding their breath from nervousness]
They need to give us one point.
[Chaos]
[Flying high!]
[We have to receive it!]
[Please miss!]
[It's still in play!]
[Please!]
[They missed!]
But we won't. So can't we just leave?
Why? What?
I know! I know!
That will mean we win?
They're going to edit out everything except the hilarious bits anyways!
Put it in already, as quick as you can-Lets just try it.
This is driving me crazy...just toss them in
Please please please![DaeIn has 3 balls, SoIn has 2 balls in the lottery]
[The team whose ball drops out first is the winner]
-Please let us go just this once![Both teams are desperate]
[WOW]
[Which teams ball will come out?]
[The first one is a fail!]
[What?]
Its red! RED![The red ball!]
[At a loss...]
[Ceremony of Celebration]
[DaeIn lost even after gaining an extra ball]
UAHKKK
[Transformation complete]
[DaeIn team gets on the bus]
[The citizens (amazingly) recognize the crew]
[These faces are...]
[Finally the bus leaves]
Wow...seriously...[There aren't really any words...]
[And the yawns are unstoppable]
- Why are you all yawning so much?
They're getting on, more people are getting on.
Hi~![They still warmly greet them]
We didn't startle you too much, did we?[...?]
I think they'd be pretty shocked.[Are they really celebrities? (Whisper)]
[(Again) Are they really celebrities?]
You really think celebrities would walk around like this?
[It's Son Dambi!][Where?!]
Please take a seat here[Trying to give up their seats for other passengers.]
You can laugh. It's fine.
Please be happy!
We lost. That's why we look like this.
Yoo Jaesuk, you're so cool!
[He's cool?!]You should always walk around with your face like this
[It's even more embarassing after they get off the bus.]
[Commemorative photo time with the citizens]
[Poor Kwangsoo..]
I'll take the picture...1,2,3![Dutifully...]
[(Again) - Snap!]
[A different parade of new games!]
[And...]
[Hide! Flee!]
[A breathaking race far different from any before!]
[Just what do the ominous bells bring!]
[A crazy hot summer]
[But what are they doing instead of playing?]
[It begins in just a moment!]