Timing and Subtitles brought to you by the Don't Walk, Run team @ Viki
[ The Third Landmark! ]
[Night at the Museum]
[The running man team cannot believe it.]
[Huge exploration journey at the science lab.]
Running Man
[Certain sunny weather in the summer.]
[Last week, latecomer Suk Jin , first to arrive today!]Going to start this way again. Filming starts after I exit this vehicle
- It starts like this again.[Compared to others there is no such thing as outdoor variety shows]
No one has arrived yet. What to do?
Since you're here already. You might as well buy the tickets And head in first.
But, I don't have money!!!
Hello.
-Free?-Four dollars please.
But I don't have money. Sorry, But can I use my phone as a contract ?
[Using his cell phone to buy tickets?] My manager will come later.
Okay. Pass it to me.
[Grab][Taken away!]
[Contract a phone for a free and easy adult ticket.]It's a free and easy adult ticket.
- Hello! - Oh, Gary!
[A man with a huge dream and ambition, Gary.]-You came here early.-Of course, I have to do my best.
Hurry, come and take.
-Take what?-Take tickets.
-You need a ticket.-But I don't have money.[Cashless...]
-Why don't you have money? You're an idol.-Hello, how much is it?
-Free and easy ticket, 2 dollars.-How much?
-Two dollars.-Oh my ticket is four dollars. Why is his two????[Prices differ between Suk Jin and Gary]
[Cashless...]What should I do?
[Gary give his vest as collateral]
This is very expensive.
[Rap idol has done this many times.]How can you take off your vest. That's crazy.
[Still giving a happy feeling.]I contracted my phone And you used your vest.
[Third person to arrive is Jae Suk.]
-Done any exercise?-Yes.
He's wearing bright colored clothes.
So that he looks younger.
He looks younger. But he's reaching 40 soon.
Oh my You look so young!!!!!!
Yes,You look very young.
Hyung. Why have your eyes swelled up?
Yesterday, My wife and I...
[ Suk Jin looks so gloomy]
Usually, it's the woman who cries right? I cried instead.
[Suk Jin the emotional man]
It's because of that matter.
-When we were playing while wearing that hat.-Oh yeah, why did you do that?
Yes, she asked me, "Why did you do that?"
[Running man episode 1 recap.]Ten years ago,
You introduced me to my wife.
Why did you do that?
[Why did you introduce me...?]
[Why did you do that?10 years of doubt forms into 1 question.]Why did you do that?!
[This shows Suk Jin's married couple life.]
I was laughing,
thinking it was a joke.
You don't look like your joking from the way you said it.
I was pretending,
to be serious.[Wedding...scary..]
-You need a ticket.-Yeah, get a ticket.[Looks like Jae Suk also needs a ticket.]
Please give me a ticket.
-How much?-Four dollars.
-I only have two dollars.-You need to use something as a contract, hyung.-He used his vest,
And I used my cell phone.
I don't have anything to use as a collateral.
[Tall man Kwang Soo and short man Haha arrive.]-Here they are, Kwang Soo!-Yeah hyung, hello!
[Both of them look alike except for the height.]
Jong Gyuk Kook.
[Sigh...]
You are seriously uptight What should we do?
[Serious Gary in a photo collection.]-The serious look while filming.
Not to long ago, Gary said,
"Haha hyung, You need to keep telling me I don't look like an entertainer."
[Serious Gary, having an alternate personality!]
Why are you like that?
Why are you treating me this way?
"You have to constantly remind me That I look gloomy."
Please, Save me no matter what.
Do it. No matter what.
Leessang is quite hot-tempered. That's another point to be showed.
There are four to five talents to show.
So I need to improve myself!
Haha , hurry and buy your ticket Do you have two dollars?
-I don't have two dollars.-I do..
Lend me two dollars then.
-You only have two dollars?-Yes.
The tickets cost four dollars, Kwang Soo.
It's four dollars.
-See, isn't it four dollars?-Those with 2 dollars can't buy Because it's 4.
[In his kid voice]Hi!
Got it![Young Haha getting a child ticket.]
Hey, what about Kwang Soo? You already bought the ticket.["Wow, your petty, why did you take my money? ]
[Ji Hyo arrives with a bright smile.]
-Did you bring money, Ji Hyo?-I've brought nine dollars.
Wow, seriously? Lend me two dollars.
And Kwang Soo needs two dollars as well.
This is for Ji Hyo's ticket, My ticket and Kwang Soo's.
[First thing Jong Kook needs to do when he arrives is to get a ticket.]
-Joong Ki, is here!-Hi, Joong Ki!
-Hi, hi!-Joong Ki, hello!
-Just now, that's not right.-What is it?
I thought Sandara Park was here, when I was at a distance just now.
[Sandara Park from 2NE1?!]
[Joking]
Congratulations. You had a good first speech.
-It's rather funny.-We have to prepare such speeches.
Wow, Joong Ki. Not bad.
Ohhhh.Sandara Park!!!!
There won't be enough time If we play games now.
But I have to let you know That there are a few among here That like you a lot.
Some men are alike.
(Nervousness abounds)
-Haha hyung, What are you doing?-Nothing, Nothing.
-Are you tense?-I'm shocked.[Candidate #1: Haha]
[Smiling Akwardly]
Hyung!!!!!
Didn't we talk about this just now?
-Jong Kook is lonely.Jong Kook is always matched In variety shows.
[Everyone agrees. Jong Kook is worried about his dating life.]
[Candidate #2: Jong Kook]I can't be like that.
He only dates while he's on variety shows.
[Dating moments = Broadcasts moments]But it ends when the filming is done.
Hey,Jong Kook.
Look here for a while.
[Ji Hyo's and Jong Kook's eyes suddenly meet.]
[Will this couple matchmaking be successful?]
That surprised me.
[But this time!]
[Someone's on their way!]
[Who was able to change the atmosphere?]
[Those who recognize him.Sigh!!!]
It's over! It's over!
Take back everything.Take it back.
Keep your hearts. It's not possible anymore.
[Eye candy Idol finally arrives]Nichkhun!!!!
This is not possible anymore. Not possible.
[Guest for today. (Nichkhun) From 2PM]
[Impossible to match-make when Nichkhun is here.]-Not possible, next time instead.
Not possible anymore. Not possible.
Oh My Goodness.. Better luck next time.
I'm going to be a comedian for a day.
Wow, my goodness.
You're inhumane, seriously.
Gary, is so happy. He looks so funny even while standing here.
[Gary, hopeless]
-Why are you treating Gary this way?-Yes, always treat me this way, keep talking about me.
Wow, really?
Seriously very gloomy.
Keep going.
Even though we're making fun of you, you do look really gloomy.
[Gary, no distinct features but serious feelings.]
Oh, who's that?
[Light steps]
[A female this time?]
[She's walking gracefully with her long hair.]
-Jessica?-Yes!
[An idol in this generation, SNSD!]
[Today's guest, beautiful ice princess, Jessica!]
You look so calm today, Jessica!
-My shoes are not suitable.-Today is Running Man, is it alright?-Yes, hello!
Come stand over on this side.
Stand beside Ji Hyo.
-Unnie, hello!-Nichkhun get a little closer, okay?
Firstly, the tickets have been separated into adult and child.
Hold on, children stand on this side.
[Arranging themselves according to the ticket title.]
[What categories are we grouping together by?]How are the teams separated today?
Height?!
[Not satisfied being in the kids group.]
[Quiet Chattering.]
-You didn't wear insoles?-Nope, too much trouble.
You aren't wearing insoles.
[A need for Joong Ki to wear insoles?]
Please take care of the girls on your team.
And everyone knows this, speak eloquently.
-Fighting!-Fighting!
[The aftermath of having an eloquent and determined heart...]
After thinking about the punishment, this is not about skill but competition.[This week's scary skill and talent competition is about to begin]
Why can't we do it well, seriously?
[Endless physical comedy,]
[and outrageous eloquent speeches.]
[The race within in the museum]
What are you doing?
[Starts now!]
[Finally entering the museum!]
Wow, it's huge!
Seriously if we run here, wow.[Afraid of enormous structures]
[This is...]
[Korea's biggest science palace Gwacheon National Science Museum.]
[Have to run out of here, before it opens tomorrow]The bigger it is, the scarier it is. The scary part is we have to get out of here before tomorrow's opening.
[Punishment for the team who is not able to get out.]The team who is not able to get out, will receive punishment.
Exits are locked!
[Exits locked!]
Hi, Running Man! I am Korea's first astronaut, Lee Sook Yin.
You will not be able to leave this museum, unless you complete the various missions.
-Yes, we understand!-In order to escape, you must win
and attain more prizes.
So, to all Running Man members, do your best.
I hope that viewers and the Running Man members will notice all of the science and technology.
Fighting!
[Fighting!]
So, we are starting now.
[First mission, find 2 Golden Pigs within the museum.]-Goodbye.
Fighting! Fighting!-Jessica Fighting![Moving towards their goals...]
Kwang Soo stop putting in so much effort.
[Both teams have to head to the 2nd level.]
They're using the escalator.
[Kid team relaxing using the escalator.]
We're rather unlucky,
but we'll be using this on the way down.
[Adult team is using the stairs...]
The adult team has to use the stairs.
[Message arrives for the child team]
Find the keyboard and play the child tune "Bicycle".
Bicycle?
Dalala, dalala. Please give way.
Do you know how to play?
I know how to; but, I don't know the tune.
[Message arrives for the adult team.]
[Go to a place where it's windy and raining.]
[This time, both teams instructions are different!]
Where's the place with the wind and the rain?[If they follow the instructions, they should find the two separate locations for the Golden Pigs.]
-I think it should be a place like this.-Yes, yes!
What's rain and wind?[Thailand Prince]
[Nichkhun, who still has difficulties with Korean.]It's just rain and wind.
Ah, it's that easy?[He's that innocent.]
Ah, seriously, why is it so big?
Somewhere with keyboards.
Keyboards, keyboards!
This is no joke, we're in a museum.
There's only us.[Looking around the spacious museum]
You guys know about Night at the Museum right?
[Thinking about the Night at the Museum set.]-Ah, I do!-If only dinosaurs,
would appear later on.
Could it be at the Basic Science hall?
-Where?-They display all sorts of things there,
-maybe rain and wind is there?-Let's start running!
This can go either way.
[Basic Science hall showcasing mineralogical science.]
[Will the weather be here?]
Ah, this is the Basic Science hall?
It should be here!
Thyphon simulation room.
[Adult team reaching the place of wind and rain.]
[This is the place!]
[This is where you can experience a typhoon first hand.]Typhoon is made up of wind and rain!
[Typhoon Experience Room]
[Putting on raincoats to shield from wind and rain.]This is the place right?
[Adult Team: This is the place they'll get to know about their golden pigs!]
Ji Hyo, put these on. Put these on, go in, and take a look.
[Enters the typhoon chamber!]
This is the right place, right?
But, there should be something here.
[Typhoon simulation in operation. Entry and exit are restricted]
[What will happen to them?]
[The other side...]We've totally lost it!
[Kid team is still looking for the keyboard]
[How can a keyboard be in the Space Experience Hall?]
Hold on, this is crazy.
We have a big problem.
[At this time]
[The 1st floor.]It's on the floor below!
I told you we shouldn't have headed up![Running to the 1st floor]
In the children's hall!
[Already tired Jessica]-Jessica!-Oppa!
Don't run, don't run!
[Children's hall built for a child's experience]
[Kid team have found the keyboard to play "Bicycle"]
[Searching the entire place thoroughly...]
It's not here, this is just the kid's section.
[Just then...]
[ Oh... ! ]
[Found it...!]
[The Performer]
Come here quickly, I found it![Excited Gary!]
[Runs over quickly]
[Keyboard sighted!]
[Above is the locations to the Golden Pigs]
[All they have to do is play "Bicycle."]
[It's not easy playing with feet.]Sing, sing!
[Firming up the notes, one by one]
[Can only get the location of the Golden Pig after completing]
[Twisted]
It's messed up! This is frustrating, just let one person play.
[At the other side...]
[Experiencing the typhoon simulation, the adult team.]It looks like water.
Oh?
[Another note for the location of the golden pig.]
-Hold on.-What is that?
[Just at that moment!]
[Strong wind!]
[Violent Rain!]
[Enjoy the cleansing from the wind and rain!]
[This is the typhoon simulator!]
[Rapidly rising wind speeds]
[Being able to withstand wind speeds of 30m/sec will lead them to the location of the golden pigs!]
[Wind speeds going past 20m/sec.]
[Cruel winds are becoming even stronger.]
[Ah, a nice Tuesday Rain!]
[Kids team final segment of "Bicycle"]
[Mi Mi So So, Do ~]
[Mission accomplished!]
What's this thing?[Upon the completion of Mission: the Golden Pig location slipped down]
[Head to the place where there is a trilobite and find 2 deposit boxes]
[The Golden Pig is at the place with a trilobite]Isn't it up stairs?
What is the other team doing?
[What else are they doing...]
[This is it...]
[Adult team has yet to see the clue for where the Golden Pigs are!]
Look at that, look at that!
[Constantly shaking]
[Finally...30m/per sec]
[Opens]
[Should at least take a look while it's open...]
[Fluttering~]
[Wind speeds 30m/sec is 10 thousand times stronger than an atomic bomb. It is something a large and strong man can not withstand easily.]
[Look at the clue, look at the clue, look at the clue!]
[Under serious fire, unable to see the clue.]
[Have to look at the clue!]
[Unable to keep their eyes open...]
[How could this happen?]
[All for tomorrow morning...to escape from this place.]
[Their only hope...]
[For the hope, step...by step...]
[Even in the fierce winds.]
[This level of storm...]
[It can never stop us!]
[Finally...!]
[Caught it!]
[Finally clue confirmation!]
[Where the trilobite is, there are 2 deposit boxes.]
[Put this period of hardship behind...move forward!]
[Slowly, slowly]
[Finally, a break!]
If this is just the beginning...
[Nickhun still dazzling after being hit by the rain!]It was really cooling!
-Where the trilobite is, there is 2 deposit boxes.-What is a trilobite?
The trilobite is a specimen, right?
-That's right, that's right.-Oh, really?-Yes.
Fossil, fossil!
Hyung, it should be on the second floor, right?
-Let's go quickly.-There's noise coming from upstairs. We have to go quickly!
-Quickly!-Suk Jin, Suk Jin!
[Kids Team reaches the Natural History Hall] -Jong Kook hyung
-Please take care of Jessica. -I'm alright! Oppas go on ahead first. I think that'll be better.
[Adult team catching up rapidly!] -They're coming!
[Rapidly catching up] -They're coming!
[Both team enters the Natural History Hall!]
[If the Trilobite is here, there will be 2 Golden Pigs!]-Joong Ki, hold on.
[Earth 46 hundred-million years ago. A time traveling experience in the Natural History Hall.]
[Bingo, this is the trilobite fossil!] [So, here is the location to the two Golden Pigs?]
[Looks around]
[It's imperative to find the 2 Golden Pigs first!]
There are also fossils here, fossils!
[Searching alone, Haha.]
[ Oh? ]
[Found it!]
[Haha found the Golden Pig!]
[Slide~]
[Ahh!]
[Shocked!]
[Golden Pigs Guardian, an Iguana?]
[Put your hand in if you dare!]
[Totally Frightened!]
Jong Kook hyung!
[Why are you looking for hyung?]
[Quickly!]
[Kid's team timid Haha, will he...?]
Hold on, there's a trilobite there.
[Jong Kook, starts to run.]
[Ji Hyo who's nearby!]Here, it should be here.
[Surrounding the world's largest trilobite specimen.]
[A fierce fight between man and woman?]
[Who will?]
Oppa!
[Jong Kook was first!]
Oppa! Oppa! Oppa!
-Oppa! Oppa!-Ji Hyo!
[Jong Kook heads through the Trilobite door!]
[Found it! The Golden Pig!]
[Found it!]
[Kid team is awarded with 1 Golden Pig!]-I found it, I found it!
[On the other hand...]
Move over, move over.
Move over quickly!
Seems like they'll become scarier if I push them.
[The one that came was the most timid...]
Move over to that side, move over!
[Darn...]
[Just then, Jae Suk approaches!]
[Notices Haha!]
[Haha notices Jae Suk too!]
[So it's here!]
[This is bad!]
[But still timid.]
[Unmoving...]
[Adult team, Jae Suk!]
[Kids team, Haha!]
[Courage]
[Determination!]
[Kids team are awarded both Golden Pigs!]
[Race Over!]
-I saw it first!-I think you should see what's,
in the display first.
[What is actually inside there?]
What is that?
[It's an iguana.]
[Both of them are equally timid...]
[Will it be an unforgettable experience with the iguanas?]
[In search of the Golden Pigs in another location, a refreshing summer day begins...]
Welcome everyone, for the game today we're playing for 500,000 won.
-Hence everyone must work hard!-Everyone please put in your best!
[The 2 teams had fought it out in the Science Center]
-Do you fancy activities related to water?-Yes, I do.
So she really likes water sports.[Ji Hyo the water sport enthusiast.]
But Ji Hyo's appearance looks as if she doesn't enjoy water sports.
-For example, club.-Yes, club.
-Jong Kook told all of us secretly.-What did he say?
[90's idol, there was a time in which a club was named YTC.]-He said he went to the health club to exercise. -Haha hyung told me it was called the YeongTeokSeu Club.
It'll burst in a short while
By stomach is going to burst from laughing
[Smack]
[Shock]
[Congratulating with water rockets]
Aigoo, that scared me.
Wow
Do you know Newton's third law?
Huh?
I don't even know one, how am supposed I to know three?
Isn't it the law of motion?
-Motion and opposing forces?-Yes, that.
You are correct!
You knew all along, Joong Ki.
It's the human rocket game.
If you are able to cross the pole to the other side, you will get a point.
You may use your teammates' shoulders or any other methods.
The team that crosses at a higher point will win.
This game requires knowledge of the third law of motion.
Well, then...
Ack!
Scenes like this show that the competition is going to start.
[Laughter]
Aigoo.
[The Grasshopper has fallen in]
Let's stop, it's childish
[Nichkhun falls in the water as well]
Where is Kwang Soo going?
[He goes to Jong Kook]
[Spin]
[Gary peacefully falls into the water]
[Splash]
[Jong Kook gets revenge on Kwang Soo]
[How dare you...]
[Jong Kook will never fall into the water]
Did you see Gary's expression when he fell in?
A peaceful look?
[Do you want to see it again?]
[Peaceful Gary]
[All the peace in the world]
We're going to start with the Adult Team
[Challenging 1 meter 80 cm mark]
How should we do this?
It would be easiest for the four of us to lift her together.
Are you going to fall head first or feet first?
-As long as I cross over, it'll be fine.-Right, as long as the pole doesn't fall.
This game is easy for Kwang Soo.
[Advantageous for tall people like Kwang Soo]
[Ji Hyo Challenge Starts]
Ok she stood up.
[Shaky]
[Being a disturbance]
One...
Wait, wait a second. [Unstable]
Move forward a little.
[Stops]
[Wait a minute]
[Having a hard time]
It'd be great if you could go over on your first try.
[Wobbles]
[Splash]
[Kwangsoo was a bit unstable]
[The human rocket fails before she could jump]
[Kwangsoo, you...]  -No we aren't done yet.
Your turn is over!!
[Extreme crisis]
What the heck.
It's over.
[Human rocket Ji Hyo fails.]
Ah, I just fell into the water like that.
[Jae Suk practices before the challenge]
[Whoosh]
[Ah, the indescribable pain...]
It hurts so much.
[ The Kid Team Challenges ]
We can just throw Jessica over and be done.
How can you just throw her like that?
Jessica.
Stand up after getting on his shoulders
and jump when you get close.
Let's do this quickly, there's not much time.
[Kid team's first rocket, Jessica]
Such selfish friends!
You're making a girl do the first jump?
[Then what am I...]
Wait, hang on a second!
No way... Even I couldn't get across
Get ready!
1, 2, 3
[Woosh]
[The Opposing force]
[Easily succeeds]
[Human rocket Jessica succeeds]
Ji Hyo, why couldn't you do it?
[Ji Hyo who failed despite the easy mission...]
[Celebrating]
[Happiness vs. Gloom]
Do it properly Ji Hyo!
Are you really not going to do it seriously?
Do you want to stay here until morning?!
Ah really.
I need to leave before then~!
[Ji Hyo is miserable, but...]
[She was met with bright smiles that morning]
There are quite a lot of people who like Ji Hyo.
[Met with the smiles of the men]
[Even Suk Jin... but now...]
Take it easy Ji Hyo.
Just do it like Jessica did just now.
She looks like Sandara Park from the back.
Why did you have to do that?
Do you have a mirror?
You'll look pretty if you cross the bar.
You'll look nice if you jump over the bar!
Forget about the mirror!
You can see your reflection in the water!
Look at Jessica right now.
Yes, I brought my towel here.
Kwangsoo will be jumping now.
Why does his foot choke me when he steps on me? Ow!
It'll be embarrassing if he can't even stand up.
Go on the left instead.
Do you want to step on Ji Hyo's shoulders instead?
[It's hard for him to even stand up...]
These two weaklings seem to be struggling.
-Can I step on your shoulders?-Shoulders?
[Stepping on the shoulders again?]-Step on his shoulders if you want to!
[Wobble]
No, you can't!
A balancing circus show?
[A balancing circus show?]
Let's move back a little.
[Ack]
[Splash!]
[Balancing attempt failed]
[However, just a minute ago...]
[Looking at Kwangsoo's poses...]
[Statues of Philosopher Kwangsoo]
-We can do it like this and...-Don't try to cheat.
We aren't cheating!
Why is everyone so sensitive right now?
[The Adult Team is incredibly defensive]
It's because of Ji Hyo.
Why? I'll do better.
No, let's not do this, let's try lying down completely.
First, lie down.
What are you trying to do?
Nichkhun, lift him from the butt.
[What are they doing?]
Shouldn't Ji Hyo be doing this instead?
Kwangsoo, you should be supporting from the legs.
What is this?
[As if offering him as a sacrifice!!!]
[They've managed to lift him up!]
[Proceeding to move forward!]
What is this?
[Again, what is this?!]
1, 2, 3 [Toss]
[Throws over]
[Human rocket Jae Suk succeeds in clearing 1m 90cm]
[100% free to use any methods]
It worked.
Ok! You guys can't use this method!
[Kid team challenges 2m mark!]
Who's going to cross over this time?[Jae Suk?]
[Kid Team discusses their strategy]
[Completely oblivious]
What is the meaning of this?
What are you doing?!
What are you doing?
Where did he even come from?
These guys are completely focused on the task.
[Because they were too focused...]
I've been here for a while now.
Also, instead of asking me what I was doing, he asked "What's the meaning of this?"
I don't understand what you're trying to say.
I understand what I was saying.
[What is the meaning of Gary's question?]
[Again, immersed in discussing their plan]
I'll go up.
[Again]Then you can support. Don't come out of the water.
No, that's not right.
Then, I'll help Jong Kook jump over.
[Again, completely oblivious]
You should at least ask for my opinion.
[Shocked!]
Why are you doing that, seriously??
[Peaceful Gary is provoked.]
Ah, I can't do this game like this!
He was too focused on planning.
[This time, Kwangsoo...]
Then this time...
Kwang Soo come here.
[Kwangsoo crept over carefully...but he was caught.]
You can't do it well.
[Kid Team Challenges 2m]
[Will they be able to clear it?]
1,2...
[Jong Kook puts in force]
[Joong Ki puts in the opposing force]
[Coolly clearing the 2m mark]
[Joong Ki succeeds!]
Wonderful!
Why does he have to look so handsome while doing this?
[He does indeed look very cool jumping over!]
Oh, Kwangsoo, you're not on my team.
[Embarrassed]
We can do it too!
But I'm going to be going next...
[Seok Jin challenges the 2m 5cm mark]
Squat down so that I can climb on your shoulders.
Are you going to be okay?
Suk Jin, is it okay if you jump later?
Right now, everyone else wants to see Nichkhun.
[Bingo]
But I've already gone up on Kwangsoo's shoulders!
It'll be a good time to increase our viewership.
You just be quiet you brat!
I don't want to see you.
You and Ji Hyo go ahead and do that...
Why Ji Hyo?-I feel irritated just looking at her.
She's just standing to the side thinking she's cute.
Her eyebrows are really long...
Why are you attacking my eyebrows?
I don't like girls with long eyebrows.
[Slowly drowning]
[Wait, you shouldn't be sinking...]
[It's... heavy]
[Intimidated by his team and keeping quiet]
Kwangsoo what are you doing?
[The four members working together to complete the challenge]
[Shaky]
[Stopping close to the pole]
But the height difference between these two is so big.
This feels weird.
1, oh wait..
[Wobbly]
Just push yourself forwards.
[Flying]
[Looks like he's ski jumping...]
[Hyung, get off!]
[Put your effort into propelling forward]
[But if he enters the water like this...]
[Success!]
[Splat]
[He looks like he is in pain]
[Adult Team succeeds in clearing the 2m 5cm mark]
How can he belly flop into the water?
I was wondering how you would fall in.
[Falling in an "--" shape]
[Adult Team challenges the 2m 15cm mark]
[Nichkhun rocket will jump this time]
[Pose?]
[Suk Jin creeps away stealthily]
Alright, let's go.
Hyung, do something to help us too!
Oh, we're ready. Let's go.
I'll help by cheering.
[Jae Suk's shoulders have suffered today]
[Very shaky]
1,2, 3...
-
[With the help of Kwang Soo's strength.]
[10 Points out of 10 points!]
Nichkhun succeeds in clearing the 2m 15cm mark!]
Outstanding! He's really is something.
I don't have any words...
This is how you do it Ji Hyo
[Again, Ji Hyo...?]
Ji Hyo you have to do it like this. Don't just stand there clapping.
[The only thing she can do is clap]
[Today is not her lucky day]
Why does Ji Hyo have to observe that?
Telling her to look at this, look at that.
[Our Cinderella for the day... Ji Hyo.]
[The pole has been raised to the 2m 20cm mark]
[Jong Kook will challenge for the Kid Team]
[Completely focused]
[Jae Suk!]
[Is he going to disturb them again?]
[Completely oblivious]
[Huh? Taking the camera?]
[Jae Suk approaches, hiding behind the camera!]
[Edging closer...]
[Gary is completely focused again]
[Carefully...]
[He is right in front of them]
[Targets Gary!]
Keep your knees straight!
Oh, why are you doing this!
[Right in front of him]
Why are you doing this, really!
[Jong Kook fails before being able to jump]
[Jae Suk prevents the Kid team from succeeding!]
Why are you doing this to me?
What the heck? Where did he come from?
The pole is now at the 2m 30cm mark. Chose the strongest people on each team to jump.
[The person who jumps over first wins]
[Kid team's representative, Joong Ki]
[Ji Hyo]
[Once the cameraman approaches them]
Are you Jae Suk?
[No.. it's just me]
I am over here.
[However, over here...]
Did you grab on?
[Very obviously...]
[Good job]
1,2...
[Gary is completely focused]
[Oppa...]
[Shocked]
What is the meaning of this really!
Really!
Although this doesn't feel too horrible.
[This weird feeling isn't that bad~]
It's not bad at all.
[This time, Suk Jin]
[The elder wants to try as well]
[Suddenly]
Why did you come here?
[Many of the younger ones did it so I wanted to as well]
[Blow]
Why did you come here?
You landed on me purposely didn't you?!
You shouldn't have come here in the first place...
It wasn't on purpose?
What happened to your face?
Why are you talking about my face?!
I was born this way!
The thing that saddens me most is when people ask me that...
[Chaotic]
-Alright alright.-He looks like this 24/7.
I'm originally like this.
[This 40 year old is highly sensitive to issues regarding his face]
[The Adult Team challenges 2m 30 cm]
Okay, let's have Ji Hyo do it this time.
- Me? Please support me well.  - Isn't it easier just to throw you over?
[Can Ji Hyo do it this time?]
You have to go a bit higher.
Ji Hyo step on my head.
[Steps]
Aah!
[Dying grasshopper]
Go over like that.
Hurry and cross already!
[Shaky]
Like that!
[In the end...]
[Indeed, Ji Hyo has failed this time too...]
Are you okay?
Ji Hyo, I forgot about the top of the hat.
[The hat top!]
[All of her weight was concentrated here...]
[Fortunate to have no head injuries!]
[Standing this firmly...]
[In addition, it's made of metal...!]
[The 2m 30cm mark has yet to be conquered]
[Joong Ki challenges the 2m 30cm mark]
[If he succeeds, then the Kid Team wins!]
[Looks really focused]
[Will Kid Team's rocket, Joong Ki, be able to succeed?]
[Jump!]
[Go Joong Ki!]
[Aw!]
[Touched a part of the pole!]
[Kid Team Joong Ki, 2m 30cm fail!]Just like that!
Yah, why?
[Time to analyze...the mistake we made in the game.]You should only jump when I say 3!
[Adult Team challenges 2m 30 cm]
Kwang Soo, you wanna try?
Don't just say yeah, you have to be really confident
You have to succeed
We really need this 500,000 Won. We really have to win, guys.
[shaky, shaky]
Stop making me laugh!
Stop making you laugh on a variety show...?
[Stood up...] [Super focused]
Turn around! Turn around! Turn around!
Isn't his face just like right before diving?
[This face is exactly like before he dived last week]
[Kwang Soo makes the same face before he messes up]
[Will he get over the 2m 30cm and become a Human Rocket?]
Right now! Right now! [The time has come]
Come on!
[Launch]
[Body is almost folded in half]
[Pass with style!]
[Proud of you, Kwang Soo!]
[Of course... gets weak right after...]
[Kwang Soo 2m30cm Success]
[Unbelieveable]
[Final Victory] [Adult Team]
[500,000 Won Achieved!!]
[But the happiness of success is only for a short moment...]
From now on, Jae Suk's Die Hard begins.
Yay our 500,000 Won! [The 500,000 Won Golden Pig won at the pool]
This makes me anxious. Hey, we have to win no matter what. [Putting it in the bag for convenience]
Next to Nickhun, our faces will look even bigger.
Face..
[Serious - furthermore because I'm sitting right next to him]
Hey, which one do you like out of these three?
Woah really
When I look at the three of you like this, it's almost like watching evolution happen
[First Man]
[Improved Man]... [Complete Man]
Wait. You're saying Kwang Soo is in the middle? Well, even I think I'm about middle at least.
[The courage of saying he thinks he's at least at middle with his face]
Don't you think it's really like the human evolution?
Australopithecus, Cro-Magnon, then modern man.
Then you're a Trilobite. (Extinct marine animals found in fossils)
The mission should be arriving soon.
[On the other hand, the Kid Team is gathered in another room.]
It's here? It's here, its here, it's here!
What were you doing?
Grab Jae Suk's name tag and come to 000.
Where's 000?
When you take off Jae Suk hyung's name tag, the location must be on it.
Oh! it's here, it's here!
Grab Jong Kook's name tag and come to 000.
[There's a hint about the Golden Pig once you take the name tag off]
That means the other team got the message of which one of us has the hint on our backs.
For now, we have to figure out who has the hint on our team.
[The Adult Team has to rip off Kim Jong Kook's name tag.]
How are we suppose to rip off Jong Kook?That's too much.
Should have place it on bull instead.
[Who has the hint?]
Is it not on Nichkhun?
[Uneasy, uneasy]
Oh~ Something is there.
Is it me?
Yea, it's you.
[Jae Suk is chosen to have the hint]
[What hint does Jae Suk's name tag hold?]
Inform me when you rip off Jong Kook's name tag.
I'll be hiding.
Jong Kook hyung could also be hiding somewhere.
Don't you think the other team also looked at their backs like us?
They don't think that far ahead.
They're reckless.
[Did the other team look at their backs?]
[...They really didn't think of that...]
Jae Suk, can I really trust you?
[Jae Suk showing strong confidence in hiding].
I'm really good at hiding.
But this friend won't be able to do it...
He's a bit slow.
Oh it's that one person from before.
[Out of breath: They found it all, hyung]
[Low-Stamina VJ who was strongly advised to go to the gym.]
It's him from that time.
Did you get a membership for a gym?
[Nod, nod]
Are you really confident?
[A fate where he has to hide and run with Jae Suk.]
Fighting!
Then...
Hyung, hurry up and go.
Hyung! Jae Suk hyung!
Oh...
Oh my gosh you scared me!
Can you take this bag...
[Gives the bag to carry the piggy banks to Jae Suk]
Do well.
Make sure to come up with a strategy!
I shouldn't be here like this.
[Jae Suk goes into hiding now...]
[Rest of the Adult Team goes off to find Jong Kook]
-Why is it so quiet?-It's like nervousness you get when it's really quiet.
They're downstairs!
The child team also discovers the adult team.
-He's there.-Is Jong Kook hyung there? -He's there.
[Goes forward without any hesitation]
Jae Suk oppa isn't there.
Face-to-face competition?
-Where's Jae Suk hyung?-Oh Jae Suk went to the bathroom.
[The other team is flustered without Jae Suk there!]
[The Kid Team still isn't aware that Jong Kook holds the hint.]
It's me! I think it's me!
[Child team extremely confused]
[The adult team using the strategy to confuse the other team.]
Jessica, come here!
[Acting as if they are going after Jessica!]
[Gather Jessica with everyone else...]
[and the real target, Jong Kook, is left all alone]
[Oh! It's me!]
[Oh my gosh! The hint is on my back!]
[Target established: Grab Jong Kook's name tag]
[Oh it's not me]
[Jong Kook is suddenly surrounded]
Hurry and rip it off.
[Fights them off with strength then escapes!]
Hey, hold on hold on. Hyung!
[Nickhun at the front of the chase!]
[Caught!]
[Jong Kook gets stopped]
[Like a rat in poison...]
No!
[No matter what... can't give it up...!]
[Jong Kook doesn't stop...]
[Drags them up...]
[Monster Power]
[What is this?!]
[Jong Kook, his truly unbelievable strength...!]
Where's my team?!
[Still standing after being outnumbered 4:1..!]
[Jong Kook in danger! His name tag falls off his back!!]
[Jong Kook's name tag is in whose hands??]
[On the other hand...]
We have to hide, we have to hide.
[ The extremely large interior of the science museum ]
[Into a tiny gap...]
Do you think you can come in?
Look at you, you're like this again.
[Hidden behind the large walls...]
During these times, you need to put the camera as my eyesight
[First criticism of his stamina and now his filming skills.]
[This place is still a pandemonium!]
[The name tag is still in Jong Kook's hands]
[Jong Kook has been holding on for more than 10 minutes]
Jae Suk.
[Haha gives Jessica the bag]
[We shouldn't all be doing this. Find Jae Suk...]
Jae Suk hyung!
[It's much more advantageous to find Jae Suk first!]
Yooruce Willis, Yooruce Willus. Die Hard.
[Yooruce Willis, who is curious about the situation outside]
Suk Jin hyung!
Nickhun... over.
What happened?
Kwang Soo!
What?
[To make matter's worse, Yooruce Willis' stomachache]
Ah... my stomach hurts...
[Slowly, the abdominal pain...]
Oh, it can't start now.
My stomach hurts because I'm too anxious.
Haha oppa is going! Haha oppa is going!
Okay Ji Hyo, I got it.
Yes.
[Yooruce Willis, moving to a safer place]
Shh! Shh!
Oh, that scared me!
[...What? Why...]
[A human figure lying on the MRI machine]
[It seems about right that he got scared from seeing that by himself...]
Oh, that's really scared me.
Oh~ It's scary by myself.
I think I heard foot steps...
Someone's coming, someone's coming
[He quickly escapes to the back of the display room...]
[Hiding specialist, Yooruce Willis]
[It's been 20 minutes here!]
[Where are all the others after leaving Jessica with the heavy money bag??]
[Suk Jin attacks with his smelly feet!]
[I feel bad for Jong Kook oppa]
He's really strong.
[Truly a monster-like strength!]
[Just then!]
[Thanks to Nichkhun holding his back...]
[Kwang Soo...]
[Successfully tears Jong Gook's name tag!]
It's done! It's done.
Jong Kook's showdown... Epic ending 20 minutes later!]
[Blank~]
[Jong Kook's nametag confirmed!]
[Tear Jong Kook's name tag and come to 242...?]
[What is 242?]
You didn't catch him?
You lost it?
[The gore that is shown through expression]
[Chaser Haha, going to the first floor to find Jae Suk]
[Finally, he goes to the place where Jae Suk is hiding...]
[There is Jae Suk somewhere around here...]
[Looking around, looking around]
He's hiding in something like a room.
Don't tell them that!
You can't tell that to the opponent's PD!
What?
They went. Run away!
Why'd you tell them that?!
They're here, they're here!
I'm in trouble, big trouble
[Emergency situation - Yooruce Willis' escape!]
[A mess]
[You should've just stayed there...]
He's hiding somewhere on the first floor!
He's not on the second floor!
He's here! He's here!
[Come inside, you'll be found]
Oh~ my gosh~
[That man from before!]
[Life shortened by ten years!]
[He goes behind the walls of the display again...]
[Haha, slowly getting closer!]
He keeps asking where we are.
PD Jo! We can't tell you. Stop talking, why do you do that?
[It's because there's been no news for 30 minutes...]
[Haha noticed from the noise of the walky-talky!]
[Haha's VJ]
[Emergency!]
[Haha, gets quick access!]
[Haha, access complete!]
[He discovered Haha's shadow]
[There's only one wall between them...]
[Extremely anxious]
What can I do, what can I do? Where did he go, where did he go?
[VJ lowers his position as well...]
[Found!]
[Haha is waiting outside!]
[An escape for life]
Catch him!
1st floor!
Where? Where?
He's there, there's there.
[Jae Suk quickly runs to the restroom]
[Managed to flee!]
[All of them pile in]
You should come out~
Guys, run quickly.
Let's attack him with water!
No! The camera, camera!
Is the camera more important than me, right now?
I'm about to get hit by water.
I'm giving you ten seconds.
[Water bombing!]
Oh, it's cold!
I...
am someone who has been in a swimming pool!
Hey...
Do we have a hose?
[A mess that doesn't know what 242 means yet]
What are you doing? Jae Suk.
What? What did you say?
Hey... please come out now.
These kids are hitting me with water.
[Going to save the captured Jae Suk]
We have to find him fast!
Jae Suk!
What floor are you on?
[Struggle, struggle]
He's on the first floor!
[Meanwhile, Kwang Soo and Nickhun are finding the 242 hint]
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are going down to the first floor to find Jae Suk]
[Oh my arms...]
[After the waterbombing comes the stepping on feet]
I think these are the lockers, the lockers.
[Would the identity of 242 be a locker number?]
It's here, it's here!
[What is in locker number 242?]
[The last key to finding the location of the Golden Pig!]
The Golden Pig is located at the first broadcast and communications satellite.
[The Blue team, pretending to leave!]
[Did they leave? Why is it so quiet?]
[There's no way!]
[To catch Yoo Jae Suk's nametag!]
[Face to face]
Run away! Run away!
[Gary obtained Jae Suk's nametag!]
[Name tag check]
This isn't a time to be like this, get up!
Lift him up!
[The taste of death]
The lockers, the lockers!
[Bingo!]
Oh, what is that?
Where is our nation's first broadcast satellite located?
The second floor! Second floor!
[To the state-of-the-art exhibition on the second floor!]
[Thanks to the heavy bag, Jessica sitting down at the first floor again]
Wasn't there something about a rocket here last time?
Yeah. Jae Suk, that's it!
No one haven't been on this floor before. [Adult team runs toward the courtyard]
- It's over there!- Woah!
[A rocket appeared in the science center's courtyard]
[South Korea's first radio broadcast satellite, MuGoongHwaHo]
I found it, I found it!
[The Kid team still in the Aerospace Engineering museum]
They went outside!
Adult team went outside.
Run, run, run!
It's right that it's outside, then!
Please breathe comfortable. [VJ: I'm not straggling behind.]
Please breathe comfortably.
Don't do this.
[Adult team closing toward MuGoongHwaHo]
I found it!
It's here! It's here, noona!
It's here!
Found it!
What is it?
[Adult team, one Golden Pig obtained!]
[Where is the last remaining one?]
There's another one somewhere.
[The other one is in a nearby bush...]
[Leaving near the rocket and digging through a trash can...]
[Where is it...]
[At that moment!]
[Looking through the suspicious bush]
[It...it's here]
[The Kid team who's late and running to MuGoongHwaHo]
Quickly quickly!
Jae Suk!
I FOUND IT!
WE FOUND IT!
What, they found it?
-
Friend...
This person runs well.
The VJ is impressive~
[Our VJ has changed]
[Currently Adult team winning]
[Now the most humiliating game starts...]
The race this week was difficult, wasn't it?
We all have been through the punishments, right?
If you think about the penalty, this isn't variety. It's war!
That seems too cruel.
It was hard to hide for a long time.
My VJ received a call asking where we were.
He told them right away where we were hiding.
I'm currently hiding, inside the building,  a place looks like a room.
Don't tell them!
[Since last week, the VJ and the gold have been a combination]
It seems to be the piggy bank, so I ran towards it.
When I ran, the VJ said, "don't run, don't run."  But I kept running.
"Running there alone is useless!"
"It's won't do anything!"
[The VJ was tired, so he threatened(?) him]
Also the prize for this game is 500,000 Won.
You know curling, right?
[Trash Can Curling!]
[They'll be pushing the trash cans with their teammates in them]
[To try and get inside the circle mark in the middle]
[The team with the most people in the circle win!]
[As long as you stay inside the trash can, you can use any method to win!]
You can sit this way.
We can kick each other.
Please explain more in details. Can we Kick each other?
[Shocked]
It's fine to kick each other? [Kicking and pushing makes a big difference!]
We can push each other.
- So it's pushing, right?  - You're right.
Ok, I got it.
Everyone's ready, right?
[The two teams head to opposite sides]
[The staff are getting ready for filming]
[They are practicing seriously...]
[The trash can goes who~oosh]
It's strong, it's strong.
[The Adult team's trash can that doesn't travel well]
Only one person...
[The really weird adult team's trash can]
[Where is Kwang Soo going?]
[Kwang Soo, where are we going...?]
[Kid team focusing on their training]
[Pretends to be arranging]
[Fail to noticed the situation...]
[Bin got switched]
[Without hurrying, naturally]
[The bin that got switched]
[The perfect crime]
Come first!
Do it first? Okay.
Let's do some games that we can do really close in the future.
Why? Why?
No, the game is just too far away.
I think that guy is younger than me!
Is he the only one that works out?
[Jessica, getting into the trash can]
Oh no, you went in too much!
She went in too much!
[She fit right into the trash bin]
Are you Bin-ssica?
Stay up with your arms!
They're not on our team, Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo Oppa, who has a lot of affection]
[The oppas on the same team are just staying still...]
Did it work?
Jong Kook Hyung, who are the two people pushing?
We'll decide that on our own.
[Oh... that's right...]
Why are you so curious about them?
[Only the males are competing!]
- Okay!- Deal!
[The Adult team starts first]
Be careful, be careful.
[The first player, Suk Jin]
[Devising a plan...]
Hey, then I'm going to go across the entire floor!
[Players must try to get in that hole!]
[Ji Suk Jin, take off!]
You calculated this, right?
Of course we did.
[Slowly~]
[Settled into the wrong place!]
Oh...!
[Far from their target]
Hey... what is this?
This is a broadcast, but what am I doing, facing away from the cameras?
Hyung, you're not appearing on the broadcast!
Hyung, just look outside.
[Lonely...]
[Moving]
[Nichkhun moving the camera for Suk Jin]
I'll be shooting a documentary by myself here!
[Uncomfortable face]
We're going now!
[Kid team first player - Jong Kook]
Jong Kook Hyung is going!
Jong Kook Hyung, this is a game. You know that right?
[A girl called him hyung?] (Girls call older brothers oppa, not hyung)
Jong Kook Hyung is just a name.
[On the other hand...]
[Jong Kook Hyung, blast off!]
- Stop stop stop!- Good!
- Hey...- What is this?
[Minus this person...]
[Even Jessica comes to argue...]
It's not that much.
[Standing, standing]
What are you doing? You guys!
Stay out of this! Don't come!
[This person is an exception...]
This Hyung can't see!
Hey... I guess it's pretty fun back there!
[They don't care!]
Is there something fun happening?
Don't worry, Suk Jin Hyung, there isn't much happening.
It looks like you're having fun.
[They're telling him to stop caring...]
You can't move anymore! What are you doing, Oppa?
Ji Hyo, why are you so angry?
[Trying to organize the situation]
[Except for this person]
[I'm curious...]
Let's not touch anything.
[Peeking]
Is that all?
-Hyung, you're okay, right?-Of course.
Hey! Yoo Jae Suk!
I'm sorry, but next time, can you push someone here to kick me to the middle?
That's a little hard.
I really want to see what's going on!
[Second player, Nichkhun]
Jong Kook Hyung, they're aiming for you.
[Push me to him]
[Uneasy...]
[Nichkhun, takes off!]
[The direction is good!]
Push him, push him, push him!
[He pushed him out of the circle!]
[And Nichkhun is in the circle as well!]
What... what is happening right now?
We're doing well, right?
[If it's good then it's okay]
[The Kid team, whose goal is to knock Nichkhun out with Haha]
[Running]
[Concentrating on the game]
That's good!
[Whoo~oosh]
Surely Jae Suk won't, again...
[Going behind concentrated Gary]
[He fell for it again!]
[Do you not see him even though he comes near?]
Why are you like this?
Why do you keep doing this to me?
I think I'm going to get neurosis, really.
Kwang Soo, what's happening...
I'll tell you after the game is over.
[When is it going to end...]
[Haha, aimed towards Nichkhun!]
[Haha's pushing, success!]
[Pushed Adult team's Nichkhun out!]
[If this continues, the Kid team will win!]
Jae Suk Oppa!
Things are out of hand, right?
-Very!- Yes!
[Obviously cutesyness is Girl's Generation!]
Ji Hyo, do it once.
Please talk to Ji Suk Jin a little!
[I'm used to it now...]
Suk Jin Hyung has to know what it means to suffer outside of his home!
[Rage]
I'm so angry right now, because I can't move.
Let's win, let's win!
This is the last one.
Fighting, fighting!
Please let our team win...
Fighting!
[Target acquired]
Kwang Soo, fighting!
[Ready]
[Kwang Soo takes off]
[Please go straight!]
[What will be the results?]
Okay, okay, listen...
The winner...
Will be announced next week!
[The sensitive museum!]
[The museum is alive?]
[In order to escape, the relentlessly running Running Man members!]
[The breathtaking race, just how will it end?]
[First mission : Escape the bus!]
[A night dance party?]
Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
[August 8th, at 5:20 in the afternoon, Running Man continues]
[Summer Story]
[To the ocean! To the ocean!]
[Emergency situation]
[That started in the middle of the ocean]
[Popular horror!]
[Will be starting soon]