[The landmark in the heart of the city]
[The story that you don't know about]
[This time it's the Suwon World Cup stadium]
[Running Man will appear here]
[Out of breath running rapidly ]
[A variety action show with a new concept]
[It will surpass your imagination]
[Exciting games!]
[The running starts now]
[A day in July, 2010]
[Suwon City, Jang Ryong Mun entrance]
[One by one, the running man members arrive]
[Instructions are given to find the place where they'll do the opening]
What is this?
[Where is today's opening going to be?]
[Yeonmu Dae]
The place where we're doing the opening today...
Please find where you need to go.
[Hopeless]
[At the eastern side of the stadium is a martial arts platform. Korean imperial soldiers trained there.]
If you arrive at the starting place first, you get the privilege of picking your teammates first.
[The key is to know how to read Hanja!]
[Are they running like that because they already know what it is?]
The place probably won't be found easily, right?
[Jeju Island actress, Song Ji Hyo]
Ah, I shouldn't have worn high heels. They're so uncomfortable now.
[Because of these super high heels, she can only walk in small steps]
[Another clueless mystery girl]
[Professional running athlete idol: Goo Hara]
I think I dressed too chic today.
[Trips]
[I'm guessing that no one saw that?]
[Kwang Soo is asking for help from a passerby]
I don't know (Speaking in Japanese)
[Out of all people, a Japanese tourist!]
Excuse me, would you happen to know where this place is?
I'm not sure. (Speaking in Mandarin)
[This time it's a Chinese tourist]
[Why is nothing going well for Kwang Soo]
Oh! Liang Wu Tai!
[Liang Wu Tai is the mandarin pronunciation!]
Thank you.
[They all ask for directions to find the platform]
[Don't walk, run!]
[Finally, the members arrive at the platform one by one.]
[Another mystery guest!]
[He's back! Lee Chun Hee.]
I'm in a hurry to get to the martial arts platform. Would it be ok for you to take me there?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
I guess I'm going to be first place.
People should use their brains.
[Everything is under control]
Thank you.
I'm first place.
[Running Man's staff are gathered at the martial arts platform]
[What are you doing at the martial arts platform entrance..]
[Oh Chun Hee, where are you going?]
It looks like someone is on their way here.
Who is it?
[Only now he enters the martial arts platform]
Chun Hee!
What brings you here?
How can you start the show without me?
What's the occasion?
What brings you here?
- It's because I heard you were doing a new show.
- That's why.
- I decided to make a comeback.
- The show was about to start recording, I didn't think he'd come.
There might be an overlap in character.
Their characters are so alike.
Kwang Soo acts like how you used to be.
He looks like how I used to look like in the past?
It's Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo it's been a long time.
Hello.
[Jae Suk's exaggerated welcome greeting]
Do you guys not know Ji Hyo well?
Why are you acting like you're so close with her?
You should call her "Song Ji Hyo" properly.
[Bullied from all sides!]
- You should not treat surnames lightly!
- Do you like Ji Hyo?
Because she's my hoobae and younger sister I can address her informally
It seems like Ji Hyo was the last to come. Let's check to see if we're all here.
Suk Jin...
I heard that Suk Jin fainted.
[Suk Jin fainted?!]
We thought over this very carefully.
He was the main guest last time, right?
For his sake, just for the time being let's not mention him.
- This is for his own good.
- Isn't it a little too early to be saying that?
The quicker you decide, the better!
He's actually a good older brother.
Just going like this is a pity.
This time our Kwang Soo-Kwang Soo why are you holding Joong Ki's cardigan?
You weren't his friend?
It was thrown next to me.
When I'm saying all this, he should take the cardigan away from me now.
Joong Ki doesn't seem to have that kind of vibe.
Joong Ki and I have different styles.
It's completely different.
Alright, I think we're all here.
Let's get into teams.
Who was first?
Lee Kwang Soo.
[Lee Kwang Soo was the first to arrive!]
I want my priority to be democratic.
I want to know who are the people who want to be in the same team as me or not?
Maybe the weather is too hot. Our brains don't seem to be working properly.
Even though it's hot, who wants to be on my team?
Why don't you pick one of the girls first?
If that's the case then...
- Even though you two must be very nervous
- I'm not nervous at all.
[Taken aback]
- It's because Kwang Soo was trying to be polite.
- I'm sorry.
- I didn't mean anything by it.
- I want to pick Ji Hyo.
[Ji Hyo is Kwang Soo's first choice!]
Then next I pick...
I'm going to pick the next team member now.
Ha Ha!
- Why don't you let us know the reason?
- Why did you pick Ha Ha?
Because he's so cheerful and-
- As a person he doesn't get upset easily.
- Loosen up your necktie you'll be more comfortable.
I'm not going to pick you.
This is the first time Kwang Soo said that he doesn't like to be criticized.
It's rare to see Kwang Soo showing his true colors!
It only happens when he's really mad.
Then why did you pick Ji Hyo out of Ji Hyo and Hara?
Hara and I don't seem to go well together.
You still have to pick two more members.
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Yoo Jae Suk is chosen!]
Why did you do that?
Gary!
[Gary is chosen!]
[Kwang Soo's choices are Ji Hyo, Haha, Jae Suk and Gary!]
Last time you said that we don't go well together.
[Flinches]
Even though we're not completely sure, the people standing on this side are the people who made Kwang Soo uncomfortable.
Rules of the new Running Man game.
As soon as all the entrances are open and the exits are locked, the mission starts.
All members must wait until the locks open up tomorrow. Only the group with the most money can leave.
There are two methods to getting cash!
First method-play a game to earn 500,000₩.
Second method-find cash filled golden piggy banks that are hidden in the stadium.
But the catch is the amount of money the piggie banks have will only be revealed right before you leave the stadium.
Who will get the most cash and be able to leave the stadium?
Mission start!
- And
- It's here.
[The instructions are here]
I think I've been to that place before.
It says "Go to the Suwon World Cup Stadium."
Let's go.
[Home team: Jong Kook, Joong Ki, Chun Hee and Hara]
[Away team: Jae Suk, Gary, Ha Ha, Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo]
[The cars are entering the football player's specially reserved parking garage]
[Excited]
Thank you.
So this is where the professional league players enter the stadium.
[The exact spot where the Taeguk warriors get off their bus!]
Let's go in first.
I'm feeling a bit uncomfortable from nervousness.
Look at what's in front of us!
[This right here is the tunnel where the athletes enter]
Of course.
[Only players get to enter through this honorable tunnel]
[Running man enters]
[The official soccer ball will always be displayed every time you enter the field!]
[Exchanged with the golden piggie bank?!]
Because that's what our mission is based on.
Magnificent view! The spacious stadium.
[The second landmark is the Suwon World Cup stadium]
[Surface area of 42000 square meters (13,000 ft.) Can accommodate 44000 people]
[How will our running man members escape from this gigantic field?]
[Touched]
This is so cool.
I think I'm supposed to enter with this.
Bring it in.
[Holding the golden pig like a soccer ball]
[Enters the ground field]
Let's go in!
[They actually need to compete in a race in this wide stadium]
[Sky cameras were also used in the 2010 Fifa world up in Africa]
[Interesting]
Today we're going to be doing a game that will last until tomorrow morning.
And we have to complete our mission here.
Suk jin is here.
- Why are you here?
- Running man!
[Suk Jin is late due to his schedule]
[The word "Bang!" appears again]
I heard that you weren't going to come.
So we told you last time that that kind of thing could happen.
That's why I hired a spy because I wanted to know how you would start the show.
I had a deep conversation with Gary.
- There's something that never ends, right?
- Wow your mouth got bigger in two weeks.
[At this moment]
It's coming out.
The exits are sealed.
We can't get out until tomorrow morning.
[It's happening again]
[Bleacher gate]
[Parking lot gate]
[Office gate]
[Even to the main gate, everything is completely locked!]
[Clueless]
That was the sign to let us know that we're starting.
Hello running man members.
I am the goal keeper for the South Korea national team
Jong Song Ryeong.
To the citizens who loves and supports our South Korean team, I would like to say thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Starting now, only the team that gets the most money can exit the stadium.
All the prize money will be donated to the soccer charity foundation.
So please try your best!
Good luck Running Man!
Good luck Song Joong Ki!
[With Jung Seong Ryung's encouragement, everyone's morale is boosted.]
Jung Seong Ryung said "Song Joong Ki, fighting." Do you do two know each other?
Jung Seong Ryong is the coach for our soccer club.
Ah, club soccer team.
I met him through that team.
[Wow I'm jealous]
Just like Jung Song Ryung said, whoever get's the most amount of money gets to leave, right?
Alright! Please start giving out the hints.
So we really do need to find them.
[Video hint?]
[This match is..]
[2002 Fifa world cup South Korea. Round 16, facing italy]
[The goal from Ahn Jung Hwan lead his team to the quarter finals]
Isn't this the scene where they get into the quarter finals?
- Can you tell who it is?
- Ahn Jung Hwan
It was here?
Victory ball!
Then shouldn't the ball be over there? This is the ball that Ahn Jung Hwan won with.
Because it's the ball that won the match, there's a chance it's displayed somewhere in the stadium.
[The away team are already on the move]
I really don't know how to find this.
I really don't know where I can find it.
[They're acting like they're clueless but they already know the answer]
They still don't know the answer.
- They still don't know.
- We've figured it out already.
What if they already know the answer?
I'm going to go and get changed first, and I'll call you guys after.
[Meanwhile, the other team appears to be clueless]
There's a map over there.
[Discovered the map?]
[Without knowing the answer, the map is useless!]
Shall we go down again?
[The away team goes outside again]
Kwangsoo, where are you headed?
It might be hidden in a very difficult area.
- There should be a map around here somewhere.
- I don't think there'd be one?
It's over there.
It's right over there!
[Easily spotted the information directory]
World Cup memorial hall! World Cup memorial hall!
[Discovered that there's a World Cup memorial hall!]
[Sprinting]
Elevator! Bro, there's an elevator!
[Out of service]
It's only one floor! Running would be faster.
What about Suk Jin?
Suk Jin should go down too.
To the first floor.
It wouldn't be good if the doors are locked.
[Would their prediction be the correct answer?]
[Meanwhile the away team searches the water drainage]
I've never thought of memorial halls or museums,
but there's nothing else other than that.
Let's hurry and go up there! This is just a water drainage.
I think I saw a memorial hall when I first entered here.
- We should hurry and run towards there.
- Where?
[After Suk Jin changes clothes]
World Cup memorial hall.
[Gasp]
[The away team is also rushing!]
Let's go.
[The away team is right behind them!]
[The two teams meet!]
[The home team got caught up by the away team!]
[The home team arrives at the museum first]
Close the door!
Shut the door.
[Blocking is such an old trick]
[Should hurry and find the golden piggie bank while they have time]
[The away team rushes in]
[This place is]
[The suwon stadium's world cup museum!]
[Inside the museum there is...]
[2002 Round 16 match, the ball that Ahn Jung Hwan shot in]
[The victory ball!]
[Furthermore, during the game an Italian player was ejected off the field]
[Thus the red and yellow cards]
[Inside the museum, there are a total of 4 piggie banks]
It's right here.
[Their goal of course is the piggie bank but]
[But the most attracting items are memorial items!]
It's here!
[Oh my gosh!]
[Out of all of them, only one of them is real. The rest are fake]
[Hurry and find one that's heavier]
[Both teams are gathered in the theater!]
[Chaotic]
[Did someone already find the real one?]
[This one is light]
[someone's already dizzy from trying to find the piggie bank]
[It's like Gary is exercising around the museum[
[Found it! A piggie bank that is disguised as one of the museum items]
[Oink?]
How do I get this?
[Carefully]
[Gary acquired the gold piggie bank!]
[Because the mission only ends with the horn sound, he is being careful as to not be spotted]
[It's still a mess inside the theater]
[At that moment]
[Kim Jong Kook got the gold piggie bank]
Check it.
- They're all empty
There's none that have money in it?
- Is there one with money in it?
- There's one with money in it!
[Empty]
[Now there's two golden piggies that are left to be found]
[Holding onto the empty piggie bank with a sad feeling]
[Gary who already found the piggie bank is being careful]
[Diligently searchers every single corner]
[Looking around]
What is it?
[Just then Hara discovers something]
[A corner of the museum that's dedicated to Park Ji Sung]
[The uniforms that Park Ji Sung wore]
[Even the diaries from his childhood are here]
[But within them...]
[Park Ji Sung's piggie bank?!]
There's another one?
[Hara saw it!]
[Hara acquires the next piggie bank]
[Hara! Like with God's help finds a piggy bank]
[Out of 4]
Now there's only one piggie bank left!
Look at this!
The hint that we got earlier was related to this.
We knew it right away.
- Saying that you knew it right away.
- That's right.
I know.
[Location of the last piggy bank]
[The official balls used in the world cup: But!]
[While the guys are having their immature arguments]
[Hara is trying to find it diligently]
[Oh!]
[Glances and tries to be careful as to not get caught]
[Lightly]
[It's almost coming out but]
[Ji Hyo happens to be walking nearby!]
[Tries to hide]
[What is she doing?]
[Tries to run away]
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are trying to block her!]
[Shocked oppas are on the move!]
[Special command is to save Goo Hara!]
[Until the horn sounds]
[The piggy bank must be protected!]
[Race Over]
[Final score-Away team: 1 & Home team]
Our future looks very bright.
[In this race, the home team beats the away team!]
- How about this?
- What?
We'll play rock paper scissors and the loser has to give up a piggy bank.
Because we have three.
- That sounds alright.
[Let's do it!]
[both teams are discussing it]
Alright, we'll bet one.
Let's just bet one.
So whichever team has one person left is the winner and gets the piggy bank.
Try a practice round.
[Jae Suk vs. Jong Kook]
[Since it concerns a piggy bank, it seems like there's so much tension]
Are you waving your fist at me right now?
I'm actually this kind of person. What about it?
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Jae Suk wins]
Jong Kook. Other than having muscles, what else can you do?
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Suk Jin wins]
[Ha Ha wins by playing a weird set of scissors]
[Both teams are getting serious]
It's not even this!
What are you going to play?
Me?
I'm not going to tell you.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Hara wins]
[There's three members left from each team]
Ji Hyo, you need to win.
Hold on! You guys have one more person. Then that means one of you has to come over here.
- Who?
[Huh?]
[There are the same amount of members, what is he talking about?]
[Has Suk Jin been transparent this whole time?]
Look, even your team members don't know your existence.
I didn't think you were here.
Let's do this.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Hara wins]
[I didn't even find a piggy bank]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Even though Hara was late, she still lost]
[Intimidating]
We won! We won!
How could you do that?
Is Ji Hyo actually angry?
- That scared me.
- It was my first time seeing her like that.
- You were too much.
- You were surprised too, right?
I was surprised.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Chun Hee wins]
This won't do.
[The away team only has Kwang Soo left]
[The two teams may end up with two piggy banks each!]
[Or one team may end up with all four piggy banks!]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Chun Hee wins!]
[In the end the home team ends up with all four]
[The only piggy bank that the away team had...]
[Bitter]
We should play again.
Let's play again.
But it looks very light?
It looks like it's empty?
- It should look like it's heavier.
- Let's see everyone's acting skills.
Pass it along to each other and try it.
One at a time.
How am I supposed to do this?
[Hesitantly]
Oh, that's good!
[Acting like it's heavy?!]
[Getting worked up]
[Satisfied]
You can't pick it up by yourself!
[Kwang Soo goes in to help]
Is it really that heavy?
[Ah, my foot!]
[Terrible acting]
[Ultimately even Gary joins in]
Don't let go of it with your hand.
Ji Hyo!
Let Ji Hyo do it by herself.
Can Ji Hyo do it by herself?
[Thud]
[Satisfied~ Up till now it's been good]
[Getting up with difficulty]
[Succeeds in lifting it above her head]
[Lastly it goes to Jae Suk]...
Jae Suk!
[A light thud sound]
The sound!
The end was a bit...
It was good up to here, but
The sound is what made a difference.
[A clear light sound!]
[High treason]
Let's just go.
We watched it well.
Just give us one.
Please give us just one.
Without any idea, what did you do?
- We even put the piggy bank on our feet.
- Let's put in our hands together.
I'm sorry but please do push ups.
It was my fault this time, but we just started. You know we have to stay out there until tomorrow morning.
There is the next game so let's cheer up.
- Fighting!
- We really have to try and do well.
He's regretful.
[MC Yoo is feeling hurt?!]
I feel a bit guilty.
[Number of piggy banks found]
Ah, during the first game unfortunately we were very regretful due to Hara.
What do you mean unfortunately~
- It was perfect.
- From our perspective, we're regretful.
- But it's not all good. We have to carry all of these piggy banks around.
- If it's inconvenient then give it to me.
What is the game this time?
That's far.
Please don't make our team climb around.
It's a cheering speed game.
The person giving clues stands in the audience seats. And the other members stand at the bottom, listen carefully and guess the answer.
It's easy.
What about the winner? How much money do they get?
You're going to give 50,000₩?
Ok, Ok.
Ok.
- Ok.
- They only have to explain what the answer is right?
Ha Ha can explain first!
[The first to explain is Ha Ha]
This is very easy, we can finish it quickly.
Shall we start?
- What is that?
- South Korea!
[No way!]
[Cheering squad game: Guess the answer through the shouts of people cheering!]
[Absurd]
[Everyone thought that it was an easy game]
[Now they can't see Ha Ha!]
South Korea!
[Since we're at a soccer stadium, we definitely need a game like this]
Jae Suk!
Where are all these people from?
Anyway, please take care of us.
[Can he be heard through the shouts of the cheering squad?]
Fighting!
[The sound is the same as how everyone hears it. The audience can join in the guessing too.]
[The answer: Bat]
Batman!
[As expected they can't hear at all]
It's an animal!
Bat!
- At Hagang River!
[Monster]
A girl with headphones!
Tyrannosaurus?
Young go and DDang Chili!
- Maeng Gu!
- Young!
Yeong Gu!
[Transformers]
- Robo cop!
- Iron man!
[Car... transforms?]
Transformers!
[Shout~]
How are we supposed to get it right with this kind of quiz?
Is this possible?
This is too tiring.
Next is the home team!
Kwang Soo, what happened?
He's holding the stick.
Please give him the stick.
[Why did Jong Kook take the gong stick?]
[And that~]
That thing is mine!
That's my lunch box!
Fighting!
[Home team: Song Joong Ki]
[Cheer: Go!]
- Follow me!
[Yi Sun Shin]
- Don Quijote?? (A Japanese store)
A Korean person!
Yoo Kwang Soon!
- Yoo Kwang Soon!
- Mac Arthur!
Kwanghwamun!
- Kang Kam Chan?
- Yi Sun Shin?
[Kim Yoo Shin]
[Hitting the horse...?]
- Kim Yoo shin!
- This is tiring!
- Ji Hyo's drama!
[Ju Mung]
- Drama!
- Frozen flower!
Frozen flower!
- Drama!
Ju Mung!
The person who invented this device.
[Edison]
[The one who invented the telephone is bell...]
Einstein?
Edison!
Choi Soo Jong!
We are losing. Give us a chance.
Just finish the game we will give it to you.
This round will decide who wins.
Simply put, please be kind!
Why do I have to say this? Then please get on
your knees and say~
- I must kneel?
- Just do push-ups!
- It's not a big deal to kneel.
No problem, it's not a big deal to kneel.
Just kneel once.
Yes.
Ah, yes.
Then kiss my knee...
[Kneeling replaced by kissing the knee!]
[Use Jae Suk's lips(?) for a chance to win!]
Please take it easy. Don't use too much strength~
Let's do our best.
[A decisive round!]
[Cheerleaders! GO!]
Sport! Sport!
[Figure skating]
Kim Yuna! Kim Yuna!
Skating?
Figure skating!
- Aaaarrg~
- Monster??
[Wrestling]
Wrestling!
[Back throw?!!]
Movie! National representative sportsmen~
Ski jumping!
- Ok Ju Hyun-ssi!
- Soccer!
[Yoga]
Soccer! Yoga!
Let's rest for a while.
Everyone help out a bit. Next one, next one.
[Cheerleaders! GO!]
[Harp]
Harp!
[Shout it out...]
Cello!
[Cello]
[Beat box]
[Acting like a fool]
Aaa~
[Opera]
[Castanets]
Castanets! Castanets!
[Home Team: 5 successful answer!]
[Kissed the knee and still lost...!]
[Lost again...]
It's the Home Team.
[Total number of golden pigs earned
Home Team: 4 golden pigs + 500,000₩
Away Team: 0]
- Everyone knows this game.
- Of course!
Hara, Ji Hyo, and Chun Hee might not know it.
[Last week's hot topic, and outstanding game!]
[Don't get your face blocked when the photo is taken!]
[Last week's shot!]
It's very simple. Even if we don't know when the shot will be taken,
the team with the most members shown will win.
We are confident because we have this hero here with us.
[Hero, peaceful evangelist, Gary!]
A friend who appears out of nowhere.
[Appears at the corner!]
- The national team has a special pose.
- It's like this.
This game is worth 500,000₩?
Ah! We must do our best.
Jong Kook looks so relaxed!
What, everytime it's like this? It's annoying!
In my next life, I'll begin exercising with dumbbells from 1 years old.
[Extremely naive]
You must study in our school.
[National team takes a photo!]
Yes!
[Hara quickly steps up]
[Very important to choose the right place first!]
[Come to the stage and disturb the others]
[At 190cm, the tallest player, Kwang Soo]
[At 171cm, the shortest player, Ha Ha]
Joong Ki, the camera isn't even on yet.
[How to pose?]
[Push]
[The Away Team looks favorable to win!]
[But]
[Joong Ki takes revenge!]
We are about to take the photo!
[The shot is coming!
Find a good place...]
[Jong Kook, a strong guard]
Hey, Jong Kook!
[Equally matched!
But must take a good pose!]
We won, we won.
[Home Team's Hara and Chun Hee with two good poses,
Success!]
Gary is there again!
Gary, you're there.
[Huk!]
Gary, look at your peaceful expression.
Our Jung Dae Sae is there.
Don't push, just block the other's faces.
With a smiling face and showing the teeth like this.
[1. With smiles 2. Show you teeth]
Players on the field!
Same places.
No pushing! Chun Hee, why are you like this?
Come here.
[Be careful, an early testing war]
You're here.
[Don't show this mouth!]
We're about to take the photo!
[Hard to breathe]
[Obviously~]
[Worth to see]
[Both teams show teeth!]
Aaa!
[The shot is taken!]
[Fell together, Round 2 colleagues!]
[The result is?]
It's there.
[Both teams are equal at 3 members each!]
Gary, how do you do this?
My childhood school photo.
Is it an ID photo?
Where did Ji Hyo and Hara go?
[When the photo was taken!]
[Both fell]
This time it's jumping.
Players on the field!
Greet the others.
Nice to meet you.
[To be captured by the camera when it goes off you need to continuously jump!]
We're starting now!
[Too bad if you fall!]
[Keep jumping and get into the angle!]
Run! Run!
[The atmosphere is slowly getting heated]
[Chaos in an instant]
[Shooting over]
[Huh? How did the picture come out?]
[I am unaffected...]
[The situation comes to a close]
[Today's photogenic!]
[He was definitely running...]
You just tiptoed, didn't you?
[The moment of glory]
[Right then!]
Isn't that photoshopped?
That looks like a passport photo!
How can his face come out so seriously?
Only Gary succeeds!
This time, you have to be within the specified area.
Make sure your face is visible.
We have Gary on our team.
[This game is easy for me!]
No matter what, Gary will show up.
Players, please enter the field.
Let's win this time.
[They have to crawl to fit in the frame!]
[All snuggled in!]
We're starting the shoot now!
[They have to pose avoiding the hands!]
[This time too...]
[It looks like he's going to be in the frame.]
[A last-minute effort!]
[Ji-Hyo hasn't won yet-she's getting rough!]
[Time to check the photo!]
[Gary isn't in it...]
[Ji Suk-Jin!]
[Comfortable...]
That's funny!
Ji-Hyo did well.
We have three team members in the photo.
I should have tried harder...
'Home' team wins!
Is there anything left to do now?
[A last-minute twist]
Let's have a game with just the ladies.
[A 1v1 face-off!]
[Hehe~]
You can win this! -She'll definitely win.
[Worried...]
The one who's captured jumping and smiling will win.
Players, enter the field!
[The representative players, to the front!]
[The ladies' battle of pride!]
[Jump! Jump!]
[Trying to smile and block at the same time]
At first, it looks like they are dancing!
Look at the camera! Look at the camera!
[When you look at it from a distance, it looks like a spectacle!]
[The shot is coming!]
[The ladies battle! The result is?]
[This?]
[is margin?]
[Collapse!]
You can see Hara's forehead!
You can see her forehead!
You can also see Ji Hyo's hair!
[Both of them failed!]
How about Gary and Sukjin Hyung?
Shall we do a jump shot?
We have to be in the right timing. Right?
[First, look for the right angle.]
It's funny already!
[Practicing the peaceful expression]
Who will have a more peaceful expression?
It's like your not jumping.
That kind of expression.
[Can I win over Gary?]
I believe in Gary.
This means nothing to me.
Gary doesn't really look like an entertainer.
Now we'll start the photo shoot!
[Photo zone war for the King of Kings!]
[Boink! Boink!]
Jump, Hyungnim!
[Already starting to jump, the trend of rap!]
It's not time yet.
I'm looking forward to this.
[Suk Jin Shot.]
- You have to smile.
- Make a natural expression, a natural expression.
[Both are slow to warm up.]
[Almost time to shoot!]
[Everything depends on this moment!
[Everything depends on this moment!]
Oh, they look very peaceful right now!
[The Battle of the Kings! Now, the results...]
[Between the two of them... the most relaxed is?]
[The photo is out!]
This one!
[No matter what happens.]
- This is hilarious!
- I knew this was going to happen!
[The game has ended!]
[Satisfied.]
[This... photo taken whilst jumping!]
How does he do this?
[Relaxed.]
- That's amazing!
- Our team wins!
- What exactly do you do?
[Photo Zone's Three Letter Summary.]
[Sense of Presence]
[Sense of Entertainment.]
[South Dae Sae]
*Pun off of Jung Dae Sae, a North Korean Soccer Player.
[Champion.]
[Gold Piggy Bank Count]
Oh it's here, it's here.
Hey, you're on our team.
You are an important person!
Find a swimsuit that matches your team's color and take the bus to the pool.
Where are the swimsuits?
An important person... a VIP?
- Oh?
- Shh!
Now, the bus to the swimming pool can be reached through the route to the right.
You need to get to the bus quickly.
[The bus leaves every ten minutes!]
[Five golden piggy banks wait at the swimming pool.]
Let's talk outside.
[Away team... What place?]
- Ji Hyo is right, an important person...
- VIP!
We can get there if we walk over here.
Run, run, run!
[The Away Team shows confidence for the first time today.]
- Isn't this the right color?
- It should be blue.
Is it a soccer uniform?
Let's go to the locker room first.
[Home Team: "Important Person" =Athlete]
Let's open the lockers. We might find something there.
[Home Team is heading towards the players' locker room.]
That's right, athletes would be important.
[The Home Team starts searching.]
Seems like it'd be here.
What is "your most important person"?
It doesn't seem to have a particular meaning.
- Then we need to start by finding clues.
- Oh, blue!
[Did we find it... Our team's swimsuit...]
[What did Chun Hee find?]
It's just a blanket. I really thought you found it.
[ There is a blue blanket in the locker ]
[ Disappointed ]
Are there any here?
It's locked
[ Oh! Again! ]
What is it?
Did you find something?
Come take a look here.
There are some uniforms hanged here.
It's here!
[ It's only the player's socks. ]
[ No matter how you look it,
these uniforms are strange ]
[ Are these swimsuits? ]
It's not the right color.
[ Searching carefully, trying to find the swimsuits ]
The word " Precious " seems to have a special meaning.
- No. I don't think so.
- There are still some more changing rooms over there.
The VIP room.
The VIP room..
The VIP room, where the most important people go.
- Yes.
[ The home team heads to the VIP room ]
[ At the other side, the away team
that noticed the VIP hint first. ]
[ The VIP Lounge ]
[ 3rd floor, the VIP Lounge is found ]
[ Where the important watch
the match from, the VIP lounge ]
[ Home is still searching for
their team's swimsuit color? ]
[ Lets go up, It doesn't seem like it's here ]
It's not here.
[ The 3rd floor VIP room, nothing is found ]
[ It must be the 4th floor, then ]
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
[Get on, get on!]
Is everything okay?
[The Hope Team arrives to search the 3rd floor.]
[The Yang Team finds the same clue.]
- We have to go that way?
It's hard to find clues.
- That team looks like they haven't found anything.
- Should we just give up?
We can't give up...
Bring the walkie talkie.
Ah, there's nothing...
Where do we have to go?
Joonki, can you hear me?
What about you Hara?
I hear you.
[Warm atmosphere]
This is too big.
Our color.
Over here.
[Named after many gems, the 4th floor VIP room.]
[The VIP Room that matches the swimsuit and team color.]
We're red, so we're not diamond.
[Diamonds are clear gems!]
The away team is searching the ten gem rooms one by one.
The blue tinted gem, Opal.
Oh? Where is it?
[The three go to inspect the balcony.]
[Jihyo finds something under the seat!]
[Unusual bag]
[First, open the bag to see what's inside.]
- Lock the door! Lock the door!
[A blue swimsuit!]
Who is blue?
[If it's blue, then it's the Home Team's swimsuit.]
[Where is the Away Team's swimsuit?]
Follow me!
[Goes to search VIP hallway again.]
[Location of Away Team's swimsuit.]
[Haha hides Home Team's bag first.]
I found the other team's swimsuit,
but we need to find ours.
- Jae Suk, where are you?
- He's with me.
[Gary starts to walk faster.]
I found it!
Is it the right color?
[They found their team's swimsuit outside of the Ruby Room.]
Hyung, we found it. Hurry, hurry!
The Away Team is the first to gather.
[The shuttle arrives in one minute!]
Found it! Found it!
Jihyo's the one who found it.
[VIP Room Search's hero, Jihyo.]
It's thanks to Ji Hyo.
[The fateful, Spring-like meeting of Ji Hyo.]
[Meanwhile, Joong Ki and Hara saw everything.]
That team seems to have found their swimsuits.
- Hurry!
- Take the bus, take the bus!
[Unexpected Meeting.]
Wait a second, let's talk for a bit.
Wait.
[Pretending...]
Hurry and find your swimsuits.
- Hold on for a second
- You guys should go look for it.
[Home team's swimsuits.]
[Without a walkie talkie, they can't do anything...]
[The shuttle arrives!]
You guys can't go on now.
[The Away Team is stopped by Joong Ki and Hara.]
[We also wanted to find our swimsuits...]
We can leave once we all get on.
We worked really hard to find this.
Run over me!
Catch the next bus!
[The next bus comes in 10 minutes...]
We're leaving!
- Don't be like this!
- Joong Ki, see you later!
- See you later!
[Catch your swimbag!]
[Fooled!]
[Complete Success.]
[The smiling winner, Ji Hyo!]
[The golden piggy banks and more await them at the swimming pool.]
Where did the hyungs go?
Where is it?
[Working hard on the fourth floor.]
You guys found it?
- Where did you go?
- They already left!
- What?
They took both of them and we couldn't get on the bus.
- We have to wait for ten more minutes.
- Is this ours?
They tossed it to us after leaving.
Where did you find it?
Why didn't you contact us?
They didn't have the walkie talkies.
So, we couldn't contact you guys.
In my opinion, it's his fault.
If we're late by 10 minutes, how badly will that affect us?
Since the other team already left, they might find the piggy banks in the first ten minutes.
Can we save time by changing into our swimsuits here?
What if we miss the bus while we're changing?
That's the worst case scenario.
Let's just go ahead and change.
Hurry up and change.
[Quickly changes into the swimsuits.]
It looks like we just broke out of prison...
[Looks like a pile of prison outfits.]
It's here, it's here!
Joong Ki! Hurry!
Wait just a second! I'm putting on my underwear.
Joong Ki!
Where is he?
Hurry up.
Alright, let's go.
[The Home Team Gets on the Bus]
[To the Swimming Pool!]
[The Away Team Arrives First.]
We should hurry!
[Quickly put on the swimsuits and rush to the pool.]
[The gigantic pool after closing hours.]
Why are we here?
[They discover the golden pig on the diving board!]
[First to catch me will be the owner! Hurry up!]
Why is it up there?
- But how do we get up there?
- Just go up and grab it.
[Haha heads up the 3.5 meter platform.]
Ah, how do I do this?
[Jae Suk heads toward the 10 meter platform.]
Oh, I'm really scared now.
Do we need to go further?
[Ji Hyo easily reaches the 10 meter platform.]
[First two to arrive at the platforms.]
[Alone on the shaking diving board.]
Hold on to this and stop shaking.
What do we do if it falls?
If it falls, grab it and fall with it!
[Will the timid Kwang Soo have enough courage?]
[He only needs to reach out his hand...]
[Kwang Soo acquires one piggy bank!]
[Timid third person claps behind them.]
[The Away Team leads with one piggy bank!]
[Meanwhile, at the 10 meter platform...]
[Just getting to that height was difficult!]
- Are you not scared?
You aren't scared?
Can you reach it?
[Dizzy.]
[Kwang Soo is also scared to get close to the edge.]
[Taking large steps.]
Hey, be careful!
[Grabs]
[Ji Hyo grabs the second pig.]
Are you still not scared?
[Ji Hyo who loses all the time is not scared.]
I'm still scared.
You have no fear. Can you walk to the edge?
[Kwang Soo stands at the edge, looking for another pig.]
Oh, there's one over there!
[Hehehe.]
Let's get down first.
Where is it?
I'm going.
Hurry, hurry!
[Ji Hyo supervises from the platform.]
Where are they?
Go over there!
Where Haha is standing!
[Inside the water?]
[There's a golden pig at the bottom of the pool!]
[Splash!]
[Kwang Soo goes in.]
Do you know how to swim?
It's really deep over there.
[Something is there!]
Do you know how to swim?
Are there swimming goggles?
Kwang Soo, move over there a bit.
[Getting closer.]
[It's down there!]
I'll go down and help!
[Haha jumps into the pool.]
[Jae Suk joins the two as well.]
[If they get this one, they'll have three.]
[The golden object is very far down.]
How deep is this? Five meters?!
[Very serious.]
[Ji Hyo runs to help the guys.]
[Provides swimming goggles!]
Fighting! Fighting!
Jihyo, take care of the pigs!
At this time, the Home Team arrives ten minutes late.
Hara's here. Oh they're here!
- Oppa, oppa!
- What's happening?
Is there something in there?
Go!
Chun Hee dives into the water.
- It's somewhere in the swimming pool.
- Where is it?
[Jong Kook also enters!]
[Just like before, going close below is difficult]
[It's down there, but it's somewhat dificult to reach...]
[Even if you have a scuba diving certification]
[Whoosh]
[Energy zero!]
[Kwang Soo tries again]
Why do you keep taking off your clothes?
[By any chance if you have a naked body will it be possible to go close?]
[As expected. A pointless expectation...]
[Jong Kook tried one more time[
[Tries to submerge in the deep!]
[Oh?! That is...?]
[Something... is strange]
This isn't a pig?
[Kwang Soo hears this and reconfirms]
[By chance, there's a ball on the bottom of the swimming pool]
It's not a pig!
It's not a pig?
It was pink!
[The home team moves on to find another pig]
What is this?
[There's really a golden pig!]
[Diving Pool]
[Haha's one man challenge!]
[without any obstacle, goes deep]
[This time it's surely a pig!]
First take a deep breath of air and hold your nose.
And dive.
[Kwang Soo did it as he was taught but]
[this time HaHa?!]
[As expected!]
Don't do it, don't do it.
[The Home Team leaves to search the other side of the pool.]
- How did you do it?
- Like this.
[Kwang Soo challenges!]
[Without stopping]
[Finally grabbed it!]
[Unexpected image for the timid Kwang Soo!]
[The Away Team acquires three piggy banks.]
[Disheartened]
[Searching here and there]
[Hara, the only one who didn't go into the water]
[Something glimmers from in the water]
[General Pool]
[Hara enters the water]
[Indeed, it's a golden piggy bank!]
- Oppa!
- Did you find one?
[ It's a bit too deep for Hara... ]
[Jong Kook goes after it]
[ Home Team acquires a piggy bank! ]
- Did they find one?
- It was over there.
[ Did Chun Hee find something? ]
[ Did I see it incorrectly? ]
[ It's over there... ]
[The last piggy is between the floating mats and the rubber plates]
[ Hara searches the deck after finding the piggy in the water ]
[ Looking ]
[ Hara finds something underneath the stack ]
[ Carefully ]
[ Hara finds the last piggy bank ]
Found it!
Oh, it was scared. Look, it's peeing on itself.
- This time...
- There's another round?
It's a cumulative diving competition.
As you can see there are 1.5 m, 3.5 m, 5 m, 7.5 m, and 10 m boards.
Each team member's platform height is added up and the team with the greatest score wins.
Each person picks a height to jump off the diving board.
The team with the greatest cumulative score wins.
If you choose a lower height,
the next jumper would have to pick a higher platform in order to make up for it.
Suk Jin used to be in the navy.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, but we didn't learn how to swim in the navy.
We only did performances while holding a mic.
For our team,
let's start with Haha.
[Chill ]
Let's start with the weakest member first.
Fighting!
How many meters are you going to challenge?
I'll decide when I get there.
No, you have to decide first before you dive.
Haha, how about 1.5 meters?
[ Recommends the lowest height for the other team ]
This is like your apartment's balcony.
[ Worry ]
Eh, you have to go at least 5 meters.
That's really high...
- How can I do 5?
- 3.5 m then, 3.5.
-3.5!
[ Haha bets on 3.5 m ]
[ Deep breath ]
Haha,
I'm really disappointed in you.
[ Throw ]
Okay.
[ Away Team's Haha bet on 3.5 m ]
[ This one ]
[ Still confident ]
I really wanted to go from this height...
[ That's understandable... ]
[ But a man has to maintain his pride! ]
[ What is he doing? ]
Is he going to take that with him so that he doesn't die?
[ Taking the buoy. Life Instinct! ]
[ The steps going up feel heavy ]
[ Finally reaches the platform ]
Oppa that isn't it.
[ Disappointed ]
It's not that one.
Oh, this is really no joke.
Haha, just do it.
Suddenly, I'm starting to tear up.
It's not that one!
It's the one next to it.
[ Finally arrived at 3.5 m ]
Is it high?
That height is alright.
Going down is really scary.
[ It feels higher when you actually get there! ]
You can't buy time like that now!
[ Hwak ]
[ Checking the drop time? ]
[ At 3.5 m, it's more than twice Haha's height. ]
- Why do you keep taking off your shirt?
- My face would be covered by it.
[ Tucking it into his pants ]
It looks like he's really scared.
This is really no joke!
Haha, you have to.
[ Get into position ]
Applause!
Wow!
Haha fighting!
Hurry up and do it!
Fighting! You can do it!
To be honest, that height doesn't deserve applause.
You look funny right now.
If you're scared go from the 1.5 m board.
I'm going!
[ Here I go ]
Seriously uncool, seriously!
[ Shaking ]
If you can't do that, you're not a man.
I'm not a man!
[ We can't wait anymore! ]
You can do it!
Run with your eyes closed!
Close your eyes and jump!
[ Okay! ]
[ Just once, with eyes closed... ]
[ For the sake of the team... ]
[ Jump! ]
3.5 m, success!
Seriously not cool!
[ Sinking for a while ]
Seriously uncharismatic.
Away Team's Haha succeeds at 3.5 m.
You came out well.
I'm disappointed in you.
I'm disappointed, really...
Why?
Our total is 3.5 m.
- Who is going first?
- Hyung, do 5 m.
If I do 5, the next person has to do 7 m.
No, that's not the rule...
- I'll just do 3.5.
- Just do 5.
[ Oh my ]
- How can I do 5?
- You have to do the height you said you would.
How can I do 5?!
I'll jump from 5 m then!
Really?
Joong Ki challenges 5 meters.
[ Home Team's Joong Ki bets on 5 m ]
[ Though he appears to be calm... ]
[ 5m is a dizzying height... ]
[ If he can succeed, the Home team would have a 1.5 m lead ]
[ His footsteps are steady ]
[ He goes up, and up... ]
[ And finally arrives ]
Woah!
How is it?
Because the water is so deep, the fear is doubled.
It'll be okay!
It's really scary!
You don't have to do it.
You can do it! Fighting!
It's not something to be embarrassed about if you can't.
Just give up!
Just go down by one platform.
Just go down by one! Give up!
I'm going!
[ The 1.5 m...
[ is definitely ours! ]
[ Will Joong Ki succeed the 5 m jump? ]
Don't look over here!
[ You must jump to succeed. ]
[ If I don't jump high enough... the others have to take a higher platform. ]
And...
Another obstacle beyond imagination!
[ Sprinting up 43,000 flights of stairs! ]
[ Which team will escape? ]
Running man.
You're really out of shape...
How are you going to continue like that?
[ Heros Preview ]
[ Preview ]
How old are you IU?
[ Who is the most popular amongst them? ]
[ For the sake of ranking popularity ]
Rude!
[ Invited to stay for their first night ]
Heros