Original hardsubs by KJK Global
Transcribed by HapB
Color and alignment by SamFive
Today's
Landmark
SBS Broadcast Center
The place for producing
all of SBS programs
Unusual guests for today
Jang
Dongmin
Lizzy
Jihyo
Unrelenting fight of
willpower
Today SBS will be their
running field
A hectic chase to deliver
the tapes in time
Now starting
Mokdong
Broadcasting Center
Eh?
Only 3 people?!
What? We're on standby?
We're on standby right now.
Hey, let's start.
Here, come here.
You should stand here.
Flustered
Why are you like
this from the start?
If you stand here, then hyung can
get the feeling of being in the center.
How can you go to the other side??
Why is hyung so persistent
of being in the center?
Hey, Jaesuk hying is not here,
what do you mean by starting?
They'll come after they
done the punishment.
Right, the punishment.
I'm looking forward to them.
From what I know ...
Omo...Omokgyo... They have
to start walking from there.
* Omokgyo is one station away from SBS
Punishment: Walk from Omokgyo
station to SBS in hot pants
Omokgyo?
Yes.
Showing their thighs
3 men coming to work
Wearing filming costume on top of hot pants
More embarrassing this time
Before the Chuseok holiday weekend
more people on the streets
Entering the coffee shop
Hello.
Surprised
It's Yoo Jaesuk.
We should order whatever
that is available fast.
What is available in the shortest time?
Iced Americano.
3 Iced Americanos, then.
All at the same time
Coming outside
Chaotic
Embarrassed
Hello everyone.
Its raining.
It is raining, but ...
Just when we are in hot pants.
hot pants
Hey, this makes us speed walk.
Speed walking.
So embarrassed they start to speed walk
Almost there.
Twist
Oh, they are here.
Embarrassing
We're not changing?
Alarmed because they must
film the opening in hot pants
We should be able to change.
Kwangsoo ...
We should change clothes or do you
want us to film the opening like this?
You all are so comical.
And Kim Jongkook you were ...
Yes.
... so happy you were exempt from the punishment
that your smile went all the way like this.
Yah, you really ...
Wow, today really ...
Today, really...
We were trying to recruit
Song Jihyo to our team.
No, oppa.
Which team you want
to be in? Here or there?
Then Jihyo will go to your team?
Earlier you told us that you wanted
to come over to our team.
When did I say that?
Didn't you say so?
Contradicting
When did they
become so close?
Earlier, 10 minutes ago.
No, I didn't.
Close your mouth ~
Here they come.
Welcoming the guests
At this time
Lizzy ~
Funny man
Jang
Dongmin
After School's
youngest
Lizzy
You move away, go over there.
Betrayal
Oh, Lizzy.
Hello ~
I wanted to meet you.
Hello, we wanted to meet you.
Lively 19 years old girl
So cheerful.
Today's guest Lizzy is so lively.
Wow, Lizzy is here, Lizzy.
Lizzy's hot blooded fan
Ah, Lizzy ...
Ah, Dongmin ...
Why are you wearing this?
Shy
Dongmin, tomorrow is Chuseok weekend ...
Yes.
If you take part in Running Man you'll
have a hard time going back tomorrow.
Well ...
When I received the invitation
from Running Man ...
Yes.
... I thought I was doing well.
Then I heard that filming is today ...
... and I realized I was invited
because no one else is available.
Everyone else is rushing
back to their hometowns.
No, that's not it.
Lizzy, your hometown
is in Busan right?
Yes.
The slight satori we hear has warmth.
It does have warmth.
It's very charming.
I'm from Busan.
Proud
You're from Busan.
Today's landmark is no other place
but SBS broadcast station, so ...
... we're familiar with this place.
Very familiar.
Dongmin, aren't you familiar
with this place too?
Here?
Yes.
I should know this place well, but ...
Don't you come here often?
SBS ...
No, I did radio shows
here about twice.
Lizzy, which is the most
familiar place for you?
KBS.
Innocent
maiden
At SBS Lizzy said the name of
the name of K-company
Well, that's where Lizzy goes often.
Nation MC taking care
It's the place Lizzy visits the most.
She's more familiar with KBS, not SBS.
You guys should get them here more often.
Please invite me more often.
Cheerful
There are lots of
things I want to do.
What do you want to do?
I would like to be in sitcoms.
What role?
A cheerful character.
Yes, I'd like to do that and ...
A darling, she is the new
darling of variety, our Lizzy.
And I hope to try MC too.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I want to take part in WGM too.
* WGM = MBC Show "We Got Married"
Why say that at SBS...
A strong character who ...
wants to be in all three
broadcasting companies
So candid without any fear.
Anyway ....
Anyway, Running Man today ...
Today's Running Man
Lively and cute Lizzy ...
We have the fearless Lizzy ...
... and Dongmin together.
... and also smart and witty Dongmin
Although I do not know
about today's mission yet.
First of all ...
Yes?
Lets decide on the punishment first.
Shall we?
I heard that it's been decided for today.
What?
Take part in SBS Morning News?
Today's
punishment
SBS morning program
Live broadcast
What time is the program?
Because you are already here ...
... the punishment has to be in
line with the station's specialty.
We're going to go on the show?
What will we have to do?
It's a live broadcast, how would we...?
There's a segment ...
Yes.
... ﻿and you have to take
part in that segment.
Morning Wide
Part 3
Actual situation
Running Man on Morning Wide
Four members from
Running Man are here.
Hello ~
Celebrities' biggest fear:
Live broadcast
Revealed later
Will Jihyo have to draw a mustache?
A yangban mustaches.
* Yangban - Aristocrats/gentry of historical Korea
I've noticed that even without
drawing a mustache ...
... after filming, your mustache will be growing.
Indeed
Slanderer
Kwangsoo
Always due to this kid.
First of all, this ...
I have a question.
What is it?
Can the guests receive
the punishment as well?
Of course.
I'm happy, I will be able to take
part in a live broadcast program.
Today's variety's darling Lizzy
anticipate her upcoming performance
So lively, really lively.
I like coming on TV.
Wow, this is really awesome.
Here's the cutting edge
News Center
This is my first time here.
They have a huge ...
Working section and broadcasting coexists
to ensure swift news
Exactly.
What's that? The stuff that's all lined up?
If there's a news story ...
... so they can broadcast
the latest news instantly.
Oh, there are these, as well.
This is a prompter.
A tool so the news anchor can look
at the camera while reading the script
Prompter
Words will be shown there.
There’ll be text here? Ahha ...
Jongkook furtively sitting on the anchor seat
Do I look like an anchor?
You look like an Olympic gold medalist.
Olympic gold medalist?
Newscaster
Kwangsoo?
This place is so impressive.
First game will be right here
in the news broadcast center
Everyone knows where is this place right?
Isn't this the News Studio?
Where the 8 PM news is broadcast.
Yes, the 8 PM instant news.
So shall we start now?
Yes.
First Mission
Catch the thief
The 9 members will get a
Running Man postcard each.
The thief
One of the cards
is the thief-card.
Each member will draw 1
card from the next player.
Thief
At the end, all will receive a Running Ball
except the person holding the thief-card.
Are we going to get it done in one go?
Yes the postcards.
Wow, the postcards are so pretty.
Who do you think this picture resembles?
I saw who drew this.
Uncle Yoo Jaesuk.
* Seonssaeng literally means teacher, but is
used to convey respect and age difference.
Lizzy, I am not an Uncle.
Uuuuuncle~
Uncle Ji Sukjin, Uncle Kim Jongkook.
Please don't.
Who is oppa, from what age?
Oppa?
Yes, starting from who?
HaHa oppa?
To Lizzy the 32 years old HaHa is her oppa
Of course.
Why am I not oppa?
Annoyed
32 years old Uncle Jongkook
Because you're over 30.
He's over 30 too.
Ah, really?
Oppa.
Alright
Okay.
immediately dismissing his anger
Upon hearing oppa
She doesn't just say oppa.
Oppa ~
Jihyo, you need to ...
Pressures Jihyo to be
more charming
Close your mouth ~
Strongly rejecting
Are you ready?
Yes.
Everyone take 1 card, just 1.
Please do it properly today.
This is mine.
Don't mess up.
Have you shuffled?
Yes, I've shuffled.
Who will get the the thief card?
Don't let others see your card.
Like this, and take a look at your card.
Jaesuk
Thief card
Bingo
Not like this?
Lizzy mistakenly shows her card
You can't.
Change quickly.
No.
Lets redistribute.
Stubborn
No, wait.
Hey, he's acting weird.
I'm holding the thief card.
Re-shuffle, I'm holding the thief card.
Thanks to Lizzy Jaesuk is revived
Otherwise Jaesuk would have been
the thief for 2 consecutive weeks
I was about to cry, really.
Why am I always the one?
I'm sorry
Please shuffle properly.
Seriously, why am I always the thief?
You pick one out from the stack.
Alright, then I'll pick one first.
You pick one first.
Okay, that's it, you don't
bother about the rest.
I will distribute the rest now..
Okay, for Jihyo.
Really, if I get the thief card again ....
Uneasy
Please take it.
Helping Jaesuk so hands of misfortune(?)
will not go through him
I got a shock just now.
This is quite nerve wracking.
I was so surprised.
This time the thief card
falls into whose hands?
Kwangsoo
Running Man card
Jihyo too
Anticipating Jaesuk turn
Happy now?
You're really like a sculpture.
Surprised?
Running Man card
You are trying to look at
mine secretly, aren't you?
So it's mine?
Then Jongkook?
Thief card
Bingo
Deep ...
sigh
Let the person next to you
pick one card from you.
1st round of card selection
Starting from me?
Kwangsoo, you only have
to give her your card.
Noona for you.
Well prepared card.
Dejected looking thief Jongkook
Dongmin will choose from the cards.
Have to pretend they
have the thief-card
Take it.
Seems like the thief-card is there.
Don't let anyone see.
It's very important not to let anyone see.
Anxiety
Too bad, it
goes this way
You know, right? I am
famous for being unlucky.
Even if I'm the thief ...
In the 13 episode I got the
punishments about 10 times.
Punishment specialist
Even when I got 3 Running Balls,
none of them came out, remember?
Trying to smile The thief on-duty
Quite relaxing.
This? You sure?
Uneasy
Only the viewers and Jongkook
know where the thief card is
Really, I have no idea.
I have absolutely no clue today.
Finally Jongkook's turn to get rid of a card
Of course.
Please...
take it
Frozen
Where is Lizzy reaching?
The thief card Lizzy
Hey, its visible.
Bitter
Awkward smile...
That's right.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, that's good.
Lizzy trying to be cool
This one?
Yes.
No.
This one?
Yes.
This one.
Gary didn't pick the card Lizzy suggests
That's good, guess correctly.
What is
going on?
Lizzy still holding the thief-card~
End of card picking
What is the next game?
Word games.
Since we're at a News Center
Conveying our language properly
Word game?
Is two syllables okay?
* Saying words with 2 syllables, next person starts
with the syllable the other person ended with
Yes.
Two syllables.
He's so confident.
The winner gives away their
card and leave the game
We'll play with 2 syllables.
We'll begin from HaHa, start.
Please start quickly.
Goosebumps.
So-Reum
Music.
* Reum to Eum is okay since it's a sound rule
Eum-Ak
Instrument.
Ak-Gi
Skill.
Gi-sool
Wine glass.
Sool-Jan
Draft liquor.
Jan-Sool
Wine bottle.
Sool-
Byeong
Byung ...
You can’t curse.
Slanderer Kwangsoo's
sudden attack
Out ~
Blank Jihyo
Out
How hard must it have been, Jihyo out.
My lips really wanted to say it.
Song Jihyo, out.
Start, quickly.
Ousted ones
Jihyo - Dongmin
Tunnel.
Teo-Neol
Plank.
Neol-Pan
Board.
Pan-Ja
Child.
Ja-Shik
Food.
Shik-
Poom
Out of stock.
Poom-
Jeol
Rick cake ~
Jeol...Pyeon
Hey, your pronunciation.
It was Jeol-Pyun ~
Letters.
Resuming
Pyun-Ji
Ji-Soo.
Ji-Soo?
Huh?
Jisoo?
Ji-Soo.
Who is Jisoo?
My girlfriend from 8th grade ...
... Jisoo.
Out.
She's the one who lent me
her choir book at church.
It’s like Bruce Lim.
I didn’t have a choir book.
It’s like 'Bruce Lim' from two weeks ago.
Why can't I recall my first love?
You’re out ~
Kwangsoo, HaHa, Gary, Lizzy,
Jongkook, Jaesuk is left
Glasses.
An-
Gyeong
Police ~
Kyeong-
Chal
Chal...
Glutton rice cake.
Chal-
ddeok
Suddenly
Glutton rice cake ~
Boldly helping Gary Jihyo
You ...
Think it to yourself.
Jihyo ...
We told you to think it to yourself.
A barrage of complaints
Jihyo style is like those who at home answer
the questions on a quiz show themselves.
Please let it go once, this is
the first time she helped me.
Okay.
It was the first time.
Okay, gluten rice cake.
Jihyo's gluten rice cake is okay
Twig ~
Ddeok-
Nip
Situation ~
Ib-Jang?
Caught
What's with your situation?
You can’t do that.
Ah...
Oh, my face is getting
all red, he said ib-jang.
It’s supposed to be a "p".
Because we understand your situation.
Yes ~
Can't even insist
Easily agreeing
It’s me ~
Only 5 people
left, right.
Let's go.
Kwangsoo HaHa Gary Lizzy Jaesuk
Again starting the word game
Professor.
Bak-Sa
Person.
Sa-Ram
Rambo.
Lam-Bo
Gem.
Bo-seok
Slate.
Seok-
Pan
Cardboard.
Pan-ji
Jisoo.
The name he always thinks
of when he is clapping
Why are you like this?
If it starts with 'ji' he wants it to end with 'soo'
Big Nose hyung's feelings
Why would you go, hyung?
Why won't you let me think
of my first love Jisoo?
Why do you keep jumping in?
Because we're clapping,
I want to as well.
Then don't clap.
Hyung, go to the back.
And those who aren’t playing stop clapping.
Everyone else please do not clap.
Income.
Soo-ji
Ji?
Jihyo?
Ji-hyo? ♥
Calling in a low voice
that name Jihyo ♥
Jihyo works too.
Nonsense
No, that doesn't work.
out
Gary
Jihyo?
Let's start with HaHa.
Kwangsoo HaHa Lizzy Jaesuk survived
How is HaHa doing so well?
Good news.
Nang-Bo
Expectation.
Bo-Ram
Rambo.
Lam-Bo
In his memories(?) of Jisoo Big Nose
Fortnight.
Bo-Reum
Tone deaf.
Eum-Chi
Sound rule
Fool.
Chi-Gol
Headache.
Gol-Chi
Range.
Chi-Yeok
Mathematics
Weight.
Yeok-Ki
Well done
Train.
Ki-Cha
Outfit.
Cha-Lim
Cough?
Outfit.
What is this?
It worked.
King.
Im-Geum
Cough
I apologize.
No ~
You're out ~
When put in a corner
Kwangsoo's cough
No, you’re out.
Ah, so funny.
If you lose the beat, you’re out.
But I started coughing.
From when you coughed.
This is a complex of mine.
It’s okay, he looks like he's in pain.
Because he was funny they try to help
Look at him, he’s hurt.
Yah, Kwangsoo ...
He's choking, give him some water.
It could have been bad.
That’s not fair.
We can't do that.
Using a witty trick(?) to get away
from danger Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo, you can't cough any more.
Yes, I understand.
Outfit.
Cha-Lim
King.
Im-Geum
Sound rule
Gold tooth.
Geum-Ni
Nipper ~
Ni-Peo
Puzzle.
Peo-Jeul
Jeul ...
It's here The attacking syllable
"Jeul"
COUGHING
This time won't go easy
Kwang
soo
out
Who’s left?
HaHa
The only ones left
Lizzy
Jaesuk
Lizzy, me and HaHa.
How is HaHa doing so well?
Let's see ...
I only have to beat HaHa
and Uncle Jaesuk?
thief-card away for sure
I'll give my
Okay, let’s start.
Jaesuk
HaHa
Lizzy
3 strong players
Dialogue.
Dae-Sa
Boss.
Sa-Jang
Rose.
Jang-Mi
Art.
Mi-sool
Wine glass.
Sool-Jan
Grass ~
Jan-Di
Design.
Di - Ja - In?
Jaesuk
out
There's nothing for "Di".
Di-Geut.
* Koreans have names for their letters
and digeut is the name of "ㄷ"
Ah.. there was Di-Geut... ha ha
Two people left, HaHa starts.
Now if Lizzy can beat HaHa
goodbye thief-card
The last round
HaHa
Lizzy
Chair.
Eui-Ja
Heir.
Ja-Sik
Meal.
Sik-Sa
Fact.
Sa-Sil
Director.
Sil-
Jang
Tall stature.
Jang-
Sin
Shoe.
Sin-Bal
Ballet.
Bal-Let
Let's ... go.
HaHa
out
Lizzy wins.
Whoohoo~
Word game Lizzy 1st place
Is this the power of the thief-card?
Well done.
It is a pity to be in the 3rd place
for a 2 syllables word speed game.
It’s just a game.
Yawning Dongmin caught
As if 2 midnight recordings
Are you alright?
I was excited.
Looks like a very tired excited expression
The game is surprisingly interesting.
I'm not the thief, so don't reject it.
Of course.
Lizzy, just bang the cards
down on the table directly.
Just bang it down?
Right, don't choose me.
Just like this.
That's it.
Without saying...
the thief
Controlled expression
Ha ha ha
Mixed
feeling
2nd card picking
You will get a good card.
Meaningless acting in front of the thief
Seriously.
Current thief doesn't need to think much
But this man is very worried
Tell me when you're ready.
Jaesuk's cards now
2 Running Man
A thief card
Are you done?
Why are your hands shaking?
What?
This is heavy.
This is heavy?
Yes.
Your hand is shaking violently.
You haven't held 3 cards before have you?
And...
Is it really?
The thief card
Survived
Impressive
fake sigh
And
Why are you suddenly doing
something you usually don't do?
a real deep sigh
Ha ha ha
The thief Jongkook who doesn't
know how to control his feelings
Why are you suddenly...?
The other Running Man who are
unable to comprehend the situation
Are you acting right now?
It was a
nightmare
Jongkook who is continually
fated with the thief card today
What will Gary's choose?
The way you are looking at me is weird.
Thief card with full
marks popularity today
The intensity of the card drawing which is
comparable to the pain during childbirth(?)
Did Gary pick
that card...?
Gary's forced smile
Holding his
laughter
The viewers
Gary &
Jongkook
know where the thief-card is
Can I pick now?
Which one is it.
Gary looks really ugly today.
What did you say?
It is okay if other people say it ...
... but on what grounds
can you say that I'm ugly?
Because there will be a thief
who is as red as my face.
No way...
Explodes
Gary
pushing it up
with his thumb
So it's like that.
It'll end after Jihyo picks a card
HaHa
Jihyo doesn't know anything Goes forward
Come here, come nearer.
Hold on a second.
Why are you angry?
Ah, why do you act like that?
This is supposed to be a segment
where we take our time.
I get it, hurry up.
Jihyo picked a card
without hesitation
But why this...
The thief card is just like a baton
Amazing
being passed on during a relay
Don't tell
me Jihyo?
Jihyo's expression is a little ...
Now the thief card
is with Blank Jihyo
Phew...
The next game is a very simple
game called the Zero Game.
From 1 to 7 whoever gets it wins.
Call out a number from 0 to 7 and
if the numbers of raised microphones
tally with the number called out, you win
It's that simple.
Two winners will get running
balls and will exit the game.
Ah good, two people.
From 0 to 7... Ready, start.
Two.
Slide~
You can't be like this.
Peaceful Gary is the only
person who raised the mic
How can you look directly into her
eyes and raise it just like this?
I can hear Jihyo's voice through my ears.
Automatic
response
Seven.
Self performance
Shouting by himself
and raising by himself
Anxious thief Jihyo
Two.
3 people raised it Unfortunate failure
Three.
A shout in silence
Even though he shouted loudly...
What are you doing?
That was to me?
Compared to the failure
Gary's sadder that Jihyo didn't raise hers
Didn't you hear my voice?
Now HaHa.
Three.
Hmm?
Slow motion?
I thought you were
shooting a music video.
Now, Ji Hyo, Ji Hyo.
Me?
The best chance to
get rid of the thief card
Three.
But?
Success
Pleased
What are both of you doing?
Why did you raise it with her?
Jihyo success.
Nervous HaHa knows Jihyo has the thief-card
Now Dongmin.
Three.
Got a shock
Why do you keep raising?
Dongmin the 2nd person to succeed
Why do you keep raising Gary?
I'm not very sure of the game rules.
I raised because I got a shock.
I really got a shock.
Zero Game Winners
Jihyo & Dongmin freed themselves
from their cards
You can go first.
Jihyo * Dongmin
Who will they give their cards to?
Me?
Yes.
Start talking.
Give Jihyo the cards and make it a 3 bomb.
We can do it like that?
I'm giving it to Donghoon oppa.
What?
Shocked
Give this to him at the same time.
Because he provoked
Jihyo without reason
This will do, good job.
Card rich HaHa who got 3 cards at once
The thief card is back with HaHa
Lastly let’s play rock paper
scissors to change seats.
Rock paper scissors?
Rock paper scissors.
Sukjin
Gary
Win
Rock, paper, scissors.
Paper
Rock
The fate of the thief card
will fall on Big Nose hands
Jaesuk, I have treated you well, right?
Of course.
Give me a kiss here.
Sukjin requested a knee kiss
Doing as told to avoid getting
thief-card
Once is enough doing it
five times is too much.
Just once?
Yes.
I have no other motives,
I just wish to sit beside.
Really want to sit beside me?
Yes.
Always beside hyung~
Change place with Jaesuk.
Jaesuk
HaHa
exchange
seats
I have no other motives, I only
wish to sit beside hyung.
Thank you.
Exchange of fate between them
Jongkook both of you change seats.
exchange
seats
Gary
Jong
kook
I've known Jaesuk for many years,
so I don't want him to have 4 cards.
Therefore, lastly, exchange
place with Jongkook.
Lastly
Jong
kook
Jaesuk
exchange
places
Jongkook hyung
is in danger
Ha ha
Is this the end?
It wouldn't be here, right?
Now nobody knows?
Don’t know.
Now let's show our cards.
Starting from Jongkook.
Jongkook's thief-card confirmation
Ha ha
Don't worry it's not there.
Thief
Jongkook's day?
A good choice
Jongkook is the thief
So it is there?
Today's wanderlust(?) The thief-card
went all around and came back to Jongkook
Bitter
So it is here, I thought it was with Gary.
I thought it was with Jongkook.
Most probably Jongkook will going all
out in the hide-and-seek game today.
Just wait and see.
Pricked
If I catch you, I may
even rip open your back.
Everyone gets a ball except Jongkook
Only Jongkook didn't get a Running Ball ...
... so Jongkook will choose
his hide-n-seek team.
Jongkook hyung ...
Rushing
toward~
Jongkook hyung ~
Dong Min ah, what are you doing?
I want to present this as a gift.
Actions speak louder than words
I should give something
before speaking to you.
I'll choose both of them first.
It's time to let them go.
It’s not the right time yet.
For the girls ...
It doesn't matter if there's more
than one girl on the other team?
But it won't be interesting, right?
What is this?
Because I'm shy.
Do you really have to do this?
I'm shy, that's why I can't
give it straightforwardly.
But you didn't even write my name.
Jaesuk's unique skill showcase
in order to get the last position?
Manual Running Man vending machine?
That's disgusting.
What are you trying to do?
Opposite effect?
The displease leader
Panic
No matter what ...
... I’m going to choose a person
I want to order around.
Use me ~
You can use me as you please.
I am Yoo User.
My family were slaves for generations.
Passed down
from generations?
Self-PR Dongmin
saying as he pleased
Dongmin, come over here.
In the end Jongkook chose Dongmin
This can't be.
Do we have to be chased again?
This is absurd.
Weak Mission Team
Jihyo * Jaesuk
Kwangsoo
Sukjin * Lizzy
Very strong Chasing Team
Jongkook
Dongmin
HaHa * Gary
Suddenly felt like the word
friend didn't mean anything.
Growing friendship and dispute
You write it using close
chin and long-lasting gu.
Another brotherhood story
I remember how it used to mean that it was
meant to keep for a long time and to cherish.
Don't let me see you on the street.
I never blamed you even when
things became like this.
I'll let you go ...
... on air.
Beginning now is a story that
surpasses the movie <Friend>
Lizzy, I don’t know whether you
are aware of this, but in fact ...
... the three guys here.
Yes.
... are scarecrows.
The 3 men who haven't even completed one mission
Something came.
Find the 4 tapes within an hour and bring
it to the 7th floor master control room.
Tapes locations
1. 2nd floor museum
2. 6th floor editing room
3. 9th floor reference room
4. 16th floor variety production
We're supposed to find these?
Aren't there 1000 of these tapes?
This is really hard today.
Oh, the ones with the
Running Man sticker on it?
Let's win. Really, let's win.
Lizzy, do you like this kind of game?
Yes I like them, it’s so exciting.
Do you know about the nicknames?
Meanwhile
Chasing
Team
Strategy
discussion
Yes.
Who do you want to be?
Clint East Dong Min.
Clint East Dong Min
Ah, "East" that's what it's "Dong".
East side
(Dong Jjok)
Let's start.
Come on let's do a group cheer.
1, 2, 3, fighting.
Will they continue their victory today
just like last week...?
Remaining Time
1. Level 2: SBS History Museum
20 years of broadcasting history
The SBS History Museum
Hey, Kwangsoo ...
One of the 4 locations
where the tapes are...
Here's years of SBS broadcasted
variety shows and recorded clips
Where is it?
2. Level 6: Editing Room
Chasing Team goes to the editing rooms
on the 6th floor
Wow, it's showing what we filmed earlier.
Amazed
Dazed...
Jihyo looks pretty
through the monitor too .
This is Running Man editing room.
That's last week's episode.
Hello ~
Jongkook enters Running Man editing room
You re in the middle of editing?
Yes.
Please add in more of my parts.
Greedy for more screen time
I didn't have much
screen time last week.
1. Level 2: SBS History Museum
Jaesuk * Kwangsoo
Still absorbed in searching on the 2nd floor
Looks around
Didn't they say there's one the 6th floor?
Hyung, I found it.
It’s here?
1 out of the 4
Running Man tapes found
It's dangerous to stay Move on ...
Tape on 2nd floor found.
We found the tape on the second floor.
Smooth progress for the time being
There are too many tapes
here on the 16th floor.
4. Level 16: Variety Production Bureau
1. 2nd floor CLEAR
The are tapes everywhere on the 16th floor.
The office on the 16th floor
is full of tapes
Lost
Here~
There~
The tapes are
everywhere
Bell sound...
Chasing
Team
Who...is here....?
With a red cap
The person is
HaHa
Jihyo's search disrupted Going into hide
The attacking kid gradually coming closer
Any
mo
ment
now
Only one column between them
Jihyo will be in danger like this...
Stealthily...
Jihyo
escaping
Fast...!
Jihyo escaping at the speed of light
It's Kim Jongkook
Collapsed
Jihyo, what happened?
Her legs
automatically
gave way
I didn't do anything.
Trauma
Sparta Kooks
didn't do anything at all
You really scared me.
I was really scared.
A while ago
It's a girl, is it Jihyo?
Jihyo
was being
chased by HaHa
Hiding
at the
junction...
Just like this...
Jihyo was
captured
Jihyo, have you completed the mission?
Not yet.
I can't believe you told us.
With this information
they continue the ambush here
Come here.
Blank Jihyo...
I'm only here to find the video tape.
Oh, they're looking for video tapes.
Oh my...
Looking for video tapes?
Of course, this is SBS
the video tapes heaven.
Making a late excuse
Please spare me.
Please let me go just once.
If we let you go you have to lure
a person from your team here.
Trick a person
from our team?
... lure a person from your team here.
Betray a teammate
in exchange for her survival?
Just one person will do.
Glare
What kind of person
does this oppa see me as?
I'll call Jaesuk oppa here.
Betrayal
Okay, ask Jaesuk to come here.
You can’t mention other things.
Jihyo's betrayal for survival
Oppa where are you?
Where are you, Ji Hyo?
Tell him to come quickly to the 16th floor.
Jaesuk oppa, where are you?
I'm at the meeting room on the 13th floor.
Jaesuk oppa can you come
to the 16th floor for a while?
16th floor?
Okay, 16th floor, I got it.
Help me, oppa.
What does she means by help me?
Jihyo don't tell me you're caught?
Suspicious
.........
Jaesuk, Kwangsoo
felt that something is wrong
What should we do?
Jihyo, did you get caught?
100% suspicious
I'm not caught. Jaesuk oppa
come here for a while. S.O.S.
But why do you want
me to go there alone?
......
I have something to tell you.
Suddenly asking him
over to say something
Can’t you say it through the walkie-talkie?
Sensing something's weird
Relaxed
Anxious
You have to help.
Betrayal isn't easy
Ask Kwangsoo to come, Kwangsoo.
If not, is Kwangsoo there?
Why me?
I already found a tape, why me?
Totally mad
Quickly come over to the 16th floor.
What are you doing instead
of looking for the tape?
Jaesuk, Kwangsoo
Even more certain Jihyo has been caught
Kwangsoo, how does
the tape looks like?
Sukjin doesn’t even know
how the tape looks like.
Sukjin, how have you been looking for the tape
all this time without knowing what it looks like.
Sigh
Aish, there’s really no hope for this team.
One betrayal and...
One has no idea how to search...
We're at the corridor on
the 1st floor, come here.
We have to find the tape here,
come over to the 16th floor.
You can come down here.
Relaxed...
It's not working.
Seems like they figured it out.
Then there is no choice but
to tear off Jihyo's name tag.
Blank~
Kwangsoo says he'll come.
When?
Sorry Jihyo ...
Let’s reach a better
conclusion next time.
Jihyo
Time left
3. Level 9: Reference Room
1. 2nd floor CLEAR
How are we supposed to find it here.
The tape is too small.
All the broadcasted tapes
are kept on the 9th floor
Best thing to do is to look carefully
Running
Man
Tape!!
Whoa, I really found it.
Lizzy discovered
Running Man tape
2 out of the 4
Running Man tapes found
We found it.
Now going to look for the other two
But at this moment
They're here.
They are there ~
Let's catch them.
How in the world did you find it?
Stumble ~
Be careful.
Bell sound...
HaHa & Dongmin enters the information room
Over there.
Whoosh~
Lizzy hiding in a corner~
Jingle~
Who is here?
Chasing Team setting the trap slowly
I don't know, I just saw the clothes.
Where's Sukjin planing to hide?
You're scared right?
Oh?
Between the glass wall and blinds?
Just come out now and
we'll settle it peacefully.
Let's do this easily.
Anxious
The blind is
popping out
Behind
the blind...
Mister ...
You look busy.
I'm found?
Gives up escape because it is too cramped
I am a glass window.
It is very dangerous to
hide in this kind of place.
I can't get
caught too
Sukjin who blocked his own escape route
Sorry, I'm caught.
Sukjin
Run immediately if we're found.
On the 16th floor ...
... if HaHa is alone we can
go against him together.
That's right, of course we can do that.
Jaesuk Kwangsoo reached the Variety Production on the 16th floor
Carefully...
It’s quiet hyung.
You go out and take a look.
...Who to go...?
Kwangsoo's VJ is sent out to spy
Sshhh, don't get found.
No alternative Kwangsoo's VJ on spying duty
Seems like nobody from
Chasing Team is there
Nervous
When did you get here?
You're really fast.
Lizzy mysteriously appeared behind them
I saw them, Jaesuk is there at the end.
Slowly
Wagger
Ha
ha
After 20 years of exercise ...
What?
Nothing ~
Beep
Door opened
They're here ~
It's the Chasing Team
Run
Lizzy this way, quickly.
Hurry up, Lizzy come here.
Empty
16th floor
Too late...
Gary come over here.
Jongkook making sure they
went towards the opposite exit
The elevator which has already
made its way down numerous floors
I'll go after them and you stay here.
There's definitely a tape here
that Jihyo was searching for.
She hadn't completed the mission,
so they will come back for sure.
I don't like
to hide
You can go there.
Nagging
Hide inside there, okay?
Yes.
You got it?
Why ask me to hide? It's too boring.
Gary hiding accordingly
How will it turn out?
As both of you have a
tape, you go together.
It's alright even if I get caught
as the tapes are not with me.
You two go together.
What what if both
of us get caught?
How about hiding the tapes at a
particular place after finding it?
Oh~
Good idea...
We are now ...
Put the two tapes they've found
in the microwave on the 3rd floor
Where are they now?
Hyung, did you find the tape?
Found one on the 2nd floor
and one on the 9th floor.
Jihyo and I are caught.
Jaesuk and Kwangsoo found
the one on the 2nd floor
Lizzy found the one on the 9th floor
Hyung, what did you find?
Big Nose
said it like he was the
one who found them
Lizzy, Kwangsoo and I found the
ones on the 2nd and 9th floor.
Lizzy said she found it,
I was just beside her.
Lizzy said she found it.
Trying hard to dip your foot into
something that's almost done
Did they find the one on the 6th floor?
You have to find the one on the 6th floor.
Going to
the 6th floor editing room first
Kwangsoo*Lizzy reached the
editing room on the 6th floor
Lightly
Ah, why do I feel uneasy again.
Jaesuk goes to the 6th
floor using the stairs
Chasing
Team
HaHa heading to the 6th
floor using the stairs
Yooruce Willis
Goes to the back door instead
Must get on the elevator
that Kwangsoo and Lizzy used
Hurry up ~
There's a bell sound here too
The one by the stairs is
Sparta Kooks heading towards the 6th floor
Jaesuk
Jongkook
Kwangsoo & Lizzy
HaHa
In fact
all of them are gathering on the 6th floor
What
will happen
on the 6th floor?
I'll block them with my body.
Run to the elevator once we find it.
Heading towards the
back door to hide
Sparta Kook
Horror
What's the chance of meeting like that?
On the other side is HaHa
Chasing Team's
Special surround attack
Also going to
the 6th floor office
Yooruce Willis
Jaesuk's elevator
door opens
Witnessed the horror scene
Closing the door quickly
before Jongkook sees him
Kim Jongkook ...
Falling unconscious...!
Quickly heading for another floor...!
Extreme horror
Kim Jongkook was there.
Had Sparta Kook seen him
it could have been total annihilation...
I thought you'd come this way.
That gave me a fright.
We also caught Lizzy.
Kwang
soo
Lizzy
Remaining time
There's someone going to the 16th floor.
I think they won't go to the 16th floor
but they will walk up from the 15th.
Bingo
Got off at the 15th floor
and walk go up
Yooruce Willis
Chasing Jongkook
Escaping Jaesuk
Now is the true start of their match
I saw Kim Jongkook’s back.
They got caught here, I thought I
was going to have a heart attack.
HaHa
In that time came upstairs
from the 6th floor first...
Hey, you're by yourself.
Burst
If it's only HaHa it's possible
Press the elevator button.
Ouch, it really hurts.
If he's not next to Sparta Kook
he's just a little kid
Press the elevator button.
Wait, it hurts.
Yooruce Willis
Pushed HaHa into the elevator
Ridiculous
You be quiet and stay still.
I'm going to yell at you.
Oh, go down.
HaHa
ends up going to tell Sparta Kook
Go down quickly.
Okay, let's go.
If its only HaHa I can go pass him easily.
Before JongKook comes
Has to get the tape from level 16
Gary
That's right
Undercover for more than 10 minutes
Yooruce Willis
runs away without even
trying to find the tape
Ran around the place to the
front door that he came in
Hurry up.
Get the elevator.
Hyung, level 16.
Sparta Kooks joins Gary from the back door
Yooruce Willis
Is able to take on Gary himself
But if Sparta Kooks comes ...
What to do?
Block, come here and block them.
Make sure Jongkook
doesn't get through.
Calls for the VJ in charge
Stand here ~
Give me the camera.
Took the VJ's camera
Here, you stand here.
What are you doing?
Yooruce Willis
desperately
running away
Where is he going?.
Why are you so strong?.
Ah, seriously.
The elevator door shuts
What are you doing?
The plan succeeds
Jaesuk and VJ teamwork
Ah, seriously.
Find out where that hyung
went, walkie-talkie HaHa.
It's either level 9 or level 6.
It's level 6, I just missed him.
It's going down, level 10 and 9 now.
Time left
1. 2nd floor CLEAR
2. 6th floor Editing Room
4. 16th floor CLEAR
Editing room ~
Yooruce Willis
is in the general
editing room
Is it here somewhere?
No, no, go to 6th floor.
Jaesuk's VJ spotted
They're here to meet...
Then...
Surely on Level 6
Come to the other door on 16th floor.
Hey, come to the other door on Level 16, the other door on Level 16.
Huh...?
It's in the machine?
Presses
Expected
Running Man tape
Okay, got it.
Mission
Team
3 out of 4
Yooruce Willis
found
a tape
Now only one remains on Level 16
Just misses him by a close second
Go to the other side.
Yooruce Willis
secretly going by the stairs
Ah, I forgot they left
the tapes on level 3.
The two tapes they've found
are in the microwave on level 3
Excuse me, please give
this to my VJ brother.
Decides to take a rest on Level 9
I need to go looking around level 16.
That is??
Come to level 9 quickly.
Since long ago
Been undercover
on the 9th floor
Chasing
Team's
Dongmin
He's going by the stairs.
Can't believe he stayed
undercover for so long
He's going up from level 9.
But the door isn't opening?
Level 9.
Darting in and out
Sparta Kook is already on level 9
I'm not going to miss him this time.
Yooruce Willis' hardship
that has not ended yet
Which way did he go?
Here ~
Where?
Why are you coming from that way?
Come here.
Come help me block the door.
Again?
Yooruce Willis
Takes a VJ's camera again
Please ...
Opens...
What happened?
Absurd
He's making it difficult for
us if he's playing this way.
I knew it
would happen
Dongmin, come up.
I got the camera again.
Getting the two tapes that were on level 3
I found them.
It’s so tiring.
Utterly ...
... exhausted
I have no choice but to
film myself finding the tape.
Please understand the
situation right now.
When I find the last tape, I can end it
all by playing the tapes on 7th floor.
But I don’t know what’s going to happen.
I have 3 tapes on me.
I'll try my best to find the last one.
I think it’s somewhere here.
Every program from SBS
is controlled in this Master Control Room
Next to it is NQC Room
where local broadcast is possible
Excuse me by any chance... The tape...
You have to bring 4 tapes.
It's hard to carry these around ...
... so do you mind if I just
leave them here until then?
I know I have to bring
them all at once, but ...
Last mission
The bureau on 16th floor
Flinches
Someone...
is coming?
It's the VJ...
Ah, there he is.
Well done ~
I thought you had bells on you.
I need to go and find it.
Is no one there on level 16?
How did you go on blocking Jongkook?
Yes, I blocked him.
I missed you.
Friendship
Me too.
Where were you?
Now working as a team
beautiful(?) teamwork
I was blocking the door for you.
Yooruce Willis, will he die or live?
4. Level 6: Variety Production Bureau
Come here.
Just needs to find one more
then he can go to the control room
Going straight to where Jihyo told him
Running Man tape is in the editing machine
Also here
Yooruce Willis
gets the last tape
Ring~
He is here...
Sparta Kook...
He will win if he passes
this crucial moment
You have been seriously
escaping so well like an eel.
Did he
see me?
Hiding is all good with me, but ...
... but what are you going to do about
the reflection of your legs in the window.
He spotted him by the reflection
Did you really have to catch your hyung?
Everyone up to the 16th floor.
Must you catch your hyung?
Come up to level 16, but come
through both doors with Dongmin.
I respect you
Yooruce Willis
Split up and come.
Come both ways.
But it's now
all over
Yooruce Willis...
Today...
Jaesuk escaped many dangerous situations
Ah, the tapes are on 3rd floor.
Regardless of fear
Jaesuk got through all those moments
Jongkook hyung ...
Get the elevator.
Kim Jongkook ~
Is it going to
end like this...?
I'll admit it today.
Ah really, if only Gary or HaHa
had been here by themselves.
If one of them was here ...
... I wouldn't be going through
such humiliation like this.
Hyung we should stop.
Okay, let’s just take this outside.
Okay wait a minute.
Don’t humiliate me like this.
Okay ~
The boys are also here
You two are nothing without him.
If he wasn’t here I would ...
Lets just calm down.
Where's Dongmin?
Dongmin, he's gone solo now.
Huh?
Suddenly changing the topic?
Dongmin, one time he ...
Looks around
No it's not that ...
Dongmin was alone for 10 minutes ...
Pushes Sparta Kook and
runs away
Yooruce Willis
this is his last chance
He left this.
The front door won't open
So running back to the back door
HaHa keeping his position Going on defense
Hyung, come quick ... Arrgh.
Yooruce Willis he oppresses HaHa
in the blink of an eye
Hurry up and hold this.
Back to the VJ again
What is this situation?
Succeeds again by using the VJ to block
Chasing
Team
they will lose if
they fail to catch MC Yoo
Go down the stairs.
Where
are you going?
Jaesuk are you alive?
Jaesuk ...
Yooruce Willis...
Where are you?
I won't let you go this time
Jaesuk ...
No response from
Yooruce Willis
Oh.
Mission
Success
Really?
On all monitors in the SBS building
it reads "Mission Success"
Mission
Success
Got the last tape from level 16
Mister ...
Yooruce Willis arrives alone
in the master control room on level 7
Managers to pass it onto the engineer
along with the rest of the tapes
Hero Yoo Jaesuk
the mission
proudly succeeds
Mission success.
Overwhelmed
Thank you.
Also thanking the engineer
in the control room
Happy Chuseok, thank you.
We're proud
Yooruce Willis
Mission
Success
A glorious return
What?
Can't believe I succeeded.
Brother.
Also giving a big hug to the VJ
who contributed big time
Here's a Running Ball for each of us.
Mission
Team
Succeeds
A Running Ball for each
And...
Envious losers...
Current time
Thanks to Yoo Jaesuk we’ve
each got a Running Ball.
Yes, but this ...
Morning wide is going live soon.
Give us the punishment outfit now then.
First time in Running Man
Jongkook has no Running Balls
Put them in here.
Jaesuk Sukjin Kwangsoo
Jihyo Lizzy
balls
HaHa Gary Dongmin
ball
It feels weird.
I have a feeling Jaesuk
is going to go live on air.
I don’t feel confident.
How many chances do we have?
I will start it now.
I'll start it now.
Lets go one by one.
The first draw begins
There's no one with 3 Running
Balls, so we still have hope.
Please ~
1, 2, 3.
It's here.
Who will it be?
Kwangsoo excluded from punishment
Yes!
Yah, Kwangsoo ...
Kwangsoo finally gets excluded
from the punishment in 4 weeks
Yes.
How long has it been?
1, 2, 3.
Who'll be the 2nd person to escape?
Who is it?
Please...
Let it be me...
Gary?
Gary
escapes
He only had one Running Ball
but he luckily escapes
Didn't he only have one ball.
He only had one.
He only had one ball,
but he still escapes.
Jealous
Come on.
Who will be the third lucky person?
Doesn't get punished 4 weeks in a row
Jihyo
It's Jihyo again.
We only have 2 people left now.
Please, Ji Sukjin.
100% pressure Who will be the one to dodge
out of the live on-air punishment?
Congratulations
Yoo Jaesuk
Yoo Jaesuk ~
Jaesuk have carried out 7 of them
Of 10 Running Man punishments
He goes from unlucky guy
to a lucky man this Chuseok
Thank you ~
It's good to go on a morning
show on Chuseok, right?
The one who will be
doing the punishment
From the five people who can
escape who will be the last one?
Except Jongkook Who'll be the lucky person
to escape the punishment?
It's the last one, the
lucky person is ...
Who remain?
1, 2, 3.
Who will remain and carry out
the live on-air punishment?
Who will it be?
Ji Sukjin wins
Sukjin miraculously exempted from he punishment
Look ... Ji Sukjin.
Victory Ceremony
I get to be on TV, that’s good.
We'll be watching Morning Wide.
We shouldn't complain.
Right, be happy.
Yeah, it's Chuseok.
Yeah, since its a national holiday.
15 minutes before live
Part 3 of Morning wide that informs
the hot issue and featured information
No brush teeth No shower
Got changed into Chuseok Hanbok
Trying best not to show
they’ve stayed up all night
Hello ~
Politely greeting the Morning Wide staff
I’m nervous since we're going live.
When you speak, make
sure to look into Camera 1.
Yes ~
Hurriedly memorizing the script
Lizzy who dreamt of becoming an announcer
practices clear pronunciation of sentences
Scary thinking about the live broadcast
Do well.
Make sure you do well, okay?
Ripping out a part to copy
No brushing teeth No shower
Quickly checking their appearances
Going live is the only thing left to do
Already?
Are they coming on now, Jihyo?
The ones who managed to escape
waits for the broadcast in the lobby
Now ...
Morning
Wide
The actual broadcast of Morning Wide
It's here, it's on.
All nervous because
it's a live broadcast
Can they do well?
Finally standby
Nervous
Sighs~
Are they coming on now?
I think it’s about time.
Magazine
The corner Running Man members were on
Next to me, it's rich and plentiful like Chuseok.
We have 4 members from Running Man.
Hello ~
Over-reacting
Hello
Loud
Cheers
Since it's live, please keep
your voices down a bit.
Yes, understood.
Please introduce yourselves.
Funny
Ah, yes ~
You slept right?
Yes, I've slept.
We filmed and...
Look at Jongkook hyung talk.
He’s a chatterbox now.
We ran whole night and sweated a lot, so please
be understanding if we don't look as great.
Should we start with HaHa then?
Yes ~
It's a story from aunt Cha Sasoon.
Let's have a look at the VCR and
please introduce the story to us.
Yes ~
The VCR
plays first
Do I read
it now?
Staff comes in
urgently to help
This is what was broadcasted
last year in Morning Wide.
The person narrating now is HaHa?
She passes the driving test.
HaHa is
doing well
But the staff is coaching him
throughout step by step
We admire your passion.
She is really amazing.
Morning Wide is really funny.
HaHa will now show a Dooly dance.
* Dooly dance = Korean anime feat. a green dinosaur
Me and Kim Jongkook will do it.
Can't say no since it's a live broadcast
Big laugh from the start
of the morning on Chuseok
I can't watch this.
Showing off individual talents
Dongmin's Taekwon V impersonation
From the early morning of Chuseok.
How was it today?
We're very happy that we
were part of this show.
Thank you for the special memories today.
Thank you ~
Finishes with a belly button bow
Happy Chuseok.
We'll be back
with more exciting punishment next week