Original hardsub by iSUB
Softsub by SamFive
(color and alignment etc)
Today's landmark
Hanyang Women's University
A place for people with
both wisdom and growth
Hanyang
University’s
female
Gary?
And then junior is exposing
Kwangsoo's secrets?
First time in Running Man
Two-way hide-and-seek
Get the female student's help
complete the mission
Yooruce Willis
Sparta Kook
And Kwangsoo's
truths or lies!
It all
begins now
A sunny autumn day
Hanyang University garden
It's been a long time since
we sat in a classroom.
Yeah, really ...
How long?
Already almost 25 years.
30 years already?
Like hell.
25 years...
30 years...
Anyway, to Big Nose it's a distant past
Hyung, it's Joowon.
It's Joowon.
Today's guest
Neighborhood brother
Ko Joowon
Joowon was supposed to appear
at the opening of the show.
Precisely ~
But something else cropped
up at the last minute.
Details will be revealed later
Actually we wanted to let
him debut in our ﻿show ...
... but doesn't like the attention.
Is that so?
That is why it is hard
for me to say these ...
Didn't you see the look in his eyes?
What?
"Hyung, what do you know about me?"
I know him very well.
Doesn't look like we’re close.
Definitely not easy Ko Joowon
his new image today
Jihyo, because we're afraid
you would misunderstand.
HaHa asked me to clear
the misunderstandings.
Yes.
Internet search popularity increase.
Internet search: HaHa ♥ Jihyo
Did Jaesuk reveal HaHa's heart?
Why?
I ﻿said this to you the previous time ...
... Jihyo really doesn't like you, right?
Blank~ Jihyo No reaction
That's right.
I don't like you one bit too, understand?
Getting
excited alone
Then shut your mouth.
Why'd you want me to shut up?
The more HaHa denies
the more suspicious he gets
I wanted Jaesuk to not misunderstand.
I ﻿went to HaHa's house the other day.
Framer mobilize?
Uneasy
He had collected Jihyo's
hair from her collar.
Special ops framer
Is HaHa a crazy fan of Jihyo?
That was the best.
That's Lizzy's ... Lizzy's.
Nonsensical
How is it Lizzy's.
One day his feeling will be exposed
We are 1 hour from the start of filming.
The reason why we got you
all to assemble here is ...
... in a while, we will
have a 1:9 showdown.
Again?
With who?
With Jung Yonghwa.
Yonghwa ~
Everyone has to deceive Jung
Yonghwa to get Running Balls.
Today's
Deceive Jung Yonghwa
Complete 10 questions of
conversation dictation.
All together 10 questions and
make Yonghwa the last place.
Dictation doesn't sound easy.
Confused~
Harder than imagined
Dictation
That's right, it's not easy.
The good thing for you is that ...
... Yonghwa has been studying in
the States since he was young
... so he isn't familiar with Korean writing.
Being more familiar with the recent online
chat lingo may get him even more confused.
I will reveal some of the questions.
Yes.
To ascertain the member's level beforehand
Pre-test on the spot
"To be beaten", write "beaten".
* Beaten = 뭇매 (MutMae)
Ah, beaten.
First time hearing this word.
Whining
This is difficult.
Really.
Please don't cheat.
Their average age is 30 years
On-the-spot dictation in their memories
I haven't had dictation
in quite a long ﻿while.
Feels like we're back in the past.
Gary covers
his writing
as in school
What's there to cover with your hand?
Hyung, you keep looking.
A sure find in school
Almost everybody quarrels after cheating
Why would I need to peek?
What a quick eyes.
All finished?
Yes ~
1, 2, 3.
Correct:
MutMae
Everyone's answer revealed
It ends with "siot"?
* Korean letters have unique names and ㅅ is called 'siot'
Is it 'siot'?
Mud Mae
(instead of Mut Mae)
Ermm...
Is it not "jieut"?
Ah!!
HaHa wrote MunMae
MuttMae, MujMae
All kinds of answers appeared
Is it 'jieut'?
It isn't 'jieut'?
Even the model student is confused
It's not 'jieut'.
It's 'siot', 'siot' is correct.
We were thinking too hard.
Thinking too hard?
It's difficult.
If everybody's standard is like
this, it will be hard to succeed.
Pre-test outcome
Lacking beyond expectations
Very hard.
We'll give you the answers.
You can only succeed if
you memorize the answers.
Spelling is difficult.
On the handouts are 30 questions.
How much time left?
We'll give you 5 minutes.
Only 5 minutes?
There's not much time left.
Anyway Just make Yonghwa come last
Let's first ...
Let's first make a small copy.
Battle plan ...
If Yonghwa tries to cheat ...
HaHa ... study.
Stop!
Jihyo, do you really not
feel anything for HaHa?
Assuring the fact
Yes.
I don't like her either, she
means nothing to me.
What are you saying?
Oppa, you're really too noisy.
I wanted to leave you alone, but do
you really want me to harass you?
Ha
gone
crazy
I won't let you sleep well at night.
I send text ﻿messages to
delete, send and delete.
Pick up the phone and put it down again.
You'll even have me in your dreams.
You'll be finished in 10 minutes.
Look here ~
New love triangle
Is HaHa's feelings confirmed?!
Now your heart is moved, right?
What heart is moved?
I'm not moved even a bit.
Yah, because of you Jihyo has to
reply and delete text messages.
One Boyfriend's mixed feelings
Jihyo noona really wrote, deleted and
re-wrote text messages many times.
She wrote them again in an attempt
to make the scolding sound harsher.
Stuck on framing
Not missing an opportunity
Framer Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo, you can only think of these?
Thinking of framing 24/7
Ah, Kwangsoo's really scary.
Because he betrayed everyone
The test suddenly draws near
Which school did you graduate from?
Dokpo High School.
I heard many rumors about you.
Heard rumors!!!
A lot of rumors?
The Kwangsoo we know is fake?
Truth
Or a conspiracy?
What are you doing?'
Ya, you.
Soon
Framer Kwangsoo's real character is exposed
What?
Time's almost up.
Always leaving things until the last moment
Hyung, when you read 'Long Days' ... Ah.
Wanted to ask Jongkook But quickly turned to Joowon
Hyung, when you read 'Long Days' ...
Why did you ask him and
then changed to another?
Come on, ask me.
Got caught by scary hyungs
When is Yonghwa coming?
He already arrived.
He's still in the car.
Hurry up.
There's 2 minutes left.
At the
same time
Hello ~
What was given to Yonghwa
Then ... is it a spelling test?
He got the answers to the test?
I'll do my best.
Jung Yonghwa's role is cheating.
Yonghwa's
Reverse 1:9 hidden camera?
... cheating.
I will definitely deceive all
the members and win this.
Fighting.
A few days earlier
Broadcast Center
Public Hall
This is my third time
appearing on Running Man.
Yonghwa
Talking with Running Man PD
Really, I would rather die
than wear those hot pants.
Idol
If I have a Running Ball ...
... I'll have the chance to escape.
No matter what, I want to
get hold of a Running Ball.
That time we deceived Gary hyung ...
At the same time ...
... while they try to deceive
me, I will ﻿act like I'm fooled.
And I won't be discovered.
The loser  gets the Running Ball ...
Act deceived to
deceive the others
... and the others won't get any ball.
I don't know if this format is going to work.
Yonghwa vs Running Man
Really bold plan
We will consider your suggestion.
Ah, yeah ...
However, if the members find
out that you are cheating ...
... then you will lose.
Yes.
It'll only be you who won't get a Running Ball.
Yes, I understand.
If you can make them help you to
get 3 correct answers, you win.
Yonghwa has to get
3 correct answers from the members
All together I have to get 3 correct ...
... answers from the members to win.
Yes, ﻿I'm confident.
In Running Man, the most important
thing is the Running Balls.
Can you teach me some
methods to get the Running Ball?
Fighting ~
Deceive Yonghwa
Running Man
I'm so going to have bad luck.
Jung Yonghwa
Cheat Running Man
The inescapable battle is about to begin
The filming will begin now.
Is everyone ready?
1, 2, 3.
Ooh.
Oh, what to do?
So cute~
Today we're at Hanyang
Women's University.
Today's landmark
Hanyang Women's University
In fact, we are here for the first time.
That's right.
Every man's desire
Women's University
A blooming garden of female students
Nurturing next generation of talented women
U-20 Women's World Cup Star
Ji Soyun's Alma mater Hanyang Women's University
Isn't there an objective for
coming to a women's university?
Ah, that's right.
Very excited
Just hearing of it makes men excited
Women's University
You permed your hair.
Did you perm your hair
because we're coming here?
Miss Jongkook who had a perm
Did you use the big thing on
the head when you had a perm?
Yes, I used it.
Recently more pretty
Miss Jongkook
Today Joongki is here too.
From now on Joongki is able to
come every week, that's great.
Drama ended...
Will be able to see Joongki every week
The smooch Devil.
Your fans said they were sad.
Hurt many female fans with the stolen kiss
Yes ~
My fans said the same thing.
What did they say?
Why did I let Joongki steal it?
Same issue Different reaction from fans
Wait a minute.
Today's guest come on stage
It's Ko Joowon.
They're coming together.
Korea's attention
attracting actor
Ko Joowon
Always looking
handsome
Jung Yonghwa
Yonghwa came the previous time
when we played hide-and-seek.
We're looking forward to
today's performance too.
We have an agreement today too.
Trying to pull him to your team already?
Of course.
Ah, Joowon ...
Awkward
... this is our first time meeting, right?
Stammer
Ah, very handsome.
Everybody got stunned during the show.
No, it's not like that.
Learning very well, very competitive ...
... and really ﻿good during
the hide-and-seek game.
Then what about today?
Are we playing hide-and-seek?
What are you saying?
Jaesuk gets nervous when playing 1 vs 9
What is this man?
What kind of person is this?
No matter what...
Members are able to cover up
Are we having lessons now?
Not now, later.
Ah, that's later.
Won't we be disturbing the students
while having lessons in the daytime?
The reality everyone knows Such a funny scene
You really like learning?
I like it so much.
Pretending not to know
is tiring
Let's head in.
Start with the hide-and-seek game.
What are you doing?
Nation's MC is still nervous
So let's head in, let's go.
Loner Yonghwa knows everything
Let's do that.
The 9 people trying to trick Yonghwa
If they want to win
have to try to guess each other's thoughts
Start of the two-way 1 vs 9
The reversal again and again
Yonghwa vs Running Man battle
Begins now !
We are back again at a campus
classroom after a long absence.
Long awaited campus classroom
Feeling impatient now.
There were no instructions, but
everyone wrote on the blackboard.
Messy scribbles
"Noisy people are Ji Sukjin and Go Joowon."
"People who fight, Song
Jihyo and Kim Jongkook."
"Kim Jongkook is crazy."
"﻿Person who consumes alcohol
during lunch time, Song Jihyo."
"﻿Person who plays with toys, Kim Jongkook."
He he
Not a bad
sabotage
Since we are at a university ...
Yes?
... we'll have a spelling test on paper.
A spelling test.
All 10 of them knows about it
Spelling test
There's a total of 10 questions.
Except for the last person ...
Fake
rule
After the 10 questions, except the person
at the last place, others get Running Balls
... the rest of the people will get Running Balls.
But the 1:9 battle has
already began
Their mission is to
make Yonghwa be the last
Yonghwa's mission is to get
3 members to give him correct answers
Come...
Test me...
Today, I won’t be the one giving the questions.
It will be given by another person.
Who is it?
Hello.
I am the broadcaster for
Hanyang ﻿Girls College ...
... global tourism major, Park Soohee.
Cheers
That's good ~
Luckily.
Me too ...
I used to be the broadcaster in
my college broadcasting station.
Ah, really?
Joongki used to be one too.
My sister-in-law is a broadcaster.
* With sister-in-law he means Jaesuk's wife
Na Gyoungeun who's an announcer for MBC
That's right, that's how they fell in love.
This situation
Looks similar to the situation where MC Yoo fell in love
How are they going to see each
other if they don't even meet?
Annoying
Now, I'll give the questions.
The tangled up  relationship
between Jihyo and Gary.
Question
Tangled up relationship
between Gary and Jihyo
Oh, this is really difficult.
Yes.
Tangled up ~
I will repeat the question again.
<Tangled up> isn't easy to spell
Tangled up relationship
between Gary and Jihyo.
First ﻿I'll make some mistakes,
to get some sympathy.
Not sure whether it will work.
Because it's a test, it should be difficult.
How to
make mistakes naturally?
It's difficult.
Is Gary hyung's name
spelled Gary or Gaery?
Wasn't this written on the blackboard?
This is of course very easy.
Joongki peeks at
Yonghwa's answer
Shakes head
Squint~
Okay, let's check the answers.
Tangled up relationship of Gary and Jihyo.
Yonghwa
Gary
2 people got it wrong
Yonghwa's strategy
Answer 1st question wrong
Gary sacrificed himself so suspicions won't arise
Should have let me know about it.
Calm Gary
the wind suddenly made him like this
Difficult.
Gary also got it wrong.
Maybe because he's younger, that's why.
Console
But this is very difficult.
Everyone gives encouragement
to Yonghwa who studied in USA
It's very difficult.
Isn't it very difficult?
The strategy of gaining sympathy
seems to have succeeded as expected
Do you want us to change seats?
Yes.
Those who got it wrong,
have to move to the back.
Too obvious.
Too many people
got it correct
Yes, no need
for everybody
to get it right
Continue with the plan
It's very difficult.
Gary is dressed very smartly.
Question
Gary is dressed very smartly
Why is it me again?
Gary is dressed very smartly.
Oh, so difficult.
How am I going to
write this wrong?
Let's check the answers.
Gary is dressed very smartly.
Jaesuk Jihyo Jongkook Yonghwa
4 people got it wrong
4 of them wrote 'smartly' as 'mature'
Yonghwa followed his plan
Wrong
Jongkook sacrificed himself
to get rid of Yonghwa's suspicion(?)
Permed hair blown back
making his hairstyle look elegant
That was scary, really scary.
Looks like the woman
in the Greek mythology.
... Medusa.
Greek mythology
Medusa hairstyle?
Ah, it's actually a double syllable.
Pretends not to know
Ah, seriously.
Yonghwa answered zero questions right
Sits at the last place 10th seat
I'm behind, right?
This..
isn't difficult
Will he get a Running Ball?
He managed to get it wrong so far
Can he trick them?
Hyung, why did you
get it correct so well?
Cringing
Yonghwa catches people by surprise.
Yonghwa did the same mistake as I did.
It's okay, we're on the same boat.
You don't even know that?
I don't know.
That "smartly" spelling, you really didn't know?
That was already very difficult.
You don't know that word "smartly"?
I've never seen that word before.
Acting
Ah depressing, told you.
HaHa is bragging although he
already knew the answers
I completely don't know.
Okay, continue.
Sukjin easily gets angry in his later years.
Question
Sukjin easily gets angry in his later years
Chuckle~
Sukjin easily gets angry in his later years.
Later years?
Get old?
Similar spelling in Korean
Ah, I really don't know.
Diversion
Very difficult.
Time ~
Irritable
Don't look.
Spelled
'angry' wrong
Why is it wrong?
You wrote 'throw a tantrum'.
Spelled
'later years' wrong
Should I go to the beach?
Hyung, your tone can't be like that please.
Gary ...
Crying
What are the 2 of them
doing during lessons?
Blank~Jihyo wrote what Gary told her But it was wrong
Sorry.
Oh?
Gary got it correct?
Traitor
What's wrong?
No, I wrote it anyhow.
Why?
Wrong answer?
It's correct, what's wrong?
That's right.
This must be correct.
It's correct.
PD made a mistake
It's correct
Permed blown for no reason
But
At this moment
Already
Yonghwa has started
his 1st challenge
Let me
take a look
What?
At a loss
Show me the answer
Look, hurry look.
What to do?
For the Running Balls
I can't let you look
In this case
Idol Yonghwa won't be able to make it
Jaesuk is unable to sit still
Running Balls are very important in the show.
"﻿Hyung, can you help me get a Running Ball?"
Indeed
Jaesuk's decision is?
Sincere
Soft
Look at this
Soft-hearted MC Yoo
gave him the answer...!
Even to that extent
Guiding him graciously
Yes it's this, this is correct.
Awkward acting
Don't know if he helps Yonghwa
or tricks him until its verified
If Yonghwa gets it correct
he'll succeed 1 out of 3
Jaesuk hyung
thank you
Yonghwa, you wrote it
wrong so many times.
Thanks to Jaesuk Yonghwa got it right
So currently, Jihyo is in the last place?
Jihyo, right.
I ... managed to
succeed once?
Jihyo, I'm sorry.
Change seats according to the rules
Forget about it.
Jihyo, I'm sorry.
Must be really disappointed with Gary.
Gary made a joke that he
shouldn't have done
Time to temporary change the tape
Very difficult.
It's too difficult, Mr PD.
What
is she going to do?
Too difficult.
I'm an idol, what to
do about my image?
I became the idiot.
It's too difficult, too difficult
PD, can you edit out this part?
It is already planned that
this will be broadcasted.
Yonghwa uses the plan of being worried
of his image to soften the members' hearts
People who believe that
Yonghwa is really worried
We are starting.
Yes.
This is going to be a problem
Going to be the last again.
Let Yonghwa get it right for once.
The question begins.
Jongkook's exoskeleton.
* Exoskeleton = Outer skeleton (like lobster has)
Question
Jongkook's exoskeleton
This is difficult.
This sentence is really used correctly.
What's exoskeleton?
A brain.
Gary says that it's a brain, he he.
Quoted from Gary
Exoskeleton
Brain
Looks around
Talking about the world's
best, it's that meaning.
Jihyo laughs when she sees Yonghwa's answer
Target verified
Blank~Jihyo immediately avoided his line of sight
Teach me once
I really ...
HaHa, stop writing.
Yonghwa continues to beg
for the correct answer from Jihyo
What?
As expected Jihyo...?
Showed it to him
As expected from Jihyo
Did she give him the right answer?
I really hope there's this word.
Check the answers
Okay, let's check the answers.
Sukjin Kwangsoo Jaesuk
3 men
Wrong
That scared me.
Thanks to Jihyo
Gets it right a 2nd time
Oh...?
Got it right?
Woah ~
A big problem.
Yonghwa has gotten 2 questions right
Jaesuk*Sukjin*Kwangsoo Same marks
Although I don't know about the others,
but Jihyo noona ﻿has a soft heart.
Yonghwa's 2nd strategy
Attack
soft-hearted Blank~Jihyo
I think she'll teach me, so I'll
have to pander to her later.
Blank~
Let's change our seats now.
Jaesuk*Sukjin*Kwangsoo*Yonghwa
answered 2 questions correct
Now 4 people
in the last row
Oh, I was at the back only for awhile.
Only awhile.
Jihyo, you're here?
Ah, it's the second time.
Hmph~
Pretending not to hear?
What did you say?
Gary, you're not supposed to sit here.
Can't I sit here?
No.
Sudden~
Yah, those two are a little ...
Very sweet today too
The school's Monday Couple
Gary
Jihyo
Sorry.
Gary hyung is in 5th place?
Now I'm in 5th.
Surprisingly Gary is in 5th place
Yonghwa, stay strong.
HaHa is in
3rd place
HaHa is another unexpected result.
Even so, how
can you hyungs ...
Jongkook finds Jaesuk like a Homing Pigeon.
Question
Jongkook finds Jaesuk
like a Homing Pigeon
This time
it's a confusion of similar syllables
I found it.
This word is really not easy.
Okay, let's check the answers.
Checking the answers
Yonghwa's answer is...?
Wrote 'homing pigeon' wrong
Jongkook*Kwangsoo*Yonghwa
men
Wrong
Why?
I got it wrong?
Oh?
That means?
Why?
Jongkook got it wrong?
Let's see it again.
Ah, it's correct.
Why are you like this?
Rage
How many times have you
done this to Jongkook?
I even permed my hair
before I came down today.
Director, you just casually neglected him.
Kwangsoo and Yonghwa answered 2 correctly.
Sukjin and Jihyo answered 3 correct
and Gary and Jongkook answered 4.
HaHa he's... really... in 3rd place?
Got 5 correct 3rd place
I didn't think it would be like that, sorry.
HaHa The highest score in his life
Whatever he kept in his heart
is now said out loud.
On the other hand, Yonghwa
and Kwangsoo, stay strong.
Only got 2 correct
Yonghwa, Kwangsoo in last place
Help cheer each other on.
It's okay, come on.
No matter what,
I have only one
more chance
Okay...
Starting the question.
Joowon snatched up
Yonghwa's biscuit in a jiffy﻿.
To escape being last
completely focused
Kwangsoo
not easy
Ah, it's hard.
Joowon snatched up
Yonghwa's biscuit in a jiffy﻿.
Question
Joowon snatched
Yonghwa's biscuit in a jiffy
Who snatched?
Yah, what is this?
HaHa, what is this?
This time it's the handsome kid
HaHa hyung
Please help
me once
I don't know.
It must be correct.
Which word?
"Snatched up"
Faster.
Ah!
HaHa is teaching
Only two remaining
questions
Running Man must push
Yonghwa to the back
Jihyo only knows how to write by
herself at the corner from the start.
Will HaHa teach Yonghwa
the correct spelling?
You still said you didn't know.
Yes, because of the dongsaeng.
Acting like he's following HaHa's instruction
Yonghwa wrote the answer
If the answer HaHa taught is correct
Yonghwa's mission is a success
Okay, Joongki ...
Checking the answers
Yongha, that isn't Yonghwa's name.
Snitchy
Quickly spray him.
What did he write?
Yongha (wrong)
Yonghwa (right)
You don't even know his name?
What?
Joongki is stuck in his drama character 'Yongha'
You wrote it as Yongha.
Saddened
You can pretend you didn't
know and let it pass, right?
Can't turn a blind eye on a apparent mistake
Firm on his principle Joowon
No, that would be giving in too much.
"You don't even know his name?"
It's correct, right?
His answer is
Correct
How sad.
This word is so easy.
It is correct.
Yah, Gary ...
It isn't wrong.
Raise it properly.
Also Gary
wrote Yonghwa as Yongha
Quick raise it properly.
Why did you have to expose it?
Is it written as Yongha?
It's Yonghwa ... Yonghwa.
I'm sorry Yonghwa.
If I get this wrong, will I be the last?
He's lost his confidence.
One last question
Must prevent Kwangsoo from getting last
Kwangsoo ~
He got it right.
Kwangsoo gets 3 questions right
He looks like his confidence is diminishing.
Yonghwa's answer is?
HaHa told the answer
Will Yonghwa's answer be right?
Because of the wrong answer
He becomes the lone last man?
HaHa, how come you
could answer so well?
Thanks to HaHa
Yonghwa got 3 questions right
Success
Why are yours so bad?
These are still the basics.
That's too much
HaHa ... that's enough.
Why?
What?
Immediate stop
Joowon is first?
Joowon only answered 1 question wrong
So it's like that?
Currently Ko Joowon is first.
Running ball ...
... goes to Jung Yonghwa.
What?
Yonghwa gets the Running Ball?
Flabbergasted
What is this?
Really?
Shocked
Why did he get it?
What's happening?
Why did Yonghwa get it?
Everyone's spelling mission
was suggested by Yonghwa.
Yonghwa's challenge was ...
... to make you teach Yonghwa 3
answers and getting them right.
I taught him.
And then it was Jihyo and
lastly HaHa who taught him.
In total 3 times.
Why did you have to teach him?
He acted so realistic
Oh, we got scammed.
This is too much.
I also didn't think it'll be that easy
for people to start teaching me.
Didn't you say you were
in America previously?
I stayed in America for around a month.
Yonghwa came away clean
Absolutely hoodwinked by him
Jihyo noona also secretly taught me.
When did I help you?
Jihyo, you ...
When did I teach you?
Gangster Jihyo
Sudden
change
Yonghwa, who did you think
was the funniest amongst us?
In order to fool Yonghwa
the Running Man members acted a lot
Everyone was funny.
On the side saying this and that.
"How do I spell this?", saying stuff like that.
Oh, how shameful.
What to do?
Everything I did in front of him
is appearing in my mind now.
How shameful.
I asked Yonghwa where
he stayed in America ...
... he said See-Attle.
It's Seattle.
Speak English.
What did you say damned kid?
Burst
of anger
What did you say damned kid?
Still saying we didn't do well today.
Who says we didn't do well?
Ah...
Because we didn't complete
the Seattle Night well?
But
The night Yonghwa didn't
complete well starts from now
To commemorate winning a Running Ball
Yonghwa's impromptu performance
Huh??
Pirated lead vocals(?)
Over here is the drummer extraordinaire...?
Temporarily
CN Blues(?)
Ah, it suits us well.
Gradually lost to the music
Yah, look at Kim Jongkook.
Yonghwa's solo A handsome ending
Multi-talented
Yonghwa follows up with the drums
Twist
Hip hop
Open the door gently
This is
Hip Hop
Gary follows the beat
As expected
Dance competition prize winner Kang Gary
♥ At Jihyo
shooting aegyo ♥
A bit burdensome But decisive
Jihyo, you should accept it.
Our Monday-in-laws
match very well ♥
In the year 2007, the group
who won a big ﻿prize for ...
... the university song festival ﻿is from
this Hanyang Women's University.
They have a band and traditional instruments.
A place where many famous people are from.
We are now in the band practice room
We have a reason for coming here, right?
This time's mission is to perform band songs.
2nd mission
Guess the song that the band plays
Performing band songs.
Yes, everybody will be forming their own bands.
Get into new groups, perform a song as
a band and led someone guess the title.
Everyone will perform themselves.
You should perform the song.
If it is performing, only
Yonghwa knows how to.
The rest of us don't know.
Yes, that's why there will
be a volunteer group.
Adding volunteers to make it easier
They're here to help us?
A volunteer corp?
They're coming out from there.
They're
Hanyang Women's
University students
First of all, they're here
to help because of us.
Let's applaud the 11 students
of Hanyang woman university.
Welcome
But ...
... how are these eleven
students going to help us?
Among them are only three students from
the music faculty who can play instruments.
It's very hard.
You will form three groups and ...
... each group can choose 1 person.
Real? Fake?
Find the real music faculty student
To decide who are the 3 students ...
The 3 music faculty students
are among these 11 people
... we will first discuss with our team.
To help us, we'll ask each of them a question.
Each team will choose one
student to perform with them
So starting from Miss Jooyeon ...
... please introduce yourself in order.
Hello, I am Chae Jooyeon from ...
Number
Chae Jooyeon Piano major
... the faculty of music, majoring in piano.
Hello I'm Ahn Eunryong, a student of ...
All of them are pretending to
be students of the music faculty
... the music faculty, majoring in vocals.
Number
Ahn Eunryong Vocal major
She looks like she can sing well.
Hello, I'm Lee Jisoon, a student of the ...
Number
Lee Jisoon Violin major
... music faculty, majoring in violin.
Hello, I am a student of Hanyang
Women's University's music faculty.
Yes ... I ... eh ...
Stutter
Miss Eunji ...
Yes.
She's so nervous.
I'm goodwill ambassador of the university ...
Number
Choi Eunji Composition major and
goodwill ambassador of the university
... majoring in composition, I am Choi Eunji.
Hello, I'm Min Jieun student of ...
... music faculty, musical major.
Number
Min Jieun Musical major
Hello, I'm Ahn Eunji, student ...
... of music faculty, flute major.
Number
Min Ahn Eunji Flute major
No, when I looked at the broadcast ...
Can I talk a little bit?
He really talk a lot, right?
Yes.
Eunhye ...
Hello, I'm Park Eunhye, student of ...
Number
Park Eunhye Piano major
... Hanyang women's ﻿University music faculty.
I'm majoring in piano.
It's looks like Running Man
and I are fated to meet.
Why?
My nickname is the female version of Gary.
Nickname
Female
Gary
Shall I show you Gary's usual expression?
Gary's peaceful expression?
Gary's peaceful expression.
A photo copy
Hello, I'm Lee Seungjin, student of Hanyang ...
... University music faculty, piano major.
Number
Lee Seungjin Piano major
I've played piano since I was 3 years old.
Among all these people,
I must be the best pianist.
I'm majoring in vocal, Bang Jin.
Number
Bang Jin Vocal major
Nod
Hanyang Women's University can do sports well.
Sorry
She said she can sing well.
Maybe she's pretending.
Sorry miss Bangjin.
Hello, I'm from Hanyang's
faculty of social sports ...
... social sports.
Social sports...?
Isn't she from the music faculty?
Did you say it wrong on purpose?
Bass major Kim Songbok.
Number
Kim Songbok Bass major
Did you intentionally ... ?
Ah, she might have said it wrong on purpose?
Hello, I am Lee Eunyoung Hanyang
University music faculty student ...
Number
Lee Eunyoung Composition major
... ﻿majoring in composition.
Now it's time to
ask questions
Because we don't have much time.
Everybody quickly asks questions.
If you don't have question, we
will continue to the next team.
Worry
Miss Eunhye, you said that you ...
Her fate is with Running Man
Number 7 Park Eunhye
... has fate with Running Man, right?
Yes, when 1st episode of Running Man was shot ...
... ﻿I'm one of the citizen who walked on the road.
I appeared for a moment.
Really?
Last July First broadcast
Team members who won went outside
At this time
Eunhye was captured by the camera
I gave thumbs up and shouted
Mr. Yoo Jaesuk's name loudly.
Very happy
Yes?
I don't know if he pretended not to hear,
because I called his name really loudly.
He pretended not to hear you.
It's not a joke.
Now it's the framer  trend
I didn't hear you, really didn't hear.
You really gave me thumbs up?
Yes, I gave you thumbs up.
Recently when I went to the toilet,
I saw Jongkook hyung was crying.
Why?
I asked why.
He said Jaesuk hyung
slapped his the cheek.
... slapped his the cheek.
You're really, really ...
Slapped his cheek?
Yes.
Proud
There's something I wanna say.
Ehm?
Do n:o 11 Eunyoung want to say something?
Yes ~
Kwangsoo oppa ...
... what's your high school name?
I was student of *** high school.
I'm from *** high school too.
I heard lots of rumors.
High school
confession
Heard many things
about senior Kwangsoo
I heard lots of rumors.
What is it?
Say it quickly ~
About senior Kwangsoo
Heard lot of rumors
She knows Kwangsoo's past
You're finished.
Framer Kwangsoo's  face is turning red
What is it?
No energy
Jihyo, look at Jihyo.
Excited
In Running Man
Things that comes to Kwangsoo's mind
It's said Jihyo's always angry at people.
Things which
can frame Jihyo
It's said that her nickname is Song JiYok.
In Apgujeong I saw Jongkook doing nail-art.
Finally we can hear
rumors about Kwangsoo
What's the rumor?
You're a transfer student before, right?
Yes.
I heard in his previous school ...
... he always beat his friends.
Problem
Always beat his friends?
When he went outside the door ...
... he'll spit on the floor.
Problem
Kwangsoo spits on the floor
That's enough ~
Song JiYok(?) is very happy
There are a lot of women
who likes tall men and ...
... he never refused a woman's confession.
Problem
Never refused a
woman's confession
A Casanova who never refused a female student?
Now we know Kwangsoo.
Kwangsoo really, how did
you become like this?
How can
this be?
Faced with his own medicine
he can't say anything
Hoot~
Did I do well?
How could you be like that?
Tsk!!
Look ...
Turned
His true
colors?
If it's true what the junior said
so this is the real Kwangsoo
You ~
This kid is really.
Oh, what?
Startled
Wh...What did you say?
However, all the problem
about Kwangsoo's past ...
If any of you can tell us,
all of you can help, please.
What kind of person is the real Kwangsoo?
We want to know
about Kwangsoo
Phone
number
Receive information about this person
This is the Kwangsoo that we know.
So tense.
The truth about framer Kwangsoo
Really?
Yes.
Give us a lot of information about Kwangsoo.
What are you doing?
30 seconds.
It's time for the questions to find
the real student of music
If you don't ask question in 30 ﻿sec,
we will continue with the next team.
Start.
Can we keep asking for 30 seconds?
No, just one question.
Only one?
Yes.
10 seconds has passed.
Miss Che Jooyeon ...
Team
Jongkook
question
Che Jooyeon
When I looked her for the first time ...
Her appearance is that of a teacher.
Honestly, it looks like she's
been In lot of performance.
Nods without
saying anything
Looks like a pianist.
When you applied to the
university, isn't there a test?
What song did you play.
At that time I played "Meditation".
She clearly remembers the test
I played "Beyer's ..."
* Beyer published piano instruction books for children
Jaesuk's skill
I played "Beyer's for children".
Ah, you played the owl violin.
Yeah, the owl violin.
Kwangsoo
pretends
to know
That was the yellow book.
That person so scary.
Today he can't say anything
Miss Seungjin ...
Jaesuk
team's
question
Lee Seungjin
... what piano genre do you play?
Jazz ~
You have long nails, is it really
alright playing piano with that?
My finger nails aren't long?
Ah, it's nail art.
Yes.
Where did you do it?
You want do it together?
So it's true what Framer Kwangsoo said
about nail-art in Apgujeong?
Do it.
Next week his bang will change like this.
Flute major
Question for student Ahn Eunji
Miss Ahn Eunji ...
... you played flute.
Clarinet, flute, oboe.
Among all these 3 instruments,
which one has the highest tone?
Oboe.
Is it right?
I don't know either.
The right answer is still a maze
Among the 11 women
Who are the music students?
Miss Eunryong and Miss Bangjin ...
Vocal majors
Eunryong
Bangjin
High note
competition
... please sing Do Re Mi.
High note competition.
Said they're majoring in vocal
Unstable pitch
Until the end ...
What is this?
If that's the standard,
I think I can do better.
HaHa, try doing Do Re Mi too
If HaHa wins ...
Everyone knows about HaHa's high note(?) skill
... today's standard is a little bit.
No one can win over HaHa.
In the whole ﻿world, HaHa's
the undefeated champion.
Try it.
You first.
No, start from a higher note.
Oh~
Strong confidence
Same note
different scale
Why?
Aren't you confident?
Bold high note expert(?)
You should be confident.
Doesn't care
Why are you not confident?
HaHa
wins
No one in the whole world can beat him.
High note owner Jongkook also admits it
But if you notice, their voice are not so good.
High note(?) expert is suspicious of their voices
But it is possible that they
did it like that on purpose.
Unstable note...
Real?
or
Pretending?
We don't know.
Which 3 students
Who are the real student of music faculty?
We'll choose one person among all of you.
Who ﻿is the real species and who pretended?
The real species  ?
Back to the game
Let's check it.
First to choose is the Jongkook Team.
First to choose
Jongkook*Gary*Jihyo*HaHa
Composed and elegant
exterior of a piano major?
Chae Jooyeon
Wunderkid who played
piano since age three?
Lee Seungjin
Who will they choose?
Number 1, Miss Chae Jooyeon.
Chae Jooyeon
Ah, really.
Everyone's regretful toward
Jongkook Team's choice
Ah, she's ours.
How about we choose Lee Eunyong ...
Next up is Sukjin*Joongki*Kwangsoo
... to further expose Kwangsoo?
Popularity of
Eunyong
There are many areas where we
have suspicions about Kwangsoo.
Responsible for framing Kwangsoo
Lee Eunyong
Or choose the student
who can help using her music specialty?
What will their choice be?
Lee Eunyong.
Lee Eunyong
Really?
Collapse
There're definitely some remaining secrets.
We have to listen to an authentic
source for more of Kwangsoo's past
Okay, we'll pick one too.
Really the feeling.
Whisper
You're taking about the past?
He already said just now that ...
... he'll hurt her if she opens her mouth.
Sukjin's
framing
Next up is Jaesuk*Yonghwa*Joowon
Joowon, just follow your gut feeling.
Giving talented Joowon the power to decide
I'll follow Joowon's gut feeling too.
What will Joowon's choice be?
Flute major?
Ahn Eunji
Piano wunderkid?
Seungjin
Miss Lee Seungjin.
Lee Seungjin
Oh, number 8.
Really?
Good, Miss Lee Seungjin
please come this way.
There's a bit of similarity too.
Selection complete
So now let us check.
Final checking time
So first let's have our team come out.
Team
Jaesuk
Chose Lee Seungjin
Lee Seungjin, please go to the center.
Seungjin, if it's correct then say 'Correct'.
If you study music say
Otherwise
"Correct"
"I am very sorry"
If it's not then say 'I'm very sorry'.
Is she or is she not a practicing
student of a music faculty?
Lee Seungjin
I'm Lee Seungjin, music student
at Hanyang Women University.
I started to play piano
from the age of three.
What type piano do you play?
It's jazz ~
She answered
without hesitation
Is she really
a practicing student of a music faculty?
I'm very sorry.
Team
Jaesuk
Wrong
choice
Yah, really our team ...
Then what's your major?
I'm a First Year Broadcasting Design major.
But you can play an instrument?
I've never even played once,
I don't even know where 'Do' is.
Pitch black
... don't even know where 'Do' is.
Completely of no help
But they still have to perform together with her
Jaesuk's Team
is a performance possible?
Now let us listen to Jooyeon's answer.
In my opinion, Jooyeon seems
most likely to be a pianist.
Come we'll confirm it.
Are you a practicing student of a music faculty?
I'm Chae Jooyeon, a practicing
music student majoring in piano.
A pianist.
That's what I say.
For my piano exam I played 'Meditation'.
Even spoke of a rare piano
piece without hesitation
Is their speculation
correct?
I'm sorry.
Reversal
Team
Jongkook
also chose
wrongly
Great ~
Shock
They were really convinced about the choice
And it was really a thorough check.
What faculty is Jooyeon in?
Processed foods faculty.
2nd year student of
Processed Food
Jooyeon
We cook.
You cook?
Miss Jooyeon cooks.
You're really not from any music faculty?
You really can't tell.
Now it's Miss Eunyong.
Lastly
Sukjin's
Team
chose
Lee Eunyong
Are you a student of a music faculty?
Is she a student of music?
I'm Lee Eunyong majoring in composing.
I've heard many rumors about you.
Compared to composing topics
even more topics regarding Kwangsoo
Often hits friends.
Is she a student of a music faculty?
I'm asking Miss Eunyong.
Are you a student of a music faculty?
I'm sorry.
Sukjin's
Team
also chose wrongly
Good ~
Everyone worked in vain
All teams failed to choose a student of music
I am from the Knitting Designs faculty
A 1st year Knitting Design student
Little design?
Bad ears?
Not little but knitting
Designing items as small as lighters?
You really studied at that one school, right?
Yes.
Was what you said just now is true?
So the rumors about Kwangsoo is true?
Yes, they're true.
Framing
Who amongst them
are the real students of music?
Are you a student of a music faculty?
Yes.
Kim Sungbok
1st year student majoring in bass
Yes, I am.
Ahn Eunryeong
1st year student majoring in guitar
Bang Jin
1st year student majoring in vocal
We thank Hanyang Women's University
students for assisting in the filming
Thank you for participating in the program.
2nd mission
Guess the song the band is playing
Team
Jongkook
Players: Gary, HaHa, Jihyo and Jooyeon
Challenger: Jongkook
Jooyeon just follow what you hear to play.
Study Food Processing
Playing drums for the first time in her life
Fighting
Time limit
100 sec.
Start.
What is this melody
Absurd
HaHa looks like a Guitar God
I already know.
Can't you hear?
Loveable?
Answer: Jongkook's "Loveable"
How did he answer right?
Correct
This is
"Loveable" by Kim Jongkook
2nd song performance
An even more passionate performance
Performing using all their strength
Maldalrija?
Answer: No Brain's 'Maldalrija'
Is he a genius?
Continuous
Correct
Jongkook...
The one who can find all hidden things
Mr Capable
Jongkook
Failing right from the start
HaHa, that's not acceptable.
Pay attention to
the facial expression
Forbidden to use direct body hints
Look at me.
Lee Moonsae?
Red Sunset?
Unbelievable
Team
Jongkook
3 consecutive
correct
answers
How can you hear 'Red Sunset' from this performance?
He totally looked at HaHa's expression
This time it's HaHa
playing the synthesizer
A familiar melody?
It's Gary's Leessang's song
Girl who can't break up.
You have to say out the correct song title.
Boy who can't break up ... no.
Girl who can't ... no.
Knows the song
but got the title wrong
Repeat the whole thing again.
Boy who can't breakup, girl who can't leave.
Just has to change the order
The girl who can't break up,
the boy who can't leave.
Team
Jongkook
Answered the 4th question
with difficulties
He guessed correctly.
Rather than using performance
Answered the 4 questions using
expressions and actions
2nd team
Sukjin's
Team
Players: Joongki, Kwangsoo and Eunyong
Challenger: Sukjin
Let's work hard together.
Start.
What is this?
Eunyong doesn't know how to play but is very serious
Ah, 'To You'.
Answer: Endless Orbit's 'To You'
Endless Orbit
To You
Correct
How can he
know this?
Joongki's performance
made them succeed in one flash
This melody?
"I'm A Loner".
Answer: CNBlue's 'I'm a loner'
2 questions
in a row
Correct
What happened?
Sounds familiar...?
Vaguely
Hyung ~
You don't
know this?
Sukjin's
Team
2 question's correct
What was it?
That was HOT's 'Candy' just now, right?
Right, how did you know?
Of course I know 'Candy'.
If you listen
carefully it's
'Candy'
♪ ﻿Even though I'm lonely  ♪
♪ even though I'm sad. ♪
No, not that one.
To Big Nose 'Candy' is an anime's theme song
It looks like you were
playing the instrument.
Yes.
Really?
A junior who's the same as her
thick-skinned senior Kwangsoo?
Her skin's very thick.
Team
Sukjin
2 questions
correct
Very well done.
Excuse me ...
Team
Jaesuk
Lastly
Players: Jaesuk, Joowon and Seungjin
Challenger: Yonghwa
Seungjin are you ready?
Fighting ~
They're unnatural
Holding instruments for the first time
Start.
This melody?
Jaesuk using bodily hints
What is that?
Audience please make a guess
♪ ﻿Love has left. ♪
Obstructing
What is this?
Correct, that's it.
Depressed
Obstructing
Just holding the guitar
Depressed
Ah~Ouch
I've gone mad.
♪ ﻿Tell me your wish. ♪
* SNSD's classic "Tell me your wish"
Innermost answer?
No, it's not ~
It's not
* HaHa dances "Tell me your wish"
Cocky
Joowon plays the tune on the guitar
Eh!!
Jaesuk's using gesture to give a clue
Does he know it now?
Like this?
Yonghwa knows it?
What is this?
Knew the song but forgot the title
Nobody ~
Answer: Wonder Girls' "Nobody"
Finally
Team
Jaesuk
1 question correct
The next song
What?
Play a little bit more.
I can't play more.
This one also know...!
♪ ﻿Just ten minutes. ♪
Explodes
Just ten minutes
Lee Hyori [10minute]
♪ ﻿Just ten minutes. ♪
Yonghwa finally realized
Team
Jaesuk
Answered one
question correct
Victory goes to
Jongkook's Team
Jongkook Gary HaHa Jihyo
Awarded
Running Balls
With Hanyang Women's University students
spent a short but meaningful time
But...
Now it's time to do a difficult
mission with them
Snooping
Looks like the students are
waiting for something...?
Today we are at the University ...
Hanyang Women's University's Design Center
Together with the students
Playing an unexpected hide-and-seek
... with all the students still inside.
Although it's late
many students are still here
With team-work to
complete this mission
Play this game together with them.
Can we use the help of the students?
They can help us.
Later...
Joongki and students' big risk...!
Here it comes.
Mission
Team
Instruction
Within 1 hour find and ring 4 bells.
Mission:
Find 4 different bells within 1 hour
And ring them
Within the
building
find 4 different
bells to ring
There is one in Basement 1, total of 8 floors.
Hanyang
Women's
University
Today's mission takes place at
The University's Design Center
Design Center
A total of 8 floors with students
Search it to complete the mission
Time remaining
In the corridor
you can see short love messages
Song JiYok
The result of
Kwangsoo's
sabotage
Chasing
Team
Searching
Hey.
Did anyone came here before?
What are you doing?
Doing a report.
Ah, really?
What course?
Design.
If any ants were to come ...
If any of those members wearing blue come ...
Yes?
... you must tell me.
I trust you.
Oh, so handsome.
Will the students really
tell them about the Mission Team?
Kwangsoo
Sukjin
Jaesuk
Mission Team arrives at
Basement 1st floor
Kwangsoo
Jaesuk
Sukjin
Hints for the bells locations
1. Knitting room
2. Film to photo
3. 1 - 750 Celsius 2 - 1200 Celsius
4. Miniature house model
Here is the kiln room.
Kiln room Clay works are being
shaped and baked in this place
The crafting students products
are place in this room
Here it is 1300 degree Celsius.
According to the clue
1-750C, 2-1200C Is it here?
Meanwhile
Today HaHa is acting
alone in this movie
Today's movie
Child version of
Mission Impossible
No choice
Main lead
HaHa
Hang on ...
The satellite is detecting the position.
Using turned off computer to connect to the satellite
Yes!
Right here.
Playing by himself
Kiln room
HaHa
Coincidentally
As if knowing the real position
goes to Basement 1st floor
HaHa
Bell sound
Hyung, bell sounds.
Scared
Shhh
Lock it
Lock the door
HaHa is still filming his own movie
In movies you
must do this
Sukjin
Looks like there is someone there
HaHa
Based on a movie
Catching someone
Eyes met ... HaHa.
Before he calls for help ...
Capture him.
Are you alone?
Easy to bully
HaHa's
alone~!
HaHa is easy to bully when
he is alone
Help, basement 1.
HaHa
Basement 1, it's too far.
Who is the Mission Team?
Who is the Chasing Team?
Stop there ~
Mission
Team
Captures HaHa
Can't even move
Quiet, hyung take him away.
HaHa's movie has
such a sad ending
Being bullied into a classroom
First ever hostage
What is this?
What do you want to do now?
Which floor is Jongkook on?
I don't know.
To HaHa he's still the master
Evil Guy
Totally immersed
The master must go through
tough times(?) of testing?
I don't know.
Too immersed
Can't differentiate reality from fiction
Jongkook?
I don't know.
We go there first.
Too much time wasted
Take the walkie-talkie and leave
But HaHa isn't so easy to bully
Watch out
for your back
Beautiful
retaliation
HaHa
Finally revealed the Chasing Team's real face
This is unbelievable.
Let's run away quickly.
Escape quickly
Big Nose's situation is none of our business
Competent
Sparta.
Jongkook
Running faster than anyone
Run
... Both?
Caught
Capable
Captures Yooruce Willis
Capture Kwangsoo.
Kwangsoo
Chased by Joowon
Hides under the lecturer's table
Enters the
classroom
An obvious hiding place He got caught
Hyung, wait.
Wait for what?
Kwangsoo
Nice to watch
In front of the students
Yooruce Willis amazing escape
Chasing Team
All members gather
Unknowingly coming
to Basement 1st floor
Again hiding in the Kiln room
Too fast
Abandon the VJ outside the door
Hyung ...
What?
Let's discuss for a moment.
What did you say?
Discussion?
I will let you go if you tell
me Sukjin hyung's location.
Really?
No loyalty
Yooruce Willis gives up easily
Yes.
Good.
Sukjin Hyung is at the 3rd floor.
Betrayal
Hyung ...
What?
Escape further.
Okay, I understand.
Bell...!
Yooruce Willis found the first
of the 4 school bells
How could we have missed this one?
1 of 4 bells ring
School bell
Success
Meanwhile...
Today in this all female university
a miracle happened
Total beauty ...
Flower Boys Duo
What is happening?
face
Yonghwa
Joongki
Two boys walking in front of their eyes
Today's appearance
Flower Boys Duo Miracles await...
Hello ~
Gentle
Where is this place?
Hearing his voice
Swept away by its magic
Unplanned fans gathering atmosphere
Garment Knitting Room?
Clue
Garment knotting room
No worries
Automatically directing them
Over there?
Thanks ~
Students surround the 2 boys wherever they go
Hey ~
We don't disturb you in any way?
Humble
Can we all make a deal?
A deal with Joongki...?
Later when you see Jongkook's team, those ﻿red.
Tell them that you haven't seen us.
Yes ~
Nod
Yes~
Thanks.
No need to worry.
HaHa
Yonghwa & Joongki
Reaching the 1st floor
HaHa
Bell sounds ~
Students:
Students report Anxious
HaHa appears
Where are they?
I'm very sure they were here.
Excuse me, have you seen Yonghwa?
No ~
Have you seen Yonghwa?
Of course The students cutely lied
Where did he go?
Yonghwa, Joongki~
They're hidden because of us~ Understand?
The lonely and helpless
movie protagonist ...
Meanwhile the Flower Boys Duo
Quietly sneaks away to the 6th floor
Joongki was in a hurry and entered a lecture room
There's still a lot of students inside
If the Chasing Team comes and
one girl talks there will be trouble
Outside the room is
Mr. Capable
Pretends they don't know
Thump
Is that true?
If Yooruce Willis took a photo
with you, you ﻿have to tell him?
I'll take a photo with you.
From dangerous risks comes
gracious gratitude FLASH~
Even the professors wanted his signature
Time left
Sukjin
Darkroom
Where HaHa was
Big Nose hyung
is safe
The sound of bells
Mr. Capable
Sparta.
Jongkook
Oh?
Another room in here?
Darkroom...?!
Hints for bells location
1. Garment knitting room
2. Film to photo
3. 1-750C 2-1200C CLEAR
4. Miniature house model
Big Nose
The 2nd School Bell
Found
2 out of 4
Ringing the school bell Success
What that's sound?
Click...
Big Nose
Mr. Capable was waiting for you
Oh~
Yah, you scared me ... Wait.
Panic
Jongkook, I'm your hyung.
Against Mr Capable
struggling is useless
Sukjin
I thought my whole spine
was going to be ripped out.
Remaining time
It's 5th floor.
Oh, please take the elevator.
Bumping into students who are going home
There's no one here, right?
No one at all?
I think there was one, Gary.
Gary, where is he?
He's searching in the
stairwell on the right.
Which floor are you going to?
Taking the elevator together
All are going to 1st floor
This How did Gary?
The moment Jaesuk closed the doors
Gary pressed the elevator's button
Jongkook hyung ~
Gary gets pushed out by Yooruce Willis
Jongkook and the Kids
Without Jongkook they're just kids
Jaesuk oppa, quickly come in.
Student:
Gary will always be the stubborn Gary
Sorry, can you please
hold him for a moment?
Hold him for me.
Easily got rid of Gary Must escape
What!!!
Jihyo too
Monday Couple joint attack
Chasing
Team
Surround strategy
Jaesuk
Why are we always so easily caught?
It must be Jaesuk ~
Intuition
Yooruce Willis is probably getting caught
He's probably got caught at this exact moment.
Sorry hyung, I'm a bit late right?
Finally they all reunite
The 3 prison regulars
The roads were too congested, sorry.
Today is actually the day of vacation.
You've worked hard.
Be careful on the way back home.
We've finished making oppa's
punishment clothes already.
You've made mine already?
How do you know I'll get punished?
Of course it's expected.
Alright, if I get punished
I'll definitely wear them.
This week's punishment clothes
Goodbye and thank you.
The Fashion Design major's students
have designed a pair of shocking trousers
The unimaginable pair of trousers
will be revealed later
Time remaining
Yonghwa
Don't go there.
What?
They've all walked that way.
Classified
information
Thank you.
Yonghwa enters the Interior
Design classroom on 6th floor
The birth place of Korea's future stars
of interior design
The place of
"Miniature model houses" ... ?
School bell
3 out of 4
Ringing the school bells Success
6th floor Ready for ambush but a bit dazed(?) Blank~ Jihyo
Day dreaming in the corridor
Slight bow
Joongki
Jihyo unnie
is so lucky
Can Joongki escape
while Jihyo is over there
Eh?
?
Suddenly
Yonghwa
Oppa, Yonghwa is on 6th floor.
On 6th floor.
Joongki's day is full of frights and scares
Oppa ...
The vigorously trained Jihyo
Monday Boyfriend heard it
Joowon also heard it
3rd floor.
Finally discovered
Rumble jumble
Gary
He won't let you go this time
Yonghwa
Flower Boys Duo
one has regrettably ...
Last strand
of hope
Joongki
Mission
Team
If anybody asks, tell them
I went to the 6th floor.
No, to the 7th floor.
Joongki moves toward 1st floor
1st floor where the bell wasn't found earlier
"Garment knitting room"
Where's the place where they knit sweaters?
Over there ~
Mr Capable always stayed on 3rd floor
Where?
Heading in that direction
Gasp...
Joongki is on the 1st floor
Jongkook
Joongki
If it continues
Joongki will be
caught on the spot
... floor.
Which floor?
1st floor.
2nd floor?
Jongkook is at 2nd floor ~
Shocked
2nd floor prison
Where Jaesuk, Sukjin, Kwangsoo are
Noisy
Press
Mr Capable is held up
Don't come to 2nd floor ~
Kim Jongkook is coming down ~
At that moment Joongki is on 1st floor
Safely enters
"Where woolly sweaters are made"
Kim Jongkook is with us ~
Killing 2 birds with 1 stone
Tying Mr Strong up
Protecting other members
As a result Mr Capable takes a different route
1st floor Computer Knitting Room
Their last ray of hope Joongki
Sweaters are made here
Mr Capable arrives late on 1st floor
Here Joongki asked the students to help him
Have you seen Song Joongki?
We only see Jongkook oppa.
Gary oppa came here before.
Pretending
Why are they
saying that?
Last bell is supposed to be here
There
...Oh?
No doubt Mr Capable
must have found Joongki and approaches him
There seems to be something here.
... Some other place...!
If you get caught by
us, you're done for.
We're already matching clothing,
we're like copies of each other.
Shussshhha~!
What did Joongki say?
Huh...?
What did you say?
Ring
Found all 4 bells
Mission
Team
Ringing the school bells Success
Joongki rings
the last bell
Mission
Team
Wins
Ah, Joongki ...
A glorified return
The main character
should've been me
Sukjin*Jaesuk*Kwangsoo*Joongki*Yonghwa
get Running Balls
These are the clothes that the fashion
design students designed for us.
Today's special punishment's clothing
Their finished designed products.
Joowon worked really hard today, but ...
Statistics
Yonghwa
ball
Jaesuk*Jongkook*Sukjin*HaHa
Gary*Joongki*Kwangsoo*Jihyo
balls
Confirmed
punishment
Joowon has 0 Running Balls
Sorry Joowon.
Does this means 5 people will be exempted?
Escape
rule
Collected balls are put into a lottery machine.
The 5 names drawn will be exempt from punishment
Today's
punishment
Wear the clothes at
Shindangdong Ddeokbokki Restaurant
At this hour it's many people in the streets.
Please ~
Lastly
Lottery machine of destiny turns
Oh, it's me.
Jongkook
Confirmed
to escape
Muscle man
Joyous shouts
The 2nd escapee?
HaHa
Confirmed
to escape
Who's the 3rd escapee?
Jihyo
Confirmed
to escape
Next member to escape is?
Kwangsoo
Confirmed
to escape
Rejoice
Now the last chance
Yonghwa
Confirmed
to escape
Happiness'
Lets go.
Deflated
Where are we going again?
Sorrow
Of course going to Shindandong
To Shindandong.
The special shorts collection
These are given to us and designed by students.
Pink pig's tail
It looks good, but ...
A brown bushy rail
... he's the most good looking.
Men's beauty
furry shorts
It's filled with masculine beauty.
Pure white feathers
Today's spotlight
Convenient and practical
Shorts that replaces cushions
Arrives at Ddeobokki restaurant
In a chilly weather spicy rice cakes are the best
Hello, ﻿it looks tasty.
Awkward
Welcome
Eat a lot.
Thank you.
This looks really delicious.
Mouth-watering
Warm cozy atmosphere
Is the dukbokki tasty?
Tourists from Japan
Very delicious, eat some.
Those pants are really weird.
Reinforcing
Sukjin's cushion replacing shorts
Interesting
experience
in Korea
You've ate it all?
The bowl is now empty
This is no joke, we've really ate
Thank you ~
Today's
Punishment completed