Original hardsubs by iSUB
Transcribed by HapB
Color and alignment by SamFive
The harbor city of Busan
Running Man
Cruise Special
the Busan girl Lizzy
On the cruise
Crossing fates of people
Romance on the Cruise ♥
The first time
Unveiling bare faces(?)
The rising sun marks the beginning of
the running battle
Cruise
Special
Starts now
It has been quite a while, but
Running Man gathered again.
Today's landmark is ...
Today, we are here in Busan.
Korea's largest port city
Busan
Running Man is here in Busan
Cruise special issue
Today Gary is using sea
sickness patch on his ear.
Seasickness
patch
Jihyo is really disappointed.
Just in case I get seasick.
You won't be seasick on a huge
ship, never been on one before?
Stop saying that.
Why?
Recently, the Hide-n-seek
has become the hot topic.
Ah, yeah.
But for my son, it is a desperation.
Why is that?
Last week, when I opened the door.
My son was very sad after he watched it.
Unexpectedly, he went to the kitchen.
He made himself a milk bomb by
mixing yogurt and strawberry milk.
The hurt feeling is
like drinking strawberry milkshake
Now, we are here in Busan.
Today we have invited a guest from Busan.
She is Busan's representative.
Lizzy.
Busan's representative
Lizzy
She enters
lively!!
Hello, I am here.
Lizzy, finally after so long ...
I'm here.
Everyone is poisoned by 'I am here'
How long has it been since you
went back to your hometown?
I haven't come back for few months.
This time I'm really happy
that I got to come back.
Today, Lizzy is with us again.
The stage for Running Man is on ...
Just take a look at the back.
... a big structure on the sea
A cruise
The cruise travels between Japan and Korea.
We'll stay here until the next morning.
There are six stories above
ground and two underground.
Kwangsoo, did you ever
ride on this before?
This is my first time coming to Busan.
First visit?
Yes ~
Don't speak so kindly, you scary person.
Startled
Excuse me, please take
off your spectacles.
Surprised
Evidence by a junior previously about
'playful Kwangsoo' is true?
As expected.
Kwangsoo, well done.
It's time to get on board.
Are we sailing off?
Of course we must.
Really?
Yeah, why?
What do you plan to do at sea?
You want to be like Titanic?
The greatest romance
Titanic love on board
Sure enough...
Later on
Noona, last time wasn't
there the Titanic?
A three way relationship
♥ Love story on a cruise
Why do I have to see this?
The two indulge in a romance
and a man in grief
It's tiring to like you.
Later all myths will be unveiled
The male lead actor of Titanic has a
seasickness patch stuck on his neck.
But here, the lead actress
hasn't prepared anything.
I have also prepared for you, dummy.
Gary's never ending love for Jihyo
What will happen to Running
Man on the cruise today?
We'll have to get on board to find out.
Shall we go now?
Yeah ~
Let's go.
In the blue autumn sky
Warmest welcome given
by the captain and crew
Oh, there is an escalator here.
High-class and
ambiance indoor
Interior of a ship?
Feels like entering a hotel
It would be interesting to
play hide-and-seek here.
A total of
130 guest rooms
Can go outside from here.
Highlight
The wide deck
We can hold party here, drinking wine.
This is the main deck.
Lighthearted mood
HaHa wants to fly with the balloons?
Very funny, HaHa.
Tongue-in-cheek
Kid in high spirit since he got on board
Thanks to HaHa
Everyone is happily preparing to sail
The boat reached
the Busan coast
The cruise is ready to depart
All stations standby ~
What's this?
They said standby, so we'll depart soon.
We're departing.
The cruise
sails off
The boat is going where?
Heading to Kwang-An Bridge.
We plan to stay a night
near Kwang-An Bridge.
Crossing Busan's ocean
Heading to Kwang An Bridge~
What is the first game?
One vs. eight game?
Today, is one vs. eight Game.
First mission
game
A detective game, find the criminal.
Detective game Find the criminal
That game is awesome.
Find one person?
Yes, but who's the criminal
hasn't been decided yet.
What?
All of you will receive instructions later.
Is that so?
The criminal needs to complete
a task without being discovered.
The criminal has to disrupt the
game without being discovered
Like what we did on X-Man.
Who will it be?
If the criminal is caught the
others will get Running Balls
Where do we receive the instruction?
Everyone go to the captain's room ...
If the criminal isn't discovered
only the criminal gets a ball
... to receive their instructions.
Understood.
Can I go first?
Jaesuk's acting skill is bad.
This place is
the captain's room
Captain Kim Seungryul
Speechless
Are you giving me an award?
Yoo Jaesuk is ...
Yoo Jaesuk The criminal ...
Yes?
No?
Hello.
Welcome.
Come over here please.
Wow, so handsome.
Handsome?
Yes.
Ready to get your instruction?
Yes I'm ready.
You are ...
Song Jihyo The criminal ...
Yes?
No?
You are ...
the criminal ...
HaHa
Is he the criminal?
the criminal ...
Or the pretty boy
Joongki?
the criminal ...
Or the saboteur
Kwangsoo?
Find the criminal and
the other 8 members get Running Balls
Criminal
Running Man
Lizzy, are you the criminal?
Nope.
Is it Song Jihyo?
I kind of wanted to be
the criminal for once.
Song Joongki should be
We really don't know who it is,
but the criminal is one of us.
What game are we playing?
The game in a singing relay.
Yes?
In 100 seconds, sing different songs
according to the given topic.
In 100 seconds 9 people will sing
different songs for the given topic
100 seconds ...
The topic will be changed every round.
The criminal has to make them
fail the singing relay
The first topic is Kim Jongkook.
Song relay game
Topic: <Kim Jongkook>
Any Kim Jongkook's songs is fine, right?
Ready ...
The 9 of them aren't allowed to repeat
a song in 100 seconds
Ready, go.
Gary, you are very suspicious.
Blank~
♪ You're lovable from head to toe ♪
Jongkook's most
popular song
<Loveable>
Unsure
♪ There's a man who loves you so much ♪
Volume 2
<One Man>
I was going to
sing this song
Turbo's 1st song!
<Childhood Dream>
♪ I keep walking in one spot ♪
Volume 3
<Walking in
One Spot>
♪ I keep walking in one spot ♪
HaHa's turn
Uneasy
Hurry ~
Hurry up ~
♪ One person ... ♪
Wrong
Is HaHa the criminal that is
intentionally wasting time?
Hurry, start over.
♪ You're lovable from head to toe ♪
Need to start over if it's wrong
Again
<Loveable>
Turbo
<Black Cat>
A recent song ~
Remake album "Song"
<Come Back to Me Again>
♪ To eat with gusto, is  ♪
♪ an evil reason, missing ♪
Remake album "Song"
<The Neck of the
Rapid Waters>
Jihyo hurry ~
Wait, what else is there?
Nervous
Did anyone sing Black Cat ?
<Black Cat>
has already been sung
Sang it already?
Because
the time is up
Failure
Unknown punishment came on
Funnel hitting
memory on boat
Welcome
Punishment
Fast and strong
I was hit so hard.
I saw your face.
They were our managers.
Found out the identities of the punishers
Their managers
Really?
They're our managers.
We wasted too much time at the front.
We have to find the criminal.
Jihyo noona is very suspicious.
Confused~
I didn't know that someone
already sang Black Cat.
I was trying to think what song to
sing, so I couldn't hear you guys.
I could hear.
Do you have ear problems?
The suspicious people now
are Joongki, Lizzy, Jihyo.
And Kwangsoo is also a little ...
Unexpected suspect Kwangsoo?
You follow me to the front.
You're a little weird too.
When was I?
Their hearts are filled with suspicion
When I'm around you, I'm always weird.
This is weird.
Why?
Aren't you feeling hot?
Strange
Wearing a warm jacket
in a warm room!?
Wearing a fur-collared jacket,
you must be feeling anxious.
You permed your hair?
It was already permed.
The curls are slightly gone.
Let's stop for awhile.
The second topic is trot.
Pass the music
Main topic: Trot
Ready, start.
♪ Jjan jjan jjan ♪
♪ Unable to speak the words in my heart ♪
Pronunciation ...
Wrong
♪ Chan Chan Chan ♪
♪ Unable to speak the words in my heart ♪
♪ I can't say the words "I love you" ♪
That's it ~
Pyeon Seungyeop
<Chan Chan Chan>
♪ Men are boats, women are harbors ♪
Shim Soobong
<Men are boats
Women are harbors>
<Love Manripo>
Taking a breath?
Joongki's all weird, you're
arousing suspicions like that.
♪ Who are you waiting for, sweet 18 years old ♪
Is this trot?
Fail
Isn't there that song by Park Hyunbin?
Starting from Jihyo again
Gary, this trot is for you.
♪ I can't say the words "I love you" ♪
Why must it be that song?
Jang Yoonjeong
<Heaven>
♪ Her face is V-line ♪
♪ Her figure is S-line ♪
Park Hyunbin
<Shabang Shabang>
♪ Gondeurae manderau ♪
♪ I'm ... ♪
♪ ... so drunk ♪
Still Park Hyunbin
<Gondeurae
Manderau>
Why are you showing off
your singing skills here?
Sim Soobong
<Hate it>
♪ Don't know when it'll come ♪
♪ The goodbye at the harbor ♪
Countdown
Sim Soobong
<Men are boats
Women are harbors>
Okay, but ...
What, I haven't even sung yet.
The manager squad
Appears
The managers
got better at punishment
They'll do it seriously
The outstanding mangers
Come here ~
Inspector Jongkook's
manager is
captured
Jongkook's manager is punished
Yah, Jongkook ...
Making last minute threats
and leaving the scene
Crazy
Gapjin
Gapjin = Jongkook's manager
Isn't that Jongkook's manager?
Oh, he really hit me hard.
Can even suppress the
punishment squad
Commander
This time we didn't even get close.
But trot was such a good chance.
They're weird.
Jihyo was weird and Joongki too.
I really couldn't think, I panicked.
Something's fishy...
Joongki could be the criminal, his
acting is good in the first place.
I really couldn't think of anything.
Why don't Lizzy go to the front then.
Suspects
Lizzy*Jihyo*Joongki
All to the front
Lizzy, Jihyo and Joongki,
all of you go to the front.
Joongki is definitely 100% the criminal.
He's normally full of vigor.
His brain's also good, gives
others ideas all the time.
You're the weird one.
It's Joongki.
Blank Jihyo is also weird.
I didn't even do anything.
How could you sing Chan
Chan Chan as Jjan jjan jjan?
So it's...
Did Jihyo sing wrong on purpose?
But Jihyo is always like that.
I don't think she's acting right now.
It's possible.
♥ Because it's
Blank Jihyo...
Happiness~(?)
Let's move back a bit.
You either wear it ...
... or take it off.
This is suspicious, is it because
he's nervous he's acting like that?
It's because I'm feeling warm, my t-shirt
is a little unfitting for the current season.
Anyway, you just want
to show off your arms.
No, that's not it.
There's no one in the world
that would notice your arms.
Who do you think
would notice your arms.
Who would be concerned?
I'm Just like that because I'm hot.
It's because I'm hot.
Tap
Come come, let's tap it
so your veins pop out.
Nurses should like it,
they like it like this.
Missed injection rate ZERO
Jongkook's arms
I heard from the coordinator that ...
Sabotage
... when his jacket is taken off, the
coordinators must prepare a t-shirt.
To show off?
Buzz!
Immediately regrets
It's okay to regret when
you stand close to him.
Maybe because Jongkook
is right beside the framer...
Song relay
Last round
The main topic now is the sea or Busan.
Last
round
Song relay
Main topic: Busan or the sea
♪ Like the stars in the sky ♪
♪ Like the salt in the sea ♪
* Lizzy who is a member of Afters School is also
a member of the subgroup Orange Caramel
Orange Caramel
<Magical Girl>
You're stalling for time.
♪ I'm lying on the sea ♪
♪ becoming a lonely seagull ♪
Place of High Notes
<Living on the sea>
Look, she's weird.
♪ Seoul Daejeon Daegu Busan ♪
♪ Take a photo Ah ha ♪
Kim Hyejoon
<Seoul Daejeon
Daegu Busan>
♪ Let's go, let's go toward the sea ♪
Kim Jeongu
<Harmonies
of the sea>
♪ My big sea, my blue skies ♪
<Big sea>
Everyone's thinking of this song
♪ Let's go, let's go toward the sea ♪
♪ Busan seagull ♪
Self-cover
Jongkook's
<Busan seagull>
Sea ~
* Pada means sea in Korean, but it's also the name of a singer
♪ I'm so mad ♪
The criminal?
Singing a
Bada song
I really don't know
any more sea songs.
Fail
How could you sing Bada's song.
Again starting from Lizzy
Not much time left
Everyone speeds up
♪ Busan's seagull ♪
Steals Jongkook's song
Pass
Argument
Hurry up ~
Oh...?
Intentionally stalling for time?
Jongkook immediately discovers
Jongkook's manager Kim Gapjin
getting punished by Jongkook
Lizzy also resists
Constantly "taking care"
of his manager
Commander
The manager punishment squad retreats
Jaesuk hyung is also very suspicious.
It's not me.
Aren't you the one who
knows a lot of songs?
Jaesuk, you stand here.
Also Jaesuk is forced to the front
But...
the game has already ended
Hyung, the game's already ended.
If we ask nicely, won't we
be given another chance?
Can't we get another chance?
Trot in 50 seconds ~
Male Idols in 50 seconds ~
No, it's too difficult.
Then, male idol groups in 50 seconds.
He's being weird.
Because he's the MC for a music program
he chose idol songs as the main topic?
Currently it's a group game
I will move to the back then.
No need, Joongki you stay there.
I think Jaesuk hyung
is really very weird.
Gary is always suspecting Jaesuk
Jaesuk hyung should
go to the 2nd position.
I agree, Jaesuk hyung should be 2nd.
I already told you it isn't me.
The top suspects
forced to the front
The real last round
<Male idol songs>
Thinking
Ah, Kwangsoo you ...
♪ Lies... ♪
Ah, too much rap.
Big Bang
<Lies>
Jihyo is also wasting time
She's really weird.
I wanted to sing Big Bang.
Hurry up ~
♪ Look at me at me Gwisoo ♪
We are cool
Big Bang's Daesung
<Look at me
Gwisoon>
Confirmed
It's correct.
Big Bang
<Sunset glow>
♪ 10 points out of ... 10 points ♪
This is...?
Why?
Wrong
He sang the song wrong
Plus time's up
What was that?
10 points out of 10 points.
It's Jihyo noona, no mistaking it.
Joongki was under heavy suspicion
Suspecting Jihyo now
If you knew Big Bang songs you should
have told me, why you keep it to yourself?
That's ridiculous.
Just letting me sing Big Bang like that.
Didn't I already teach you to
sing "Look at me Gwisoo"?
Stop lying oppa.
Seriously...
But I really thought you to
sing "Look at me Gwisoo".
Ah, that's right.
How can you acknowledge it so fast?
That isn't Big Bang's.
Yes, it is.
I don't know who it is.
Causing the game to fail
Who is the real criminal?
Who can it be?
It really isn't me.
It would be good if I was really the criminal.
Everyone's pushing it on me.
You're becoming anxious,
you must be the criminal.
It's because I'm sea sick.
Suddenly saying what...
...sea sickness and stuff.
Time to point out the criminal
Everyone sits down and closes their eyes.
Then you take turn to point
at the criminal from behind.
Everyone in front should shut their eyes?
Please sit down.
Please keep your eyes closed.
HaHa starts pointing
out the criminal
It's seriously not me, this one is too hard.
The weak kid HaHa isn't investigating...
acts tough behind them
I think it's pretty easy.
Pretends to be mighty
It's seriously not me.
HaHa votes for Joongki
Who will Gary point out?
Guess who?
Always jokes with Jihyo
Monday Boyfriend
Later...
The Monday Couple's big reversal
Oh, Jongkook looks like the Terminator.
Gary points out Jaesuk
Joongki
votes
Popular
Jaesuk didn't follow the
rest and points out Sukjin?
Oh?
Kwangsoo's choice is?
The first time HaHa?
Mighty mode?
To express his dissatisfaction
of Jongkook just now...
Surprised
Kwangsoo, why?
Why are you like this?
Toying with HaHa?
votes
Joongki
Jaesuk
votes
Jihyo
vote
And the results are in.
Results:
Joongki
Jaesuk
Sukjin
Jihyo
All the votes ...
Final scores.
The criminal
is inside this cruise
The suspect that was chosen the most is ...
It's Song Joongki.
5 votes
Joongki overwhelmed with votes
It's Song Joongki.
Song Joongki, please step forward.
The chosen criminal
Joongki
First to face the judgment
So is Joongki really the criminal?
If Joongki's the criminal
the other 8 members will win
1, 2 ...
The only one with a lot of mistakes
It would be good if I was really the criminal.
Was it all...
because of seasickness?
Everyone is pushing it on me.
... 3.
Is Song Joongki ...
... the real criminal?
Is Joongki the criminal?
If he's the criminal
the other 8 members win
Is incorrect.
He isn't.
Incorrect
Joongki isn't the real criminal
I told you he wasn't.
Then is it Jihyo?
I really forgot the lyrics.
I told you it wasn't Joongki.
Jaesuk ...
Could it be the one
with 2 votes Jaesuk?
It's not me, I just didn't
think about it before.
First of all, everybody fails
and the criminal succeeds.
Am I the real criminal?
Is Jaesuk the criminal?
1 ...
Please.
Yoo Jaesuk ...
Instead of singing
about Bada (sea)
Jaesuk sang
a song
by Bada
(Choi Seonghee)
Is he the criminal?
He isn't.
Didn't I tell you that it wasn't me.
Jihyo noona is the real criminal.
Is Jihyo really the criminal?
1, 2 ...
The girl that was already
a suspect once
Made a few mistakes...
But she's a girl with a pitiful image
... 3.
Is this girl the criminal
that tricked all the members?
Is Song Jihyo the real criminal?
She is the criminal.
The criminal is
Correct
Blank~ Jihyo
Shocked
Was that your acting?
Jihyo is really the criminal.
Ah, it's Song Jihyo.
Ha ha
Sorry
Song Jihyo you are the criminal.
Jihyo appointed by the captain
as the criminal
Ah, seriously she's not Blank Jihyo.
I suspected her in the beginning.
But she said she was always like that.
Just because Joongki suddenly
started to behave suspiciously.
Was that all acting?
Hey Jihyo, you're seriously too scary.
Anyway, for the first round ...
... Song Jihyo wins.
Only Jihyo gets
a Running Ball
After the first round
the cruise has arrived at the Kwang An Bridge
We have arrived at the Kwang An Bridge.
This is really beautiful.
In the middle of the sea
transform into a Love Cruise ♥
Last night
in Busan
We've gathered on a cruise
here during the weekend.
Isn't the Kwang An Bridge
very beautiful right now?
The Busan landmark
a bridge that leaves your eyes hanging
This is wonderful.
A night scene that is worth seeing
when you are on a weekend trip.
This is a tourist attraction too.
That's right ~
In the past, do you know what?
There was a famous
foreign film called ...
... the Love Boat.
Which means a boat with love.
Yoo Jaesuk knows, I also
remember it very clearly.
It was aired in our nation back in the 80s
The American film received a lot of popularity
It was a love story.
A different kind of love story
will happen on this cruise
It was the first love story movie
that happened on a boat.
And did you know that Lizzy's
home is around there.
Busan girl
Ah, that's very close to Kwang An.
Somewhere near the Kwang An Bridge.
Then we can see your mother.
But my mom is living at my
grandma's place right now.
You can't see her, very straight forward.
She's honest.
The second mission.
Second mission
Just now, Ji Sukjin already mentioned it.
The Love Boat.
The Love Boat
Pick one you want to share a scene with.
Love
Boat
Pick someone you like to share a
beautiful night scene with. Only
the chosen couple will get Balls
Yes.
Only couples get Running Balls.
Giving the Running Balls to the couples.
Doesn't that mean that the girls will
automatically receive a Running Ball?
That's not true.
Why's that?
If the girl doesn't choose the one
that chose her, they won't get a ball.
Am I allowed to discuss
this with the others?
We should help each other out.
Jongkook, Lizzy help each other
Choosing each other?
It's an honor.
What did she say?
Jongkook just discussed with Lizzy, but ...
... I think there's going to be a problem.
Lizzy will pick Joongki.
Picking based on appearance.
Is there really a meaning to this pick?
Why?
Honestly
Flower Joongki is placed in the front
First choice will be based on
appearance, do you hear me?
Where are you going?
Gary gives up?
We still don't know what kind of
appearances fit Lizzy and Jihyo taste.
That's right.
Then the guys will pick first.
One out of the two girls.
Can you close your ears?
Then we'll start with Kwangsoo.
1st challenger
Kwangsoo
I'll choose based on what I think.
Then just say it out ... 1, 2, 3.
I choose Jihyo noona.
Song Jihyo
You said you chose me?
Embarrassed
Ah, embarrassing.
Even Kwangsoo...
For me, I choose ...
2nd challenger
Ji Sukjin
... Lizzy.
Lizzy
Okay, Jongkook.
Jihyo ~
Very well, I got it.
3rd challenger
Jongkook
Jihyo
Joongki is next.
Jihyo noona.
4th challenger
Joongki
Jihyo
Okay, Gary.
Song Jihyo.
Lizzy, what's going on?
Obviously said Song Jihyo...
Jaesuk playing tricks on Gary
Lizzy, what's going on?
Song Jihyo, I chose Song Jihyo.
Yelling~
Song Jihyo!!!
What's wrong with you.
5th challenger
Gary
Song Jihyo
Ah, is that Pororo?
6th challenger
HaHa
Pororo~
It's Pororo ~
The one that loves to play Kid Pororo?
Okay Pororo, please choose.
I seriously never thought of that.
Not satisfied being called Pororo?
Be quiet and listen.
Pororo is really weird.
You're the adult version of Pororo.
Haroro's 1st pick is?
Okay Pororo, choose.
When I first met Song Jihyo ...
... her eyes were really big.
But only the eyes are big.
There isn't a single charm
that attracts me to you.
But it seems like she stole your heart.
Are you kidding?
I am HaHa.
Bad boy?
You are Pororo.
Why do you keep on
bringing up Pororo?
That trend makes him even smaller
Alright then, Pororo's pick is?
None.
Tough
Reversal
As expected of bad little rascal Haroro
Looking at the current situation, it's
going be hard to become a couple.
Then, I will pick.
Last challenger Jaesuk's pick
When I first met Jihyo ...
First time seeing her ...
... I seriously thought that among
the numerous celebrities I've seen
... I felt that it's a waste if this
face only appeared on TV.
How about compared to your wife?
What?
Aigoo, we are not talking about that now.
Why are you mentioning
her all of a sudden?
Haroro and Grasshopper
are battling a childish war
Pororo ~
Results
for round 1
Okay, now it is time for
Jihyo to choose a man.
It's finally time for the women
to make their decisions
Jihyo ...
Based on looks?
Yes, only looks.
Calm appearance of
Monday boyfriend Gary?
The prettiest man
Flower Boy Joongki...?
It can't be
Pororo's style?
Song Joongki.
Song Jihyo
Song Joongki
Clearly~
I just knew that things
would turn out this way.
He is disappointed.
Monday Boyfriend is heartbroken
1st couple
Jihyo
Joongki
What's wrong with my face?
Gary is still hoping?
Aren’t you the Kang Gary?
I saw it.
Let’s block our ears.
It’s Lizzy’s turn.
Kang Gary.
Lizzy
Kang Gary
Oh, what did she say?
She didn't say Joongki?
Did she say HaHa?
No, it wasn't HaHa?
Kang Gary.
Oh, really?
Kang Gary?
We didn’t hear Lizzy's choice.
Must have been Gary.
Garyzzy.
* Instead of the polite form Gari-ssi she
combines their names (Gary+Lizzy=Gary-zzy)
Ah, really?
Garyzzy is my choice.
Ah, Garry-zzy.
Gary + Lizzy
Garyzzy
Although it is weird, it’s still
easier to call him Garry-zzy.
Okay, time to start the Love's Cruise.
Imagine that this is the location of your date
and you find out about each others' feelings.
Now the two of you ...
Oh, what are you doing?
Applying lipstick, oppa.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I'm anticipating it
Why does it seem like
you want to kiss today?
Joongki was like that the other time.
Remembers the kiss
the previous time
Kwangsoo you can start and select
one of them to play a game with.
I ...
... would like to try with
Jihyo noona for once.
The relationship between lovers.
Love's Cruise
Kwangsoo's feelings
Noona, I’m sorry I came late.
It's okay, let's have a drink.
Lovers in
the restaurant
but...
Drinking again?
Jihyo has suddenly turned into an alcoholic
I’m not the one who brought it.
Desperately
explaining
I'm feeling so frustrated.
Kwangsoo's impulsive feelings
Drinking the wine
What are you doing now?
Not understanding his feelings...
Seems like he's going to confess soon
Can see a confession coming.
I have something to tell you, noona.
I am ...
... just a kid.
That's enough ...
It was good until there,
what were you thinking?
I was just starting to be romantic.
What starting now?
Not able to let go of
his romantic feelings
Okay, next is Joongki.
I will do it like ...
... a confession I did in
high school to a senior.
Jihyo noona again?
Love's Cruise
"Senior, shall we date?"
Oh, how have you been?
It’s been a long time.
This is really good.
Meeting the senior which
he once had a crush on
The ambiance is good.
I have prepared something for you.
Jihyo seems to be sweeter now?
Different attitudes toward Kwangsoo and Joongki
Looking
straight
Romantic ambiance in the restaurant
While we are in this
restaurant I wish to ...
... give noona something
Oh, what is it?
It is cold, so wrap the
shawl around you first.
Song Jihyo, what kind
of expression is that?
Oh, keep quiet.
Warning the audience
It's so sweet.
Since we're done preparing ...
... help me, noona.
How do I?
Let’s walk over there.
Walking with his noona
to another place...
Moving around is good,
I should do that too!
Audience
full of anticipation
Aigoo, Lizzy.
Regretting
Why couldn't I do it this way too?
Jongkook taking care of Lizzy who is alone
Why didn't you do that to me?
The space between the two of them
Not happy!
Wow, seeing this place
like this is really good.
Drama ~
Standing here at the night ...
... with noona reminds me of the
movie with Leonardo Di Caprio.
Titanic ~
The pose.
The romantic Titanic pose
girls wish to do
Want to do a Titanic pose?
Even the shy Jihyo
will like it
Not happy
Why?
So romantic.
Seeing this now is so romantic.
Agitated
Stand here.
In a world of their own...
Why do I have to watch this?
Angry
The Monday Boyfriend is angry.
Of course.
Finally
feeling like they're flying in the air...
Spreading out
both her arms...
No matter
what people think...
This is
their own time...
Standing
together...
Looking at the same place
the two of them
And...
The two lonely boys
Like a drama.
Noona ...
Yes?
Let's... date?
The shy
confession
What...
does this mean?
Okay, let’s stop.
Jihyo was going to agree, seems
like she was really considering.
Jihyo was moved?
No matter what, please
do not misunderstand ...
... as this is just to
get a Running Ball.
Don't misunderstand.
However, it seemed like Jihyo
was really going to agree.
Okay, I am anticipating.
Kang Gary.
Monday Boyfriend turn
What kind of circumstance?
Gary chooses Jihyo without hesitation
Being in a relationship for 100 days.
After being in a relationship for 100 days.
100 days into being in a relation
Oh, it's 100 days already?
Okay, start.
Jihyo, what are you doing?
Love's Cruise
The first 100 days
You are late.
Sorry.
Oppa was preparing something.
Let’s look at the waves.
Learning from Joongki?
They are moving too?
Let's date, Jihyo.
Hold on to oppa.
Looks like he wants to
re-enact Joongki's Titanic?
Let's date.
Reluctantly with one hand
No ...
Sorry Jihyo.
What's happening?
Jihyo ...
On drugs?
I have something to tell you.
Really?
Although the sky and the sea are very far
apart, they still can be together, right?
Really?
Open your hand.
Rushing like he’s reading off a book.
Gary's speaks so fast
it seems he's reciting
Whenever oppa say something ...
Calm
Yeah.
... put down your fingers
The game of five fingers
Song Jihyo, bend a finger.
Jihyo, bend.
The prettiest lady who stands
in front of me, bend a finger.
A confession
that's as natural as the game
Has spent 100 days with
me, put down a finger.
Now there is
only the pinky left
What's there?
A ring from
the innocent man
To celebrate this day,
In the end a ring is
put on the last finger
The couple's
100 days celebratory ring...
The ring doesn't fit.
Wrong size
Knew it would end like this Like a comedy...
I can do it for you.
My love is for no one but you.
How big is your finger
that she can't wear it?
Honestly, being with her is tiring.
Next, Pororo.
Haroro doesn't know Pororo.
Fighting well means
being a good actor?
Of course not, you are cute.
Who will HaHa like to act with?
I want both ~
The bad boy
It's coming again
This is really not a joke.
Love's Cruise
The bad point
of a bad boy
Stand up.
Get up ~
Telling her to get
up once it starts
Thinking about it
makes one angry
Telling Jihyo to get up.
Sitting on Jihyo's seat...
You stand up too.
Then...
uses both
chairs
Ridiculous
What?
Stand straight.
Straight.
Before the two of
you get injured.
No matter what ...
Congratulations to
the both of you.
Why congratulating them?
The two of you have
been spotted by me.
Speechless
Spotted by him?
Getting weirder
This is too ridiculous.
Flip!
Oh!
Can't reach the chair
His legs are too short.
Big humiliation
Short legs make it end with an NG
Bad boy's tragic ending
Because his legs are too
short, it ends like this.
What should I do?
I also...
Yoo Jaesuk also participates.
Last challenger Jaesuk
Who do you want to be your partner?
Because a lot of people chose Jihyo.
Lizzy.
I'm choosing Lizzy.
Oppa ~
We're schoolmates.
Friend ~
I'm a dance crew president.
The most famous in school
Dance crew president?
It can't be ~
This acting situation
is a big joke
Why?
It's all up to me.
Dance crew president.
It doesn't make sense, hyung.
Why?
However he'll appear later
Legend's best dancer
You really like dancing.
That's right.
You're a person who
really likes dancing.
Girlfriend of dance
crew president
Lizzy please sit down.
On last week's episode, there was Joongki
and Yonghwa with the flying petal CG ...
What?
Can it be that
he wants this?
What did you say?
The staff will give a lot of flying petal CG.
He really wants the petal CG
What are you doing?
I already said I'm the
dance crew president.
Please think of a
more realistic setting.
When I pass by, please say ...
There's still one more request?
... wow!
He's really happy alone...
You must be crazy.
Do you want to be a king?
It doesn't make sense.
What's your name?
Call me Hyuk.
Quickly
Don't know why but it's a good name
Yoo Hyuk
Yoo Hyuk ~
Loves's Cruise
Legend's best dancer,
Yoo Hyuk
Ordinary students who adore Hyuk
He's coming ~
At this time
Yoo Hyuk appears
His appearance makes
these students agitated
He starts to
dance beautifully
This is the reaction that he wants...
Confidence is flowing
Showing his dance
moves one by one
Full of reaction
Yoo Hyuk
Explosion of confidence
Even
New dance move~!!
Doesn't care what dance
Yoo Hyuk performs ...
Blank~ Jihyo is
kneeling...
Yoo Hyuk, let's eat after this.
Friends want to get closer to him
Oppa, let's shake hand.
Yoo Hyuk gently(?) refuses
Giving a dance instead
Yoo Hyuk ~
Members passionately adore him
Legend's best dancer keeps
performing new moves
Hyuk's dance has ended...
Going to sit beside Lizzy...
Falling
There's someone here.
Hyuk's humiliation
Even for just a while, how
did you feel to be a king?
Very happy.
But what's this?
Its a dance.
What's this? Dancing?
Special one...
This is...
But what was that?
That was clearly a move
from citizen exercises.
Next you'll get a sketchbook and pen.
Confession
time
The men write the name of the
woman they like and the women
do the same to decide the couples
Male members will write the
name of the girl they like.
After that, female members will do the same.
If there is a match, they become a couple.
Now, please all of you write your choice.
Cruise of love
Who's inside these people's hearts?
Next, let's have the male
members read theirs first.
One by one read it.
1st confession
Kwangsoo
Knowing her, meeting
her is my happiness.
Who is it?
The result
Who's inside Kwangsoo's heart?
Lizzy ~
Final decision
Kwangsoo
Lizzy
It's touching.
Because I never knew
he would choose me.
So are you giving up
Jihyo to choose Lizzy?
Of course not.
Next is Joongki.
2nd confession
Joongki
I am ...
actually very scared
Oh, it's really annoying.
Romantic man label
Joongki
I'm... actually a coward.
Please continue.
When I watch horror movies,
I don't dare to open my eyes.
Why are you getting jealous over that?
Aren't all of you men?
It's cool ~
If I go to a high place ...
... my legs will shake.
I'm a coward too.
But for me the most scary
thing is when I can't see you.
Joongki is giving
a deep look to Jihyo noona
You're the view I'm missing
But we meet each other every
week, so what do you mean?
Will these two hearts unite?
Joongki
Jihyo
Bitter
Senior Jihyo ...
... please choose me.
A wide smile
Who is inside Jihyo's heart?
Next is ...
3rd confession
Ji Sukjin
I don't know if my confession has any meaning.
So I'll make my confession a bit different.
In this world there's no one like
"Yoo Sujeong"
I love you forever!
What?
In this world there's no one like Yoo Sujeong.
A confession for someone at home
I love you forever.
Yoo Sujeong
Sukjin's wife
You're too much.
It's just a game.
This is my true feeling.
Next is Kim Jongkook.
4th confession
Jongkook
Kim Jongkook ...
Is it really from your heart?
What would it be like if
I don't get a Running Ball?
Can you imagine?
If I don't have a Running Ball, how is it?
Let's imagine
If he doesn't get a Running Ball
It must be scary.
It's creepy.
Lizzy... help me.
Oppa doesn't want to be the last one.
Jongkook
Lizzy
Next is Gary.
5th confession
Gary
For most people, Monday
is the most tiring day
For me, it is the happiest day
For most people, Monday
is the most tiring day.
For me, it is the happiest day.
Seriously feeling the
confession from Monday Boyfriend
Gary
Jihyo
Deep look~
Very nervous, I'm going crazy.
Next is ... Pororo.
6th confession
Pororo HaHa
It's me, HaHa.
You must make the right decision.
Bad boy who played with these two women
If you don't want to get hurt.
My choice ...
Who
is his choice...?
HaHa
Lizzy
Lizzy ~
Lizzy already got
three confessions
Look how happy she is ~
Let us see mine.
Last confession
Jaesuk
Show it to us.
It ends here
(Hyuk-inun yoo)
It ends here.
Appear once again
Yoo Hyuk
I'm dance crew president Yoo Hyuk.
We're waiting for your choice.
Legend's best dancer
Yoo Hyuk's choice is?
Lizzy ~
Jaesuk
Lizzy
I love you.
What's this?
If I knew earlier, I would
have been nicer to her.
final decisions
Male members
Can people become a couple
and get the Running Ball?
Now let us see the females decisions.
First, Lizzy.
Right now?
Yes.
Lizzy's
confession
Truthfully wants to
become a helper
I truthfully want to become a helper.
Become a helper...?
But I also was impressed with
Yoo Hyuk oppa's sexy dance.
Jaesuk's dance made Lizzy...?
But I'm a loyal girl
But I'm a loyal girl.
Helping one man
Kim Jongkook
Jongkook oppa.
First couple
Lizzy
Jongkook
Jongkook oppa.
How can it be?
Compared to sincerity
Running Ball's more important
Pyong
What's that?
Simple fireworks appears behind them
What's this?
What? How can this happen?
In the end
Celebrating the newborn couple
What's this?
It's like... Fireworks...
It's too modest.
Busan's night sky is
decorated with modest(?) firework
Don't be like this, so depressing.
What's going on.
I don't care, I'm happy.
Doesn't care about fireworks
One Man is very happy for getting Running Ball
Finally we have Lizzy-Jongkook couple.
Jongkook
Lizzy
become a couple
Jongkook
Lizzy
get one Running Ball
I guessed she'll choose Yoo Hyuk.
I'm waiting for that too.
I really thought I was the
owner of the Running Ball.
Next is ...
... Jihyo.
Jihyo's
confession
That's right!
Look here...
Just like this, look at me!
[That's right! Look here...]
Just like this, look at me.
We all will.
Read it for us.
Jihyo's #1-ranked in terms of looks
Joongki
Just like this, look at me.
We know ~
Isn't it like this.
Gary's having a bad feeling because of
the memory of inducing the
slowest heart rate on Jihyo
But I can also see
my incompetent man
But ...
I can also see my incompetent man.
A flash of hope
Seems like she's not talking about me.
What can I do about this?
Always wavering
on decisions!
An incompetent man, what do I do?
If it's incompetence...
I feel so sad.
Pure Gary
has already smiled
The ring just now can
still be worn, right?
Shy
Monday Couple jjang
Monday Couple jjang.
Gary ah.
Last couple
Jihyo
Gary
Gary was very anxious
Afraid he wouldn't be chosen
Today...
it is Monday...
Nooo ...
It's a match for the blissful
Monday Couple
Running Ball.
We know, you don't have to say it.
Song Jihyo and Gary.
Gary & Jihyo couple is formed
Running Ball.
The conclusion is too desolate, right.
These four people have
gotten the Running Ball.
Gary♥Jihyo and Jongkook♥Lizzy
receive Running Balls
So lastly is just hide and seek.
Now we'll announce the Chasing and Mission Teams' name list to everyone.
Yes ~
The Mission Team includes
Ji Sukjin, Yoo Jaesuk ...
... Song Jihyo, Song Joongki,
Lee Kwangsoo and Lizzy.
The Chasing Team includes
Jongkook, Gary and HaHa.
The three of them are chasing all of us?
Everyone, before the hide-n-seek
you will go back in and sleep.
We can sleep?
Shocked
Tomorrow morning the competition
starts the moment the siren sounds.
Does it start immediately?
If we win the race, then I can escape?
It's like that.
If the Chasing Team wins ...
... there's no need for drawing of balls
Exactly ...
... because they don't
even have one ball.
Those without a ball automatically
receive the punishment
You're all dead.
Staring
If, if we.
The mental battle has started
You go away too.
Swoosh~
Why?
Hey, Pororo.
Staring
You did it on purpose, right?
Sorry.
Hwak.
Yoo Hyuk revival
I'll do this...
Hwak!
Hwak.
From now on
a hide-n-seek
beyond imagination starts soon
Revealed together
with the shocking bare faces
It's here it's here,
what does it say?
Mission
Team
Instructions
arrived
Before the ship reaches the harbor
find 6 hidden treasure map pieces
Go to the place indicated on the map
3 of the map pieces are inside
3 pieces are hidden outside
Find the six hidden treasure map pieces.
Then arrive at the map's indicated venue.
Three map pieces are hidden
outside and three are inside.
What does three on the
inside and outside mean?
They need 6 map pieces
to find the destination
It means that 3 pieces are
indoors and 3 are outdoors.
It starts in the morning
the moment this siren sounds
If we don't hear this and continue
sleeping then we are finished.
It's really not a joke.
For me, if I can sleep for
awhile it would be great.
Weary
Current time
Mission
Team
in there individual rooms
Already asleep?
Big Nose
immediately
lays down
Wow, that's great.
I will not fall asleep.
We can sleep.
We are now Running
Man yet we can sleep.
This is great.
Goodbye ~
I'm going to sleep ~
Every Mission Team
member asleep
On the other side...
I have never once been
in a situation like this.
An advantage to wear
the clothes to sleep
Should we start?
Haroro has been in a state of excitement
since the start of the "lovers" failure
1, 2, 3.
Jongkook and the Two Kids
in a 3-man pirate gang transformation
We're just going to sleep like this?
Of course.
Uncomfortable...
Wow, it's just nice.
Go to sleep.
Really tomorrow once we
wake up we have to ...
... let them all see.
Seumdwa.
Catch them all just like that.
So I'll be looking forward to it.
Seumdwa.
The mission starts the moment they get out of bed
What will be the actual fate of the two teams...?
The next morning...
The gradually lighter
Kwang An Ri sea
The boat that is moving gradually towards
the Busan harbor, arriving in 100 minutes
Sukjin and Jaesuk seems to have fainted...
Jihyo and Lizzy are also in deep sleep and not moving
What about Joongki and Kwangsoo..?
As expected
Already awake
With almost no sleep
as they make preparations
Jaesuk hyung ...
Sukjin hyung ...
Blank...
All our team members
seem to be asleep.
Worried
Siren
This sound is the signal to start
Hide-n-seek
Suddenly
This is ...
... the siren, right?
Dizzy~
Who am I...
And where is this place...
Feels like their body isn't theirs
Noona get up quickly.
But...
who is this person?
Please ...
Why am I wearing
these clothes?
No matter what
first revelation of their bare faces(?)
Still very
Blank~
Meanwhile
Sukjin & Jaesuk
Hyung, these hyungs are really.
Hyung the alarm has rung, hurry.
Shocked
If it weren't for the juniors
Jongkook would have caught
them while they were sleeping
Hyung, why didn't you wear your clothes?
Didn't you say that you wouldn't sleep?
Oppa, what should we do about your hair.
Famous in Family Outing
Jaesuk's sticking-out hair
Meanwhile
Suddenly
At the same time
Chasing
Team
also wakes up
Wearing pirate clothes
while not fully awake...
Sorrowfully
I'm going crazy, speed it up.
Chasing Team's mission
Rip off the other team's 6 name-tags
We must complete our
mission before we arrive.
Commander
transforms to a pirate captain
Hurry up.
I know.
Impatient~
Do it quickly!
Why are you taking so long
to put on the shoes.
HaHa is oppressed from the start
Before reaching harbor
time left
Chasing Team 3-man pirate gang starts
All 6 of the Mission Team
Will they actually get caught
Ringing sounds...
Sukjin
escaped to the top of the outdoor deck
Which of the 3 pirates
is coming closer and closer?
The ringing sounds
are just to the side...
Commander
Jongkook
Haroro happens to be near
Fisherman's luck
Jihyo is in the midst of escaping
Wait, oppa is alone, right?
Hwak
As expected
Haroro is still very weak in a 1:1 with Jihyo
Rip~!
Why did you tear my name-tag.
Because you're easy to bully
Joongki and Kwangsoo
attacking Haroro from both sides
Making their getaway after a thorough lesson
Full of
desolation
after a
disaster
This is unacceptable, it hurts my pride.
I'm really ...
... too speechless.
...The "movie game" starts
Today's movie:
Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Haroro
I can't bear this anymore.
I know I want to make all
of you disappear already.
I want to destroy all of you.
Destroy all of you.
Jaesuk Joongki
are on the top floor
Who is coming.
Joongki hides first...
Ah, this... it's this.
Is this ...
one of the 6 map pieces?
Mission
Team
1 out of 6
map pieces found
Yooruce Willis
& Haroro's
direct stand-off
Why is it me that has to escape.
I'm going to transform.
Crash
Yooruce Willis
makes sure Joongki escapes safely first
As planned
Joongki safely escaped
Success
Trying to fight back
yet still the weak Haroro
Exhales...
Still a long before arriving
at the harbor
One by one...
I'll gradually capture all of you
Better be mentally prepared
Yooruce Willis
We'll start off by capturing you...
We were sleeping soundly, but
once we opened our eyes ...
Why must I be chased by the kids?
Exhausted hero
Yooruce Willis
The resolute Haroro
We meet again.
Gary...!
As expected
Yooruce Willis
Making a direct breakthrough
Using his strength to keep Haroro under control
Gary, catch him ~
Escaped from Haroro, but gets blocked by Gary
Come over quickly.
Yooruce Willis doesn't want to get invaded
But ultimately...
Got caught by Haroro's passionate pursuit
Hold on.
Getting caught by the both of
you is really humiliating for me.
It's not, it's nothing.
Tiring, isn't it?
I'm not tired at all.
Let's rest for awhile.
Locking the
legs together
Stretch
Immediately
Caught in their own trap
They aren't Two kids, but they are Dumb kids
You guys have to be a little careful.
Jongkook hyung ...
...Eh?
But
Above his head is a piece of the map?
No, oppa ...
... I can't help you.
Eh?
Swift
Where did that come from?
Mission
Team
2 out of 6
map pieces found
What's that?
Yooruce Willis
was under the map, but didn't know it
What was that? ... Ahhh.
Struggles
It's time we get separated
2nd map piece was found
thanks to
Yooruce Willis
Today,
trying to make himself into a devoted hero
Commander
Jongkook
Startled
In front of
Commander
what hero is there to be
Jongkook again.
Jaesuk
Remaining time
Until arriving at harbor
Kwangsoo is searching
the interior
Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo reached the boat's KTV
Map piece
Is this originally pasted here?
3 out of 6
map pieces found
I've found the karaoke room piece.
Joongki
On the deck
Joongki is searching
It seems like there is a piece here.
Another map piece here
Noona, Jihyo noona.
4 out of 6
map pieces found
What's written?
Where will the final destination be?
Oh my ... Oh god.
I'm showering right now,
how could you come in?
Lizzy:
Sorry to intrude, but ...
... this is the men's bath.
I'm showering.
What are you doing
in the men's bath?
I already said I was showering.
It's already closed, please leave.
Without a doubt
Like a trapped rat~!
I'm sorry.
You can't ~
Struggle
Lizzy
Time left
Eh?
Can't be...
Who's sleeping(?) in the open...
Another scene from ...
the movie "Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Haroro"
Haroro's personality transformation
In older days, performers dawdling by dancing
Big Nose didn't get enough sleep
Entering a dead end where he
could not even move properly
Sukjin
Sukjin hyung, sorry.
Jaesuk hyung, sorry.
Lizzy, I'm really sorry.
I, myself
don't know why I'm doing this
Craziness
Uncomparable acting 1:
It's Kim Jongkook.
Uncomparable acting 2:
Dual personality
What's with me?
Time left
I'm coming.
In the end
confront the enemy
Gary & Jihyo
Keep the memory fresh
from last night
Monday Couple
is the best
It was like a dream
when their heart beats became one
But ...
that sweet memory is a short one
Now meeting up
they are enemies...
Jihyo ...
Yesterday when you and Joongki
did the Titanic pose together ...
... I was really hurt.
How could you do such
a thing with Joongki?
It was still Monday.
It was Joongki.
If you do the same Titanic pose
with me, I will let you go.
Oppa, what kind of timing is his.
Why suddenly do the Titanic pose?
Do the Titanic pose once
with me and I'll let you go.
Gary is filled with jealousy
Quickly, before Jongkook comes.
...Eh?
Really doing it?
Gary & Jihyo
Titanic
This place is also the first
time we have been here.
Awkward
I'll help you to fly to the sky.
Even though
same place where Joongki did it the feeling is different
Close you eyes and spread your wings.
Let's forever be
the Monday Couple
Jihyo ... !
Who am I?
You're Jamsil's Kang Gary.
Hey ~
What are you doing?
Suddenly
Embarrassed
Jihyo, escape quickly, hurry.
Speechless
Kang Gary ...
... what are you doing?
I already caught Jihyo.
There isn't one reliable brother
Jihyo, really thank you.
I will not forget this.
I'm the Gary who lives in Jamsil.
Goodbye, be careful.
I'll feel more scared if you say that.
Jongkook is at the top,
so you go that way.
The next time we meet ...
it wouldn't be the sight of your back anymore
Dying to see you...
Jihyo ...
Other side of the
men's bathroom
Joongki, Kwangsoo
Joongki Kwangsoo
Lizzy previously hid here
Found it.
5 out of 6
map pieces obtained
Just need to the find last map piece
Sparta!
Commander
Jongkook
Joongki
Let's put them together,
who has the pieces?
Joongki held the 5 map pieces
There is one more left to collect.
Earlier ...
The last destination looks like the "captain's cabin"
What's to do there?
Just need the last piece
Hyung, found it ~
You found it?
All pieces found
The last piece obtained
Jihyo
once she gets the 5 map pieces
Meet up with Kwangsoo
to get the last piece and it's mission complete
Kwangsoo, where are you?
Jongkook should be able
to catch him all by himself.
Exactly.
Kwangsoo is holding the last piece
and heading to the prison
There seems to be some
ringing sounds nearby.
Looks like it's the meeting point with Jihyo
It's all seen
I saw it ~
Jongkook is here already.
Heading straight for Kwangsoo
He has caught Kwangsoo.
Already knew where he was hiding
Unlucky
Unexpected
Commander
appeared...
Kwangsoo
Listen up ...
... Jihyo should be coming
here, we have to catch her.
Grabs
Tightly
Aish, you really ...
Remaining time
The thought of only needed the last piece...
Commander
guarding the prison
it will be twice as hard
Song Jihyo ...
... this is HaHa speaking.
Since you'll get caught eventually,
why don't you just surrender?
We won't be hard on you since you're a girl.
How is she...
going to cross
this obstacle
I have a feeling that everyone
here is waiting for Jihyo.
Then she'll be standing on top and you
will throw the map piece up like this.
That is not it.
But you all keep looking up.
Has Joongki come up with a combat plan?
That's when only two of us left.
Eh? Where did the cloth come from?
Throws around~
Commander
Trapped..?
Tightly secured
Still thinking of intercepting the map?
Quickly, grab his leg.
Mission
Team
All out attack
Jihyo, you can come back now.
It's a bit funny right now,
five of us are holding him.
Jihyo, where are you?
He is now like a prisoner,
hurry up and come over.
Perfect timing
Jihyo arrived
Hurry up.
Grabs his hair
Forceful!!
Swoosh
Jihyo didn't go in without a plan
Gloomy
Tamper
In this
moment
Commander
Raging strength
All five guards...
Destroyed
He's like the autumn gale
sweeping away the fallen leaves
A bull ~
Without any
restrictions
Running after Jihyo
With the 6 map pieces
heading to "Captain’s cabin"
Will it be Jihyo...
Or the Chasing Team?
Who will
be the victor of this mission's outcome?
Anxious...
Jihyo comes back after awhile
Jihyo, were you successful?
Is that an expression of victory?
Ah...
Jihyo's name-tag got got taken away
It got ripped off.
What exactly happened?
Jihyo reached the captain's cabin first
But chasing right behind is
Commander
Captain, here they are.
Before the captain could verify the map
Jihyo
Chasing
Team
Just like that
Mission
Success
Are you guys the newly formed group?
Newly formed
Pirate Boys
Slowly ending
A long excursion day
Now the cruise is reaching the location.
Cruise arriving
towards the pier
Where will we be going now?
Jaesuk*Sukjin*Joongki*Kwangsoo
Got 0 Running Balls
Have to take
the punishment
This is the international passenger traffic pier.
Greeting the people at the station will do.
There will be foreigners.
Worried
Jongkook and Lizzy came out
looking like close brother and sister
While the 4 people wearing hot
pants are cold and shivering
The sea breeze of the shore
greats their thighs~
Cold ~
Arriving at the tourist stopover station
There'll be foreigners here.
Worried
Hello.
How will the foreigners react about hot pants?
Curious
Hello ~
Have a wonderful vacation.
A foreigner appears
Using short broken English
to communicate Success
Such a group of
interesting guys
Packed and crowded
Thanks for everyone's hard work.
Giving tourists a happy experience
Original hardsubs by iSUB
Transcribed by HapB
Color and alignment by SamFive