Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by iSUBS
Today's
landmark
Korea's
Center of postal service
Seoul Central Post Office
Return of variety man Kim Jaedong
Strong hide-n-seeker Yonghwa
Revealing
Stars' one night post office mission
Also
Special
Tricking Gary
Restlessly opening all the
secrets in the mailboxes Charge
It starts now
Where is this?
This is the Seoul Central Post Office.
Today's landmark
Seoul Central Post Office
Once we start ...
... these people will always stick together.
As expected
Jongkook and two kids
Like that ... ah, really.
Are you sure you've changed your clothes?
Why are you only doing this to me?
Suddenly
Song Jihyo, you still like
to pay attention to him.
Why can't I look?
Rage
Every time we talk about Gary,
you step out to look at him.
Since last week For or Gay and Jihyo
non-stop scandal making
Which part of him attracts you?
Whatever.
People usually pay attention
to the person they like.
From now on, we will step
back and look at each other.
Speechless
Like we introduced earlier, this
is the Seoul Central Post Office.
Advanced technologies and unique exterior
Post Tower
This is Korea's biggest and oldest,
even though it was reconstructed.
Are all the malls delivered through here?
Yes, that's right.
It's Chuseok right now.
That's why they are very busy ...
... receiving over 200,000 mails everyday.
The Post Office
deals with citizen's postal needs
Today Running Man
will chase through the night here
Now we should introduce our
Running Man guests for today.
Today's guests are?
Please welcome.
Which female guest will it be?
Returning hide-n-seeker
Jung Yonghwa
And ...
Jung Yonghwa and the manager.
Rock idol
Jung Yonghwa
Eloquent king
Kim Jaedong
Welcome
Algo, Yonghwa ...
On a weekend variety after a long time
Kim Jaedong
Jaedong ...
It's been a while since we've seen
him on a weekend variety show.
This is the first time after X-Man.
Jaedong loves wearing
mountain climbing clothes.
Did you wear it just for the show today?
Climbing clothes for show?
Even the color is matching.
His own cordi
Wearing matching colors(?)
I put a lot of effort into this.
That's right ~
This one right here is very old fashioned.
The best idol
Old fashioned clothing?
The collars are pulled like this.
Becoming longer
With these clothing I won't
even step out of the house.
Why did you two just naturally
"stand" beside Kwangsoo?
Being pushed to the
end by the guests...
Kwangsoo won't say it, but
he's feeling very hurt inside.
Even today
Kwangsoo's humiliated
Because it's the first
recording with him.
Also first time meeting Gary.
Ah, that's right.
Almost 3 years with Jongkook.
Yeah, almost 3 years.
But seriously, it's been a while since
you've come on a weekend variety.
Doubt
Why  ...
two of them hiding their smiles?
Also other Running Man members ...
Except the peaceful Gary
What
is going to happen...
In fact ...
Not 3 years ago ...
Rewind 3 hours before recording
All the members
have gathered ...
Why did they tell us to come earlier?
Sukjin hyung wrote a letter to the
producer and suggested an idea.
Arriving
earlier is Sukjin's idea?
Yes ~
It's okay.
3 hours ago
members gathered
He only thinks about
Running Man everyday.
Of course.
Peek
Oh, and there's Jaedong.
What?
The guests also arrived earlier
Even Yonghwa
We've talked about it before already.
3 hours ago
Everyone except Gary arrived
Jaedong, you can do it.
Topic changed
First time filming together after X-Man
After X-Man, this is his first weekend variety.
Back then he was the only one
who stayed until the very end.
Jongkook was the last one to quit back then
When Jaedong was the
team leader back then ...
... he said that you were scared
to make eye contacts with him.
Different era
Look at him now, he even became a leader.
Still
Eloquent king Jaedong
Yeah, Kim Jaedong.
Happy HaHa
Back in the day, we wanted
Kim Jongkook to do a dance.
It took a bunch of us
3 hours to convince him
But these days, when you go to the washroom ...
... you'll see him practicing by himself.
Framed
Looking at the mirror like this.
HaHa totally agrees
The stuff that came out of Lee Kwangsoo's
mouth ﻿about the washroom, they're all lies.
Kwangsoo, isn't there
anything about Jihyo?
Continues framing
This is not the end
What about Jihyo?
She's also known as Song Jiyok.
* Yok = Cures / Evil
Jihyo AKA
Song Jiyok
Dumbfounded
You sure saw a lot in the washroom.
Kwangsoo's framing
Kwangsoo, after the ﻿club incident
is there anything else about Jihyo?
It's not only the club incident.
What is it?
Uneasy
I have a friend who lives
around the Il San area.
When he was younger,
Jihyo stole his money.
Framed
Jihyo stole money from someone
She'll hit him once for every 10 won.
Jihyo is no joke.
Non-stop
Kwangsoo framing
Looks like Sukjin's idea was taken in.
Anyway
3 hours earlier gathering
Sukjin's real idea is?
A message came from
last week's Running Man
"﻿When I watched Running Man at home, I
saw that Gary got tricked by Jaesuk again."
"So if we trick him together,
maybe he won't even notice?"
The screen shows Sukjin's idea
"Let's trick Gary once."
"The idea isn't bad?"
Jaesuk often plays tricks on Gary.
But he gets tricked every time.
Even when edited, there are still some.
Always falls for it
Childish Gary
He gets tricked 100% every single time.
This time...
This time we all trick him together.
All members
trick Gary together
When we're playing games ...
... we should be at the post office, right?
So during the "stamp" game ...
1:8
Luring Gary
1. Make a fake Running
Man stamp-game
When Gary isn't paying attention ...
... we stamp his exposed skin.
2. When Gary doesn't pay attention
stamp on his face or body
What do we get if we succeed?
If everyone succeeds In tricking Gary
everyone will receive the Running Ball.
But if Gary figures it out,
only he will get the Ball.
If Gary figures it out only
he gets the Running Ball.
So it's going to be Gary against us.
Then
1:8 to lure Gary into the trap
That means we should team up.
Have to work together for the plan
That's right.
But Gary is very sensible.
I don't think so.
But he is new in variety ...
... he would probably accept
it even if we stamp on him.
For the show to be funny
Gary always gives his best
Even if we make it obvious,
we ought to succeed.
If it's stamped on the body
it easily get exposed
We should change it to smearing ink.
Switching to smearing ink
1:8
Luring Gary
Secretly smear ink on
Gary's neck or face
Just naturally wipe ink on him should do it.
When is Gary arriving?
Gary should be arriving now
We should use hints and
not make it too obvious.
Make Gary constantly doing the stamps.
We should get disqualified first,
so he can become number one.
We should get disqualified first
then Gary becomes No. 1 ...
That's right.
We pretend to cheer and find
a chance to smear the ink.
I have a suggestion.
We'll start from the face and then ...
That won't do.
Timid Kwangsoo gets cut off again
That's what happens when
you sit beside Jongkook.
Yonghwa, what do you think?
I like that idea too.
2nd appearance
Full of wit
Aigoo, my stomach.
Yonghwa solo
You don't know?
Know what?
That's Yonghwa's talent.
He's the Mimic Machine.
Voice machine(?)
Yonghwa?
Imitate Jaedong.
Imitating Jaedong?
Oh oh, Jaesuk hyung.
Confirmed voice imitation
Good job ~
Today's voice imitater(?) participation
Please anticipate
I didn't know how to give
a reaction at that time.
Unexpected
An ex-team leader with little reaction
I'm too slow.
When you can't figure out what to say ...
National MC
Can't figure out how to
give reactions?
... ﻿just lean back like this.
Uh... just
Lean back
So then others can't spot you.
Jihyo, what is your plan?
We should do it one by one.
How?
Why?
Please give us a reason.
If we all do it at once, it's very ...
... dangerous.
Laughs~
Learns
immediately
Can't imagine hiding during a talent show
Oh, where did Jihyo go?
She just disappeared.
She went to washroom to practice cursing.
Just like that...
Everything goes according to plan along with laughs and chatter
Gary
arrives
And...
The show with the
clueless Gary starts now
Bright
Gary
Fighting ~
Let's all go inside.
Let's go.
Using
each other's ideas
First time ever
1:8 battle starts now
Please come in ~
Different Jaesuk welcomes
Come on.
Why is he
like this?
Wants a successful prank Excited members
Although the 1:8 battle didn't start yet
everyone is in a nervous state
Today is not going to be a team battle.
It will be a solo battle.
A solo battle?
Gary has never heard of this, but ...
Solo battle.
... the other's have known it for 3 hours
Once you obtain a Running Ball ...
... put the balls into the machine
with your names written on it.
If the ball that comes out has your name
on it, you won't receive the punishment.
What is our first game?
Ah, the 'Stamp Quickly' game
First fake game
Quickly stamp the mails
Last time, there was even
examinations for the workers.
Fake
rule 1
Within 1 min stamp as
many letters as possible
This is not easy.
I've got confidence in this, when
I opened a roast pork store ...
... ﻿I always stamp the plastics.
Trap set
The rule is to disqualify the member
with the least stamps after 1 minute.
Fake
rule 2
After 1 min the member with
the least stamps gets disqualified
The winner can receive a Running Ball.
Fake
rule 3
The last winner gets a Running Ball
Doesn't know anything
If Gary doesn't find out
the other 8 will get a ball each
If Gary realizes it
only Gary gets a Running ball
1:8 battle
Jihyo ...
She doesn't want to talk to me.
Immature
For the sake of HaHa's plan
she naturally sits near Gary
Shy Gary sits next to Jihyo?
Wait ...
Sit down.
Not you, don't sit here.
Without judgments
Jaedong tries to sit
Why are you treating Jaedong like that?
The other 8 members
slowly drifting away
Don't sit over here.
Just sit here will do.
Start
The 1:8 battle begins
Gary shows his speed
It is not easy to do.
It isn't as easy as they thought
You have to stamp properly.
Serious
Time is almost up.
Stamp properly in place.
Either way still focused
Totally unaffected
You fouled already.
Look at Gary.
Out~standing
I'm enjoying
this game...
Counts the stamped letters with scrutiny
1, 2, 3, 4, 5 ...
Whisper
Have to stamp it deeper.
This is stamped nicely
Kwangsoo attempt to do the mission
... ﻿7, 8, 9 ... 17, 18, 19
Trying to stand behind Gary
Scared me...
Immersed in counting his letters
... Rescue Kwangsoo ...
Uneasy
Worried
If one fails
everyone risks failure
... 20.
Placing his hand
Timid
Can't wait any longer
Jihyo gets ready
This doesn't count, it
doesn't show the date.
Gary is totally focused on winning
The date has to be readable.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 ...
Now's the chance
Jihyo tries to poke his cheek?
Nervous
... this doesn't count, 7.
Only needs Gary to turn around
Finally smeared it on Gary's face
Could it be that ...
... it's discovered?
Gary's sure his face was smeared
How should
Jihyo explain this?
What do you mean by this?
... you mean by this?
Totally misunderstood~ ♥
Lucky~
Why do you always treat me like this?
Shy
Jihyo tried to make a mischievous but
frail smiling face~
Focus, it's my turn counting
Battle 1:8
Jihyo is first to do it
Completed
Feeling happy ~
But there's still 7 people
who needs to succeed to win 1:8 battle
... 9, 10, 11, 12.
Timid Kwangsoo's still standing there
Jongkook also prepares
It's hot in here.
The nervous Jaesuk is
sweating ~
Gary stamped so much.
Kwangsoo, finally...
Turns~
Timid Kwangsoo
1st attempt
Failed
HaHa, how many
have stamped?
Eight? You have
been eliminated
Since 8 is the lowest, there
is no need to count the rest.
Sobs...
Kwangsoo's 2nd attempt
Interrupted by Jaesuk
Again
failed
Jihyo, 1, 2, 3, 4 ...
It's more than eight.
Having more than eight is enough.
and win for the mission to succeed
Gary has to be in the game
It's really weird now.
Trying to be pitiful
Just counting roughly
Why don't you finish counting it all?
Look at him just standing
there and counting randomly.
Pretends to be dissatisfied with the counting
Affectionate
Still pretending.
Passionate
HaHa eliminated.
HaHa eliminated
I also want to.
Previously letting Jihyo off
Still doesn't know the task at hand
What are the two of you doing?
It's Jongkook's turn
Gary, look at Jihyo.
Perfectly executed ~
Now the second round.
The second round.
Only looking at Jihyo.
Used the right moment
Jongkook task completed
Are this two having a love line?
It's not exactly a love line.
Its my love line.
This time we will follow
the rules much stricter.
This round ...
... two people will be eliminated.
First to be greedy
Gary has full desire to win
You can't do it like this.
Okay, ready ...
Ready ... start.
Properly stamp the seals in position.
Stamp it properly.
Jongkook's pacing slowly
Still not knowing anything
Gary continues with speed
Completely focused
Isn't it already 1 min?
Stop.
Enough ~
Gary uses all his might until the end
Gary is doing great.
He stamped so many.
Everyone is praising Gary
Come and have a look.
Pleased
Counting their own letters
Why is your hand so black and dirty?
Ink smeared all over Jaedong's hands
As if he tried to complete the mission several times
How did it become like this?
Checks
Stupidly
Getting ink on his own hand
How did you?
I was too excited, that's why.
Give us some napkins.
Napkins?
Jaedong hyung ...
Even the kid is trying
something unthinkable
Yonghwa uses a different method
A napkin with ink on it
Acting natural to clean up
Slowly rubbing it
and it's finally on...!
What are ... ah, Yonghwa.
Did he find out?
Applied too much?
Nervous
Don't rub away the mark
that Jihyo gave me.
Emerged
Gary integrating himself
Sorry Yonghwa, but ...
... I wish to keep it until tomorrow.
Great method
Yonghwa is 3rd to complete the task
Getting closer with Jihyo and
also doing well on the game
Gary's mood becomes
much happier
HaHa found his courage and tries
4th mark
HaHa's mission completed
Hurry, lets continue the game.
Totally unaware
Everyone crowding after HaHa succeeded
Hyung help me massage my neck a bit.
Ah, so you want to relax?
Who are you trying to talk to now?
Sukjin's attempt Went for the neck
Clear new ink marks
5th mark
Big NoseTask completed
You can also stamp
two together at once?
Happy
How about we work together?
Can't believe
Gary's egoistic ingratiation
Let's just work together.
Just seal it together.
It's fun, aren't you going to continue?
* Hinting at those who haven't finished their mission
Firm
It's fun, aren't you going to continue?
Remaining people Jaesuk*Jaedong*Kwangsoo
Okay, let's start the next round.
I didn't know this is such a fun game.
Ah, this is nerve wrecking.
Alright everyone, lets all
go stand in the middle.
Those who haven't completed the task is also nervous
This is Jaedong's seat.
Jaedong, what's wrong. Hurry up.
Game is over when they complete their mission
Please pass over some letters.
Gary only thinks about getting 1st place
Strategy discussion
Glances
I have to do
it this time
Oppa, there is something here.
Jaesuk takes a chance when Gary's relaxing
With the help from Jihyo
Jaesuk's task completed
The 1:8 competition
Remaining people
Jaedong-Kwangsoo
How does it feel getting
all the attention today?
Your slightly shaking here.
Confident
This time around
A bonus smear from Jaesuk
Big crisis
How will it end
Will Gary figure it out?
Ready ... start.
Quickly
Regains focus
Totally lucky
Engrossed
Doing great, Gary's really doing good.
I almost made
a big mistake
This cant end like this.
Only Jaedong and Kwangsoo is left
Gary only cares about the letters
There's 14 here.
Then Gary has 18.
People are walking around during the counting
... ﻿12, 13, 14, 15.
But Gary's still focused
Once the 2 of them succeed all 8 of them gets a Running Ball
Gary stamped one within 2 seconds.
Victory is in front of them
Wow, it's really fast.
But Gary only thinks about his own victory
Kwangsoo, what are you doing there?
HaHa goes to help Kwangsoo
Supporting Gary to stamp even faster.
Kwangsoo tries right away
Shiver~
Nearly brushing it
Such a pity
Jaedong feels the same
Ah...I've got to
do this quickly
Also Jaedong is nervous
Two haven't completed their mission yet
Kwangsoo*Jaedong
Battle between the finalists
Jihyo vs Gary
Battle 1:8 final
Plus 2 people try to complete their mission
An applause for the final round.
Pretends to give massage The final attempt
Tremble~
Another attempt
Finally smudges it
Kwangsoo 7th place
Success
You can say a few words to
each other before the final round.
Now only Jaedong remains
I'll do my best.
I'll do a little less than my best.
Gary giving boost to Jihyo
for the Running Ball?
My chance
Jihyo, do you want the Running Ball?
Yes.
Do you really want it?
Just look straight ahead.
I just want you.
Ink smearing
Success
As expected of Jaedong
All 8 completed the mission
Do you want the Running Ball?
Yes.
I only want you.
Oblivious Gary is in high spirit
Fool.
Meaningless final round
They're good.
They're nervous.
I think I left one out?
Awkwardly
Where?
Ah, it's here
Dawdling on purpose
to let Jihyo win?
Jihyo wins.
Hurriedly
Jihyo
wins
You're doing it on purpose.
There were two stuck together.
Blaming the envelopes
The first Running Ball goes to ...
8 of them
thinks
Gary...
sorry...
Jihyo...
you're thankful, right?
What Gary is
thinking
Running Ball goes to ...
... the other 8 people except Gary.
Why?
Pranking Gary
Big success
Why?
Still at loss
Take one ball each.
Everyone gets rewarded with a ball
What's going on?
Why?
Reality is hard to believe
It was Ji Sukjin's idea.
For the first time a perfect chance
to trick Gary
Smear ink without
him noticing
What have you done to my face?
Even as the fake game went on
Gary couldn't sense it
Why didn't I notice?
The cruel reality
Only now he realized
Sorry.
I said "I only want you" with this face?
Is that why you did it?
To confuse me?
Did you do it to confuse this heart?
Jihyo, explain it to him.
I'm sorry.
What time did you get here?
At nine.
We got here at 7.
I was wondering ...
Normally I come together with Donghoon.
* Donghoon is HaHa's real name
That's right.
But when I called him earlier ...
Normall he would say "Hyung
come over to my place".
So I called and ask what time I
should come, but he just said ...
"I'll Se you there hyung".
I was a little disappointed.
You should've done better than that.
I was scared he'd find out,
he is really quick-sensed.
Scarred all over
Gary you did a good job.
Thanks to Gary we all got a Running Ball.
Battle 1:8
Remaining members win
Gary special episode.
You're the star here.
Let's see about it next week.
Vouching for revenge
But the thing he's most upset
about is Jihyo's heart.
Current time
We're now at the mail sorting room.
This is where they sort
all the Korean mails.
All the Thanksgiving (Chuseok)
mails and packages are sorted here
The empty room is borrowed for a mission
So tonight we are going to
do a simple game in here.
A simple game called Catch The Thief.
Second mission
Catch the thief
Catch the thief.
All the 9 members
are given postcards
One is the thief-postcard
Each member take a postcard
from the person on his/her right
The person who ends up with the thief-
postcard won't be given a Running Ball
Here it is.
Whoever has this postcard is the thief.
So everyone except the thief
will get a Running Ball?
That's right.
I'll hand it out one by one.
At random.
This is worrying.
Uneasy...
Even if you are holding the thief
you pretend like you don't have it.
Yes, you can't let anyone know.
All set?
Checking the postcards
I'm going crazy.
For now Jaesuk isn't the thief
Neither Kwangsoo is the thief
Yonghwa*Jihyo also avoided the thief-card
Are you all done?
Yes ~
Big Nose hyung's card is?
First, we will start with
the postcard selection
Choose a postcard from
the person next to you.
Controlling face expression
Jihyo can take the postcard from Kwangsoo.
First postcard selection
Jihyo takes Kwangsoo's card
Now Jihyo has it.
Yes.
Yonghwa chooses from Jihyo's 2 cards
That's good.
Yonghwa ...
Sukjin has a thief-card and a Running-Man-card
One of the cards is
the thief
It's shown in the reflection?
Like a thief caught in his act
A little suspicious
He's hiding something.
Jaesuk still doesn't know
that Sukjin has the thief-card
Here I go.
Running Man card?
No!
Thief-card moved to Jaesuk
Oh My God !
His startled face is so obvious
Sukjin's now in high spirits
What happened to them?
Taking a dangerous angle that people can see the cards
Can you move back a bit so people can't see.
Don't you know the rule?
Did you just study at school?
Never played this before
When was he ever studying that hard?
Give me this one.
Are you sure?
Yes.
The one Jaedong chose
is the thief-card
Are you sure?
Yes ~
Jaedong continues to tease Jaesuk
Apart from hosting he doesn't
know how to do anything?
Excitedly kept chattering
I mean someone who always on shows ...
Hurry up and look at it.
Wounded
He is back after a long break
and just throwing in small talks.
Okay, sorry.
Just look at it first because we will
be watching your face expressions.
Ah, really?
You'll be watching my face?
Well ...
Only an empty laughter
Check
The current thief is Jaedong
What is it?
Obscure
We still don't know
what your fate will be.
If you don't choose carefully
your muscles might burst.
Give me the front one please.
What did you say?
The front one.
The front one?
Are you sure?
Thief-card is
at the back
You won't regret it?
The one in front?
Jongkook steadily choosing the front card
Jaedong is still the thief
Only Jaedong
knows where the thief is
The color is different, isn't?
Checking
Jongkook's both cards are Running Man
And now it's Gary's turn to pick
Hurry up.
Why are you angry at me.
The tension is killing me.
Because I am making Gary
nervous your heart is on fire.
I'm sorry, Jihyo.
Ridiculous
Postcard pick completed
Somebody here has the thief.
One of them is ...
... the thief
The winner of this game can give their card
to someone else and get the Running Ball.
The winner of an intermediary game can
give their card to anyone else and leave
The winner of this game can give
away their card and leave the game.
Before we go to the second round,
we'll distribute the cards this way.
What game will we play?
Oh, pulling out stacked packaging box.
Package box pullouts
Like that Jingo game, that ...
Unsure
Jenga ~
Everybody jumps in on Jongkook's mistake
He's just dirty.
* Play words on jingo
Embarrassed
He used to play by himself.
Since he hurt his back
he's becoming cuter.
Cutie
pie
Package box pullout
game warmup exercise(?)
Hilarious
How do you feel tonight?
Slow to adapt
Apart from this I'm okay.
Yonghwa is fully into it
Let us decide the order
with rock-paper-scissors.
Show your hands or you're out.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock*Scissor
Bottom and top rounds
Rock, paper, scissors ~
Gary last place ~
Stand in order.
What about me?
Hyung, you should stand here.
No ...
I won.
I was the one who won.
Arguing over who won
I showed rock and you scissors.
I showed paper.
Oh?
I won.
More
intense fighting
Make peace ~
There's no way to stop this fight
It's clear that I won, ﻿can't you see it?
This is seriously not important.
He said he won.
I said I won because
I won, I showed rock.
You never showed rock, did you?
You never think.
Hyung ~
Let's take out the camera and watch.
If we rewind the game
Rock, paper, scissors ~
Lost
Scissors
Won
Rock
Jongkook is the winner
Oh, really ...
Stupid ~
Although he lost
Sukjin can still be cocky like this
Hyung despised me, I said the truth.
I'll watch it when it airs and
if I won I'll never let you go.
I said it seriously.
Does it hurt?
Yah, I ...
Let's discuss it again later.
Jihyo, at moments like this you should
just say, "Oppas, don't be like this".
At this time
they want Jihyo to help stop the fight
You shut up ~
Really underestimated Jihyo
They'll take out a box based on their
order. Those left when it falls will win
What?
Doing it carefully.
Jaesuk's the first
challenger
Amazed
Have you never played this game?
I don't know about this.
Boxes higher up are
shaking ~
Hold it and then pull it out.
Yeah ~
It's okay it won't fall.
One more time carefully
Success
It won't fall.
Happy
Still amazed
So there's a game like this?
We'll take if easy on Jaedong this time.
We should have bought him
the original size
He keeps asking if there's a game like this.
Amazed
Don't tell me that Jaedong was thinking
of taking ﻿this and run to the post office?
So that's not how we play it?
There's a smaller version,
it is made out of wood.
Ah, made from wood.
If I didn't tell him, he would've taken
it and ran straight to the post office.
The 37 years old uncle almost
went to the post office
There's room.
Look at that.
With small scrap
success
Kwangsoo slowly
Success
Next is Jaedong.
Finally Jaedong's turn
First time playing this game
It seems this is his first time.
Hard ~
Come to my house on the weekend.
Let's play Jenga together.
Hyung, punch it.
Should I knock it?
Just use little strength.
Tok
Will it work?
Going to the front to pull it out
Carefully take it out.
You can't let it fall, right?
Right, it can't fall.
Very concentrated when playing this game.
Along with the viewers.
Looks like removing a bomb
He keeps talking.
Aigoo, look here.
More nervous
Startled me.
Oh, Jaedong is very upset.
Jaedong ...
Just a little more, now.
Pull a little more﻿
Did it.
Success
Thrilled
Did it, good job.
Now it's Gary's turn
Some boxes are easy to
pull, but some are hard.
Concentrate
Exactly.
That's it.
It won't be a success.
He has to choose the right one.
To the front, now pull it from the front.
I know, I'll find a way.
Blocking it
Why doesn't
it move?
Pull it from the front now.
Slowly ~
What are you doing?
I didn't do anything, I tried to help you.
It doesn't
feel right
Slowly pull it, slowly.
I'll find the way.
Strong jokes for Gary
This is really an interesting game.
It's my turn.
And finally Gary
Success
No, I didn't know it'll change like this.
One more chance to  Jaesuk
Very interesting.
Happy
Very good.
Crisis
Tickles
Can he do this?
Can he do this now?
What is it?
He tickled me.
Secretly they find a way to win
I absolutely didn't.
I can't bear being tickled.
Shaking
What should I do next?
HaHa is next to challenge
He disturbed
me before ...
Pushing the box with his foot
It seems to fail ~
Jaesuk doesn't know it's a bottom box
Jaesuk's happy even
when he's wrong
Use more strength.
Jaesuk hyung ...
... not there but in here.
Here.
Laughing at his foolishness(?)
It's at the bottom, but he
blocked the one above.
Shy
Ah, it's really embarrassing.
Jaesuk wanted revenge but got
shame ~
After knowing this game ...
... now I feel it's very interesting.
That's why I said this weekend
you must come to my house.
HaHa
Success
One box left in
the crisis situation
Now all of you gather it
quickly and bring it home.
Jaedong, it must be smaller.
Buy the game in smaller size
If our relatives can come it'll be better.
This is family size.
Good idea ~
If it's smaller would they want to come?
Take it ~
Yonghwa in a short time
success
This time I'll be more offensive.
That's right, because ...
He can make next challenger lose
... if you succeed it'll be harder
for the next challenger.
I understand.
Oh, it's a good choice.
Making the structure unbalanced
It won't be easy for next player
Can I pull it?
Yes.
It's not easy.
If he succeeds, this game
will get more interesting.
Kwangsoo smooth
success
Isn't easy for the next player
Who's next?
Jaedong ~
Jaedong, except for this
there's no other choice.
Jaedong can only take this out.
There's one in the middle.
Can only take this out
You should pull it out.
That's right ~
Serious
Doesn’t care what people say
Jaedong never played it before.
Frozen pose
When he comes to your
house give him this game.
Like a craftsman sculpting
Jaedong, wipe your sweat.
Sweat flowing...
Jaedong I'll buy it for you.
Ah, he really likes this game.
He must take this out
to throw away the thief-card
When a man focus he'll look sexy.
Ehm...
He is doing well.
Shaking
Can he succeed?
No way.
A little support
Pull it out ~
Has to take it out completely to succeed
Jaedong, take it out.
Slowly.
Aren't they falling now?
Jaedong, try taking it out.
Jaedong a miracle
success
If it's like this ...
This is a really interesting game.
Jihyo who's next is hopeless
This is a very interesting game.
If Jihyo fails then Jaedong
wins
Jihyo, you're doomed.
I really enjoy playing this game.
And he can throw away the thief-card
There's one way.
Punch it from here.
The only way to help
helpless Jihyo
That's right.
Punch it from here.
Send the middle box
flying away
If you hit the box hard, the top
will settle at the bottom part.
Right, there is still opportunity.
Jihyo, try it.
It would be good to have one
chance to use Kim Jongkook.
In this crisis she wants to use Jongkook
Then, what am I to you?
Gary oppa is hurt
Oppa also learned boxing.
Give it a try.
Forget it.
Then I want to use Gary oppa.
If it's like that, I will do it.
Gloriously happy
But this is too hard.
If he is successful, it will be
very cool and popular scene.
What does he get for
becoming the black knight?
Grant his wish.
She should grant his wish.
Is that how
it works?
1, 2 ...
Jihyo's black knight
Gary
Can he
succeed?
Punch
The result?
Jihyo's black knight Gary
fails
Jihyo doesn't have to grant Gary's wish
Pity
Jihyo failed so the player
before her Jaedong
wins
Current thief
= Jaedong
Jaedong can give his
card to another player
Do you want to know something?
One word and then over.
This is the thief-card.
Really?
Everyone's confused
Wait, Mr Jaedong ...
Yes?
Congrats, you are number 1.
No one knows if it's really the thief-card
Thank you.
Jaedong hyung is the most handsome.
To avoid getting the card Non stop praises
Jaedong, I really have a dream
to grow up just like you.
Ah, really?
I ﻿want to give you one
set of wood block game.
That games ...
... let's play it together.
Are you coming alone?
Who else do you want to come?
Your friends?
Yeah, I got it.
Everything is okay
Play together.
How about with the friends of my wife?
What?
My wife's friends.
I have seen them all.
More words of talk.
Is Gary not going to say a word?
Have nothing to say?
I thought Wonbin was sitting there.
Both eyes closed
Did you like that?
Not like that!
Didn't you like that?
Are you living for tomorrow?
I'm just living for today.
Really cool.
These words ...
Dialogue from the movie 'Mister'
All of you live for tomorrow.
I'm living just for today.
Are you living for tomorrow.
Those words comes out
from this guy's mouth
I'm just living for today.
Oh, what?
Really cool.
Trying~
to restrain
Really cool ...
Wonbin ~
I thought it's Song Daewoo.
Really similar.
Where did you buy this nail polish?
Are you kidding me?
Nail polish?
Where did you buy this nail polish?
You're only thinking about nail polish?
I only think about today.
What are you?
Thinking about you because of nail polish?
Nail polish?
You only think about nail polish?
I'm ﻿only thinking about right now.
I've decided
So 1st place is Jaedong's cards
1, 2, 3.
Who will get it?
Jaesuk
chosen
Although the others don't know
the thief-card is now with Jaesuk
But we still don't know.
Take a look at the card.
Using all his energy
to hide his feelings
Picking cards 2nd round
We have to control our emotions.
How do you feel?
Why ask the
obvious?
Jaesuk's situation has improved, hasn't it?
Jaesuk has three cards
Uneasy...
Which card will Jongkook pick?
Jongkook, choose wisely.
You know?
Sighs...
How do you feel?
We're still in the middle of the game.
Ah, really?
Look at him, he's so detestable.
Jaedong became the 'manager' of the
game after obtaining a Running Ball
What's the next game?
Joining the words.
Joining the words
I really like this game, but ...
Someone once said I have
a full storage of vocabulary.
Specialty
The pro of word joining Jaesuk
Joining words, everyone
knows that I'm the king.
All the viewers know this.
The winner of this game
will give his card to another player and exit the game
It's survival time, eliminating people.
Survival mode
Eliminating one by one
Last one standing is the winner
Folk songs.
Folk songs
Out ~
So easily
Jihyo
out
Old man.
Old man
Sergeant Im.
Sergeant Im ?
Sergeant Im?
Who's Sergeant Im?
There was a Sergeant named Im
Taecgeun when I was in the army.
Only Sukjin knows
'Sergeant Im'
Sergeant Im was so good to me.
He treated Sukjin well
'Sergeant Im'
Of course it can't be accepted.
Does it even makes sense?
Using it as a normal noun
Impossible
I miss Sgt. Im
Sergeant Im treated me so well.
Although we feel sorry for 'Sgt. Im'
Sukjin
out
No, "Sergeant Im" is not accepted.
After a few rounds...
Survivors
Jaesuk, HaHa, Kwangsoo, Yonghwa
The remaining ...
Isn't this very advantageous for Jaesuk?
How about we restrict it to 2 words?
Shall we go with two words?
Let's start with stamp.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Stamp.
Stamp
Flow.
Flow
Orange.
Orange
Phonetic law
Ja ...
Out.
Yonghwa
out
There's a time limit of 3 times.
Shrinking numbers of contenders
3 times.
Let's do 3 words, two is too simple.
Going back to using 3 words
Then let's do 3 words.
Starting word: Mailbox
Mailbox.
Mailbox
Sweatpants.
Sweatpants
Jitterbug.
Jitterbug
Watercress.
Watercress ?
Watercress is wrong.
Why?
It's "Pak".
Previous word ended with 'pak',
but next begun with 'pa'
Ah, really ...
Thick skinned
Didn't you guys attend elementary school?
It should have started with 'pak', not 'pa'.
Absurd
There isn't such rule.
Why is he talking about the rule?
There is such rule.
Aren't you going to shut up?
Suddenly
You idiot.
The stubborn will always be stubborn
No answer...
HaHa
out
Why does he look
like a survivor ...
Didn't you already lose?
I didn't.
Yonghwa, you lost just now.
I didn't, aren't we restarting?
Stubbornly insisting he's still in the game?
Yonghwa, this is really...
I'm not.
No ...
Sukjin is really a bad influence.
Teacher of lying
What are you talking about?
Yonghwa, you were eliminated.
No.
Yonghwa, too many people are watching.
You can't always
cheat your way to winning
You can only do it when
there's no one's watching.
He's such a bad influence.
This was what happened
during scissors-paper-stone.
Scissor-paper-stone
The mistake of a disgraceful middle-aged man
Why didn't you double check
for me during that game?
Suddenly
Too many people are watching this time.
Ready?
Yes.
The finals Jaesuk vs Kwangsoo
How do we start?
Hyung, let's do 2 syllables.
Starting with 2 syllables this time
Okay, two syllables.
Joining the words
Final round
Starting from you.
Starting
word
Hanbok
Hanbok.
Costume.
Costume
Joke.
Joke
Grass.
Grass
Greenery.
Greenery
Green.
Green
Expression.
Expression
Glasses.
Glasses
Listen ~
Listen
Alcohol.
Alcohol
Weekends.
Jihyo
Weekends?!
Wrinkles
Jihyo...
Joining the game
Weekends.
Wrinkles.
Told you to think silently in your head.
Said what came to her mind
Why did you join in?
It gave me a shock.
I thought noona was helping me.
Jihyo lost in the first round Why suddenly ...
She must have thought it to herself ...
... ﻿and just said what she thought.
Your brain made you say it.
Jihyo, why did you
do that so suddenly?
I was too focused.
Jihyo, you've already been eliminated.
I'll just clap along.
So now it's down to the 3 of us?
Keeps rejoining the game
Told you not to do that anymore.
Yonghwa, why are you being like this?
It's all because of Jongkook.
It started with these two
Hurry up and check the
scissor-paper-rock game.
I told you I won.
Let's start again.
Last round restarting
Alcohol.
Alcohol
Wrinkles.
Wrinkles
Food.
Phonetic law
Food
Plates.
Plates
Decision.
Decision
Scenery.
Scenery
Upstream.
Upstream
Gentleman.
Phonetic rule
Gentleman
Straightforward.
Straight
forward
Tone.
Tone
Expression.
Expression
Scenery.
Scenery?
Didn't you already say that?
A word that has been used
Isn't it the first time?
Can it both end with the same syllable?
Didn't you say 'calculate' or 'scenery'?
Thick skinned
I said 'calculate'.
Speechless
Cheating again?
Yonghwa, are you still in the game or not?
What?
Of course I'm still in the game.
I was winning.
Everyone's
trying to cheat
I heard 'calculate' too.
If all 3 of them insists
they can create what doesn't exist
You said 'calculate', not 'scenery?
It was 'calculate' ~
Alright, then ... 'Shan'.
Jaesuk...
Had no choice but to continue...
It's 'shan' then.
Arithmetic.
Arithmetic
Lesson.
Lesson
Report.
Report
Staring.
Staring
Music.
Music
Phonetic law
Shake hands.
Shake hands
Watermelon.
Watermelon
Clapping.
Clapping
Watermelon.
Watermelon
Watermelon Jaesuk repeats a word
Watermelon.
Same mistake as Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo ... wins.
Although a pity
Jaesuk
out
Kwangsoo wins the game
After receiving the Running Ball
to whom will he give his card?
Kwangsoo ...
You know, right?
I voted for your 'calculate'.
Jaesuk had to win
to get rid of the thief-card
Let's decide the winner now.
Fire phoenix Jung Yonghwa
Yonghwa, why are you being like this?
Why are we deciding the winner?
So real that it's scary
Yonghwa's weird talk
The 2nd winner Kwangsoo
gives his card to Jaesuk
Jaesuk's still holding the thief-card
Sukjin draws a card from Jaesuk
The card Sukjin drew is?
Jaesuk looks significantly happier
Did Sukjin draw the thief-card?
Yonghwa drew a card from Sukjin
Despair? Or acting?
Ah~~~
Yonghwa's expression is different
from when he drew the card
Which of them
has the thief-card?
In the 3rd game
'Hit the hand' Gary won
Let's switch.
I can change the seating order?
Yes.
Gives his card to Jaesuk
Mixed
feelings
Jihyo ... number 4.
Jihyo moves to Jaesuk's seat
Sorry Jihyo.
Will you trust oppa
and go to number 4.
Jaesuk doesn't look happy, so
isn't any of his cards the thief?
Jihyo, set number 4.
Only Jaesuk knows the truth
Yonghwa and Jongkook.
Yonghwa
Jongkook
change seats
What do I do?
Let's change.
Anyway...
Gary doesn't know where the thief card is
I don't know either.
I'll do it one more time.
My seat is very good.
The two of you change seats.
Sukjin
Jihyo
change seats
What will the result be?
Switching seats completed
Gary, will Jihyo survive?
Although it's a pity ...
... but the person with ﻿the thief
card can't get the Running Ball.
Everyone else will get a Running Ball.
Let's start with me.
Jaesuk starts
Revealing their cards
Please.
Jaesuk switched seat with Jihyo
Like this ...
1, 2, ... 3.
Revealed
Jaesuk Running Man
Jihyo...
Sitting very still because...?
My turn.
HaHa reveals his card
Also HaHa has a Running Man
1, 2, 3.
Running man.
Yonghwa
passed
1, 2, 3.
The person on Yonghwa's seat
is Jongkook the thief?
Ah, it's not.
It was not!
Jongkook
Passed
What, no?
I'm not the thief?
I thought it was me.
Jihyo and Sukjin
Only they remain
Why were you all looking at me?
Because it's all up to Jaesuk ...
... there's a 98% chance that it's this side.
Let's see them one by one
Did Jaesuk have it?
Sukjin starts to reveal 2 of the 4 cards
1, 2, 3.
Both cards
Running Man
1, 2 ... 3.
At...
...last
1, 2, ... 3.
Jihyo is the chosen thief
Jihyo sits on the thief-chair
Gary,
It's all because of Gary.
Today Gary keeps bringing misery to Jihyo
It was you who told us to switch.
Heartbroken, right.
I picked the card from Jaesuk's 4 cards.
Sukjin took the thief-card
But from my two cards ...
The lucky Yonghwa picked the right card
... ﻿Yonghwa, he took the Running Man card.
Then
Sukjin had the thief-card all the time
How did it come to this?
Woah, this was totally awesome.
All thanks to Gary
the last round was a long playoff
The last round ~
Except for Jihyo
all get a Running Ball
Looking for passwords
inside the central post office
Now
the most exhilarating
fateful round of hide-n-seek begins
Blue
Team
Kwangsoo Jihyo Jaesuk Yonghwa Sukjin
Red
Team
Gary Jaedong Jongkook HaHa
Bells of hide-n-seek
It's here?
Hiding team
Instructions arrived
This number ...
In the post office
find the four hidden passwords
1. B2F - Philatelic museum
2. 10th floor - Conference room
3. 4th floor - Arrival room
4. Basement 2 - Postal service
One of the passwords is on the 2nd floor.
Use the passwords
to open a mail box in order to win
No, this password has four digits.
This one ~
Right.
Let's hurry, it's so quiet here.
Harad Pitt.
Batman.
Seekers play Hollywood-actors-name game
Kooks.
Gaecholas Cage.
Fighting ~
Time remaining
3rd floor or 4th floor?
Meanwhile
Blue
Team
Jihyo & Kwangsoo
1. 2nd floor basement - Mail storage center
2. 2nd floor basement - Postage stamps museum
3. 4th floor - Mailing room
4. 10th floor - Conference room
This place...
Not your average storage room
Noona ...
Noona, this elevator is moving.
It can only be the Red Team coming
Sure it's...
Sparta.
Sparta Kook
Following behind is Mr. Bin ...
Panic
Must hide myself properly
They looked around carefully ...
... but couldn't find their opponents
From what I see ...
I don't think they came
up to the 4th floor yet.
Let's go to the 3rd floor first.
2 people cramped on 4th floor
Escaping ...
Catching ...
1. 2nd floor basement - Mail storage
2. 2nd floor basement - Stamps museum
3. 4th floor - Mailing room
4. 10th floor - Conference room
Creeps in the escalator Sukjin is hiding
Bell sounds
Sukjin spotted
Still trying to hide
Ha
ha
Has anyone
seen me yet?
There's nothing here.
Slyly
Relieved
There's nothing here ...
... so I'll go up to the 1st floor.
ha
Ha
I hid well
Is he gone?
Chatting
Gone...
Attack !
Oh !!!
Wait.
Hyung, why?
Why are you so easy to catch?
Ashamed
The mission has only just started ...
How many minutes since we started?
Hyung, only 3 to 4 minutes passed.
Blue
Team
Sukjin
Remaining time
Meanwhile in the
Stamp Museum
In here
Hard to find the hidden password
After awhile of diligent searching
Yonghwa checks the exhibit of
Korea's all valid stamps
This!!
Yonghwa has finally
found something
This is
first question for the first password
What month is the Mid-autumn
Festival in the Lunar calender?
Month of
festival
This is the Postal Stamp Museum.
Let's go to the storage room.
We go there first, there's
something we need there.
Since you're our elite player, I will
sacrifice myself if we are attacked.
I'll take a look.
Red team
He's here, Gary is here.
Quickly, go inside.
Running to the outside is dangerous
Ah, what to do?
The sound of bells are coming closer
Major crisis
Red Team
Entering the postal stamp museum
Right in front
Walked away
No one's left?
No one.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't run away anymore.
I told you to be quiet ... be quiet.
Although Yooruce Willis is a coward
he bravely goes outside
Where are you now?
Arrived at the mail storage center
Again
Red
Team
strikes
From 4th floor Jongkook and Jaedong
Yooruce Willis is
right behind them
I have to run upstairs, even
though I probably can't do it.
Yooruce Willis escapes
Spotted
Red Team
Immediately starts chasing
Because I was caught right at
the start of the game, my kids ..
It'll be so hard for them to win.
Masculinity
Chased after ~
Jaesuk ... !
No doubt he's Yooruce Willis
Escapes at highest speed
Jaesuk ... !
Vrooom~!
What to do?
Heading to the toilet
I got spotted.
The bells keep getting closer
Is he gone?
I have to pee.
Gosh, hello.
First greeting each other normally
How come you're here?
You've came to go sight-seeing?
Why don't we take a rest?
No need to rest.
No, rest awhile and drink some water.
Coming
Going
Ahh, I'm so ...
If I'm caught like this ...
Here, drink some water.
If you hesitate, then I'm going to leave.
What?
Just leave like this.
So annoying, I'll leave then.
You can't follow me.
It's okay ~
You seriously let me leave?
Hurry run.
Sparta.
You're so ...
Don't do this.
Really, you're really low.
Yah, honestly ...
Escapes the fox but meets the tiger
Yah, you're too much.
Ouch
Blue
team
Jaesuk
Remaining time
Yonghwa searches the quiet surroundings
1. 2nd floor basement - Storage
2. 2nd F basement - Stamp museum (clear)
3. 4th floor - Mailing room
4. 10th floor - Conference room
It's like a letter
so maybe it's inside a pamphlet?
Bingo
Yonghwa finds another password
What is Korea's
postal code?
Month of
festival?
Postal code
of Korea?
Yonghwa found 2 of 4 passwords
In a while ...
Sparta Kook arrives a second to late
Why is this board
pulled out?
I think they already have
done their mission here.
Sparta Kook
has animal-like instincts
They already found something here.
Nothing more at the bottom floors,
we ﻿have to search the upper floors.
Don't come down, search
the floors on top like crazy.
1. Storage room (clear)
2. Stamp museum (clear)
3. 4th floor mailing room
4. 10th floor conference room
Kwangsoo was still hiding
Now there's nobody here
Kwangsoo is feeling energized
Following Jongkook's instructions
Gaecholas Cage is coming up
Woah!!
Eh...
Yah!
Aiyah... Of all timings...
Our Kwangsoo...
Even if he runs for his life...
Finally running into a dead end...
Has only been hiding
Kwangsoo
Time remaining
This is boring, until now I haven't ...
Oh, he came.
All of you got caught?
We haven't found anything yet.
Yonghwa boldly went to the prison
You haven't been caught?
Here.
You already found two?
Found it ~
I'll go to the 10th floor.
The passwords have to be decoded.
All of you must stay here.
We can't go anywhere.
This guy is really amazing.
Admiring Yonghwa's courage
I kept on hiding.
I thought he was already caught.
In my opinion, our problem is ...
Sukjin-Jaesuk-Kwangsoo's problem is
fear
... fear.
I'm going to be Yonghwa's fan.
I don't think this is time
to be playing around.
This person also
wants to be a hero
We should walk around.
Why are you carrying
around that bag?
What are you doing?
Hiker chaser appears
Yah, why are you walking
around with my nametag?
Collection of nametags
What?
It's originally like this.
Where is Jongkook?
Call him and ask where he is.
Wants to know the location
of the opposite team
Jongkook ...
Innocent?
Straight faces
Jongkook ...
Is it turned off?
You need to press the side button.
It's on.
It's on now?
If he talks more
Jongkook's location could be exposed
Try it, ask Jongkook where he is.
Deceit
Jongkook wanted to meet here.
You all think I'm a fool?
Hyung, seriously ...
I'll ask Jongkook "Where are you? ﻿You
said you want to meet here, right?".
Jaedong unexpectedly became smart.
Jaedong is the smart one.
News?
Sukjin's inquiry
of Sparta Kook's whereabouts
Failed
Jongkook ...
What?
Red Team gather on 4th floor
Where are you?
Over there, at the back, hide over there.
Sparta Kook's
attack instructions at 4th floor
I'm going to 2nd floor, so you stay here.
Yeah ~
Got it?
Sparta Kook is
carefully assigning their positions
Relieved
4th floor is
fully guarded
Someone's coming down from the 10th floor.
But...!
Jaedong:
Someone's coming
from the 10th floor
2nd floor?
Who is coming from the 10th floor?
Then I should go to
the 1st floor to
try to catch them
Gary took the elevator to the 1st floor
Also HaHa heard the message
and heads to 1st floor
If it's like this
Empty 4th floor
Jihyo comes to the empty floor
No one...
is here...??
1. 2nd floor mail storage (Clear)
2. 2nd floor stamp museum (Clear)
3. 4th floor mail room
4. 10th floor conference room
No one's here
Still difficult to find it
Suddenly
The secret code
Jihyo is more anxious now
What time does
the post office open?
Month of
festival?
Post office
opens at?
Serial of
the office?
Heading to
the final hiding place at 10th floor
Red
Team
At the 4th floor
What happened to
working together?
Currently at basement 1.
1. 2nd floor mail storage (Clear)
2. 2nd floor stamp museum (Clear)
3. 4th floor mail room (Clear)
4. 10th floor conference room
Dashing in to the first meeting room
Checking all the places
Looking everywhere~
The last
secret code appeared
Jihyo
The last secret code
found
What's the block number
of the presidential area?
1. What month is the
mid-autumn month?
2. What's the block
number of the
presidential area?
3. What time does
post office open?
4. How many numbers
are there in the serial
code of the post office?
I still think it is better
to wait at the 4th floor.
Why is it
so quiet?
...Err??
Empty~
No way!!
Where are you all.
3rd floor.
Gary: 3rd floor
Why aren't you at 4th floor?
HaHa is at 4th floor.
Gary: HaHa is at 4th floor
Where?
HaHa isn't here.
Yes.
HaHa: Yes
I asked you to guard here,
where have you been?
Why are you so angry?
Gary: Why are you so angry?
Ridiculous...
Where in the world is Haha?
I asked you to guard
here and you did not.
Agitated
I told you to guard the 4th floor.
Where are you, seriously?
Where did the four of them go?
Quickly come to the 4th floor.
Gary following
We reached the 4th floor.
The envelope that Jihyo left
We're too late.
Looks like someone had done the mission.
Unhappy
If you had been here to guard,
they would have been caught.
I originally wanted to wait here.
What were you doing?
Can't you do it properly?
I ﻿thought the walkie-talkie would
explode because of your shouting.
I really got shocked.
"Gary", talk passionately like this.
Okay ~
Remaining time
Meeting at the 10th floor
Blue Team's heroes
They need to figure out the
answer to the 4 questions
The post office opens is at 9 o'clock.
Month of
festival?
Presidential
block area?
Time post
office open?
Numbers in
postal code?
Which month is the mid-autumn month?
It must be 8.
The block number of
the presidential area ...
... must be 1.
8, 1, 9 ...
There's one more digit.
How many numbers in the
serial code of the post office?
I already gave the last
code to the hyungs ...
... to let them figure it out.
Let's count it and send it over to them.
The hyungs in prison try to solve the code
That means we can be of little help.
Happy
Of course, we are very important.
Not familiar with the newest phones
Aye, it shouldn't be done like that.
What are you doing?
Young and weak Kwangsoo
Ah, we can't even do this well.
How can we even do missions?
Deng ~
Someone is coming
They're anxious but still need to hide
Eh?
Caught
With Jihyo blocking
Yonghwa escaped
Heading towards the
2nd floor mailbox
Hey Jihyo.
Jihyo blocking Jaedong's vision
Success
Why are you always chasing after me.
Why don't we talk about it?
Only person left to trust is Yonghwa
Give me the 4th number quickly.
Speak slowly, slowly.
What's the 4th digit?
The 4th digit is 6.
Punch the code here
What's happening?
* Yonghwa forgot the month of the festival
The code is wrong.
Wrong code
Red Team
Coming from all directions
Due to nervousness...
he can't remember the 1st digit
Yonghwa
Please...!
Big problem, I don't remember the numbers.
He doesn't remember the numbers.
The 3rd digit is 1.
The third digit is 3 ~
They confused the numbers all together
Then there is still one more.
What was the 2nd question?
I really don't know what the numbers are.
Who...
Who...!!
I really don't know what the numbers are.
What? Whose that?
Catch it!
Take it
Really didn't know what
the numbers were.
Relaxed
Catch it.
It isn't confirmed yet
But cheering
Blue
Team
Received
package
Mission
complete
Also today the hero
Jung Yonghwa
I'll come down.
Yah, he is really too strong.
Touched
Blue
Team
In the box is
the member's name on balls
Love ~
It's was 8.
Due to nervousness the
1st digit was confused
It was 8, right?
It was 8, wasn't it?
We hyungs were too useless, sorry.
HaHa will be scolded again.
I have seen all of them and ...
... yet HaHa is no where to be found.
Unhappy
You ...
Helpless
... come over here.
I told you to guard the
4th floor, why didn't you?
Come here.
Where have you been?
Wants the truth
You told me to go to the
4th floor, so I went down.
I said I was going, you should
have just stayed there.
Didn't I tell you to guard the 4th floor?
No, Jaedong said to meet at the 2nd
floor, then go up to together, right?
Now Jaedong is drawn into it
I asked where you were,
you said ﻿to go together.
That's why I went down.
Where did you go?
Are you looking for an excuse?
It's not an excuse.
You should listen to Jongkook's words.
If you'll look at the broadcast,
you all are seriously ridiculous.
Jaedong In order to not
be scolded by Jongkook ...
But it's not Jongkook that's ridiculous.
It's not me that's unreasonable.
I really saw your mistake
Why don't we let them stay here?
There's nothing to be proud of.
You stay here too.
You didn't do anything good either.
What did I do?
I was paired up with him, but ...
Red
Team
Publicly
disbanding
Let's not fight anymore.
Let's go together.
Our team isn't like theirs
Hyung, let's go together.
Hyung, come here.
Tsk...
Yah ~
Hyung, let's go together.
If you had guarded the 4th floor,
none of this would've happened.
I already did ~
HaHa Finally throwing a
white flag at Jongkook
The child has had enough of scolding
If you had guarded the 4th floor,
it would not have been like this.
4th floor
told you to stay there
I told you to stay at the 4th floor.
Why did both of you leave,
one could have stayed.
For this time, everyone knew it
would be a personal challenge.
I have 3 balls, Sukjin also has 3.
The first 5 names that
comes out on a ball can leave
Jihyo has 2 balls.
Jihyo 2 balls
The rest all have 3
On our side only Gary has
one ball, the rest have two.
Again the punishment
is wearing hot ﻿pants.
And you have to wear
it on the bus home.
First let's put all the balls in.
Gary's ball.
Finally
Putting in their personal named balls
I'll put it in last.
Okay.
Praying
Gary only has one ball,
if it gets picked then ...
Only one ball
If Gary's is picked it would be big
Everyone has put in their balls.
Among so many balls ...
This really is ...
Only 5 can escape
the punishment
Machine of fate
Starts to spin
Sukjin ~
Jaesuk ~
Coming, the first one ...
Indeed
1, 2, 3.
Who'll be the first to escape the punishment
Not a team battle But individual battle
Double the nervousness
2 balls came out at the same time
Song Jihyo.
Jung Yonghwa.
Jihyo&Yonghwa Escape confirmed
Now only 3 more can escape
Please ~
Who will it be now?
Again
2 balls came out
Jaedong and HaHa.
Jaedong-HaHa Escape confirmed
Finally something happy ~
Disappointment
Please ~
Now only one more can escape
Please just once.
It's starting.
4, 3, 2, 1.
Who'll escape?
embarrassing hot pants?
Who'll escape the fate of
Coming out
Who is it?
Who is the last lucky person?
Ji Sukjin.
Ji Sukjin
Escape
confirmed
Really?
Lucky
Lost
Unbelievable.
Is using
one wrong?
Until now, I've got punished
every time except twice.
Innocent
In my house I already have
three pairs of hot pants.
More innocent
Punishment in flowery(?) hot pants
Feeling the breeze
on their legs
The pants are too tight, I can't walk.
At this time ...
... we should have confidence.
Just ﻿like you are when
wearing normal clothes.
As if it's normal clothes.
Can't really pass as normal clothes
Aren't you suppose to return to Anyang?
They are all going in different directions
I can sleep anywhere.
Gives up
They all decided to stop at Jaesuk's house which is the nearest
Then where should we take the bus from?
I really thought you were a normal citizen.
This can't be?
Just passes by like that
Are you Jaedong?
You shocked me.
Normal citizen out for
a morning exercise
Look so much alike.
Escaped freely
On the way home, why don't we eat a little?
Go home, wear proper clothes
and the come out and eat?
The pants are too tight, can't eat anything.
Amazed
Here comes the bus.
The bus is here
Embarrassed
Oh my gosh
Going to the gym for 10 years ...
Suddenly
... and he still has to sit like that.
Puts his muscles
in a small space
Just like that another
day has passed