Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Don't Walk, Run team @ Viki
The Third Landmark!
South Korea's Heart of Science  Gwacheon National Science Museum.
The museum is alive!
Running Man's unbelievable
Science vs. Expedition
Starting now!
Will blow away the heat wave to pieces
Science Expedition Part 2 will begin
-Does everyone know curling?  -Of course
Meanwhile from last week!  Hey, you have it all calculated right? Its calculated? Wait a minute.
Using the Law of Inertia, in human curling
With no sign of backing down and a golden pig worth 500,000 Won on the line
With twist after twist in repeat
Currently Team So-In is at an advantage!
And Team Dae-In's last runner! Kwang-Soo is starting!
-Is this the last time?-Yeah-Jaesuk is this the last time? Ok. Fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
Super Nervous!-Ji-Hyo, you have to push really hard
Please let our team be the ones cheering...
Fighting!Team Dae-In's last runner Kwang-SooFighting!
Iron wall defense-Fighting!
Has to push Haha who is in the center circle-Kwang-soo fighting!
With all hopes, Team Dae-In starts
Heading straight towards Haha
Please...
No way...
Come and get me.
Last ChanceIf he can't push Haha out then they will lose.
Ok Ok OkLets listen to hear who's voice is cheering...
The shouts of victory are coming from...?
[bingul-ul-ul-ul]
Went past him!
Team Dae-In FAILS to enter to the center of the circle
[suuuk]
Disappointment
Lets do this again
Team So-In WIN
[Spiteful Remark]Hey why are you over THERE?
Ah I put too much power into it
Since this is the last round
Lets everyone come on this sideFinal RoundStand at the start line and push the trash bin to the opposite side line. Whoever gets the closest to the line WINS!
and try to get close to the opposite side line.-Oh your talking about Cola CiderBut if the trash bin crosses the start line located at the opposite side then they are OUT!
Kwang-soo again switching his trash bin for a good one.
And again just walking naturally
Isn't that used when you play pool? -Yes your right
-Like throwing coins~Everyone is gathering at the start line on one side
-We're going to be going first-Okay-Thank You
Whichever team's trash bin comes closest to this line is the winner-Fighting!
Fighting!
Team Dae-In Jae-Suk gets ready to go first
-Ahh it was too strong[shuuuunnng]
If you cross this line then you are OUT!
Getting closer to the finish line!
Wind resistance...?!Flapping of the grasshopper wings
Disqualified if he crosses the finish line!
Will he make it?
Crossed the line!
I told you its about 30 steps...
Team Dae-InJae-Suk DISQUALIFIED-I told you about the steps
I told you that its about 30 steps
Pathetic...-I should have pushed by myself-I told you to push slowly
Failed to control strength because it was his first time
Can't you give me another chance? -No No No
You know, being over there by yourself will become very fun
Curse?-I guarantee that someone else will also come this way
Team So-In is now getting ready-Hey this...
-Hey we really need to do good. 500,000 Won is on the line. This is really important.With 500,000 won on the line, they are all sensitive
Team So-In's first runner Haha-Haha you can't get all the way over there.
-We are going-He's going to go past it
Haha is riding the faulty trash bin that Kwang-Soo switched-Your probably going to go past it.
-Your going to go past it! Your going to go past it!-I have a weird feeling
We are not going to die!
[Dul-Kung]
Pretending not to know
Out! Out! Out! Director Out!
- What does it look like from that angle?-Out!-Out!
-I was looking at Haha the whole time!Judge Yoo was looking the whole time while in the corner?
- Out! Out! Out! Out! Out!-Your out because you went too far out.-Why are you deciding on your own authroity?
-Over there? Sorry but could be be more quiet?
Yeah yeah Out!
Team Dae-InSecond runner Suk Jin
[Flapping]
[Sululululululululu]
With no strength the trash bin stops at the center
- What is this...-Kwang Soo that was too slow
[Again his back is turned to the camera]Man everytime I do this I am always facing this way.
Again...Suk Jin's lonely back...
The lonely man that appeared walked through pouring rain...-I know Suk-Jin really well, he is really nervous right now
Loneliness, first time doing outside variety in 10 years-Yours was a little weird
You all look so close!
-You all look so close-Don't meet outside of work
Between the members that meet outside of work...
Tried to endure all the humiliation...
But since last week...
Becoming alone
makes me so sad...
-YesNo matter what is going on Team So-In is getting ready
Lonely-Gary come visit me.
-I'm ready-We are goingPeaceful Gary is always ready
-Ok.-I'm nervous I'm nervous
-Let's go!Peaceful Gary! Let's Go!
-Here. Where you need to be is here.
-Good Good!
Safe steady speed-Go!-Good Good!
Safe and steady speed
[Screech]
-Good!
-We did well!
-Gary is doing well.
In the midst of all this, one person is still alone...
Oh that's right, he can push Suk Jin.
Now Dae-In Team's last person, Kwang Soo
Kwang Soo you have to do well!
-Okay! -Fighting, fighting!
Kwang Soo think about the punishment
The Finish line is close! They have to push Gary away!
A successful push!
Crossed the line. Gary eliminated!
You did it!
-It's done  -Isn't this cheating?
Kwang Soo was good. Kwang Soo did well.
[Proud]Thank you
He remains peaceful although he was eliminated.
[Now it's So-In Team's last challenger, Joong Ki]Fighting, fighting!
Teeth clenched tight.
Worried.
-Go, go, go!  -Why does this make me so nervous?
What kind of variety show is this?
Legs fell asleep-It's the first time I'm this nervous.
They are worried and the trash can isn't in good shape...-Our ride isn't doing well.-Can't you do it a bit faster?
Go, go, go. Just go.
Stops-Ah, what is this?
Annoyed What are you doing?
Oh, Jihyo's real personality is showing.
All of them are sensitive to the 500 000 won they need to escape!-No, but why does the time take so long..?
Jihyo, you're doing well!
Let's go, let's go!
So-In Team just needs to push Kwangsoo to win!
This is it! This is it!
I'll push you away!
The silence of an estimated attack!
Crash!
He definitely pushed, but...-You need to push him hard!
They're both moving?!
Who is the final winner?
Joongki went over the line. Eliminated!
Kwangsoo stopped just before the line. Safe!
The final winner is Dae-In Team!
Dae-In Team's celebration
Huh? Why is Gary cheering?
What is happening.
Dae-In Team gets the price of 500 000 Won.
Oh... I misunderstood...
Film him one more time.
Today's MVP: Kwangsoo!-So awesome! 500 000 won!
Currently, both teams are competing...
Eight hours ago, at the pool within the museum...
Oh, Jaesuk is good at swimming.
(Interesting swimming grasshopper) Wow not bad swimming. Show us some Butterfly too.
Hmph Butterfly is easy~
Splash
You could join the Olympic.
[Doing the butterfly in a shallow area while walking!]
You're a good swimmer.
-I'm doing Butterfly but my chest hurts so much.
Haha, try a breaststroke!
It's a butterfly! Superfly!
Superfly...? Not a butterfly?
splash
Haha also does a butterfly with a foot on the pool
[The expression of a competitor]
[Sparkling]
Doesn't your face hurt?
This game also has 500 thousand won on the line.
Let's play the game.
It's Gary Game.  [The game called Gary Game]
In that case...
In any situation...
A game where you can see Peaceful Gary
- Photozone  - Yes, photosone. [Photo in the pool]
The team with the most clear faced team member pictures wins
You guys got it?  -Yes
In this game, everyone is getting onto this sausage boat...
We will only recognize the people who get on.
[Complicated]  It's too hard.
- Photo will be taken over there?  - Yes.
- Can't we sit up there without pushing?  - Like that?
Ok.
Are you negotiating?
Let's go.
[Get in the pool first]
slips~
[Be on your guard.]
First, Joongki is trying to get up
Sausage boat seems difficult to get on
Flustered~
my pants are falling off!
Gary aims for the side where it is less competitive
Quarrel~  Hurry
Jongkook, Haha gets onto the boat
[Suddenly.]
~ Gary gets onto the boat on his first try~  Please take the picture quickly.
Please hurry! Take the picture for us!
Me too! Me too!
Mc: We're going to take the picture now!
I'm going to get on too!
Huh?
EVERYONE ENTERS THE WATER
Strenghtless while Jaesuk is trying to climb on
With the flash everyone falls off
Overturn sausage!
[Picture was taken when they fell in the water...did anyone show up?]
Again its Gary? Its Gary again!
Peaceful Again
Gary how did you take that picture?
Unbelievable
Right at that moment the sausage boat turned over...
Hyung Suk Jin is getting attacked right?
[Poor Big Nose Hyung...]
-And at the moment Gary is able to hold up a V-Right
At that moment a "V" Point
[Nichkhun and Gary picture taken. Tie.]   I actually took note of the expression in my eyes.
Gary Gallery  Nobody got in the picture, but I get in it everytime.
Round 2: Taking a picture on a big floating platform! Let me brief you guys first..
Nickhun just told me, It's kind of tiring.
We will be going for hibernation when we get home.
Female members are disappearing.
Please don't do it yet.
Joongki just asked her not to leave.
Hahaha.  Mc: Please get on the floating platform.
[Haha and Joongki goes first]
[Child, you are here?]
[Smack]
[Gary moves away from the chaos.]
[Gary gets hit while trying to find easier place]
Hey! Nickhun!
After disposing Joongki, next he targets Gary!
You don't have to play that aggresive.
[Complete mess!]
Let's take a photo
[Panic]
[This is a chance]
[No way]
[Jihyo blocked Haha]
[Nickkun's powerful defense]
[Wow, All members from taller team are on platform]
We have to get on  splash~ splash~
Hey, Stop.
[At this time, Joongkis last attack]
[Who will be on the picture?]
[Click]
[Finish taking photo]
[When did Gary come up?]
[Gary is in the photo again!!]
[Peaceful]
[Jihyo and Gary tied]
I look handsome.
Can't Gary just take picture by himself?
[Gary looks so peaceful]
What is his job?
And I thought only Jihyo got taken
[Gary Gallery]
[Sukjin's suggestion for 3rd round]
After going under the water
You have to hold your breath for 10 seconds.
Everyone can hold their breath for 10 seconds.
Let's start
One, Two, Three
[Dive]
[Gary looks determined]
~bubble bubble~
[Looks funny from the top]
[Are they able to hold their breath until the picture is taken?]
[Sukjin the one who proposed the game, is up first]
[Some members are still under water]
[Short team! Get out!]
~bubble~
[Taller team's interruption.]
[Who are you?]
[Jihyo fail]
[Of course, Gary is the only one left]
[Was the picture not taken?]
Photographer was not able to hold his breath.
[WTF]
[Sorry]
My focus was blurred.
Your excuse was nice
[...]
[3rd round restart]
[Both teams are involved in physical fighting]
[Underwater is..]
[Chaos]
[Point: Gary will be on picture or not?]
[Nickhun is right in front of camera]
[Gary is pulling Nickhun away]
[Click]
[Gary and Nickhun were only people remained]
[Who is on the picture?]
Hahahaha
[What's all this fuss about?]
[This is Nickkun's photo]
[Taller team won]
He covered whole screen.
[That's Gary]
[Is that Gary]
[Nickkun won against the champion]
[Gary's first time losing this competition]
[There is no more Gary in photo zone]
[Jihyo is caring Jessica?]
She cares about me first.
Jessica, I think something is falling out.
[Quiet]
[What is falling out?]
Something is falling out from her eyes.
[Ah... Jessica's fake eyelashes]
[Last game, Water jump photo]
Wow
[Have to be on this angle in order to be in the picture]
[Ready!]
[Starting to check each other]
We have to block Gary
[Gary is the most powerful competetor]
[I'm going to take photo]
[Jump, Jump]
[Who will be on the photo?]
[Winning team will win whole water photo zone game]
[Winning team will win $500}
[Point: Will Gary be able to keep his crown?]
[Click]
[Return of the King]
[Return with peaceful face]
[Shorter team won this game]
[Shorter team earned $500]
[I can't beat him]
[Gary Gallery]
Say something Gary!
[Gary's congratulation ceremony]
[Anticipating]
I don't know.
[Flying]
[We took the picture] [!!!!!]
[Levitation]
[He is in different class]
[His ceremony is also an art!]
[Peaceful]
He is amazing!
[Peaceful Gary Religion]
[Everyone worship him]
everyone is amazed by him.
[Gary Gallery]
[One of the laboratory in Science Museum]
We got wet, so we needed to change.
Finally we taking a rest.
Hyung, do you know?
If you cover your eyes and drink
[You can't tell the difference between cider and cola when your eyes are closed]
you can't tell.
I watched this game from another program.
-No seriously, if you close your eyes, you can't tell.  -Who are you trying to fool?
[Extremely sure]
For real, for real, for real.
I will show you. Give it to me.
If I guess it correctly, what will I get?
Just a minute. For real.
-I'm ready.  -Let's bet money.
I want to rinse my mouth.
[It's not like you're drinking wine...]
[It's not like you are wine testing...]
[So, the cola and cider blind test begins]
[Starting with the first glass of cola]
[Will Haha be right and a distinction can't be made?]
?
[He really doesn't know?]
I know. I know the taste of cola.
-It's because I have been drinking a lot of cola since I was young.  -You have to pinch your nose.
I know the taste of cola is, cause i've been drinking a lot since i was young.
Okay, Cola.
[Correct]
There are still 4 more cups
[The second glass is cider]
This is soda.  [Correct again!]
You got it totally wrong.
Give me some water!
I am a co-mmelier.
Commelier?
Sommelier for wine. Commelier for cola.
[gargle, gargle]
[The third glass is cola]
This is cola.
[Third continuous right answer!]
[Fourth glass is cola]  How many did he get right? 3?
I know this, cola.
[As expected, correct!]
If you get the last one right, it means you got 1 out of 5 right.
[The last cider! Can the commelier get it right?]
It's cola.
[Commelier. Fail!]
~laughter~
Hey. This is really amazing.
-Did you change it after I drank?-I didn't change it.
You really didn't change the cups?
-Nickhun, are you feeling okay?  -Yes
Hyung, are you okay?
Is your undergarment okay?
Your undergarment in the front looks like it belongs to your wife.
[What is he talking about?!]
I thought he was wearing women's clothing.
It's possible that you might misunderstand. My manager
forgot to pack my underwear today,
so my manager bought some for me at the convenient store.
But.. it was the triangular type.
I was so surprised.
It came up to here.
[Flustered, flustered]
I was surprised too! The lining was all the way up to here.
[Since they can't go outside, they have junk food for dinner]
I'm so hungry!
[He keeps on hanging around near Jihyo]
Couldn't you leave Jihyo side?
[MC Yoo professional false scandal makerMakes a couple?]
This is just for fun.
Who is you ideal type among us?
You may take it lightly, but it's not a joke to Haha.
If you pick me, you have to accept my kids as well.
[If you pick me, my kids comes along as well.]
Think about watching this with you wife over the weekend?
Before marriage, what was your wife like?
A deer.
How about now? After marriage?
Imagine a deer chewing a rabbit.
[A carnivorous deer?]
I really don't understand this about women, even before I got married.
Why does she ask if she looks different
when she just slightly cut her hair?
[100% agree]
She cuts her bangs 1 centimeter...
and asks if there's anything different about me.
Hey, if you can't get it right, you die.
After marriage, my home has turned into a quiz program.
[Married life is a quiz program?]
"Do you know why I'm mad?" Buy a buzzer before going home.
Beep!
"Do you know why I'm mad?"
How about when apologizing?
- I'll tell you.  - Yes.
You all listen carefully.
I was tired after filming Running Man,
My wife was cleaning and I lifted my feet slightly to get out of her way.
'Oppa wait, let's talk.'
Then I have a bad feeling.
'Why are you angry?'  'You don't know why?'
It's the start of the quiz.
I have to get it right in one go or I'm dead.
So I asked "Is it because I'm not helping with the cleaning?"
She said "That's not it!"
It has to do with consideration.
She wanted to hear "Are you tired? Do you need help?"
[Ah~]
But on the weekend, he went to the movies with his wife.
Didn't you fall asleep while watching movie?
No, no. We watched movie with the kids.
The children say everything their parents say.
You kid is 9 years, right?
He is 9 years old, but is so cute looking.
It was a really hot day and we got in the car.
He says to me "Dad, can you super BLAST the air conditioner?"
! !
[The short break time ends...]
[And then!]
Now, the race starts in a most unique location where the mission is to find the hidden golden pigs.
[The fifth mission: Find the 2 golden pigs hidden in the science museum!]
[The instructions arrived]
[A380. There are 2 piggy banks]
A380?
-Oh! It's here!  -It's here?
Could it be area A, area B, area C and so on.
The museum usually has many areas.
-Should we start moving?  -I don't think it's the locker
Hyung! The parking lot! The parking lot!
The parking lot has A, B, C, D.
But the number 380...
Is the number too big?
Look Hyung! Here is C1, P1. I think we have to look for 'A'.
-What's "math" in English?  -It's "Mathematics".
-It seems like Jong Kook is better than Jessica at English. -No, no
This is something like a chemical, right?
[As expected of Running Man's brain]  So maybe the 'A' stands for something.
How about Biology?
- Wow, you're good at English.  - That's not it.
What about A?
Artist?
How do you say aerospace in english?
Astronaut.  [Jong Kook speaks even advanced English]
Wow, really. We're too smart.
It's all written here.
[The words Jongkook used are all written there]  Earth Science, Biology, Chemistry, Physics, Mathematics.
I didn't see it, seriously. [That's not the case, I really know them!]
[Disappointed]  Oppa, I thought you were really smart.
I think you're right.
It says we are here right now.
That means that there should be something here.
-It's the second floor  -The second floor!
Before, we saw the space airplane room. [The A in A380 is connected to the space airline}
-It's the second floor.  -Jessica, you did it.
-We are finally working together.We are the brains.
[On the other hand, the Shorter team hasn't found much] There's a map here.
Oh, where are they running off to?
It's here!
-Oh! It's there?  It's here! It's here! Look!
[Even though they don't know why, A380 is the second floor! Go Go!]
They are following us.
They already went up to the second floor!
[Taller Team is one step ahead and arrives at the 2nd floor exhibit] Hyung, "Advanced Science" has an "A".
[The country's achievements in astronomy, aerospace, science and technology can be seen all in a glance here at the museum]
[Is this where A380 is?]
-A380?  -Yes, it's 380.
[Everyone looks for A380 in the exhibit]
[Is it here?]
[At a loss.]
Look at the second floor.
[The golden pig is sitting near them!!]
It's here, here!
[Kyaaaak~]
[They thought they were going to get the pig, but an astronaut suddenly approaches!]
What is this?
[Entrance blocked]
[The mysterious astronauts surround Jihyo!]
[For now, she passes the golden pig to Suk Jin]
[Huh? Something's off?]
There's nothing in here!  [It's a fake empty golden pig]
[Jihyo is locked into the mysterious chair!]
[If you find a fake golden pig, you get a punishment!]
Mommy!  [Spin!]
Mommy!
[Game where if you sit in the revolving seat, you will become familiar with the loss of balance in space.]
[But to her, it is only a punishment...]
[Top speed.]
[Ah... today is seriously...]
[I had to deal with Sukjin's annoyances...]
[I had to fight with Jongkook...]
[I had absolutely no luck today...]
[Now...I have to deal with a punishment]
You look like you're going to be possessed by the Gumiho
[Nine-tailed fox with one shoe?]
What are you doing?
Jihyo!
[The gyroscope punishment ends!]  She lost her mind.
[Dizzy, dizzy]
Ah, I'm getting motion sickness.
Jihyo, what are you doing?
I got caught while looking for the golden pig.
[What an eventful day for Jihyo]
[Answer reveal: What is A380?]
[Within the Science Museum, the cutting edge technology of flight space on the 2nd floor.]
[The very large aircraft, Airbus A380]
[The place where the golden pig is hidden is...]
[right above the seats and inside the cabinet!]
[Oh?! Jaesuk found the right place]
The airbus 380 is here.
[He checks the cockpit]
[As expected, detective Joongki finds A380!]
Walkie-talkie! Walkie-talkie!
[He needs to let his team know, but he doesn't have any walkie-talkies...]
[On the other hand, Jaesuk just needs to turn his head..!]
[It's right there]
[Ah... he just passes by it...]
[What a waste...]
We have to find it.
This place is so large that I can't figure out where it is.
Oh, ooh.
[Jaesuk was searching well for a while, but gets distracted]
It says A380 on the outside of the airplane.
[The Taller Team enters A380]
Open stuff like the cabinets.
[Jaesuk... is now openly playing]
[The Taller team checks the seat cabinets!]
[Here it is!]
[This is the real golden pig!]
[The Taller Team finds 1 golden pig!]
[Though they were wrong about the meaning of 'A', they are the first to find the piggy bank]
[On the other side...this person is still in childlike state.]
[And the little brother who imitates him]
But we haven't found them all. There is one left.
We found both of them.
One was an empty piggy bank...
That means that there another one!
[We will reveal where the other golden pig is located]
[An impossible-to-find golden pig, no matter how hard the Running Man members try]
[That secret is right here...]
[1 hour ago...]
[A walking astronaut mannequin?!]
[A staff member puts the golden pig in the helmet he is holding]
[Struggle, Struggle]  [Please close the door for me~]
They are coming in, move!
[The staff withdraw quickly after the members arrive earlier than expected]
They're here!
[Car's selection Team So In arrives.!]
[Super nervous]
[She doesn't suspect anything!]
[Jihyo... simply passes by]
[Jaesuk!]
[Of course, passes]
[Even though many people pass...]
[right in front of him... They don't know!]
[No one has noticed yet.]
[20 minutes has passed and hasn't moved...!]
I feel like there should be one over there.
[9th level quick-witted Suk Jin is fooled...]
[Phew... Thank goodness]
[Looking, Looking]
[Emergency! Jong Kook approaching!]
[He's right in front of it!]
[Rigid.]
[Hmmm... something...]
One more?
[Jong Kook, keeps going around...]
[Ah! He bent down!]
[Will he see the golden pig in the hand?]
[Thump, Thump, Thump, Thump]
[Jongkook! Did he find out?!]
Surely it wouldn't be there.
[Surely, it wouldn't be there!]
[Jong Kook sees a display manequin.]
[10 years shaved off]
[He pushed the pig in more so it can't be seen]
[Phew... that could have been bad]
Where could it be?
Something is weird. This is...
[A suspicion that can't be explained.]
[Why did you come back?!]
Why does this open?
[The door opens?]
[As expected, something is off]
[Looks like Jong Kook can see something.]
[People have started to gather.]
Nice, nice, nice, nice!
[He puts his hand into the helmet]
[Will Jongkook take the golden pig this time too?]
[People leaving due to the human manequin defense.]
I think this is right! Keep going!
The helmet! Hyung, the helmet!
The helmet! The helmet on top!
[No one has yet to suspect that the astronaut is a person]
[Sukjin enters the glass box]
[Stealthily.]
[If you lift it...]
[It's here!]
[Oh my god]
[Sukjin found the golden pig!]
[Suk Jin's surprising glorious...What?]
[It was a person?]
[The astronaut attempts to run off with the golden pig]
[Huh..?]
[Astronaut breaks through using all his strength.]
What's happening?!
[Combat.]
[The owner of this golden pig is still undecided]
[Astronaut who overcame many critical situations.]
[Can he safely defend the golden pig again?]
[The golden pig is Jong Kook's!]
[The Taller Team succeeds in getting 2 golden pigs]
[Regretful~]
I found it first!
[Smart but weak older brother!]
[Teamwork and strength brought Team So In complete victory!!]
[Race Over]
[A little later in the garden within the Science Museum...]
Okay, everyone. As you may already know,
It's a time where you go between reality and dreaming.
I know. You can't give us that long of a resting time.
-Yeah, yeah. -We'll fall right asleep.
What's surprising is you think Jong Kook is a man of few words? He's not.
[Jong Kook's talkative lips during rest time!]
[Jae Suk recognizes Jong Kook as the greatest chatterbox]
What are you talking about?
-Me? -Yes, yes, yes
By the way, our Jong Kook and Yang Hyun Suk...
-Ah, stop it! I don't want to do stuff like that!  -Aw, please just do it once.
[What is this all of a sudden at dawn~Caught at the time you are most sleepy...]
Why do I have to do this right now?
Just do it once.
-I always knew that Jong Kook was a good dancer but never this good.  -It's not that I'm good at dancing.
Ah, please do it for us! Please do it!
Kim Jong Kook!
Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
-When I was young, Mr. Yang was my hip-hop hero.  -Of course!
So when Mr. Yang came out on a program,
he would often highlight Hip-hop.  -He would do that often in the past.
-And you know, the people on the program would ask "Oh, please teach us some Hip-hop."  -Yes, of course.
He would wear the hat very often.
He'd be like "Hip-hop isn't hard."
"Just pretend that there's a doorway and that you're going through it."
[Showing the hip hop spirit with his whole body?]
Wait, how do you go through it?
Just pretend that there's a doorway and that you're going through it.
Go through the door.
Go through
[If you go through the door... OK]
[Do you know hip hop?]
[Hip hop feel that spreads in the dawn.]
[Jong Kook, chatter and threshold hip hop!]
[How about Kwang Soo?]
It's because it's the middle of the night and we have to stay awake.
The door is here and you have to pass it. How?
How?
[Move limply~]
[This... what...]
[Asked to leave!]
He is too enthusiastic.
[What...everyone is sleepy...]
Gary, don't you dance well also?
No, I can't dance.
-Gary has gone to dance contests. -Really?
[Blank]
Just show us a little bit.
You might be surprised by this, but
he used to be a member of H.O.T.
Why? What are you doing?
Seriously, he was supposed to be Kang Ta.
I'm Kang Gary! Kang Gary from Jamsil!
[What H.O.T. could have been like?]
Gary, please show us some of your dancing.
My dance isn't technique based.
I don't need stuff like this.
-It's not technical, it's more based on movement.  -So, please show us this dance.
Seo Tae Ji and the children were popular for
the butterfly dance.
[Move limply]
[An unknowable dance...]
[Seo Taiji and Boys' 3rd album (Dreaming of Balhae) announced in 1994]
[This dance. Topic of conversation butterfly dance.]
[Wriggle~]
[Gary's dance that looks completely different from the original.]
[Excessive wiggle is the key!]
If Hyung Yang Hyuk does this dance, he has to wear a hat.
[First, jam your hat]
[Muscle hip hop wiggle.]
[Beats the original wiggle.]
[If you dance like this Jun Ho Hyung-Nim?!]
[Tornado storm finish.]
[Instinctive dance that doesn't sink.]
[Aigoo~ My knees]
It's funny!
In a club, you don't need to dance anything else.
All you need to do is this, in front of the speaker.
[Gary...Excited!]
[Jae Suk immediately follows.]
How do you do it?
In front of a mirror.
Is this right?
It's the same as this for Hyung Suk Jin.
Do this and then naturally flick up.
towards the right~ right~ wu-sa!
I'm interested that way.
jwah-sa~
Jwah-sa? What is 'Jwah-sa"?
Lovely ladies enter to the left.
Lovely ladies to the right.
Lovely ladies to the back.
You've woken up now, right?
[Definitely woke up from the sleepy dawn...]
[The next game is?] What is the game this time?
Something is coming!
-What is it?  -It's a bus. -Why would a bus come at this time?
Why would a bus come at this time?
Where does this bus go?
-Why are there so many people on it? -There's a ton of people on it.[Overcrowded]
What do you want us to do?
Member from each team please come out
and go inside at the same time.-Yes.
The person who gets out of the back door first wins
Running there?
-It's incredible. -Is this 500 thousand won?
-If we win this then we have basically won.-We basically win.
Let's win this for sure!
One two three
-Fighting!  -We have to win this!
when I was younger, I often took buses which were this crowded  1,2,3 FIGHTING!
I'm going first!
Why are you saying it so loudly?
Just come out.
Then, Jaesuk will go first.
It's weird to say my own name.
-Who's coming out here? Haha?-Then it's me of course.
Haha, please go back
AH~ WHY?!
Jae Suk is going. Jae Suk has been working out lately.
[Boastful] -Let's go Jae Suk.  - We'll send gary out there.
Kang Gary is going.
-Nice to see you. -Nice to see you.
Could you move up a little more?
[Short Team: Excercised Grasshopper vs Taller Team: Kang Gary who lives in Jamsil] -Gary, Fighting! -Jae Suk, show them.
-Ready! -Show them. -Fighting!
Go!
[Breaking away quickly!]
[Gary boards first.]
[Can't see the two people in the crowd!]
Everyone, please excuse us for a moment!
[Pierce through the dense crowd]
[Got through 1/3 in a flash!]
Don't be like this, Hyungnim!
Jae Suk, this one!
-I can't see Gary Hyung.  -Where's Kang Gary?
~peaceful Gary is Here~
-I can't hear.-It's pandemonium inside.
At this time  squeezing through the obstacles which the staff prepared
~indeed. Very packed~
Gary! Just like that, Finally through.
My clothes are gonna rip!
woo~
te...ar...~
The escape from Jaesuks grasp, Gary rips his own clothing...!
~but if sexy gary leaves the bus, what will happen to his clothes?~  Jaesuk, good work. Thats it.
Jae Suk Fighting!
-Jae Suk!  [Grab] -Ah!
What is this?
[Killer grasshopper!]
~laughter~
He pressed it. He pressed it.
[Gary, pressed the bell!]
[Exit open!] -Jae Seok, press it. Press it together.
From now on, escaping the bus is they key.
Hyung! Just endure a little more.
No!
[Right in front of the exit!]  -Gary Oppa, come out!
Come out! Come out!
Come out!
Peaceful Gary has aged a lot.
Even if i die, I can't let you go...!
[How can I let you go...]
[If you want to leave I will rip all your clothes...!]
Go in! Go in!
[I have to go! Let me go.]
[Don't go! I need you.]
[Dump]
[Taller team: Gary's escape is a success!]
[Sigh...]
[Wreck]
He reformed his clothes inside!
[This is a true ten thousand won bus look.]
It's sexy. Sexy.
Gwang Soo, you have to win.
if you lose this, we can't even have a team challenge.
-You have to win. -You can do it.
Start!
You have to get in front.
You're doing good. Just throw him.
Throw him.
Look at that kid.
Throw him and leave
~pinned~
laughter from the members.
-Good job. This is fun too.
Go run. You won.
Go go go!
He won. He won.
-He won.-He's fast.
He's the best.
encountering the staffs who are obstructing them.
Everyone!
both of them are about halfway through the crowded bus!
Hyung Ha Ha, it's been a long time.
Please Gwang Soo!
-I'm begging you. You have to win, Gwang Soo.
Gwang Soo. Gwang Soo.
- That's right Gwang Soo.  -Gwang Soo!
Gwang Soo. Gwang Soo. You can do it!
That's it!
now, he only needs to press the bell...
He missed!
That's it!
Ok!
Gwang Soo, you won. You won.
He's long.
Gwang Soo come out.
Come out.
You have a mouth.
[Gwang Soo...Towel attack!]
[They're both completely exhausted]
[Aargh~]
[Bringing him back by his nostrils!]
[Fighting spirit.]
[I won't let you go.]
[Gwang Soo's time of suffering.]
Gwang Soo just come out.
Hyung!
You just have to come out.
[Plop~]
I didn't have any expectations for him anyway.
[Current score: adults team 1, children's team 1]
How is the competition going?
Staff will get off.
You will get on. The last person to be on the bus loses
Everyone goes in together.
You worked hard.
Wow there really was a lot of them.
There were a lot.
Thank you. I'm sure it's hard, but it's the last game so please cheer up.
A thank you to the staff and people who came down to help <3
Let's go.
The men aboard the bus.
Everyone. I'm Song Ji Hyo.
Fighting! Red team!
[This much is okay~]
Hello. I'm Jessica from Girl's Generation.
Please help us.
Jessica! Jessica!
if they are comparing the cheers, obviously Child Team's Jessica is the winner!
Air conditioning is coming out, but still.
The heat. Heat from people.
We have to win.
Keep in mind that Jong Kook is here.
Like an idiot I came here.
Yes, Khun is here.
Let's win! Fighting!
Let's win!
This is the final game to determine who will be the winners and losers.
Fighting!
They're coming. They're coming.
They're coming in.
~nervous~
One by one they all re-enter the bus.
Please help us.
I like everyone here. please take care of me well.
Thank you
Just be comfortable.
Jong Kook is strong.
no, no im not. ~ both teams are trying to gain sympathy from the crew. ~  he likes to show off his strength.
No, it's not like that
Is everyone ready?
Please take care of us!
Yes!
Fighting!
Start!
You can't pinch!
Once it begins, the rear of the bus too...
Only grabbing SukJin in their battle!
Slowly, Nichkun.
They're plan is weird.
HaHa, Grabbed Gwang Soo as well!
In the front of the bus is a duel between the two pretty boys. <3
Hey. Hey.
They're planning something weird.
It's the last person to leave right?
[Since the last person off the bus loses, it's every man for himself!]
[On one side, there's Jae Suk and Gary]
[Jae Suk and Gary are tightly holding each other's clothes]
[Embarassment!]
[Goodness, goodness, goodness. . .]
[What are you doing there, hyung-nim?]
[Once again, it's Jae Suk, who won't let go, even in death]
[Gary approaches the exit!]
[Gary, who becomes topless as soon as he steps onto this bus...]
[What's going on here, hyung-nim!]
Just let me off!
[But he's so close to getting out...!]
What on earth are you doing...? [Oh my...]
[Rip~]
[This is crazy!]
[Gary escapes first!]
SEXY~~~
[Don't look at me...
-Get off!-Ok, I'll step off the bus, too!
[Jae Suk escapes second.]
[Looks just like a spiritual man...]
...I'm- [On another side, Suk Jin is firmly caught]
[Stretch!]
[Attacking Suk Jin's weakness, his nose, again!]
It's hot. Hot. Engine. Engine.
[He's sitting above the hot engine.]
[Huh?]
[I've well and truly caught Suk Jin!]
[Even looking like this, it feels good to have escaped the bus...]
[They can't move an inch]
I'll hurry up and go.
Hurry up and get out.
[Haha attempts to escape!]
Take him with you. Take him out.
Come out!
-Hyung! -Suk Jin hyung!
-Hold on a second...-Suk Jin hyung![A situation that's beyond description]
That's too much!
Too much!
Hyung Suk Jin!
Come out!
I want to go out too, but I'm stuck.
-I'm stuck. / -Hey, move it! [You sure talk a lot for someone who's stuck...]
Are you disregarding your eldest brother?
Don't you have an elder brother?!
[Thinking of his elder brother, he takes his burdensome shoes and...]
[The socks impart a youthful sensation]
Jae Suk!
-Hey, Jae Suk! -Why? What is it?
Yell at him!
Seriously, you...! [The second hyung scolds him in Suk Jin's stead]
Don't you respect your hyungs?! [Kwang Soo and Haha almost reach the exit]
Don't you have any hyungs?!
[The short hyung keeps yanking his hair today]
[Sock attack.]
Don't do it! Hyung!
...I'll get off the bus.
Hey, Jae Suk! Jae Suk!
-Out, out, out! Out! -Hyung!
Hey, we can't get off back here! For the love of God, just step out! [Could fall asleep, if this goes on]
[Rip~]
Come out! Just come out, first.
I'm on my way!
I'll get off! [Without meaning to, the topless bus claims Kwang Soo]
I'll go out.
...just leave, quickly, would you?!
That's right! Eject them, eject them! [Haha and Kwang Soo simultaneously escape the bus]
Sexyyyyy~
[You can come over to dress yourself, as well]
Joong Ki oppa, come over here! [The handsome men are still in front of the bus!]
What are you guys doing?
Come out!
Jae Suk!
You guys hurry up and get out.
What are you doing, Hyung? Come out!
Hey send Nichkhun.
Come out. Come out.
I have to block him.
I don't think we can fight now...
That's it! Suk Jin hyung, that's good!
Oppa, our team has to win.
Did everyone leave?
Leave, leave!
Leave, leave! [Joong Ki plans a different way of escaping!]
Hey Nichkun come help me.
[Nichkun is able to help Suk Jin!]
-What! -Nichkhun!
[Situation where Jong Kook needs to escape fast!]
Don't block the way! Move, move, move! [Nichkhun is moving to block Jong Kook!]
[Nichkhun, by a hair's breadth! He blocks Jong Kook with his left arm!]
[From here it's a battle of strength!!]
[I can't just stay still!]
Why are you taking off my shoe?
Hyung, hurry up and come out.
[Jong Kook vs Nichkun]
Oppa come out.
Oppa, come out, come out!
[Will it be Jong Kook first? Will it be Nichkun and Suk Jin first?]
[Wow, Nichkhun. With just your left arm, Jong Kook was...!!]
slip~
Hurry up and come out!
[Jong Kook and staff escape together!]
Countless bare spots.
Hyung, are you okay?
the unlucky(?) staff taht followed them also feels giddy
Are you okay?
He's a monster. A monster.
Team So In wins!
Wins! Received 50 thousand won prize money!
bearing in mind that the child team is quietly leading, all that is left to decide the winner is the golden pig!
Are you okay? You seem lost.
I am really sleepy.
Ji Hyo, this about this.
If we lose we have to do the punishment and go home.
Suddenly it is a must to stay energetic!
How many golden pigs do they have?
It's here.
Open the roof and two pigs.
Rooftop.
"Penetrate the roof" sounds like a hint~
Break the roof and two pigs.
A place where you can see the sky.
The observatory.
We have to find it.
Instructions came.
This is a game with no end.
Break the roof and two pigs.
do we have to go to the roof quickly after receiving this order?  ~child team also started raking their brains...~
I don't think it's just a rooftop.
I think it can only be the rooftop.
If you break the roof it's the rooftop.
Let's go.
Let's think about it first.
Should we go out?
We really have to win.
Roof?
Is it that?
[Bingo! They found the observatory!]
Break the roof.
Break the roof. Break the roof.
Hyung! Ah Ah!
We are at the Science Hall.
There should be a place where we can see the sky. The roof would open there.
-To see the stars.-He is really smart.-Really?
You are right again.
There is. I saw an observatory.
-Right? -Be quiet.
Earlier outside I looked and looked.
are we going to start running?  ~Moving towards the place of the observatory~
Jessica has a pretty stride.
One step ahead of finding the observatory station.
Its there! Its there!
There it is.
Sprinting
What is that?
That's right I saw it. That's what I was talking about since the beginning.
I saw it here.
two teams sprint towards a common destination.
Hyung, behind the building.
they are here too hurry up!
The kids are coming so hurry up.
We are one step behind.
Which team will be able to find the 2 golden pigs first>  Going to the same place
I can't have poor stamina.
Red team enters the observatory first
Here it is.
ah! penetrated the roof
Here it is. Here it is.
So where are the golden pigs?
where?
trying to beat the childs team...
Blue team now enters the observatory.
[Just then!]
[Golden pig]
[Both teams see the golden pig!]
Distant...
I think it's right.
[Joong Ki just goes up.]
Still quite a distance.
Nichkun. Nichkun.
how do we get up there?
How are we supposed to go up?
[Come and get me~]
On top of the roof. On top of the roof.
But there's nowhere to go up.
-[The golden pig]  -[Where they are]
Hyung! Hyung!
Over here.
-Ok -Hyung, block Gary.
Block Gary.
Gary, who followed Gwang Soo and SukJin
"highkick" Gwang Soo who climbed up to the roof.
[The golden pig is watching]
Looking around~
It's not here.
No way of getting to the golden pig.
Now realized how high the golden pig is...
Let me think.
[Jong Kook found something!]
[A control for the roof!]
[Switch On.]
[Runs to the roof as soon as he presses it!]
[It starts to move.]
[If the roof closes you can get the golden pig!]
[The golden pig that come closer and closer.]
We have to close the roof so go up.
Go up. Up.
I closed the roof, but how do I go up?
[There's not much time left!]
the roof is closing fast.
It's coming. Hold him.
Hold him!
Hold him.
How do I go up?
Behind. Behind.
That's right.
That's right!
Sadness... Happiness..
[No!]
That's right!
It belongs to SukJin!.
Wow!
I closed the roof.
[Team Dae-In acquires 1 golden pig]
Collapsed... ~ Did you find it?
Close the roof like that
What to do...
[Now there is only 1 golden pig left!]
Ji Hyo and Jongkook go to different rooms to find the last one.
There earlier on the other side...
there was a pig where the roof opened.
Found the controls!
It's one the roof again?
Is there anyone from our team?
Oppa!
[Jong Kook, again turns the button on.]
the roof opens slowly.
Is the golden pig really here...
Oppa! Oppa Jae Suk!
Oppa Jae Suk!
Frustrated
JaeSuk investigates it.
Oppa! Hurry!
[There's nothing?!]
Back to looking for the golden pig.
If its not there then there's no where else to hide it.
The last gold pig is actually in here.
Gwang Soo missed it.
[At this time, Jae Suk...?]
[Huh? Just the lid...?]
Of course its like this...
This time SukJin goes towards the golden pig
Short teams HaHa comes over
There's nothing. Nothing!
[Pretending not to see to make HaHa go away.]
smart 40 year old, Sukjin tried to get rid of Haha by pretending not to see it.
[He's not leaving...?]
Hey! It's here!
Drags HaHa away!
[It's on that side!]
To get the last Golden pig
It's in there.
Fierce Battle
Gary goes in for the pig..
Who does the golden pig belong too?!
[Ji Hyo got it!]
[Team Dae-In acquires all 2 golden pigs]
SukJin and Jihyo combination success!
Race over!
after a long night
Sunrise greets the Science Museum
How many do we have?
We only have two.
If you have 500 won in there and we have 10 won then we can lose.
Right now, Ji Hyo
really wants to go home.
Can she escape today?
It's already daytime
It's time to count the 500,000 won
It's both 50 won and 10 won.
The feeling is good.
Why is there so many?
[The coins keep coming out.]
If we go over 34,000 won then we win.
Blue team needs more than 34000 won to win
34,000 won is all we need.
If there is only 10 won coins in there then we win.
Oh my..
Silver color is coming out.
Its all silver~
Let's start.
The results are hard to tell
100 won and 340 won are coming out.
[Please...]
of course
We went over.
Blue team wins!
[Bitter]
Adult team has to stay for the punishment.
[Now time to leave!]
Its time for us to leave, yay
Thank you, Thank you for the hard work.
Kids team leaves after 18 hours in the museum
The world outside
FREEDOMMM
oppa, Look at the sunrise.
1, 2, 3...
Freedom!
Today, we have to clean.
~ empty. ~  everything has to be clean before the museum opens.
[This large place...]
everyone is diligently cleaning their area
If you date a guy, you ignore him right?
I think you're right.
She does have charm.
Are you confessing your love?
Why are you cleaning like that?
~sleepily cleaning~
What is that?
Thats understandable.
He is really tired.
Sukjin has fallen asleep but with a lurking Nickhun nearby.
Hello running man! I am Kim Yuna.
I will cheer for you so run hard.
on the next episode of running man..
people will fight to win.
people will be betrayed
Strangers will be used
help will be needed.
But who will answer the call?
Find out on the next episode of running man, rman FIGHTING!