Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by iSUBS & soshisubs & RDRsubs
Today's landmark
Yongsan 'I' shopping mall
South Korea's most crowded
shopping district
Today's strongest
guest SNSD Yuri
Mission
Yuri
Tricking her
Tearful 1 vs 8 challenge
The outcome is?
Night hide-n-seek competition
in an empty shopping mall
Kid HaHa and Jihyo
strenuous battle log
Begins now
Today is another Running Man recording.
We're at Yongsan's biggest shopping mall.
Today's landmark
Yongsan 'I' shopping mall
There are 350 thousand shoppers everyday.
350 thousand shoppers in one day
This shopping mall, is really the biggest.
We're here to start Running Man.
A place with the latest
trends and high value
Last week, Joongki ...
Yes?
Last week's
hot topic was Joongki and Jihyo
... gave Jihyo a kiss on cheek.
As they recall it
both are still embarrassed about it
I have something to tell noona.
I won't call you noona in the future.
Can I say "you" instead?
And...
Carefully approaching
Sudden kiss
Gave everyone a shock
Train romance ♥
Joongki's career is going well now ...
... and now with the love
relationship, it's even better.
How many are you pushing into the drama?
Unsatisfied
This is really good.
Isn't the involved party important too?
There are two sides in a relationship
Have to listen to Jihyo's side
Let Jihyo say her perspective.
I ...
On Mondays ...
... I've got a man.
On Mondays
I already have a man
... I've got a man.
That guy
Jihyo's
shocking
announcement
Now
Gary
Jihyo
Admitting to be(?) Monday Couple
Ah, look at her.
Frantic
You only mentioned this
today, which is too selfish.
Then, which guys are you going
to meet from Tuesday to Sunday?
Jealous
Keep quiet
You heard that, right?
She already has that guy on Mondays.
There are Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday,
Friday, Saturday and Sunday left, but ...
... there isn't any spot for you.
HaHa was never
in Jihyo's heart
There won't be you.
HaHa's lonely love life
Jihyo said there won't be you.
You don't even have the right to qualify.
Cold
Fine.
Then you like her?
No, I don't.
HaHa denies any feelings
If it is a no, you have
no right to question her.
Get lost.
Who's the person, whom
is already married?
Kwangsoo looks like he
plans to frame someone.
I went to Anyang last week.
Now you're even doing
long distance slander?
Why did you go to Anyang?
Uneasy
Jongkook who stays in Anyang
I saw Jongkook when I was there.
Oh, really?
He played rubber band skipping
with children in a village.
Betrayal
explosion
Sexy girl Miss Jongkook
Working out for 15 years skipping rubber band
He jumped this high.
Rubber band skipping is an intensive exercise.
As long it's exercise, Jongkook will do it.
Kwangsoo's betrayal success
Anyhow, we have to get going.
Who is today's Running Man guest?
Is it only us?
Anyone else?
Is there a guest?
Comeback with 'Hoot'
SNSD
Yuri
* BGM = "Hoot" by SNSD
Warm welcome from the guys
Ah, Yuri came.
With her sparkling smile
Goddess Yuri
Yuri is so busy yet she
is still able to come.
Yuri is busy with overseas activities
Yuri ...
N:o 1 on Oricon charts
Started a SNSD fever in Japan
They are really popular in Japan right now.
We stirred things up slightly in Japan,
and then we returned to Korea.
Agrees
Slightly?
Yuri, you're the best.
She didn't even deny it herself.
Face flushing
You definitely stirred things up there.
It's not just us.
Korean celebrities are popular in Japan.
Me too?
Ah that, well ...
I'm not?
You should not have asked ~
Kwangsoo, say something.
Kwangsoo is being shy.
Kwangsoo has been shy from the start
Kwangsoo, greet her.
Hello.
Kwangsoo really likes Yuri.
Framer Kwangsoo is a fan of Yuri
Yeah ...
Kwangsoo ...
Do you have any information
that will put Yuri in bad light?
I have nothing.
That isn't fair.
Kwangsoo forgets about the plot
against Yuri when in front of her
He's protecting Yuri.
Please look after me.
Ah, really ...
At this hour it's empty and ...
... the shopping mall will soon close.
Jihyo, in an empty mall which
store do you wish to go to?
Shoe shops.
Shoes.
Yuri?
I ... grocery store.
Food.
Yeah.
That was simple.
What about Gary?
Me?
Of course Gary will go to
Yes.
I'll go to the shoe shop.
the shoe store
Why?
You already
know why
Jihyo ~
Jihyo, what's your shoe size?
Even asked for her shoe size.
Isn't today Monday?
* Running Man is recorded on Mondays
Recording day
Today is Monday
Yeah, that's right.
Soon, after midnight, it'll be Tuesday.
You don't have much time left.
Like I said before ... Eh, nothing.
Earlier?
Two ...
The opening is right now
when was "before"...?
And their awkward smiles
Suddenly everyone is nervous
What's with everyone?
That's it.
Rushing with the closing
Can someone do it for me?
Frantic search for a substitute MC
I'm having trouble ...
Why is he
acting like that?
He was going to talk about how
these two reminded him ...
* Announcer Na Kyungeun is Jaesuk's wife
... about how he and
Kyungeun used to date.
That's how people date.
That's right.
Yuri is clueless
All members have this awkward smile
And look nervous
What exactly happened?
Going back in time
Prior to the opening
1 hour ago
Soon we'll start filming today’s episode.
Everyone
has
gathered
Except
Yuri
The reason I brought you here ...
... there will be a 1:8 challenge.
Today's
Trick the guest
Doesn't everyone know if they
already watched the broadcasts?
Worried
There will be a guest later.
The guest is the target
Who is it?
SNSD Yuri.
Oh my gosh
What to do?
Kwangsoo, what are you doing?
Kwangsoo's face blushed instantly
Do you like her?
Look at his red face.
Kwangsoo really likes her.
Kwangsoo is already nervous
even before meeting Yuri
Do you like her that much?
Well, that ...
Just thinking about it makes him happy
I think he likes her a lot.
You like her as a woman?
No, it's ...
Try to like Jihyo noona.
Instantly
Serious
Can't hide ~
So how will we do it?
With her recent album activities in Japan ...
... she hasn't watched the episodes with
1 vs 8, so Yuri doesn't know about it.
But how will we pull it off?
Solve 10 riddles in 100 seconds.
Tricking Yuri
While solving 10 riddles in 100 seconds, they
must fail to answer the questions given by Yuri
Basically a speed quiz game.
Speed quiz game.
10 in 100 seconds?
Yes.
The catch is that ...
... you can't answer correctly
when Yuri is giving the questions.
But you have to answer ...
Answer the other members questions
correctly and Yuri can answer those too
... correctly for your own riddles.
So when we are asking the
questions we can't get it wrong.
Can we pass?
No pass.
Additionally
Can't skip any questions
We can't skip a question.
We have to start, before Yuri arrives.
Are the riddles difficult?
They are.
Since the questions are so difficult
the answers are revealed to them
Is it difficult?
That's the problem.
That means we also will
get difficult questions.
That's what I say.
How are we supposed to guess correctly
for 'Coiled far-infrared radiating heater'?
Very difficult
'Marquis diamond'
How are we supposed to explain that?
There's more than one round,
there is also round two.
In addition
The main subject for each round is different
What is this?
How are we going to illustrate this?
We must...
memorize all of this...?
That means we have
to answer all correctly.
Memorize the answers in order.
It's too difficult.
That why
The riddles comes in a certain order
Ah, they'll be asked in a fixed order?
Everyone should memorize a portion.
Everyone memorize.
Let's have Yuri go last.
Strategy
Decide when Yuri will go
There's nine of us.
If Yuri goes first, she'll do it twice.
With 10 questions If Yuri is the first
she'll also present the last question
Right.
Strategy
Answer the first question right
but guess the last question wrong
Let's answer the 10th question wrong.
When Yuri starts ...
... Mannequin.
Is it my turn then?
Sukjin hyung's TV is?
45-inch flat screen TV
Unison
How did all of you know that?
Only Sukjin should know that.
How did you know that?
If Yuri finds out she's being tricked
the members
lose
We can't let Yuri find out we're tricking her.
Next is Jihyo.
4th question
'Infrared Coil Heater' is the answer
Kwangsoo, you brought this because it
was cold while we were filming outdoors.
Heater ~
Where is it made? ... Ah, no no.
Trying to say the brand name?
I'm really worried about her,
she might laugh too much.
Jihyo...
She makes silly mistakes.
Worrisome...
I think I'll laugh too much.
You used this while we
were filming outdoors.
Jihyo's second attempt
Heater.
It emits hot air.
But that thing has ...
Coil ...
Stammer on purpose
That's too ...
Coil far-infrared ...
Are you filming a sitcom?
Being over-dramatic...
is also troublesome
Won't Yuri know this?
Will Yuri fall for this?
No, she won't.
I have to be mean to her,
until the end of first round.
I heard that Yuri is the
smartest among SNSD.
Warning
That time I was tricked and you
randomly guessed the words ...
... I didn't realize I was tricked.
Because you were so funny, I was
distracted and didn't suspect anything.
Strategy
Distract her by being funny
We understand.
Then we need to have
some good reactions.
Strategy
Members would have to reactions
Doing it one by one.
You have 5 minutes left.
The situation is still uneasy Yuri arrives in 5 minutes
Really?
We don't have much time
left, so let's go quickly.
She'll arrive in 5 minutes.
Everyone remember your parts?
Which is the sequence?
Remembering their sequence is the key
Who is second?
I'm second.
I don't remember.
I'm doing this on.
Coiled far-infrared radiating heater.
I feel sorry for Yuri,
but what can we do?
Will they be able to deceive Yuri?
Exactly.
So it was planned like this.
Will they
earn their Running Balls?
What's there to be sorry about?
Yuri, I'm so sorry.
Joongki, so you understand now?
Battle
Finally
the time has come
Opening without revealing their plot
She is unaware
Yuri
Yuri and SNSD have been
doing promotions in Japan.
But now they have a break and ...
Must deceive Yuri
in order to get Running Balls
... today she'll be with Running
Man at the shopping mall.
Are you ready?
Yeah ~
Let's go in.
Guess the answer from other's actions
Battle of 1:8 begins now
We're now inside the shopping ball.
Shopping ball?
Did you just say "﻿Shopping ball "?
You must be obsessed with Running Balls.
Yuri also knows that
we have to get the ball.
Did the most punishments
in Running Man (9 times)
Without a Running Ball, you'll
face immediate punishment.
Have you watched this show before?
Yes, I've watched it.
Due to activities in Japan
we thought you hadn't watched it?
Not all of it.
So you didn't watch the recent episodes?
That's a relief ~
That's a relief
Unknowingly
Jaesuk reveals his thoughts
So what's today's first game
to get a Running Ball?
It's the Running Man speed quiz.
First fake mission
Running Man
speed quiz game
We have a master of speed quiz here.
Joongki is a speed quiz master.
Yuri, are you good at quiz games?
Yuri still hasn't realized
They are setting the stage
Me? I just do it.
Modest
I think she'll be good at it.
Tony was here last week's, but ...
Yes ~
... he ﻿didn't manage to get a Running Ball at all.
Unfortunate for him.
That was unfortunate for him.
For today we don't want
that to happen to anyone.
Yes.
We decided to make it easier for
everyone to get a Running Ball.
Sounds good ~
Is it because Yuri is here today?
It kind of seems like it.
A fake rule to deceive Yuri
So are we competing against the staff?
Thank you.
You against us?
All of us can get a ball?
Yuri's the only one who doesn't know the real rules
Yes.
That's great.
You'll be given 100 seconds each.
Serious
Answer 10 riddles within the time limit.
Fake
rule
They have to answer 10
riddles in 100 seconds
Isn't this too easy?
10 riddles in 100 sec. is too easy.
So we have 10 sec. per question.
You'll have a total of 3 chances.
Fake
rule
Total of three chances, but
they won't be allowed to pass
3 chances.
If we succeed in the first round,
we'll get Running Balls, right?
But you can't skip a question.
Yuri is really our lucky star.
But it's actually
Yuri against the rest of them
In what order shall we go?
Decide yourselves.
Let's have Yuri go first
What?
Yes, since you're our guest.
Yuri will go first.
Yes.
The meeting room
before the recording
Shouldn't we change when Yuri will go?
We can't let Yuri get suspicious.
Since it's Yuri's first time ...
We'll guess correct on her first question.
I'll go next.
Wouldn't it be bad if I was first
and I got stuck at the question?
Worrying
No, it's okay.
Feel like she's the smartest.
I'll go last then?
HaHa you'll go last.
First ...
Yuri stands first.
Yuri, come over here
Let's try this ...
But they will line up according
to the pre-planned sequence
Everyone else just stand where they want to.
Yuri will be first, followed by Jongkook.
Just stand somewhere, hurry.
Did they
from the start
get the sequence wrong?
Yeah, just stand somewhere.
Just stand somewhere, hurry.
Don't feel pressured.
This way
That way
So we have to guess the answer?
We just have to play the speed quiz.
Sukjin totally forgot his place
Joongki, stand here.
Come on guys, find your spot.
One at a time will try
to explain the word.
Hyung, are you
supposed to be here?
We're not allowed to skip a question.
You can go out there first and ...
Is this how we start?
In the end brainy
Joongki settles it
Yes.
The starting people are worrying me.
This is ...
Why is HaHa messing up the sequence?
Come here.
You're just trying to stand beside Yuri.
The mob of 8
Will they be able to trick Yuri till the end?
I just wanted to be near her.
Shall we stand here while guessing?
Stand in a line by that rectangle.
Ah, yes ~
Yuri stands there and then she returns.
Fake
rule
If Yuri can make some answer correct, she
rejoins the line and it's the next one's turn
Then the next person do it.
Will only Jongkook oppa answer?
No, everyone will try to answer.
All of them can try to answer
Everybody?
Ah, easy easy.
Easy ~
Yuri, for you
it'll be hard
Alright, Yuri ...
Yes.
Fighting ~
Let's get all the riddles right.
The first rounds question are related
to something in the shopping mall.
Shopping ~
Can I describe it with words as well?
That's right.
Start.
* Jongkook's manager is holding the sheets
Mannequin
Like this ... to display clothes.
Mannequin ~
In unison
The first question
Successfully answering according to plan
Cheerful
45'' flat screen TV
Ah, Sukjin hyung ...
... you told me you bought that TV.
What?
Sukjin, the TV you have at home.
During the meeting
As discussed with Sukjin
45-inch flat-screen TV?
Correct.
What?
Blurry
The TV you bought.
Wall-mounted TV ... digital TV.
45-inch color TV.
... color TV.
What?
45-inch flat-screen TV.
They aren't confident
but they still got it right
Wow, they
are good
Bidet
Something that everyone often uses.
It's not a-idet.
Eh?
Bidet ~
Not a-idet, but b-idet.
Dumbfounded
How did you get that right?
Coiled far-infrared
radiating heater
Kwangsoo ...
What is it?
They planned to have Kwangsoo
answer this question
Say something, we're
running out of time.
The heater that you use to
warm yourself during winter.
What?
This...
explanation is seriously...
Heater ~
It's a heater ...
... but not the ultraviolet kind.
What does it look like?
Heater ...
... but not the ultraviolet kind.
Long answer is hard to remember
Infrared?
Is it coiled?
Infrared heater.
Infrared hand heater.
Coiled far-infrared heater?
A hand heater?
An infrared mat.
Coiled infrared heater.
If they don't get this riddle
then Yuri will be the winner
A coiled infrared heater.
A hand heater.
An infrared mat.
Far-infrared heater.
Coil far-infrared radiating heater.
Sukjin can't stand it anymore Shouts the answer
Yes, that's right.
That was hard, seriously.
Aigoo, you couldn't
memorize that!
It's too difficult
No interest
for 3 months
How should I describe this?
Hurry up.
That ...
... installments.
3 months ~
He only said installment and they immediately...
No interest for the first 3 months.
Well done.
Yuri got it now.
All-in-one DVD
home theater
You watch this at home.
You watch TV at home.
A movie.
You watch movies at
home on video or DVD.
... video and DVD.
Huh!
As expected she's quick-witted
Home Theater!
All-in-one DVD ~
They're going to be exposed if this continues
DVD "blank" ...
A home theater.
All-in-one theater.
Yuri, that's not the answer.
All-in-one DVD home theater.
I said that.
LED-functioning
pest control lamp
Jaesuk, I told you this before.
Jaesuk, my son was badly
bitten by mosquitoes ...
... so I used this.
Insect repellent.
That's right.
But what is it called?
You mean the LED-functioning pest control lamp.
Correct ~
Even if you heard it twice
still a hard phrase to remember
My kid got many mosquito bites.
LED ...
... functioning lamp-pfhh.
Functioning ...
... lamp-pfhh.
Jaesuk suddenly burst into laughter
Functioning ...
Just for Sukjin's son
LED-functioning insects repellent?
Why are they
like that?
LED-functioning pest control lamp.
Controls his laughter
Correct.
This situation is ridiculous
LED-functioning pest control lamp.
Correct.
Naive
Yuri didn't notice anything
Regular sale
What's happening today
in the department store?
Bargain sales.
In unison
It's not that.
Regular sales ~
The way that they rehearsed it
Wow
Impressive
teamwork
Marquis
Diamond
How much time is left?
Gary hyung ...
... when we were all
together on Jihyo's birthday.
I bought shoes for her
and you bought this.
Diamond ~
Diamonds for a
birthday present?
Marquise diamonds, right?
Monday Couple suddenly started
to give diamonds as gifts(?)
What is this?
Ceramic pot set
10th and final question
Yuri's turn
Our moms use ...
... this pot, oops.
Only 10 seconds left.
Can they avoid answering
Yuri's question correct?
Yuri
Running Man
... oops.
10 sec left.
It's okay, just hurry.
In the kitchen ...
Trying her best to describe
A pot.
What kind of pot?
There's many kinds of pots.
Nickel silver pot.
Not silver pot.
Stainless steel pot.
* 'Stain' in Korean is short for 'stainless steel pot'
They were answering so well before
... different kinds.
Now they just guessing wrongly
Not silver.
Stainless steel pot ~
Ceramic.
Ah, it was ceramic?
Ceramic ~
Everyone is acting as if it was a pity
Ceramic was too hard.
You should have given an easier one.
LED-functioning pest control lamp
But he could guess that
How could we have guessed that it was ceramic?
This is hard.
Naive
Ah, Yuri ...
You failed the first try.
Why blame me, I did well.
Not bad ~
Encouraging her first
Yuri did well ~
Yuri got a lot right.
But ...
... ceramic was too difficult.
Ceramic was to hard.
Why are the questions so hard
like the infrared radiation?
So Yuri won't be suspicious
they blame it on the hard questions
That's right.
Mentioned it before.
You and I ...
How did you know?
The thing, you know it ...
I guess they researched ...
The questions were based on what has
happened to the members of Running Man.
So this was what the
phone interview was for?
* Sukjin is lying, there was no phone interview
... the phone interview was for?
Ah...
So that's how...
You gave a diamond as a present?
What the ...
When we gathered for her birthday.
Tossing around lies
I gave her a small one for her birthday.
Really?
A diamond as a birthday present?
It’s a Marquise diamond.
It wasn't anything expensive.
Showing off?
What's a marquise diamond?
An octagonal diamond.
That's so nice.
Really?
Jealous
Are you envious?
Yes.
Then you just have to date Gary.
However he’s not free on Mondays,
you can only date him the other days.
On Mondays he belongs to Jihyo.
Do you really like Gary oppa?
Could she be lying in a broadcast?
That was close.
We have two rounds left?
After Yuri failed as planned
Running Man round 1
Success
Did we get 3 questions right?
Ah, we were so close.
It’s alright Yuri, fighting.
Sorry, I'll do better next time.
Let's send Yuri to the back this time.
But we have to have a good plan.
Wow, ﻿because I did one thing wrong ...
No, it's okay.
... Jongkook is like "Send Yuri to the back".
No, that’s not it.
Jongkook just followed the plan
and send Yuri to the back
How could you say that?
Is that how you treat a girl?
No, but ...
Ceramic was too hard.
Hurt
Actually, ceramic was too hard.
I was trying to reduce her burden,
being at the front is too stressful.
Part 2 of the plan
Putting Yuri at the back
Jongkook just meant that at the back
you only need to explain one problem.
That's right.
Then we win.
Yuri did two last time.
We have to reduce her burden.
Right.
What's the topic for the second round?
It' dance.
Ah, dancing.
Excuse me, can I change my clothes first?
Sudden
situation
I'm really sweaty right now.
And I also need to go to the toilet.
Can't I?
Jaesuk's sudden action leave everyone bewildered
Do you feel warm?
It's too hot.
Okay, go change.
I'll be back soon.
I’m just going to the toilet.
The cameraman can stay here.
Why did Jaesuk suddenly
need to go to the toilet?
Script writer
The answers to the questions
Write it down.
I can’t remember it..
He forgot all the answers
I forgot my sequence.
Same situation here
Memorizing what's written on Joongki's palm
What a pity.
How will we get everything right?
How will they do it?
By memorizing it with exhausting effort
Isn't that person Baek Boram?
Luckily Yuri is still clueless
All of a sudden, I couldn't remember anything.
Because I was trying to
play without this method.
"Kamarinskaya".
You wash your hair with rinse.
* Sounds like kamarinskaya (a dance)
I'm not going to remember that.
Later
Why did you change in the middle of filming?
To prevent Yuri from suspecting
Jaesuk really changed his shirt
I ...
Yeah?
... took some time.
You changed into thicker
clothes, weren't you hot?
Didn't he say it was hot? So why
did he change into a long sleeve?
Exactly.
It doesn't seem like you
went back only to change.
You went to the bathroom and ..
Forced to say
I went to take a dump as an excuse
I went to take a dump, sorry.
Yuri is here, so ...
... stop talk about those things.
It’s a normal thing.
Why are you sweating so much?
What's wrong with you today?
During times of emergency
showing the witty MC Yoo
He said he had problems in the bathroom.
It's possible.
Are we ready now?
Let’s start, everyone in position.
Now you're moving on to the 2nd category.
The theme is dance.
A noun related to dancing
in the 2nd round of Speed Quiz
The theme is dance.
Taking a peek again
And this time ...
... only actions and mimicking voices
are allowed to explain the words.
This is hard, only gestures are allowed.
It’s not like we know all those dances.
Let’s start.
We only need to answer
10 questions correct ...
... ﻿within 100 seconds.
Let’s start ~
Positioning themselves according to the plan
Let's try getting in line.
No, that's not it.
Nervous Jaesuk forgot his position
The positioning seems incomprehensible this time too
I don't want to go to the front.
If the smartest Joongki is like this ...
Is the order that important?
Hurry up and pick a spot.
The order is really important.
I'll be the 6th.
Jaesuk's tongue keeps slipping today
I'm the 8th.
No, you aren't.
Oppa I think I can do
well, I'll be the first.
What...
first position?
... I'll be first.
Excuse me?
Can't I be the first?
They memorized everything in order
thinking Yuri would be last
Going to mess it up
at the first question
No ...
There’s still another chance,
how about the next time.
Panicking
Ah, you ...
Could it be?
They got caught?
Ah, you keep ...
... doubting me oppa?
You keep doubting me oppa?
What
a
close
save
How could you say that?
No, that's not it.
You stay here and only
need to get one word right.
Innocent Yuri has been fooled completely
Okay, I understand.
If you want to be first then go ahead.
It'll be alright.
What is this?
You can if you want to, but
then you have to do it twice.
No, it’s alright.
Okay oppa, I'll just stay here then.
That’s good.
You only have to get it right at the end.
Yuri, I'm sorry
Wait a minute, Yuri is the last ...
We need to get 10 questions right, so
Jongkook has to do it one more time.
Yes, I'll do it twice.
You better get it right.
I got it.
Nagging at Jongkook
to avoid Yuri's suspicion
He has danced a lot so he should be fine.
Yuri, that’s what he said ...
"﻿If you lose, you can forget about
holding on to the Running Ball".
Why are you like this only to me?
We won't lose
because of me
I’m looking forward to
Jongkook oppa’s dance.
Understood.
Yuri
Running Man
Now ...
Go inside.
Move back a little.
Fighting ~
Rule
Trick Yuri till the ens so the 8 Running
Man members can get Running balls
I'm in trouble if we don't win this time.
Ready ... go.
Salsa
Salsa.
Even before the explanation...?
How did you get it right?
Salsa ~
He just pinched his flesh and
got it right
No matter what the rush is
he should have waited for the explanation to finish
How did you get it right?
Great ~
Halo freeze
A type of B-boy dance
'Halo Freeze'
How do I explain this? Hold on.
Hip Hop!
Dance convention candidate Gary
showing off his skills
No ~
B-boy ~
A freeze.
Halo freeze ~
Well...
actually
this is halo freeze
Halo freeze ~
I know all this.
Kamarinskaya
Halo freeze ~
Oh?!
I know all this.
What...
was that again?
Explain ~
I'll do Kamarinskaya.
That's fine ~
You should dance a Russian folk-dance.
You're going to say the answer?
He practiced the dance
You dance, then I'll say Kamarinskaya.
Blank~
Explain it.
Didn't you
practice just now
Explain.
Totally
blanked
out
What is it?
Head spin ~
What?
Head spin.
What
Head ~
Kamarinskaya.
Correct
Okay.
What is it?
The explanation was weird
But Jaesuk still said the memorized answer
Kamarinskaya.
Okay.
This time it's really obvious
Was it right?
It's correct ~
Can they through with it?
Was it right?
On purpose
It's correct ~
Okay.
Yuri is unable to tell what's going on
Was it right?
Exposed...
That's it, he got it right.
Was too anxious
Yah, this ...
Traditional
exorcism dance
Yah, this ...
Traditional exorcism dance.
That's right.
Just raised his arms and got the right answer
Traditional exorcism dance?
Traditional exorcism dance.
This is easy, exorcism dance.
Luckily
Yuri is only focused on answering
Ocho Atras
Ocho atras
A woman's tango move of back
steps and turns than form an 8
You have to dance it.
Hurry up and dance.
Use gestures, you can't talk.
Biting on the
stem of a rose
Smile?
Tango ~
Ocho atras ~
That's right.
What was that?
Dizzy headed
Ocho atras.
Ah, really?
I learned that when I as learning English.
Hurry ~
Samba
Samba.
In unison
Samba ~
One word and everyone got it right
"Oh~"
Samba ~
Ridiculous
HaHa hyung, you know this one.
What is it?
That one time ...
What explanation is that?
South America ~
Cucaracha.
Correct.
Cucaracha
A Latin dance step where
the feet are close together
Cucaracha.
That's correct.
Ah, cucaracha.
A strange atmosphere
Bharata
natyam
Bharatanatyam
Indian classic solo
dance move for women
Bharatanatyam ~
Is this right?
It's an Indian dance.
Pretends
to know
Rumba
Rumba ~
Yuri accidentally said the answer out loud
Pretends not to hear it
Rumba.
(Rum) Ba Ba Ba ~
What is that?
Members
Playing dumb
Chacha dance
Illustrates more seriously
Blues.
It's okay, explain it slowly.
Except rumba All other dances are named
Blues.
No ~
Tango ~
Waltz ~
Cha Cha Cha.
Answering but avoiding the right answer
No, two syllables.
Two syllables?
Dance.
Salsa.
This time
Shouting dances with two syllables
Swing.
That's salsa.
Swing my baby.
Cha Cha.
No.
Why can't you explain this?
How do I explain that?
What was it?
End of a bumpy 2nd round
8 Running Man members
Succeed
Rumba.
Ah, what do we do now?
Only left with the 3rd round then victory for
the 8 Running Men
Rumba has to be a little slow.
Rumba is too difficult ~
The problem is so difficult.
It's difficult when you don't know the answer
Did we get 8 right?
I suddenly remembered kamarinskaya.
Who got kamarinskaya right?
Jaesuk hyung.
You got that right?
He danced that in Infinite Challenge.
I danced that.
Lying that he learned
this dance in another TV-show
You did kamarinskaya?
I learned kamarinskaya ...
... and he said rinse.
Washing his hair.
* Kkama is wash in Korean
You did it, right?
Wash ~
Kamarinskaya just came into my mind.
An outrageous lie, but
he is still able to say it smoothly
Ah~ That's how
he got it correct
When ﻿Jongkook pinched his flesh ...
* Sal (flesh) + Sa (four) = Salsa
I pinched my flesh and showed four fingers.
Salsa ~
Wow, that's really the best.
What was Jihyo doing?
Ocho atras.
How did you get that?
Suspicious?
Because she already knew the answer
What's ocho atras?
Isn't this basic knowledge?
Arrogant
Cheating his way...
I know ocho atras too.
That's incredible.
Do we have one chance left?
These people are...
really outstanding
Using only gestures...
they knew each other's thoughts
Only touched his hair
and they shouted Kamarinskaya
Teamwork
But one thing
Yuri doesn't know ...
... is that this teamwork
is to fool Yuri in a 1:8 game
Let's do the final 3rd round.
Now
is the 3rd and last round
We can do it.
Let's do a cheer.
1, 2, 3 ... fighting.
This time Yuri gets to choose
where she wants to stand.
Stand wherever you want to.
I'll be the third.
3rd ~
Let Yuri choose where to stand
so that she won't get suspicious
Let's go this way.
Jihyo stay there and I'll go here.
Okay ~
Are we done?
It's difficult.
It's okay.
All of you are so good.
HaHa ...
1st challenger
HaHa
This rounds theme is animals.
Can we explain with words?
Animals will be easy.
No, you can't.
Only use gestures and pseudo-words
Start.
Spotted lizard
* Eremias Argus (aka Mongolia racerunner) is a species
of lizard found in Mongolia, China, Korea, and Russia
Snake.
Lizard.
Wasting time naming other snakes...?
Cobra ~
Wh...
at...?
Viper?
What is that?
Aren't they getting it wrong on purpose to delay time?
Shark.
But they doesn't seem to know the answer
Muddled~
Shark ~
Oh my gosh
Might as well turn around and take a look
What's that?
Spotted lizard?
Is that right?
You saw "Animal Farm", didn't you?
That's right.
Wow ...
Unbelievable.
You got it right.
It was on the show "Animal Farm".
Ceratosaurus
That ~
A cute version of a carnivorous dinosaur
Tyrannosaurus?
A friend ~
Ceratosaurus.
That's right.
Oh that's right, Ceratosaurus
Oh my God
Tyrannosaurus'
friend is Ceratosaurus?
Dazed after answering
Weird Speed Quiz
Of course lastly Yuri's question
We can succeed this time.
The problem is
finishing it to the end without Yuri noticing
The Running Ball
is ours
We can succeed this time.
Irrawaddy
dolphin
First ...
Irrawaddy dolphin
About 2m in length, known for it's round
head and absence of snout. Lives around
Myanmar's Irrawaddy River
What is that?﻿
Crane? Rabbit?
Whale ~
What?
Crane? Rabbit?
Of course that's wrong
Whale ~
Whale.
Two ..
* Yuri means the pronunciation of 2
but they think of it as number 2
What?
Two whales?
Do Re Mi Fa So ...
Describes every syllable
La?
Whale la ?
Two ...
Yuri, keep going.
Yuri explains well and calmly
Do Re Mi Fa So ...
Godzilla.
Ra.
Yeah.
Irra Dolphin?
Oh, almost there.
Close to the correct answer 'Irrawaddy Dolphin'
They don't know the answer
They lose if they accidentally say the right answer
Yuri might win the 1:8 challenge
But what kind of dolphin?
Deer?
Tries hard to describe till the end
Whale?
Gorilla.
Spouting whale.
Irra dolphin?
Ah, be quiet and slowdown.
Anger
Be quiet and slowdown.
Two and then Sol.
Yuri, are you angry?
Take your time.
It's okay, take your time.
After Sol is?
Do Re Mi Fa So ...
La ~
Irra and then ..
* I (two) + Ra (La can be pronounced as Ra in Korean) = Irra
Now she needs to explain 'Wa'
Crazy ...
Me ...
Frustrated
What is it?
Iraq whale?
Hurry up!
Wa...!!!
* She shouts 'wa' since it comes after irra (Irrawaddy)
Artillery
Roar
All frightened
What the ...
Yuri is it irra?
Very frustrating
Irra spout dolphin?
Yuri is it irra?
Just needs to describe it
But how to describe wa~
Irra spout dolphin?
Irra princess?
Wa...!
Don't know anymore
Again
wa~
Irra ... Irra king dolphin.
Don't know what to do with
an SNSD's scream
Irra king dolphin.
members
Running Man
Wins
Ah, what is this?
How are we suppose to guess that?
Now finally
the members are helping Yuri
This isn't Yuri's fault.
There is no way we
could have guessed that.
It's okay.
What's an Irrawaddy dolphin?
How frustrated she must have been to ...
Yuri is really crying.
Seriously.
Yuri, it's okay ...
Crying~
... even though we don't get any balls.
Yuri, it's okay ...
Feels sorry Yuri can't even lift her head
... even though we don't get any balls.
She's really crying.
But why is she crying?
Because it was too difficult.
Yeah, it was very hard.
A self blaming innocent minded
SNSD's tears starts to flow
It was too hard.
Embarrassment
That was too hard.
I didn't know what that was.
It's okay ~
Intentionally not answering the question
but still say "It's okay"
Because of this Irrawaddy Dolphin.
It forced our Yuri to go "Wa!"
The very frustrated Yuri
Wa~
SNSD Yuri
First time being like this
This is my first time seeing Yuri like this.
But if she had done better,
we would have succeeded.
Why are you being cruel like that?
It's okay since no one got a ball.
It's okay
The Running Man Speed Quiz.
You failed.
Feeling guilty believing it's because of her
they didn't get any balls
And the Running Balls ...
... go to the other 8 members.
We failed, but we'll get Running Balls?
Huh...
But...
Something is...?
I'm sorry.
Yuri, you still don’t know what's going on?
There's no ball with your name on it.
Huh...?
Why is my name
not there?
Yuri ...
You don't know what's going on?
Why do you think your name isn't there?
Didn't you think we were
too good at answering?
Ah, what is this?
Now Yuri figures out
We even rehearsed.
Yuri, look at my hand ... kamarinskaya.
This is too much.
Seriously too mean.
That was my first time
hearing about those things.
I'm not that scary of a person.
You guys are so mean.
I wouldn't be like that to you.
Jongkook is the most innocent today
Didn't you find it weird?
It was very weird.
What was the weirdest?
That was my first time
hearing those words, but ...
"Doesn't everyone know those words?"
And I thought that HaHa
and Gary were too smart.
As always...
The only ones being suspected
Why only us two?
I kept saying "Everyone knows what
it is", while standing next to her.
Giving her pressure.
That was so mean.
Can you imagine how frustrated Yuri was.
After saying "irra" she just went "wa" ...
Highlight of the day
SNSD Yuri's scream
... in order to describe Irrawaddy dolphin.
Jaesuk went to change so he could cheat?
To write down this.
I made the coordinator run
here to help me change.
I thought that oppa had
too much armpit sweat.
Ack!
As expected of the last reversal...?
Yuri, that's not why.
Thought he was sweating too much.
That's possible.
At the end Yuri is the only one that
didn't get a Running Ball, but then ...
Next venue is the place
where Yuri said she wants to go Food store
This place has
Many things to eat
The food sampling section.
Refreshed
We're here today at the Food Mart ...
It's been a while since I went to one.
It's impossible to not circle around here ...
Gulp
A place that everybody loves
... because you want to eat everything.
You'll be full because of
all the sampling stands.
Tasting corner
Yuri, what do you want to eat?
Bulgogi.
* ﻿Bulgogi = Barbequed beef
Jajang.
* ﻿Jajang is a black bean sauce
usually served with noodles or rice
What about Jihyo?
I want pork belly.
Pork belly
Then, I choose bulgogi
Suddenly
Why are you acting like that today?
Suddenly Kwangsoo's bulgogi confession
Keep saying things like that.
Experienced?
No ~
What's this?
What the ... ?
Why are you acting like that?
I think Kwangsoo really likes Yuri as a fan.
Wide grin
Framer Kwangsoo ♥ Yuri
The birth of another Monday Couple?
... and likes her.
But it won't turn out well.
No, seriously ...
When did you start enjoying
shattering other's dreams?
It is because he is a
precious dongsaeng ...
... I don't ﻿want him to get
his hopes up and get hurt.
He might give all his Running Balls to Yuri
But he's already hurt
That could happen.
Then what does he get in the end?
The punishment.
Anticipating
Punishment
Just punishment?
Punishment and a good image.
Hyung's unimaginable
kind heart
That's good enough.
We've come to a grocery store, but ...
... what do we have to
do to get a Running ﻿Ball?
Yuri doesn't have one?
None, there's no way
I could have any.
She's earnestly wants to get one.
Since you're hungry, you're
going to compete using food.
2nd mission
Must gain 1kg of weight
We are hungry now,
we really want to eat.
There are tasting stands spread out.
You'll divide yourselves into groups of three.
And increase your total weight with 1kg.
So you are saying that each group of three ...
3 people per team will taste food within
the given time limit and come back
... will circle around the tasting stands and
... when they come back, they have to
have increased their total weight by 1kg?
No more or less?
They succeed if they gained 1 kg
Exactly 1 kg?
Honestly, we're hungry right now, so ...
How can we be so accurate?
The main POINT is to gain 1 kg
I think we're going to eat like crazy.
There's a lot of sample I want to eat.
I want to eat everything.
They're worried because
they're hungry and might eat to much
If we're at the Food Mart
Tasting corner
Need to gain exactly 1kg
The food is being revealed
Healthy food
Arrowroot
juice
Happy food
Acorn
jelly
and tofu
Jewel of the tasting corner
Donkatsu
Plus there are all kinds of food
full of nutrients and protein
3 people per team
Gain 1 kg after tasting the food
We need to weight ourselves first right?
1st team
Jongkook and the Two Kids
Of course.
Don't eat everything.
Hungry
First Add up 3 members total weight
225.1kg
Jongkook and
the Two Kids
So they have to weigh 226.1 when they return?
226.1kg means they have succeeded.
Then the 3 members please go ahead.
Eat freely to
gain exactly 1 kg
That team has a disadvantage ...
... because Jongkook takes
care of his body too much.
Takes care of his body
Jongkook's picky eating problem
He won't eat randomly or
too much after midnight.
What is that?
First tasting corner
It's Arrowroot juice, isn't?
What is this?
Late night energy recharger Arrowroot juice
Wait, let it go.
Picky Jongkook won't let go of
anything that's good for the body
Let it go.
Why can't we drink it?
Is this healthy food...?
Let me drink one.
We'll drink it when we come back.
You'll have to eat the good
stuff with an empty stomach.
<Jongkook and
the Two Kids>
Strategy
Jongkook will eat
the healthy food
Gary and HaHa will
only eat what
Jongkook gives them
Hurry up, we're hungry too.
He's the type that drinks ginseng by himself.
Caring
He doesn't want the kids to get full
so he only eats the good stuff(?)
Ah, Jongkook seriously.
Only cares about his own body.
I knew he was going to be like that.
Do you enjoy living alone for 200 years?
When a tiger dies it'll leave behind it's hide ...
... and you'll leave behind your dumbbells.
Wow!
What?
Jelly ... Tofu.
Don't eat this one.
Jongkook and the hungry Two Kids
Think about the weight, then eat.
HaHa quickly loses interest(?)
Strength remedy?
Filling his stomach with tofu
Commander
Exciting midnight snack time
Completely excited Two Kids
Jewel of the tasting corner
Donkatsu
Because it's deep fried, you're
only watching and not eating?
Don't eat anything fried.
The lively Two Kids are
different from the cold
Jongkook
Only takes care of his body,
what do you think about that?
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it? I agree.
Honest(?) unanimous answer
Kim Jongkook ~
Did you hear that?
Doesn't care and stuffs HaHa with dumplings
I'm so thirsty.
Hurry up and eat this.
Can they gain 1kg like this?
You're thinking of eating
on behalf of me, right?
Passionately gives Gary a bite
What's this?
Next food stand
Can Jongkook
eat it?
or not?
Jongkook, can't you eat a little?
The nation's famous dish
Pork belly
No doubt The stiff Jongkook
I should've eaten more at the beginning.
Regretful
Ah, delicious.
Once again Jongkook feeds Gary
Ah, it's so delicious.
Also HaHa gets a bite
Arrives at the last tasting corner
How come there's nothing to try?
What's this?
What?
You gave me a fright.
Hot and steamy~
Tasty
Jajangmyun
Jajangmyun.
What a surprise.
Eating without hesitation
Yummy~
Don't eat everything.
Jajangmyun is my favorite
Jongkook﻿, are you still not eating?
I can absolutely not eat this.
Aren't there any more food?
It's over.
Its over?
Jongkook and the Two Kids
Finished
eating
How much did you weigh before?
225.1 kg.
The target is 226.1 kg
The starting weight
Target weight
He only ate 3 pieces of tofu.
Kim Jongkook only had 1 cup of
arrowroot juice + 3 pieces of tofu
If they win, we're done for.
They must gain exactly 1kg
in order to win the game
Undoubtedly
Target weight: 225.1 + 1 = 226.1 kg
Lacking 100g
Close
Wow, it's 226.0 kg.
It's because you didn't
want to eat anything.
It's our turn now, Jihyo.
Jongkook and the Two Kids
Failed
We have to weigh ourselves first.
So hungry
Jaesuk sets off without weighing
I'm too busy thinking about eating.
197.2 kg.
Jihyo and the
Two Uncles
Then that means Jihyo
only weighs about 52.2kg.
Huh?
What are you doing?
If you take away 145kg,
then you're left with 52.2kg
* Earlier Jaesuk and Sukjin weighted themselves together
Trying to find out Jihyo's weight
The annoying bullies(?)
It's because I'm wearing my shoes.
The shoes weigh about 3 kilos.
I'm also wearing a lot of accessories.
Don't forget the vest.
My new fur west is also quite heavy.
Did you put lead inside your vest?
Latest fashion trend Vests made of lead(?)
That means our target weight is 198.2 kg.
Target weight: 198.2 kg
Gain
precisely 1kg
How much did you guys eat?
Puzzled
Is it a game or a dinner?
I'm not sure, I just ate
whatever Jongkook gave me.
Hopeful food-testing trio
Isn't this Jelly?
And there's tofu.
A food-testing stand that Jongkook could eat from
This is so tasty.
<Jihyo and
the Two Uncles>
Strategy
Is to
EAT
Even carefully picking the banana slices
Concentrating
Focused on eating Blank~Jihyo
She's taking this really seriously.
Feeding...
her a slice of banana?
I want to eat jajangmyun.
Requesting
Yes, okay.
I want to eat jajangmyun.
Embarrassed he eats it himself
Say sorry to Sukjin hyung.
Let's go.
I thought you were
that type of girl.
What's that?
Is it something I like?
Bread ~
Soft fresh
bread
I like to eat it.
There's no buffet like the Tasting Corner
It's good.
This side tastes better
than those over there.
That side simply doesn't
taste as good as this side.
Is that why Sukjin got rejected(?)
The strong willed Sukjin
So he tries again
Catches?
Use your mouth.
Nagging
Hyung, what are you doing?
Again
Getting angry
Use your mouth to eat it directly.
The heck does this mean.
He's so scary.
That's what you want.
Bickering
Yakking
Are you supposed to talk
to your sunbae like that?
Eat this then, oppa.
Suddenly
Feeds him
a piece
How can I eat with that look on your face?
The atmosphere over there
seems pretty good ...
They are feeding each other.
Not knowing the truth
the envious kid
They're looking at us from over there.
Sorry, they didn't hear
what we said just now.
They didn't hear what they said
so I looked harmonious
What's the point?
Cold
They look like a real family, that's so nice.
Envious
Actually
They do look harmonious
Filled
with laughter
You're too much.
Why are you like that, oppa?
Furious
You talk to a sunbae with this attitude?
I ...
want to be part of that team
The bread was really tasty
The constantly bickering
Will they be able to gain 1 kg?
Tasting finished
Ah, my stomach hurts.
The two of them probably didn't eat
enough, they're probably still 1 kg off.
No, that's ridiculous.
We'll see how much they ate by weighing.
You guys have to reach 198.2kg
Jihyo and the Two Uncle's target
They have walked around
all the food-tasting counters
Original weight
Success?
Or failure?
Target weight: 197.2 + 1 = 198.2 kg
Look at that.
Again
Lacking 100g
Fail
Ah, such a pity.
I will eat a lot.
Go weigh first, the 3 of you.
Yuri, you get on first.
Last challenging team
Youthful Girl Boys
Let's all get on at the same time.
1, 2, 3.
Oh my gosh oppa, get on.
What the ... ?
Look at him trying to be considerate.
Shy
Why are you so shy?
No, I'm not.
Stop being like that.
Even his legs are shaking.
His legs
are shaking
Put both of your feet on.
Why are you crossing
your legs and being shy?
Wide grin~
195.5 kg.
Weight before eating
The three of them looks like ...
* MT (Membership Training) = Gathering by certain
work or social groups to get to know each other better
... they came out of an MT.
College students.
Right, they give up that feel.
What television drama is this?
Youth drama
'Supermarket scandal'
They look like they are filming a drama.
Theme of the drama:
Blooming romance and strong friendship
The way I see it, Joongki and
Yuri are dating in this drama ...
Male lead
Joongki
Couple
Female lead
Yuri
But Kwangsoo ...
... is senselessly butting in.
(Unattractive) friend role
Kwangsoo
He's a troublemaker.
The conclusion
it won't...
work
He barely has
one hand on it
That kind of person buys stuff, goes home
and eats dinner, the sleeps like this ...
* Jaesuk says that the person who senselessly
butts feels no guilt and comfortably falls asleep
The script should
be like this ...
Let's calculate what we eat.
We must know what we eat, so that ...
<Youth Girl Boys>
Strategy
Calculate
the food
eaten by
previous teams
Let's do a little calculation first.
To prevent failure
remember how much they ate
Really tasty.
The team with a sense of logic
Delicious.
A ﻿cup of arrowroot juice ...
Now one person needs to get
1 cup of
juice
3 tofu
pieces
... plus 3 pieces of tofu.
What's that?
Pork cutlets ~
Carrying out their plan
Youth Girl Boys
Will they gain more than 1 kg?
How many slices should we eat?
Yuri, can you do me a favor?
Yes ...
Can't you feed Kwangsoo a small bite?
Why are you saying that?
Acting as a friend helping a friend
It's your wish.
I've fed food to my fans before.
Oppa, here.
Romance with Yuri
that bloomed from a slice of pork
I'm envious.
Why ... ?
As expected
Kwangsoo...
is smiling
You two can go and eat
somewhere else, I'll stay.
You are...
my true friend
Ah, it's so delicious, really.
Harmonious Kwangsoo and Yuri's
pink sentiment?
Oppa, chew thoroughly.
For Yuri...
we must win
Youth Girl Boys
Food tasting is over
They're back ~
You know the guy from the movie "Home Alone"?
You look exactly like him.
Are you
Kwangsoo?
This is impossible.
Hurry, finish eating and stand on it.
Youth Girl Boys
Total weight
Their carefully calculated efforts
Have they
successfully gained exactly 1 kg?
Target weight: 195.5 + 1 = 196.5 kg
Strangely also they are lacking 100g
Youth Girl Boys
Failed
This is so strange, we're all the same.
Fascinating, how did we all lack 100g?
This time, eat another
100g within 1 minute.
All three teams
fell short by 100g
Failed
100g?
Just gain that amount.
Starting at the same time
The team who first gain 100g wins
We need to gain 100g?
Speed is the crucial strategy
Oppa ...
Advancing toward the food again
I want to give up.
Pretty Boy Joongki suffers from being to full
Won't we be okay if we eat one of these?
Will Jongkook eat more for the sake of victory?
Don't eat it.
Blank~Jihyo and the Uncles
are focused on the fried food
Stop eating.
It's an advantage to reach the scale first
Hurry up.
Jihyo ...
We have to hurry and weight ourselves.
When Jongkook eats tofu it gives off a CF feeling
The team who gains
100g first will win
Come over here.
Jihyo ...
Dashes off
Let's go.
Battle of speed
Blank~Jihyo and the Two Uncles are first
Their goal is
They can win Running Balls
They need
precisely 0.1kg
Gained 100g
Success
We won ~
The miserable teams who lost
Running Balls.
Sukjin*Jaesuk*Jihyo
Earns Running Balls
Yuri's stone glazed face
I also have a Running Ball here.
Gary's full stomach became a Running Ball
Yuri doesn’t have a ball.
She's in real trouble.
But ...
Do you want us to run
after eating like this?
Seriously ...
These guys mobility is very ...
Due to over-eating Gary and
HaHa's mobility dropped rapidly
But the most terrifying side of them
will be revealed now
Bond of friendship that's
even tighter than a family's
But ...
Today's
mission will ...
I'm sorry.
... break up the
bonds of brotherhood
It's war...!
Are you happy breaking up with hyung?
Noooo ...
Big war
The unavoidable face-off
between brothers
Mission
Team
Today's instructions
Collect the receipts in every cash register
to total 200 thousand won and above.
Mission
Team
Collect receipts in sum of 200 thousand
and above to exchange for Running Balls
This time we immediately report
on how much each of us collected.
Saying how much is very important.
I'm going to collect 140 thousand.
Who are you kidding?
Out of 200k Gary plans to collect 140k alone?
I'll just try to be funny, so I'll
collect the other 60 thousand.
There is already ...
...a lot of funny scenes recorded.
Rejoining
Mission
Team
HaHa
Will he be serious in completing the mission?
Time remaining
The recording is done under the safety measures
by the assistance of the shopping mall staff
HaHa's
desire to
be the hero(?)
I'm going to do a little something today.
What's he thinking to do today
I'm determined to be the hero alone
HaHa has always been disregarded
Can he emerge as a hero...?!
Mission Team
Mission
Team
Jaesuk*Jihyo*Joongki
Heading to 2nd floor
Spacious area on 2nd floor
at women's department
Here's the girls department place
How do we search for it?
At the shopping mall
Products in sight But where's the cash register
7th floor.
Noona, shan't we head to the 7th floor?
Isn't
this it?
Isn't this the cash register?
Bingo
2nd floor cash register found
Open the cash register
and get the receipts inside
Ding
Jackpot
Running Man receipt
Ah, its here.
How much?
75,000 won.
We've already found 75 thousand won.
Need 200k won and higher
Obtained 75k won on one receipt
We found ﻿75,000 won.
Jaesuk:
Argh
I should have
found it
To 3rd floor Prestige living goods
Ding
Again
Running Man receipt
Let me see.
This time there's a lot of them
Amazing ~
5000 plus 4000 ...
The receipts adds up to 49,000 won
How much?
26,000 won ...
Oppa, I found more.
200k needed
They already found 124k
How much?
A total of 49,000 won.
Ringing bells
Things ran smoothly
then they heard bells
I hear bells.
Clash~!
Bang
Loud noise attracts the enemy
Due to the spacious area
it's easily detected where sounds come from
The sound.
Jaesuk & Joongki quickly run to another floor
Ringing bells...
coming closer
Sparta.
Commander
Jongkook
Yooruce Willis
escaping to the hallway
Please save me.
Joongki is surrounded
Jongkook, he's here.
Chasing
Team
Using their surround tactics
Suddenly
Joongki
Joongki oppa, sorry.
What are you sorry about,
when you didn't take these.
Joongki still has the receipts he found
23,000 won ...
Time remaining
In midst of the chaos
Hiding on 3rd floor Blank~Jihyo
3rd floor Still possible to find a receipt there
This time
Ringing bells
Sounds like it's near and coming closer
...Oh?
What's on
her mind?
Perfect hiding cover
Chasing
Team
Yuri is nearby
Right in front of her
is the unrevealed bed
Will it...
be discovered?
Just passing through
Gone?
It's now
Has she...
already fallen asleep
Meanwhile on 4th floor
Two Kids hiding safely
HaHa
Gary
So who is still unable to
find even one receipt
...what's that?
Fax machine area
Stopped in his path
What does this do?
No, this isn't a cash register.
Wow
Doesn't know what a
cash register looks like
Still wants to be a hero...?
Ring~
Approaching
Ringing bells
Whatever you're doing do it quick
Scatter and hide
Commander
Jongkook
Gary is unable to hide
Confrontation
Why does it have to be me?
Gary has always been on Chasing Team
But today he's Jongkook's enemy
4th floor, quickly come to 4th floor.
Hyung, why did you suddenly stop?
Why did you suddenly stop?
After being separated from me ...
... are you happy?
Ah, it's tiring.
Stealthy
Just hurry up and come to
the 4th floor using the stairs.
Kwangsoo arrived from behind
That's it ~
Commander's new right arm
Kwangsoo attacks
Oh...?
Was HaHa going to do something?
HaHa tries to help Gary by attacking
Eh?
Why is he aiming for Jongkook's name-tag?
Oh my god
Chasing
Team
Old habit
Ripping the name-tag without hesitation
In the end
Gary
Bang
HaHa tried to be a hero
Resulted in doing nothing
Unconditionally
escaping
Sadly HaHa
having a change of plans
Time left
Silent...
Blank~Jihyo
Didn't sleep and appears once again
Properly tidying
Joongki, where are you?
We're on the 2nd floor prison,
hurry up and get the receipts.
Stumbled
Getting the receipts
that Joongki collected
Out of 200k
They already have 124k
It's still 76 thousand short.
Fighting.
Make sure not to drop it.
Got it.
As expected the calm and
cool hide-n-seek heroine
Blank~Jihyo
She's doing good.
You head over to 3rd floor.
It was a good move
going to 3rd floor just now.
Delighted~
Blank~Jihyo
Right arm
Kwangsoo attacks
Scurry
Jihyo noona ...
Unfortunately found by Kwangsoo
This is not right...
It can't end like this
Yah ...
What?
Blank~Jihyo suddenly turning into Bad Jihyo
Her opponent is the easily bullied Kwangsoo
Smack
Jongkook ...
Flinch
Unfortunately there's no one around
Just try and follow me, you ...
Swoosh
Swing
Throws her shoe
Don't try to follow me.
Who would believe
this could happen
Remaining time
Meanwhile at 6th floor
Arts & Interior Goods
Found it
Press
Huh?
Cash register won't open?
If it can't be open it's gone
What do I do?
At that moment
Chasing
Team
Big Nose spotted Yooruce Willis
Almost opening the register
Aww
It's Big Nose hyung
20 years of brotherhood
Now vigorously in pursue
It's Jaesuk hyung.
Exposing his position
while escaping
What should I do?
What does he mean with "What
should I do?", just catch him you fool.
Yooruce Willis
escapes to 4th floor stair exit
Jaesuk is in here.
Ugh!!
Yuri chasing with all her might
Yuri ~
I caught Jaesuk oppa.
Yuri, your good intentions ...
If Yuri is alone there's a chance to escape
Right arm Kwangsoo joins in
The whole Chasing Team arrived to catch Jaesuk
But at the same time
Arrived at
4th floor
Arrived at the battle ground
Almost got caught on set
I just need to go to
the 2nd floor right?
Yuri, don't joke around.
Jaesuk
Now only 2 people left
Jihyo
Returning to
4th floor a bit later
Blank~Jihyo
A cash register
Out of the 4
Found 3 cash register by herself
It's here
Running Man receipts
Including these the total is 51,900 won
Out of 200k won
Found 175,900 won
Now the approaching
ringing of bells
Jihyo's position
Why is it ...
Commander
Jongkook
Listens to sounds coming from elsewhere
Mission
Team's
Blue shirt spotted
Ha
Did they see me?
He saw you.
Hides the receipt so they won't be found
Huh?
Jihyo is walking out?
Enduring...!
Using the same tactic as against Kwangsoo?
Huh?
Kneeling down??
Just this time.
The opposite tactic toward Jongkook
Absurd
Suddenly
Huh
Even a big bow
It's here
Her specialty
Grabbing the leg
Oppa, just let me go this time.
How am I suppose to do it?
Just close one eye please.
I'm really going crazy.
Oppa ...
All this time
when I escaped from oppa
Oppa should
know how tired I was
All you have
to do is stop
It's alright if you
let me go this time
...what to do...
Hurry, turn around ...
Turn around??
Hurry and leave, really go.
Really?
Is the Commander
letting her leave?
Hurry and run, okay go.
Because of dignity
So others
won't see
Letting her off quickly
Hurry up and leave.
Suddenly
I'm really going crazy.
A Commander like him
letting that girl go
I'll catch her again really quick anyway.
Meanwhile the wannabe hero HaHa in on 6th floor
Oh??
Finding a cash register for the first time
The cash register
that Yooruce couldn't open
...What is he doing?...
Sorry
Clack
It suddenly opened
Finally
Found the Running Man receipts
On the 6th floor
Total amount:
Total: 227,900
Can now exchange it for Running Balls
See...
I did something
good too
What!
Big Nose in here
Jihyo ...
I found a 47,000 and a 5,000 won receipt.
Coughs
HaHa, filming his own movie again
Sorry, I'll send both receipts over to you.
Today's theme
The Kid's
Heroic Act
Lead actor: (Acting by himself again) HaHa
Lead actress: (Listens emotionless) Jihyo
Sorry, Jihyo you must succeed.
Engrossed in his own tearful act
Unknowingly...
Everyone loses themselves in this movie
The indispensable characters of
the movie are the bad guys(?)
When Jihyo noona reaches the
1st floor, we can throw it to her.
Plan
Jihyo waits on the 1st floor and
HaHa throws his receipts to her
HaHa, hurry and come here.
Hurry ~
Most important now is to get HaHa's receipt
HaHa, hurry and come here.
Sorry Jihyo, you must succeed on your own.
At the 1st floor
Exchanging 200k won receipts
on the 1st floor for Running Balls
Jihyo is handing over
the 175,900 won receipts that she got
Did you find all the receipts?
Just a little more.
How much more?
We're 24,100 won short.
24,100 won? HaHa is coming over now.
Then we'll throw it to you.
Jihyo ...
... hide and come forward
when we say "Thank you".
... when we say "Thank you".
'﻿Thank You'
Secret code for throwing receipts
HaHa hyung has to come.
HaHa, hurry over.
Please.
HaHa, hurry and come to the jail.
What are you...
good at...?
I ...
want to be...
a hero
In more dramatic situations
Appear
more on TV
The days when HaHa
was bullied and ignored
Although he wants to be a hero...
Although he said that...
Doesn't want to be like that anymore...!
Today...
I must
do something great...!
Because the movie is ending
My happy ending belongs to me
My legs, I have no strength.
What's that for?
Let's fight.
What did you say?
Going nuts?
On his feet
Challenging
the Commander?
Fool ~
Do you feel good being
on a different team?
Of course not, hyung
HaHa... You've said... HaHa
You've said enough, HaHa
just come over here now.
You have to come, you'll become
a hero when you come, please.
Turn the camera here, this
can be used for the preview.
Is the movie not over...?
Commander and
his victim
The change in the victim
who desires to be a hero
Cut ...
You worked hard.
No!!
Noooo ...
Always shouting 'No~' when he gets caught
There's only Jihyo left.
HaHa
There's only Jihyo left?
Chasing
Team
wins if they catch Jihyo
I got 2 receipts, I'm going to 1st floor.
Heading towards the jail with the receipts
What did he say?
Hurry.
Fine
Just hurry to the 2nd floor
and hand over the receipts
HaHa, you just have to come.
Please.
Anxious
Please, just this once.
HaHa, well done.
Although he was caught
Returns
with dignity
Well done.
I told you to not waste any time.
The plan to pass the receipts starts now
HaHa hands over 57k
worth of receipts
Chasing Team is still around Need to wait
Thank you HaHa, thank you.
The secret signal 'Thank You'
But must not let
members of Chasing Team find out
Have you caught Jihyo?
Thank you Jihyo, thank you.
Jihyo finally found the right time
Throw
Bang
HaHa's receipts
successfully passed to Jihyo
Jihyo runs towards the reception
Must hide from the Chasing Team
to submit the remaining receipts
It's about to end
Jihyo must not be found
Anxious
Mission success ...
Mission success
Obtained more than 200k
Successfully exchanged
them for Running Balls
Blank Jihyo ~
Indeed
Mission
Team's
calmest hero
Blank~Jihyo
HaHa
completed his own mission too
Jaesuk*Gary*HaHa*Joongki*Jihyo
Got Running Balls
Current time
Jihyo and I have 3 balls ...
Tally of Running Balls
Jaesuk*Jihyo
Jongkook*Kwangsoo
Sukjin*Gary*HaHa*Joongki
Yuri
... but I still feel uneasy.
But Yuri doesn't have a single one?
Yes.
That's how life is.
With 0 balls Yuri is confirmed for punishment
Is it 5 people?
The owner of the ball selected from five
chances will be exempt from punishment
What's today's punishment?
In hot pants ...
... going to Noryanjin Fish Market.
Today's
punishment
Wearing hot pants
and going to a seafood market
Please ~
The draw that determines their fate
Everyone, 1, 2, 3.
1st person to be exempt is?
Jaesuk
Exemption
confirmed
Cheering
Waah~
Prayer of gratitude
How much is this exemption worth?
Jaesuk, your VJ is clapping.
Jaesuk's VJ
Sharing the joy of exemption
Let's go home.
Man, seriously ...
Four people left.
Who will the next lucky person be?
Joongki
Exemption
confirmed
Joongki ...
Please ...
The third person is?
HaHa
Exemption
confirmed
HaHa ...
Joyous
dance ceremony
Seriously, he never gets chosen.
Gary ...
Jihyo
Exemption
confirmed
Jihyo ...
1 ... 2 ... 3.
It's down to the last person
Who'll be
exempted
Who'll be facing
Embarrassing punishment?
Sukjin
Exemption
confirmed
Sukjin ...
Really?
So happy he lies on the ground
Look at that hyung.
Mixed feelings
No expectation at all
No Running Ball Yuri
It seems like Kwangsoo doesn't
hate the punishment today.
If he can be together with Yuri
even punishment bring happiness
Arrived at the seafood market
The smell from Noryanjin fish market.
The strong smell of seafood
I'm seriously embarrassed.
3 men with exposed legs and
Yuri covering her face
It fits you.
1, 2, 3.
Curious
What's wrong with her face?
Cute~
Became Mustache Yuri
You look cute.
They're already up and working.
The workers are
working even before dawn
Seafood market
with bare legs
Hello ~
Why are they walking
around in hot pants
What happened to her face?
The mustache suits her, right?
It fits her well.
Nods
Today's
punishment's complete