Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by SoshiSubs
and Don't Walk, Run team
The third
Landmark
South Korea's Heart of Science
Gwacheon National Science Museum
Is that a robot?
Frightening night
at the museum
Run the other way.
It's coming.
The Running Man can't believe it
What's going on oppa?
Science museum vs. Expedition
From now on
Blow away the heat
Science lab expedition part 2
Starting now
You know curling?
We do.
Have you calculated it right?
Last week
Wait ...
Using the Law of inertia
to play human curling
Stop ~
Very good.
When a 50,000 won golden pig is on stake
no one is giving in
What are you doing?
With twist after twist
Child Team has an advantage at the moment
Kwangsoo is Adult Team's last bet
He sets off
Is this the last time?
Stay in the center to win
Fighting ~
Good ~
When the time is right Jihyo,
you have to push really hard.
Super nervous
Please let me hear my team cheering.
Fighting ~
Kwangsoo is Adult Team's last bet
Iron wall defense
Need to push HaHa who is in the center circle
Kwangsoo fighting.
No way, no ...
With all their hopes Adult Team starts
Heading straight towards HaHa
Please...
No way...
Come and get me
Last chance
They'll lose if HaHa isn't pushed out
Okay, let's hear to who's cheering.
The shouts of victory are coming from...?
Round and round
Went past him
Adult Team loses this round
Peek~
Disappointed
Another round.
Fighting.
Child Team
Wins
This time ...
Why are you over there?
Spiteful remark
This requires strength.
Since this is the last round ...
The team who pushes the bin
closest to the line is the winner
... let's stay on this side and try to
push the bin close to the other line
... but if it crosses the line it's a fail.
But if the trash bin crosses
the line then they are OUT
Ah, you're talking about Cola Cider.
Yes.
Okay.
Again Switching to a better trash bin
This is going to be interesting.
Moving away unnoticed...
Isn't it like playing the table game?
Yes, you're right.
Gathering on the same side
Like throwing coins.
We're going to go first.
Okay, start.
Whichever team's trash bin comes
closest to this line is the winner
Fighting ~
Two people pushing isn't accurate, one is better.
Adult Team
Jaesuk gets ready to go first
Ahh, the push was too hard.
If he crosses the line
Getting closer to the finish line
Wind resistance...?!
Flapping the grasshopper wings
If he crosses the line
Disqualified
Outcome?
No points ...
Crossed the line
No.
I told you its about 30 steps.
Adult Team
Jaesuk
Disqualified
As I said before, we have to cooperate well.
Have to control the strength when pushing.
Lonely...
One person should push.
I told you to push slowly.
Too much strength since it was the first time
Can't you give me another chance?
No ~
You stay there on your own, it looks fun.
I'm sure someone else will come this way.
Curse?
It's Child Team's turn
Hey, this ...
Fighting.
We really have to play well,
500,000 won is at stake.
The 500,000 won prize makes them competitive
This is really important.
Okay ...
HaHa you can't get all the way over there.
Child Team's first runner is HaHa
We are going.
He'll cross the line.
You'll do well.
HaHa's riding the faulty trash bin that Kwangsoo switched
You'll cross the line, will cross.
Use strength.
Over the line.
Cross the line.
Disqualified.
Time out
Time out.
Next ...
Out ~
He's out.
Commotion
What's your opinion?
Out!
From what I can see he's out.
A judge in the corner?
He's out ~
It's out from Jaesuk's point of view.
It's only his judgment.
Continuously
OUT~
Out ~
Sorry, but could you be quiet?
Yeah yeah, out.
Adult Team's second try
Sukjin
Flap
Great.
Stopped at the center
What's this?
Kwangsoo, that was too weak.
But I'm always facing the entrance.
Again his back is turned to the camera
Again... Sukjin's lonely back...
Looking back...
I now Sukjin well and he's nervous now.
The man appearing in the rain...
It's a little weird when you do it.
Lonely
First time outdoor variety in 10 years
I also think so.
You all look so close.
I met up sometimes.
Members that meet
outside of work.
Tried to endure
all the humiliation...
End.
But...
Since last week
Why ...
Becoming alone
It's not this way, no.
What's going on?
makes me so sad...
Let's go.
Yes.
Child Team is getting ready
Gary, come over here and play.
I'm ready.
Peaceful Gary is always ready
We're going.
I'm nervous.
Let's go.
Peaceful Gary
Let's go
Here, you need to come here.
Go.
Good ~
Safe steady speed
Nice ~
Screech
Good ~
Close to the winning line
We did well ~
Nice, Gary did well.
In the midst of this
one person is still alone
Oh that's right, he can push Sukjin.
Need to use more strength.
Adult Team's last bet
Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo, you have to do well.
Understood.
Fighting ~
Adult Team's victory
lies in Kwangsoo's hands
Kwangsoo think about the punishment.
Need to use more strength.
Go closer to the line
or push Gary away
A successful push
Well done.
Gary crossed the line
Eliminated
Well done.
You did it.
Closer to the line Adult Team is in lead
It's done.
Isn't that cheating?
Kwangsoo was good.
Kwangsoo did well.
Thank you.
Proud~
Nice ~
Wow seriously, Kwangsoo fighting.
Still calm after being eliminated
Nice.
Child Team's last hope
Joongki
Fighting ~
Good.
Clenching
teeth~
Worried
Go ~
It really is tense.
What kind of entertainment is this?
But it seems so tensed.
It's the first time I'm so anxious.
Leg cramps
Our cart isn't good.
Anxious...
Uncomfortable with the bin...
Please hurry.
Go, go, just go.
Stops
What is this?
Annoyed
Angry
What are you doing?
Oh, Jihyo ...
... that's not like you.
No, but it takes too long
to play the game like that.
Everyone became sensitive
because of the prize money
Jihyo, well done.
Let's go ~
Here it comes.
Child Team wins if Kwangsoo
is pushed across the line
Here it comes ~
Attack on Kwangsoo
I'll push you away
Prepared to be attacked
Crash
Clash
Push harder.
He pushed, but...
Both of them are moving?!
Who is the final winner?
Joongki crossed the line
Eliminated
Push harder.
Kwangsoo
Safe
Near the line
It's crazy.
Adult Team wins
Adult Team's celebration
Huh?
Why is Gary cheering?
Why?
What's happening?
Adult Team gets the prize of 500 000 won
500,000 ...
Oh...
I misunderstood...
Film him one more time.
Kwangsoo, this is 500,000 won.
It's seriously an important 500,000 won.
Today's MVP
Kwangsoo
Currently both teams are competing...
Eight hours ago
at the pool in the museum
Oh, Jaesuk is good at swimming.
Wow, not bad swimming.
Interesting
A swimming grasshopper
Show us butterfly style.
Butterfly is easy.
Splash
You could join the Olympic.
Using his legs to swim in shallow water
You're a good swimmer.
My chest hurts when I swim butterfly style.
HaHa, try breaststroke.
I'll do superfly.
What's superfly?
Superfly...?
Not butterfly style?
Splash
Also HaHa is using his legs for butterfly
Expression of a competitor
Sparkling~
Doesn't your face hurt?
Oh, it's okay.
Also now 500,000 won is at stake.
Let's play the game.
Everyone knows this.
It's called Gary Game.
The game is called Gary Game
In that case...
Nice.
In any situation...
Taking a picture now.
In this game you can always see
Gary's peaceful expression
Photo-zone?
Yes, photo-zone.
Photo in the pool
Well played.
The team with most faces in the picture wins.
You guys got it?
Yes ~
In this game ...
Yes?
Sit on the sausage and the team
with most faces in the photo wins
... everyone is getting
onto this sausage boat.
We'll only recognize the people who get on it.
Too hard.
Difficult
Hard
Stand on top.
So the photo will be taken over there?
That's right.
Shall we go up there nicely?
Really?
Yes.
Sure.
Are you negotiating?
Yes.
Let's go.
Get in the pool first
Cautiously~
Go on top.
Be on your guard
Joongki is first to try to get up
Sausage boat is difficult to get on
That ...
Flustered
I'm dropping my pants.
Gary aims for the side with less competition
Hurry.
Quarrel
Jongkook & HaHa
Gets onto the float
I'm up.
Suddenly
What?
Please take the picture quickly.
Gary gets onto the boat on his first try
Please hurry and take the picture.
Acting professionally in front of a camera
Gary
Me too ~
We're going to take the picture now.
I want up too.
Huh?
Everyone falls in the water
Strenghtless
While Jaesuk is trying to climb on
Everyone falls in the water while
the camera flashed
Sausage capsized
Picture was taken when they fell
Who's photo was taken?
It has been taken.
What is this?
It's Gary again.
What's going on?
Again
Peaceful...
Gary, how was that picture taken?
Unbelievable
Just before they fell into the water
It looks really serene.
Sukjin is getting attacked, right?
Poor Big Nose Hyung...
But Gary still managed to
pose with a peace sign.
That's right.
V-sign
He even made the V-sign.
I actually took note of the
expression in my eyes.
Nichkhun & Gary are in the picture
It's a tie
Gary's Gallery
Nobody got in the picture,
but I get in it every time.
Taking a picture on a big floating platform
Nickhun just told me ...
... "It's kind of tiring".
When we get home we'll
be going for hibernation.
Female members are disappearing.
Please don't leave yet.
Joongki just asked her not to leave.
Please get on the floating platform.
HaHa and Joongki
Go up first with nimble hands
Child, you
are here?
Smack
Gary moves away from the chaos
Found an empty spot
but got hit
Hey, Nickhun ...
After disposing(?) Joongki
Next he target is Gary
... you don't have to play that aggressive.
A complete mess
Going to take a picture.
Instantly panic
This is a chance
No way
Jihyo blocked HaHa
Hyung ...
Nickhun
Iron defense
Everyone from Adult Team is on the platform
We have to get on.
Splash
Then
Jongkook's final attempt
Who will appear in the picture?
Click
The picture has been taken
When did Gary get up?
Gary ~
Gary appears again.
Peaceful
Adult Team
Child Team
Jihyo
Gary
Again
it's a tie
I am always in the photo
because I look handsome.
Can't Gary just take a picture by himself?
Gary looks so peaceful
What does this kid do?
I thought only Jihyo was photographed.
Gary's Gallery
Everyone, please take
note this 3rd time round.
Sukjin has a proposal
Let's play this way ...
After going under the water ...
Stay under the water for 10 seconds
Then the picture will be taken
... you hold your breath for 10 seconds.
Everyone can hold their
breath for 10 seconds.
Let's start, 1, 2, 3.
Following Sukjin's request
Under the water for 10 seconds
Submerge
... 3.
Determination
~bubble bubble~
Looks funny from above
Are they able to hold their breath
until the picture is taken?
Sukjin who proposed the game gave up first
Some members are still under water
Child Team
Get out
~bubble~
Ah, my face hurts.
Disturbance from Sukjin
Jongkook
Eliminated
What happened?
It hurts.
Who are you?
Jihyo
Fail
Of course... Gary is the only one left...
Why wasn't the picture taken?
The photographer wasn't
able to hold his breath.
The PD couldn't hold his breath.
You need to hold your breath.
Sorry
We risked our lives holding our breath.
I was because the focus was blurred.
The PD's excuse was okay.
Restart
Both teams are involved in a fierce battle
Underwater is ...
... chaos
Will Gary be in the picture or not?
Nickhun Right in front of camera
Gary is pulling
Nickhun away
Click
Gary and Nickhun
were only people remaining
Who is on the picture?
What's the fuss about?
This is Nichkhun's solo shot
Unexpected victory
Adult Team won
Why did he cover the whole screen.
Is that Gary?
Nichkhun won against the champion
Yeah, Nickhun ... yeah.
Gary's first time losing this competition
There is no more Gary in photo zone?
It's alright.
Jihyo is taking care of Jessica?
Huh?
Jihyo, take care of your own team.
Unnie always takes care of me first.
Is that so?
Sica must have things
constantly falling off her.
Quiet
Did you drop some hair?
What did she drop?
Something keeps falling off Sica's eyes.
Ah...
Fake eyelashes...
Can you try jumping?
Final round
Water jumping
Photo
It's too high.
Only accepted when
the face is in this angle
Get ready
You have to jump.
Yes ~
Secret plan in motion
Nickhun, what are you doing?
Nothing.
Jongkook, don't do this to me.
We have to block Gary.
Gary is the number 1 competitor
We'll take a picture now.
Jump
Who will be in this picture?
In the end
Winner of this round will win the whole photo game
Winning team will get 500,000 won
Gary
Can he get back on the throne?
Click
I got it.
Return of the King
Returning with his peacefulness...
Child Team
Only Gary succeeds
Final winner
500,000 won ~
Child Team earned 500,000 won
I can't beat him
Gary's gallery
Oppa, say something.
Say what?
Water photography
Gary's celebratory ceremony
Anticipating
Eh, I don't know.
Flying~
We took a picture
Levitation
He's in a different class
Even with the golden pig
his ceremony is an art
Peaceful
Calm
Are you sitting?
He is amazing.
Best!
Tranquility
Gary's school
Everyone worships him
Gary's gallery
In one of science center's
laboratories
We got wet and had
to change clothes ...
... so we got a chance to rest for a bit.
Finally earning some rest time
Finally we're able to rest.
Do you know?
Cola and cider ...
* In Korea cider refers to carbonated
drinks similar to 7up and Sprite
If you cover your eyes, you
can't differentiate the tastes.
When blindfolded
do cola and cider taste different?
I watched this game in another TV-show.
Seriously ...
With closed eyes, you can't tell.
Who are you trying to fool?
Confident
For real ~
I'll show you, give it to me.
If I guess it correctly, what will I get?
Hold on ...
Are you for real?
Determined to prove everyone wrong
I'm ready.
Let's bet money.
What are we betting on?
Immediately preparing the drinks
I want to rinse my mouth.
It's not like you are wine testing
As if you're a gourmet.
Line them up.
Start
Cola Cider
Blindfold test
* In Korean: Cider = Soda
There are five cups.
Here you go.
My guess is ...
Cola
First cup challenge
... cola.
Will HaHa be right?
Can he differentiate between the drinks?
Really
He doesn't know?
I know the taste of cola ...
... because I have been drinking
a lot of cola since I was young.
You have to pinch the nose.
Okay, cola.
Correct
There are still four more cups.
Cider
The second glass
This is cider.
Correct again
You got it completely wrong.
I need some water.
Because I'm a commelier.
Commelier?
For wine it's sommelier ...
... so for cola it's commelier.
Gargle
Cola
The third cup challenge
This is cola.
3 consecutive successes
Cola
Fourth glass
How many did he get right?
Three
Three?
I know this ... cola.
As expected
Correct
If you get the last one right, it
means you got 1 out of 5 right.
Last cup Cider
Can the commelier get it right?
It's cola.
Commelier
Fail
This is really amazing.
You didn't swap the cups?
I didn't.
You really didn't change the cups?
Nickhun, are you feeling okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Hyung, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Is your underwear alright?
The front of your underwear
looks like it belongs to your wife.
What is he talking about?
I thought he was wearing women's clothing.
Did he see women's underwear in the changing room?
It's a misunderstanding.
My manager ...
I forgot to pack my underwear today.
So my manager bought some
for me at the convenient store.
But it was the triangular type.
I was so shocked.
It went up to here.
Just like that.
Embarrassed
I was surprised too.
The lining was all the way up to here.
Since they can't go outside
they have snacks for dinner
I'm so hungry ~
He keeps on hanging
around near Jihyo
Can't you leave Jihyo's side?
False scandal maker expert
Makes a couple?
MC Yoo
This is just for fun ...
Since they're on that topic
... but who is you ideal type among us?
Who is Jihyo's ideal type
among the Running Man cast?
You may take it lightly, but
it's not a joke to HaHa.
If you pick me, my kid comes along.
Be careful ...
You'll probably watch this with
your wife over the weekend.
It's okay, I'm fine.
So then ...
... what was your wife
like before marriage?
A deer.
And now?
How about after marriage?
Imagine a deer eating a rabbit.
A carnivorous deer?
Carnivorously.
What to do?
Even before marriage ...
... I couldn't understand when women
trim their hair just slightly and ask
Married man Sukjin has a lot to say
"Do you notice something different about me?"
How am I supposed to know?
The men sympathize 100%
After trimming a few millimeter of her hair ....
... and asks if something looks different.
It happened before?
Hey, if you can't tell the difference ...
... then you just die.
Jessica seems to be unable to comprehend
Every time I go home it's a quiz program.
Why?
Married life is a quiz program?
"Do you know why I'm angry?"
When you go back home ...
... buy a bell to say the right answer.
Hit the buzzer before answering.
"Do you know why I'm angry?"
What if you say you're sorry?
What's the situation like when apologizing?
I'll tell you something, she
was cleaning the floor ...
All of you, listen carefully.
My wife was cleaning ...
Sukjin lying on the sofa because he's so tired
... and I was really tired the
day after filming Running Man.
I lifted my feet slightly
to get out of her way.
"Oppa wait, I think we need to talk."
That was when I got this bad feeling.
"Oppa ..."
I asked, why are you angry?
"You don't know why?"
That's the start of the quiz.
And the answering session starts now
"Don't you know why I'm angry?"
is the start of the quiz.
I must get it right in one try ...
... a wrong answer and it's all over.
So I asked ...
... is it because I am not
helping with the cleaning?
"That's not it!"
It's the thought that counts.
You just need to say one thing.
He need to say it sincerely
"Are you tired? Let me help you."
But on the weekend, he went
to the movies with his wife.
Silent when
talking about the movie
Didn't you fall asleep?
No, we watched movie with the kids.
Children copy everything their parents say.
Garnering attention
Like kids listening to their parents
Aren't your son nine?
He's 9 years old now ...
... and he's really innocent and cute.
One day it was really hot and when
we got in the car he said this  ...
"Daddy ..."
What?
"Turn the air-conditioner
all the freaking way up."
The momentary break is over
Do you know how shocking that was?
After the chit-chat they start to run again
"Dad, turn the air-condition
all the freaking way up."
And then...!
Searching for golden piggy banks
in the most unique place
It's about time the instructions come.
Science center
Find two golden pigs
Mission description
A380 (there are 2 piggy banks)
It starts with A ... A380.
A380?
It's here.
It arrived?
Adult Team's mission description
A380?
Could it be area A, area B, area C and so on.
A380 (there are 2 piggy banks)
A museum usually has many areas.
Should we start moving?
I don't think it's the locker.
Hyung, the parking lot.
A parking lot has signs such as A, B, C.
But the number 380 would be a bit too ...
Is the number too big?
Hyung, look.
Oppa, do we need to bring that?
Looking at the museum guide for a hint
Child Team
Here is C section and B section, so I
think we have to look for A section.
What's "math" in English, Sica?
It's "Mathematics".
So it's "M".
Jongkook is better in English than Jessica.
No, I'm not.
Isn't C like Chemical?
So isn't A an abbreviation of something?
As expected of Running Man's brain
What's biology in English?
Isn't it Biology?
You're good at English ~
No, I'm not.
What does A stand for?
Artist?
What's something related to space?
Airplane?
Astronaut ~
Accurate pronunciation
Oh, space pilot.
Jongkook can use difficult English words with ease
We're really smart, seriously.
Complacent
We are so smart
Even we get surprised.
It's all written here.
Earth science, biology, chemistry, physics, mathematics.
The English words Jongkook
used are all written on the board
I didn't see that, seriously.
That's not the case
I really know those words
Oppa, I really thought you were smart.
Disappointed
I think you're right.
We are here right now, so there
should be something on this side.
Earlier we saw the
space airplane room.
It's on the 2nd floor
2nd floor.
It's the 2nd floor.
and the A in aerospace is confirmed
A link between A in A380
Near the helmeted astronaut.
Sica ...
What?
... you did it.
It's upstairs, go.
We have great teamwork right now.
The harmonious Child Team
We're the leading characters.
On the other hand
Adult Team is still clueless
Oh, there's a map over there.
Where have they gone?
It's here.
Oh, it is?
It's here, look.
2nd floor ~
All they know is
that A380 is on the 2nd floor
They already went up to the 2nd floor.
Okay ~
This is advanced science.
Child Team is a step ahead
Advanced science starts with an A.
The country's achievements in
astronomy, aerospace, science
and technology can be seen here
Is this where A380 is?
A380?
Everyone looks for A380 in the exhibit
Yes, look for 380.
Is it here?
At a loss
Look at the second floor.
The golden pig is sitting near them
It's here.
Kyaaaak~
They thought the astronaut was a dummy
But suddenly he walks toward them
What is this?
Pass it to me quickly.
Entrance blocked
The mysterious astronauts surround Jihyo
Throw it.
They pass once Sukjin gets the golden pig
Oh?
Something is wrong?
What? There's nothing in it.
It's a fake and empty golden pig
Jihyo is locked into the mysterious chair
If you find a fake pig
you get a punishment
What's with this?
Mommy ~
Spinning
Punishment:
Sit in a revolving chair that makes you feel
a loss of balance as you would in space
But to her
it is only a punishment...
Highest speed
Ah...
I am seriously...
Do you really want to
stay until the morning?
She had to deal with
Sukjin's bullying
She had to fight against
Jongkook's body
It is so hot and she is
still looking for a mirror.
She had no luck at all today
Jihyo ...
In the end ...
Jihyo also has to deal with this punishment
Looks like you're possessed by a Gumiho.
Are you a fox spirit
in disguise?
Disheveled hair
Fox spirit??
What are you doing?
Jihyo ...
The gyroscope punishment ends
She looks lifeless, lost her mind.
Dizzy
Ah, I'm getting motion sickness.
Of course you'll be dizzy.
Jihyo, what are you doing?
I found a golden pig and somehow ended up here.
What a disastrous day for Jihyo
Revealing the truth
What is A380?
Aerospace engineering exhibition
2nd floor of the museum
The gigantic aircraft Airbus A380
The place where the golden pig is hidden is...
The carriage compartment above the passenger seat
Huh?
Jaesuk found the right place
This is Airbus 380
The airbus 380 is here.
He checks the cockpit
As expected of
detective Joongki
Finds it!
Walkie-talkie ~
He has to tell his team but
he doesn't have a walkie-talkie
It's this.
It's time to look somewhere else
On the other hand
It's right there
Ah...
He missed it just like that
What a waste...
We have to find it.
This place too wide, I
have no idea where it is.
Jaesuk was searching but gets distracted
It says A380 on the outside of the airplane.
Child Team enters A380
Open stuff like the cabinets.
Open it up like a jewelry
box and look around
Jaesuk...
is now only playing
Take a look in that seat cabinet.
Child Team
Closing in on the seat partition
It's here
Here it is.
The authentic golden piggy bank
Child Team
Obtain 1 golden piggy bank
They were wrong about the meaning of 'A'
Still they were first to find the piggy bank
Child Team
What a genius, we're all geniuses.
Meanwhile...
he's still in his childhood
And...
the little brother imitates him
But all of them haven't been
found, there is one missing.
Haven't two been found?
But one them was empty.
Then there's another one.
Revealing the location of the other golden pig
A hard-to-find golden piggy bank
no matter what
That secret is right here...
1 hour ago...
A moving astronaut model...?
Staff member holds the helmet
where the golden pig is hidden
Struggle
Please close the door~
They're coming, get out of the way.
Please make way.
A team arrives earlier than expected
The staff is in panic mode
Just do it roughly and get out of here.
They're here.
Nervous
Child Team is starting to arrive
Extremely nervous
Looks away~
Jessica didn't suspect anything
Jihyo walks in...
Simply passes
Jaesuk
Walks by as expected
Although a lot of people walks by...
They don't even know they are ...
passing a golden pig
Running Man
All of them failed to see the astronaut
He hasn't moved for 20 minutes
There seems to be one over there.
The sharp Sukjin got deceived unknowingly
Phew~
Thank goodness
Looking left
Looking right
Alert!
Jongkook's approaching
Stopping right in front
Rigid
Stiff
What's this?
One more?
Jongkook keeps going around
Ah!
He squats down
Will he see the golden pig inside the helmet?
Thump
Jongkook
Discovered it?
Surely, it wouldn't be there.
It can't be there
So close
Luckily
Keeping still even in front of Jongkook
Lost 10 years in a blink of an eye
Pushing the pig further in where it can't be seen
Phew~
That was a close shave
Where's the other one?
It's so well hidden.
Something is weird, this is ...
Hesitating
This side looks weird
That looks strange.
Although he can't put words on it
he still finds it weird
Why did he come back?
Gimmick~
Why can this be opened?
The door opens?
Indeed Something is strange
Jongkook seems to have found something
People have started to gather
Fidgets~
He's inside the glass showcase
Nice ~
Reaching inside the helmet
Will Jongkook find the golden pig again?
Shaking~~
What's this~~~?
No, it's not there.
People leave due to the mannequin's defense
I think this is right, keep going.
The helmet ~
The helmet on top.
The helmet on the head??
No one suspects that the astronaut is a person
Sukjin enters the glass box
Adult Team
It definitely is there.
Swiftly~
If you lift it...
It's there
Adult Team
Sukjin
Found the golden pig
Old Sukjin is surprisingly glorious
What?
It was a person?
The astronaut tries to escape with the golden pig
Huh...?
The astronaut breaks through using all his strength
What's happening?
Combat
The ownership of this golden pig is still undecided
An astronaut who evaded a lot of problems
Can he safely defend the golden pig again?
Golden pig ended up in
Jongkook's hands
Child Team gets both golden pigs
What a pity~
I found it first.
The hyung with a strong brain but weak body
Our team is awesome.
With great teamwork and strength
Child Team
Victory
The best ~
They seemed crippled in front of us.
That's right.
1, 2, 3, fighting.
A little later
in the museum's garden
Everyone, as you already know ...
... now is the time when we
drift between reality and dreaming.
I know, you can't give us
that long of a resting time.
Yeah ~
We'll fall asleep easily.
What is surprising is you think
Jongkook is a man of few words.
He's not.
His mouth ...
Talkbox during the rest time
Kim Jongkook
He's been going on and on since afternoon.
It's my first tim encountering
this kind of naggy person.
What are you talking about?
Jaesuk is confirming
Jongkook is the
greatest chatterbox
Me?
Yeah ~
By the way, our Jongkook ...
You know president Yang Hyunsuk, right?
* Yang Hyunsuk was in the 90s dance group Seo Taiji & Boys
He the founded YG Entertainment (Big Bang / 2NE1)
Stop it, I don't want to do that.
Just do it once.
So sudden early in the morning
Okay.
He could have done it in the time they were persuading him
Give it a try.
Why do I have to do this right now?
Do it once for the viewers.
I knew that Jongkook was a good dancer,
but didn't know he danced this well.
That's not dancing well.
Just do it.
I can't.
Just do it once for us.
Kim Jongkook ~
So when I was young ...
... Yang Hyunsuk was like a hero in hip-hop.
Of course.
It's such an impression on me.
Once when he was on a show he
gave a short lecture about hip-hop.
Emphasizing a lot on hip-hop
spirit whenever he's on TV
He did that a few times.
They asked these kinds of things ...
"How do you do hip-hop? Teach us."
He often uses the hat.
He wears the hat.
Wearing the baseball cap is a must
"Hip-hop isn't that hard."
"Just imagine that there's a door
in front of you and walk through it."
Expressing the hip hop spirit with his whole body?
How do you go through it?
Just pretend there's a doorway ...
... and go through it.
Just turn around at the door and it's OK
Show us some other dance moves too.
Do you know hip-hop?
Hip-hop feeling in middle of the night
That was funny.
Jongkook's chatter and
door passing hip-hop ends here
Can Kwangsoo do it?
How about Kwangsoo?
So we can stay awake in
the middle of the night.
The door is here, so
just walk right trough it.
How?
How to do it?
Lively~
What...
is this...
Asked to leave
He was too enthusiastic.
What...
Because everyone is sleepy...
As idols ...
I heard Gary dances well too.
No, I can't dance well.
There were dancing competitions in the past.
Yes.
Gary went to those dance contests.
Really?
Is that true?
Blank~
Show us a little bit.
If this gets revealed everyone
will be surprised, but ...
... but it ill be known some day.
He was a candidate to
be a member in H.O.T.
Why are you like that?
Seriously, he was supposed
to take Kangta's place.
Why do you say that?
I'm Kang Gary.
Kang Gary from Jamsil.
Did they add this member?
Gary, show us the performance
you did on the dancing show.
My dance isn't technique based.
Right.
I don't need stuff like this.
It's not about technique, it's
more based on movement.
So, please show us this dance.
"Seo Taiji and Boys" had a dance called ...
... "Butterfly".
Lively
Wriggle
This is an unknown dance
The song was released in 1994
Seo Taiji & Boys 3rd album
<Dreaming of Balhae>
The dance known as
Butterfly dance
Wriggle~
This is how it should be done.
Gary's dance looks completely different from the original
Overly exaggerating on the wiggle
If it was Yang Hyunsuk
who did it instead ...
... the cap is a necessity.
Starts by pulling down the cap
Muscle Hip-hop Wiggle
Beats the original wiggle
If you dance like this ...
Explosive whirlwind
Ending
Instinctive dance move whether sitting or standing
Aigoo~
My knees
It was hilarious.
In a club I don't have to
perform other dances.
I only need to do this
in front of the speakers.
Gary...
is excited
Jaesuk immediately follows
How do you do it?
In front of a mirror.
Are my dancing skills good enough?
Everyone is concentrating on the dance
Sukjin's dance is the same as this one.
Retro dance
When I am dancing that, it
automatically becomes this.
Wo~sa ...
* Wo = Right
I'm satisfied like that, wo~sa.
Jwah~sa ...
* Jwah = Left
Jwah~sa?
What's jwah~sa?
There's an adorable lady on my left.
Jaesuk explains it
Lovely ladies to the left.
To the right.
On the back.
Lovely ladies on the back.
Awake now?
Yes ~
So you're awake now.
Definitely woke up from the sleepy dawn
Incredible ~
What is the game this time?
The next game is?
Something is coming.
What is it?
Bus.
Why would a bus come at this time?
Where does this bus go?
This bus ...
Why are there so many people on the bus?
Overcrowded
Really a lot of people.
What is this about?
What do you want us to do?
A member from each
team has to come out ...
Yes.
... and board the bus
at the same time.
Yes.
Squeeze your way through
the crowd to press the bell.
The first one getting out
of the backdoor wins.
Running there?
Getting out the backdoor.
Incredible.
Is this the game that determines
who'll get the last 500,000 won?
If we win this, we'll win it all.
We need to win this one.
We must win ~
Fighting.
1, 2, 3, fighting.
We have to win this.
When I was younger, I often took
buses which were this crowded.
Me too.
1, 2, 3, fighting.
I'll go first.
You seem to be full of yourself.
Just come out.
Then Jaesuk will go first.
Didn't I just volunteer myself.
That's what I said.
Is HaHA my opponent?
Yes, it'll be me.
HaHa, please go back.
Why?
Jaesuk said he has exercising a lot lately.
Let's go Jaesuk.
Boastful
We'll send Gary out to challenge him.
Kang Gary is going.
Nice to meet you ~
Could you move up a little more?
Jaesuk fighting.
Gary fighting.
Child Team
Gary who lives in Jamsil
Jaesuk, show them.
Adult Team
Exercising grasshopper
Fighting.
Go!
Immediately getting behind
Gary is first to board the bus
Unable to see them among the passengers
Excuse me, let me pass.
Squeezing through the dense crowd
Got through 1/3 in a flash
Don't be like this, hyung.
Jaesuk's over there.
I can't see Gary.
Kang Gary, where are you?
Peaceful Gary is here
I can't hear.
It must be messy and chaotic inside.
At this moment...!
Squeezing through the obstacles which the staff prepared
Indeed
Very packed
Gary!
Just like that Finally through
My clothes are going to rip.
Tear...
To escape from Jaesuk's grasp Gary rips his own clothes...!
Jaesuk, that's the way to do it.
But if sexy Gary leaves the bus
what will happen to his clothes?
Jaesuk, that's the way to do it.
Jaesuk fighting.
Approaching the bell at the rear of the bus
Press it ~
Grab
What is this?
Carnivore grasshopper
Press it ~
Gary
Pressed the bell
Exit door opened
Jaesuk, press it together.
From now on escaping the bus is they key
Just endure a little more.
You can't ~
Gary
Squeezing through Jaesuk's side
The open door is right in front of him
Gary oppa, come out.
Come out ~
Peaceful Gary has aged a lot
Even if I die
I can't let you go...!
How can I let you go...
If you want to escape
I'll rip all your clothes
Go back ~
I have to go
Don't go
Dump
Child Team
Gary's escape
Success
Sigh...
Wreck
He even altered and redesigned
his shirt while inside the bus.
Not bad, it's sexy.
It's going to be the new fashion craze
The 'bus look'
Kwangsoo, you have to win.
Adult Team
Kwangsoo
Child Team
HaHa
If you lose this, we can't
even have a team challenge.
You have to win.
You can do it.
Has the taller contestant an advantage
or the shorter contestant
Ready ... Go.
You have to get in front.
You're doing good.
Throw him away.
Look at that kid.
Throw him and leave
Pinned
This is fun too.
Good job.
Go run.
You won.
Go ~
He won ~
Using his advantage of being small to catch up
He won, he's fast.
He's the best.
Encountering the staffs who are obstructing them
Everyone ...
Both of them are halfway through the crowded bus
They're so fast, Kwangsoo's so tall.
HaHa hyung, it's been a long time.
Also HaHa is being blocked by the staff
Kwangsoo, please ...
I'm begging you, you have to win.
Adult Team
Putting all their hopes on Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo ~
Kwangsoo, that's the way.
You can do it.
Kwangsoo, that's it.
Kwangsoo
Moving forward with the advantage of being tall
That's it.
Now he only needs to press the bell
That's right.
He missed.
Pressed it
That's it.
Okay.
The rear door finally opens
Kwangsoo, you won.
He's long.
HaHa is pulling Kwangsoo's hair
Kwangsoo, come out.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Kwangsoo...
is using towel
attack
Both are completely exhausted
Aargh~
Bringing him back by his nostrils
Fighting spirit
I won't let you go
Kwangsoo's time of suffering
Kwangsoo ... come out.
Hyung ...
Just come out.
One more step
And you'll be outside
Come out and it'll be over.
Plop~
Just come out.
Adult Team
Kwangsoo's escape
Success
I didn't have any expectations for him anyway.
Current score
Adult Team
Child Team
Now let's have a team challenge.
How do we play the team challenge?
First the staff will get off ...
Yes.
... and then all of you will board the bus.
The team that escapes last will lose.
Understood.
Everyone goes in together.
You worked hard.
The passenger are leaving the bus
About 50 passengers squeezed in the crowded bus
Wow, there really was a lot of them.
There were a lot.
I'm sure it's hard, but it's the
last game so please cheer up.
Thankful to the staff who came to help
Let's go.
The men board the bus
Everyone, I'm in the red team.
Everyone ... I'm Song Jihyo.
Jihyo's tries to win over the citizens
Fighting, let the red team win.
This much is okay~
Hello, I'm SNSD's Jessica.
Now it's Jessica's turn
Nice to meet you.
Please take care of us.
Like she's doing an election campaign
Jessica ~
Comparing the cheers
Obviously Jessica is the winner
On by one they're boarding the bus
Air conditioning is coming out, but still ...
The heat, heat from people.
We have to win.
Keep in mind that Jongkook is here.
Like an idiot I came here.
Khun is here?
Yes, Khun is here.
I'll block Sukjin
Let's win, fighting.
Sukjin has no idea what's going to happen
Cheering happily
Let's win.
This is the final game to determine
who will be the winners and losers.
Fighting ~
Finally the passengers are entering the bus
They're coming ~
They're coming in.
Nervous
One by one they all re-enter.
Please help us.
I like everyone here.
Please take care of me.
Thank you.
Just be comfortable.
Jongkook is very strong.
No, I'm not.
He likes to show off his strength.
No, I don't.
Both teams are trying to gain sympathy from the crew
No, it's not like that
Is everyone ready?
Yes ~
Please take care of us.
Alright.
Fighting.
Ready ...
... go.
Group battle
You can't pinch.
Once it begins, the rear of the bus too...
Only grabbing Sukjin in their battle
Hold on, take it easy.
Slowly, Nichkhun.
Jongkook, perfect trap
Their battle techniques are so weird.
Tightly
HaHa grabbed Kwangsoo as well
In the front of the bus
A duel between two pretty boys
Hey ~
On the other side
Sukjin is unable to escape
Their fighting is so weird.
What are you doing?
It's the last person to leave right?
Successfully caught Sukjin first
The last person leaving the bus loses
Jaesuk and Gary
Jaesuk grabs Gary's shirt again
Embarrassment
OMG
What are you doing?
It's Jaesuk again Won't let go till he dies
Gary is close to the exit
Gary will be half-naked
as soon as he steps out
What's going on here?
Just let me off.
Gary's almost outside
What on earth are you doing?
What to do...
Tear~
This is crazy
Gary is first to escapes
Don't look at me...
Get off.
Okay, I'll step off the bus too.
Jaesuk's the 2nd to escape
He looks like a monk
I am ...
Sukjin still being grabbed tightly
Stretch
This is Sukjin's weakness
Nose attack
Ah, so hot ... engine.
HaHa is sitting above the hot engine
Huh?
Sukjin
Truly being caught
It feels good to
have escaped the bus
They can't move an inch
I'll hurry up and go.
Being caught well(?) Sukjin
Hurry up and get out.
HaHa attempts to escape
Take him with you, pull him out.
Come out ~
Hyung ...
Sukjin hyung ...
Indescribable
situation
Wait ...
Sukjin hyung ...
What are you doing?
That's too much.
Sukjin hyung ...
What?
... come out.
I want to, but I'm stuck.
I'm stuck.
He sure talk a lot for someone who's stuck
Hey, come out.
You're not respecting your hyung.
Don't you have an elder brother?
Caring(?) for his hyung
thus taking his burdensome shoes off
Socks gives out a youthful feeling
Jaesuk ...
What is it?
Yell at him.
The second hyung scolds Jongkook in Sukjin's place
Seriously, you ... !
Hey, don't you even respect your hyungs?
KwangSoo and HaHa
almost reach the exit
Don't you have any hyungs?!
The short hyung keeps pulling Kwangsoo's hair today
Sock attack
Sukjin
Don't do it hyung ...
... I'll get off the bus.
Just go out like that.
If this goes on he'll fall asleep
Hey, we can't get off
back here, just step out.
Come out.
Rip~
Just come out first.
I'm on my way.
Unintentionally made
Kwangsoo half-naked
I'll get off.
I want to get out.
Just leave, quickly, will you?
HaHa
Kwangsoo
escape the bus
at the same time
That's right, eject them.
Come here and
dress yourself
The pretty boys are still at the front of the bus
Joongki oppa, come out quickly.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Come out.
Jaesuk ~
Jaesuk!
Pathetic cry
Hurry up and get out.
What are you doing, come out.
Send everyone out
Let Sukjin and Jongkook battle
Hey, let Nichkhun leave.
Come out ~
Why?
Come out.
I have to block him, right?
I don't think we can fight now.
You did well Sukjin.
Oppa, our team has to win.
Everyone left?
Can I go out from here?
Violently
Leave ~
Joongki escapes alone but that wasn't the plan
Hey ... Nichkhun come and help me.
Nichkhun can help Sukjin now
What?
Nichkhun ...
Change of plans
Now Jongkook has to escape quickly
Out of my way ~
Don't block the way, move.
Nichkhun went to block Jongkook
Nichkhun, in the last minute Blocks JongKook with his left arm
Now the battle of strength begins
Can't just stay still
Why are you taking off my shoe?
Hyung, come out.
Jongkook
Nichkhun
Come out ~
Will Jongkook get out first?
Will it be Nichkhun and Sukjin first?
Nichkhun
Blocked Jongkook with only his left arm
Slips~
Hurry up and come out.
... and come out.
Jongkook and staff escape together
Countless bare spots
Are you alright?
Get up.
The unlucky(?) staff that followed also feels giddy
Are you okay?
He's a monster, a monster.
Victory goes to Child Team.
Child Team
Wins
Receives 500,000 won prize money
Bearing in mind that the Child Team is quietly leading
All that is left to decide the winner is the Golden Pig
Are you okay?
Inside the technology center
Adult Team
Strategising
You look exhausted.
Now is the sleepiest time
I'm really very sleepy.
Jihyo, think about it.
If we lose we have to do the
punishment before we go home.
Suddenly it is a must to stay energetic
How many fewer golden
pigs do our team have?
We have 4 and they have 5.
Falling behind in the number of piggy banks
It's here, the message
The two pigs that penetrated the rooftop.
Instructions arrived
There are two pigs that penetrated the rooftop.
Rooftop ~
Will there be any on the rooftop?
'Penetrate the roof'  sounds like a hint
Outdoors.
Break the roof ...
A place where you can see the sky.
The observatory ~
Observ
That's right.
atory
We have to find it as soon as possible.
Adult Team
Departs to search for the observatory
The instructions came.
It's here again?
This game never ends.
Two pigs through the roof.
There are two pigs through the roof.
Wait, ah ...
Shouldn't we hurry and go?
It wouldn't be just an ordinary rooftop.
Child Team
Also started raking their brains
In my opinion ...
... it can only be the rooftop.
If you go through the
roof, it's the rooftop.
They don't really trust HaHa's simple thoughts
Let's go.
Let's think about it first.
There's a guide close by, so let's think there.
Okay ~
Adult Team are searching for the observatory
Should we go out?
Let's go outside first
We really have to win.
Roof?
Arrived at the theater of the science center
Where?
Isn't it that one?
Bingo
They found the observatory
Through the roof ~
Still struggling in front of the directory map
Ah, hyung ...
Ah ~
We are in the Science Hall.
There should be a place to observe the sky.
The roof has to open up in
order to observe the stars.
Go to the place where the roof is penetrated to observe the sky
To see the stars.
He is really very smart.
Really?
You are right again, I saw
an observatory just now.
Brainy Joongki Brawny Jongkook
A perfect combination?
There is?
Right.
Jongkook saw the observatory during the bus game
Be quiet.
A while ago ...
... I was looking around
and saw an observatory.
Are we going to start running?
Moves toward the astronomical telescope
Jessica runs so graciously.
Jessica looks like this when she's running.
One step ahead of finding the observatory
Adult Team
The observatory is right there.
It's there ~
There it is.
Running with
all their might
What is that?
Following closely behind
Child Team
That.
Yes, that's what I saw.
The observatory is there.
Found their target destination
I saw it here.
All that is left is to battle with time
Next building is the observatory.
Two teams are sprinting toward a common destination.
Hyung, behind the building ...
Hurry up.
... the astronomical observatory.
The kids are coming so hurry up.
Ah, they're already there.
We are one step behind.
Which team will
find the 2 golden pigs first?
Going to the same place.
This is why you can't have poor stamina.
Adult Team
Enters the observatory first
It's here, search quickly.
So where are the golden pigs?
Where?
Trying to beat the Child Team
Child Team now enters the observatory
Right at this time
Sparkling
Golden piggy bank
Both teams discovered the golden pig
I'm right here
Distant
That looks like one.
Joongki tries to climb up
Still quite a distance
No ~
Nichkhun ~
Jaesuk's calling for Nichkhun's support
How do we get up there?
How are we supposed to go up?
Come and get me
On top of the roof ...
... but there's nowhere to go up.
The golden pig
Their current position
Hyung, over here.
What?
He called Jaesuk
but useless Sukjin came instead
Over here.
Okay.
Hyung, block Gary
Block Gary.
Gary followed Kwangsoo and Sukjin
"High-kick" Kwangsoo climbed up to the roof
* Kwangsoo had a role in the
drama "High-kick to the roof"
The golden pig is
watching(?)
Looking around~
Wow
We can't get it from here.
No way of getting
to the golden pig
Now they realized
how high up the golden pig is
Let me think.
Jongkook What did you find?
A control for the roof
Power
Runs to the roof as soon as he presses it
The roof starts to move
If the roof closes they can reach the golden pig
The golden pig is slowly getting closer
The roof is closing, so we have to go up.
Go up. Up.
I closed the roof, but how do I go up?
Hyung ...
There's not much time left
Up there.
The roof is closing fast
It's coming, hold him.
Kwangsoo catches Gary
Come up and grab it.
Catch it ~
Who will get the golden piggy bank?
How do I get up there?
Jongkook doesn't find a place to go up
How do I go up?
Behind you ~
That's right.
That's right!
Sukjin will just grab it like this?
Sadness
Happiness
No!
That's right ~
It belongs to Sukjin
Because it was a harder task
Twice as happy
But I was the one who closed the roof.
Adult Team wins a golden pig
Did you find it?
Collapsed
Close the roof like that
What to do?
Now there's only 1 golden pig left
To find the last one
Jongkook and Jihyo go to another room
The telescope on the other side
There should be a pig
where the roof opens up
Found the controls
Is it the roof again?
Is there anyone from our team?
Alert
Oppa ...
Jongkook
Pressed the button again
The roof opens slowly
Is the golden pig really there?
Oppa, Jaesuk oppa ...
Frantically calling Jaesuk
Hurry up and come here.
Frustrated
Come quickly.
Jaesuk investigates it
Did you find it?
Oppa hurry.
Joongki seizes the opportunity
There's nothing?
Huh?
Back to looking for the golden pig
If it isn't there, then there
is no where else to hide it
The last gold pig
is actually in here
Kwangsoo missed it
This time
Jaesuk ... ?
Eh?
Just looked at the lid?
Of course it's like this
This time Sukjin goes towards the golden pig
Short team's HaHa comes over
Sukjin
Found the golden pig
It's not here ~
Smart 40 year old
Tries to get rid of HaHa Pretends not to see it
Didn't it work...?
Hey, it's here.
Drags HaHa away
It's over there
It's over here.
It's right here.
Get the last Golden pig
It's in there.
Fierce Battle
Gary goes in for the pig
Who does the golden pig belong to?
Jihyo got the piggy bank
Adult Team
Acquires all of the 2 golden pigs
Jihyo finally got it.
Sukjin and Jihyo combination Success
The long night has finally
passed
And the morning finally arrives
at the museum
Wait, how much is this?
Time to decide which team gets to leave
We only have two.
If they have 500 won coins and ours
are 10 won coins, then we can lose.
Mysterious piggy banks
We can.
Of course.
No one knows how much money
there is in each piggy bank
Just now Jihyo said ...
... she just wants to go home.
Jihyo stayed behind last week as well
Did she lose last time?
Yes, she did.
Will she leave early today?
It's already a bright day
We're starting out 500,000 won behind.
Adult Team
Child Team
They are 50 and 10 won coins.
That look nice.
It can change depending
on how many they have.
Why is there so many?
The coins keep coming out
It was 534,000 won.
If we get more than 34,000
won, then we'll win.
That's right.
So if we go past 34,000 won, we win?
Needs more than 34,000 won to win
Child Team
That's right.
34,000 won is all we need.
34,000 won.
If they have only 10 won coins,
then we still have a chance.
Just 34,000 won.
Kids Team starts counting
Silver color is coming out.
It's all silver.
Here we go.
The results are hard to tell
100 and 340 won coins are coming out
Please...
Of course...
We went past it.
Child Team wins
Bitter
This is sad.
Adult Team has to stay for the punishment
Disappointing, we lost in the end.
When will the doors open?
Now it's time to leave
You have to open the doors for us.
Thank you.
Thank you for the hard work.
Child Team leaves after
18 hours in the museum
Ah, sorry.
The world outside
We're outside.
Freedom.
We're out~
Oppa, look at the sunrise.
1, 2, 3, ...
... freedom.
Today, we have to clean up.
Empty~
Everything has to be clean
before the museum opens.
Today's punishment
Clean the museum
This large place...
Everyone's diligently cleaning their area
If you date a guy,
you ignore him right?
I think you're right.
* Word play
That is also a charm.
Are you confessing your love?
Why are you cleaning like that?
Clean seriously.
Sleepily cleaning
Clean properly.
What is that?
Bodies are tired after 18 hours
then a punishment
That's understandable.
Fallen
He is really tired.
Sukjin fell asleep but Nickhun is lurking nearby
Disturbed
Hello Running Man, I'm Kim Yuna.
Next landmark
Seoul Tower
I will cheer for you so run hard.
On the next episode
People will fight to win
People will be betrayed
Strangers will be used
Help
will be needed
But who will answer the call?
Oppa, fighting.