Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Mostly based on hardsubs
by KJK Global & byakucii
City Center Landmark
And
The unfamiliar landmark at night
Now in the city at night
Running Man in action
A new concept action variety show
You can't imagine
Their night ...
... will be revealed now
Running Man
Some night on June 2010
A car approaches the SBS building
And one man gets out of the car
Ah ya ya ...
What is this?
Yoo Jaesuk
Opening Mission: Find the newly
reconstructed rooftop garden
Rooftop Garden: 9th Floor
8th floor
Jaesuk's current location
The rooftop garden is
located on the 9th floor
... but Jaesuk got
off on the 8th floor
Hello.
The security guard on patrol
Where is the rooftop garden?
How do you get there?
Nervous
Could you please tell
me how to get there.
I heard there's a variety show.
That's right.
Nice to meet you.
I have to get back to work.
Are you going to leave
without telling me?
Will I appear on the
show by any chance?
Will it come on screen?
If it's not interesting,
it will be edited out.
At this time two cars arrive
HaHa
Kim Jongkook
Hello, long time no see.
A loyal meeting in the lobby
Look for the roof garden together
Cars continue to arrive
Who are they?
You know this from before.
Their first meeting...
Will they be able to find it?
Heliport
I think it's here ... It's here?
Rooftop garden?
Ah, it's right here.
Jaesuk finally succeeds
in finding the rooftop garden
Ah, it's here.
Jaesuk slowly enters
Why is it like this?
Lost
Eh, it's like this again.
At SBS's 9th floor
The rooftop garden
Do I just stand here
until everyone gets here?
I said, do I just stand here?
Maunders
Maunders ~
There they are.
Jongkook and HaHa.
Come here quickly.
Suddenly A formal greeting
Don't do that
HaHa, don't be like that.
It's embarrassing.
Rigid
That friend is ... ?
Oh, Kwangsoo?
"High Kick Through the Roof"
A shiny newcomer Kwangsoo
Ah, Kwangsoo ...
Hello ~
Please move over.
Oh! He is tall
HaHa quickly gives up his spot
No, move back.
My leg hurts.
Please get up.
Hello.
Bends over to greet Friendly Kwangsoo
First of all, the title of this
show is ... Running man.
If his legs are apart
he will be shorter ..
Don't walk, run.
This is something very ...
Isn't it Health Man?
No, it's not.
A handsome silhouette
never seen before
Firstly ...
Hello.
Song Joongki.
Actor
Song Joongki
Drama: "Obstetrics and Gynecology Doctors"
Newcomer attracting a lot of attention lately.
The pretty boy with a beautiful smile.
He's even wearing a flower brooch?
Ah, to celebrate the opening.
Flower... brooch?
Charisma
Someone else is coming...!
Joongki ...
Oh, Gary.
Hip-Hop musician LeeSsang's Gary
Gary ...
"I'm not smiling" "Leessang Blues"
The star behind many hit songs LeeSsang's Gary
Aren't you Jung Daesae?
Soccer star
Jung Daesae
Hip-Hop star
Gary
Jung Daesae, aren't
you looking good?
He looks good but funny somehow
Why are you laughing?
Yo, what's up?
Rappers and their hip-hop style of greeting
Oh!
PAK
Your chest is too big, man
Chest too big.
Pants ~
Firstly, Gary ...
... also Joongki and Kwangsoo,
nice to meet you guys.
It started raining, but we have
to continue and we'll get wet.
Are you alright?
Who is this? Walking in the rain
I'm alright.
Hello hyung.
20 years of variety Ji Sukjin
Hello ~
I know Sukjin very well.
This hyung is very nervous now.
Nervous because he's on
an outdoor variety show?
Although he seems very natural ...
... he is actually very nervous now.
Yes, its been a long time since
I have been out of the studios.
It is his first outdoor variety show
since "Boyar Expedition" in 2003
Is today your first time meeting ...
... Joongki?
A female figure?
Yes.
Ah, someone's coming.
Confident
Sexily walking towards us
with her head up high ...
Her first sentence is...?
Give me an umbrella ... umbrella.
Hyori.
Ah, seriously.
I was told that I'm the special invited
guest, how can you let me get wet?
Tonight's main character.
Ah, is that so?
I'm the main character for today?
Running Man first guest
The invincible Lee Hyori
Yes, you're tonight's star.
Please wait.
My mascara is dripping.
Where? How?
Where don't want to get
wet, your shoulders or...?
My eyes.
Ah, eyes.
Yeah.
To begin a show this way isn't bad.
Because of the rain I drew
my eyeliner thicker today.
Ah yeah.
Another back view of a lady?
Someone is coming.
She who came here
listening to the little rain?
Hello.
Aiyoo, Jungeum.
Jaesuk oppa.
Running Man first episode guest
The refreshing Hwang Jungeum
It's seems like it's been a while
since meeting with an audience.
Don't walk, run ... Running
Man ... Hello everyone.
Sunday night New variety show
We'll start one by one.
Since this is the first show ...
... please do a brief self-
introduction and greeting.
Starting with Ji Sukjin.
Hello.
You all know me, Ji Sukjin, right?
The rain starts to pour...!
It's raining hard!
Why did it start when I'm talking?
I've done many variety shows, but ...
... I've never had openings
where it rained like this.
They say it's rainy season.
Bad luck rain.
It's been fine all day
and suddenly it rains
This won't really do.
Hyung ...
Sukjin walked over to get a raincoat
... you can't do that.
No hyung, you can't do this outside.
What are you wearing that for?
Ah, I really haven't been
outside for a long time.
Dumps!
We'll finish this quickly from now on.
No raincoats?
Joongki, please introduce yourself.
Yes.
Hello, I'm Song Joongki and
I'm 26 years old this year.
Like a blooming flower
Born in 1985
Song Joongki
It seems like Kwangsoo and
myself are the youngest here.
Cute
I'll work hard with the hyungs, fighting.
* Hyung = What boys call older boys
Ambitious
Desire
Next up, our Kwangsoo.
Hello.
Soaked
I'm Lee Kwangsoo.
Suddenly, the rain pours down
Why did it get so bad from the start.
I can't see...
I ...
I... am a sprout!
Yes?
...am a sprout.
Ignoring
Messy~
Oppa, Jungeum's tears are flowing.
Are you okay?
Put this on.
I'm not done with
my introduction
I still have
a lot to say
Everyone is distracted by the rain
Hello.
Due to the rain no one hears him
I was born in 1985.
Wait, Kwangsoo is introducing himself.
Listen to him.
Yes, I am Lee Kwangsoo.
He continues the introduction in the rain
I'm 26 years old.
Kwangsoo is crying.
You're filming a drama, right?
Ah yes, together with Jungeum.
Smile ~
He smiles
Immediately~
Right now, we're filming Dong Yi.
He's become very popular.
Thank you.
He's someone to look forward to.
Please tell us about your plans.
I will strive hard.
Newbie Kwangsoo
Recently under the spotlight He will
attract you with his unique charms
What about Gary?
You've come on a variety show again.
Hello, I'm Kang Gary who live in Jamsil.
Your surname is Kang, oppa?
Kang Gary.
Although I don't know Gary very well ...
... I heard he's an incredible friend.
Gil oppa can move aside.
I heard he's at least
10 times of Gil's power.
Guards
Nervous
I heard he's at least
10 times of Gil's power.
I'm a witness.
We look forward to your effort
Mr. Kang Gary !
There are many other witnesses as well.
Then we will work hard.
Please anticipate.
Don't walk ...
Run.
Running Man.
The sudden weird pose that came out
Since it's the first time, just use this.
Okay, Hyori says use this.
Embarrassed
How would you do it?
Running Man ... Bang!
Bang!
What is this?
Old fashioned!
Running Man ... Bang.
Seems to fit Sukjin well...
Just like that...
Running Man
The first episode starts
Their first Landmark
Seoul's Yong Dong Po Gu's T Shopping Mall
With a total of 37,000 square meters
and 10,000 people visit every day
The largest shopping mall
with about 200 stores
New concept variety show
Running Man
Once the exits are sealed,
the game starts
Search for the secret tube
that holds the secret code to exit
The device given to the two
teams to receive instructions
The unimaginable through race and game
Collect the secret codes
to escape before the mall opens
Awaiting the losing team is
an unexpected punishment
Running Man
According to their shopping characteristics
they're divided into Cheap and Expensive Team
You've all finished changing, right?
Yes ~
Expensive Team
Joongki Jungeum Kwangsoo Jaesuk Jongkook
When the instructions come, just head over will do.
Yes ~
Message arrived
First Landmark
'T' Shopping Mall
Ah, it's near.
Just head there will do.
Let's go.
Hurry, get in.
Expensive Team sets off
But what are we going
to do when we get there?
They have no idea what they will be doing
Nowadays, the producers don't
reveal such things anymore.
Jungeum, today we might film
overnight, is that alright with you?
Oh, I slept the whole day today.
Previously, when we filmed
High Kick Through the Roof ...
Kwangsoo & Jungeum starred in the same drama
Ah yes, the both of you.
During the overnight filming,
she really wasn't tired at all.
To me, overnight filming is nothing.
Suddenly
barging in
Ah ... it wasn't easy for
Kwangsoo to say something.
Oops
Kwangsoo is a very reserved person
Hmm...
Kwangsoo keeps everything in his heart.
Exactly ~
He remembers them.
I was thinking if it was because
what I said was boring so ...
No, that's not it.
Kwangsoo... Will he hang in there well?
At the same time...
The other vehicle in transit
No matter what, Hyori has quick eyes.
Cheap Team
Hyori Gary HaHa Sukjin
I can quickly sense what's going
on and oppa can use your brain.
Actually, my IQ is quite high.
Calling himself smart
Sukjin
How many years since
the last time you ran?
I don't run!
You should since this is Running Man.
Don't worry, I grew my
nails to scratch people.
And grabbing people by the hair ~
Yes. the hair.
Traveling into the changing city night
Finally reached 'T' Shopping Mall
Cheap Team arrives
The empty mall with nothing
finally enters
This is the start.
No, this is really... This is huge.
Take a look
the interior is huge
It's beautiful.
Ah really ...
... we will be stuck here today.
They're here ~
Expensive Team arrives
Lost ...
Is this where they want us to be running?
They don't want us to walk, but run.
Wow, this is too much.
The time now is 10:50 PM
When the shops are all closed
Now is when the shops are all closed.
You guys haven't been to a mall where
the shops are all closed, have you?
It's what every female dreams of.
Just like a scene in a drama.
The kind where you'd come in ...
... and just shop as you wish.
I feel happy
imagining it
Nods
Both teams, from now
until the stores open.
The team that loses the
game will not be let out.
Rule 1
Only the winning team
can leave the mall
From now on ...
Rule 2
The losing team will get
an unexpected penalty
... we are enemies.
Yes and also this name tag ...
If you get caught, this comes off.
Is that so?
If that happens, you won't be
able to participate in the game.
Rule 3
When an opponent takes your
name tag, you're out of the race
Ah, is that so?
That... Can you see that?
What's that?
Shocked
Exits Sealed
In the middle of sealing the exits
Wow, it's like a movie.
This is totally like a movie
Happy although they're being locked up
Blank~
Once all the exits are locked
no one can leave
West entrance
Sealed
East entrance
South entrance
Sealed
11:00 PM
Main Entrance is sealed
Sealing is complete
First, from this point,
we can't go anywhere.
Only the wining Team can leave?
Not even a footstep outside
No one else?
The winners can go
home just like that?
Regardless of the time?
Now, Cheap Team ...
... please move to the
3rd floor immediately.
Wow, this really is like a movie.
Cheap Team, lets go.
Hyori ....
... do well.
Lets go ~
The search for the first code has begun
Cheap Team
Heading to the 3rd floor
From now on, there is no one who is
going to give us hints on where to go.
Where is the third floor?
This is second floor.
Your is stamina is pretty good.
Right from the start
An overexcited 43-year old Sukjin?
I'm getting tired already.
Wait, let's come up with a plan.
Because Hyori is known for foul
play, let's come up with a plan.
That's alright.
In order to keep in touch with other
members, they are given walkie-talkies
Hello, 1, 2, 3.
Grasshopper, come out. Over.
Grasshopper is out.
Nice ~
Where should we go now?
There should be a message.
Waiting for the message
about the first code location
It's here.
The message has arrived
Go to the store that sells
the most expensive item.
Hello! This is SBS Running Man
Find the store that sells the most
expensive item in this building
Difficult level 1
Hyori knows.
Their 1st code is at the most expensive store
Wait, no ...
If were talking about expensive,
shouldn't it be jewelry or similar?
That's right.
A convincing guess from the start
No matter how expensive the bags are,
they can't be as expensive as jewelry.
Mustn't it be designer items?
No ~
Go to the most expensive place in the mall.
I know where it is?
Where is it?
In most shopping malls, the first
floor has the most expensive stores.
Let's stay calm.
Let us first start moving
and have a look around.
Okay, lets go.
First Let's start searching randomly
Expensive Team
We aren't going shopping.
Even so, I'm still happy.
Urgent
I need to go use the restroom first.
No, hold it in.
So busy looking around, but
Jaesuk wants to go to the toilet
It's really urgent.
Let's move together, first.
It doesn't seem to be here.
Ah~ ♥
What surprised Jungeum?
None other than...
Shoes that ladies are attract to
These shoes look like they
have been waiting for her
Stop her, get her.
As if attracted by
a magnetic force
Jungeum is a shopaholic
No, it's not there.
But those are expensive things too.
Really?
Yes.
Beauty, fancy, art ...
It's not the food court,
young sports or casual.
Cheap Team
Focused on analyzing the mall's directory
Beauty area?
Hyori uses her shopping experience
I don't think it will be beauty,
it's more of make up and stuff.
Let's try going over there.
I don't think it's there, oppa.
I've shopped before, so I know.
To be honest, I am not
familiar with these things.
The shopping world is difficult for men
It should be sports accessories.
If it's about expensive ...
Where's the most expensive item?
Oppa, it doesn't seem to be here.
Level 3F seems to be
filled with accessories
Yeah, it doesn't ~
Lets go the jewelry area.
Let's go up first, since no one is there.
Jewelry is normally ...
On the first level?
You have to think carefully.
Expensive Team is at 1F
Cheap Team started on the 3rd floor.
Since the teams are on 1F respective 3F
We have to move accordingly.
There is a big possibility
that it's on the 2nd floor.
the code must be on 2F?
Hyung, we should go up.
Go upstairs.
Don't walk, run.
Let's go to the toilet first.
Being able to run like this
in a shopping mall is ...
This program seems so fun.
Jungeum finds this place very interesting
While she running, Jungeum keeps giggling.
He he ~
Why are you so happy?
It feels like returning to childhood.
I actually really need to use the toilet.
Urgent
Let's look for the toilet first.
Someone go find a bathroom ~
The secret code is nothing
Jaesuk only cares about the toilet
I'm dying
I think Jaesuk has to go
to the bathroom first.
Oh there it is.
I'll go to the toilet.
I shall go too.
You have to keep the walkie
talkie on even in the bathroom.
Hurry
What kind of camera would
follow us even in here?
Go to the shop with the most
expensive merchandise.
Where is the most expensive item?
Bag? Necklace? Cosmetics? Clothing? Shoes?
The answer is this crystal brand shop
Expensive crystal products
Magnificent and valuable products too
Among those, the most expensive product is ...
... this 200 million won watch
Right behind it
the first pass code
Jaesuk is still using the toilet
Jaesuk oppa, does it feel nice?
Jungeum, you shouldn't be like that.
Call Jongkook.
Jongkook oppa, does it feel nice?
Don't ask, a lady shouldn't ask that.
Fooling around at the toilet...
The very carefree Expensive Team
The other team is working hard
Cheap Team
Let's go to the Jewelry area.
Let's go and have a look
around since it's not here.
Jewelry is usually ...
... on the first floor.
Jewelry is not on the top floor
We have to head down.
Oppa, check if 1st floor
has any jewelry shops.
See if they have jewelry shops.
Over there.
What?
Did Sukjin notice something?
Isn't that it?
Ah, yes.
Correct
The place that sells the most expensive item
That's expensive.
Is it?
Of course, it should be there.
Jongkook, does it feel good?
Carefree Expensive Team who
isn't aware of the situation
Don't ask.
You shouldn't be asking such question.
Fun ~
Hide ~
Surprised
Shocked
Catch them, don't move!
Gary, get them!
Expensive team
Wasting time at the toilet
If you get your name tag
ripped off, then you're out
Let's search, hurry up.
Seizing the moment
Hyori runs to the jewelry shop
Why ... ?
Why is it so loud?
Hyung, it's not time for such a thing.
Rapper Gary is right in front of them
In a split second
Rip off the name tag.
Gary is attacking Kwangsoo's name tag
Wait a moment ~
Kwangsoo
Also Jungeum is in danger
No, don't.
Taking a looking at the situation
Expensive Team's Joongki goes in
Behind Joongki is ...
Kim Jongkook
Save me~
Must hide from Jongkook first
Full-time sprinter Joongki
Turning the situation around
Surprisingly Sukjin is also very fast
Avoided Joongki very well
Where are you Hyori?
She is ...
Seizing the chaotic moment
to run to the Jewelry shop
Where did they go?
I'm all alone, where are they?
Luxurious
Oppa, Gary oppa.
Where are you, Hyori?
Come to the Jewelry shop.
Okay, I'm coming.
Starts to hurry too late
Expensive Team
That's why I said that it's better to control ...
Where is it?
Has a feeling that it's here...
Where are you?
Come to the Jewelry shop.
It must be here.
Oh, this is... Wait a second.
Hyori noticed something
I found it, this is ... Oppa.
Gary, I found it.
Cheap Team
Found the first secret code
The first password is?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Number of people =
Okay ~
What is this?
They found it.
Round 1
I found it.
First secret code race
Cheap Team victory
Where did you go?
Left me alone, where did all of you go?
The only person OUT
sitting next to the toilets
How long do I have to stay here?
After 25 minutes...
Have you found the code?
Yeah, we found it.
Hyori has, as expected of Hyori.
She found it herself.
Then let's share it.
Why reveal the number?
Jungeum, ask her.
What's the code?
Look her in the eyes and ask.
Opened your eyes wider.
Scared
You can't be afraid.
Hyori unnie is so scary.
No, I can't have that kind of image.
What do we have to do now?
Game.
The PD is passing the game
* PD = Producer
Ah, this person ...
This ... Okay, I got it.
Okay, it's done.
Immediately got the feeling
Let me explain the game.
Just look.
This race is a clothes hanger competition.
Right now, on the clothes rack ...
... there are four pieces of clothes
that side and five on this side, right?
The number of clothes equals the
number of members in each team
Wear the clothes and
move forward together.
With the clothes rack? Unbelievable
It's written like that?
You must have read it wrong.
Hyori, would I lie to you?
Did the nations MC misunderstand it?
Would I lie?
It's true.
I means four people
have to form a line.
Exactly.
And the winning team can
start the next race first.
You have to win first and then
you can start to find the code
From what I saw in the first round ...
... it's very important to set off early
and immediately start searching.
It is my first time playing
like this in a shopping mall.
It's nice since there's no people.
We're starting, please start the camera.
Starting to get nervous
variety newbies Joongki & Gary
Cue!
(Recording starts)
Wait ~
That's not it.
Why?
Gary, it's not yet.
That's the cameras cue.
Mistook the start of recording
as the start of the game
How can the game start
just like that, suddenly?
Because the two are new to variety
Please wait a moment.
Since it's the first time ...
MC Yoo
Variety basics course
When they say cue  it means that
the camera is going to start rolling.
Yeah ~
Start  is for the game to start.
You got it?
Everyone fighting!
A kind variety teacher
MC Yoo~
Let's clap.
Livening up the atmosphere
Wa~it.
Ready.
Finally
The variety newbies are nervous again
Start ~
Speed
Joongki is fast too
Song Joongki ~
Dress quickly and run with the rack
Joongki, wear your clothes properly first.
First ...
Joongki is first to start
Woo~sh
The way he is running is a little ...
Gary sets off too
Finally turning
Joongki has a sharp turn
Urgent situation
For the two newbies, winning
is more important than laughter
Hit!
Hit~
Joongki was faster than Gary
You have to wear the
clothes with the hanger.
Expensive Team
Second person Jongkook
Cheap Team
Second person Sukjin
Oppa ...
Joongki fighting.
Right, left ~
What are we doing in the early morning.
Very serious...
Happily experiencing the human hanger
The onlookers are embarrassed
Cheap Team leads by a little
Calm down ~
Cheap Team
Third person HaHa
Joongki ~
Expensive Team
Third person is Jaesuk
Ready? Go.
HaHa hasn't put on the clothes properly
Go ~
Just go.
Right ~
Jaesuk's footing
is wrong
They are saying right foot
But Jaesuk moves his left
Suddenly~
Jaesuk, just stand on top.
Seized the chance to lead
Cheap Team
Turning around at the halfway point
Now going to fetch the last member
Jaesuk moves the wrong foot again
Hurry ~
Last person Hyori
Cheap Team
Expensive Team
Last people
Jungeum + Kwangsoo
Go.
1, 2 ~
Expensive team starts too
Right foot ~
...Huh? Stands still...
Why didn't you wear it Jungeum?
Joining after it started
Just like that The gap gets wider again
Jungeum just stands on the
rack due to her nervousness
But the gap seems to have gotten large
Conflict~
Pinch!
Whoops!
Hyori is holding tightly on to Jaesuk's hair
When did the gap become so small?
Cheap Team still has a slightly lead
Will they win just like that?
Or a big reversal win?
At this moment...!
Speedy~
Jongkook is on full power
This... What happened...?
They are all standing on the rack
Only Jongkook and Kwangsoo run
Expensive Team
Expensive Team reached
the finish line first
Drama-like reverse
Expensive Team
Cheap Team
Isn't pulling hair a foul?
Outdoor variety newbie lost his soul
Gary, take this off.
Variety newbie
The last round is the deciding battle.
Hyori and Jungeum, the both of
you should go against each other.
Good ~
You can do it.
You haven't told Jungeum
my nickname, right?
She should know.
You know it right?
But I hope it's not true.
I hope you don't get hurt.
It's really not like that, but due to
the game it will turn out this way.
You start to focus.
You must try really hard at this game.
Smirk~
When Hyori has that expression ...
... it means she figured
out a good way to cheat.
I know since I've worked
many times with Hyori.
If Hyori smiles with her eyes then ..
... she's thought of a good way to cheat.
Be careful.
Hyori fighting.
One round to decide the winner
Let her see what foul play is.
Start ~
That way...
Suddenly?
Grabbed it
Did her smiling eyes mean this
Ya, Lee Hyori ... !
A scary scenario for a newbie
What is this...
A match between women
Push~
How dare you
But Hyori chases her
Even though Hyori cheated
Jungeum is in the lead
Hyori grabs her again
Excited
How long is she going to hold on?
Is Hyori going to?
Eh?!
Oh my!
The threatening hair pull
Jungeum, grab her too.
This time it's Jungeum
They are scary.
The hair pull once again
Could it be?
Retaliation
Late-night fight at the shopping mall
Women's boxing tournament
I will not lose
Dizzy
Zoom~
A second later
I'm scared
Expensive Team Jungeum wins
A mess!
Let's reconcile.
The first time someone cheated Hyori
Hyori, stay calm.
Come out. Where is she?
Forgive me
Sorry.
Surprisingly a strong girl Jungeum
Jungeum isn't normal either.
Jungeum, with her innocent face.
Everyone, please don't misunderstand.
They get along well.
The game was just too wild.
How about shaking hands?
Shake hands.
Slap
So cool.
Well known cool sister Hyori
It has been a long time
since I saw Hyori scared.
When was I like that?
It showed a little.
The winning team will receive the
clue to the secret code first and ...
... the losing team will receive
a penalty before they proceed.
Okay, great.
It's okay ~
Is it really okay?
Lonely~
Really?
For the Cheap Team ...
... you have to drink this
before you get the clue.
Punishment
Cheap Team has to drink a bowl
of water before starting the race
And we don't have a penalty, right?
Expensive Team gets the hint right away
Is that right?
Aren't we supposed to
continue running later?
Then we'll need to go to the
bathroom throughout the race.
You can just run to the bathroom.
I can't believe it
After you start, we'll set off.
Don't breathe in the middle.
Punishment begins
Ready ... go.
The clue is here.
It's coming.
It's here.
Message arrived
Hello! This is SBS Running Man.
Hint: In times of expensive oil
prices, we solve air conditioning/
heating problems by 0000.
Go to 0000.
Difficulty level: 3
We solve climate problems by 0000
Maybe it has a sunroof on the top?
Meanwhile the Cheap Team is ...
I hate sucking on this.
Everyone generously
giving theirs to Sukjin
It's so disgusting.
Hey ~
You're probably thirsty from
all the running so drink up
What are you guys doing?
Kwangsoo, think of a 4 letter word.
Joongki, Jungeum, Jongkook.
Let's all think of a 4 letter word.
The most important now is
to think of a 4 letter word.
Hybrid?
That's five letters.
It's too many syllables
The hint is air condition.
That's right.
Where is the second secret code?
What is the word?
Expensive Team
They go upstairs without a plan
Look up there.
Huh?
Don't do that.
Okay, fine.
Ha!
They do anything since no one's around
Let's see, what's there?
Regardless of what it is, just say
something with four syllables.
Think of any word with 4 syllables.
Ah, this is so tiring.
You were so bright and
enthusiastic just a while ago.
You had fun.
But the question is so hard.
Complaining
Let's think while sitting down.
It's not like we can figure
it out by walking around.
Laid back?
They sit down without a plan
Think of something with four syllables.
Repeating
Jaesuk focused on syllables
Isn't heating and cooling
powered by electricity?
Oil.
Electricity.
Wind power.
No, does that even make sense?
Immediate rejection
Why not? This place is so tall.
Should we look at the message again?
Carefully
Ignoring
Should we look at the message again?
Kwangsoo tries hard to say something
It can't be because this place isn't windy.
That doesn't make sense.
I think the answer can be in the prob...
Again
You ask me why it isn't windy?
I think the ...
Kwangsoo, what did you say?
Kwangsoo just tell me.
Sorry, Jongkook kept on talking.
You guys... So... I'm kind of upset...
It's not that we don't
want to listen to you.
It's because this side keeps ...
He finally gets a chance to talk
Kwangsoo, tell us.
Out of nowhere
What? It's okay. Tell us.
Kwangsoo is blocked again
Can it be related to clothing?
Can't it be slack ramie?
Oh my ...
... god
No, it's just seems like it's a ramie.
His idea is beaten by slack ramie
People who shop always wear a ramie.
The city's air conditioning
was done by clothing?
Still doing their punishment
Gary is the man.
Give us the clue please.
Punishment is over
Let's take a look.
In times of expensive oil prices,
we solve air conditioning by 0000.
Go to 0000.
Central Heating Room.
Solar energy?
Have to use their brains since they are behind
Can solar energy provide cooling?
Do we have to go to the roof?
The roof?
It could be the roof.
Let's talk while we walk.
The Cheap Team is focused
It's not oil or gas.
In order to save gas ...
Let's go up first.
Startled
That team doesn't know either.
Do they see us?
Discovered each other
They saw us ~
Don't want to reveal where they are headed
I can see them
Since they are hiding like that, does it
mean that they already know the answer?
No, they still don't know.
They are just trying to
take off your name tag.
Kwangsoo experienced it before
Let's take a look upstairs.
Expensive Team is on the 4th floor
Cheap Team on their way to 5th floor
The roof ~
No, maybe it isn't the roof.
The roof is right ~
Can the secret code be located at the roof?
It is rooftop.
Not hiding anymore Running...!
We'll win if we get there first, hurry.
We have to find it.
Be quiet and don't act like you're in a hurry.
Can you lock the door?
You can't?
Wait, isn't it the rooftop?
Expensive Team is in no hurry
That's what I kept saying.
Let's go to the roof and take a look.
Those guys are running.
Let's go to the roof.
Hurry ~
Where?
Isn't it there?
This way and that
Hurry and film us
Cameramen, you must film us
Oh my God.
Chases although they started first
Run ~
Are the other team already on the roof?
Cheap Team is already at the rooftop
No, I don't think so.
Is the secret code at the rooftop?
Roof park.
There is a sign here.
Where?
It's here.
Answer: Roof garden
It reduces the temperature of
the building by about 16.5 %
The sky park.
Run ~
Run, they are coming.
Catch them.
They are here, run.
Run ~
The gap between them is getting shorter
Be careful.
Catch up with them.
Hurry up and run.
Have to be faster than the other team
The secret code isn't easily visible
The person who gets it first is the keeper
I found it.
Found it
Here it is
Hurry.
Here.
The second secret code
The secret code is placed
on top of the sculpture
Its here ~
Where is it?
Get the secret code
that's hanging in the air
Bend down.
Gary immediately gets down
Will Hyori get the secret code?
No!
It's mine!
She lost it
Hyori was off by a little
Whose hands will grab the secret code?
Fighting for the bottle
Confrontation
HaHa takes this chance to climb
HaHa just needs to reach out and grab it
But at this time
Snatch
190cm Kwangsoo jumps and easily gets it
Expensive Team wins the 2nd round
This game was a disadvantage for us.
Second number =
Thanks to Kwangsoo's height.
Proud
3 hours since lock-down
We need to finish filming
before the mall opens.
6 hours until the mall opens
So let's hurry up.
And make this fun to watch.
Yes ~
Kwang Soo, are you okay?
I'm oka...
Why is the radio suddenly...
Uhm, let me ...
Joongki, let me
do the interview
Tell us ~
I'm okay ...
walkie-talkie
He is interrupted again
Yes.
Now, the game we will
be playing is Chicken Fight.
They say that the team to go
first has more of an advantage.
A fight you don't want to miss
So let's play a game to
decide who will go first.
It will be Lips Rock-Paper-Scissors.
How do you do rock?
Mouth paper-scissors-rock
Rock?
Scissors.
Paper.
Got it?
Let's begin with Sukjin and I.
Sukjin
Jaesuk
I look forward to it.
Oppa, men can also be cute.
Connected caps so their faces come closer
Of course.
Oppa, take off your glasses.
Why?
Why do I have to take my
glasses off for this game?
Flustered
Speechless
Why do I need to take them off?
Because your face will show better.
No, why...?
There's no need.
Hey, my glasses ...
Oh my...
I have to take them off?
Get close and open the
gates to your hearts
The cap that opens the door of the heart
Okay.
Talk about things you haven't
been able to say to each other.
I do have something to say.
What is it?
Jaesuk ...
10 years ago ...
... you introduced me to my wife, right?
Of course, I thought that you
two would match really well.
Why did you do that?
What is he saying?
Are you going to be okay
when you go home?
Angry because Jaesuk introduced his wife?
I just wanted to say that.
I wanted to ask you once.
Why did you do it?
Your wife will be looking
at this at home though.
It's not like that.
Okay, I got it.
I was just curious.
Hyung, I'm sorry.
Hyung, it wasn't that, you know me.
It's not that, I'm really grateful.
Seems like a long story
Like I said before.
When I introduced you to Hyungsoo ...
* Hyungsoo = Sukjin's wife
... Hyungsoo called me.
What did she say?
She said you weren't the kind of man she
was looking for in a long-term relationship.
I am serious.
Feeling dizzy
Dizzy
She really said that?
Yes, your wife said it.
It's things from the past.
It's been a long time.
She called on the day you first met.
She said it only on that day?
She said that you weren't
the type she was looking for.
Also ...
Did she say that?
She really said it.
I'm going to call her and ask.
I really worked hard to
make you two a couple.
I wanted you to change your
minds about each other.
I truthfully wanted to date her.
That's right.
Sukjin fell in love at first sight
But she didn't really like me.
Yeah, she didn't.
But you continuously got us together
and we ended up getting married.
So why did you do that?
About to cry
Why did you do that?
Trouble
Your wife will get upset if you do this.
No, it's not that.
How to get out of this mess?
You still love her though, right?
I love her a lot.
That's all that matters.
Suddenly a warm ending
Mouth Rock Paper Scissors
Rock, paper, scissors.
Paper
Rock
Laughs
Revealing
Hyung ...
... why?
Sukjin's nostrils are of different sizes.
A long time ago, he had
surgery to reduce the size.
Why did you have to mentioned that?
The nostrils were like this.
During my first few
years as a comedian ...
... my fists could easily
fit into my nostrils.
But ...
... the doctor helped me fix it.
Comparison
Sukjin debuting
The doctor helped me fix it.
Game start
Again
Rock
Paper
Scissors
It's Jaesuk's turn to attack
Paper
Scissors
Rock
You lost.
Jaesuk wins
No, we're supposed to
do it one more time.
Why did you do that 10 years ago?
Cheap team
Expensive Team
The game is over.
Next up from our team will be Joongki.
Gary
Joongki
How about your team ... Gary?
Yes, I'll do it.
I don't know whose team is who now.
Already laughter
Look at them.
He looks like a military guard.
The local military-reserve rapper
He looks like a baseball referee.
Gary really has a face that can be
commonly seen in any neighborhood.
Military guard.
Let's start by saying some words
to each other about your looks.
You're handsome, but ...
You're good looking.
That's right, you're handsome.
I have nothing else to say.
Okay ...
Don't say anything.
Shh!
I didn't mean you should
compliment each others looks.
He blocked Joongki's lips right now.
Not letting others finish their sentence.
He does that a lot
with girls, to get them.
Scary~
Let's begin the game now.
Rock, paper, scissor.
Rock
Rock, paper, scissors.
Paper
Scissor
What are you two doing?
This isn't that kind of game.
Did you guys click...?
Rock, paper, scissor.
Scissor
Ha ha
lol
This isn't a couple game.
You have to be careful
when the sun sets.
Ready.
Rock, paper, scissor.
Rock
Scissor
Paper
Cheap team
Gary wins
Expensive Team
Let's have Jungeum and Hyori go now.
Hyori
Jungeum
Both girls are very beautiful.
With the beauties
A pleasing competition
They both are beauties.
How about you both say some
words to each other up close?
They are really pretty.
So you are quite young.
Say what you want comfortably.
Say what comfortably?
Whack!
Kicking people at dawn
Why are you being
like this, seriously.
Hyori's personality
is still the same
I don't know about anything else.
But...I mean you're older know, but ...
... especially the line from
your nose to your lips
... is the best in Korea, truthfully.
No, not your eyes... but here...
Hey, come here.
What did you just say?
Grabs
You said to be truthful.
Why talk about her age?
Why are you holding my hands?
So you won't be able to pull her hair.
Now, start the game.
Yes, hold hands.
Scissors, paper ...
Scissor
Rock
Paper
Scissor
Rock
Paper
Cute
Are you going to keep
pretending to be cute?
Are you going to keep acting cute?
Angry
Ah, really.
It's just a game.
No, she can just do it like this.
It is just a game.
Do you know how she did it?
How?
Just try to do it you too.
Do you want to see me
try to be cute once?
Okay, try it.
You're going to be upset.
Try it.
Provokes~
Kicking again
Why do you do this again?
Yeah, why?
You be quite too.
It's because I haven't
seen her in so long.
Kwangsoo ...
... you are just having fun
watching the whole thing.
It's interesting for the comedy newbies
Rock, Paper, Scissor.
Hmm?
Scary
The original cuteness is like that
Hyori, you get a warning.
Why? She looks cute.
What did I do?
You can't do that.
Enjoy it, Hyori.
... scissors.
Bbyong~
Mmm~
Doing the same thing?
Unnie, that's my move.
Hyori did it first.
Hey ~
What?
Again
Cute
We have no interest in the game..
We don't even know whose winning.
Let's concentrate on the game.
Rock, paper, scissor.
Scissor
Paper
Rock
Hyori wins
Cheap Team
Expensive Team
Being cute doesn't mean anything.
Cheap Team gets to play first
Since the Cheap Team won ...
... are they doing the
chicken fight first or what?
Let's do this for real.
Neither of the teams knows the rules
Are the playing against us or...?
Someone's coming from behind.
What? Who is it?
Ah, this is really ...
Who ...
... is coming?
Their identity ...
50 people of the citizen's corps
This makes absolutely no sense.
How did they...?
Nervous
Where did you come from?
Clank
Keep going straight this way and leave.
Leave this way.
Where did they find all these people?
This is ridiculous.
Confusion
Even all of us together can't beat them.
Feeling hopeless...
In place.
Brave with dignity
How many people do you think there are?
Revealing the game's rules
The game will continue until
you knock down all these people.
What?
... until all of them are knocked down.
Does that even make sense?
Laughing since it's unbelievable
There are this many people right now.
It looks like a large army.
Millions of them
The team who knocks down the
last remaining citizen wins the game.
A chicken fight that requires strategy
Doesn't matter how many they knock down
Just need to knock down the last citizen
Then we'll just knock down
one person in each round.
Then we will also do the same.
We'll try our hardest and
play chicken fight now.
The nation's first large scale chicken fight
Please take care of us.
So we won't get hurt.
Thank you.
The sound of their applause is ...
Wow, this kind of chicken fight ...
Cheap Team goes first
Let me stand in the back.
No, you can't.
You're our ace.
Our ace?
They're telling Hyori to stand in front.
Ah really.
It is absurd even from the
opposing team's point of view
Even we would never do that.
Ugh, seriously.
Get ready.
Wait.
Yelling out loud
Flustered
Panics
Don't come, we'll go to you.
Okay, start.
Com on.
You guys can to go to them.
Scarily moving forward
OUT
Invincible Hyori is
This doesn't make sense.
However
Surprisingly Sukjin is winning
Falling down everywhere
These people are really
bad at playing this game.
Even Sukjin takes out two people at once
Those who lost stand in the back
Several citizens are out all of a sudden
They're really strong.
Ah, what is this?
But...
HaHa is surrounded
Powerless Out of the game
This time they concentrate on Sukjin
He's eliminated
Gary ~
Now only Gary is left
Gary, fighting.
Completely surrounded
They are... coming...!
Good...
I'm the trend of rap Gary
Head to head like a man
They are going against each other
Falls~
The trend of rap has collapsed
The people who fell,
please go to the back.
For now, put down your legs.
Oppa, they're no joke.
Citizen Team
11 people is out
When there was only one left,
they sounded like woooooo.
Like a mouse trapped in a corner
Expensive Team
Challenges
Do you think they will avoid
Jongkook and attack us instead?
Nervous
Now 39 citizens remain
Should we attack now?
Make some noise.
They're coming again
Pak
A fierce attack on the Muscle Chicken
Attack right up front
Joongkook is still okay
You're amazing
Kim Jongkook
Oppa.
The Grasshopper Chicken is
being attacked back and forth
It's okay.
Pak
Jaesuk is out
Uh?
Jaesuk is Jaesuk but...
How did Kwangsoo...?
Running around everywhere on his own
Kwangsoo fell on his own feet
Don't step on me ~
What's he doing?
Not getting out?
He narrowly escapes
That really hurt.
Ugh, seriously.
Then Joongki is out
And Jungeum is also out
Now only Muscle Chicken remains
Oppa, win this.
Come to me if you dare
I can't back down like this
Vicious attack against Jongkook
Sways
In the end Jongkook is defeated
It really hurt.
You suffered a lot hyungnim.
Expensive Team defeated 5 citizens
Jongkook is not a human, he's a machine.
Chicken fight machine
I got hit here and there.
They are no joke.
Let's change it a little.
Expensive Team tries again
How about fighting one on one?
Match
The citizens should pick
who they want to fight.
So please choose your opponent.
I choose Jongkook.
Do you think you'll be okay?
I survived from the first match.
Confident
But this chicken won't be easy
Fighting.
Show him with one move.
Flying in mid air?
Sorry...
Next person ~
The strongest citizen defeated
Next ~
Another citizen steps up
They're citizens.
Watch yourself.
This person also looks strong
He seems to be more careful.
Sways~
Oh my god
Are you okay?
Wait ~
Pants~
Leaning on Jaesuk's shoulders
Let me hold it up for you ...
... because it so tiring.
What are we going to do?
Go away.
Don't leave me
Mr. Yoo Jaesuk
Lightly~
Falls
Expensive Team
The last player Kwangsoo
Vibrates~
Wham!
Goes down in the blink of an eye
Speedy chicken leg
He's going for it ~
Why are his legs so thin?
Actively using
his long legs
Kwangsoo wi...
Huh?
Cooly defeats his opponent
Cooly falls down
A twist
Ah, what should we do?
A unique chicken Kwangsoo
Now it's the Cheap Team's turn.
Let's do a one on one too.
Cheap Team
Challenges
You think you can?
Who will the citizen choose first?
I'd like to play against Mr. Sukjin.
A, come on ...
It seems as if you don't know me well.
Take your hands out, Hyungnim!
I'm going to make you disappear.
Bang!
That's so annoying.
They were about to forget it, but....
Ba~ang.
A greasy bang~
Mee too Bang
Okay, get ready ... Start.
With good vigor
In one go...
What is this?
Hyori ...
Cheap Team
Hyori
Citizen
What do you think about Hyori?
I'm a fan.
Please be gentle.
Smiling eyes ♥
Sway
Invincible Hyori's aegyo strategy
No, we can fight like this and then ...
Mumble
She does it so naturally.
Ang.
His leg melts like snow
It really worked Hyori's aegyo plan
They are full of complaints
You lost too easily.
Come out ... Come on.
Don't get fooled by that.
Don't mind those kind of things.
Attacks gently but...
Ah, it hurts.
Whines
You said that hurts?
Speechless
This is cheating.
It hurts right here.
It's frustrating.
Aing ~
Final attack
The men are melting
Seriously, why are you being like this?
Do it gently.
What?
Unhappy
Whoa ~
Hyori is out
You have won.
You're amazing.
That's too much
It's good for us that you beat her.
Why did you do that?
I just wanted her to rest.
Late consideration?
He did a good job.
Now it's a team event.
Just until one person is left.
Now only 14 citizens remain
Why do you stubbornly want to win?
We all have to win.
We really have to win this.
Go.
They're coming ~
Citizen Team
Scarily approaching
A complete mess
Muscle Chicken is showing off his strength
Joongki also tries his best
I should get rid of all of them
Joongki is on a suicide mission and is out
Bump
Grasshopper Chicken is hit on the tail bone
Ah ... Camera.
Cry baby
Whining
It hurts so much.
Embarrassed
Now there are only 7 citizens left
Now there are only 6 citizens left
In the back.
Jungeum also pulls a suicide mission
Muscle Chicken is also out of the game
Only Kwangsoo is left
Expensive Team
Kwangsoo ...
Excited
You have to beat three people.
Finally
Only three citizens remain
Nervous
One at a time?
They attack from here
Please ~
and there
Please.
Now Kwangsoo ...
... is kneeling down
Only 3 citizens left
This chance goes to the Cheap Team
Hyung.
It's 4 against 3, just 3 of them.
Cheap Team
Citizen Team
Cheap Team has an advantage
Just 3 people.
Why are you coming towards me?
Nervous
Cute Chicken Hyori is eliminated
They got this ~
Cheap Team has lost their ace
Excited
Interesting
We didn't lose?
The numbers are even
What are you doing?
Going for a dubble attack
on the easy victim Sukjin
Hold on ~
Hey, even if it's just one person ...
HaHa defeats one citizens
We got this ~
There's only two people left.
Just one more person.
Cheap Team
Citizen Team
Win, you have to win.
Please win.
The last citizen
Park Youngho (23)
Occupation: Bodyguard
Win ~
Huh?
HaHa out in the blink of an eye
Good ... Please ~
Please win for us.
We can't predict the result
Falling
Collapse
Sukjin is eliminated
Huh? Immediately attacks Gary
Cheap Team
Everyone is out
Expensive Team is cheering
The last citizen was great
Hold on, what happened?
Why am I on the floor when I
was just playing chicken fight?
Expensive Team gets the opportunity
We're sorry, but we have
no choice but to win.
Yesterday's ally becomes today's enemy
A game is a game.
It's just a game, so please understand.
Yes, we're sorry.
Let's do a cheer.
1,2,3 fighting.
Fighting.
Don't underestimate the last citizen
This is the last set.
Expensive Team
Citizen Team
Goes straight for Jongkook
From the start he aims
for the ace Jongkook
In the midst of it all
Joongki is eliminated
His strength is no joke.
Expensive Team
Citizen Team
Kwangsoo & Jaesuk's joint attack
Hits
Jaesuk is out due to fatal injuries
Jaesuk is dying~~
This is a position we've seen
him many times today
Kwangsoo's body-to-body attack
FAIL
Only 2 remains Jongkook & Jungeum
Confrontation
Oppa, be careful.
Taps
So gentle.
Can't see Jungeum...
The battle of two men's ego
This is no joke.
Head-to-head
No.
Can't tell who is going to win
But at this moment ...
The fight machine's offensive attack
If this attack works ...
Falls down
with a thud
Expensive Team
Kim Jongkook wins
Expensive Team finally wins
Awesome job.
Thank you, wow ...
Good job.
He's really something.
You gave us a really fun game.
You really worked hard, thank you.
Thank you for participating
at this late hour of the night
Thank you ~
You can go home now.
Be safe.
Thank you.
Wow, they did a really good job.
We have to take a look first.
Expensive Team has a head start
for winning the previous game
This is really difficult.
Yes.
There's no cheap bread?
Difficult level: 2
Definitely not clothes.
The hair clips might be cheap.
3rd mission
Locate the cheapest item
This place is really big.
It should be around 500 won.
That's right, it should be
something like a hair clip.
Run ~
Heading to the accessories shop
Jungeum unexpectedly takes the lead
Hair clips should be pretty cheap.
Hurry up.
Jeongeum ...
Jungeum What's making you so excited?
In front of them is a shop
full of beautiful things
It's impossible not to be energized
Like these.
Hair clips.
That's right.
Look at these.
No, don't look at those.
You shouldn't be looking at things you like.
Are hair clips cheap?
What can the cheapest item be?
Probably an envelope or similar
from the convenience shop.
Don't you think?
We saw a convenience store earlier.
Sticker?
Something like that.
Usually, which floor is it on?
I saw one earlier.
3rd floor?
Didn't we go to 3rd floor at the beginning?
They saw the store in the first round
at 3rd floor
One team will search for
the cheapest item and ...
... one team distracts them by
removing their name tags.
Started late so they need a plan
Me and Gary.
I'll go with Gary.
Attack Team
HaHa & Gary
You're witty, you do the search.
Search Team
Hyori & Sukjin
Fighting ~
Discreet, don't get discovered.
Carefully planned
Cheap Team
Can they find it first?
Hurry.
Trying to find the Expensive Team
Looking for the convenience store
Over there.
Not that way.
Found the sign that leads to the store
Will the cheapest item be there?
Still moving together
I'm going crazy.
I think this is the right way.
What's the cheapest then?
Over there...
Slowly approaching
HaHa and Gary
I'm really going to die soon.
Hyung, why are you sitting down.
Cautious
Careful
Becoming targets of the hunting dogs
Thirsting for Jungeum the sheep
What would be the cheap thing?
Enthusiastically runs to the garment shop
Where did she go?
To see if there's any cheap item.
They give discounts here.
They sell clothes.
Ahh
They are caught
You won't find it here..
HaHa reinforces from a distant
Not aware of anything and
just wanders off here and there
At that moment
Flipping out
Startled
Afraid
Panics
Wait a sec.
Jongkook hyung ~
Shocked
Jongkook runs to help them
Jongkook hyung ~
What should I do?
Once the name tag is removed
that person is out of the game
Jongkook hyung ...
Is his name tag really going to...?
Jongkook hyung
Save me
Hyung ~
Jongkook counter-attacks
Unfortunately Kwangsoo is the first to be out
HaHa had been waiting this whole time
Crash
Pak
Bang
Snap
In the end Jongkook & Gary &
Kwangsoo are out of the race
I have been caught, so beware of
the content from the walkie-talkie.
Meanwhile These Cheap
members are on the move
We must be careful.
When did they go?
The convenience store
Yes.
Is it the right place?
Find the cheapest thing.
There should be something
worth around 10 won here?
How much are these?
They're expensive.
Oh, they're expensive?
These are 500 won?
Take a look in that corner.
Find the item~
Oppa, look in the corner.
How much is this?
Look everywhere~
Here.
What's that?
There's only one piece.
Chocolate
- How much is this?
- Oh,
It should be cheap, it's chocolate.
= 200 won
How much can it cost?
Alright, it's the cheapest here.
Cheap Team
Confirms the item
I will keep watch here
while you're searching.
It's something big?
Inside.
There's something inside?
I should be somewhere in the store.
Where is the secret code?
Take a look up there as well.
Wow this is ...
HaHa, where are you?
Come to the convenience store.
The store on the 3rd floor.
HaHa is at the convenience store.
Overheard from the walkie-talkie
Stop, let's talk a bit.
Run to the store
HaHa follows them
You're so kind to help us although
we are not on the same team.
I must be crazy.
The convenience store ... Okay.
With the help from Gary(?) they are
going to the convenience store
There's also a mart.
* Mart = Supermarket
HaHa is still trailing them
Over there ~
Let's hide.
At this rate Both team will run
into each other at the store
I won't lose them~
It must be here, I'm certain it's here.
They know the code is there But where?
It can only be in here.
Yes, only here.
It should be here.
It's too complex in here.
It should be here somewhere.
Looking around
Not missing any chances
They're coming, search quickly.
Expensive Team's right
in front of the store
Looking left
and right
It must be here.
But still can't find it.
This is the cheapest candy
in mall at only 100 won
The clue is hidden
between umbrellas
They're coming.
Ohh?!
Hyori discovers it?
Have to go there quickly
Must stop them
It should be here...
Hyori
Finds it
finds the third clue
Where can it be?
Finally arrives at the store
Sukjin and Hyori hide
Comes in~
Sukjin has been discovered
It's not on the floor.
Where is it?
Huh?
Now is the time
Hyori safely escapes with the code
Cheap Team
Acquire the third clue
The third code =
Ah, we came too late.
Round 3
You found it in the convenience store?
She's a genius.
The night before at 11 PM
Entrance and exit were locked
The first code found
Cheap Team got it
The second code
Expensive Team got it
The third code
Cheap Team got it
And the 4th code
Expensive Team got it from the bridal shop
Now there is only one code left
Win the last game and acquire it
1 hour and 30 minutes until opening
The last location for today
The stage of bridal shop A
We met at 6 PM yesterday, didn't we?
That's right.
We've been here for
more than 12 hours.
It's about time we fall asleep.
Don't collapse.
What is Sukjin thinking?
I'm sleeping.
It's time to be sleeping.
What time is it Mr. Jong?
Mr. Jong?
Who is Mr. Jong?
All caused of fatigue
Hyung, what is this?
I'm sorry ~
Yes, I made a mistake.
What time is it?
It's about 7 AM.
6:45 in the morning
The exact time is 6:45 AM.
This game is really simple.
If you look here, there
is a stage behind us.
Yawning
Are you yawning?
Surprised
She must be embarrassed
Let's take into consideration
our beautiful Hyori's image.
For her, even raising
her hand is too much.
Yawn
The game is very simple this time.
A team battle
You go up there and whoever gets
the most people in the shot wins.
The team that's left with
most members wins
Move to the side and get ready.
Yes ~
That's good.
Ten seconds after saying 'I'll take a
picture' we'll take a wedding photo.
I'll show you my capability.
Determined
I'll take a picture, so please get on stage.
Moving towards the photo zone
Hyori ~
... so please get on stage.
Even if she's tired she's the first one up
Go away.
Pushing
Hyori ~
This is only the first round.
Isn't this the first time?
She's a girl, why are you like that?
Move a bit
Hyori, why do you do this?
You have no business
being in front of Hyori
I'll be taking the photo.
10 seconds until the photo is taken
Experience from wedding events?
10 ... 9 ...
Hastily
Put your face forward.
Move
It's you again...
It should be around this time.
Block their faces.
Click!
Okay.
Which team will have
most faces in the picture?
Okay.
Jaesuk definitely has his face captured
As for the rest We have to
take a look at the picture
Checking to see which team won
Look at me, I'm working hard.
All covered
We won ~
Cheap Team: 3
Expensive Team: 2
Cheap Team wins
Why?
Kwangsoo's hand covers his face.
God's hand
Joongki, I'm sorry.
We're on the same team.
Blocked his own team member
Kwangsoo blocked Joongki's face.
That was great.
Joongki
I'm sorry
They find hope
Kwangsoo blocked his own member.
Look at his innocent face.
Smile
Hyori, what happened
to you at that moment?
Amazing?
Hyori is great.
Perfect
Smile
She's still able to have this kind of
image under such circumstances.
The width of her gum is
proportionate to her teeth.
Gum size = Teeth size
The highlight is our facial
expressions and actions.
Let's get this started.
I'll be taking the photo after 10 seconds.
Fair play.
Let's win, let's do a cheer.
1,2,3, fighting.
Show them our strength.
I'm taking the photo.
After 10 seconds A wedding photoshoot
Jaesuk gets the spot he had earlier
Shooo~
The guests blocks each other
Immature guest HaHa
Rapper Gary stare
Shooo~
Why is only Kwangsoo
having such hardships?
Expensive Teams tactic
Blocking Hyori
Focusing on one
Bang
Will Hyori appear in the photo?
Hey ~
I can be seen
How will Hyori look in the photo?
Done ~
Your whole face is in the frame.
Why does it show Hyori?
You did
it Hyori
It's nothing.
Hyori ...
... your face will always be in the picture.
Even this time
you can see her gums
It's late, that's why it's more obvious.
Gary ~
Hyori is great.
What about Gary?
Gary ...
A hardly recognizable face
Joongki ...
We won.
No, you have more members than we.
Everyone is in It's a draw
Please handle this more seriously.
They have to do a rematch
Only those looking straight at
the camera will be counted.
So we must fully face the camera.
Hyori is awesome.
This time it's 5 seconds.
I'll be taking the photo.
We have to block Hyori this time
Okay~
I'm going to be in the photo again
Did they manage to block Hyori?
Good.
We blocked Hyori, didn't we?
I wasn't blocked.
Expensive Team is only
concerned about Hyori
Ah, Hyori is there again ~
I'm sure I covered her face.
Smiling
face
Gary ... Look there.
What about Gary?
I appeared again.
Gary's face is included.
That's so unbelievable.
How could you have such
a tranquil expression?
Peaceful
This is my first natural photo.
Actually ...
... the problem is that
the picture is funny.
Jongkook pushed him
Fell down
Too funny.
Let's make it a tie.
Let us win since Gary was so funny.
And Hyori's expression is
the best, so let us win.
Only those looking straight at
the camera should be counted.
Hyori's eyes are closed here.
No, I was smiling and I could see.
Debating
Must look at the camera.
I was smiling.
Cheap Team: 2
Expensive Team: 3
Expensive Team wins
This time you go up there and jump.
You jump and try to get
into the angle and win.
Must jump to appear in the photo
Let's do this.
Must win to get the last code
Okay, I'm going to take the photo.
I'm confident.
We're taking the photo.
Confident.
Bounce~
Jumping~
Jump oppa.
You can't do that.
They have to jump really high
Trousers, ah trousers.
Which one of them
will be in the picture?
Falls~
Hey ...
This time it can't be ...
I'm in ~
Hyori?
Hyori's face is captured.
Hyori Captured again
Ah, seriously
How come she's in the picture again.
Isn't it photoshop?
I didn't expect to be included.
When the photo was taken
Take a look at this!
Look at her expression.
Smiling alone
As expected she is in bloom.
Still smiling
You're the best.
And the next photo.
Smiling again
Oh, Gary really.
Gary is Mr Calm
Look at this.
Smiling while jumping
Different photos
Same expression
Cheap Team
Expensive Team
Expensive Team obtains the last code
The final code is
Now all we need to do is
figure out the password.
Then we can get out.
We're going ... Go.
The winning team can proceed first
Don't walk RUN
We want to get out too.
The losing team also proceeds
They're coming ~
Hurry.
Both teams rush to the lobby
Faster ~
Wait ~
They have to enter the password
The cheap team also arrives
If you get the password
right, it'll happen in a flash.
If the correct code is entered
then the number will blink
So you have to do it quickly.
It's 6, the first code is 6.
Cheating
You can't let them see it.
The next is 3.
Quick ~
Try number 5.
Jongkook remembers exactly
Anxious
Only the last number is left
We're almost there.
Enter the last digit.
The last number Expensive Team got
Expensive Team: 2
Cheap Team: 1
Expensive Team succeeds
We can leave now
Disappointed
They solved the password
Going out.
Hyori.
The exit opens
Finally
More grateful than
escaping from a prison
Current time: 8:30 AM
Now it's time to go to work
Already 8:30 AM.
We are going home now,
feeling a bit sorry for them.
It's already morning ...
... so let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Two can leave and two
will take the punishment.
That ...
Find victims for the penalty
Deciding who gets the punishment.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Oh yeah.
The curse
Sukjin who suggested it lost
Rock, paper, scissors.
Also HaHa is also chosen
Shortly after ...
In the middle of a busy shopping mall
A w...weird looking woman(?)...!
Hello ... Nice to meet you!
Penalty
Lift operator HaHa
Shocked
To the first floor ...
... going down.
Going down.
I'm carrying out my punishment right now.
Embarrassed
I think I'm going to go nuts.
What is this, really?
Going crazy~
Nice to meet you.
Burdened
4th floor, okay.
Still kindly escorting them
Good ...
Everybody, follow me ...
Say yo.
Say yo~.
Nothing to fear
yoho~
South Korea.
Those going to 4th floor, scream.
Ha ha ha ha ~
May I shake your hand?
Come on.
No.
Only a handshake?
I'll help you with everything.
Penalty
Directory guide Sukjin
No matter what it is.
This is a restaurant.
Welcome.
Bows
Ask anything.
Is this the main gate?
Yes, it's the main gate.
Hello.
Let's say Running Man and Bang
He's at it again
BANG
Don't walk, run ... Running Man.
Bang.
The second landmark is
Suwon world cup stadium
Running Man's unstoppable instincts
In order to escape
extraordinary hurdles
And ...
Jaesuk only makes dangerous choices
What's going to drive him till the end?