Original hardsub by iSUB
Softsub by SamFive
(color and alignment etc)
Today's landmark
KMA
* KMA = Korean Meteorological Administration
Sophisticated research facility
Delivers accurate weather forecasts
Weather forecasting
in harsh conditions
A battle in the worst
possible weather
With regards to MC Jaesuk
conspiracy among the members
Blooms during the intense chasing battle
Tears of
the Triangle Scandal
What will
their destiny be?
Starts now
Today is our Running Man time again.
Today's location is ...
... a place where they conduct
weather forecasting in our nation.
It's the KMA.
* KMA = Korean Meteorological Administration
Today's landmark
KMA
As the name imply ...
... this is the place for
weather forecasts.
A year of non-stop forecast.
This place is open
24 hours a day for 365 days
No wonder there are non-stop updates.
Today I didn't hear any good news,
since they said it will be cold today.
Today is especially cold.
Since we're here at the
KMA today, our HaHa ...
Yes?
Ah, what's with you.
A place with
a sort of relation with HaHa
Worried
But HaHa ...
Yes?
Ever since the broadcast
of the Pororo episode ...
HaHa got the nickname Haroro last week
... why are you coming on
with that kind image now?
Almost dressed up like Pororo?
It gives others a burden
I'm not acting like Pororo.
A scheme to target kids fans?
How am I acting like Pororo?
Your voice became cute, it's weird.
Oh really?
Acts ...
... cute
Kids can you hear me?
32 years
Because of this Pororo ...
... he even said he wants ﻿to host
an event on Children's Day.
Why don't you start now?
Other than that, Jihyo ...
... I'm curious, aren't you very cold?
Don't talk about me.
Why are you dressed up like
that in this cold weather?
Yes, I'm very cold.
That's what I thought.
Worried
When I first arrived today ...
... I thought something was a little weird.
What is it?
I wonder what was prepared for today.
Is it me against everyone?
...Oh?
Jaesuk's
You're too careless
When I arrived today ...
... I saw Sukjin's manager on the phone.
So when I walked pass Sukjin's car I
said "Oh, hyung", but you weren't there.
I asked where you went and
he said "To the meeting room".
Furious
Manager, you
little rascal!
"﻿Which meeting room?"
"The one over there, that way".
On the way there I saw the PD.
He went "Oh!".
Decisive
Yoo Jaesuk bumps
into the Head-PD
Frightened
Oh?!
Head-PD
He said "Wait hyung, lets talk for a sec".
What is this?
You're too careless.
Give me the Running Ball.
What's wrong with you, we aren't
doing the hidden camera today.
Discovered
First time in history of 1 vs 8 battle
What?
It doesn't matter.﻿
Luckily
Today's
isn't the lying game
It doesn't matter?
Ah, is that so?
You're full of yourself right now ...
... so later it'll be easier to trick you.
Really?
That's right.
Mr. Yoo Jaesuk ...
Later...
Among all the females, who's the best.
As a single man and facing numerous females ...
A desperate national MC Yoo Jaesuk
Please answer if it's not an accident.
You can't be like this type of person.
Merciless
8 members' attack
It's a misunderstanding.
Now you're screwed.
Later
MC Jaesuk in a desperate situation
Don't be surprised today.
I'm not hiding anything.
Is that so?
Heechul?
Waiting like that was too cold.
Waiting for his
introduction, but
it was too cold
Self opening
Today's guest
4 dimensional
Super Junior's
Kim Heechul
Ah, Heechul came.
I didn't even notice and Heechul is here.
Heechul ...
Hello, seems like today
will be very interesting.
Really?
Jihyo ...
Yes?
You seem very cold.
Wearing something so thin,
your lips are turning purple.
So you drank before coming again?
Again?
Frightened
Oh, what?
Looks like you know Jihyo a lot.
Knows Jihyo too much
Heechul and Jihyo were Inkigayo MCs
Because of the Inkigayo MC.
Frightened Jihyo charges in
Tell us what happened.
Right now her nose is very red.
Frame
Reveals
When we're MCing for Inkigayo,
she drank when she was nervous.
Big attack
Drinking MC?
So the stuff Kwangsoo
said wasn't all gibberish.
After framer Kwangsoo
new framer Kim Heechul
Okay, the weather is too cold.
No matter what, we are
going to enter the KMA now.
Except for Joongki who can't join due to schedules
let all 9 of our members run
Fascinated
This is my first time here.
The nation's weather center
And also they endure working over night.
Hello ~
So this is the place where
they analyze on the news.
I can see everything.
This is impressive.
We're here at the KMA.
For the Running Bell.
To play games to receive the Running Ball.
We should go to our first location.
Let's go.
Today, because we're at the KMA ...
As everyone can see.
Behind us ...
... it's called the chroma key.
Briefly try and announce ...
Chrome
Key
A technology that can
CG on the background
... a weather forecast to test it.
And also, Heechul ...
... a lot of people are anticipating you.
Because of the anticipation he is nervous
That's right.
If he comes out in a variety show ...
... a lot of people will anticipate it.
Burden
A hard time ...
That's right.
You must have a hard time right now.
To be honest ...
... there's a lot of pressure.
Ever since I've been on variety shows,
there was never pressure like this.
Since Super Junior's debut
I'm having too much
pressure right now.
The most pressure
The 3 of them are
together again
Why do you have to be
together with the Two Kids.
Of course I have to.
And both of you are wearing
your socks like that.
Seumdwa ~
I can freeze to death seriously.
It started on the cruise (I know) Seumdwa
* Seumdwa = A twist of sumnida that's
often used at the end of honorific terms
Seumdwa ~
Saying it frequently today too
Do you think that'll become a trend?
Cold hearted
Yes, for 2 weeks.
Trend setting duration 2 weeks
It's going to get popular.
Nonsense, how can that become a trend.
Of course, seumdwa.
* They replaced sumnida with seumdwa
Just now there was a person that
was drinking and said what I said.
Drunk people follow that trend?
How?
Where is your house?
I'm confident.
I'll drink 1 more cup, just 1 more.
Confirmed
Trend prediction Seumdwa~
It will become a trend later.
During an event, high-school
students would prepare placard.
Gary's placard is popular.
What did it say, on the placard.
Peaceful Gary.
I love you
Peaceful
Gary
Nowadays I rap without any expressions.
Why?
I'm peaceful Gary now.
Peaceful
Seriously, it's different compared to before.
There should be charisma when rapping
How was it before?
Before there would movements like this.
But now
peaceful Gary...
Now it's so peaceful.
Heechul can do Gary oppa's rap very well.
Oh, really?
That was before.
♪ ﻿I'm very satisfied with  ♪
♪ the words of loving you ♪
I'm really having a hard time today.
King of pressure
We are going to start now.
First mission
Running Man
Nonsense report
What do we do this?
There are 9 members, 3 members
per team, so a total of 3 teams.
Everyone would be given 5 minutes
with a script of the weather reports.
With the script.
The outfits are on the 2nd floor.
Getting them one by one.
While putting on the outfit, you'll have to memorize
the scripts and say it out loud in order to pass.
But then only one person from all
teams will receive the Running Ball.
So that means we go in 3 by 3 but only 1 person will get the Running Ball
Among them only 1 person
can receive a Running Ball.
So only the person who is successful ...
Ah, seriously.
Worried
That seriously makes people worried
We have to memorize it?
This is just like filming a movie.
Only the face Floats~
This is what happens if you wear
blue while doing a weather report.
There's only his face
Okay, I understand.
First team ...
... ﻿HaHa, Gary and Jihyo.
team
HaHa
Gary
Jihyo
Among those 3, there is 1 person ...
full of unsatisfaction
... that is very unsatisfied, which is Jihyo.
Flustered because her partners are weak?
You think you can do this by yourself?
If we don't work together
then you'll never get it right.
That's right ~
*Jihyo uses seumdwa to pronounce it
Without knowing the seumdwa-unit
Did you hear that?
Like the predicted seumdwa trend
We will win.
Seumdwa.
Song Jihyo and the Two Kids.
Okay I got it.
Hurry say it.
Okay, I got it.
That's not bad.
These three have the
exact same personalities.
Seumdwa.
Similar personalities
The time limit is 5 minutes.
Ah seriously.
Ha ha ha
Wearing blue tight outfits...
And that ...
They look like they came from
the comic 'Black Rubber Shoes'.
Giyongie.
Giyong ~
Looking the same as Giyong
Hany ~
Jihyo is
'Run Hani'
Hany, Pororo and Giyong.
It seems like it.
Only 1 person
can get a Running Ball
Okay get ready, 5 minutes.
Ready ... go.
Gary isn't holding back at all.
The Two Kids
Not even holding back against a girl
He should give in a little.
Go to report center
Get the Weather Report Script
The scripts ...
So you need to go up to get the script.
Then you need memorize the
scripts while changing outfits.
Yeah.
Receives scripts from KMA staff
Thank you.
Hurry ~
Moving and memorizing
Get clothes that
cover the blue outfit
Jihyo is the best.
Yellow and red
clothes are prepared
Where's my jacket?
Why don't I get one?
Giyong Gary
fails to obtain a jacket
Giyong is still running
even without a jacket.
The two got pants too
Give me.
Snatch
It's mine.
Just give me the pants at least.
Jihyo should be good at memorizing scripts.
Watching from the below is fun
Jihyo is memorizing it right now.
Wait a sec.
I won't be on the same
team as Jongkook?
Okay then, please treat me better.
What do you mean by
treating you better?
I'll regret it, being with Jongkook.
What's there to regret?
I want to be on the same
team as Sukjin hyung ...
... ﻿and Kwangsoo.
Seriously.
Here they come ~
HaHa is first.
It became a raincoat.
When kid HaHa wears it it becomes a raincoat
He got the pants on first.
Blast ~
Quick, HaHa hurry up.
The 1st group's forecast
is a snow forecast
Hurry up.
No more time.
Due to Siberia's high air pressure
Due to Siberia's high air pressure ...
Legs become
transparent
We have seen a large increase
in the amount of water vapor
in the amount of seumdwa.
Wrong
... in the amount of seumdwa.
The snowstorm has knocked
the senses out of HaHa
Seumdwa.
Seumdwa ~
Yah, Jihyo come to the front.
Due to Siberia's high air pressure
Due to Siberia's high air pressure ...
Huk!
A human who's
half-transparent
We have seen a large increase
in the amount of water vapor
A large increase in
the amount of ...
Wrong
Seumdwa.
A large increase in the
amount of ... seumdwa.
Hey, look at Jihyo ... Jihyo.
I thought she was teacher Tae Jinah.
Ah ha!
If you look at her...
The yellow handkerchief part
Yellow Song Jinah(?) teacher
Due to Siberia's high air pressure
Due to Siberia high air pressure ...
'Siberia high'
Wrong
Isn't it...?
Shooo
If you got it wrong, just get off
Due to Siberia's high air pressure ...
Serious
Gary became a magnet.
We have seen a large increase
in the amount of water vapor.
This snow was brought about ...
This snowstorm was brought
about by the sudden cold spell
Wrong
Seumdwa ~
Jihyo's going to succeed this time.
Only one of the three
can get the Running Ball
Get off.
Due to Siberia's ...
The thirst of getting a ball
hell breaks loose
Due to Siberia’s high air pressure.
Seumdwa.
Yah!!!
Due to Siberia's high pressure ...
Due to Siberia's high air pressure
high air pressure ...
Wrong
Freezing
Explosion of will
Invisible
man
Lost his mind
Time is running out ...
Jihyo, quick.
Due to Siberia's high air pressure.
Time's up
A total failure
HaHa * Gary * Jihyo
Attempt to get
a Running Ball
fail
Jihyo knew it all.
Then none of them get the Running Ball?
Yeah.
Next it's Team 2's turn
Jaesuk
Kwang
soo
I look forward to this.
Jongkook
Ah~
Jaesuk's worry
Even in this kind of game,
he is so enthusiastic.
Dignified
You might as well join the Asian Games.
Why?
Why are you with us all this time?
Sucks to be in the same team
If you join the Asian Games
you can even get a medal.
Singer turned gold medalist?
You're fit enough too.
Jongkook will definitely be
the first to put on the clothes.
But he definitely won't get the ball.
Will it turn out like that?
Ready ... go.
Oh, why is he running so fast?
Surprisingly Jaesuk is in the lead
Because ﻿Jaesuk is always escaping
he must feel like a fugitive.
Leading because of his escaping nature
This feels more like a race.
Thank you ~
They're coming ~
Woah, Jaesuk is the fastest.
Only 2 coats
Yah, get off me
Jaesuk leads
Safely acquires yellow coat
Kwangsoo's opponent is
no other than Jongkook
Kwangsoo really has the worse luck.
Kwangsoo didn't get any.
But at this moment
Swosh
Kwangsoo tries to steal Jaesuk's coat
Jaesuk is the only one
he can catch anyway.
Jongkook at a leisurely pace
Falls!
A red cloak paired with yellow
pants should be quite interesting.
Sorry.
It's okay ~
* They pronounces the words with seumdwa
I'm sorry.
Oh, Jongkook hyung.
Kwangsoo?
It's like Superman.
I'll protect
the Running Ball
Superkook
Time is running out because
of the hero play
Team 2's
weather
Snowing and
raining?
Snow + Rain + Wind
Totally bad weather
The Yeong Dong area was
enveloped by fog last night
enveloped by fog last night.
It was affected by the Prapiroon
typhoon from Thailand
typhoon from Thailand.
A rainstorm accompanied by ...
A rainstorm accompanied by
strong winds has started
Strong blow ...
Wrong
Next is a naked Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo's appearance?
Last night ...
Only the face
... the Yeong Dong area
Last night ...
... the Yeong Dong area was enveloped by
... Prapiroon
Wrong
Arriving late
yellow Jaesuk caster
Time for you to get off.
The Yeong Dong area was enveloped ...
Again!
Already covered
with wounds
Shooosh
Prapiroon ~
The Yeong Dong area was
enveloped by fog last night
enveloped by fog last night.
It was affected by the Prapiroon
typhoon from Thailand
typhoon from Thailand.
Seumdwa.
A rainstorm accompanied ...
A rainstorm accompanied
by strong winds has started
Yah!
Wrong
That was awesome
The Yeong Dong area was
enveloped by fog last night
enveloped by fog last night.
It was affected by the Prapiroon
typhoon from Thailand.
typhoon from Thailand
A rainstorm accompanied
by strong winds has started
A storm accompanied ...
Wrong
#%&$ seumdwa.
Rage
Jjak
Explosion
Faster.
I told you to be quick.
Stutter
Hurry up.
Faster.
Last night ...
Kick
Get off!
Impatience turned into a
martial arts melodrama
Last night ...
New technique
Rainstorm shampoo
Last night ...
Only the one that can recite the script
gets the Running Ball
Hurry up.
The Yeong Dong area was
enveloped fog last night ...
If you fail there's no mercy
Get down
Smock
The ruthless forecast center
Faster.
The Yeong Dong area was
enveloped by fog last night.
Bang
It's heated up
in the martial arts drama
This person!
Last night ...
Zock
What has this turned into?
Ruthless...!
The tragic
weather forecast
If I'm not able to
win
you can't win either
Yeongdong area was enveloped by ...
Wrong
Flying legs
Bang
The most body gags in 100 years
The Yeongdong area was ...
... enveloped by fog last night.
The Yeongdong area was
enveloped by fog last night
It was affected by the Praplroon
typhoon from Thailand.
typhoon from Thailand
A rainstorm accompanied
by strong winds has started.
by strong winds has started
Jongkook
Succeeds
He succeeded?
Jongkook
gets the Running Ball
That was awesome.
Congratulatory(?) shampoo
Why are you like this?
Huh??
An angry high kick
Kick
Is Kwangsoo still engrossed
in the melodrama?
Bow
Immediately reflecting
Are you happy that you
got the Running Ball?
Of course, I'm happy.
Jongkook has acquired a Running Ball.
King Yoohyuk's congratulatory performance
Now it's Sukjin, Heechul and Lizzy's turn.
Sukjin
Heechul
Lizzy
I have a suggestion.
What?
Our Heechul's legs aren't well, right?
I suggest a walking race instead.
I'm okay.
Touched~
All 3 of you have different hair colors.
Black
Red
Yellow
Like a band, a band.
The 3 of us is like Orange Caramel.
* Orange Caramel = The subgroup Lizzy is a member of
We are Long-time Caramel.
Still hasn't shaken off the burden
Are you alright?
Are you ready?
Start.
How is Sukjin hyung race-walking?
What kind of walk-race is that?
He passed it.
Where is he going?
Where is Sukjin going?
Oh, Lizzy is fast ~
Lizzy at 1st place
She's not walking.
Lizzy is running.
Lizzy arrives first and
grabs the red coat
After watching Jihyo's performance ...
Sukjin, Heechul fighting
What are the two doing?
What is that...?
And he said he was going to walk
to let Heechul have an easier time.
Snort~
Jihyo, do you know that you
look like this really often?
Sucking in your nose
Just use my finger if you need it.
Forget it
Sseuk~
3rd group's forecast is?
Weather broadcasting station.
Weather ...
Heavy downpour
Dripping happily~
Worried
... broadcasting station
Big Nose
Calms down and continues
It's raining ...
Dren ... ched
Heechul, many people are watching.
Reporting from the weather broadcasting
station, it is currently pouring down
station, it is currently pouring down.
North Pacific is high in temperature and humidity.
North Pacific is high in temp and humidity, it's collusion
with high air pressure results in early monsoon symptoms
It's collusion with high air pressure
results in early monsoon symptoms.
At the Gangwon-do mountain areas, there's ...
At the Gangwon-do mountain areas
there will be heavy downpour of rain
Wrong
Hair
flying
Reporting from the weather broadcasting
station, it is currently pouring down
Reporting from the weather
broadcasting station, pouring ...
Wrong
Also Lizzy
Hair
flying
I'm not doing this anymore.
Lizzy, you have to
present yourself properly.
Reporting from the weather
station, it is pouring ...
Cheap
The worst
This is too much for him
Reporting from the weather broadcasting
station, it is currently pouring down
station, it is currently pouring down.
North Pacific's high in temp and it's collision
with high air pressure gives early monsoon
North Pacific is high in temperature and ...
... it's collision with high air pressure
results in early monsoon symptoms.
And the Gangwon-do mountain areas,
there will be heavy downpour of rain
And the Gangwon-do mountain areas ...
... there will be heavy downpour of rain.
Heechul
Success
Drenched
Come over quickly.
Heechul attained the Running Ball.
I have some screen time.
Relieving the stress
Then ...
now secretly ...
They will start ...
Yoo Jaesuk ...
it's your 1:8 challenge
What are we going to do?
Today's 1 vs 8 mission
I'll tell you the rules.
The time given is 30 minutes.
Yoo Jaesuk's
lie detector
If Jaesuk lies more than 3
times in this given time ...
If Jaesuk lies
more than 3
times he lose
... ﻿the rest of the 8 members
will get Running Balls.
According to the lie detector ...
... if the finger points ﻿up it is the truth.
And if it points down, you are lying.
Showing the result with thumb
Let's get Jaesuk to sit there first.
Seems like everyone is confident.
No, we're just worried that you will be hurt.
All I need to do is to speak the truth, right?
Can I ask something before we begin?
Is it okay if you get hurt?
It's okay.
I'll apologize to you first.
Cool~
Don't be angry ~
Can Jaesuk really answer
every question honestly?
But of course.
Jaesuk
Running
Man
Although Jaesuk seems were
comical in the program ...
30 minutes
before recording
... ﻿he is very serious off the camera.
Really, right?
The other time when there were no cameras
around, he was actually rubbing his eyes.
Framing
Like I've said, you must know.
Must make
Jaesuk
tell lies
Can we do it like this?
20 years ago
Things Jaesuk have hidden?
He used to ...
He wanted to do an
operation for his teeth.
It's not only the acting that's important.
Must make him nervous
by interrogating him in detail!?
The asking of the questions are also important.
There will be more than 500
articles on Jaesuk next week.
Jaesuk
Running
Man
I have the right to keep quiet.
No ~
Nation MC's most critical moment?
Let's make him lie
But do you think
he's the only one that gets harmed?
Nation MC Jaesuk's huge retaliation
Who will be
the one in danger?
As compared to Kang Hodong ...
... I am better.
His feelings will
be manipulated
We must find a person
to test the accuracy.
Pre-test
Let Jihyo noona do it.
Why do I have to do it?
Let's get Sukjin hyung then.
1st round pre-test
Ji Sukjin
Honestly, Sukjin hyung ...
What?
Last time on the cruise
Was the confession to his wife weird?
Last time you said you love your wife.
I want to test that.
At sea near Busan Gwang-An-bridge
Sukjin's confession
Calling out her name with love
His wife Yoo Sujeong ♥
I would just like to check.
If I love her?
Yes.
I love my wife to the extent
that no one can believe.
That's what I say.
The professionals
attaching the lie detector
It is stable.
Everyone please take note.
1st round pre-test
Ji Sukjin's
lie detector test
We're starting to test Sukjin hyung now.
Although he seems to be calm ...
Is he nervous?
... he really isn't.
I feel calm.
Truth?
Lie?
He looks a little like an old man.
The clothes are too baggy.
A really old man.
Due to nervousness Big Nose is getting older
Let's start questioning.
Are you sometimes ...
... jealous of Jaesuk?
He's jealous.
I've never been that.
Never?
Yeah.
Give us the Running Ball.
Never.
Has Sukjin never been
jealous at Jaesuk before?
The result is?
Lie
The graph
is moving tremendously
Interpretation
Sukjin is very
jealous of Jaesuk
How can you make me feel so bad?
Sukjin's true feelings are
now known to Jaesuk
I's not like that.
It's because I had other thoughts.
Do you occasionally ...
... think about your first love.
His facial
expression is?
Do you think of her?
I don't think about her.
Never?
Yeah ...
Has Sukjin only one love...
his wife Yoo Sujeong?
The lie detector's verdict is?
Lie
This time too
a rapid moment
Of course
no one forgets their first love
When your wife wasn't around ...
... were you happy?
No, I wasn't.
Firmly
Totally lying
Total lie.
Erratic moment
Ah, totally lying.
Aish ...
Removing the
detector by himself
Why would it turn out like this?
I would like to protect my family.
Rather than protecting his true feelings
he wants to protect his family
Sukjin's family harmony
has been disrupted
How did his thing know.
It's interesting.
Agrees?
Jihyo ...
Why should I?
Jihyo try it once.
Yeah, let her try it once.
Blank~ One girl
Very curious about her feelings
It doesn't matter if I do it.
Anxious
Just give it a try.
Will ﻿Jihyo noona's image be fine?
I'm a little nervous.
Can I start?
Let's start with Kwangsoo.
During filming ...
... have you secretly farted?
Farted ~
I have done it too.
Not caring about actress Attacking
You will just fart when
you're running around.
Didn't she fart during Inkigayo too?
1, 2, 3.
Yes ~
Really?
The actress'
shocking confession
We are all human, aren't we?
Right, this must be the truth.
Will it
be the truth?
Truth
Truthful
The graph is calm
No, it's because Jihyo is an actress.
But you cannot ask this
kind of question anymore.
Let's relieve her burden next.
To protect the actress
not asking such questions
Shall I go next?
A guy's style similar
to Gary is attractive?
... is attractive?
In her heart is ....
Monday Boyfriend an attractive person?
Yes ~
Nods
Is it the truth?
Truth
Just like the calm Gary
the calm graph
Smiles ♥
Let's ask one more.
"﻿I ..."
"I really don't like HaHa
even the slightest."
... not even the slightest."
No, I don't like him.
I don't like you either.
Yes.
Yes, she doesn't like him.
Indeed
So...
Jihyo liking Haroro...
Is Jihyo's answer
the truth?
Or a lie?
Oh my god
Lie
In Jihyo's heart
there's Haroro
Oppa, it's not true.
Agitated
An unexpected result
How can I be compared to HaHa?
Angry
What is it that's better
with him than me?
I ...
can't be compared...
to HaHa?
Graph
Huge change
Oppa, it's not true.
It's really not true.
I did everything within my abilities.
Gary's in a state of shock
Almost fainting?
It's really not true.
Stay calm ~
Now I know that she likes me.
The misunderstandings are all cleared now.
Boastful
Instantly feeling overwhelmed
As expected, I still have some charms.
It's totally
not possible
Seems like she really likes HaHa.
Jongkook oppa, you do it.
Erupted
Blank~ Jihyo
Huge wrath
Flinch
Wrath of Jihyo
Even Commander is taken aback
Stay calm ~
Desolated...
Look at his facial expression.
Ah, I'm really angry.
How about this?
Among all the Running Man members ...
Sukjin's sudden question
... is there someone you truly like?
In this atmosphere
asking such question?
Stop expecting anything.
Could it be that...
he thinks he could win with that question?
I ask you, do you like Jihyo?
Not even this one bit.
Unbelievable
Haven't you seen my wife's face?
Why don't I let you have a look.
My wife was also very
pretty when she was younger.
Jihyo who hasn't spoken
is feeling embarrassed
Ji Sukjin is already married, right?
Why are you like this?
I read the expressions in her eyes
Pre-testing stops
immediately
Finally
The battle
Make Jaesuk
tell a lie
Let's begin now.
I'm just going to speak the truth.
Your expressions isn't so good now.
Suddenly being strapped to the machine
Nation's MC is also nervous
Just a bit.
You should be.
From here looking ...
Here looking?
He's nervous.
Yoo Jaesuk seems to be nervous
Your nervous, oppa.
We'll start the questioning
from the weakest person.
Is your name Yoo Jaesuk.
Yes.
In the Running Man variety ...
Will a hard question
make him lie immediately
... do you feel
Yes?
... that you are leading
as the center character?
Yes, I do.
On the show
Center role admitted
From a certain point.
"I look like an MC" ?
I'm working hard
in that direction.
Isn't it quite like that?
Only answer with "yes" or "no".
That is not something that I can
personally determine in advance.
Your own opinion.
I can't say no.
From the start of Running Man ...
... with initial members like Kwangsoo
and Jihyo working together
... you were worried, right?
Yes, worried a bit.
I look handsome, don't I?
You are asking whether
you're handsome or not?
Yes.
The question is similar
to your precious one.
Answer only with "yes" or "no".
Yes, becoming good-looking.
Admitting?
Alright, we'll start the questions.
Time for intimidating question?
Is this the start now?
It's starting ~
If Jaseuk lies three times the other eight
members win, otherwise Jaesuk wins.
The reason he feels
acknowledged in Running Man ...
Ask him question about this program.
Ask about the members.
Here's the first question.
"If it wasn't for me ..."
"... Jaesuk, Running
Man wouldn't exist."
"If it wasn't for me, Yoo Jaesuk,
Running Man wouldn't exist."
Been together, but
they haven't heard his inner feelings yet
What will the answer be?
No ~
A calm and comfortable answer
No?
Yes.
Finger pointing up is the truth
Pointing down is a lie
No.
For real?
No ~
Is the answer
a truth
or a lie?
Truth
The graph illustrates
Jaesuk's sincerity
I'm touched, I love you ~
First question and
is his sincerity already accepted?
You are
the best
Isn't this ...
making me say the truth?
But why must we test him?
I really don't think that way.
It's really the truth.
As expected...
Trustworthy~
Is this ...
their attack...?
Don't stand over at his side.
We are in a 1:8 battle now.
It's a battle.
We have to win.
No matter what, I will just speak the
truth and I can get the Running Ball.
I haven't gotten any
Running Balls lately.
Ask properly.
Many polls have been conducted
about women's ideal type  ...
... and Yoo Jaesuk got first
places almost all times.
Yoo Jaesuk is really popular
among the female population.
Maybe ...
... when you didn't get 1st place,
but stuck ﻿at 2nd, did it feel bad?
Does it seem like it?
No ~
Steady state of
mind of Jaesuk
Back when you were still young ...
... you were dumped
by a lot of girls, right?
Finally questioning Jaesuk
Big Nose hyung's
attack
Yes.
Do you think it was
because of your looks?
Yes.
Disappointed
You've been heartbroken
a lot of times, right?
Hyung, weren't you ever regretful?
Suddenly
Silence, we are recording.
Hurry up and ask your question.
Successful plan?
Jaesuk got agitated by it
Yes, I'll begin shortly.
Perhaps ...
Have you ever felt that
you married too early?
I felt It was little late.
Serious
Oh really?
Yes.
Marriage must be very good then.
I'm counted as very blissful.
Occasionally thinking it would be
good if my wife goes somewhere far.
It's totally a court trial
Answer the question.
Can I request for the
right to keep silent?
No ~
Don't you feel like sometimes you
just want to go on a long holiday?
Is your hand now shaking or what?
Jaesuk isn't easy to go against
Now onto the interrogation.
... the interrogation.
Aiming at Jaesuk's true
feelings of married life
Even with the love he has for his wife
But if a pretty female walks by he'd
like to have a cup of coffee with her.
If being reincarnated ...
That idea isn't bad.
If you were reincarnated ...
Attacking question
... you would still marry your wife?
What will Jaesuk's answer be?
Yes ~
Why is it like it's such a listless answer?
What?
Panicking
Victory is here, let's have a look.
If I were reincarnated
I would still marry my wife again
Truth
or lie?
Yes ~
Oh my god
Lie
Yes ~
Saying 'yes'
but the graph
is moving heavily
Sukjin's
interrogation
Success
Jaesuk
He said his
lie
Aigoo, this is a misunderstanding.
It's okay, you're an ordinary Korean man.
This is not right, this ...
The next interrogator, go ahead.
Wait ...
Let's rest for 30 seconds.
Nation's MC
Momentarily
crashed
I felt that Sukjin was really funny.
Yeah, that's right.
Because it was funny
Jaesuk's mood was slightly unstable
It could be like that.
Next up was Lizzy * Jihyo * Kwangsoo
Jaesuk spoke the truth
Now like one's own brother Jongkook's fierce attack
I'll answer it with sincerity.
So it must be real, ask those questions
that has no other choice but be truthful.
Is this even allowed?
Combat?
Trying to threaten and make him uneasy
You shouldn't be like this.
I ﻿only wanted to use your
shoulder to rest my hands on.
I can't move this hand for now.
I don't have anything to say.
Just having a little sensitive issue.
I really miss the old days ...
Yes.
The old seumdwa.
During X-man period ...
The period when 2 people went
through happiness together ...
man's
two individuals
Yoo Jaesuk
Kang Hodong
Dancing with similar movements
Having the same chemistry
Even when being naughty
they had the same expressions
Then
is the question related to Hodong?
I also felt very happy when
I saw Jongkook and Eunhye.
* Eunhye = The actress and singer (Baby Vox) that
Jaesuk made into a "variety-couple" with Jongkook
Eun...
hye...??
-man
period
The topic that brought the
ratings to a higher level
Sunday Couple
&
Maiden
Fighter
One Man
Touched
♥
Reversed to Jongkook
Stay calm ~
Commander
got blocked by
Nation's MC speech
The Two Kids giving some
stress balls to calm him
Go away ~
Venting his anger on the Two Kids
Stay calm ~
Don't be speechless, just
ask the question calmly.
What I was saying ...
... isn't related to that person.
That's why I too, cherish the time
when I was together with Hodong.
I also miss that time with Jongkook and
Eunhye, there was something special.
Jaesuk isn't going down alone
Don't be dissuaded, hyung-nim.
Jaesuk, do you think that
you are the best MC?
Suddenly
No, I don't.
Is that the case?
Withing the country ...
Big Nose
Wasn't time to make his appearance
Okay, got it ...
I'll begin the question.
Attack ~
We all mostly have a similar thing in
common which is about Kang Hodong.
Kang Hodong
Yoo Jaesuk
... Hodong.
Isn't everyone curious?
The dangerous question everyone avoided
Yah, this will produce a lot of Yoo
Jaesuk related news and reports.
Strong headline premonition?
MC Kang Hodong ...
Attack question
... everyone already said he's a good MC.
Best MC.
Best MC, right?
Yes.
"But truthfully I'm always a level higher."
I'm not.
Not even once.
Everyone is curious, but
it' a question no one dared to ask before
Yoo Jaesuk
National MC
Kang Hodong
Has Jaesuk ever felt
that he was better than Hodong
Is this statement true?
Truth
Clearly shown
graph of
truth
Hodong is a hyung I like really much.
Questioning
Failed
Not once did I think like that.
How did you manage to regulate your heartbeat?
How did you manage to
regulate your heartbeat?
I didn't ~
Not even a bit?
Not even this little bit.
This won't do.
Urgent change of attack?
Wait awhile.
Chaotic noise
Our plans up to now are all canceled.
Urgent amendment
You're already here at this point,
what do you do if you cancel them?
For the first time I really
want to get the Running Ball.
Only told 1 lie so far
Will he get the Running Ball?
Fighting ~
The truth
will be victorious
We will
make you tell lies
The questioning will start immediately.
Good.
"﻿I have a member in Running
Man that I want to get rid of."
A sensitive question
that can only be asked by a guest
What will Jaesuk answer?
1, 2, 3.
There isn't.
He's really quite good, that hyung.
They are swayed again
because of Jaesuk's reply
Please, it must come out as a lie.
Really if it comes out as a
lie, it's also difficult to bear.
A member that Jaesuk wants to get rid of
is there really not even one?
Truth
I love you so much.
Give him the Running Ball already.
Please give him the Running Ball.
Jaesuk
we love you
Yoo Jaesuk ~
Stop it, we can't become
weak, come here quickly.
Now I just need to get one more right.
Out of the 2 remaining questions
if Jaesuk gets 1 right then he wins
Nervous
There's nothing more to ask.
It seems like we have already
asked what we wanted to ask.
Just one more question
and it's all over, correct?
This round has to be won unconditionally.
Let's go.
Haroro ~
Bad boy
Haroro!
Mr. Yoo Jaesuk ...
... sit comfortably.
I am Haroro.
Don't be nervous.
Very good ~
He's doing well
Didn't you say that you
played in the past?
What do you mean?
Absurd
I played something interesting.
This interesting thing ...
What?
... where did you do it?
I went to the night club.
Wait a sec.
2nd round of emergency meeting
Members who are afraid of honesty
What's with me at this age?
We can't win.
Have you given someone else your contact
number ﻿and then gotten their number back?
Yes.
Honest
Ah, he has.
Yes, I have.
Did you go out immediately then?
Power UP
There was someone I went
out with for a short time.
We'll ask this sort of
question to the end.
Over-active
hands
Don't use this sort of power to ask.
Be careful of HaHa's fight to uncover the past
Will it fail spectacularly?
Talking
nonsense
Stay calm ~
Ah, so unlucky.
Hurry up and ask.
I want to catch it ~
Come out first.
You really are a pest.
I just answered honestly, why ﻿am I a pest?
Suk, I am your hyung of twenty years.
I know that of course.
I will know the lies you'll tell.
Hyung, really.
Once I open my mouth,
hyung, you're so dead.
Gulp
No, no way.
Sukjin backs off too
Once I open my mouth, you'll be dead.
Then I ask you.
Yes.
Yoo Jaesuk, have you
been slapped by a girl?
Yes I have.
How can it be like this?
Unbelievable ~
It's all in
the past
Wait, he's guarding against the incident where
he was slapped by someone at Bangbaedong.
Now you can say it
<Jaesuk was slapped at Bangbaedong?>
By the noona he liked.
I know ...
You say things clearly now.
Sukjin was unable to induce lies
so he brings up past incidents
Isn't there an incident where you
confessed to a noona you liked ...
Speaking about things only two people knows?
... and smack, got a slap
by that noona in the end.
Really
Really, how can you do this?
Annoyance brought by the
hyung he always trusted
Hyung ...
Then I'll also speak about everything.
The incident just now was first
mentioned by hyung yourself.
Yah, you better stop it.
Let's not die together.
The incident that happened
to hyung at Bangbaedong.
What happened to
me at Bangbaedong?
In the past when YaTa
was the trend in the '90s.
YaTa = To be pure white
Yah ~
Panics
Once he saw a beautiful woman
walk past and he asked ...
"Where are you going?"
"Omo oppa".
Sukjin asked, ﻿"Have we
met somewhere before?"
Gulp
It was my colleague's noona.
Trying hard to deny it
No, it's not true.
Why not test if what I
said was true or not?
It's too time consuming.
Evading
There's no time ...
Hurry and proceed.
Not much time left
of the 30 minutes time limit
While recording with Jaesuk,
is there nothing you know?
Ah... What do we do?
Their preparations were too sloppy.
Sneaking
Peek~
What? What are you doing?
Shocked
Even the machine is also
being dragged here
This person's really very bad.
Why?
How can you all be so relaxed?
Jaesuk sits down after
reconnecting the lie detector
Okay, good ~
Finally a fatal question?
Let's go, there isn't much time left.
Nervous
Donghoon fighting.
Mr. Yoo Jaesuk ...
I'm starting the attacking questions.
Let's start.
Ji Sukjin is in a difficult situation.
Yes?
Can ﻿you give him
200 million right now?
I can.
I'm broke, finished.
Yes, I'll give him 200 million won.
Been friends for 20 years
But can he give him so much money?
Was Jaesuk's answer
the truth
or a lie?
Lie
Yeah ~
Making
the second lie is a
Success
Yah, let's not keep in
contact in the future.
Angry
This can't be ...
He said he wouldn't lend it.
Sad
Of course ...
When hyung is in a bad situation,
of course I'll give you money ...
... but once the situation gets better,
you have to return the money to me.
We're left with the last question.
The amount is too large, I'm sorry.
Do you feel bad inside?
Of course I'd help hyung, but
the amount is really too large.
This one is the most vicious
It's the last stretch.
For the Running Ball, fighting.
Let's immediately proceed.
The final question Decides the ultimate winner
You must give a reply within 3 seconds.
Jaesuk it's been tough on you.
Now we've finally reached the end.
The last question is Gary's idea.
And I felt curious after hearing it too.
I'm starting the attacking question.
Jaesuk ...
I've known you for 20 years.
Think about the last question carefully.
"I ... "
I like Sukjin even more than Kim Yongman.
20 years for better or worse
Which entertainer friend does he like the most?
Yes ~
It means I am even better?
This question is too difficult.
Really, this question ...
Jaesuk likes Sukjin more than Yongman
Is his answer really true?
If Yongman is in
Jaesuk's heart
Then it
is a lie
Is Sukjin is in
Jaesuk's heart
Then it
is true
What's the result?
Yeah ~
True
Because he's together with Sukjin now
he choose Sukjin although it's a difficult decision
I sincerely applaud both of you.
Feeling warmth
Applauding the hyungs sincere friendship
Running Ball.
Now it's time for
bell hide and seek
Within 1 hour, find 4 hidden Running
Man umbrellas in the meteorology
building and hang them on the shelf
Within 1 hour, find 4 umbrellas
and hang them on the shelf.
Office
Instrument observation
Earthquake Center
Instrument test room
Mission Team
Find the
4 hidden Running Umbrellas
It's very hard.
You must remember ...
If our team lose ...
If Chasing Team lose
... you'll face the punishment automatically.
Gary * HaHa * Lizzy automatically gets punished
Seumdwa ~
* They mean 'understood' here
Remaining time
Kwangsoo searches the 7th floor office
A Running Umbrella is here somewhere
Ring
Bell sounds
It just started...
Who's coming...?
Commander
Sparta.
Jongkook
Always appearing so suddenly
Kwangsoo locked the door
He He ~
I learned this technique during
preparation training today.
Hide and disappear.
Hyung, I'm hiding on the 7th floor.
Proud
Jongkook hyung ... ?
Still there?
Sits where he can't be seen
Wow!
Using a CD as a mirror...!
I'm using what I learned in
preparation training school.
Proud
Can he see
Commander?
Jongkook's gone
He left?
Gone
where?
Wait hyung, wait.
Wait hyung, I'm about to pee.
It's the start of winter Not a horror special
Rip...
Start ripping...
Bite
You're biting my arm.
He really
isn't human
Kwangsoo
Searching the 2nd level
Yooruce Willis and Big Nose
We have to find it.
What?
Run ~
Why?
There's a bell sound.
Commander
Jongkook
Lost
their
souls
Big Nose
chased by nearby Haroro and Lizzy
Escaped to the end of the corridor
Led to his own death
Sukjin
Hyunwoo, dad sacrificed
himself bravely here.
Time left
Heechul is searching
the 2nd floor office
Found one.
No Running Man logo
Wrong
Should put it back.
Another?
Still...
wrong
I'm sorry.
A never ending search
Office full of umbrellas
Among all the umbrellas
where are the 4 Running Umbrellas?
Where is it?
Sorry I'm late.
You're 5 minutes late.
Prison regulars
Big Nose
Kwangsoo
The dramatic scene
getting caught on purpose just to meet
Why didn't you keep your promise?
Do you know how long I waited?
Jaesuk hasn't arrived yet?
Looking carefully
Yooruce Willis is missing from the prison regulars
Reason for being late
He's still escaping
I'll try contact Jaesuk hyung.
Jaesuk hyung ...
Where are you?
You ...
Hyung ...
... 5th floor.
It looks like Sukjin
hyung's very angry.
I was late 5 minutes.
I almost arrived, but the
traffic was too congested.
Weak Haroro tries to block Jaesuk
Sorry, HaHa.
They'll scold me if I got caught.
Butt
kick
Revenge
Do you still want to catch me?
Yes or no?
Ah, it hurts.
HaHa, sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Yooruce Willis
escaped from Haroro
Yah, tell him not to come yet.
He's so angry, his hair
is standing already.
Immersed in the dramatic act
Yooruce Willis
2nd floor earthquake
and weather center
Jaesuk
Earthquake and
weather center
365 days, 24 hours
Staff working continuously
Also a central surveying system
that works non-stop
Careful
By any chance ...
... is the umbrella placed near here?
I can't tell you.
Oh...
The look...?!
Oh?...
Is that a hint??
Umbrella
Thank you ~
But is it
really a Running Umbrella?
It is!!
Mission
Team
found 1 of 4
Running Man umbrellas
Ring~
Sparta.
Commander
Jongkook
Eternal enemies
Yooruce Willis
Commander
Fierce
Caught
Yooruce Willis...!
Hyung is barefoot.
What happened?
Escaping barefoot for 2 consecutive weeks
Where are your shoes?
Let's talk downstairs.
There's someone with him?
Who is he coming with?
Still having a good relationship.
Hyung, what time is it already.
Nagging at Jaesuk for arriving late
to their prison gathering
How late are you Jaesuk.
He's not my brother anymore.
He's so late.
You don't keep your promises anymore?
Being caught early is a type of principal
You got stronger.
Aigoo, no I didn't
Sukjin hyung is angry.
Why? What happened?
How late do you want to be?
The road is really congested,
I came from there too.
Really.
Jaesuk
The picture is complete
again, with the 3 of us.
It's really frustrating.
Even children are ﻿saying that
we are the easiest to catch.
Us three?
Yes, the three of us.
Hello children.
As anticipated, we've been caught quickly.
Children's friends
The most
easily caught
3 men team
We are the most easily
caught three man team.
Time remaining
Hide-n-seek hero
Blank~ Jihyo
Hero condition 1:
To avoid the
Chasing
Team
stay low
Hero condition 2:
When it's
time to run
move quickly
Hero condition 3:
Look around
Observe quickly
Found a hidden umbrella
Once the umbrella is obtained
check if its a Running Umbrella
Hurry come inside.
At such time locking the door is necessary
Is this ...
the 2nd Running Man umbrella?
Correct
Found 2 of 4
Running Man umbrellas
Running Man.
The last condition
to become a hero
Not caring about
your image
Can I come to the 1st floor now?
She is still alive.
You can come, it's safe here now.
Ah, can't be like this everyday.
Everyday talking about
coming and whatnot.
Pathetic
What's taking Jihyo so long?
She's here.
Jihyo delivered the second umbrella
Where did you find the first one?
On 1st floor.
I found mine on the 3rd floor.
There's one on the 7th floor.
7th floor?
And if you go to the 5th floor,
keep a look out for my shoe.
Still thinking about his shoe
There's no time to find your shoe.
Jihyo, hurry up and go.
For the incapable men
Jihyo returns to the battlefield
If there's no Jihyo,
what would we do?
I'll tell you the 3 big 'Hyo's in the world.
World's 3 biggest
<Hyo>?
Song Jihyo, Lee Hyori, Hyodoreu.
Hyodoreu (Fedor Emelianenka) = Mixed martial arts champion
Song Jihyo
Lee Hyori
Hyodoreu
On the 1st floor
Heechul
Equipment room
Necessary equipments
in the laboratory for
measuring the weather
Heechul still hasn't found an
umbrella despite searching in many rooms
Can he find one here?
There is an
umbrella here
Wow, this one ...
3 out of 4
Running Umbrellas found
Now bring it to the prison area
Pink pants over there.
Security uncle?
Color of pants may be
the meaning of being unique?
Weird
Suddenly
Haroro's transformation technique(?)!!
Will Heechul
deliver the umbrella without getting caught?
Oh, hyung.
The Commander appears in the prison
First floor what?
With the Commander here
it's difficult to deliver the umbrella
Why'd you open that for?
What are you looking for here?
Jongkook, come have a cup of
coffee or water before leaving.
Today in prison
Trap Commander in here
Jongkook, have a cup of water.
Don't give him that,
give him a new one.
Enthusiastic reception~
Ai, look at what we're doing.
Why all this formality with us?
What?
Who is ...
coming?
At this moment Heechul
Target
locked
Yah, Heechul ...
What man, getting caught now?
Heechul
Remaining time
Out of the 4
obtained 3 umbrellas
One umbrella left
Mission Team's only survivor Jihyo
Moving to the 7th floor
Looking around
Is the 4th Running Umbrella
really here...?
Just then
What?
Haroro and Gary is also on 7th floor
One mistake and she'll be unable to escape
But Haroro ran in this direction
Jihyo ...
So you were here?
Hm?
Really?
Aigoo, this pretty lady.
This big-eyed lady was here all along.
I tried very hard to find the big-eyed lady.
Ah, seriously.
Desolate
Thinking about...
What to do...
How it
was done last time
Why are you suddenly like this?
Wait ...
Sinister Jihyo descends
Hey, how can you be like this?
Hey, seriously you ...
This time totally merciless...
Unable to move Haroro
Hey, it hurts.
Butt
kick
It really hurts.
What sound?
Hey, really painful.
What the...
What...
is this...!
What are they doing?
No, I should hide.
But I can't watch the 2 of them
get intimate and still do nothing.
Ah, the more I think, the angrier I get.
Now if I were to ...
... help Jihyo escape.
It means I'm noble.
But right now, I hate to see
the both of them like that.
Let me go.
They are oblivious of eavesdropping Gary
Don't be like this, Song Jihyo.
If you're like this I'll be soft-hearted.
I've been wanting to act in a movie.
I'll be the supporting actress.
... supporting actress.
Ah, I'm going crazy.
If we play together, I'll let you go.
Acting out a movie, huh?
It's okay, Jihyo's an actress pretending
so to act in a movie is pretty normal.
Uneasy
Today's movie
A story at the
weather station
Action.
Badass CEO
Lead actor:
HaHa
Female employee
Supporting actress:
Song Jihyo
Story plot
Her revenge for being abandoned
How can you do this to me?
Why are you here again?
How could you do this to me?
Everything is fine if ﻿you're gone, there
are many people like you out there.
How can it turn out like this?
Everything is fine if ﻿you're gone, there
are many people like you out there.
This represent the ear
Huk...
I don't want to see your face again.
Ah, I'm going crazy.
Quickly get lost.
People like you are too common.
Not bad?
Pleased
Jealous incarnation appears
Two of you playing?
What were you playing?
Oh, that scared me.
Shocked
Crash
Jihyo temporarily subdues Monday Boyfriend
Why?
Angry
Really sorry ...
Hyung, it's really a misunderstanding.
Really a misunderstanding.
Panic
Unable to clear the misunderstanding
Help whom?
His friend Gary?
or Gary's Monday Girlfriend?
HaHa...
Who will he help?
Jihyo, quickly run away.
Don't worry about this, run.
HaHa, why are you doing this?
Jihyo, quickly go, run.
I'm sorry, hyung.
Don't misunderstand because
there aren't any feelings ...
It's not like that.
Hyung you have to trust me, trust me.
My love was flirting like that
Just by playing a bit of the movie
got released by HaHa
Hyung, can we change this channel to 19?
You don't know how to change the channel?
Stop pressing anything.
Oh, what's their channel number?
19.
Trying to hack Chasing Team's channel
Success
Heard Lizzy's voice
Do you guys play around
with the walkie talkie?
Huff
Puff
Why do you change the channel?
Appears like an unpredictable ghost
That was my own voice.
Give it to me.
Why? This is ours.
Let me take a look.
You changed the channel.
No, we didn't change it.
We're just joking around,
Suspicious
Beep
It's really nothing.
Strongly denies
It wasn't me.
I didn't even move my hands.
Kwangsoo?
Aish!
Heard Commander's voice
in Kwangsoo's walkie-talkie
I'm sorry.
Hello ~
If you press this, I will 'press' your neck.
Time left
Jihyo is on 7th floor
Searching for the last umbrella
It's definitely in this area.
If she finds it
Mission
Team
wins
Where is it?
Where would it be?
Is this the last Running Umbrella?
As expected
The brave Jihyo did it
Found Running Umbrella
Heading towards the lift to the prison
But ...
In front of her
Chasing
Team
Lizzy
The result...
of her fate is...?
Where is Jihyo ...
It is good if she brings it and
hang the umbrella over there.
Jihyo ...
Noise and
commotion
Hears the Chasing Team's voices...?
Jihyo, how is it?
Full of bruises
Is it the Running Man umbrella?
She found the umbrella
Found it?
She got caught.
and had her name-tag on
Hmph
Her name-tag got ripped off, but
she still found the umbrella, right?
Everyone OUT
Mission
Team
Fail
When you came?
Jihyo met Lizzy and
fought 'til the end
Ended up being ganged
and name-tag ripped off
Now, I can't hide any longer.
Let me repeat myself ...
The microphone got treated wrongly too
I really can't do this anymore.
Going back after today's filming ...
... I'm worried how everyone
will look at me.
Why?
What have you done?
I beat up Gary oppa ...
... by pushing him on the floor.
Jihyo ...
That doesn't matter
However...
Hey, he's Song Jihyo.
He's like that.
Today, Jihyo really suffered a lot.
Mission
Team
Boys wasted time
because they felt sorry
In the future you'll be responsible.
Nothing, next time I'll be in charge
of catching, no more hiding
Wow, Jihyo's scary.
From now on ...
... I want to be on the same
team as Jongkook oppa.
Right, you will be in the
same team as Jongkook.
Today's punishment
Wearing hot pants in the park
Those who has 0 balls
Sukjin * Jihyo * Kwangsoo
confirmed for
punishment
Oppa this is hard.
Oh, so cold.
Sudden morning breeze
cuts through the hot pants
Too cold, who goes jogging at this time?
Citizens starting to
warm-up in the early morning
Wow, there are still
people riding their bicycles.
Yah, let's run.
Good morning ~
This is seriously too cold.
Aren't you cold?
You should be colder, right?
Ah yes, it's okay.
Exercising requires perseverance,
that way it's good for the body.
Want to get
punished with running
again next week?
Punishment mission complete
Gwangmyeong station
They got together
I want to be on the same
team as Jongkook oppa.
What's going to happen?