Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by iSUBS
Citizen's choice
Train-ride
Today's landmark
Heart of the subway
Seoul Metro
It starts here
The ultimate battle
Heart-stopping game of
chasing
Oh, Kim Jongkook.
Impossible to
escape from him
Feet
save me
Will he be caught
or will he escape?
Hide-n-seek
in the station
I love you.
Those words
are from the heart
Are you sure?
I'll stop calling you noona,
can I call you you now?
Running Man mission
Increase Jihyo's heart rate
Okay.
Despicable
means and ways
Who is going to
open her heart?
Do you want me to go crazy?
Sometimes forthcoming?
Let Jihyo's heartbeat increase
Today's landmark
Train Carriage Depot
Largest in the east
With an area of 300,000m2
It's like a plane hangar.
So big they can't close their mouths
I believe it is apparent to
everyone, it's a train depot.
The legs of the citizens,
the train metro is here.
Maintenance, cleaning, inspection
are done before they leave again.
Since it's opening in 1974 ...
... the eight lines have transported
about 450 million passengers daily.
It's the heart of transportation in Seoul city.
Today, we'll begin our Running Man here.
It's so interesting.
Anticipation for the new environment
There are really so many
places for us to hide here.
Yes ~
Playing here is like filming a movie.
Yes.
Ah, it's like a movie.
A sense of a movie is born here
Recently, HaHa's true
colors are starting to show.
No matter if I'm being
chased or chase  ...
HaHa's zero pressure chasing skill?
... ﻿I don't really feel much
fear if I meet HaHa.
Jaesuk was being chased
but turned the tables on HaHa
Do you really want to
see my true colors?
Let me see it.
Then I let you see my prowess.
King Childish
Begins his terror threats again
Do you know why you
became suave in the end?
Why?
Because I let you off.
Jaesuk became a hero
because of HaHa's mercy?
Did you really think you were good?
King Childish
Who got shown mercy?
Who got intentionally released?
Actually, there is no difference
between him and a female guest.
If it's a real female guest,
it would be even better.
no longer trusts HaHa
Captain Kook
It'll get better.
Gary told HaHa that it'll get better.
Is it only the few of us today?
Whos' that?
* BGM = "Candy" by H.O.T
Haven't seen his face in quite awhile
It's Tony.
* Tony was a member of H.O.T
The idol prince's return
Army-released Tony
Big welcome
And one more...?
Tony's dad?
Ah, Tony's dad.
Of course he isn't Tony's father
Actor
Kwangkyu
Kim
Wow.
You were recently released from the army.
Dad, how are you doing?
Kwangkyu left a deep
impression with his
acting in <Friends>
Mr. Kwangkyu ...
A casual greeting with the Nation's MC
A role model Kwangkyu(?)
... we haven't met for some time.
Tony ...
Compared to him
a man of few words
Yes?
Why aren't you saying anything?
I haven't adapted back to civilization.
This is our agency's President Tony.
He's a President.
Tony is currently the President of
the agency Kwangkyu belongs to.
It's the same company.
He's also my President ~
Same company
Sukjin*Kwangsoo*Tony are family
I should have realized they
were all from your agency.
They all joined the agency
during my time in the army.
... ﻿so it's the first time I'm meeting them.
Our Jongkook will lead 2 children and ...
... President Tony will lead the 2 seniors.
But no matter what, I'd
like to congratulate you.
Welcome back to civilization
We missed you.
It's really hard to meet you.
Are you good at hide and seek?
I absolutely have no clue
about hide and seek ...
Then prepare to wear hot pants.
Since the first broadcast I have
been punished at least 5-6 times.
If I get 2 more hot pants,
I've collected a rainbow.
Tailoring all his hot pants into a rainbow
Explosion of anticipation from Mr. Yoo
Then let's get the company's
staff to wear hot pants as well.
Hot pants could be the new
standard wear for the agency
Kwangkyu, are you okay with hot pants?
Absolutely not.
Why?
Because not long ago ...
... I had an operation on my ligament.
We just started, so why are you
bringing up such a dreary topic?
Ah, I'm sorry hyung.
Hyung?
He's your hyung?
Surprised
This is a
I know Isee it but it's hard to believe
Is he really your hyung?
Why not?
This isn't some hidden camera?
Weird
This is really unbelievable.
You are?
Embarrassed Big Nose
For real?
Of course.
Really?
HaHa, lend me your hat.
Suddenly wants a hat?
So that's the way it is.
Now the face looks young.
Fast
Reduced 2 years of Kwangkyu's age
Kwangkyu's younger than Sukjin
Confirmed
He really looks younger than Sukjin.
Getting Kwangkyu to not use the
respectful form is really hard.
Why is the President quiet ...
Again few words from President To
... when his agency's actors are having a chat?
I'm still In the process of adapting.
Just now, Kwangkyu ...
How should I address you?
Mr. Kwangkyu ...
When Kwangkyu arrived, he
told me he had variety-phobia.
And he asked me to help him out ...
... but I feel like I'm dying myself.
Burning anxiety
Turns out it's Tony who needs help
I'm the one who needs
more help from others.
Our Gary today has really
attention-seeking clothes.
I took one glance and noticed it.
Are those holes poked through by cigarettes?
sabotage
Is it starting now?
Never ending sabotage by
Kwangsoo
Your skills at sabotage can be
compared to a turbo-charged engine.
Attaching a rocket to his sabotage
It's the strongest.
Has everyone seen last week's episode?
Jihyo's active role in last week's episode?
This kid, really ...
Ah...!
Last week
Jongkook's walkie-talkie
is with me, you rascal.
You just spoke a vulgarity.
Even Yooruce Willis was shocked
I heard it ~
You heard it, right?
I didn't.
Completely denying it
Calm Jihyo
You just said it.
I didn't say it.
So Kwangsoo's claim isn't
completely without basis.
Aiding Kwangsoo's sabotage
Jaesuk's witness account
Yes, not completely without basis.
Of course
If you look behind her legs,
you can see a tattoo ...
... "I love cursing".
Additional
sabotage
Oh...
The girl named Jihyo becomes
more and more of a puzzle
So get yourself ready
Even Jihyo doesn't know The confession of her heart
Blank Jihyo
A summer's day in June
It's Jihyo ~
the solo girl is joining Running Man
Don't you have a boyfriend?
I don't have one now.
Of course you have to say that.
Okay ~
Therefor...
The excited men?
There is one person
who likes you a lot.
There's really no difference
between her and a guy.
But can someone
among them attract Jihyo
I'm only asking this for fun.
Among us men, which one does
noona think is her ideal type ?
Who can cause
Jihyo's heartbeat to increase
Who is her true love?
Jihyo.
Aimed for Jihyo
Gary's fast and furious flirting?
Jongkook who has a love-line
in every variety he appears in?
Or HaHa
Who quarrels with her?
Shut up ~
Although he's younger
Can Joongki move Jihyo's heart?
Or ...
Is it one of them?
Let's discover the heart
that even Jihyo doesn't know about
Increase her heartbeat
and win a Running Ball
In the train waiting for inspection
Now that we've gathered in the train ...
Let's first ...
Wow, look that way.
You can't see the end of the carriages
The train can't normally be seen like this.
I want to run.
Where?
To over there.
Run here later and I'll chase you.
Just think about it.
If you ﻿meet Jongkook
in this kind of place.
If you ask me ...
Hearing the ringing of Jongkook's
bell at the end over there, then ...
... the person here will be stunned.
But later on
Just like Jaesuk said
It really happened!!
Creepily horrifying
Best hide-n-seek will be played here
But the thing that is surprising is ...
... when Jongkook is alone,
he is pretty feminine.
What's this again?
A feminine Jongkook?
I was going to say hey to hyung
but when I opened ﻿the door ...
... Jongkook was playing with a doll.
Sabotage
Hello ~
Even changes the doll's clothes.
You're the best saboteur.
So how do we get Running Balls today?
We have 10 participants today right?
Yes ~
Well use the 1:9 method to compete.
The single one is Ms. Song Jihyo.
Winning Song Jihyo
Jihyo doesn't have any strengths?
If it's Jihyo, she doesn't know
anything else except romance.
Jihyo has always been half-blank.
It's like she doesn't have any
interest in the male guests.
Hasn't it been always like that?
Today we have 9 males.
If you can raise Jihyo's heart rate
to above 130 beats/min, then ...
... the nine male participants will win.
If only one achieves that we all win?
If all of you fail, then only Jihyo gets a ball.
If we all fail?
Then only Jihyo gets a Running Ball.
Even Jihyo herself
doesn't know how fast her heart beats
Is her heartbeat already being measured?
Yes, it's already being tested.
Jihyo's already wearing a wireless cardio-meter
Is she wearing it now?
It's already measuring.
Jihyo's heart rate is shown
on the monitor
It is.
Oh, it's wireless and already measuring.
Honestly reporting
Jihyo's heart beat
So it's here.
Whoa, it suddenly went up.
In the current situation ...
... her heart rate fluctuates between 88 to 94.
What kind of charm will
increase Jihyo's heart rate?
Let's get Jihyo's heart
beating faster
Please speak.
Can we ask some questions .
Like what she likes since we
don't know much about her.
Of course~
Only by knowing what she likes
can they increase Jihyo's heart rate
Of course you can ask.
Jihyo, please come to the center.
We must get to know Jihyo first.
Investigation
Preparing a strategy by
Is there anything you want
to know about Song Jihyo?
When was your first kiss?
Absurd
Please leave ~
Forcing people to exit at the start
Should I instead have asked
her when she was last kissed?
Please don't ask these sort of questions.
Is there anything you want
to ask about, Kwangkyu?
Bachelor Kwangkyu's question is?
What does your dad work with?
More forceful exits coming up~
Please leave.
I still don't know much about variety shows.
Innocent
You don't like the bad-boys, right?
Finally a proper question?
I hate those types.
Jihyo's ideal type is
an attentive man
So you like gentle and considerate men.
But bad boys also have the gentle
and considerate side to them.
No, they don't.
Who?
Suspicious
Isn't he right in front of you?
Will the bad boy Gary
increase Jihyo's heart rate to over 130?
Then lefts chat through
the phone for a moment.
If you like the ﻿sound of their
voice, you reply with a 'Hello'.
Her heart rate will be measured
during the phone call
Otherwise you don't answer.
The pulse shown on the screen
gives a hint about what she likes
Wipe away the looks of our faces
and just listen to our voices.
Are you ready?
Only during this test
will the screen be
shown to the men
Yes.
The first phone call, go.
Hello ~
Pass.
Straightforward
Emotional
Jihyo's continually
declining heartbeat
Before hanging up the phone you have
to say, "How are you father-in-law?"
Okay, next call.
Hello?
Hello.
Cool
What do you want?
Where are you?
At home.
You've been drinking, haven't you?
Framing again
Suddenly
an alcoholic
Jihyo
Because of Kwangsoo's
framing her pulse is rising?
I bet you've been drinking again.
Where are you really?
Suspicion
At home.
With who?
Stubborn
Tell me the truth.
Talking with such bluntness
Green with envy
the irrational(?) Kwangsoo
Do you really want
to see me go crazy?
Where are you?
No changes in his facial expression
I asked, where are you?
Jihyo's pulse is
quite high now
We'll end here.
Strategy
Make her laugh or feel completely
absurd will make her pulse increase
This is really surprising.
So creative.
"Do you really want to see
my face when I go crazy?"
Who'll be the final champion?
Alright, phone call incoming
Hello?
Jihyo clearly likes
the low and husky voice
Hello?
Oh, Jihyo ... it's oppa.
The pulse increase
from the beginning
Ah yeah, how have you been lately?
Did you eat dinner yet?
I've eaten already.
Tony is attentive and caring
If you aren't satisfied with the
conversation, you can hang up.
Filming all the time must be very tiring.
You must eat well.
Touched
Pulse increases due to caring conversation
When you are done filming,
I'll come and take you home.
Most powerful
Huh?
Take me home?!
The phrase 'Take you home' made her
heartbeat go down
She didn't want you to pick her up.
It's too sudden.
Strategy
If you approach her too sudden
her heart rate will go down
If it's too sudden her heartbeat drops.
You should have done it slowly.
It's hard to understand Jihyo's mood swings
Yeah, you should have slowed down.
Who is next to call in?
Hello?
Ah...
this voice is...?
Pretty boy Joongki...!
Oh, hello?
Rapid increase
Noona, it's me.
Oh, Joongki ...
What are you doing?
What do you think?
What I think?
What is she doing right now?
Miraculous chemistry between
these two people
And...
the uncomfortable heart of the Monday Couple
I want to see you.
When?
Sweet lovey-dovey
words said back and forth
Noona? In a while.
Then can I wait in front of your house?
Huh?
My house?
Decrease
She doesn't like people going
to the front of her house.
Then where do you go for a date?
Strategy
Don't mention going to her house
You already have a boyfriend, don't you?
You hate it this much.
Framing kid is feeling excited
But Jihyo is reluctant to allow
people in front of her house.
Her pulse immediately falls
when we talk about her house.
To win the battle
they must avoid talking about her house
I shouldn't have talked about it.
Why isn't he allowed to go to your house?
Very pleased
Next ...
Hello.
Yes, hello?
It's me.
As soon as she
Seriously, at the start already.
hears this chilling voice ...
Why didn't you come today?
Careful
Today?
I just didn't want to come.
Distant
Then you can come tomorrow, right?
Pleading
It's the lowest ~
Lowest rate
The pulse keeps dropping.
Falling as a
bungee jump
It's dropping again.
I've prepared a small
gift for you tomorrow.
Can I know what that is?
A gift from a man who was rejected
I wrote a letter for you.
Hello?
When she heard he wrote a letter
the pulse dropped again
So you hate letters?
I've ripped the letter into pieces.
Jihyo ~
Don't hang up ~
Jihyo, don't hang up.
Good for nothing and
without dignity
Jihyo ...
Oh?
How about we meet in front of
your house at around 7 tomorrow?
Despicable
House?
She hates meeting at her house.
As expected her
pulse drops again
Okay, I'm not going ~
What to do?
Why is Jihyo like this when
we talk about her house?
It drops immediately when
we talk about the house.
Finally
Another call is coming.
Yes.
Hello?
Monday Couple
Gary
I love you.
Immediately
Oh!
Sudden rise
Oh, 120 ... 126.
The power of the Monday Couple?
Every single particle inside
my body is loving you.
It's a winning score but
it's only a preparation test
Jihyo's surprising reaction
to her past affairs
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
A sincere(?) romance confirmed
You're sure you love me?
I'm sure.
Seriously ...
Because ﻿I love you ...
'Bad Boy'
... come to our house.
House?
House' really can't be
mentioned, it just can't.
Immediate downfall
Why can't we go to your house?
Result of Jihyo's test
1. She likes the funny type
2. She likes to be treated with affection
3. She's extremely sensitive to
topics related to her house
The 9 of us are going to engage in ...
... ﻿an emotional battle with Song Jihyo.
If Jihyo's pulse exceeds 130
the men will win Running Balls
Are you trying to raise the tense
atmosphere so we'll start fighting?
All for the Running Ball
You can say it's a fight.
Oh, you scare me.
We're for real.
You're for real?
Yes, only real emotions will ...
Starting right now, let's all love Jihyo.
Of course ~
We'll also try our best
to think of ways to win.
The Kid is looking for
normal love too?
For example, anger, love
and aggression all works.
... or a heart filled with
unconditional love for Jihyo.
Official battle
Jihyo's heartbeat must surpass 130
All possible strategies must be used
Any way will do.
What if Jihyo holds onto my hands?
Do you think something
like that would happen?
Why would Jihyo suddenly do that?
This time they won't
be able to see the pulse-meter
Why would she suddenly
hold onto your hand, huh?
Okay, we'll start with Kwangsoo.
Are you ready?
The situation before ...
That is fine as well.
Ready go.
Meeting in the subway
with an irrational lover
Battle
I'm late.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I think I'll be at home.
At home again?
Suspicious
eyes
Why?
I heard what you said in
the phone call just now.
When? Who was I talking with?
Absurd
Meeting in front of the house
at 7 tomorrow with someone.
Stubborn
In front of the house.
House?!
Even though ...
... you always scold ﻿me,
I control my temper.
Wronged
I ...
I know you always have
your hands in my wallet.
Strike again
Irrational(?) Kwangsoo
All this time I've controlled myself.
It's a misunderstanding.
It's really a misunderstanding.
I can't live without you.
Sudden
change
Kwangsoo, this is all a misunderstanding.
Sudden Chang of character
In order to ...
... keep you by my side,
... I've prepared something for you.
To keep a girl's heart it's necessary with
real actions
In a movie this would be quite interesting.
For the girlfriend
performing magic at daybreak
Anticipating
Using magic to make the rose of love bloom
Wow~
Nervous
Handsomely
kneeling down
Take it away ~
Still very touched ~
This is so touching
This performance is
enough to make the pulse jump
The touching magic continues
First time
seeing the
sincere Kwangsoo
The big finale with opening of the fan
You're not trying to make
them fly around, right?
... make them fly around?
... fly around?
Again
Struck
Do it in another style.
The desolate pieces of petals
slowly floats toward the ground
Now the ...
End it now.
humiliated Kwangsoo
Did Kwangsoo's humiliation
raise Jihyo's pulse to over 130?
You prepared all this, but your
girlfriend doesn't seem to like it.
Next is Joongki.
Yes.
This is seriously nerve-wrecking.
It's an accidental encounter in the
subway with a sunbae from school.
Hello sunbae.
Battle
Coincidental meeting
in the subway with
sunbae
Oh Joongki, long time no see.
Are you going home?
Yes.
Can I sit beside you?
Oh, have a seat.
Warning
Not sure why hoobae Joongki
is a little shy...
I've been observing noona ...
... since you debuted.
But now ...
I want to become the guy that
understands noona the most.
Pounding ♥
In the future I won't
call you noona anymore.
Can I say you  directly instead?
Everyone's dream romance
A shy confession from a young man
But the bystanders hands
are curling up
Can't look on
I have some things to say to noona.
Go ahead.
I have to be closer to you
to be able to say this.
Okay, come and sit here.
I can only whisper it to you.
It's very important words.
What does this mean?
Okay.
Can you please close
your eyes for awhile?
Closer ...
What is Joongki leaning
to whisper in her ear?
But ...
Whispered words...
where are they...?
Sudden kiss?!?!
Shocked
Must have exceeded 130.
Attaining success through a kiss
Joongki is too good.
The train scandal that shocked everyone
But there is
an abandoned young man
Love left me
Come to
my side again
Monday Boyfriend who broke his peace
I'm shaking ~
I'm also very excited.
Everyone's heart rate
exceeds 130
Can't I be excited?
Gary is the only one who isn't laughing
I really am shaking.
That guy looks like he is about to die.
I'm fine.
The left cheek has
not been kissed yet.
Look forward
The big twist later
Monday Couple
The forehead.
Am I next?
I can't kiss her forehead.
Hurry up.
Let us have a look, hyung.
Show your true feelings.
Battle
In the train...
The useless guy...
You can't keep acting cool.
Where are you going all alone?
You're quite cool.
I am ...
... going to ChunCheon.
Eh?
Take line number 4 to ChunCheon.
How old-fashioned.
Instant outburst of
posing difficulty
You should be taking a different
type of transportation, why this?
Jihyo, where are you going alone?
I am going home.
Where is your house?
It's in Ilsan.
Ilsan?
Yes.
Can't talk about going home,
her heartbeat rate will fall.
Touch her hair.
I don't know if I should say this.
Can I call you noona?
Pirated Pretty Boy Joongki
Please close your eyes for awhile.
I have something to whisper to you.
with a different face
The same scene
Can't I ?
Well ...
I'm getting off at this stop.
Cold
You're not getting off?
Absurd
I'm fine.
Not getting off?
Yes.
Pitiful
Getting off alone
Close your mouth ~
No, it's not this friend.
Immediate change of attitude
the moment he gets dumped
She's not my type.
I got a little caught up
but she's not my type.
1st
Team
Kwangsoo*Joongki*Jaesuk
Reveal Jihyo's heart rate
Can Jihyo's pulse exceed 130
as anticipated?
Kwangsoo
I endured it when you scolded me.
A man who uses
obsession as a form of
protective love
I also know you've touched my wallet before.
Joongki
Surprise kiss from
fresh young man
Jaesuk
The one I'm looking for isn't her.
Cautious advance of
the man who
can't act cool
Can anyone of them make
Jihyo's heart beat exceed 130?
As long as one exceeds 130
all 9 men will win
No one made it.
Eh?
Even Joongki's surprise kiss
couldn't exceed 130
Kwangsoo 107.
The highest is Joongki at 117.
Jaesuk 109.
Jaesuk achieved the lowest score
when he mentioned about home.
When Jaesuk mentioned home
All-time
low
She really dislikes people saying home.
But Jihyo said she was
very touched just now.
I was really touched.
Right.
Heart rate over 130
Fail
Really, ﻿I was touched.
So for now we have failed.
Next up is ...
... Jongkook.
The love-line expert(?) Jongkook
Don't say anything to block him.
If not, we can't obtain the Running Ball.
Love-line expert.
Let's set it as a friends relationship.
Friends?
Jihyo becoming friends with Jongkook?
So she wanted to become my friend.
Battle
Meeting in the subway
Friends or lovers?
Jihyo ...
Begins with saying her name in a low voice
I have ...
Undecided
... a song I like recently,
do you want to hear it?
Ear phones.
Carefully sharing the ear phones
The man wearing a shy smile
In the train
Love song only two are listening to
Oh, this song is not bad.
There isn't any sound though.
Didn't catch the right time
Blank Jihyo
Big Nose starts singing
Jongkook's song
Oh, it's that one.
This song is really nice.
* "Come back to me" by Jongkook (ft Gary)
It begins like this
Jongkook's song A subway suggestion
Getting her
heart to beat
The night train serenade
This can't be substituted
by anyone in the world
Friend
Jihyo
Only you can give me
the Running Ball
Touched
The end.
Can the night time serenade
make Jihyo's pulse exceed 130?
Next up is ...
A time for us to rest.
Temporary break when it's HaHa's turn
... HaHa.
Little guy HaHa
Even so, HaHa♥Jihyo is
published as number 1
Battle
The kid experience
love at first sight Jihyo
Scramble courage to sit beside her
No concern
Really avoiding him.
Even
moves away
Dried-up
smile
Unable to win her heart
Oh, this is really hard.
Driving me crazy.
Can HaHa make Jihyo's heart beat faster than 130?
On-the-go plan?
Where are you off to?
Ilsan.
I'm a bit tired now.
Uh?
Lying
down?
Maybe...
thigh pillow?
Aigoo...
In the end forcefully removed
How shameful.
Ashamed
Even his ears
turn red
The kid runs away because
of his shame
Didn't return
for a long time
Next up is Gary.
Next
Hope of the men
Gary
Saddled with the pride of
the Monday Couple
Must be more serious, make
Jihyo infatuated with you.
Must make Jihyo's heart beat
like crazy
If not, we really won't
be able to get the balls
Battle
Monday Couple...
is really dating...?!
Haven't seen you for some time.
Where are you going?
Ilsan.
We have already known
each other for some time.
Two months?
Recently, I wrote some
lyrics while thinking of you.
Sincere
Surprised by the unexpected present
Want to hear it?
Yes, I do.
Can you stand up and listen to it?
While making eye contact...
Two hands held tightly
The topic is ...
... Jihyo blues.
My life, that will love no
matter how tiring it is.
Just like a discarded umbrella I keep.
The lyrics beats
that worm into my heart
Rap confession that touches our hearts
Not stopping my footsteps.
Beautiful Jihyo
Jihyo ~
The lyrics that hip-hop man Gary
composed for Jihyo
In the subway only
one person's love notes resonates
So cool.
So cool ~
Jihyo, do you want
the Running Man ball?
Gary, the simple man
makes his feelings known all this while
Yes.
I want you.
A little bit every Monday
What'does this mean?
Gary and Jihyo who are close
Today...
we...
So now can we start dating?
Can we start dating?
Gary ♥ Jihyo
couple is born?
You aren't really going to date, right?
Mischievous
You aren't really going to date?
Jaesuk can't stand watching it anymore
Don't interrupt, the atmosphere is very good.
Can I have you all to myself now?
Take one more step
and give your heart?
Your lines are too ...
Again
Interrupting
Loving her means I can
also have her to myself.
Unfair
The heart has to be given right?
Yes, but your lines are too ...
Being to greedy
Obviously gets a warning
Now Gary doesn't know
there are cameras here.
A moment with only 2 people
With the cool rap confession
will Jihyo's heart rate surpass 130?
So awkward.
Team
Jongkook*HaHa*Gary
Revealing Jihyo's heart rate
Will Jihyo's heart rate exceed 130?
Kim Jongkook ...
Jongkook
Touching subway serenade
Kim Jongkook ...
... 115.
It's high but
Fail
HaHa ...
HaHa
Used unreasonable concepts(?)
to make Jihyo laugh(?)
Haha ...
... 120.
Reversal
HaHa got 120?
Higher heart rate than expected
Even higher than Joongki's kiss
Increasingly nervous Monday Boyfriend
Gary ...
Gary
One hundred and..
For Jihyo
only one Jihyo blues
Jihyo ~
So cool.
One hundred and ...
If Gary manages to get more than 130
then the Running Balls are ours
... four.
Overwhelmed
104.
Please reconfirm it.
The true(?) feelings of Blank Jihyo
Are you buying my love or not?
A body full of scars
104?
Complicated
If this continues
it will be Blank Jihyo's victory...?!
In the end all of us from the same
company are grouped together.
Remaining challengers are
President Tony and the two seniors
In my opinion we can
anticipate from Tony.
The middle-aged men
look very tensed
Tony will be the last to challenge.
Tony The only anticipated one
You must exceed 130.
Otherwise ...
... only Jihyo will
get a Running Ball.
The three of them can do it together.
Expressionless
Do you feel impatient?
Can't you just trust us?
It's not that.
President Tony and the Two Seniors
Tony, wait for Kwangkyu and
me to set the stage for you.
You attack at the end.
If the three of you fall
we fail the mission.
Go for it.
First Big Nose's challenge
Battle
Hunting in the subway
Acting skills
makes anyone feel awkward
Feeling
After standing for awhile there's actually
a beautiful lady standing beside me.
How long do you want
to be beautiful for?
There's beauty at even a first meeting?
It appeared.
Direct using a line from
an advertisement in the 90s
These words are truly
what hyung said before.
If there's enough time ...
... let's go to the petrol
station and have a cup.
An ad line that
causes Kwangkyu also to shudder
Really, there was that line.
Then how about milk?
What?
Milk.
Do you like milk?
Yes.
There's a type of milk
that I can buy now.
Which type is it?
Couldn't be...
that...?
* Milk in Korean is uyu.
I love u-you.
Feel the blast
Straightforward Greasy Guy
Using greasy method
but will Jihyo's pulse surpass 130?
Anyway, do you have time?
Yes, it's fine.
Sorry, my schedule is tight.
What's this?
Finally ending as Cool Guy
Okay done.
Kwangkyu hyung.
Next challenger Kwangkyu
He may use comedy to
accomplish the mission.
I'll act as her high school teacher.
Battle
On the subway the
teacher is reuniting
with his grown up student
Hello teacher.
A natural start for an actor
Where have we met?
I'm your student.
Song Jihyo?
Yes.
The little thing you've grown up.
Jihyo's reaction is also not bad
It's been very long.
How's your dad?
Suddenly
Again
Reminiscing about the father?
Because the words re-appeard
Jihyo laughs hysterically
If the heart rate rises when laughing
the goal will be achieved
And then ...
Yes?
About us ...
Look at me.
Surprised
Our foreheads are a bit similar.
A natural marriage?
Having similar foreheads
Obviously making Jihyo laugh
Can it cause her pule to exceed 130?
Ridiculous.
Our last hope, you must exceed 130
The last hope Tony
Have you previously met Jihyo?
Previously she acted in our music video.
JTL were shooting an music video
when the two of them met
* After HOT disbanded in 2001, Tony
and two other members became JTL
During JTL times.
We went to Saipan, do you remember?
A meeting a long time ago
in a foreign country
President To it's all you now.
Last chance with a burdensome feeling
Acting as a friend.
Yes.
Battle
From ...
friends to lovers
Jihyo ...
Have you retired from the army?
Yeah.
Flustered
It's very late now, is it all right?
It's okay.
Actually, the reason for meeting today is ...
... there's something I'd like to tell you.
Inward expectation
Expectation
On guard
Hello everyone ...
Sudden
Shocked
The response of the other passengers
I just returned to civilian life after 2 years
in the army, my name is Ahn Seungho.
This is the ...
public subway confession
Beside me is a friend
I've known for 10 years.
A hero's elegant confession
But she is a fool ...
... for all these 10 years she
didn't sense my feelings for her.
Today I've plucked up the courage
in front of everyone to confess to her.
Love's fool Blank Jihyo
Don't say it
Enthusiastic response
for the Running Ball
Finding courage in front of many people
Going to confess...
Will it work?
Deep sigh
♪ ﻿Since meeting you ... ♪
♪ ﻿To be together with you  ♪
♪ looking at each other ... ♪
Please 130
♪ Looking at you ... ♪
My inner song is only for you
Jihyo ...
... will you date me?
A smile appeared because of
a courageous confession
... will you date me?
Touched
Her pulse surpassed 130
Certainly
Only now catching her breath
Tony's charismatic public subway confession
What's the use of singing 100 lines of rap.
Collapse
It feels like we can do It this time.
♥ Blank~
Let's stand up.
Go over and it's fine.
We'll now announce the individual
heartbeat scores for the 3 of you.
Sukjin ...
Sukjin
One hundred and ...
Slow and steady
90's flair
I love u-you.
One hundred and ...
... six.
Not enough
Fail
Didn't have any expectations for him anyway.
Kim Kwangkyu ...
Kwangkyu
One hundred and ...
Our foreheads are similar.
Made Jihyo laughing
Forehead confession(?)
One hundred and ...
... twenty.
Higher than expected
but still
Fail
Even Kwangkyu is
higher than me ...
Please ~
Tony ...
Their last remaining hope
Please ~
As predicted
One hundred and ...
Tony
Will you date me?
A girl's romance
Public confession in a train
One hundred and ...
Please...
...exceed 130!
... 25
Although the highest pulse
What a waste
Fail
In the end it's a one-person win
Jihyo wins.
Strong heart(?)
Jihyo wins the Running Ball
Aren't you happy now?
The first person to get
a Running Ball is Jihyo.
And so
Mong Jihyo's victory finishes
The 104 scorer off to
find a new Running Ball
Hide-n-seek starts now
Action
Chases
Friendship
Love
Competition
More like a movie than before
The fast paced game
This immediately
starts now
Aigoo, we're at a disadvantage.
Mission
Team
Battle strategy
You can see everything in just one look.
It's big but also very empty
The depot passages
President To ...
... why did you choose
your team mates like this?
The combined age of the 2
of you is almost over 90.
At least one of us should go to that side.
It feels like Jihyo is badly
positioned in this team.
Then let's change our positions.
No ...
Didn't mean that by badly positioned
Hints for the places where
the briefcases are hidden
Find four briefcases within an hour.
Number 3919.
Hanyang express, materials
storage room and fish tank.
1. #3919
2. Hanyang Express
3. Material storage room
4. Fish tank
There's a new rule for today.
There are revival tags in 2 of the briefcases.
Where the briefcases are hidden
The tags ﻿can be used to
save caught team mates.
The revival tags
can be used to revive caught members
You can use them after the siren sounds.
Pay attention to the sound of the siren.
Oppa, let's move out.
Because of the revival tags
An unpredictable mission
I'll go to Number 3919.
You go to the materials storage room.
Chasing
Team
Meeting
Kwangsoo, now when you
are in the Chasing Team ...
... you must adapt well
to your surroundings.
Chasing team's
new member
Yes.
We have no strategy, you
only need to get scolded.
Move fast and follow my orders.
Discovery
of his role
Will hyung do it too?
I'm the vice-captain.
It was only that time that
you were the vice-captain.
Showing off in front of the new member?
Acting close
What are you doing?
Even innocent Joongki is...!!
There are new rules today.
The captured members can be revived.
It's such a big place and
they can be revived?
So they can be revived.
How do they
get revived?
Remaining time
* Filming safely after obtaining permission
Kwangkyu-ah ...
It's hard to suddenly change into informal speech
This is the Hanyang express.
1. #3919
2. Hanyang Express
3. Material storage room
4. Fish tank
Middle-aged brothers going to Hanyang express
I don’t know if I can trust him.
There are a lot of Hanyang trains
Will we be able to find
the bag in our first try?
I'm at 3919, you search elsewhere.
Jaesuk:
Okay, search well for the briefcase.
Hyung look over there, I'll look ...
Stop calling me hyung, it isn't right.
Over there ~
Chasing
Team
Appears
How do we escape?
Flustered
Escape first then hide
Over here, they are running.
HaHa:
With time to spare
Middle-aged brothers
We'll get them no matter what
Confidence
Really fast, they kicked
up their heels and ran.
Although middle-aged they ran really far
Still close by
Chasing
Team
Oh, I'm going crazy.
Have you ever been in an action movie?
No, I mostly act.
I'm only in supporting roles.
Weak middle-aged brothers
Before this, I wanted to work out here.
Train
parts
There's dumb bells.
Matching well with Jongkook
Train wheels
Is this Jongkook's gym?
This is a gym.
Ah, dumb bells.
Can I lift these?
Careful
Chasing
Team
Closing in
Flat
earth
Why do that?
Honestly just hide
Kwangkyu ...
... you should run that way.
Then we'll meet up later.
Zoom!!
Hide ~
Kwangkyu saved me.
Kwangkyu appears after ditching Sukjin
Closing in
Kwangkyu
running that way
Listen to hyung, after you run ...
Towards the field
Emerging from the savannah
An antelope
Also Kwangsoo is here
Help me ~
Help meee
Someone
save me
Using his middle-aged dongsaeng to save himself
Kwangkyu ...
Sorry?
Cold
I knew he would get caught.
Not knowing about it
For Sukjin's survival
Bait
How afraid
In the end surrounded by three
Surrender
Only 3 minutes after it begun
I'm sorry, hyung.
Middle-aged Kwangkyu
1. #3919
2. Han Yang Express
3. Material storage room
4. Fish tank
Prepared 3919 train
Only front and back doors are open
Bell sound ...
Who...?!
It's impossible to hide if they meet
It's Jaesuk.
Sparta Kook
Sparta.
Why must it
be Jongkook?
Yooruce Willis
Running to the front door
Over here ~
Gather ~
The vice-captain?
Surround strategy begins
Kwangsoo
Jongkook
HaHa
Gary
Joongki
Jaesuk
Yooruce Willis
Escaping and leaving the VJ behind
Chasing all the way
Sparta Kook
Yooruce Willis
Will it end like this or...?
Not
there?
To the other side.
Running out of the train
Where...?
Jaesuk has run to the other side.
Isn't he caught?
If he ran in the other direction
he should've been caught by HaHa
He's not on this side.
Where's Jaesuk hyung, VJ?
Again being ditched
by Yooruce Willis
VJ in-charge
Where did Jaesuk hyung go?
I don't know.
He should be together
with the video camera.
He's still never going to say die
Yooruce Willis
Materials storage ~
Gary:
Can it be Yooruce Willis?
Ran to the material storage?
But there's still on thing(?)
Jaesuk's VJ in-charge
Here ...
Yooruce Willis...!!
Hiding behind the wall near the door
Life reduced
10 years
Are they gone?
They're gone.
Yooruce Willis'
search at train 3919
Fail
Time remaining
1. #3919
2. Hanyang Express
3. Material storage
4. Fish tank
Jihyo moves toward
the fish tank
Fish tank?!
This is the fish tank, right?
So where is the bag
Bell jingles are slowly approaching
Anxious
Where is it?
Package
found
Out of 4 items
Jihyo found one
Noise and
excitement
Not far away
Sukjin being chased
Uh?
?
Can't be
Fainted when she saw Jongkook?
Quickly turns over
Not that
Crawling to hide the body
Transforms to a dedicated warrior
Could there be a
revival tag in the bag...?
Yes!
When siren sounds
revive a captured team mate
Pursued middle-aged
Sukjin
Over here.
Oh, scared me to death.
Chasing
Team
Tightly surrounding
Sukjin
Gone already?
Hey, you need 3 people to catch me?
What is this?
The middle-aged meet up in prison
You got captured?
I even became the bait,
why did it end up like this?
Dissatisfied
It isn't like that.
Wall of distrust between the brothers
Because of you I got ...
... surrounded and captured.
After Sukjin's deception
suffered humiliation
Solemn
Stirring
Ah, our team ...
Kim Kwangkyu and I, Ji Sukjin,
both got caught as expected.
We are fools.
Only hope for middle-aged brothers
is the revival tags
Please bring the revival
tags and rescue us.
Time left
Joongki is patrolling
the material storage
Scary
Oh man...
Joongki
walks out
1. #3919
2. Hanyang Express
3. Material storage
4. Fish tank (clear)
Found a
package
on the shelf
Found the one in the storage room.
Oppa you found it?
Gather over here.
Wait a minute.
Mission
Team
2 out of 4
Got the package
Does it contain revival tag too?
Didn't contain a revival tag
Disappointed
1. #3919
2. Hanyang Express
3. Material storage (clear)
4. Fish tank (clear)
Maintenance
Yooruce Willis
Returns to
find a bag
Chasing
Team
Coincidentally runs toward 3919
Jongkook ~
VJ:
Again?
Temporarily escapes
Full speed
In the train.
Jongkook discovers
Yooruce in the train
Follow me ~
Hawk eyes
is he superman?
If it's like that
they might meet at the front of the train
Stops in the middle
Yooruce Willis
Panting
Because of fatigue
Lies down and hides from outside view
Watches commander Jongkook's activity
Song Jihyo ...
Aish, it's HaHa.
Runs for nothing
Jihyo runs inside 3919
Sharp
break
Hmm?
Why did she stop running?
What, why?
...Oh?
What oppa?
Resistance?
Against the easy to deal with
direct confrontation?
Village Imp HaHa
Bang!
Hyung, caught already?
What did you say to me because I'm alone?
HaHa gave up and quietly left
Jihyo*Gary
On each side of the door
Ho ho
Knock
Seriously, just once ...
Jihyo ...
Gary
Heartbeat attack 104 at this place
What
scene is that?
Nobody will want to be part of that situation
Jihyo?
Jihyo, what are you doing now?
Jihyo ...
Ding~
Commander
Jongkook
Ah, it's Kim Jongkook.
Strong
attack begins
What to do?
Go to the other side.
Chucklingly
waiting ...
Yeah, Jihyo ...
Wait.
Oppa ...
Swaying here and there
Wasn't meant to be like this Hugging carelessly
Jihyo ...
Thanks to Jihyo
Yooruce Willis
successfully
escapes
Fierce
Now I can't do anything at all.
I don't care that her heart beat only
was 104, she'll still be my angel.
Hyung, I caught Jihyo.
Kwangsoo, where are you?
Saw Jaesuk's clever escape
Where have ﻿you been?
Where did I tell you to stay guard?
I did exactly what hyung asked me to do.
Make sure you rip off the name tag.
Warning
She who is
unwilling to hug me Out
Let's make a deal.
What deal?
You were captured by me, but
we pretend you were revived.
Okay, I understand.
How can you be revived?
Stealthy
Will Jihyo
reveal the secret in order to live?
It's when the siren sounds.
Oh, okay.
Disclosed the secret for her own survival
Not wanting to be found out for releasing her
Don't forget the agreement with oppa, understand?
Oh, why does my leg hurt?
Thanks a lot.
Ah, Jihyo ...
Once again
Gary let her go again
Remaining time
Siren
Warehouse filled
with siren alert
If there's a revival tag ..
... we can get revived now.
With one revival tag Jihyo runs to
the prison
Shall I bring the revival tag to the prison?
Oh, siren.
The revival siren that
Jihyo talked about
Stop the reviving
Jihyo, come over to the prison.
In front of the prison...
Result?
Middle-aged brothers
Who will be revived?
Danger
Big Nose hyung
got hold of the revival tag
Chance to revive in midst of confusion
But middle-aged dongsaeng never gives up
Sukjin got saved
Jihyo
Abandoning dongsaengs
I'm running
Good job Jihyo planned to
swap with playful Sukjin
I'm revived, please help me put it on.
Oh, Jihyo got caught?
Revived
Playback a little, tell me
which direction they're at.
Stops in front of a overhead camera
It's okay, I don't wish to run anymore.
Where did they go?
Wants the camera to tell him
the Mission Team's location
HaHa won't get bewitched
Camera director
However...
Nothing in the vicinity Camera only shots HaHa
Then it's movie time
Today's shoot
Warehouse action scene
Lead actor: (No one else but) HaHa
Flower Boy Joongki got casted too
Title:
No. 3 line
Brothers
Very interesting, stifling ...
Totally engrossed
Clonk
Genuine
Ha ha ha ...
Embarrassing hyung
Using the walkie-talkie for
'shooting posture'
Why?
Innocent
HaHa hyung
is so cute ~
Without Joongki
continuing the movie
Where is ...
the Mission Team?
There!
What are you doing?
Got too
engrossed
Tony's staying still
Discovered Tony hyung
Hyung, you were there?
Stop, hyung ...
Has style when filming and chasing
Oh~ HaHa
What's this?
What's with that bag?
You scared me.
Jongkook hyung, over here.
Where is here?
Distraction
Commander
Jongkook
The calm warrior
Dodging to the left and right
Ridiculous
Please let me die honorably.
Tony...
wants to film a movie too?
Tony
Time left
Where can it be?
1. #3919
2. Hanyang Express
3. Material storage (clear)
4. Fish tank (clear)
This time going to the
front control room
Yah, it was here.
Yooruce Willis
finds the 3rd bag with a revival tag
One bag left to find for the mission to be over
Tries to run to the jail
with the revival tag to save his mates
Is there a revival tag?
Oppa, come and sit here.
If you sit here they won't suspect a thing.
If I sit in jail they'll think I'm out
If you sit here naturally ...
You're still alive?
I recently got ousted.
Here, put this on.
Hyung, help him stick it on
Revival sticker is given to Tony
Where should I start looking?
Mission
Team
Tony revived
Chasing Team
isn't spending any effort on the jail
Don't worry about here.
The bells sound is nearing, go now.
The revived Tony
goes to Hanyang train where the last bag is
Sukjin is being chased again.
Acting like he
was caught
Who's catching who now?
Watching whilst feigning death
In reality, we don't even know.
Gary is behind, be careful.
Faking it
Sukjin, what's the matter?
Sukjin was caught again after
a hard-earned revival
Where's Tony?
Don't tell Sukjin that I'm still alive.
Yah, why are you here?
Sharp-eyed Big Nose hyung
discovered Jaesuk's name-tag
If Chasing Team finds Jaesuk's name
tag still on then there'll be hell to pay
Jaesuk oppa is really making me crazy.
How do we hide this?
Hold it together, I am
now a caught person.
What about the mission?
Very easy, the moment Tony
finds it the mission is complete.
Oh ...
So that's why you're sitting here.
Hyung, they don't know
about this so it's okay.
Ah, Tony is in danger.
Chasing
Team
Again surround strategy
Looks like it's dangerous
I have to go.
Oppa, Jongkook is coming.
Retreats
Temporarily acting natural
Strong one
Approaching
Leave it to me.
Fast mumbling
Jongkook ...
Why are you only treating me this way?
Awkward
Oh no, so
unnatural
Ah, Kim Kookjong is really senile.
Finished
Big Nose hyung
How are you going to
divert Jongkook's attention?
You come here, what about Tony?
Tony!
Unnatural
Didn't discover the name-tag
because of Jihyo's cover
Covers Jaesuk
What's going on?
What do you mean?
Something's strange.
An awkward team tries to cover up
What is it?
But why ... ?
Can't be discovered
with the name-tag still on
why?
What's up?
Tony ~
Strong one
Jong
kook
feels something's wrong
Yah, Gary ...
Summoning Gary
Come here ~
Why?
Come here.
Wait a sec.
Why? What's happening?
Tony ...
Oh no...!
Starts to turn messy?
If you do that...
everyone will be attacked
All crew on board
Chasing
Team
Discovers Jaesuk's name-tag
Struggle
Plans turned into a disqualification situation
HaHa, go away.
In this whirlpool the easy kid HaHa
They are so tangled up that it's
hard to differentiate the teams
Rip off
Jaesuk
It's all because of Sukjin hyung.
Why is your acting so lousy?
Why did you act so weird?
Hyung, that was really weird.
Today's pilot of death(?)
Big Nose
Get lost.
Can it be...
X-man...?
* X-man was a show with Jaesuk, Jongkook, HaHa etc,
where one contestant should sabotage for his own team
Remaining time
Only survivor left
Tony
Where is Tony?
Have you found him?
Tony ah, go to the 5th train.
5th ... five ~
Only the 5th train hasn't been searched
Tony receives the message
5th ... five ~
5th train
If he finds it Mission success
Oh, it's Tony hyung.
Everyone spotted Tony
Tony ~
Running to the 5th train
that Big Nose pointed out
No ~
Will he find it first?
He can't ...
Or will he be caught first?
There should be
a bag there, right?
Where..
Where is it?
He told me it was here.
It's not here.
Tony
Chasing
Team
Everyone
gets a Running Ball
It's in the
5th train
Isn't it?
Today's winner
Jongkook and the kids
Current time
Jihyo and Tony got the thief card
after getting it in game three
Although today was tiring ...
Running Ball count
Jongkook*Gary*HaHa*
Joongki*Kwangsoo 2 each
Sukjin*Jaesuk*Kwangkyu*Jihyo 1 Tony 0
... our hearts are at peace.
Of course.
Only Tony has no Running Ball
Our team was very tight, right?
Kim Jongkook ~
On fire
Ah, really.
Spectacular
It's so nice listening to it.
The mark of betrayal
Saboteur Kwangsoo
Jongkook hyung ...
Only for a week a loyal oath
The might of Jongkook and the kids
Wait, Tony didn't even get one ball.
Confirmed
punishment?
No hope for Tony
He didn't get any Running Ball
That's incredible.
Big Nose prepares his hot pants
It looks great.
Army design
Lost and confused
What is today's punishment?
Wear hot pants and take the metro.
Jihyo's has to wear a mustache.
Wear a mustache.
Draw 5 balls and the owner
of the ball gets immunity
Jihyo wear it?
Jihyo's special punishment
Wear a mustache
Who's first to get immunity?
Please ~
Just this once.
1, 2, 3.
The first lucky person is?
... 3.
HaHa
Confirmed
immunity
A joyous expression
You're really so good lucky.
Super lucky HaHa
Tony has nothing to
do with this anymore.
1, 2, 3.
Sukjin
Confirmed
immunity
The failure culprit(?)
gets immunity
Please.
Come out, just come out.
Joongki
Confirmed
escape
A mixture of joy and disappointment among them
Please ~
The 4th lucky person is?
Unbelievable
Again
HaHa
I'll buy you a cup of wine for the ball.
1, 2, 3.
This is the last chance
The last to get immunity is?
Gary ~
Really
Lucky
Jongkook
A dance unsuited for his body
Together
Celebrating
their immunity
Once again Jaesuk is an unlucky shadow
Jihyo's streak of constantly escaping
punishment has come to an end
Who wants this ball?
The twice selected HaHa
can ask for another draw
Start.
HaHa ~
Ha Donghoon ~
* HaHa's real name is Ha Donghoon
Me too.
Suddenly
Boss ...
An indecisive
boss!
Aigoo.
You were cute since the H.O.T times.
Boss.
HaHa I love you.
Retarded talent showcase
Tony
Jaesuk you should come too.
I have one.
A sincere plea.
Revenge
I would rather wear a hot pants.
I'll give this to ... Tony.
Now Tony has a ball
in the lottery too.
This is really Tony's big comeback.
Who is the last lucky person?
Please
Who is it?
Kwangsoo.
Kwangsoo
Confirmed
escape
The one and only hope disappeared
Only Gary from the Chasing Team didn't
get an immunity, instead Sukjin got it.
I think I wore the correct clothes today.
Aigoo, going to work?
Yes.
Jihyo's special going-to-work style
We've worked hard.
Mr. Dept. Head has also worked hard.
Wearing long pants
Dept Head Kwangkyu
Ah yeah, we've been working hard.
Morning exercise Go go
The metro station
Entering the train
Hardworking citizens already on their way to work
Shamefully boarding
Confused~
This is the first time I've been photographed
since I finished my military service.
Oh, congratulations.
Citizens taken the 1st photo of Tony since the army
Respect the elder(?)
Gary lets Kwangkyu take a seat
Except for the hot pants ...
... he looks like going to
work without pleasure.
Congratulations.
Congratulations?
Thank you.
Congratulations.
He said congratulations.
Ah, congratulate you
on getting punished?
Yes.
The I shopping mall in Yongsan
Coming with a cute smile
Girl's Generation's Kwon Yuri
Faced with a weird ambience
The cause of Yuri's tears is?
November 31st - 5:20 PM