Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by KJK Global
Today's landmark
A place where the spirits of
the kings and the history of Seoul exists
Gyeonghuigung Palace
Seoul museum of history
I am an independent
soldier of the streets.
Dual Daggers of
Jongro is back
It hurts so much.
A jump between centuries
Running Man's new history
A leisurely cup of tea.
And...
What is this?
A shocking history of
Running Man is revealed in the Center of History
A palace and history special
begins now
Today's landmark
Seoul Museum of History
Today we're at Seoul Museum of History.
Yeah.
The history of the past
breathes amongst
today's city here
And right behind is
Gyeonghui Palace
For almost 400 years the palace has
remained in this place
Ah, Sukjin hyung is coming.
Oh, Sukie ~
Silly
Oh, Mario.
Oh, Sukie.
Sukjin
Retro fashion to celebrate the Museum of History
Hyung, why did you run like
this when you just came?
Sukjin even runs like a retro dance
It's just my habit.
They're coming ~
There comes mister
Muscle and the Henchmen.
Muscle Kim and the Henchmen
The street boss
The Boss and two Kiddies.
Henchman (1)
Hello.
Henchman (2)
I thought you were a group,
Kim Jongkook and the Kids.
... and the Kids.
Jongkook and the Kids
So now you don't need to
be selected to be in a team?
You just follow Jongkook?
Yeah, he's like a brother from next door.
Not just colleagues anymore more like next door brother
But in the last episode you were
scolded so much by Jongkook.
Last week
After losing the kids got badly scolded
Then you should be punished as well.
What do you mean I
get punished as well?
We're filming every week
from this week on ...
... but Joongki couldn't make it
today because of his drama filming.
We need him.
Worried
I wonder who is coming
in place of Joongki today.
Who are today's guests
Who's that guy?
Little Rain
Lee Joon
Oh, it's Victoria.
From China
Goddess
Victoria
Another one's coming.
Who is it?
Who's the last guest that got everyone's attention?
Jongro's
Dual Daggers
Park Joonkyu
Three mega guests today
Victoria
Park Joonkyu
Lee Joon
From the start
the 40's American style~
He's still
RapKyu
Say hello to Victoria.
Hello.
Bubbly:
Hesitates
American style as expected
Cute~
What happens now with the teams?
Everyone's here
What about the teams?
Let's keep the same teams as last week.
I think Joonkyu can go to that team.
Joonkyu
Jongkook's team
He can be in Jongkook's team.
Yeah.
.....Mmm-hmmm.....
... Jongkook's team.
I heard from PD Cho that ...
... your feelings were slightly hurt.
A few days ago
Sukjin expressed his disappointment to the PD
Why?
He complained that although Kim
Jongkook is younger than him ...
Jongkook is younger
Yes.
... ﻿and yet he has his own team.
but has his own team
When did I say that?
Yes you did.
Actually ...
... ﻿I think he looks ridiculous
whenever he tries to MC.
* MC = Host of a program
... ridiculous when he tries to MC.
Jongkook MC
Ridiculous(?)
Are you an MC?
Sad
Sukjin's MCing greed never dies
It just happened when we divided the
teams, I didn't have any other intention.
Then how about you be
the leader of this team?
Solution
Sukjin takes care of Jaesuk's team
Whose team?
This team.
No, I there'll just be a lot of complaints.
Admitting the truth
There's you in the team.
Then how about coming to our team?
Persuades
What?
Come to our team.
No, that can't happen.
Hey, no way.
I will only come on the
condition that you leave.
The team you're in ...
... that team should have been mine
The teams have been decided, but what team
do Victoria, Joonkyu and Joon want to be in.
Don't go that way.
What?
Holding ...
... tightly
..... Huh?
What are you doing?
Nonsense
We like our team like this.
Jongkook's team has been formed with holding hands
Why is Gary holding Victoria's hand?
I didn't realize ...
Shy
Sorry Victoria.
Blaming the team
I didn't know...
So this is your team?
Yes, I imagined the team
like this from the start.
Jaesuk Team
Sukjin Kwangsoo Jihyo Joon
Jongkook Team
JoonKyu HaHa Gary Victoria
What's wrong with our team?
There's nothing wrong.
What is the punishment
for the losing team today?
Should we do hot pants?
Wearing hot pants
Let's do it.
But do we have them ready?
We can buy them.
PD: We can buy them
Really?
Let's do hot pants then.
You take a bus home
in those hot pants.
Today's punishment
Take a bus home
wearing hot pants
Yah, really ...
Hot pants, that's just a bit ...
Worried
Today's punishment
Take a bus home
wearing hot pants
Expect
Their punishment full of
embarrassing moments
Do I smell?
Slides~
Which team will carry out the punishment?
Finally Running Man
in Seoul Museum of History
Seoul Museum of History
Opened 2002 and displays the history
from the Chosun period until now
The only museum that records the
history of Seoul city
Seoul museum?
Seoul Museum of History.
Do you know what this is?
Isn't it an information desk?
Huh?
Information desk...
No, it's the same thing as
in the lobby in Die Hard.﻿
<Die Hard>
Same desk?
Why do you like Die Hard so much?
Complains
What did you say?
It's because I'm Yooruce Willis.
I am
Yooruce Willis
I survived all the way
through to Die Hard 2.
Today you'll get to see more of
Yooruce Willis' action scenes
A scene in front of them as soon as they enter
What's that?
It's Jongro street.
The history of Jongro in Seoul is all here
This is the old-fashioned cafe in Jongro.
The cafe from the past
has been reproduced
I think this will suit Joonkyu.
Oh, this ...
Hang on, Dual Daggers hyungnim.
Yes!
That's right
He's the man.
Dual Daggers Park Joonkyu
Because it's ...
... my eyes are tearing up.
How come we didn't recognize
Dual Daggers hyungnim.
Dual Daggers helped to protect
Jongro from the Japanese army
Dual Daggers vs Koomajuk.
Dual Daggers vs Koomajuk was the
highlight of highlights
Dual Daggers
Park Joonkyu
In front of Dansungsa
a legendary fight
He's back in Jongro
The charisma of Dual Daggers
Still lies under the trench coat and fedora
He still suits the fashion.
Ah, the old memories...
We are ...
... ﻿the independent soldiers of
the street who use our fists, ya.
Awkward having to pose again after a long time
Hyung, why did you use blades then?
Just told us that he used fists
Here is...
in front of an old cinema?
Hey,  this ...
Inside where we stepped ...
There are hand prints.
This is ...
Countless hand prints of movie stars
This is Hollywood, Hollywood.
A reproduction of Star Square
in front of Piccadilly Theater
They had this in front of
the Piccadilly theater too.
Oh, Joonkyu's father.
Really?
Yes, really.
Hand-prints of
Joonkyu's father
Actor Park Noshik
It fits just right.
It's the same handwriting as my dad.
Dual Daggers Joonkyu ...
meets his dad in Jongro
I have the separate version
in my house as well.
Hey, there's ﻿a pancake shop in here.
This is a well-known shop.
Pi Mat Gol's oldest restaurant
Chung Il Jib was reproduced
They reproduced the shop here
after Pi Mat Gol was gone.
Oh, the desks and everything back then?
From 1945 a pancake shop
with 65 years of tradition
Yes, they moved everything here.
I think whoever drew this picture
will be crying after this episode airs.
Before moving from PiMatGol
the interior was replicated
Ahjumma ...
Naturally
We didn't say 'excuse me' in shops
like this, we went 'Ajumma'.
Memories of the past in this comfortable atmosphere
Are we eating something?
What?
No.
I feel like eating something from here.
So we're here now.
After looking around the streets of Jongro
What do we do?
You're going to play three games
that was played in Jongro.
First mission
3 games of Jongro street
Three games of Jongro street?
Yes.
Break the chopsticks that
is between your fingers.
Break it by slamming
your hand on the table.
You take turn and when one of you fail
the opportunity goes to the other team.
Ah that one.
I played it so much when I was little.
In the past every kid played it
This game should be ...
And ajumma told us to stop.
You don't need muscles for this game, right?
Of course.
Do you remember when
we played this game.
Which one?
Oh, he's good.
And you do this.
That's for beginners, you
mix that action into this.
So free
Well done ~
As expected HaHa plays like when he was a kid
That's that, but ...
... try to do that with this much muscles?
We didn't do it the way HaHa did.
Victoria, you don't know this?
Victoria is from China so she doesn't
know about Korean student games
Jihyo, you try it.
Coarse
What can Jihyo do the best.
You go like this and flick like this.
Like this?
Jihyo ...
What can you do the best?
Serious
No pressure or anything.
I'm really curious.
Are you even able to get to your house?
Why did you bring that up?
Big Nose is attacking Jihyo again?
Jihyo don't feel pressured, just
think about what you're good at.
Thinks...
Love?
Gary: Love?
Cheesy
Love...?
Jihyo is the best at
love?
What about love?
What a surprise.
She has lovely eyes.
Do you like her?
Pricked conscience(?)
What
what
what?
Huh?
Do you like her?
Look at them...?
Gary revealing his heart...?
Do you like her?
Changing subject
I suddenly feel like doing this.
Chopstick chopping
So simple
Everyone having a go...!
Elementary school kids 38 years old in average
Anyway
Gary managed to change the subject
What's Gary good at?
I'm good at enduring pain.
So random...
Really, I'm good at enduring pain.
His calm facial expression is due to endurance?
Can we really pinch you?
Can you endure the
pain when you get hit?
Of course.
Thud!
Just once ...
With a silver spoon...?
Would it be okay with this?
It will hurt...
Hit the forehead with chopsticks
Turn it backwards, it's better.
I think the back will hurt more.
Haven't felt pain in 34 years
Gary the master of endurance
Snap!!
Hit
He's calm
It doesn't hurt?
No.
As if nothing happened
It really doesn't hurt?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Do it to me, I'm sure it'll really hurt.
Looked like it didn't hurt so everyone wants to try
Do it ~
Really.
Doesn't it hurt?
Snap!!
So why did you want to try that?
Sukjin giving a go at himself
Snap!!
You endure this?
I take blows well, hyungnim.
Doesn't understand the others pain
I just hit myself.
Only if you experience it you'll know the greatness of Gary
Want to try?
Why?
He endured that pain, try it.
Really, Gary is so great.
Snap!!
Look at this.
I told you I'm good at enduring pain.
Even Dual Daggers is suffering
Just
carefree
Gary's the best
Jongkook ...
Let's just focus on what
we were doing before.
Let me hit you.
Come, you're the man.
Mocking
Come on, it'll be quick.
Why should I endure?
Why do I have to take the pain?
MC Muscle doesn't understand
the world of endurance
Why should I endure?
Just do what you're told.
Complains
All of us hyungs did it.
Just do it then.
Complains
You're very nervous aren't you?
Keeps mocking
and mocking
Ah, why is this hyung like this?
Kicks in the air
Last time they kept growling about the MC position
Jaesuk, what do I do with my forehead?
Swollen~
He hit himself and now it's swollen red
Hyung, you're a private.
* The hats of Korean soldiers
has lines to show their rank
Mocks
Showing the rank of
a soldier Two lines
You really are a private.
Pil Seung, Private Ji Sukjin reporting.
Make me a sergeant.
* A sergeant has 3 lines
He gets ranked up to a sergeant with just one more hit
Will you be okay?
Yes, I want to be a sergeant.
Snap!!
At the same time as the
promotion the pain comes
Jongkook, come here.
Don't close your eyes or wink.
Hurry up and do it.
Your hair ...
Why does
that hurt?
Do the scared eyes.
He still feels pain ...
Pain
... although he's been exercising
for more than ten years.
10 years of exercising but the pain is still the same
How can you endure this pain.
Hey, Gary just endured this pain?
Now Gary looks even greater
It's really so weird.
Snap!!
Are you really all right?
Is his eyes
starting to
tear up?
Yes, it's not so bad.
Can't you see I take blows well?
Anyway Gary
34 years old
The master of endurance
Now let's start the game.
3 games of Jongro street
Chopstick Break
How shall we decide who goes first?
Red Team with Dual Daggers goes first
You go first hyung.
Hesitates
So hard to easily slam down
I know how you feel now.
Ouch.
Bang
Red Team
# 1
Joonkyu
Succeeds
Aoh, it hurts your palm.
Looks like it hurts.
Yes, it hurts.
Red Team
# 2
Jongkook
Oh my ...
Slams
The palm pain that comes with the break success
Collapses
He doesn't know how to use his strength.
This game has nothing to do with muscles
Oh, it really hurts.
You have to hit hard.
Red Team
# 3
Victoria
It does no harm to your palm.
It really hurts, so what do
you mean it does no harm?
I'm going to die because of the pain.
Slams
Red Team
# 3
Victoria
Succeeds
Are you okay?
It broke into three pieces
Hey, hang on.
Ah, don't push down.
You scared me
You just told us you're
good at enduring pain.
Isn't he the master of enduring pain...?
I've never endured this kind of pain.
You have to hit hard.
Red Team
# 4
Gary
Arh!
I thought you were the master of endurance?
Puk
Is it ...
broken?
It didn't break ~
No, it's broken.
It's bent instead of being broken
It didn't break completely.
Red Team
# 4
Gary's turn
Fail
Now its our turn.
Are you saying this is a fail?
Give that to me.
So it can't be like this?
Let's put that here as a 'no' sample.
A 'no' sample?
An average age of 38 Risking their life for this
It can't be like this.
You have to do it properly.
Why are Korean
men like this...?
Hyung, fighting.
Jaesuk is going to do
this about 20 times.
The first goer has to do it several times
Yeas, so we have to do well.
Thump
Failure
It didn't break
He couldn't even break it but it still hurts
Hey, it has to hurt somewhere
else in a situation like this.
Hurry up.
The law of pain division?
It has to hurt somewhere else.
It hurts.
Flutters
It really hurts too much.
It means getting hurt again somewhere else
Snap
In total pain
It won't hurt when we do like this.
It hurts too much, it hurts.
Now the chance goes back to Red Team
Oh, my hand.
Victoria, say something to encourage Joonkyu.
Fighting.
Yea ~
Inattention
No, Victoria just said fighting to
you and you are like yeah yeah.
Why are you like that?
Sorry
I honestly didn't hear what
you said, say it again.
Fighting ~
Yeah.
The pain is just for that moment.
Ah, yes ...
The atmosphere changed
completely with Victoria.
Victoria managed to change the atmosphere
Of course.
You ...
What are you really?
Jihyo ...
Jihyo show them a bubbly encouragement
Jihyo, please encourage
us like how Victoria did.
Fighting.
Not like that, say it more bubbly like fighting.
Raise your tone a bit.
Fight ...
Let's just do it next time, next time.
Depressed
Blue Team
Spirit goes down
We needed that, you know
Let's win this thing.
But Red Team is full of spirit
I'll go.
Again
Red Team
# 1
Joonkyu
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Sighs...
Slams
Broken
Dual Daggers
hyungnim
Explodes
Dual Daggers
As if he gone back
Is he really angry because of the pain?
It hurts so much.
Murmurs
I got a bruise.
You were once Dual Daggers.
The mighty Dual Daggers battle with a pair of chopstick
Look at his muscles.
Oppa fighting.
Look at those muscles crack.
Are those vein pipes?
In his arms
Pipes?
He has pipes embedded into his body.
He changes to the left since his right hand is in pain
Don't change hands.
You're not allowed to change hands.
Why are there so many things
that I am not allowed to do?
You can only use your right hand.
Ah, why?
Is this hand not mine?
Are you angry?
It's not that.
Complains
Humans are allowed to play
games with both hands.
The pain only lasts for
that moment, it's alright.
Again
Yeah.
What did Victoria say?
The pain only lasts for that moment.
Quote of the day
Claps
The pain only lasts for that moment.
I was wondering why my hands
hurt when I was clapping now.
Only a few claps and the hand hurts
I was just clapping.
I'll go now.
Read Team
# 2
Jongkook
Let's go.
1, 2, 3 ...
Thud
The pain comes
when the chopstick breaks
It hurts so much.
Red Team
# 3
Victoria
Victory, fighting.
Hyung, excuse me ...
Her name is Victoria Not Victory
Fighting ~
Her name is Victoria, not Victory.
Victoria dari diri doora doo.
Victoria ~
Slams
The pain is for that moment
Red Team succeeds to #3
Didn't that hurt?
Red Team
The master of pain
Gary
Gary ~
The master who is good at enduring pain.
He can't do it.
Thud
Is it broken?
It hurts so much.
Success
It broke completely
Now only HaHa succeeds is left in Red Team
We'll win if I break this?
Tries to cheat
What? Don't try to cheat.
Annoyed
I was trying to break this
with my arm strength.
Don't do that.
Your fingers will be broken
if you can't break this.
Be careful.
Jongkook training the boy's mentality?
Are you dissatisfied with them again?
No, that's not it.
I'm already bruised.
It's better to be bruised than
getting them fractured, right?
Yeah.
What did you just say?
As if HaHa will get punished if he fails
Nothing.
If HaHa succeeds Red Team will win
HaHa-ya.
Oppa fighting.
HaHa-ya ~
Thud
It didn't break
Red Team
Fails
He couldn't do it.
Won't anyone be scary ... scared?
#1 has to go again
With HaHa's failure
the chance goes back to Blue Team
From now on, against your knees.
Knees?
That's easier ~
Kwangsoo, let's start with you.
Oh yeah.
We can change the order, right?
Wait, did you just change the order.
Yes.
No, what are you talking about?
That was dangerous just now.
The game could've gotten boring just now!
The game could've gotten boring just now.
You have to keep the same order
From now on ...
No, same order as before.
How can we change the order when
we’re not allowed to change hands?
Outburst
You're right.
Speechless
Blue Team got it right back
I shouldn't have said
that before, I'm sorry.
Regrets
If I could turn back time ...
Now Jaesuk has to go first again
Go quickly.
1, 2, 3 ...
Now
slamming onto the knee
Jumps
Double pain
The palm + the knee
Who said on the knees would be easier?
The pain ...
We have to divide the pain.
Divide the pain, divide!
No, it hurts.
Blue Team
# 2
Sukjin
It hurts.
Sukjin fighting.
Sukjin-ah ...
Slams
With a sonorous yell
Success
The yell soon turns into a moan
His hand became red
Blue Team
# 3
Jihyo
It's just for once.
Jihyo it's just for once, hit hard.
Jihyo, be funny.
Hard ~
It's only for once.
Ah, so noisy.
Are they trying to break the chopstick with their mouths?
1, 2, 3 ...
Slams
An unexpected success by Jihyo
Blue Team
# 4
Lee Joon
Joon, you can do it.
Relaxed
Like this?
Blue Team has two more to go
Thud
How
can
it
be
Shocked
Blue Team
Fails
Anxious Red Team is back in the game
I really hit hard though.
Anxious
Kwangsoo, haven't even tried it yet.
Shy Kwangsoo didn't get a chance
I'll be quick.
Read Team goes for the knee for the first time
Really.
We're going to speed up for this game.
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
Sigh...
Do I have to do it again?
Snap
Cry
Look at this.
but the pain is worse
Looked as if it was easier
I can't even clap like this.
No ...
Whines
I can't do this.
Red Team
# 2
Jongkook
Hard ...
Cries
3, 2, 1.
Is he going to collapse if
he has to do it once more?
Hit hard.
Slams
Victoria ~
Red Team
# 3
Victoria
Do you need my knee?
It'll break if you hit hard.
3, 2, 1.
Hard like that.
Easily
succeeds
They can't succeed.
Anxious
Fighting ~
Red Team
# 4
Gary
Is he really the master of endurance?
3, 2, 1, go.
Snaps
Enduring the pain(?) and breaking it
Red Team
Has only HaHa left
HaHa-ya ~
These are going to fly if you fail.
Do you know who I am?
I am
Jongro's
Dual Chopsticks
Red Team wins if HaHa succeeds
It will hurt like hell.
As hard as he can
I can't do
it anymore
Thud
Crack
Red Team
All of them succeeds
3 games of Jongro street
(1) Chopstick Break
Red Team wins
I told you I can do it.
Of course.
I didn't even
get to try
What's this?
What's the second game?
Clothes peg tug of war.
(2) Peg tug of war
Clip the peg onto your faces and pull.
The team who gets rid of the pegs from
the opposing team's the fastest wins.
Gary will be good at this, since
he is the master of endurance.
Each member gets a peg each
Put a peg on you like this.
What strategy shall we have?
I'll clip it on my mouth.
Let's not copy each other.
Yes, we can't put the peg
where some else has put it.
Stretches
Ah, don't pull it already.
Sorry.
Clipping the pegs where they feel strongest
I think anyone can.
Big Nose clips it on his nose as expected
Start, ready ... go.
Pegs tug of war
The team that pulls the other's
pegs off
wins
Wait ~
Pull!
Tight
It's hard to tell who'll win
Get together ~
Together
Snaps
One came off from Jaesuk's protruded mouth
Blue Team
Has 4 pegs left
Come this way this way.
Me ~
Jihyo's getting unstable as they move
Jihyo ...
Not allowed to
cross the line
If they cross the line they're out
Tang!!
Jihyo's peg and
Joon - Kwangsoo also unclipped
Then...
The remaining one is ...
Here
Doesn't matter where the other pegs have gone
The peg on Big Nose is still
unmovable
This  is...
the infamous power of Big Nose
1:5 face-to-face competition Winner is?
Ping!!
Piong~
Pegs tug of war
Red Team
Wins
Your nose is the greatest.
Excuse me, Big Nose hyung ...
Are you okay?
Why are you crying?
I just thought of a sad memory.
Let's do 2 against 2.
2nd round 2:2 match
One man and one woman.
One man and one woman from each team
Do you want to go, Big Nose hyung?
Blue Team
Representatives
Big Nose
Sukjin
Jihyo
Red Team
Representatives
Pain master
Gary
Victoria
Big Nose clips it on the nose
That place must be good.
Gary clips both his nose and lips
Gary, you're so handsome.
Like a robot that feels no pain
If Red Team wins this game they win
the whole '3 games of Jongro street'
Don't stretch it.
Ready ...
Your facial expressions already
tell us you are going to lose.
Still calm
I'm drooling, let's go quickly.
Ready, go.
Don't go yet.
Looking for each team's strategies
We have to stick together.
Stretches tight
Pay attention to
his facial expression
Jihyo's face is tightly stretched
Oppa ...
Oppa, wait a sec ...
Ya, don't touch it.
Oh~
Jihyo's personality gets revealed
Calm
The elastic band has been stretched so long
Tang~
Here too
Tang
One's been unclipped from each team
Ta
Tak!
Blue Team
Pegs fall one by one
We can win
Then how many pegs are left for Blue Team?
Again!!
It's Big Nose again
What is
that nose?
The one on the nose stays regardless
There's still chance in a 1:2 match
Trust...
me!!
Piyong~
Red Team
Wins
Aigoo
My nose...
3 games of Jongro street
Red Team
By winning 2 games
Wins
Really ...
Wait, Sukjin's boogers just came out.
I thought it was a fossil.
Ah Big Nose, really.
His boogers are bigger than average, ﻿since
he has a bigger nose than everyone else.
Of course that's because his nose is big...(?)
Gasp...
What did you put inside your nostrils?
Red Team gets the
first Running Ball
Next will be the race.
Next mission
Winners get 2 balls Hide-n-seek
Yes ~
Blue Team has to hide and ...
... Red Team will search and catch them.
Yes ~
The time limit is one hour.
Everyone in the hiding
team will get a phone.
The handphones come with preset alarms.
When the alarm sounds
their hiding position will be discovered
It's like a catching game.
The alarm will reveal their hiding spots.
If the
Blue Team
has at least 1 member uncaught
they'll win
Just like in a catching game.
Are we going to film Die Hard 3 today?
From now on
Die Hard 3 special(?) will begin
The time is now 11:44 PM.
The other team will go
into hiding at 11:50 PM.
You'll start from here at 12:00 AM.
Yes.
But there's a catch.
There's a condition that
applies to both teams.
You're not allowed to run
in the historical museum.
Speed walk?
Will there be sirens?
* Siren and speed walk has similar pronunciations
It's referring to speed walk.
Korean is hard~
Victoria misheard the word
In speed walking you can't lift your foot
before the other foot touches the ground.
It's not necessary to
go by the rules here.
We don't have to go by the rules.
Isn't it?
You are a bit disappointed, right?
Hyung, you just got told off.
If the other juniors say something, I'll rebuke.
The well-know Dual Daggers being told off
by Jongkook
Just now your glare at me is
the same as you did to HaHa.
Right ~
Red Team turned into Jongkook and the three kids
The glare is totally the same.
Except he's using honorifics.
Only with honorifics, but
his stare is the same.
I'm an actor, I can
tell from your eyes.
Amazing, you can tell from my eyes.
Meanwhile
At Gyeonghuigung Palace Blue Team is getting ready
Connected to the Museum of History
Gyeonghuigung Palace
Close to 400 years of history
One of the 5 biggest palaces in Seoul
Again in the center of the city
A huge hide-n-seek inside Gyeonghuigung Palace
What is this?
The alarm device for the Blue Team
They mentioned this earlier.
This alarm, we can't touch it.
They put it in a case ...
The phone is in a box to prevent
them from setting off the alarm
... can't do anything about the alarm.
Let's put on the devices.
Please help me.
When will it ring?
They can't predict when the alarm will sound
No idea.
You don't know?
They improve everyday.
The other team will start at 12,
and now it is already 11:50 PM.
If the sound is high,
doing this is useless
Shocked!
Alarm testing
They can't turn off the alarm
Is this the starting alert?
Can't turn it off.
The alarm is Beethoven's symphony no 9
<Choral>
What is this alarm?
Christmas carol?
It was an important theme song
in the movie Die Hard
The sound is so loud.
Let's split into two teams.
Split into two teams.
Gyeonghuigung palace and
the Museum Team
We must persevere, everyone fighting.
Kwangsoo & Jaesuk
Decides to hide in the palace
Kwangsoo ...
Yes?
Let's make a turn.
This palace is so huge.
But in this widespread palace...
But if we go into a dead
end path, we'll be dead.
They have not begun, right?
Eventually...
Going to the back of the palace
Gyeonghuigung Palace
Kwangsoo goes to the back near the wall
Can you see me?
Can't see you, let's hide here.
Silence
Yooruce Willis also found a place to hide
The problem is...
Can you film?
Can't see...
Then, no choice.
Is there a light on the phone?
Can you lend me?
I didn't bring my handphone.
Can you see me?
Gasp!
Can you film now?
Can film now, but ...
But the image looks like a ghost?
So why hide in such a dark spot
I become a ghost.
What should I do?
Gyeonghuigung Palace
Jaesuk
Kwangsoo
Alright ~
Ahh, this is nerve-wrecking.
Hide-n-seek starts
There is a path here.
This is the only path to the palace.
The only path between the
museum and the palace
Only one way.
Let's split up and search.
Red Team also decides to split
You guys go back.
Inside the museum: Joonkyu HaHa Victoria
The palace: Jongkook Gary
So spacious.
So huge.
The palace puts them at loss
Look ~
This place is so huge, how to find them?
Red Team
Two chasers entering the palace
My stomach hurts.
When tense, his stomach always hurts
At this time...!
Jongkook and Gary is approaching
Jaesuk's and Kwangsoo's hiding place
Jongkook moves towards the place ...
... where Jaesuk is
Where is Kwangsoo?
There's only a wall in between
Yooruce Willis
Will he meet his end like this?
No one here?
There is nothing here.
Lucky Yooruce Willis narrowly
escapes danger
But ...
It's the alarm
Noisy alarm that breaks the silence
Remaining time
Definitely...
there was
sound...?
With an animal's instinct
did the Muscular pursuer...
indeed?
What's the situation now,
did the alarm go off?
Didn't hear it...
What a shock.
During 20 seconds of the alarm
Yooruce tasted hell
Really, I thought I'd lose my stomach.
What's ﻿the interval for each alarm?
Not knowing when it'll ring the alarm bring more fear
I thought I was going to die.
And it's going to ring again.
On the other side Lee Joon escapes
the place where the alarm went off
Where?
Red Team
Victoria spotted him
First floor ~
Blue Team
Lee Joon shook off everyone
Vanished
But ...
Is there someone who
has Joon in their range?
Ignoring the need to be filmed
Lee Joon vanished from his VJ
Joon ~
Where is he...?
Going to the museum
will be a better option.
But Muscular Pursuer is blocking
the way to the museum
Let's wait and see.
There'll be some noisy.
At least once.
Watching for a chance and going forward
Yooruce Willis
But...!
The alarm sounded a second time
Flinch
Somewhere
Jihyo who's hidden also
gets a shock
Restless
But Big Nose is in the corridor
Remaining time
Joon's whereabouts
is still unknown
Heard it this time...!
Definitely
somewhere here
Trusting his hearing...
Muscular Pursuer goes in the direction of the sound
Jaesuk's hiding place
Jongkook is there ~
Jongkook
Jongkook went up there.
Instinct of a hide-and-seek pro
There's only his moment to escape from here
A desperate escape Yooruce Willis
Ooh!!
Jumping with more skill(?)
than a grasshopper
Escaping faster than anyone
at the speed of light
As expected from the hide-n-seek founder
Yooruce Willis
Jaesuk escaped from Jongkook
And...
Joon ... !
Joon's whereabouts is still a mystery
Joon.
You have filming to get on with.
Joon is here
Revealing his face on camera after 20 minutes passed
His secret hiding place will soon
be revealed
Variety newcomer in hiding again without a VJ
At this moment
Gary came from the palace to the museum
Remaining time
Lee Joon's
hiding place
Third alarm sounded
Ugh!
Alarm sound from the corridor stairs
Really unlucky
Just came on screen and ...
Hey ...
Just met his lost VJ
immediately had to escape
After hearing the alarm
Joonkyu and HaHa are in action too
Joon took off deep into the corridor
Dead end!!
Meanwhile
HaHa saw Sukjin
Blocked by Joonkyu while escaping
Sukjin
Agile Lee Joon is also
Where did you hide before?
I was hiding here at first ...
... but it was too scary, so I came out.
Spent...
20 minutes here...?
Walking towards the museum
Yooruce Willis
Analyzing the situation inside just like a hide-n-seek pro
They already caught Sukjin.
He saw me ~
Making an u-turn back to Gyeonghuigung
Cat's eye Victoria is going after Jaesuk
Remaining time
Gary joined the hunt for Jaesuk
Just then
Hearing the alarm from somewhere close
I saw him.
Victoria approaching Jaesuk
Why does the alarm ring at this time?
Ah, it's Victoria.
Position exposed because of the alarm
Hey you, there you are.
Yooruce Willis in a big crisis
... there you are.
Victoria's laughing~
Chase him in to there.
Can't end Die Hard like this
Dong Hoon ...
Nearby HaHa got into action immediately
The trapped grasshopper
Many crises...
Plenty of despair
Earning a name by overcoming them
Hide-and-seek(er)
Yooruce Willis
But...
Jaesuk's VJ:
Gasp...
No divine protection today
Blue Team
Jaesuk
Rather than being caught
by Kim Jongkook ...
Proudly
... it's better to be caught by HaHa.
A silly one-sided completion Jongkook doesn't know about
Only regarded by Jaesuk
I want to thank all my Die Hard fans
who supported me all this time.
Yooruce Willis will end just line this.
Forgive me.
A heroic curtain call for
Yooruce Willis the star of Die Hard
But next week
An upgraded Yooruce Willis will be reborn
At this time
Kwangsoo ...
Time remaining
Jongkook still wandering around
Feels like death
The alarm sounded again at this moment
This time the sound is very clear
More realistic as compared to Yooruce Willis.
Alarm sounded before the last 5 minutes
Hoping that no one heard ...
But...
Jongkook accurately pinpointed the location
Immediately
Beast
Grrwarr~
Kwangsoo's dying escape attempt
A successful narrow escape?
Kwangsoo suddenly disappeared into thin air
Hey, you're not allowed to climb over.
Hey ..
Jongkook ..
Hiding behind the bushes once again
I won't cross over because it's cheating.
But I got it.
Kwangsoo
put up a good fight but
Ah really, what a waste.
With this Creation of the fourth victim
Remaining time
Who is left?
Remaining Blue Team members
Only Jihyo's left
Only one.
Only one?
Wah, Jihyo please.
Blue Team's only hope
Jihyo's hiding place is
A corner in the 3rd floor gallery
50 minutes earlier...
Entered the quiet place
No one will find out after covering it with a sign
Hide~
Remaining time
Red Team's beginning to get anxious
There's only about 2 minutes left.
Song Jihyo ~
Red Team
Only need to catch one more to win
Discovered the strange hole
He is ...
approaching ...
Remaining time
Alarm sounded for the end of the game
Hide-and-seek game
ended
An hour passed
Today's hero
Jihyo
Song Jihyo ~
Where were you?
Blue Team got 2 Running Man Balls
Song Jihyo ~
A leisurely cup of tea.
Mission 3
A leisurely cup of tea
We‘re now inside Gyeonghuigung Palace.
The place filled with antique atmosphere
This place was used to
film dramas and movies
Gyeonhuigung Palace's hall Inside Sungjeongjeon Hall
Are these seats where the
ministers sat to the left and right?
No.
Oh, yes of course.
It looks like your body is already
sore from fatigue, Joonkyu hyung.
I've never been in a place like this before.
Ah, really?
I've filmed a lot of period films, but
I have never come inside like this.
I was always outside riding horses.
He always played a general.
Because you have had
many roles as a general.
Charisma
Joonkyu the warrior outside the palace
That's right ~
All the way out there
You didn't know, right?
Joonkyu got scolded twice by Jongkook.
The Warrior Charisma that fell to Jongkook
Why?
Please don't be angry hyung.
It wasn't scolding.
Drink and relax, hyung.
That's because ...
He talked politely, but his eyes were like
when he talked to the younger ones ...
The words were polite but...
... treating me with disdain.
the look reprimanded me
And when we were running,
you said "Hey you" to me, right?
* In Korean culture it's considered very rude
to say "Hey you (ya)" to an older person.
Sorry.
... "Hey you".
I'm sorry.
Who ~
Who said that?
He was running toward me
and shouted "Hey you ..."
After the hectic hide-n-seek comes
the unending reports
Hey you, stop right there.
Hearing "Hey you" from a dongseang
Stop right there.
He said "Hey you" to me.
I'm extremely sorry, hyungnim.
Even under the circumstances,
what's with "Hey you"?
I thought Jongkook was behind me, sorry.
Reassuring
Red Team's physical pillar and support
It's already past two ...
That is why we're having
this a leisurely cup of tea.
It's past 2 at night
Everyone ...
This is exactly the time you feel
fatigue from running around.
Yeah ~
You feel very tired.
I'm curious about this.
The fact that this is set
up makes me nervous.
* Ssanghwacha = A herbal remedy drink
To enhance their strange ssanghwacha has been prepared
Oh, this?
Because we have come to
the Museum of History ...
We are going to learn
about the members' history?
Learning about the members past
Our history?
How?
People sent in videos of your past.
Watching videos of their past
and then answering questions
Oh yeah, does it mean we will get to
see this from Jongkook's Turbo days?
Past shocking videos released to the public
Yes.
It will be fun.
When there's a question ...
Anticipating
... the team who can't answer will
drink ssanghwacha as punishment.
... with an egg added to it.
Are you talking about the yolk?
Concerned
He's at it again.
The cholesterol.
There's someone here who
plans to live for 200 years.
Jongkook's agitated when he hears about yolk
He plans to live for 200 years
The yolk is really high in cholesterol.
What's so bad about
having Yolk once?
I can't do yolk.
Is there a ball after this too?
The team who finish the drinks
first will win 2 Running Balls.
Can we receive a ball?
Ball? Yes, there'll be a ball.
There is.
Give us the first question.
Straight to the questions?
It'll be Jaesuk.
The protagonist of the first video is?
If you look at my past, it would
be 'Fierce fight, Running sun...'.
Ah, we must view it.
The comedian with 20 years of experience
National MC Yoo Jaesuk
Whoa that's so much more than I was.
'Fierce fight Running Sunday'
1991.
* The screen says 1992, but the members are saying 1991.
Frustration
This, really ...
1991 ~
If I give up here, I'll give up comedy.
Comedian Yoo Jaesuk
With his hands and feet shriveling
Newcomer Yoo Jaesuk's comment
Yoo Jaesuk ~
I love you.
I will give up comedy.
Hila...
...rious
A new face in comedy ...
How did they find that?
Yoo Jaesuk, aja.
Newcomer Jaesuk's challenge is?
Yes, on the backside.
He needs to stick like a spider, but...
On the backside.
Slide~
I didn't push you.
I knew you'd be like that.
At the time, 28
fresh Kim Kookjin
I'm going to try again next time.
1992 'Comedy Everything in the World'
<Diary of Returning to the Farm>
Wow, 'Diary of Returning to the Farm'.
Father-in-law Kim Haklae's ill-
treated foolish son-in law role
Putting your hair like that in
a side bridge was out of style.
I was the height of fashion back then.
Secretly eating chicken when
his father-in-law enters
Ugh!
Brushing his teeth with a drumstick?
Laughter
I thought up great things back then.
Even sunbae Kim Haklae
thought it was funny
Brushing your teeth?
Continuously drumstick toothbrush
Yes, I'm brushing my teeth sir.
Ah, that was funny.
It's been twenty years.
You watch you old self with such fun.
Continuing Next video is?
Ah, this is ...
Is it okay to just film?
Why are you looking in the mirror
when there's nothing to see?
2000 'Beautiful TV Face'
'Self Camera'
Yoo Jaesuk's self camera
'10 years ago'...
This is self camera.
Yes, self camera.
A popular program due to being able
to see an honest side of celebrities
Oh, your home.
Right, this used to exist.
Yoo Jaesuk's image 10 years ago?
10 years ...
"Why in the world do you not appear
on TV when you are a celebrity?"
I know it was said as a joke, but ...
... to me each and every word wounded ﻿
me deep in my heart when I got home.
Sadness from 10 years
of continuous obscurity...
These are awards I won while
in the entertainment business.
The trophies won in 10 years of broadcasting
This one is a ...
... trophy from a talk program
that Seo Saewon hosts.
And this one ...
... ﻿is something they gave out at
the end of the year for commemoration.
With only two trophies
his self 10 years ago...
Always modest ...
... ﻿and always the way I am just now.
Trying hard, being honest and sincere.
I will work hard to show that self to you.
The 10 years he worked hard
to keep that promise
His friends who know that feeling
also feel choked up
But ...
What are you doing?
Is that Jaesuk?
Who is that?
That's me.
Why did you take your shirt off?
He took what off?
Gasp!
Exposing
Are you telling us that
it was broadcasted?
Why is he like that?
That was because ...
What are you doing?
Embarrassing
Actually ...
Why is he like that? He must be crazy?
Why is he like that?
National MC's
shocking past image
Why is he like that?
His nipples are way too low.
Why did you take your shirt off
That that was for showing an
honest side of myself, you see.
Would've been a disaster if he wanted to be even more honest
What's honest about that?
Why are you showing this?
Why film your chest like that?
My face is getting all red, Jaesuk.
Embarrassed
Really ...
Why is he like that?
An image that brings up a fist
Why are you saying stuff like that?
What is it this time...?
What is this? Whoaaa ...
Why?
What are you doing?
What is this?
What in the world...
What is going on?
Good gracious!
What is that?
Victoria ....
On probation
What are you doing there?
Are you saying that was
broadcasted back then?
I must have been crazy.
Starting now
The question video 2001 Lee Honglyul show
Ah, Lee Honglyul show.
Oh-Ja time.
Only answer in five syllables
At that time very popular 'Oh-Ja time'
Let's practice, what
is your blood type?
I am an O type.
That's how you do it.
Have you ever been dumped?
Of course I have been.
Me too, many times.
What was the reason?
First question
Why was Jaesuk dumped (in 5 syllables)?
Answer.
Can I get it correct?
Yes.
For my ugliness.
For my ugliness
That's not it.
Answer.
Wrong
Cause my lips protrude.
Cause my lips protrude
For your reference ...
Wrong
That time I was slightly, just
slightly, a bit, you know ...
Wit ~
It was when I had some wit.
I don't remember what it was, but
I'm sure it must have been funny.
Confident
What's up with your expression?
Answer.
Ain't it obvious?
* Sukjin is using internet lingo, trying to sound cute.
Internet slang that wasn't used back then
What are you saying?
That time that wasn't ...
Ain't it obvious?
That didn't exist back then.
Does it have to do with looks?
Answer ~
That side first.
The chance to answer goes to Sukjin
Because of my face.
Because of my face
Blue Team
Success
Because of my face.
That's that, but why did you
do that with the self camera?
Anyway
Must talk about the embarrassing 'Self Camera'
Why did you do that?
That's not even honest,
it was just plain weird.
What were you showing us
with the camera in the front?
I think that should
have been edited out.
A past he wants to keep hidden
Edit what? You were
the one with your chest.
This is the first time I have been
embarrassed to say I know you.
That's true.
And your boxers weren't even nice.
You had striped boxers.
At least they were shorts
That was the problem, I
should have worn briefs.
Joonkyu ...
Why do I need to throw this?
Didn't answer the question
Red Team's
punishment
It's okay, please throw it.
It'll let us know how many yolks to add.
Adding as many eggs
as the dice shows
One ~
One.
And Red Team's amount is?
Five.
Five
Five ~
Add 5 egg yolks
Can't even say anything to Joonkyu
Sorry
You're only putting in the yolks?
Winning team separates the yolks leisurely
Not the whites?
Of course.
Do you know how to sift it?
What?
Like this from, left to right.
Clumsy
I know how to.
Without popping it.
Worried
What to do?
Five yolks
Adding
Jongkook, four ...
The whites ...
Please sift out a lot of the whites.
... five, yes.
Full with nutritious egg yolk~
Why are you popping them?!
That was five, right?
This is the first time I have
been so happy cracking eggs.
Three, okay ...
... this is four
Also dropped in Joonkyu's cup
... this is five.
Victoria, this is three, right?
Now putting eggs in Victoria's cup
Yes.
Oops.
But even added the shell
Oh oppa ...
What did you do?
As it's not settled
I'm sorry, please switch.
Changing with Gary's cup
What is this?
Four ...
Always a pushover to Jaesuk Gary
That's it, I think we're done.
Red Team
Adding 5 yolks
Completed
Let's continue, quickly.
So that team may also ... ?
Yes.
It's the next question.
Next question.
The protagonist of next video is?
I can't believe we didn't get that.
Let's view it.
HaHa ~
All-around entertainer
HaHa
What's this?
Ah, this ...
Jikiri?
What's this?
HaHa's debut group 'Jikiri'
Jikiri?
A fresh newcomer singer's look
When is this from?
Donghoon when was this?
Only looking at the camera
The rookie HaHa
When was this?
What year was this?
When is this?
2001?
It's 2001, but it is this unsophisticated?
It's the 21st century.
This is after 2000 but why is
it so unsophisticated HaHa.
It was filmed 4 years before then.
Filmed 4 years before
A music video with a long story(?)
Oh, really?
Oh, Gary.
This time it's Gary
Honey Family time
How tacky ~
Preposterous hair style
Scream
But it's okay.
Behind, there's Gil hyung.
Looks like he's mad about something Gil Seongjun
Gary, you were, then ...
You looked better then.
I mean, Gary, you ...
Tranquil
Charisma
Now Jongkook.
We must view this.
Debut 16 years ago
Jongkook
Turbo, Heidi, Tak Jaehoon, please come out.
'Jump Champ' introducing newcomers
At 20 Baby-faced Jongkook
Everyone is cracking up
Automatically clapping
Hey, I'm Kim Jungjam from Turbo.
And I'm Kim Jongkook.
And the person beside you?
He used to wear that kind of clothes.
Hello, I'm Heidi.
Picking at their clothes
My clothes look like hanbok.
Stage of newcomer Turbo
'My childhood dream'
Oh my gosh.
Dance moves
with restraint
Oh my gosh.
20 years old
Muscle Jongkook's younger self
You dance well, Jongkook.
I'm going crazy.
Hello? Yes, I was paged...?
1995 <Good Friends>
'Love Introduction'
Yes, this is Kim Junseong.
You got my message?
Nervous
Ah, yes.
That's Jongkook's voice.
"﻿I'm Kim Junseong".
But what's this?
I'm Kim Junseong.
Kim Jongkook (playing Kim Junseoung)
Cute
Awkward acting
It's acting ~
Standing up at his acting
Young acting You can feel the freshness of a newbie
Kim Jongkook (playing Kim Junseoung)
Jongkook's face became red
I can't believe I'm acting.
Starting now The question video
It's the question.
Nice to meet you, please
introduce yourselves.
Super Sunday
Hey, I'm Turbo's Kim Jungnam.
Are my pants hanbok?
I'm ﻿Kim Jongkook.
Turbo, your wardrobe is ...
What is this?
To Lee Youngja's eyes
weird costumes
What's wrong with it?
What happened here? Let us know!
Yes ...
Since you were a fashion
model, Park Yeonseon ...
The MC used to be a fashion model
... ﻿please appraise Turbo's wardrobe for us.
Second question
Instead of the MC, what was Jongkook's answer?
Wardrobe appraisal?
Instead of the MC, what did Jongkook say?
At that time ...
... I was very skilled at speaking in public.
You don't remember, right?
I have no clue.
He doesn't remember the answer himself
Answer ~
We'll wear it next year?
Wrong
Answer.
This is what I'm going to
take after my wedding.
If I could say that, then
I would have been an MC.
Wrong
That skilled answer is MC level
Why aren't we answering?
Answer.
It's an Arabian concept.
Wrong
It's a my neighborhood concept.
But seems to be close
It must be similar.
But this wasn't when Jongkook
was skilled at talking in public.
Answer ~
It's a oppa I know concept.
They went "Oh".
I got it.
So close but
Wrong
Answer.
"﻿Oppa I know".
Getting closer to the answer
It's my village concept.
Answer.
It's something similar.
Wrong
It's a village oppa concept.
Correct
We were almost toast.
Extremely fortunate
Jihyo, you can throw it.
The team who didn't answer throws the dice
What is Blue Team's yolk amount?
Four ~
Broad smile
You seem really happy about this.
Yes ...
Who?
I'm only happy that we
got the answer correct.
Spontaneously laughing when thinking
of adding yolk to their cups
This time
Red Team's
egg yolk sorting
Here, Joon one ...
Why is this one overflowing with egg white?
Since it's someone else's cup Working with enthusiasm
One is just as much as two.
Here this one is all done.
Kwangsoo, this one ...
4 yolks per person
I hope it's delicious.
This is like egg gruel.
Mixing the 4 egg yolks well
Oh, this is bad.
Thinking about drinking it brings worries
The hand-wipes are ...
This is good for the body.
Of course.
Definitely looks like it'll be good for the body
Looks like it'll be good for the body.
No hand-wipes?
The last question, let's view it.
It's Joonkyu hyung.
Actor Park Joonhyu
What will it be?
There'll be a way to defeat them.
Charismatic actor
Kim Boseong
Joonkyu 27 years
old at that time
We mustn't forget that and work as one.
Movie 'The Man of All of New Korea'
Yes, you're right.
Since it's a movie from 20 years ago Awkward dialog
Yes, sir.
Is that you, hyung?
What's this?
20 years ago
Joonkyu's unfamiliar image
You look very young.
At that time, I used to
wear heavy make-up.
Ah, I can't watch this.
Continuing with Jihyo's past video?
Jihyo ...
Shocked
5 years ago
Jihyo as a hamburger CF model
This is you, Jihyo?
Is that really you?
You're so pretty.
So pretty.
Look at the eye.
You're so pretty.
Areum says she can't
go on our class trip.
Kwangsoo's debut CF
You ...
This is you?
Areum, let's go together ~
He left a strong impression immediately from one CF
You were Areum.
Abashed timid Kwangsoo
The 'Tech School, Areum' commercial.
I knew of that.
With their past they can learn
more about each other
It was a popular commercial.
Yeah it was.
But I didn't give any material.
What will be Big Nose's past?
I'm Ji Sukjin and I'd like to enter
the SBS MC and Reporter audition.
Shown to the public for the first time
Sukjin's MC debut audition video
In the archives for 17 years
The MC contest?
I would like to audition because
I am very interested in ...
The SBS MC contest.
SBS MC selection audition
Really.
... the work of an MC and a reporter.
Tense because it is an audition
At the time 26 years old Sukjin
And uhm, MC or reporter ... who knows?
To do this kind of work ...
Who knows?
Immediately starts to nitpick
Jongkook
Buttery then and now ...
I also like to sin in a lot.
You know about 'All for One', yes?
It is a song that was number
one on the Billboard charts ...
... for about 10 weeks, "I Swear".
I like this song a lot, would
you like to hear a little bit?
♪ ﻿I swear ... ♪
♪ ﻿... by the moon and the stars. ♪
Oh my god
The 'I Swear~' that spreads through the palace
Funny no matter how
many times you look at it
He reminds me of me ~
Please read ...
Going to read the report he prepared
Hello, this is Ji Sukjin.
Immediately in a cheerful mode
I'm here at Noryangjin Fish Market.
Why are you holding your lips like that?
Hello, this is Ji Sukjin.
Why are your lips like that?
This is so funny.
To show you how fresh
this fish is, I will touch it.
Oh, look ...
Awkward
Hilarious
Oh look, it's still jumping around.
Laughing and being alarmed at himself
like an earnest MC applicant
If you come here ...
... you can buy this kind of
fresh fish at a cheap price.
This was Ji Sukjin at
Noryangjin Fish Market.
This is hilarious.
Judge
What does others say about
your broadcasting style?
Third question
What's Sukjin's answer to the question
about his broadcasting style?
What do they think?
What?
How embarrassing.
Shall we try to touch it?
Immediately
following
Hyung, please sing "I Swear" for us.
The topic of conversation 'I Swear~'
Why did your voice ...
And your lips ...
Why were your lips doing this?
The point is
on the lips
I think it was because he
was trying to keep smiling.
Too busy making fun of Sukjin to answer the question
I was trying to smile,
but I was so nervous.
My saliva dried out, I think my
lips just shriveled up inwards.
You were really funny.
Completely tense aspiring MC
When was this hyung?
That's ... 93.
1993 ~
1993 SBS MC contest video footage
This is the first time I'm seeing that video.
First time Sukjin watch this video
That wasn't aired, was it?
Video that SBS had stored for auditions
That's an unaired video.
Finally! Seeing the light by giving us many laughs
That wasn't broadcasted.
It makes me feel good.
What could you have said?
Do you remember?
But they have to get the question right
I don't remember.
Answer.
"Who knows."
Wrong
Answer-
They say I'm like a pro.
Answer.
Wrong
They say I'm fresh.
Answer.
American style.
Wrong
Answer.
They say I should be an anchor.
Wrong
What could you have said?
I think it would have
been very brazen.
In total ___
Like an ________
Hint
In total they say I'm OO
Answer.
In total, they say I'm easy on the eyes.
Wrong
Aish ...
In total, they say that
I'm too good for this.
It probably wasn't an amazing reply.
In total ...
It must have been something ...
... I said to look good, so I could get picked.
Must have been something like that.
Answer.
He didn't say anything and just did this.
He must have said something.
Answer.
In total, they say I'm funny.
Hyung, tell us too.
Answer, in total they say I'm tidy.
Correct
Celebratory feeling
Again getting egg yolks~
In total, they say that I'm tidy.
Tidy broadcast(?)
Or so they say.
Red Team
The amount of yolk they have to add is?
Three ~
3 added
Jongkook is eating his life's
worth of egg yolks today.
He probably has never eaten
this many in his whole life.
Add 3 to the Red Team 8 in total
I really can't drink this.
How do we do this?
Just drink.
What'll we do?
Why do I feel like mine has more?
It's because it's all mixed.
A leisurely cup
Add a full cup of water and the
team who drinks the fastest wins
I have a lot too.
What will I do?
Oh, it's cooking inside.
Jongkook, yours is orange juice.
Egg yolk juice?
What happened to it?
Joonkyu, yours looks like a coffee latte.
Look at mine, this looks like a ...
Creamy yolk latte?
I really can't drink this.
Taste of death
I can't drink this
You can drink it.
The team who starts is at a disadvantage.
We're at a disadvantage.
4 egg yolks
Blue Team's also adding water
Common sense says that egg
whites have more protein ...
... but it's actually the yolks
who has more protein.
Since they have less yolk than Red Team they add more water
Really?
It's so hot, how am I
supposed to drink this?
It's too hot.
This is good for the body.
Hypnosis
Good for the body
Let's try to win this!
Fighting ~
Drink as a relay
The team that drinks faster
wins
Ready ... go.
Jaesuk
Jongkook
1st from Red Team
1st from Blue Team
It's hot.
Hot?
Because there's less yolk
more hot water was added
Why are you so slow?
Less water so it isn't hot
Jaesuk, hurry up and drink.
Hey ~
Hot.
You can't spill.
It's so hot.
We have to win.
I understand, but we have to win.
No matter how hot it is must drink to win
Hot.
It's hot even for me.
Jumping up and down like crazy~
Hyung ...
It's hot
Just a little bit more
It's delicious, but it's too hot.
So hot.
So it is delicious?
Jongkook, hurry.
Oppa, drink quickly.
This really ...
* Lyrics from a song by Park Hyunbin
Ah it's so hot so hot
My heart's on fire
because of you
Even mine is hot.
Hyung ...
Became a hot man unlike himself
Fireworks Jaesuk
3 set
Okay, Joonkyu hyungnim.
Silently one shot
Jaesuk
Joonkyu
I, really ...
Strong yolk taste
Ah~Oh
Hurry up and drink it.
I feel like I'm eating lava.
Lava ssanghwacha
Just pour it over your head.
Hurry up.
Finally
Jaesuk finished
Hurry up.
Continue with Sukjin
Start
Was hard on Jaesuk
What about himself?
As soon as it touches his lips
Jump
We have the advantage.
An advantage.
You guys, start trying to cool it down.
A hotness that makes his eyes pop out
Hey, we ...
Meanwhile
Joonkyu finished
But really, it's too hot.
2nd blue member
Sukjin
3rd red member
Victoria
That is because you're
trying to drink too fast.
Victoria drinks it well
I feel like I'm eating a stew.
... a spicy stew.
Drink quickly.
Wow, Victoria's no joke.
Victoria finished in one shot
How'd you drink it so fast?
Can't we share?
I feel bad starting early, hurry.
Red Team
4th player Gary is leisurely ...
You try it, you scoundrel.
We're lucky that we had a lot of eggs.
It's really hot.
We shouldn't have answered
right and gotten more yolk.
That's what I'm saying.
What's this?
We answered right, but
we're at a disadvantage.
That's the charm of Running Man.
Finally
Sukjin finishes
Jihyo, just try to drink it.
Bottoms up.
Don't stop, bottoms up.
Of course ...
The heat that can't be suppressed
Ah, Beogeo girl.
Jihyo, don't you want to go home?
This isn't an act.
It's not an act.
But it looks delicious.
Good~
It's delicious.
Serene Gary waits for her
It's not impossible to drink.
It's delicious.
I need to eat like 30,000 ice cubes.
Jihyo no need to hurry, I'll wait,
It's really is a cup of tea relaxation for you.
You guys, cool your drinks.
A true leisurely cup of tea
Torment from a cup of tea
Are you okay?
She drank it all.
Shake, quickly.
Prancing from the heart
Jihyo is really cute.
Drink ~
Jihyo finished
Really if this wasn't that hot.
Blue Team's 4th member
Kwangsoo
Red Team's 4th member
Gary
If this wasn't that hot.
Kwangsoo can drink this well?
Undoubtedly
Kwangsoo, just a bit more.
Gary with his 8 yolk ssanghwacha
It's like that even though you cooled it down?
Lava ssanghwacha
Also too hot for Kwangsoo
Wow, there’s still steam.
It's because you have less yolk ...
... so you have more hot water instead.
Hot
Torment
Quickly, we can win-
We can win.
Evenly matched
Oppa, quick.
Right now
Gary can't be tranquil
Gary can't drink this.
Hurry up.
Hot ~
You're at similar levels.
Kwangsoo, drink faster.
A heated look
Kwangsoo ~
Hey, he really ...
Jihyo is
pinching
But at this time
Gary finishes
Lastly HaHa starts but ...
Oh my god~
The child HaHa can't drink it
It's over, Kwangsoo.
This is our chance
Only a little more and we win.
Kwangsoo ...
Drink faster.
With Jihyo's help(?)
It's delicious ~
Kwangsoo finishes
That's right, it's delicious.
It's done ~
Blue Team
Lastly Lee Joon starts
Joon ~
OMG~
The torment still hasn’t faded
Joon, it rests on you.
The fate rests on the last players
Just shove it in.
Just shove it in, straight up.
It must be hot, leave some
because I want to try.
Last player
Lee Joon
HaHa
Joon, no you can't do that.
Endure a little more.
Hurry, here's not much left.
This side is flustered by the hot drink
Ah, feels like death.
Please, that's right.
What will
happen?
Will it be the Red Team who drank the yolk stew?
Or the blue Team who drank the lava ssanghwacha?
Which team will get the Running Ball?
Joon, faster!
Red Team
Wins
Give that to me, I want
to know how hot it is.
How hot could it have been
It just comes up.
Words won't come out of my mouth.
Is it really hot?
Can't even swallow once
You can't drink it?
It's okay in the mouth, but
when you try to swallow ...
Feeling the heat as he tries to swallow
It came again.
Red Team
Acquired 2 balls
Finally, the time to choose has come.
Today in the Museum of History ...
Time to decide which team will leave
... the number of balls we have
is 2 and the Red Team has 3.
Blue Team
Running Balls
Red Team
Today's punishment is hot pants.
Checking
Today's punishment
is hot pants
First everyone, please put your balls in.
Don't do anything with chi, just put it in.
I've noticed it doesn't work
if you get carried away.
Let's add chi to ours.
No, don't add chi.
Please~
We'll add chi.
We should be indifferent.
Just add them.
Okay ~
The team whose ball
comes out will go home.
Yes.
Blue ~
Please ...
I wish there will be a drama.
For 2 straight weeks the team with less balls won
Will the extraordinary happen again this week?
A dramatic twist.
Are we ready?
Please ~
Blue Team
2 balls
Red Team
3 balls
Oh, please.
Spinning
It's coming out.
Please ...
Everything rests on this moment
The probability is definitely
in the Red Team's favor.
Who'll be able to leave?
Who'll suffer the indignity of wearing hot pants?
Jaesuk oppa ...
Opening the hole of the lottery wheel...!
The team whose colored ball comes out wins
A red ball
Yeah ~
Red Team
Chosen to escape
There was no extraordinary twist
We did it.
Bleak
Hot pants ~
This must be a bad dream
Shortly...
In sleek(?) hot pants...
Gasp!
Armed with hot pants
Beautiful men
Isn't only embarrassing...
Red Team
Also drew on their faces
It's unbearable to watch.
Even Jihyo from the same team ...
I was wondering who you were, Jihyo.
I thought it was some random bearded man.
You look like four relay racers.
It looks like you re out to exercise.
It's a nice look.
Very pretty.
It looks refined.
Does it really look like
Sukjin is going to exercise?
Anyone can tell that this is a punishment.
Who would make their
face like that and exercise?
I mean ...
Who'll exercise with 'Big Nose' on the forehead?
It even says Big Nose on his forehead.
Decided to split in 2 teams and return home
Jaesuk-Sukjin-Joon
Kwangsoo-Jihyo
Hello.
The bare legs of
3 men who brighten our morning
I haven't worn this since elementary school.
After elementary school ...
Hello, it's like a swimsuit ...
Hello? Yes?
Why do you pretend
to be on the phone?
Because it's so embarrassing.
Embarrassed
Everyone's looking
Shabby
Modestly gathered legs
Oh, it's here.
Their bus arrives
Thank you.
Full of people
going to work
Excuse me.
Click
Hello?
Again!
Pretend to use the phone is perfect when embarrassed
Why pretend to be on the phone?
There's a smell coming
from me, isn't there?
Slide~
It seems you're a bit ...
Meanwhile
Kwangsoo and Jihyo
Yawn...
Lonely in an empty bus
Jaesuk-Sukjin-Joon
Finally getting off at Gangnam
It's cool ~
Thank you, Mr. Driver!
Let's do this next time as well.
Please let us use this as the
punishment next week as well.
Due to frustration and
wants revenge
Even shorter pants.
Even shorter
Just like this.
One's that's really high cut
A triangle.
Let's do it that way.
Next time
Stronger hot pants will come