Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by iSUBS
Today's landmark
station
Rush to the train before
it sets off
Be fast and get to
Gwangmyeong station
To save one more second
breathless race toward the finish
The best chasing team
has been formed
Kim
Jongkook
Song
Jihyo
Everyone has to be on alert
Today you'll be caught
The real ace's battle
will begin
And...
Unexpected reversal
An unfair deal
Intelligent action film
Running Man
It
begins now
It's Running Man again.
Today, it'll be held at Haengshin station.
The weather today is really cold.
And Jihyo's outfit is very thick.
The weather last week was too
cold, everyone criticized me.
It wasn't cold last week.
You just wore too little.
Yes, that's why this week ...
If Jihyo had gone to a club ...
Last week
really thin exercise clothes
... she would look like a ball.
Club disco ball style
Disco ball ~
Aigo, why must these two kids
always be at Jongkook's side?
We can't not be here.
Of course.
Lately it seems that you
like having this kid-image.
Why?
You've become Po.
* Po from Teletubbies
HaHa is a Teletubby
I don't spend much effort on my outfit.
You don't spend an effort at all, really.
You just have to be natural, there's
no need to spend so much effort.
Wear your glasses, aren't you Haroro?
No, do I really?
We all have our own concept.
The 3 men's character package
Now I will transform into what
everyone has been anticipating.
Dainty
Muscleman, Rubber shoes and Haroro.
Muscleman 28
Black shoes
Haroro
At this moment
The important thing now
isn't the answer, I will ...
Big Nose with a sad expression
Hyung, why are you looking at
me with that longing expression?
Jaesuk, you just pay attention to them.
The reason for Big Nose's awkwardness
will be revealed shortly
Hello ~
Who are they greeting?
Hey
Kim Jaedong when did he appear?
Shocked
You scared me.
Why are you here?
I'm probably here for the filming.
Calm
For a guest his entrance is too ...
It's Jaedong.
We should take good care of our guest.
Really just passing by?
I'm looking forward to who it is.
I'll ﻿wait here until the guest arrives.
Yeah ~
Who is today's guest?
I will announce it in 5 seconds.
It's really you?
The nation's
most eloquent
Today's guest
Kim
Jaedong
Yes, it's me.
Since the train is here, it's time to go.
Yes, I should go.
As if he's returning to his hometown
Thank you ~
We've filmed Running Man together before.
They seem closer this time
We're really thankful to be
able to film together again.
Today we're at Haengshin station.
Are we supposed to travel somewhere?
Today the target destination
is Gwangmyeong station.
Today's landmark
Gwangmyeong station
Gwangmyeong station.
From Haengshin station, you will pass by ...
Haeshin
Yongsan
Gwangmyeong
... Yongsan to reach Gwangmyeong station.
Complete a mission on each checkpoint
First time to arrive gets a Running Ball
Yes ~
First team to reach Gwangmyeong
station will get a Running Ball.
Are we all going to take the same train?
Wait, because this is a team game...
All team members must complete the task
at every ﻿station within the given time limit ...
... before boarding the train together.
So if we don't board the train
in time, we'll be eliminated?
Is it okay if I don't board the train?
What type of a question is that?
It's just a game.
Jongkook oppa is really scary.
You're right, Jihyo.
Jihyo, you aren't simple either.
Commander is equally scary as the inferior Jihyo
You're really scary.
Shut that mouth
I used to seem scary, but not anymore.
I'll split you all into teams.
Yes.
Split into 3 teams
Kim Jongkook ...
Please ~
Blue Team
Jong
kook
Gary
No way ...
HaHa
Lizzy
Seumdwa ~
What?
Ah, you still don't know that phrase.
You still
don't know?
Kwangsoo ...
Red Team
Kwang
soo
Ah, I don't like it.
Jihyo
That's great.
Joongki.
What are you two doing?
The not welcomed team
member Kwangsoo?
Monday Boyfriend joins
What are you doing?
So the three of us are a team?
Automatically
Sukjin Jaesuk Jaedong became a team
We three?
How can this be?
Strong opposition
Does this even look okay?
Jaedong doesn't even know
what is going on right now.
And lately Jaesuk and I have
been awkward together.
I haven't done anything.
Why is everyone so angry at me?
Everyone, at 7:35 PM you must get
on the train at Haengshin station.
Yes.
Once you get in the station ...
... you must buy your train
tickets at the ticket machine.
Next, everyone has to
buy a hot beverage ...
... from ﻿the vending machine
and bring it up the train..
Time is now already 7:30 PM
Let's go ~
Buy tickets and drink
Board the train on time
Jaedong, hurry.
It they are too late
the train leave without them
Oppa ...
I'm right behind you.
Neither the staff can be late
Everyone's headed home
in the crowded station
Joongki ...
But tickets first? Or the beverage?
Joongki, coffee.
Where?
Where are the ticket machines?
That way.
Thank you.
It's right there
Oh, it's here ~
Blue Team gets there first
First find the right train
0318.
All teams find the ticket machine
It's here?
It's here ~
1 minute already passed
Joongki, come here .
Ah, this isn't it.
There ~
Bang
Monday
Couple?
Just physical violence
Hyung, Jongkook hyung.
Noona, do you want to
drink Cocoa or Coffee?
I don't need a drink.
Cocoa.
Having Jihyo's ♥
love is enough
Red
Team
Jihyo * Joongki
successfully buys drinks
Okay, one more cup.
Let's go.
Kwangsoo ...
Red Team
Ticket
Beverage (complete)
Yellow Team
Ticket
Beverage
Blue team
Ticket
Beverage
Calm
Okay, we're done.
Red Team
Ticket
Beverage (complete)
Yellow Team
Ticket
Beverage
Blue team
Ticket (complete)
Beverage
Now Yellow Team has bought their 3 drinks
Let's go ~
Red Team
Ticket
Beverage (complete)
Yellow Team
Ticket
Beverage (complete)
Blue team
Ticket (complete)
Beverage
Jaesuk, what are you doing?
Yellow Team just have to buy tickets
Don't do that.
Joongki presses for Jaesuk on
the ticket machine's reset button
Jaesuk, what are you doing?
Red
Team
Jihyo, with her
blank innocent look
Red Team
Ticket (complete)
Beverage (complete)
Yellow Team
Ticket
Beverage (complete)
Blue team
Ticket (complete)
Beverage
Joongki, this isn't easy at all.
Joongki, quick, let's go.
Go ~
Red
Team
Just have to get on
the train and they are
It's not here we board?
KTX boarding area.
KTX boarding area, it's there.
How do I use this?
Anxious
Yellow
Team
Red Team
Ticket(complete)
Beverage (complete)
Yellow Team
Ticket (complete)
Beverage (complete)
Blue team
Ticket (complete)
Beverage
Let's go, run.
Yellow
Team
Also just need to
get on the train
Blue Team is still buying drinks
Quick, put the coins in.
My hands are shaking.
Anything above 300 won doesn't work.
Cocoa or Coffee?
Relaxed?
The other teams have left
1 cup of Cocoa and 1 cup of Coffee.
All Cocoa.
They thought they were first
to buy tickets and now ...
It's coming out.
When it's ready, take it out quickly.
Oh, we need 100 won more.
What happened?
Eh?
But 4 people x300 is 1200 won
The 300 won is all used.
It's still not enough.
Looking for 100 won in the return slot
The 7:35 PM train will be leaving soon.
Get on the train
or be eliminated
Hurry ~
Yah, you're just holding
1 cup and you can't run.
Because of the hot cups
they can't run very fast
Still a long
bridge to pass
Jaesuk hyung is here.
There's no time, are we late?
Looking at her run, it
looks like we are late.
Yes it seems so.
Oh, the all left.
Hot ~
Yah, this ...
Lagging behind and starting to panic
Busy
Messy
It looks like there's another.
Hurry.
There's no time.
We must get on the train.
Surprisingly strong
Yellow
Team
Did you not see that?
What?
It looks like we're late, then
we can't get on the train.
1 minute before departure
Wait, number 13, let's get on.
1 minute
to run to carriage 13
Come quickly.
Which carriage?
Get on the train first.
The camera crew hears
the public address and
are also panicking
The 7:35 PM train is about to leave.
Red Team is first on the train
Aigoo, I picked the wrong team.
Let's get on the train first
before finding Carriage 13.
Yellow Team also boards on time
But Blue Team is behind
No ~
The train is about to leave.
If they don't make it,
they won't be able to film
Also the crew is in a rush
The 0318 train is leaving.
It's really about to leave
The whole crew makes it
on to the train
Hyung, block the train.
Will Blue Team be eliminated like this?
The train is now leaving.
Closed
As promised to the passengers
Departing at exactly 7:35
Heading toward Yongsan station
Didn't Jongkook make it?
Jongkook didn't make it.
That rascal didn't make it.
Commander's
Blue
Team
didn't make it?
Looks like he didn't make it.
Holiday spirit
I knew this was going to happen.
What happens when you don't make it?
You lose ~
Mission fails if you don't make it
you'll go straight to Gwangmyeong
Then you can't get the Running Ball.
Looks like he really didn't
make it, that rascal.
No sight of them at this moment
Jongkook hyung didn't make it.
Can't believe he didn't make it
No way.
It's very possible that
he didn't make it.
Didn't make it
Blue
Team
arrives
... that he didn't make it.
Commander and his 3 kids
Ah, how is that possible?
What took you so long?
Go in first ~
Didn't have time to reach the
front of the train
We won't make it if we run to the front.
Enter the train no matter what
Enter the train before door closes
then find the front cart
Blue Team
First mission Everyone succeeds
The 2nd mission is inside the luggage
that everyone is holding right now.
Yongsan station mission
Oh, really?
Let's open it.
What is it going to be again?
Instructions and a bank card
Looks like it's the same.
All teams with different missions
No, it's not.
What's your mission?
Withdraw 10,000 won and buy a
book called "Myeongshim Bogam"
* "Myeongshim Bogam" was written by Chu Jeok in
14 century and used for children's moral teaching
Withdraw 10,000 won from the machine and ...
Red
Team
... go to a store to store to buy a
book called "Myeongshim Bogam".
Withdraw 10,000 won and buy yellow waffles
equivalent to the your number of members.
Blue
Team
That one is hard.
Withdraw 10,000 won and buy
kimbap, wafers for 30 seconds ...
Yellow
Team
... 2 bottles of cider, wet tissue,
hot dog and 2 hot buns.
Predicted to fail this mission
For this mission ...
... each team can only send
out one person to finish it.
How can you do this by yourself?
If that person doesn't
come back in time ...
... then no one in that team
can board the train.
Oh, really?
A burden for the team's representative
So do we have to get off and wait outside?
Then there might a chance
that all 3 teams won't make it.
Yoo Jaesuk is fast.
He runs very fast.
Yellow
Team
Recommends Jaesuk
as representative
He's seriously fast, right?
Yeah.
Ah, seriously
Unanimous vote for Jaesuk
as their representative
I'm so tired, so just let Kwangsoo go.
Red
Team
Long legged Kwangsoo
as representative
What about you?
Our team will be Jongkook.
Blue
Team
Of course it'll
be Jongkook
Unfair competition(?) Negative feedback
Gary ~
What did you say?
If we send Kwangsoo, then our
team will definitely lose, right?
Yes.
Then me and Jihyo noona will just forfeit ...
... and head straight to Mok Po for a trip.
A trip
to Mok Po with noona
Flower Joongki's exploding confession?
Jihyo, why aren't you answering?
Jihyo didn't say no
There's no such thing, right?
Are you really going?
A trip with Joongki...?
What's there to say?
Not...
denying
You'll arrive and find out
that I am already there.
I'll ride the helicopter there, don't worry
The KTX door seems like it's automatic, right?
Will always depart on time
Once the time is up, then
it'll close no matter what.
Didn't the trains from before
have their doors opened?
If the train leaves, ﻿he will just
use his hands to pull it to a stop.
Jongkook the robot
Earlier when we ran ...
... Jongkook had a runny nose
and it looked like it was blue.
Framing
Sorry, ﻿I was just kidding.
Just kidding?
Slowly approaching Yongsan station
Yongsan station is here.
Quickly getting off to prepare
The train's departure time is
Current time
Only 7 minutes
left
The representatives quickly depart
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Within 7 minutes
complete the mission and return
Kwangsoo, fighting.
Fighting ~
Hurry and go.
Joongki, cheer for me.
Kwangsoo, fighting.
A little worrisome
Oh my god
If he doesn't come back, then
the team can't board, right?
Then no one can go.
If we can't get the first Running Ball.
That means we pretty much
will receive the punishment.
The spacious Yongsan station
First to arrive
Jaesuk * Jongkook
Yellow
Blue
Team
Withdraw 10,000 won
and buy four waffles
There's the smell of waffles.
Where is it?
Expected
Commander smells the waffles?
Do you know where the waffle store is?
Waffle ~
Don't know?
Beside the pharmacy.
Citizen:
Where?
The pharmacy is over there?
Pharmacy ~
At last discovered the waffle store
Hello ahjumuni ...
... please give me 4 waffles.
4 waffles ~
While she bakes he goes to withdraw money
Luckily the ATM is close
Bank card password is ...
I didn't look at the password.
The password is on back of the card
Why didn't I look at the password?
Yellow
Team
Withdraw money and buy kimbap,
wafers, cider, tissue and buns
Ah, where is it?
Red
Team
Withdraw money and buy
the book "Myeongshim"
Searches right
Searches left
It's Yoo Jaesuk.
Jaesuk*Kwangsoo
Both searches for the ATM
Excuse me, is there a ATM here?
Over there
Towards the ATM at the same time
Push
Pull
Arrives at the ATM
at the same time
Gasping for awhile
Who will be
first to withdraw 10,000
Kwangsoo withdraws first
Success
Immediate disturbance
Kwangsoo rushes to find a
book store while out of breath
Hello, do you know where the book store is?
Just around the corner over there.
Thank you.
10,000 won.
Excuse me.
4 minutes left until departure
Do you believe that Jongkook will take the win?
Seumdwa ~
Continuation of the trendy phrase
Seumdwa
group
Blue Team
Seumdwa ~
Yellow Team
Sincere praying group
Jaesuk ~
Only blank~ and waiting
Red Team
Calm group
Meanwhile Jongkook found the password
Because of anxiety the eyes are blurred
I'm really going crazy.
Frustrated
Finally enters the password and finishes
Straight back to the waffle store
4 right? Here you go.
Already finished the waffles
Thanks for the hard work.
Blue Team
Jongkook
Mission success
Buying waffles completed
Yellow Team
Jaesuk must buy a lot of snacks
Wafers ...
Too anxious and panics
... where is it?
Cider, 2 ciders.
Calm down ~
Cider, 2 cans.
First takes the two ciders
Excuse me, can you help me
heat a kimbap for 30 seconds?
Also need to heat up a kimbap
Where is it?
The microwave is over there.
Please give me 2 hot buns.
2 hot buns.
Where are the wet tissues?
Wet tissues, thank you.
Finds wet tissues at the entrance
The tissues are outside?
Wet tissue ~
Do you have hot dogs?
Hot dogs are over there
Ah, thank you.
Goes to the back again
Hot dog ~
Do you have wafers?
They are in the middle.
Ah, the middle.
Runs forward again
A route without much productivity
Where is it?
Seems like playing a game with the employees
This one, right?
Sorry, 3 wafers.
Still he finishes buying everything
The total will be 7300 won.
Thank you, 7300 won?
Thanks to you two, I managed
to finish within five minutes.
Thanks.
Do you need the receipt?
The receipt, I don't have
enough time right now.
Thanks for the hard work.
Ah, hello ~
Yellow Team
Jaesuk
Mission success
Now to the train
Kwangsoo wandered for awhile for the book store
Book ~
2 minutes until departure
Among numerous books
Dongui Bogam.
* A Korean medical textbook written in early 17th century
No <Myeongshim Bogam> only <Dongeui Bogam>
Dongui....
Almost out of time
Myeongshim, there are only Dongui Bogam.
Myeongshim Bogam.
Myeongshim ...
Found it
Rushes to cash out
Hello.
Red Team
Kwang
soo
Mission success
Buying the book success
Thank you ~
How many minutes left?
Those waiting are also very nervous
How many minutes?
There's 2 minutes left before departure
Kim Jongkook ~
Still no one to be seen
All teams have finished the missions
But they must get on the train
Someone's coming.
Who is it?
Please...
Be our team...
Who is it?
Waffle holding
Commander
Kim Jongkook ~
Jongkook
At this time
Jaesuk appears behind him
Cheering
He's coming.
Kwangsoo...
The teams that arrived board the train
Let's go, thanks for your hard work.
Shooting crew, get on.
Take us ...
Unnie don't go.
At this time Kwangsoo is on
his way to the platform
If he runs faster he can arrive on time
Not enough time.
Oh?
What?
Oh!
The other side of the platform...!
It's time for the train to depart
Blocked the entrance
Kwangsoo ~
Closed the doors
Can see the end of the stairs
but no Kwangsoo in sight
What are we going to do?
Bewildered
What?
It's not time yet.
He ran to the wrong platform
Oh, there it is.
He can see his hyungs in the train
Jongkook ...
Now he realizes the situation
But it has already become a joke
It's unbelievable.
Even if he shouts from across...
Because it's far...
They can't hear him...
Kwangsoo hurry up.
Hurry ~
With long legs
he tries to run fast
Hurry ~
They won't make it.
The train is already moving
Myeongshim Bogam.
Don't leave.
Crying
Going far away
Oppa...!
Goodbye.
There's noting sadder than
this train station farewell
No ...
Hit
Bang
Angry
High kick
The cause of this sad farewell is ...
Lee Kwangsoo
You ... !
You come here.
Kwangsoo ...
Kneeling to apologize
I bought it earlier than them.
But why weren't you coming, why?
Noona ... ah!
What is this? We're cold and hungry.
I bought ...
.. Myeongshim Bogam.
Running Ball
Already left with the train
Sorry
You must do all of today's
punishments alone.
Today's punishments ...
Reconciliation with
hands on shoulders
We're starting now.
How much money is left?
7,040 won.
Joongki checks the money seriously
We must think positively.
Right.
We're all starving.
Exhales
At this time, we all must
think calmly and carefully.
We'll use this money to buy
one portion of fish cakes.
Why?
It can be a more precious memory for us.
No glancing
How dare you talk about memories?
We'll buy fish cakes and
each person will get one.
The caring hearts
of two young men
It's okay.
Let's go.
Fish cake
instead of a Running Ball
I'm sorry.
Joongki, I'm sorry.
Red
Team
Eliminated
What game are we going to play?
Remaining two teams
Blue Team
Yellow Team
Next team who will be eliminated is your.
Pure and well-mannered
Lizzy is just sitting there.
I'm okay.
Lizzy in the corner
You didn't know that Lizzy
really likes our team?
Lizzy?
Seumdwa.
Together, seumdwa.
The already trendy seumdwa
Going to the final destination Gwangmyeong
Now it's the last mission.
Last mission to get Running Ball
We must eliminate that team.
There is a Running Man flag at the
highest place of Gwangmyeong station.
Final
Mission
1st team to arrive at the flag wins
The team ﻿with all of their members
to arrive there first will be the winner.
All team members must arrive
All ﻿team members?
All.
We have Lizzy
But you have Jongkook.
It doesn't matter, we have to run first.
Block that team, don't let them run
Worry
What are you saying?
All ﻿of you run first and I'll clean them up.
Running Man's final destination
Today's landmark
KTX Gwangmyeong
The nation's first train station
Earliest KTX train station in the nation
Highest place is the final destination
Arrive in a couple of minutes
In a moment we'll arrive
in Gwangmyeong station
However, we must get the Running Ball.
Preparing before the mission starts
Everyone is already prepared
Kim Jongkook, you already started.
Hey, look at you.
Jongkook
blocking
the exit
We've been blocked.
Producer, he won't let us out.
They are blocking us.
Let all of cameramen get off.
Kim Jongkook, you're really ...
Let the cameramen get off.
Finally the train stops
Who'll be the first to get off?
Still chaotic inside
Door is opening ~
Soon door opens
Last mission is very fierce
Don't block us ~
Finally the door is open
Commander is blocking the Yellow Team
Three people start to run
Finally Yellow Team takes off
The team who arrives first with all
it's members will get Running Balls
Faster ~
Bang
Tidy clean up(?)
Where is it?
Jongkook hit me.
All arrive on the platform
Blue Team's 3 kids are going up
Run faster.
Lizzy ...
Absolute defense
Alone blocking 3 people
Doesn't tolerate gaps
Let us go.
Run faster.
Blue
Team
Except Jongkook arrives
at the highest floor
But to win all members must arrive
Quickly, we're arriving.
Blue
Team
3 kids
But also Jongkook must arrive
Now it's a 1:3 competition
Now there's no strategy Just unconditional speed
I'm off
Aigoo, he's too fast.
Blocking 3 people alone No lack of stamina
Who will arrive first?
Who'll be owner of first Running Ball
Who'll appear first?
Commander
Jongkook
Blue
Team
Jongkook also arrives
Blue Team finally wins
Blue Team gets Running Balls
We haven't got a Running Ball in a long time.
What about Red Team who was left at Yongsan?
Jihyo and Kwangsoo, where are they?
Shall we try to call them?
Don't let them worry, we both losers
Already lost so why waste your energy?
It's connected.
Where are you?
Sukjin ~
Like children who lost their mother
Oppa ...
Afflicted
They got the Running Ball.
Announces the
Running Ball news
They got the Running Ball?
This is Running Ball.
You're the same as us.
How nice.
Quickly come to Gwangmyeong station.
Well be right over.
Eating waffles instead of
fishcakes to calm their hunger
Kwangsoo ...
... can you stomach the waffles?
Then eat a lot more.
But it's still because of you that
we're not getting a Running Ball.
Reversal
But the chance
to receive a Running Ball ...
Later at Gwangmyeong
Why did we have to
run that desperately ...
... there's still the unhurried team coming.
Waiting for the losing team
If we'd known we wouldn't win,
should've stayed and take next train.
We could have eaten ﻿some
fishcakes while coming over.
Regretful
Jongkook even said that they didn't think
they could find the waffle shop that fast.
Even startled
themselves
We used light speed to get there and back.
Run, get away, run.
What's so difficult for the commander?
It was a little embarrassing.
To Jongkook this type of
level like waffles won't do.
Dragging the neck of an ox will do
or hauling tires is more like it.
Recommended activities
for the Commander
Drag oxen
Haul tires?
To counter Jongkook, there
must be other missions set up.
I was running hard just now.
These two got Running Balls only
because of association with this team.
Benefited from association(?)
The people who didn't manage
to get into a good team
Be satisfied with what we have.
Reflecting?
Reading from
"Myeongshim Bogam"
When living on earth, it's not
all about coveting things ...
Greed, with regards to the
lust for the Running Ball.
Who am I
talking to?
With the KTX it only takes 10 minutes
with the car it took 50 minutes
Let's go together
Oppa ...
They're here.
These three people are
completely in Christmas attire.
Kwangsoo, what happened to you?
Just like meeting a lost family
It's been hard on you.
Why is there cool air coming
off from your clothes?
The cold winter made their clothes cold
Wait a moment.
Did you find the "Myeongshim Bogam"?
Why?
Because you didn't search fast
enough it affected the whole team.
Ah, it's disappointing
You made it in time, but why did
you ﻿run to the wrong platform?
When I came here just now
I finished reading the book.
Satisfied
Although we don't know how
today's results will be like ...
Today's guest is Kim Jaedong.
Is it us against Kim Jaedong today?
Battle with Jaedong?
Ah, how did he know?
...Oh gosh
Just like Jaesuk said, it's a 1:9 battle.
Exactly.
Today's 1:9 battle is "Let’s raise
Kim Jaedong's heart rate".
Let’s raise Jaedong's heart rate
We have had experience.
Ah Jihyo, we played once with Jihyo.
Previously
Jihyo did that battle
That was really very fun.
The time limit's 30 minutes.
Jaedong, put on the heartbeat meter first.
Put it on.
Eh, but ...
why are the looks...?
Before the filming started
9 people are assembled and avoiding Jaedong
The weather's become colder
Yes ~
Why have we been called
together again today?
Today we'll also be proceeding with the 1:9.
You have to make Jaedong
say predetermined the lines.
The real mission
Hasn't Jaedong done this before?
He'll certainly discover it.
But...
Jaedong is already
familiar with 1:9 games!?
Even if Jaedong finds
out, it doesn't matter.
So we still win.
Make Jaedong say predetermined lines
within 30 min. Everyone has to succeed.
But the time limit is 30 minutes.
Complete it within 30 minutes?
This doesn't seem too easy.
Here is the mission.
We just have to make him say
the lines that are written here.
Joongki shall choose first.
So what sort of lines
must be heard from Jaedong?
Can't I change it once?
What is it?
What's the line Joongki
must hear from Jaedong
This is an impossible
mission to complete.
Curious
He definitely will not
say this to Joongki.
You are ugly
The world's Flower Boy Joongki
must hear the line 'You're ugly'
Can't I do that?
For me it would be easy
It's too ridiculous for words.
The line Joongki must hear
You're ugly
Jaedong often says this type of line to me.
Don't joke around
The line Jaesuk must hear
You're so funny
You're so funny.
The line Sukjin must hear
You're so funny
Ah, this is too hard.
Do you love her?
The line Kwangsoo must hear
Is there a problem?
What, is there a problem?
The line Lizzy must hear
Make him say a famous saying.
Make him say a famous saying
The line Jongkook must hear
A wise saying!
That's easy.
It's over in one shot.
The line HaHa must hear
In one room ...
That's too easy.
If it's one room
you're finished
Are you interested in me?
The line Jihyo must hear
Ah, this is too hard.
How can this be possible?
I envy you
The line Gary must hear
If Jihyo and you have any bodily contact ...
Easier than first imagined
Bodily contact would crate envy
The Monday Couple has broken up, oppa.
What is this
Because of the betrayal(?) last time
they broke up
It's just starting now.
Doesn't want it to end
It doesn't just end when
anyone simply says it ends.
I already said "I love you".
Almost like a fool.
Jaedong's almost here, let's prepare a bit.
Time limit is 30 minutes
Will all these lines
be heard from Jaedong's mouth?
Fighting.
Embarrassed
We have to shout 'Fighting'.
1, 2, 3, fighting.
Putting a fake heart rate monitor on Jaedong
That one is too hard for me.
Discussing tactics
Mine is the difficult one,
you guys have to help me.
Jaedong thinks
it's the 'Let's raise the heart rate' game
The monitor that doesn't need to be started
If we make Jaedong's heartbeat rise
to 130 and above then we will win.
Fake
This scene seems to be seen often.
The not working
heart rate monitor
You'd better perform well today.
Perform well today.
Real
rule
They must make Jaedong say
predetermined lines within 30 min
For this sort of game,
I still have confidence.
Don't be anxious.
The lines Jaedong must say
Is there a problem?
I envy you
Don't joke around
One room ...
Wise saying
You're ugly
You're funny
Interested in me?
You love her?
You might as well make it to 140.
Is your relationship with Lee Hyori alright?
This question is a good one.
Yes, our relationship isn't too bad.
Everyone knows Hyori
has considerable charm.
Kwangsoo wants Jaedong to say:
Do you love her?
She has a lot of charm.
Even once ...
... have you felt her to be very feminine.
No, not even once.
How to put it?
I've almost never felt it from the
standpoint of the opposite sex.
Dejected
Don't hesitate to ask any questions,
I will talk about everything.
It's not easy
Friends like Hyori who are rich celebrities ...
... and also have a lot of charm.
If you met her you'd be shy right?
What?
Kwangsoo, why are you like this?
Impatient Brain Joongki gives a helping hand
Do you like Hyori noona?
Oh, Kwangsoo ...
Indulging
in fantasy
Will Jaedong
finally fall into the trap?
Kwangsoo is it possible that ...
Do you love her?
Please...!
Do you love Lee Hyori?
First round:
Kwangsoo
Succeeds
Come back in.
That type of answer will do.
but he just looks down
Kwangsoo wanted to show happiness
Kwangsoo almost showed happiness
Go back.
You're in love with her.
Next week I'm going mountain
climbing with ﻿Lee Hyori ...
... do you want to come with us?
Jaedong thinks that
Kwangsoo really likes Hyori
Yes.
We'll change the person asking.
Your heartbeat index has
already risen up to 140.
Lie
Really.
I'm not easy to bully.
I have a reason
for ding this
I wish I drew this, I can do it well.
Don't joke around
Strategy
Twisting the arm...?
Hyung you first.
Just trying it first.
Stabbing pain
No, your expression is to intense.
Aren't we friends?
Competing for attention
You two look really close.
Ah, really ...
When you go in the future,
don't say you're ﻿close to me.
Say you were close with me.
Don't joke around
This is really very hard
Jaesuk's attack?
Be mischievous unconditionally
Isn't this too childish?
Okay ~
Will that work?
Sit down first.
Ah, let go of me.
Just say:
"Don't joke around"
Don't scratch me I'm very ticklish.
Hyung, don't you remember that time?
Suddenly HaHa appears
What?
What did you say to Kim Jongkook?
In one room you're finished.
One room ...
That's too easy.
What did you say to Kim Jongkook?
Have Jaedong said that to Jongkook before?
You can't do it like this.
What?
Jongkook looked very bad
at that time, very horrifying.
Looks like Jaedong heard this for the first time
Talking
nonsense
Not easy, right?
Honestly speaking, that was hyung, right?
Yes ~
The sigh that comes from
things not going his way
Come, get in line.
No, why?
HaHa who is talking nonsense
and Jaesuk who prevents it
Today's 1:9 battle
is a bit worrisome
It's ended, it didn't work, right?
Yes.
Everyone ...
Unnecessary nervousness
Frustrating
Let's encourage ourselves a little.
Do well
Just like me
Keep your cool ~
Real intention
Say the line
Everyone keep your cool.
We got it.
As expected Jaesuk don't keeps his cool
and starts tickling again
Overboard joke
Jaesuk tries to make him say <Don't joke around>
Has he really
gone crazy?
Jaedong say
'Don't joke around'
for me
Many people are watching.
What's going on?
The heart rate index ~
Jaedong is convinced that the running is
a strategy to increase his heart rate
Not moving at all?
Hypocrisy
Of course no... It isn't even activated
Hurry up and take a seat.
Not a single success?!
Jongkook acts along rashly
Now I know.
You're trying to make me
do childish things, right?
This isn't childish
but mischievous
Take a seat, I won't
pull the chair again.
Just now I was too much.
Please forgive me
Don't do childish things anymore.
Jaedong ...
Yes?
Very mischievous
What are you doing?
Don't you feel warm?
Why are you doing this?
Trying everything just to hear
'Don't joke around'
Don't you feel warm?
No, I don't.
Besides doing absurd
things, anything else?
Anxious
Excuse me.
What?
How did
he get in?
No, why are you like this?
Finally
Are we ending this in the process of mocking?
'Don't joke around' say it please...!
Why are you so childish?
Why are we childish?
So difficult
Childish, totally childish.
Again ...
Keep your cool ~
Jaesuk's attempt
Fail
Why are we so awkward?
Our Kim Jaedong ...
Come back ~
We'll talk later.
Star without a brilliant strategy
Retreats
In 2003 ...
'You're really funny'
... you came to my child's first-birthday party.
Yes, I went.
Back then, why did you wink to my wife?
Huh...?
'This hyung is really funny'
say it please
What is that?
No, I didn't wink to your wife.
Just strong denials
My wife told me about it.
"Why did Jaedong wink at me?"
But why would I do that?
'You're really funny'
Stubborn Sukjin wants to hear that
Frustrated
She would never say that.
Unavoidable
Is that so?
Jaedong always deviate from the wanted answer
She's not worth winking to?
That's enough, come back.
No but ...
... I heard that many female celebrities
including Song Jihyo like Kim Jaedong.
Jihyo?
Did you know about it?
Song Jihyo, please come out.
Blank~ the line to say
only when Jihyo enters is?
Are you interested in me?
Jihyo, is it okay for you since
you have never done this?
You can say something like ...
"Oppa, why do you go
hiking with other women?"
Strategy
Use the fact Jaedong
hikes with female celebs
That could work.
'Are you interested in me?'
The line that
Jihyo
wants Jaedong to say
You know Jihyo, right?
Song Jihyo, please come out.
Jihyo is good right?
Did you peek at her before?
Information
Was Jaedong always
interested in Jihyo?
Yes, I did. She's very pretty.
But how come you never say that
you want to go hiking with me?
You might feel it's tiring.
That was too fake.
You can't stand there dumbly,
you have to ask something.
Can you say why you never once asked to go
hiking with her, but always goes with others?
Hand on shoulder?
Flushed with joy~
Hey, what are you doing?
Running Man members are helping each other
Please also ...
... include me to go
hiking next time.
Go hiking together...?
... go hiking next time.
Let's go hiking.
I really like hiking.
Shy
Alright, let's go together.
Sticky situation
What should I do?
Let's go next time.
Really?
Yes, let's go.
Be more proactive.
Be more
proactive?
Jihyo has mentioned in a show
that ﻿Jaedong is her ideal type.
That's right, she mentioned that before.
'Are you interested in me?'
Jaedong should say that
You truly seem to be a caring man.
Jaedong is really like that.
You are becoming more charming.
Continuous compliments+concerns strategy
Just now during dinner, I
wanted to take care of you.
Are you not feeling well?
Yes, I am not feeling well today.
Cheer up.
Let's also go hiking together.
Now
'Are you interested in me?'
say it please
Seriously?
Frustrated
If you walk away after increasing my
heartbeat rate, I won't forgive you.
What did you say?
Didn't realize people who like Jihyo are lining up
the sincere Jaedong
I didn't mean that.
This is really tough
But I think this is the first time I see
Jihyo confessing to a guy like that.
That's right.
To be frank, she told me
that Jaedong is her ideal type.
(Try covering his eyes)
I'm very close with Jaedong ...
... so I'm envious of him.
Will Sukjin's strategy work?
Not going to say the line even when
she shows this much affection?
Who am I?
Smiling
There is only one
female on that side.
Shy~
Who else can it be?
What happened to you today?
Helping
I am like this because I like, why?
What did... she say?
Are you interested in me?
Sure Jaedong's next line is?
Are you really interested in me?
Ha ha
Finally he said it
Seriously?
Why are you not answering?
Even though this is a game ...
There's no need to cover her mouth
Jaedong is getting
more excited alone(?)
Please calm down.
As I said, you'll walk away as soon
as my heartbeat rate increases.
Jaedong earnestly wants
to know the answer
It's only for Running Ball, right?
Why can't we continue asking?
Sad?
This is a game.
Jihyo
Success
Jaedong oppa,
I am sorry
I am sorry, but you must
hear a lot that you're ugly.
No ~
Trying to provoke me?
... hear a lot that you're ugly.
No ~
He won't say that to Joongki.
Can't I take that one instead?
It's mine
Joongki has to first act cool.
Strategy
Joongki has to act cool
to irritate Jaedong?
I am sorry, but you must
hear a lot that you're ugly.
You are ugly
Joongki
No one has said that to him
But he wants
to hear it from Jaedong
No ~
Not even once has someone said that to me.
Hey, no way ...
Even though you are Joongki,
you shouldn't have said that.
What did he say?
You haven't heard those
words even once?
Hyung, be the first to say it.
No one said that to me.
At first, I never thought that Joongki
could have such a good complexion.
Jaedong thinks Joongki's appearance is
It's burdensome.
burdensome?
You're right.
It's burdensome.
My apology, shouldn't have said it.
No, never mind.
So you're saying that you are handsome
because you are really good looking?
I'm better looking than him.
Stir-up
Jaesuk who is on the same level
irritates Jaedong
This is really unbearable.
Why?
Anybody can tell without fail
that he is more handsome.
In my opinion, Jaedong has good looks.
Listening to those words is
what I wish for in my life.
Just realise what he wishes.
What is your wish?
So far I only heard that
I'm cute and handsome.
How can you say
such words yourself?
Has Jaedong been hooked?
I've done all this so
please say the line
Well, you are not
especially good looking.
Why does this sound more hurtful
than the supposed line?
Why are you being tactful?
What?
Just say it.
Frustrated
A face like yours is
considered common.
Any sense?
Joongki has a common look
That's for faces like mine.
I apologize.
No, don't do that.
Frustrated
to death
Why?
Just say it affirmingly.
Joongki's fans are watching.
Hyung ...
For some unknown reason
Jaedong worries a lot
Don't do that hyung ~
Just assert yourself.
You ...
In my subjective opinion ...
... you are uglier than me.
Joongki
Success
That's ridiculous.
Members are cheering for Joongki
for being ugly
Kim Jaedong ~
3 have
succeeded
Joongki gives a reconciliation hug
I'm supposed to make sunbae's pulse
rise, but mine shot up as well.
Brain Joongki brings up the heart rate topic
It's okay.
Envy
This is what Joongki wishes for.
By the way
I have to worry?
What's wrong?
What should I do?
There are 5 minutes left.
Don't joke around
Crisis?
5 minutes left
Only 3 people
succeeded
Say a famous saying
You are really funny
If it's one room,
it's finished
Is there a problem?
Lizzy's strategy is?
Wait a minute.
Ridiculous
Laughing
to hear 'What's the problem?'
Hurry up and ask
what my problem is
Oh really ...
Therefore Jaedong ...
... is simply confused
by laughing without reason
Lizzy is just laughing
Jaedong's comment is?
Laughing because you
think my face is funny?
No, I don't.
Laughing because you
think my face is funny?
No, I don't.
... my face is funny?
It wasn't because of that.
Yes you're right, you
look funnier than me.
Lizzy ...
What?
Failing strategy of reckless laughing
... don't laugh like this anymore.
I don't see 19 year-olds a women.
I'm not interested in you.
What does this...
Calm down ~
Sudden incident of the overexcited Lizzy
Lizzy herself is not well prepared.
Who said what?
Absurd
For someone like me, how do
I become others' ideal type?
Suddenly
I envy you
I really don't have anything.
(You must say the words
I want to hear...)
I look ugly, what should I do?
Repeatedly saying
I have always respected hyung a lot.
If you were in three rooms you'd be finished.
If you were in one
room you'd be finished
(Please say
my line...)
Absurd laughter
Time is almost up ...
Everyone started shouting attempts
But these two people are really funny.
Really hyung ...
If it's one room
it is finished
I envy you
... I can't be compared to you.
From Jaedong's viewpoint
these two have difficulty partaking in the game
If we're not playing the game ...
(Just say this line)
... you'd be finished in two rooms.
I've never heard others
say "I respect you" or ...
What?
... "You are my mentor" or
words like that before.
Although frustrating it's hilarious
Come on, let's play 'Speed Quiz'.
Speed quiz?
What's this again?
Time is almost up and
various strategies are used
What are you doing?
Ka Bul Ji Ma
(Don't joke around)
One syllable
at a time
Peeling a banana?
Ka Bul Ji Ma
(Don't joke around)
Peeling a banana?
There's no fire.
Ka Bul Ji Ma
(Don't joke around)
The letter
Too anxious
SNSD's 'Gee' dance
Ka Bul Ji Ma
(Don't joke around)
Ji?
That's right.
Ka Bul Ji Ma
(Don't joke around)
Horse?
Just say it?
Say it.
He has to say the whole sentence
Yes.
Don't ... joke ... 'ride' ...
He just need to say one more word
It's not 'ride'.
What is it?
Please say it
It seems too easy?
Taken for a ride
There's no time left...
Jaedong found out in the end
I'm just trying to make
your heart rate rise.
Wait a minute ...
I seem to have a bit of
a feel for things here.
Completely aware of
strange vibes from Jaesuk
Aigoo, really ...
Hyung, I have always been
very respectful towards you.
There's still time left.
Please sit down.
It doesn't matter that Jaedong found out.
As long as he says the line they will win.
I've always envied you so much.
Okay ~
Pleading with Jaedong who found out
Hyung, I'm in a relationship with Jihyo.
Immediately folding
I got it ~
Hyung, say "Five rooms"
and see what happens.
What?
5 rooms.
Five rooms?
Are you talking about the
five-rooms-game now?
Ah, really?
Does HaHa want him to say 'one room' like this?
I'll play too ~
Hilarious
Ready, go.
5 rooms.
4 rooms.
3 rooms.
2 rooms.
1 room.
* Jaedong uses the word "il" for one but
the mission is to make him use "han"
Fool...
Why would you say "one room" that way.
It can also be said as "one room", right?
Speechless
1, 2, 3, 4 ...
* HaHa is counting with native Korean
numbers instead of the Sino-Korean.
What kind of game is this?
Four rooms ah ha.
Still persisting with the
speed quiz
What are we doing now?
Two rooms ah ha.
Running Man's plan
becomes nothing
Jaedong, just save me once.
What?
Save me once.
Well I don't know
Jaedong, look this way.
Tap
Go away.
We're doing this.
You already have a Running Ball.
Hyung ...
There's tobacco, but no fire.
Do you want to smoke?
A little...shy
Why are you doing this?
I have just always been
very envious of hyung.
I envy you for smoking.
Suddenly
You fool, you already know.
Tap
Yes?
You almost guessed this.
The nation's MC
showing willpower
mission
Fail
This was too difficult ~
Weren't they originally very confident
Only Jaedong gets a Running Bell.
A Running Bell ?
Running Bell ?
You might as well just say Running.
Resentful
Jaedong a Running Bell
Ball
achieves
Embarrassed
Jihyo, what did you mean
when you asked him ...
... "Are you interested in me?".
Don't joke around.
So you knew it?
Of course I figured it out.
That's so depressing.
Look at that face, if you were
in one room you'd be finished.
Jaedong had it all figured out
What's wrong? Is there a problem?
Whatever it is, the person
who gets a Running Ball ...
... is our Kim Jaedong.
Jaedong gets the Running Ball
Congratulations.
But ...
Jongkook * Jihyo
What's the meaning of their profound smiles?
The first feelings of wearing
Yellow Team uniforms is a little ...
Finally it's 'Bells Hide-n-Seek' time
Mission
Team
Wearing yellow training gear
How about we take the
train back when it comes?
Take a train?
The trains won't start running
until five in the morning.
Ah, is that so?
Can we go home when the first train comes?
I'm sorry, I wanted to do
a little something so ...
Instructions arrive
Find 5 train tickets within 1 hour
and exchange them for a Running
Ball at the Central Ticket Booth
Instructions
Find five train tickets
hidden all over the place
Meanwhile...
Now ﻿I don't want to hide anymore.
The ace Jihyo
who rejected the mission team
I don't want to hide anymore.
I want to be in the same
team as Jongkook oppa.
Joined forces
Commander & the Ace
From now on I want to be a Catcher.
The strongest Chasing Team is born
Mission Team, just you wait.
We're all prepared, right?
Yes ~
Chaotic
All prepared, fighting.
If we work as one, we
can get a Running Ball.
Time left
Will be good if it's like that
Ringing
sounds...!
Already coming closer
What now...
from the start...
Frozen
This is crazy.
Run away first
A mistake from the start it'll just be one sweep
The owner of he ringing sounds
Who is that?
Ace
Jihyo
Jongkook oppa, there is
someone on the 2nd floor.
There's someone on the 2nd floor.
Terror-struck Mission Team separates
Yooruce Willis
Kwangsoo,
Joongki
ride the elevator
Which level do we go to?
Hyung, there are only two buttons.
Gary, Gary's here.
Sllliiide~
The door already closed?
Yah ...
Why are you opening the door for Gary?
A death wish determined...!
Gary already got a Running Ball
Could he be betraying again...?
Gary, there isn't anyone upstairs, right?
They're all upstairs now.
They won't follow us downstairs, right?
Gary, go off first.
Suspecting
Get out
Push hard
First checking the surrounding
Go and look for it quickly.
Gwangmyeong station is ...
... just like Africa's grasslands
Yellow herbivores just surviving
There's a big deer
There's also a pretty flower deer
An ordinary looking deer too
There's also a cowardly grasshopper deer
There are also dangers in the grasslands
For example
Animals like the lion
Yellow deers running
without knowing anything
Shocked by the
lion that suddenly appeared
The food chain
Yooruce Willis
deer was caught
Life reduced by 10 years
Mission
Team
Jaesuk
Why'd you have to catch me like this.
That's why I said I didn't want to be
partnered with Kwangsoo and Gary.
I said I didn't want Kwangsoo.
Finding his next prey
Yah, now ...
... you come up with all sorts of things.
Kwangsoo flees in panic
Yah, Lee Kwangsoo!
Ace Jihyo's chasing to the end
Oppa, Kwangsoo is on the 2nd floor.
Kwangsoo impatiently gets into a room
Eh?
But the inside looks like...
Huh!
Of all places!
Hides where males are prohibited
Oppa, that corner on the opposite side.
Walkie-talkie confirmation
Nursery room
Di
ring
ri
Crumble
What... are you doing?
Someone might come Must hide
This time?
Huk!
Hiding under the sofa?
It's now quiet outside
Gone?
Where do you
think you're going?
Traumatized
Hyung, wait a sec ...
What happened? Wait ...
Mission
Team
Kwangsoo
This is the breast feeding room,
men aren't allowed to go here.
Why did you go in here?
I'm sorry, but ...
... I thought I was going to die.
Time left
Bravely hiding Haroro
Train ticket
Jump
Too short
2nd try
As expected Too short
Lizzy can't sit back and do nothing
Mission
Team
1 out of 5
train tickets attained
Self-confidence
I did it.
Time left
Joongki searches the platform
Wow, Gwangmyeong station is really big.
I really don't want to get
the punishment today.
Where should I look?
Bet you're laughing on the inside.
Hu hu hu, like that?
Isn't that Joongki?
Jongkook ...
... first floor and first
platform, Joongki is there.
First floor and platform?
Tip-off received
Heading to the waiting room
A is train ticket here
2 out of 5
tickets attained
However
Chasing Team is closing in
I found one in the waiting room.
Teamwork
Ace Jihyo
gives directions to the Commander
Jongkook oppa ~
First floor ~
Platform, there ...
Shocked
Came at the right time
Joongki just can't shake him off
With Jihyo as his eyes
Commander chases frantically
Strongest
chasing team's battle
Joongki
Great.
Shocked
It's Jihyo ~
Jongkook oppa, Sukjin is hiding over there.
Jihyo's precise orders
Commander's tight execution
Target captured
As expected the strongest
Chasing Team in history
Sukjin
Jihyo, this time...
Gary,
Lizzy discovered
Gary and Lizzy are outside.
Jongkook executes
If Jihyo instructs
Lizzy
Strongest coordination
Who is able to escape?
Gary
Time left
Hyung, why are you so late?
My bad, there was a jam on the road.
Hyung, you should have
taken the train instead.
Once again the prison drama starts
You are so late.
This is my first time being
late, I'm always on time.
You bunch of extras.
Why are you so late?
I was the first to arrive.
Where did you go?
Toilet.
In the toilet for so long?
My stomach was feeling very bad ...
... so I went for a while.
We're really lucky we didn't
get caught by the ace.
I just came out ...
Who were you caught by?
Jongkook hyung.
Now, he's the greatest opponent I've seen.
Jaesuk was caught by Jongkook 2 minutes after start
The African gazelle ...
Joongki, you were caught too?
Sluggish
Joongki can't be caught.
Who caught you?
It was Jongkook.
Jongkook again, I'm going crazy.
Time left
Suddenly...
Movie game begins
Right ...
Become the hero ...
During this period
From a viper...
To the Haroro image...
Really absurd... Looks too absurd...
It begins now.
Haroro's epic twist ...
... please look forward to it.
Really...
Can he become
today's hide-n-seek terminator?
Frightened
What hero...
Which hero escapes down and out like that
Getting chased at the start of Movie Game
We're not playing hide-n-seek.
I wanted to become a cool hero.
I got it, I'll let you go.
Call Jaedong over here then.
Okay.
Oppa, you already have a Running
Ball, so it doesn't matter to you.
The Commander is coming
Help me hide.
Caught him already?
What to do...?
HaHa oppa...
Last week...
HaHa oppa who took...
the blame to help Jihyo escape
Today...
Should I help him out?
There
Jihyo
HaHa's position...!
Song Jihyo, why did you tell him?
Song Jihyo is a liar.
Song Jihyo
I trusted you
Ah, wait a sec ...
You can say anything to me
But right now ...
I really need a Running Ball
Meanwhile
In a secluded room
Jaedong
Hasn't taken even one step until now
Gathers courage
Finally heads out
Panting
Hyung, Jaesuk hyung ...
I'm trying my best to find and they
look like they are having a lot of fun.
Slacking
Jaesuk hyung ~
If I don't want to help you,
I can just turn myself in.
Whatever you do, don't turn yourself in.
You have done nothing
wrong, why surrender?
Don't surrender.
We'll lose if you turn yourself in.
You guys left so much for me to do.
Jaedong already has a Running Ball
If you're tired, just turn yourself in.
Jaedong, don't do anything rash.
If Mission Team loses
Jaesuk*Sukjin*Kwangsoo*Joongki automatically get punishment
Only if you do something
wrong, then you surrender.
Don't let Gary make Jaedong surrender.
Anyway the tickets can't be found.
Where do I look for so small
tickets in such a big place?
There's one at the West Hall platform.
Where's the New Hall, New Hall?
Commander
Looks like he wants to talk?
Don't come over, talk from there.
Hyung ...
You already have the Running Ball.
What?
Let's make it simple.
Then what do you have to offer in return?
Hyung there'll be a lot more next time
This illegitimate offer
will it be established?
You stand still and don't come over.
You and I, we won't get punished anyway.
Battle of strength
Meanwhile Ace Jihyo is looking for Jaedong
Last target's position confirmed
Jihyo goes straight into pursue mode
Oppa, first floor.
Over there
Victory or defeat
Oppa, Jaedong is heading
towards the 2nd floor.
He's happy since a girl is chasing him.
How can Jaedong be caught by Jihyo
How can he be caught by Jihyo noona.
In a while
This is
Jihyo's sure-kill method Wrestle
Finally Ace Jihyo did it
Let me stay like this.
Selfish
Mission
Team
Totally
Mission
Team
Fail
Jaesuk * Sukjin * Kwangsoo * Joongki
Gets the punishment
Thick hot pants suitable for winter
Really, there's all kinds of hot pants.
Today's punishment as usual?
You're not taking the punishment right now.
What?
Next week we'll film the Christmas special.
You don't expect us to wear these then?
Angry
You have to wear them to work
for the Christmas special.
Strong objections
These are to common.
It's the Christmas special.
Then we should use red, green, red, green ...
That's ridiculous.
It's Christmas .... it's a Christmas special.
1 week later...
The punished 4 man gang's car arrives
Oh, so cold.
Early December winter
Bare legged
Woah so cold.
Let's stop it.
Big 'L' mart
<Athena: Goddes of War>
Kim Minjong and Choi Siwon together
Christmas Special
Reminiscence of childhood?
Merry Christmas
Also...
discovered a Santa Claus body?
Merry Christmas
Running Man