Original hardsubs by iSUB
Transcribed by HapB
Color and alignment by SamFive
On the first night
of snow in Seoul
In central Seoul
in the corner of Nam San
Together with
the flying snow
Today's landmark
Korea House
And the Running Man scandal
that will occur here
Pretty Boy from the Joseon era Playboy Joongki
And...?
I ...
Goo Yongha
Hey, Geol Oh.
* Geol Oh = Crazy horse/beast (Moon Jaeshin's
nickname in "Sungyungwan scandal")
It's been a while.
Hey, Geol Oh.
Joseon era
Beast Man
Geol Oh
The very popular lead character Geol Oh
Aren't you Geol Oh?
The first snow has arrived.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to the Korea House
to get a Running Man Ball.
Don't even think about it.
Kim Jongkook wants you.
What did you say?
Kim Jongkook, come out.
From the opening
An all-out challenge against Commander Jongkook?
Don't be like that, don't treat
Kim Jongkook hyung like that.
What?
Threatens
You talkative guy.
Not knowing how to continue
Running Man
Scandal
Go back.
I'm even tearing up, this is so funny.
Want me to go back?
Yes.
Ridiculous ending
It ended just like that?
But what's up with you Yongha?
Too shy.
What are you doing?
Just looking at your hair
I know you are a villain.
Cover the eyes and
he's completely alike.
Kwangsoo with the same get-up as Geol Oh
Okay, the place where we're
at today is the Korea House.
Today's landmark
Korea House
This was the private home of
Sayuksin's Pak Paengnyeon ...
* The Sakyusin's were 6 ministers executed by
King Sejo in 1456 for plotting to assassinate him.
... who was a scholar during King Sejong's reign.
This place Ia an attraction for
tourists from other countries.
An average of 100,000 foreign tourists
experience Korea's traditional culture here
Directly experience Korea's culture
and the myriad of flavors of it.
Today, we are here to cook as well.
So we're learning it here.
Where did you learn to cook?
So noisy.
Running Man
Korean food project
What're you doing?
A no retreat cooking battle
Let's have a taste of Jihyo's cooking.
This is special sauce.
A professional group of foreign judges
The conclusion is?
Oh no, no more special sauce.
In a while
Cooking competition
Looking at Jihyo ...
You can see she did some
research on fashion recently.
It's starting to snow and
Jihyo wears such thin clothes
When she arrived ...
... I thought she was a Dracula.
So it's not Dracula but biker fashion?
My name is ...
Blank~pire(?)
* Blank-pire instead of Vampire
A few days ago, Jihyo
noona gave me a call.
She's saying the trend nowadays is her
and asking me to trust and follow her.
Really?
Yeah ~
Jihyo?
She said she wants to
start a swear words line.
... swear words line.
A very smooth frame expert Kwangsoo
Gathering everyone who swears?
Ah, really.
Let's first welcome our guest for today.
Please come out.
Now part of the family
Lizzy
How do you do?
Oh, Nichkhun.
Today's guest
compliments the snow well
Nichkhun
Nichkhun has been to
Running Man before.
Nichkhun participated at the Science Center
Yes ~
Nichkhun suffered a lot during that time.
Were you alright the next day?
I was okay.
Ah, really?
Yes, I slept for 14 hours
before waking up.
Running Man's recordings
are nicknamed the Deep Sleep
14 hours, looks like
that's not good either.
So I must definitely win today.
I heard we must wear hot pants.
Every time I hear those
two words I start coughing.
I wear hot pants every week.
I'm feeling very happy that
Nichkhun is here with us today.
I hope to get more shots with the both of us.
I'm going to Thailand for a fan meeting.
* Nichkhun is from Thailand
Really?
So if I appear often with Nichkhun ...
Fans from Thailand
are you seeing this?
Is that so?
I heard a rumor.
What kind of rumor?
At Apgujeong ...
I heard Jongkook hyung booked ...
... an eyelid enlargement
surgery next week.
Before going to Thailand
a hasty eyelid surgery?
Cut eyelids
Talkative Jongkook becomes
mute in front of Kwangsoo's framing
Anyway, after recently getting
a hair perm, he has changed.
I've heard of this change.
But Jongkook...
won't only concentrate on his appearance
What concerns him the most
is the Running Man's name-tag
Yah, it's Kim Jongkook.
Today
Running Man
First time in history
Just stay there.
Chaser
Jongkook
Running Man
It's Kim Jongkook ~
Kim
Jongkook
Running
Man
Here is the unbelievable 1:9
We have entered the room.
But this mic...
The ambiance is a little...
Is this a hidden camera?.
Suspicion
Who is it this time? Nichkhun... are you?
Starting off with suspicions
No, I don't know.
Puzzled
Lizzy, don't you know?
I don't know anything.
We're all trying to avoid it.
Stopping suspicion in it's tracks
the innocent Lizzy
What is it?
Today is also a 1:9 match up.
The main lead today is HaHa.
You knew about the
mission from the start.
I really didn't, really didn't.
But HaHa didn't know about it either
Isn't it to make HaHa
oppa's heartbeat increase?
This is too serious, Jihyo.
Causing Song Jihyo to experience
seduction in 10 seconds or something.
Would you like to go crazy together?
I must start courting girls.
Bad Boy Haroro
Using HaHa's strong points, if
HaHa wins, only he gets a ball.
HaHa
Running
Man
Using HaHa's strong
point(?) to fight it out
If HaHa loses, the other 9
members get Running Balls.
If HaHa wins only he gets a ball
otherwise the others get one
What is HaHa's forte? His forte?
With HaHa you'll have ...
Very curious about HaHa's strong point
... a knowledge battle.
Knowledge
battle
This is the funniest thing I've
heard all year, really now.
Out of all things today,
this is the funniest.
The most, most ...
Why don't you give us the ball first
before we start, give us the ball first.
No worries
Why don't we try it out then?
I will let you know the
meaning of being shamed.
Taunting
Nothing to say
Do we all have to win?
I will tell you the rules.
HaHa will be giving
the questions himself.
Mobilizing all of HaHa's knowledge
Giving questions himself
Really, he's giving the questions?
The nine of you will win if you
answer 5 out of 9 questions correct.
Answer 5 or more of HaHa's
questions correct and they win
It's also impossible to win
HaHa on every question.
Some of us are also feeling nervous.
Tremors
Jumpy
Shudder
Why are you looking at me, hyungnim?
The nervous(?) Monday Couple
The things I don't know about ...
... HaHa doesn't know either.
I'm sorry, but ...
... the things I don't know
about HaHa will never know.
Now I don't need anybody
else, only Jaesuk will do.
We can test HaHa's level of knowledge
by giving him a knowledge quiz.
HaHa, go over there.
The question is too easy.
Hyung, getting mistakes on
purpose is not allowed.
It will be very easy today.
Okay, first question.
Which is the day with the
longest night in the year?
Isn't it winter's day.
It's not winter's day...
Why?
Winter solstice.
Kwangsoo, don't laugh if
you didn't know the answer.
Don't laugh Blank Jihyo.
Why not?
Don't laugh if you're unsure.
Kwangsoo, you knew the answer?
Of course.
... acting
Fake ...
There are some people
here who didn't know too.
Some people are awkward but still enjoying it
Next question.
Who is the mother of Yul Gokyil?
Shinsa Imdang.
* Korean calligraphist, poet and mother
of the Confucian scholar Yul Gokyil
HaHa
correct
He's pretty smart.
When did I turn clever?
Answering 1 question
and becomes arrogant
When did he turn clever?
He became clever?
He's pretty smart.
Next question.
In the tale of Shim Cheong, the place
where she drown herself was at?
Lake Park.
Ah, what was it again?
Hodangsu...ahh...
You're saying Hodangsu?
Ah, wait.
The correct answer is Indangsu
It was 300 something.
Just tell me the consonants.
It's ieung.
* Korean consonant 'ieung' is written as ㅇ
Really?
Yes.
What I read was something else.
You are talking about Shim
Cheong, right? The blind dad?
And then she drown herself.
That's right.
With rice bags ~
It's not that she throw herself
whilst holding the rice bag.
Awkwardness
What kind of books have you studied
Gary, sorry.
Eungdangsu.
It's not Eungdangsu.
Wrong
It's not that.
What? Yongdangsu.
Isn't it Imdangsu?
Answer
Indangsu
Isn't it?
We have done a few test questions.
Now HaHa is going to come up
with some questions for us.
In the next 30 minutes
He'll come up with his own questions
I understand.
Very good.
The 1:9 match begins now.
HaHa
Running Man
Based on knowledge ...
easily handled person is ...
... Kwangsoo, Gary and Jihyo.
Kwangsoo
The easily tackled
3-person gang?
Gary
Jihyo
The person who is the
hardest to deal with ...
I'm most worried about Joongki.
If we competed on general knowledge,
I might as well not have any.
Ah, what questions is he going to ask?
From movies ...
He always watches movies.
Or something to do with Running Man.
Bob Marley, he likes Bob Marley.
Bob Marley ~
Reggae ~
If Jamaica and Reggae are mentioned,
the answer would be Bob Marley.
Brain at full throttle
HaHa's 32 years of knowledge
The 9 members
area of specialization
Carefully matching
the quiz questions
With confidence
HaHa
Running Man
The battle of knowledge starts
Why is he taking so long?
HaHa you are not important to us.
Yes, I know.
I can't wait for you I
almost died just now.
Let's start the first question.
The questions are based on
HaHa's area of knowledge.
These are really only known to me.
They're not questions from smart phones?
Or the internet, right?
General knowledge.
Okay.
Who should we choose first?
The culprit Jaesuk that always
treats me like I'm easily bullied.
Me?
I wanted to come out to answer now.
You come out.
Of course.
Why don't you hurry up, you.
Knowledge battle
HaHa
Jaesuk
I'll give you a hard one.
Do that.
For Jaesuk hyung, my general
knowledge isn't enough anyway.
I must come up with something
that even if the answer is correct ...
... it must be shameful.
Anyway
As long as 5 get it wrong
Strategies to discredit the opponent
It must be weird if you get it wrong
and even weirder if you get it right.
Yoo Jaesuk.
Yeah.
Difficulty level of 4 stars.
Okay.
Difficult level of 4 stars?
The category is ...
Hurry up.
... movies.
Okay.
Jaesuk, didn't we already guess a
question would come from movies?
I really love movies.
It's starting.
Everyone keep quiet.
When Yoo Jaesuk's
wife doesn't know ...
... he closes the room door.
Never failing to do so everyday at 4 AM.
Collecting all magazines and
broadcasts since his college days.
In the adult film that
Yoo Jaesuk watches ...
... what is the name of the
female lead in "Emanuelle"?
* Emanuelle = French erotic movie from 1974
Is it a quiz? Or an exposure?
I... now...
I have to answer this?
Jaesuk, you have to answer it.
If I answer this wouldn't that
mean I'm admitting to it?
You just admitted to it.
You know the answer?
Do you not know it?
I know ~
I know it, but not from
watching the movie.
So you must've watched on TV?
Answer me, quickly.
Even if I get it right, everyone
please don't misunderstand me.
Jaesuk claiming it is
common knowledge(?)
Even if it's shameful, I will answer it.
This person, during our school days ...
... she taught us something we shouldn't
have known when we were students.
This...
I must get it right?
Quickly say it~
Sylvia Kristel.
* Silvia Kristel (born September 1952)
is a Dutch actress, model and singer
Sylvia Kristel.
Correct
So cool ~
Getting it right only
damages his reputation
And what did you get?
What do you get from answering it?
Yah... really now...
HaHa
Running Man
Right answer with many bruises
Yah... HaHa is really...
Noona ...
Noona is old now, right?
I really liked noona.
Please come next week, next week.
Sylvia Kristel noona.
Next up is... Nichkhun.
It can't be Nichkhun.
Already shaming Jaesuk(?)
Definitely won't let Nichkhun off easily
For Nichkhun, it must be
that kind of category.
Khun ...
... do it.
Looks like Nichkhun doesn't
have much confidence
You can do it.
Nichkhun's category is regarding broadcasts.
Discomfort
Recently in Running Man ...
in Running Man ...
This type of question ...
Causing a public discussion because her
weight doesn't match with her profile.
What is Song Jihyo's weight?
Hey, how would he know that?
This is too ridiculous.
How would he know that?
Why ask
about me?
Because during the broadcast there were some
captions that started a heated response.
197.2 kg.
Jihyo's weight is 52.2kg.
Why did you bring that
up, it's all in the past.
Wave of anger
Weight, that's really hard.
Then I'll give you 3 chances.
49 kg.
Wrong
You have 3 tries.
Anxious
Can I carry her?
Okay, that's not a problem.
Not okay
Can't you change the question instead?
The irritated
Monday
Boyfriend
Powerful
The couple that change variety
into a movie
Displeased
Omo ~
Shy...
Weighing...
Acts like he
doesn't see it
Jihyo, are you that happy?
Look at Gary's expression.
But
Just by doing that...
How much does
she weight?
Ah Jihyo, we were just discussing ...
... that Jihyo really judges
other by their looks.
From what I know, apart from Gary's
looks, she's satisfied with the rest.
Apart from his looks the perfect
Monday Boyfriend...(?)
I have an answer.
55 kg.
She's not that heavy.
Yah, Jihyo ....
Jihyo, why are you looking so frustrated?
She bites her finger
Jihyo, you're 55 kg.
The feeling is pretty similar
to when I carry Jo Kwon.
Oh, the same as Jo Kwon.
Yah, why are you like that too?
An angry accusation(?)
I'm sorry.
Now for the last chance
Jihyo's weight
Can he guess it correctly?
51.5 kg.
Wrong
What is this? Why?
But how heavy is she?
52.5 kg.
It was close. Ah...
A question that fans
the flames(?) of Jihyo's anger
Jihyo is really frightening right now.
Look at her, didn't you see it?
A fired up(?)
re-enactment
This is really no joke.
Noona, I'm sorry.
This kind of thinking(?) Not bad HaHa
The weight that day wasn't real, right?
That day's weight was
really not the real one.
Ah, I didn't think so.
How many kg is your shoes?
3 kg.
Emphasis
What about your overalls?
2 kg.
Next up, Lizzy.
HaHa's 3rd choice Lizzy
Lizzy, fighting.
Lizzy, didn't we discuss a lot just now?
Oppa ~
Lizzy's specialty
strong aegyo
Okay Lizzy.
The category is ...
... music.
A person ~
Lizzy, you know this.
Running Man members'
predictions are spot on
What is this?
Nothing ~
What is the music-related question?
He really likes Bob Marley.
A Bob Marley question
Sukjin's prediction
If he mentions anything about Jamaica ...
Is it that question?
... without doubt the answer is Bob Marley.
Reggae is Bob Marley.
Jamaica ...
As expected
Spot on prediction
Let's say for example Bob Marley ...
HaHa's sure kill knowledge "Bob Marley"
Lizzy is still young, she shouldn't know this.
HaHa believed that
the young Lizzy wouldn't know this
Accurately seeing through HaHa the 9 members
Celebratory mood
In the end, all your knowledge
is in the grasp of our hands.
Jamaica could be something else as well.
The father of music ...
A name that spreads the fame of Reggae.
Lizzy ...
Bob ...
Ah... could it be...?
... Marley?
Bob Marley.
HaHa's shallow knowledge is
seen through by the members
As expected, all your knowledge
is grasped within our hands.
The match against HaHa's knowledge
HaHa
Running Man
1 to 2, currently it's 1 to 2.
Next up is ... Song Joongki.
The 4th contestant is Song Joongki
Ah, I feel burdened.
You have to win this.
Difficulty level, 4 stars.
The theme is ...
... politics.
You know about politics?
How can it be?
I don't know much about politics.
A word which is the opposite
of presidential election.
What?
The opposite of...?
This is a question on politics?
You're the only one
with the nonsense?
To win I have no choice but
to come up with nonsense.
Against Brain Joongki he
can only use this method
Is this even a question on politics?
Yah, is this politics?
If it's not politic, then what is it?
I'm really going crazy.
The presidential elections?
Give me a hint please.
Try telling him he's handsome.
Handsome HaHa hyung.
How handsome?
It is ...
Hint
... a lot more childish than you think.
So it's that one.
You know it?
Ah, so childish.
Joongki, it's very childish.
Answer ~
Does our brain Joongki
know the answer?
The opposite of 'Presidential election' ...
... the sitting president.
* 'Election' sounds like 'stand' in Korean
Little Presidential election.
Wrong.
The opposite of 'presidential election'
is 'the sitting president'.
Ah, so childish.
More childish than you could imagine
Collapsed
It makes me nervous.
How can you possibly use
that as a politics question?
Ah, what a shock.
HaHa
Defeated with my strategy
Running Man
A city man.
Sukjin
Correct
HaHa
Running Man
Seoul Broadway Station.
HaHa
Running Man
Jongkook
Wrong
HaHa
Running Man
If Kwangsoo and Jihyo
fail then HaHa wins.
Both of them need to pass
in order for us to win.
Next person ...
This is making me crazy.
... Song Jihyo.
We're screwed ~
They already lost spirit?
So if I get it wrong then oppa
will get the Running Ball?
Exactly.
Then let Kwangsoo go first.
Acts clueless Pass?
You can't do that.
Jihyo, you can do it.
This guy completely set
up his question as traps.
Jihyo, please get it right, please.
What's the topic?
Running Man.
Question topic
also
<Running Man>
Running Man?
At that time you were a bit blank so
I don't know if you still remember.
I'm curious, that's why I'm asking.
What is it?
In the Design Fair week.
During Song Joongki's
hidden camera ...
Because Kwangsoo got
the correct answer ...
Oh, that one.
... Joongki's fans sent him 100 hateful notes.
What was the answer to that question?
You know what it is, right?
Blank~
Kwangsoo ...
Sept 26's broadcast
Pygmalion.
Song Joongki ...
Pygmalion effect.
Hyung, I haven't finished answering.
Which lead to Joongki's fans sending hateful notes
Kwangsoo answering incident
Pygmalion ...
What is this.
... effect?
Blank Jihyo do you still remember this?
You think that because I looked
blank I wouldn't remember?
Jihyo you know it, right?
Give him a surprise.
You know, right?
I'll 'seriously give you a surprise.
That's right ~
That's right, give him a surprise.
If you get it wrong, you know
how shameful that will be?
Then if I get it correct them you
will have to get blown 3 times.
What, you want to fight?
No.
Jihyo ... do it.
Bet is on Blank Jihyo's self confidence
Just say it, you know it already.
Pygmalion effect.
Correct
Because of Blank Jihyo...
gets blown 3 consecutive times
That's right Jihyo.
Happy ceremony dance
Jihyo ...
... you dance like this.
So you can be like that too.
Year end award show
Blank Jihyo's ceremony
I'm so happy 'cause
I answered correct
4 vs 4 now.
Tied
HaHa
Running Man
Lastly Kwangsoo ...
Last participant
Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo fighting.
Fighting.
A Running Ball runs towards Kwangsoo
Will Kwangsoo get it wrong
and HaHa receive the Running Ball?
Or will everyone
except HaHa receive Running Balls?
HaHa
Running Man
Last question
Question topic ... acting.
Acting ~
Anticipating HaHa's
question about acting
As an actor ...
... in order to act out a certain character
... in order to act out
a certain character
... the person will use this
certain person's mask.
Wearing a mask?
The person will use this
certain person's mask.
Persona
The Mask presented to satisfy
the demands of the situation or
the environment, and not representing
the inner personality of the individual
What is the word for that?
What did you say?
Never heard of
Do you know?
That's my first time hearing it too.
Experienced Blank Jihyo's first time
hearing this unfamiliar question
Do you know the answer to this?
Of course I do.
Are you sure you know?
I'm using the word that my
actor friends always use.
Give us a hint.
If I give you a hint then I'll lose.
Quickly on his knee
Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo, don't do that.
Hey, if you're going to kneel then
at least kneel with both knees.
It looks like you're proposing, you
might as well get on both knees.
That's proposing, proposing.
Yah, I don't want you to kneel ...
... tell your leader to come out.
If Jongkook won't kneel, then I won't tell you.
Hyung, please come out.
Ah seriously, what is this?
He just needs both knees to touch
the floor, then I'll give you the hint.
Why do I have to kneel? Kneel for what?
For the hint.
Please hurry hyungnim.
You should know how important
it is to get the Running Balls.
This is too burdensome for me.
Just pretend it's like an exercise
and bend your knees once.
That's right, just pretend it's an exercise.
The last question's hint
relies on Jongkook's knees
Let me make your heart feel better.
Can you please pick this up.
This should make you feel better.
I'll be standing here and then you
knock my knees from the back.
Ah, yes.
Knock
Commander kneels
in front of Haroro
Feels good
Jongkook gets humiliated
for the sake of the team
Kwangsoo good job.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Give us the hint.
Hint is ...
... 4 syllables.
I seriously don't know.
What kind of hint was that?
Ah, I know what it is.
Did Gary figure out the answer?
Then if Kwangsoo gets it
wrong, give Gary a chance.
I'm serious.
Gary knows, he knows.
I'll give you 50 chances.
Just tell us the first syllable.
I won't ask anything else.
Pae ~
Gary, do you know?
Seems different from mine.
What did you think it was?
I thought it was "Pantomime."
As expected
What's a Pantomime?
I'm sorry ~
Pantomime? Ah, seriously.
I was thinking of this.
How can you not even know the basics?
5, 4 ...
Wait, I'm going to answer.
Kwangsoo must guess correctly ...
... for them to get Running Balls
Persona.
When acting in a film ...
... and they show a different expression.
Does Kwangsoo know that 'persona' is the answer?
Per ...
No way...?
Pernisim ~
Wrong
HaHa wins
The 9 members failed
to get Running Balls
Is it Pathos?
Isn't it Pathos?
Pathos:
The arousing of feeling
of pity and sorrow
HaHa wins.
1:9 competition HaHa wins
Thanks for the hard work.
Ah, I lost to HaHa hyung.
Losing to HaHa is …
all members’ big humiliation
But there is still
an unique mission
waiting for the members
We've all put on the chef uniform.
So are we going to cook?
In Korea House ...
.... we've set up a traditional Korean food tasting
experience for the visitors in this Experience Hall.
Ah, is that so?
Today everyone will have the challenge
of making traditional Korean food.
I'm confident.
After making the meal, the judges will rate it.
Foreign judges who are passionate about Korean food will rate it
The team with most points ...
... gets Running Balls.
Oh okay.
The team with most points
will receive Running Balls
I've never cooked before.
This is like a game made for us.
Full of ...
... confidence
Ah, I wasn't going to
brag about my son.
Please tell us.
This morning I heard some dok-dok sound.
Yes?
So I went out to see what was going on.
My kid was ...
... making full course Korean
dish with Goo Jeolpan.
Exaggerates
How old is your kid now
to know how to cook?
Bragging about his 9 years old son?
You don't know what kind of kid my son is.
What kind of kid?
Because his dad is tired ...
... he starts his part time job
at 2 AM as a substitute driver.
2nd exaggeration
Receives good reactions
on bragging about his kid
Aigoo, that was funny.
That's a kid worth bragging about.
What kind of dishes are we making today?
The dishes covered in front
of you are the ingredients.
Yes.
You'll use these as the
main ingredients today.
The cooking time will be 40 minutes.
40 minutes?
That's too little.
Then let us choose our
ingredients in front of us.
I'll choose one.
I want to choose something like chicken.
We'll choose this one.
Please do.
Choose carefully.
Yellow
Team
Decision made
Once you pick it up you can't change.
Just choose this since we
don't know what it is anyways.
Red
Team
Also decision made
Should we choose the bigger one?
No, this one.
Why?
Jongkook choosing that one without knowing?
Why do we have to choose that one?
We should choose this one, it's bigger.
Immediate suppression
3 members from the team said choose that
one sand he's still choosing the other one.
That team, seriously.
Khun, just choose whichever one you want.
Just choose that one.
This one, right?
Nichkhun agrees with Jongkook
Khun, even you're like that.
Thai Prince scared of
Commander?
You don't have to be scared of him.
Khun, don't be scared.
Yellow Team will reveal first.
1, 2, 3.
Oh, octopus.
Octopus is delicious.
Fresh
octopus
It's really fresh.
It's still alive.
Red Team's main ingredient is?
1, 2, 3.
Chicken ~
Oh, this is good.
The ingredient Jongkook wanted
I hope it's meat.
If it's a meat it will be just great.
Will it be meat like Jongkook wished for?
1, 2, 3.
Meat prize
Celebrates
Meat is relatively easier to cook
results in a celebratory atmosphere
What are the ingredients that weren't chosen?
King crab
It's still alive.
How is this alive?
It's really alive.
I'm letting you take a look.
Blank Jihyo's voice is really loud
The last one...
Jihyo ...
It's a pumpkin.
pumpkin
Ah it's really funny.
What is so funny?
It's a pumpkin.
The 19 year old girl that finds even
the movement of tree leaves funny
Lizzy, what is so funny?
We'll time 40 minutes starting
now, so you must move fast.
The time limit
is 40 minutes
Let's go ~
Each team goes
to the assigned counter
We are cooking here.
Korean food competition
We can't do a very ordinary dish.
Red
Team
Discussing menu
We need to come up with a new idea ...
... to get high marks.
So what should we do?
I've done Ddeok Kalbi in the past.
* Ddeok Kalbi = Minced beef patties similar to burger
Then let's do chicken Kalbi.
Chicken Kalbi
Using chicken meat to make patties?
Chicken Ddeok Kalbi.
This is better, it won't be too spicy.
Red
Team's
menu
Chicken
Ddeok Kalbi
If it's too spicy, then it won't be good.
We must make ...
Octopus
Yellow
Team
Menu discussion
... the most traditional Korean flavor.
That sort of flavor that's refreshing and spicy.
Let's do something like soup.
Sujebi.
* Sujebi = Hand torn noodle soup
Kimchi and octopus sujebi.
Good, it's settled.
Yellow
Team's
menu
Kimchi and octopus Sujebi
Although Korean beef is the best,
but cattle beef is also very delicious.
What's cattle beef?
This is cattle beef.
Female cows are dairy cows,
while male cows are cattle cows.
Of course female cows are dairy cows.
Could it be that female
cows aren't dairy cows?
Cattle
cows:
Cows that are raised for their meat,
male dairy cows that don't give milk
Didn't he ask what
cattle cows are?
Doesn't our country have
cattle beef and Korean beef?
There are many who eat cattle
beef because it's delicious too.
Foreigners in general don't
really like soup dishes.
Then let's stew it.
Let's begin to stew the meat.
The seasoning sauce is
the most important thing.
Who'll make the sauce.
Blue
Team's
menu
Cattle beef stew
I'll do it, I'll make the sauce.
First chop this up then
add the ingredients.
Now the actual
cooking starts
You try it.
Okay.
Can you do it well?
Twist
Of course.
Just look at her.
It's too awkward for a 19 year old girl...?
Twist~
Incorrect...
without any scruples
Omo ...
Thump
Chop
Doing everything that has to be done
while hesitantly bumbling her way through
We must definitely get the Running Ball.
Of course, no problem.
Back and forth
between an aggressive and cowardly girl
Is the chicken still alive?
What is it?
I touched the chicken's neck.
This skin was all stripped off by you.
No matter what Lizzy completed
the preparation of the chicken
I'm so scared.
Now it's time to mince the lean meat
Half of our cooking is spent mincing things.
Ingredients must be minced very fine
It's done ~
Mixing the ingredients well
Add the chicken thigh and the breast meat.
Putting too much garlic will make it spicy.
Oppa, do you need the rice cake?
You go cut the rice cake.
Okay.
The egg yolk also has to be put in, right?
Why must the egg yolk be put in?
It'll taste good just put it.
Red
Team's
debate
To put the egg yolk?
Or not the egg yolk?
It's a little ...
We must put egg yolk.
Convinced
Right, we must mix it together.
When cooking, shouldn't
it be put in together?
Finally the yolk goes in
It's not like this.
Vaguely~
No, it must be put in.
That's salt, wait a while.
Lizzy is seriously cutting the rice finely
Salt can't be added with sugar.
Oppa ...
Why can't salt be added with sugar?
... how is this size?
Why did you cut up all the rice cakes?
Lizzy, the rice cake should not be chopped.
Where do we use it when it's that finely cut?
Why did you cut up the rice cake?
Sukjin told me to cut it.
Hyung, why did you tell Lizzy
to cut up the rice cake?
It has to be mixed together.
Mix together with what?
Isn't it Ddeok Kalbi?
It isn't called "Ddeok Kalbi" because of that.
Then how should this rice cake done?
It's a possibility, but
rice cake has to be served separately
The rice cake is the last to be put
into the pan to be fried together.
Ah, that's Ddeok Kalbi.
Really?
It's not called Ddeok Kalbi
because they're mixed together.
Is that so?
Embarrassingly pressing
together the cut-up rice cake
Jaesuk.
No, hyung.
If it's like that, then let's do two,
this and that, this is made by me.
Making one portion with rice cake
and one without
Two types are made
Alright ~
The blood from the meat is all released.
Now put the leek and garlic in for awhile.
In the midst of preparing the vegetables neatly
Chief Khun is skilled with knives
Oh~
Proceeding thoroughly...
The preparation of the vegetables
and cattle beef is finished
Do we have to put a little something
to tenderize the meat like wine?
Jihyo... Jihyo's coordi might have some.
* Coordi = Coordinator (term used for coordinator/stylist etc)
Blank~
Use corn syrup to gently soak it will do.
Really?
Corn syrup?
Hyung, Gary hyung said to use corn syrup.
Corn syrup... with the meat?
Really?
Yes, you put corn syrup into the meat.
Are you sure?
Yes, it'll become tender.
Into the meat..
put some corn syrup?
Do I put in the water?
Yes, we have to start cooking.
How much?
Just put in a lot will do.
I put in a lot.
That's not right.
Put a bit more.
You can't put too much water.
Then I'll add some corn syrup.
No, wait a while.
It's not like this.
Blue
Team's
debate
Add corn syrup when cooking meat?
We cook this first.
Finally explodes
Argghh, really.
I won't put in all of it.
No, you take a look at this.
We have to put garlic, right?
You don't do anything for now.
The garlic's already put in.
Put a little less water to steam it first.
This is steamed so put in this much.
This has already become soup, the meat
stock will all be gone when cooked.
Endless
Then the meat stock will
just become meat broth.
arguing
But you can't put in this much water.
Shall I put in the potatoes?
Put them in.
Why do you guys keep putting things in?
We have to cook the potatoes.
But we have to steam the meat first.
Using their mouths to finish the cooking
The potatoes cook the slowest and
that broth is not to be poured away.
It's not like that.
I'm not sure and I don't dare to say
anything, but it's not done like this.
It's like this.
In the end the pot is just full of potatoes
Hyung, go cut up that potato.
Cut it here directly?
Huh
Cutting potatoes in the pot
Yah ...
Yah, cut it up out there and then put it in.
The kalbi stew...
can it be completed well?
Why are you putting it inside to cut?
Meanwhile
Yellow
Team
Preparing the octopus
Use salt water to wash it.
Then ...
Do we still have to strip off the skin?
We must remove the skin.
We can't strip it off.
Huh?
Octopus skin... peeled off?
There's little time but still insisting on that
No, this skin is very tough.
Why are you peeling the octopus skin?
It doesn't have to be peeled off, right?
Who told you to peel it off?
Blank Jihyo noona told us to.
Noona, stop it already.
Hmpf~
It just should be
eaten like this
This skin, you see it's
already become squid.
Slippery~
Then we just won't peel off the skin.
We'll boil the water first ...
.... the broth has to be simmered out.
That's right ~
Anchovy soup ~
How much water must I put in?
The volume of water must
be carefully coordinated
Is it too much?
It's not.
We have to put a bit more.
Potatoes ~
Sujebi must have potatoes.
Where are the potatoes?
Hurry to that team and
get a few potatoes.
Finish cutting and then put
them in, why cut them inside?
Blue Team is in the midst of debating
There are some people that
may also like whole pieces.
That atmosphere
is a little ...
It's not even cooked properly.
Why did you put it in?
Stealthy
Jongkook felt unhappy from the start
I feel this really can't be done
like this ,we must take the meat.
Can the potatoes
be taken from here?
I did it in the past.
Stare
What?
Now the atmosphere here is rather sensitive.
Why are you here?
I'm just going to the toilet.
Kwangsoo, hand me the corn syrup.
Hyung can you do this?
Can't go back empty-handed
Yah!
Frightened
What are you doing?
This?
What? What? What?
It's very sensitive now.
Why don't you say something.
If you're not careful you'll die.
Say something ~
Seriously, if you're not careful you'll die.
He didn't catch the right timing
Why don't you say something.
What?
Pepper ~
Yes, what about pepper?
Potatoes
Bring the pepper over.
Swoop~
If I want it...
there's only this method
Yah, you let go first.
Hyung, give me a potato.
Please give me a potato.
Do you think I would give it to you?
♪ Only using words that love you ♪
You can't even sing the lyrics correct.
Ah... I'm becoming like this to get one potato...
Even so that's still Jongkook ♥
In the end a potato is received
Red
Team
Proceeding with the preparation
Lizzy, turn on the fire.
Yes, chef.
Everything is going on the right track
Everything's going smoothly.
I haven't been cooking for so long.
This is precisely the Joy of cooking.
When other people eat what I cook,
I feel happy when they eat well.
Wow, it should be very delicious.
Broiled to a brownish color
Dak Ddeok Kalbi
ladled onto a plate
Proud
Pour a little fructose syrup here and
pour a little condiment sauce there.
Pouring sauce
for the meat
Let's have a look this is.
How's the taste?
Salty
It's just soy sauce.
Why are you using that to taste it?
Whohoo... Salty...
We can't use this to make sauce.
Thinking it was sauce they almost used it
How to make sauce?
Urgently making sauce
Soy sauce + corn syrup
+ flour?
So we must make the sauce.
Try it.
And the taste?
Is it weird?
If we tell by his expression it's a little bit...
Should we put red pepper paste?
It's useless even if we put in.
Can't taste it~
It's sweet and salty...
It's not so bad.
Not so bad.
Not so bad...?
How is it?
It's bad ~
Honest
It's bad
Is it bad?
Very frank.
Eng?
Quickly stir it.
Sukjin
put yolk into the sauce?
Is that egg?
Exhales...
It looks delicious, really.
Can the Red Team make a good sauce?
We must make delicious sauce.
Pepper powder
Just use a small amount of pepper powder.
+ corn syrup
Garlic's smell is too strong.
+ chopped garlic
It's okay we must mix it all.
Hyung try tasting this sauce.
Time to check the sauce for Kalbi Stew
Oh, it's weird ~
You used his finger to taste it.
It's okay, we're not strangers.
Now they're like a family who uses their fingers to taste
Is there something that I missed?
Not too sweet?
Anxious~
Yes.
Okay?
It's suitable to Nichkhun's taste
Yeah, I like it.
Who made it?
Hyung.
Hyung made it.
Glaring...
Hyung, don't be too quick to judge.
Now we start it.
Let's marinate the beef now.
Take out the beef.
Now?
Take this out?
It isn't cooked?
Take it out now.
There's no time.
If we boil it too long, it'll become hard.
Don't care if Jongkook accept it or not they still do it
No, it won't.
Is the beef
going to be tender?
Quickly take it out, why are you so slow?
Don't pour all of it out, do it little by little.
Use this to pour it.
I understand, okay chef.
Actually they should put all the sauce to be mixed
Should we put the beef one by one
into the sauce, so they can be mixed?
Marinate with a small amount like this
Don't put it into the water, put it on the beef.
Use the chopsticks to put the
beef one by one into the sauce.
Yes, one by one.
I think it's enough, let's boll it again.
How is the taste...?
Hyung, should we slice it with scissors?
I asked before if we
should slice it with scissors.
Now ~
So he appears ...
Hello doctor.
... surgeon Haroro
You will help me.
Yes.
Scissors.
Clamps.
Nurse Khun
Slice it well, don't move.
That's looks hard.
That's big.
Careful
Don't slice all of it.
Hyung, should we try to taste it again?
Okay you try, I'll cut it for you.
Looks like it still hasn't cooked yet
Is it okay?
I said before, it's hard.
It's hard.
I said before, it's hard
Wait until the beef come tender...
I'll pick it for you.
It's okay, why?
Chewing
You look like you're chewing gum.
Didn't I say before that
we should boil it longer.
Let's change dish.
Use only potato and
take out all of the beef.
Kalbi Stew doesn't need beef?
Yellow Team's Sujebi dough
Great skill in
mixing the dough
Sujebi King
Song Takgoo
* Kim Takgoo = Main character in "king of baking"
You're like a chef.
Doesn't hear it...
Like a mixer, we should
mix the dough like this.
Passionate
If we look at it, it looks like you're
making jajangmyun manually.
Joongki, can you hear me?
Kwangsoo cowardly obtained potato
Noona, put in the potato.
The most important thing is the potato.
He shows how to put them in...
Noona, don't let the water splash.
Not interested
Angry
Doesn't care what Kwangsoo says
You both together ...
2 people's world
This kimchi very delicious.
There is garlic in the kimchi,
don't put too much.
It's not much.
Am I invisible?
Finally add dumpling
Stretch it like this.
Piece by piece full of sincerity...
Thinner.
Should we add pepper too?
That's too many, too many.
It looks like too many
Joongki, listen to me.
Everything!!
It's okay.
Full of pepper
Put in spicy kimchi...
Taste it directly
We haven't put in anything.
How's the taste?
It's bland.
Too much water.
No, boil it a
little longer
There's so much water.
So take out some of the water.
Preparing to add pepper powder
So much
You're so noisy.
Too much..
You're noisy, go to that side.
Now we must find way
to bring the taste out.
In no time the soup turned red
Add the octopus.
I'll put it in.
All 3 octopus
We don't slice it?
You must slice it.
Must slice it.
Explode
Yah, you do it.
Kwangsoo
Blank~Jihyo
Joongki
You added too much pepper powder.
It's already wrong.
Just help with what you can do.
Nothing satisfies Kwangsoo
Prepare an egg.
There must be a fresh taste.
Yellow
Team
debate
Add an egg
No!
If we put an egg in, the
taste won't be like this.
So add green onions.
That's right, add a little ...
All of it
Full of green onions too
Okay, time is over.
We're done.
Chicken ddeok kalbi is done
We're done too.
Kalbi stew is also done
Are we really done?
Kimchi and octopus sujebi done
Lastly
The "cooking" finishes like this
Red
Team
Friend rice cake and potato to
to compliment
Ddeok Kalbi
Yellow
Team
Spicy(?)
Octopus sujebi
Blue
Team
Taste of high quality
Kalbi
stew
The result
Which team will get Running Balls?
Each team already finished their dish.
Now it's time to taste it.
There are 5 guests who came to judge.
Please come in.
Hello ~
Introducing the Korean dishes
to 5 foreigners
Nice to meet you, hello.
It's dawn now.
It must be sleeping time.
Thank you, all of you who wanted to come.
Once again, thank you very thank you.
What did he say...?
Our dish is ...
1st challenger
Red
Team
... Chicken Ddeok Kalbi.
Chicken
Ddeok Kalbi
Dak Ddeok Kalbi.
Interest...
Try the sauce.
Korean style sauce.
Try it please.
Dip it.
Joe MacPherson
First judge
(USA) Korean food blogger
The sauce is very delicious.
Ang~
Result
Chicken Ddeok Kalbi's taste is...?
What...?
This expression...
Embarrassed
His face turned red.
Hasn't said anything yet
Sauce is life ~
Simon
Martina
couple
(Canada)
UCC Star examiner
It's okay, don't dip it.
Martina is trying the sauce
Sukjin, did you make the sauce?
The sauce is really a downfall?
Don't dip into the sauce.
Dip in the sauce.
The sauce, a lot, a lot.
A lot ~
Hooked~
How is...
The taste of Chicken Kalbi?
When judging, you should use a lot of sauce.
What is this?
Ehm~
It's done.
Can't tell by Simon's expression
Jennifer
(USA) Korean food evangelist
Silently... Drinking water
She drank the water.
It's a little salty.
Truthfully the sauce is the problem...
Rob
(Canada) Korean food blogger
Liar ~
Can Red Team's dish ...
satisfy the judges?
Yellow Team
Kimchi and
octopus Sujebi
Hello ~
Our dish's name is kimchi ...
... octopus
... flour.
Flour?
Yes, flour.
She can speak Korean well.
This time 5 people try it all together
Oh, it's tense.
Eat well.
Is this taste suitable with their appetite?
Potato ~
Potato.
Very delicious.
Look at their expressions.
Are you okay?
Nod
Simon are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
Another bite
Perfectly cooked.
Made a perfect dish?
Very delicious.
The egg is delicious?
It's not "Egg" but "Very".
It's a little bit bland.
It's not salty?
Not salty.
Marinated it a lot
but to much water
Yes, Jennifer I love you.
Excuse
Salty and spicy is not healthy.
It's just that the spicy flavor is a little lacking.
It was made with water and kimchi, right?
If the meat was prepared at the beginning
it would probably taste even better.
She knows much more about
Korean cooking than we do.
Tell them to have a drink of water.
Please water, rinse mouth.
So they all can understand him.
Last food.
Blue Team
Kalbi stew tasting starts
Main food.
Main food(?)
Main course ~
What is 'main food'?
You first ...
... special sauce.
Oh no, no more special sauce.
Experience from the Chicken Ddeok Kalbi
sauce must have been quite shocking
Different ~
Not the same sauce.
Okay.
Hey, come on.
Joe takes on the Blue Team's sauce challenge
I'll dip the meat in the special sauce.
...Hmm?
Critical situation
How can the meat be this hard?
He can't even bite the meat.
Joe's face turns red again
Tell him the meat isn't the
main feature of the dish.
He's saying that the meat isn't
the main thing in that soup.
The meat, the kalbi is not the
main part of the kalbi stew?
Steak ...
It's a potato stew.
Potato stew
So he eats a
mouthful of potato
Oh~
What is this reaction?
Compared to the reaction
we got, it seems even worse.
It's delicious.
Simon & Martha couple also tastes it
The steak ... decoration.
The meat is decoration?
Try to make them eat only the potatoes
Only decoration.
First eat a mouthful of potato
The potatoes are very good.
The sauce is good.
Seems to really have a lot of flavor
They have to eat the meat to be fair.
The problem is the meat
No need to.
The meat is not the most important thing.
For kalbi stew, shouldn't the kalbi
be the most important thing?
Simon & Martina couple
challenge eating the meat
Chewing it a little finely
Yeah, it is ...
... gum-style, you know.
Accepting the cheap(?) English very well
Gum style?
You're really too much.
English ...
Yes, I can speak English very well.
Sharp analyzer Jennifer's turn
Jennifer please.
Jennifer is trying the meat first
A lot ~
It's really strenuous to chew the meat.
Ha ha ha, what did she say?
She said it's very hard
to chew the meat
I've eaten well.
The panel's food tasting ends here
Please raise the color of ...
Voting
method
The panel will raise the color of the team
they think cooked the best. Most votes win.
...your chosen team one by one.
First, we'll start from Rob.
1, 2 ...
Don't over do it.
Blue Team's Kalbi Stew?
Yellow Team's Kimchi
and octopus Sujebi?
or
Red Team's Chicken
Ddeok Kalbi?
... 3.
Rob
Yellow
Team
chooses
Kimchi and octopus Sujebi
Yellow
Team
vote
received
Rob chose the Yellow Team.
Next is Jennifer.
The critical expert Jennifer's choice is anticipated
Are you ready?
Jennifer.
1, 2, 3.
She can make Korean food
even better then the members
Jennifer
Blue
Team
chooses
Blue
Team
Kalbi stew
vote
received
Jennifer ~
Next is the Simon and
Martina couple together.
Both of their votes can probably decide the win
1, 2, 3.
The pleasant couples choice?
Octopus Sujebi
Kalbi stew
Yellow
Team
votes
Tied
Blue
Team
Red Team automatically eliminated
Yellow
Team
The points now:
Blue
Team
Tied!
Okay, now it's a tie.
Last is our Joe, who'll he actually choose?
The outcome depends on 'Joe'
Which team will Joe choose?
1, 2, 3.
Beef Kalbi stew?
Kimchi and
octopus Sujebi?
Joe ultimately
chose Blue Team
The four guys are victorious An unexpected result
The delighted 'Rabbit dance' ceremony
Jongkook, Gary, HaHa, Nichkhun
Receive Running Balls
At this time of dawn, we
express our thanks to ...
... the five guests who really
like Korea and Korean food.
Next is hide-n-seek time.
That's right.
Today there's a special rule.
What is it?
Kim Jongkook will be on
the Chasing Team by himself.
Commander
Jongkook
One-man chasing team
If he catches all nine
people by himself ...
... then he alone will
receive a Running Ball.
If the other nine people hide from
him and complete the mission ...
... then the nine people receive a Running Ball.
Won't we be in a position
of absolute advantage?
It's actually not the case.
Truthfully it's actually not
the case ... that's right.
If Kim Jongkook succeeds, then ...
If Jongkook wins
... these six people would just have to
automatically accept the punishment.
Yellow and red team have zero balls
Blue team members
already have balls and will
be exempt from punishment
Ah, that's right ...
... we already have Running Balls.
First I felt that we would be at
a great advantage at 1:9 ...
... but it's very disadvantageous for us.
Now...
the historical
Jongkook 1:9 hide and seek starts
It's here ~
Mission
Team
Instruction
received
Find five missing longevity
pictures and complete the
longevity folding screen.
Mission
Team
instructions
Complete the longevity folding screen
There's ten longevity pictures and we
must locate the five remaining ones.
Pine tree
Fungus
Crane
Turtle
Deer
Find these five
If you find them the screen
should be prepared already.
Fighting, we can do it.
Beat Sparta Kooks for once.
But the
opponent is...
Commander
Sparta.
Jongkook
For the Commander
it's more convenient to be by himself
Today's battle is in a narrow venue...
It's more advantageous for Commander Kook
Yoo Jaesuk ...
... just wait.
Mission Team searches for longevity paintings
Runs alone toward
the top of the hill
Yooruce Willis
...Huh?
Prepares to start and
checks his shoe
Commander
Shocked
Yah, what is this?
Jongkook is there.
What?
I really almost died.
Went to the tiger's lair on his own
You saw Jongkook?
I ran up there to look around
and when I went up ...
... the camera filmed him.
Ringing sounds...!
Ringing sounds.
Sukjin, Jaesuk hurriedly hides under the table
Also Gary ran inside after hearing the sound
Gary ...
He's here...
Commander...!
He he he
A killer smile(?) shows on his face
Gary ...
But the Commander
doesn't know that also Sukjin and Jaesuk are here
Shake
Gary.
I know already.
Gary ...
... let's talk.
Okay.
Really, why is it like this?
Commander
blocks Gary's escape path with chairs
Oh... but it's like this....
Sukjin and Jaesuk may be exposed...
Discovered...
At this time Gary succeeds in escaping
Yooruce Willis also?
Succeeds
in escaping
Escape quickly.
Jaesuk escape.
I'm really going to die
soon, it is too scary.
Sukjin
Meanwhile
Searching the theater
HaHa
Nichkhun
What?
Pine Tree
Take them down.
...Ginseng?
They don't know which is right
Take both away
Very good ... take them both down.
Beep
A siren will ring when a drawing that doesn't
belong with the specified ten pieces is taken
Huh?
This siren sound...?
Joongki?
How come he is so dubious
Oh!
Commander
didn't even notice...?
Could it be because of the dim light?
What's this?
You are here?
Found Joongki
Oh, what is this?
Still holding your mission piece.
Meanwhile Nichkhun
collected a few drawings of the ten needed
However, Commander is here too
Begins with Lizzy
Oppa, Jongkook oppa.
Lizzy
Where are you running to?
Run away ...
Jihyo ...
Commander's lion roar makes you drop...
Let's go, faster.
Jihyo
Flustered
Until now the busy escaping Haroro
Uneasy
...wait...
Come to think of it ...
I ...
Why am I helping these people?
Ah... if this is the case...
Current Running Ball owners are
Jongkook
HaHa
Gary
Nichkhun
So if Mission Team loses, then automatically
Jaesuk Sukjin Joongki Kwangsoo Jihyo Lizzy
punished
I have no reasons to help them.
For Gary HaHa Nichkhun
they won't get punished if Mission Team fails
Those people have no Running Balls.
It's not like I won't see
Jongkook anymore.
Won't it be miserable
when we meet next time?
Why am I like this?
Finally...
The movie game begins
Today's movie
Haroro's Unethical Deal
Great.
The Betrayer played by:
HaHa
As long as I don't get punished.
Haroro...
his dream of
the Unethical Deal
how will it end?
Jaesuk
Searching in another building
Yooruce Willis
This is it.
Right?
It's right
One of the longevity
Fungus
What?
What is this?
Beep
Aigoo, scared me.
This should be the one.
So this is the one.
Bamboo
Huh...
Fungus is the correct one...?
Yooruce Willis
left the correct one and took the wrong piece
Oh, found it?
Why do we need to find so many?
Are they the useful drawings?
Coming ~
Commander's sound is like a curse
He's here
Commander
Not sparing a chance to take a break
Kim Jongkook is here.
Run away in full force
He's here ~
It's Jongkook ~
The Unethical Deal's Haroro's
final action
Hyung, Gary hyung, come over here.
Only called Gary who is in the same situation
Just so
happens
Commander
goes to HaHa and Gary's place
Of all places they are in a dead end
As a rat in a hole
Commander and the Two Kids
and their fate is...?
Hyung, listen to me first.
Why should we help the Mission Team?
Since we won't get punished if we loose.
Won't we be seeing Jongkook in the future?
Ah, of course we will
still see each other.
The unethical deal
We will help hyung.
Tear mt name tag off and
stick it back on again.
To gain trust
Let me help you.
Alright.
Now you trust me, right?
Let me know their locations later.
I am a criminal, how
would I not help you?
Next week after this is broadcasted,
please say something for me.
Alright, I'll help you.
Now who do you want
to capture the most?
First ... we must catch
Nichkhun and Kwangsoo.
Jaesuk can be the last one to be caught.
The unethical deal
established
Get me at the courtyard.
Then ...
You run first and let me get you when
you reach the center of the courtyard.
Naturally... acting...
Here.
Naturally fall down at the
center of the courtyard.
Don't forget the deal
I got it.
For the deal
Gary
Hey, very good, thanks.
The acting is very natural.
Don't forget ...
Torn down.
Those who don't know the truth
Distressing
Ha ha ha...
My scenario...
You got caught?
It's okay, never mind.
Now Gary is the spy in the room...
Ah, I'm really unhappy about this.
Teammates still clap for him without
knowing they are in the dark
Ah, my heart.
But didn't even find one?
Ah, there is nothing over there.
Jaesuk hyung took everything.
Stealthily begins
the spying activity
Yooruce Willis?
You didn't even know he was there.
Wearing a crew's clothes and bag Hiding
How to let Jongkook
know about this...?
Jaesuk's VJ has to be further away.
Seeing you sitting there
will make him realize.
Don't film me ~
Go there ~
Who doesn't know that you
are here to shoot Jaesuk?
Even my mom can recognize you.
Still shooting here?
Kwangsoo, where
is he hiding?
Kwangsoo hides under a table
Uncomfortable
The real race starts now.
Oh boy...
Oddly, the ringing bells disappear...
Walking indoors without shoes with bells
Ah,  it's Kim Jongkook.
Drag
Oppa he is just behind you, behind you.
Extremely nervous
Help me.
What happened?
The Unethical Deal's Haroro enters
Kwangsoo.
Jaesuk ...
Acting
... Kwangsoo got caught.
Tries to lure Yooruce Willis out
Jaesuk hyung ...
Hurry up.
Hyung, I'm fine.
Hey, get it done and over with.
I said to get it done.
What are you doing?
Is HaHa helping Jongkook?
What?
Jaesuk help, HaHa is weird.
Because of Kwangsoo's words
the unethical dealer has to settle aside
Kwangsoo
After an attack from the Unethical Deal
He's coming ~
Jihyo:
Don't show any unnatural movement
I'm talking to myself.
Hyung ...
Why did HaHa treat me like that?
What?
Donghoon hyung why is
he with Jongkook hyung?
* Donghoon = HaHa's real name
Pricking
Jongkook, is Donghoon on your side?
Sukjin:
What?
Is Donghoon on your side?
Pretending
No.
Gary, where
is Nichkhun...?
Over... there
Nichkhun spotted
Sigh
Oh...
Hoo hoo...
The deal has concluded
I saw you because a little was exposed.
Nichkhun
Yooruce
Willis
Playing the detective game well
so far, and still wearing a jacket.
Sukjin:
Really ...
How to inform him
about the location
of Jaesuk?
You caught these popular idols
like that, feeling relaxed now?
Very relaxed, huh?
Sitting over there very comfortably.
Tip-off
Sitting very comfortably?
What is
he saying?
It would be the end...
... if Commander gets the meaning
Swing...
Didn't understand...!!
Wasteful
Hey ...
Yours has to be torn down now.
They are suspecting us.
Tear!!
Hurry and stick it back.
Hyung ...
You don't trust me?
This isn't what
we discussed
Unaware of Yooruce Willis' location
It's a ToSaGuPaeng ending
* ToSaGuPaeng = Get rid of the weak/useless first (Korean saying)
You just stay and don't move.
Confused
...What's in his mind?
The Unethical Dealer Haroro has self-revived(?)
I stuck it back, just ...
Why sticking it back again?
I said everyone is suspecting us now.
I have to catch you first.
Commander worries that the deal
will be found out Decide to force HaHa out
I have to show it to them.
Come over here.
Jaesuk, come help me.
Act more naturally.
Okay, got it.
That kid is weird.
But it still feels fishy
Jaesuk oppa ...
Let me go.
Jaesuk hyung ~
The unethical deal's proposer Haroro
ends up useless
HaHa also got caught.
Their only hope now
Yooruce Willis
You're the only one left, Jaesuk.
Hyung, HaHa seems to be acting.
Fishy
Is this some hidden camera thing?
They must have talked over.
Hey you ...
Which side are you on?
Hyung, why did you do that to me?
What?
Jongkook wanted to tear the name tag,
why did you follow him and help out?
An interrogation atmosphere
You covered my eyes, blocking my sight.
This person ...
Yooruce Willis spotted
Alright, just wait,
Let's go ~
Old enemies
Yooruce Willis
Commander
The winning of the last battle...
Yooruce Willis
Sprints straight
to the building
Isn't it this one?
Being left behind
Got the Fungus drawing again
Is this for the mission?
Let's go for now.
Can't find anything else.
Tiger
Dragon
These are the two false drawings
Deer is correct, this is the right one.
Deer is correct.
The unethical dealer
took the false Ginseng drawing
Huh!
Purposely hung the false drawing
He's acting strange.
Sukjin:
Silence...
Waited at the entrance for quite a while
Fell down
Hyung, what are you doing?
Hyung ...
Plea
Do you have to catch me?
I have thrown away your shoes,
so you won't be able to find them.
Not only yours, also your VJ's.
VJ has no shoes to wear,
please return them to him.
Would I give you time by searching
for your shoes, so you can escape?
How would I run?
You just run.
Run without your shoes.
Last bargain
to escape without shoes
If you are caught ...
... I will tear your name tag.
Really not giving me back my shoes?
Dirty, cobbled road...
To run bare foot ... !
Hyung, you head to that tree.
Once you reach there, I will start chasing.
You mean here?
Nervous
I'm here now.
Chasing
Ah, my feet hurts.
The last hide-n-seek battle
The winner is...?
Reached the jail with the folding screen
Will Jongkook tear down
Yooruce Willis' name tag first
Or will they complete the ten drawings
Rip off
Torn off.
Ah...!
The dragon drawing is still hanging there
It's already ripped off.
Dragon
The collection isn't complete
Mission
Team
Failed
1: 9 mission
Jongkook
Wins
Also for the Unethical Dealers
Winning
Really, these two kids can't be trusted.
Our Jihyo is totally disappointed in Gary.
Including Nichkhun these 4
are freed from punishment
I'm really disappointed in oppa.
Gary, Jihyo was on our side.
Monday Couple ends here.
Jihyo, I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Sulky
Right, you should be on Jihyo's side.
Ah...
Is the ending of the unethical deal
also the end of this love relationship
The cold morning breeze is
nipping at their bare legs
Wear hot pants on streets
Ask for free hugs
Today's
penalty
Arghh, this is so cold.
Go away, Jongkook leave quickly.
Punishment
members
Have 0 Running Balls
Sukjin Jaesuk Jihyo Joongki Lizzy Kwangsoo
Jihyo, the beard suits you.
A group of bearded sisters?
Jihyo's beard
Lizzy's mustache
Go well.
Penalty exempted
Jongkook and
the Two Kids
Broad smiles~
Hey, we need to know the way there.
Searching for the
punishment location
Ah this one, it's clear enough.
Penalty site
of today
Myeongdong
station
Shortest walking distance
takes only 6 minutes
Hyung, so you also know
how to use a smart phone?
Jaesuk:
Modern people have to know how.
Sukjin:
Penalty site reached Myeongdong station
This is really cold, this
punishment is really ...
Where citizens go to school or work
Ask for free hugs
We have to complete this
punishment as soon as possible.
It's too early The street is quiet
Anyone can hug me, anyone please.
Please come and hug us.
It's too cold
Actually those who need
free hugs are...
Running Man
Aigoo, have a nice day aunt.
Let's hug together. This is so cold.
Very cold
Running Man gives each other hugs
Meanwhile...
Kwangsoo on a filming set
With the hot pants...
Confirmed
Ha ha ha
Director Lee Joonki
What is this?
Jung Jinyeong
Ridicule...
All the sunbae's  encouragement
Painful punishment
Seon Wooseon
Embarrassed
Next week
must
get a Running Ball
Hello everyone, this is
Running Man weather forecast.
Running Man weather forecast
It's raining.
Running Man took over the observatory
Rain * Wind * Snow
A 4D full body experience
Running Ball
Who will get it?
Yoo Jaesuk...
Sure enough...
What
is his true self?
Mr. Yoo Jaesuk, you are finished.
Original hardsubs by iSUB
Transcribed by HapB
Color and alignment by SamFive