Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsub by iSUBS
First time on variety TV
Today's destination is
The Republic of Korea's
Performance Art Cultural Center
Sejong Center for the Performing Arts
Going to stand on the stage of dreams
Coming up ...
Strange sounds of bells
coming from nowhere
This eerie sound
What does it mean?
In the end, it's still me.
I thought I could escape this time.
The secret of the bell and
Yooruce Willis' setback
starts now
Gathered at the
Sejong Center
Every Running Man member has
gathered here together day again.
After one week, Jihyo
is back with us again.
Welcome
Let's welcome Running Girl Song Jihyo
Everyone should know that today's destination
is the Sejong Center for Performing Arts.
Today's destination
Sejong Center for Performing Arts
Isn't it amazing?
I've come here two to three times
for a performance before, but ...
The exterior structure
Beautiful design
... I've always been curious about what's inside.
First time ever on variety TV
Exposing it all
I've come here to collect an award before.
Proud
Really?
You're speaking a lot more lately.
You've become a chatterbox.
Moving mouth
Chatterbox Jongkook
The nation's first Muscle MC.
It's very regretful that Kwangsoo
cant' be here with us today ...
Regretful
Due to conflicting schedules
Kwangsoo didn’t come
... due to his conflicting drama schedules.
I talked to him on the phone just now.
Because he couldn't come,
he nearly cried on the phone.
Kwangsoo himself feels even more regretful
He called me too.
Later
Before daybreak
Kwangsoo appears
Hello...
friend...
But why did Kwangsoo come?
Oh, Kwangsoo ...
The moving story of Kwangsoo's return
Although it's a pity, but instead
we have a lot of guests today.
Today's guests are?
You get to find out a different
side of you in variety shows ...
Super idols of k-pop
Jung Yonghwa
T-Ara
Han Eunjung
Jo Kwon
Three of the best idols
are here with us today.
All of you, welcome.
We have Eunjung here with us.
She's a main character in a drama.
The drama just ended,
so she's here with us.
Eunjung's amazing performance
in the SBS drama "Coffee House"
"Coffee House".
First of all ...
Yonghwa and Kwon, you
should just join my team.
Greedy
Pulls Yonghwa and Kwon to is own team
We think that our guests'
views are very important.
What are the idols' thoughts?
Which team do you want join?
I want to join Jaesuk's team.
Jo Kwon
Jaesuk's team
It's because I've watched last weeks' episode.
Jongkook said that he hated the
punishment that was proposed ...﻿
... Muscle No. 28.
Of course.
After watching it, I felt
really annoyed as well.
Reason
Jongkook didn't like Muscle No.28
It's not like that.
So I want to join JaeSuk's team.
Good, what about Yonghwa?
I want to join Jaesuk's team too.
Yonghwa
Jaesuk's team
Why?
Because even if we lose,
you will be very forgiving.
Reason
Thinks Jaesuk will forgive everything
Aigoo, my stomach hurts.
You don't know "Aigoo,
my stomach hurts" ?
Yonghwa can do a really good
imitation of Park Youngkyu.
Yonghwa's
only variety talent
Imitating Park Youngkyu
Show us ~
Just show it to us once, Yonghwa.
Alright, I understand.
Aigoo yah ~
Aigoo yah
My stomach hurts
Good job ~
Yonghwa seemed to be normal but had this side to him
Okay fine, these two can ...
Then Yonghwa and Kwon
will be on my team.
Jo Kwon - Yonghwa
Jaesuk's team
What about Eunjung?
I don't mind.
Eunjung
Really?
Joining Jongkook's team, good.
Jongkook's team
Jaesuk's team
Jihyo Sukjin Kwon Yonghwa
Jongkook's team
HaHa Gary Joongki Eunjung
Today's mission, I said it just now, right?
Warm up mission
You've seen this hat before, right?
You know why this hat is called
"Why did you do that"-hat?
It's a 'couple hat.
Isn't there are a lot of
people down there?
Yeah.
You need to ask a citizen to
wear the couple hat with you.
After you put on the hat, ﻿you need to look
each other in the eyes for 10 seconds.
Oh, we have an advantage.
Isn't HaHa looking cute today.
Jongkook's team
Decides on cute HaHa
It's okay?
Then should we choose Sukjin?
I think we could win against Sukjin.
Jaesuk's team
Old boy Sukjin
Who would want to wear
a couple hat with him?
It's been a while since you
have been that confident.
If I get defeated by Sukjin, I'm going to retire.
Retorts
Yah, are you looking down on me?
Are you looking down on me?
Not going to lose
A battle of dignity between these two men begins now
Hyung, show off your 90's sass.
Let them be shocked for a bit.
In the past(?) the popular big nosed hyung
I used to be a
delicate beauty too
Try to act as cute as possible.
I'm the cutest one of all.
Cute
Victory is mine
Transforms to a cute little boy
HaHa
Cute ~
Who will be the one to capture the
hearts of the citizens in Sejong square?
In front of Center for Performing Arts
Countless citizens
They must be picked by them
To be frank, in your group
you are the weakest one.
Hyung, I'll give you a chance.
Both are full of confidence
You can start hunting first.
Excuse me, this one ~
The first Running Ball is at
stake for this warm-up mission
If you win, then you can take this.
Hello, please support Running Man.
First greet with intimacy~
Hello.
Enthusiastic response from the citizens
HaHa is rather popular.
Of course, I'm sure we'll win.
Sukjin is also very popular.
Hello.
Just talking does nothing,
ask them right away.
Sukjin
Greets and advances at the same time
Hello.
They're dodging away from you.
What's this...
Everyone is moving away from Sukjin
Excuse me ...
Panics
Hello.
Full of confidence
HaHa challenges
Hello, nice to meet you.
Still moving away...
Worried
How come nobody dares
to get close to them?
They really aren't popular, these two.
Shouldn't they have their own fan-clubs?
Hello.
Picking up his courage
We're Japanese.
Oh, you're Japanese?
* Speaking Japanese
After so many tries He found Japanese tourists
Hello.
That's amazing.
Japanese, that's good.
Agitated
Will speaking Japanese work?
Do you like Korean singer?
Kiddie English?
Who?
CN BLUE.
Immediately
CN BLUE, Jung Yonghwa.
CN BLUE, my brother.
Excited
(He's there~)
CN BLUE ~
Right here
♪ ﻿I'm a loner ~ ♪
Jaesuk's team
Seems to be in the lead at the moment
Our team ~
CN Blue's Yonghwa.
Jung Yonghwa.
♪ ﻿I'm a loner ~ ♪
Bribing their hearts
I'm a loner
Just listening to the song made them happy
Do you know it?
I'm over here
♪ ﻿I'm a loner ~ ♪
Taking out something
As expected A hardcore CNBLUE fan
Jung Yonghwa.
She's your fan.
Yonghwa, our team.
Opposing team's HaHa is even more enthusiastic
Sing for her, sing.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Singing for a dedicated Japanese fan
♪ ﻿I'm a loner ~ ♪
Seriously?
For real?
I can't believe this
Real Yonghwa's live performance
Seriously touched
Sign ~
Immediately
Sign! Sign!
I'll help you get his signature.
Snatches
I'll help you
Ten seconds, just look at
each other for ten seconds.
Warm-up mission
Wear the couple hat and stare
at each other for 10 seconds
You can't look away.
Pick me
You have to pick one of us.
You've got to pick one out of us two.
Who will she choose?
I think HaHa will get chosen.
Please.
Because HaHa was ﻿the one
who introduced Yonghwa.
The one who introduced Yonghwa
HaHa?
You have to consider that
Yonghwa is on our team.
But HaHa introduced him.
Or Yonghwa's team
Sukjin?
You tell her, that his
dates ends immediately.
If I lose here
then I'll lose my face and dignity
Whoever that dates him,
doesn't last long at all.
One of them will be chosen
Yes, choice ~
In the end
Welcome to Korea.
Embarrassed
Everyone is tense and waiting
Who will get the first Running Ball?
All bets are on these two
Sukjin
was chosen
What is this?
This is impossible
Disappointment
Joy
... ﻿5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Have to look at each other
for 10 seconds
Jaesuk's team
Warm-up mission
Victory
Happiness~
in Sejong square
The earnest searching of hope
Jaesuk's team
Earns the
Running Ball
FIRST
To be able to leave they have to win
many Running Balls
Running Man finally
enters Sejong Performing Arts' Center
A true eye-opener
Sejong Center
for the performing arts
Wow, this Sejong Center really is ...
I thought I came here before ...
... but actually, this is the first time.
Oh, it still looks the same as the
time when I came to get my award.
Over 1 million audiences
Held 800 performances
A true representative of Korea's
cultural and artistic space
You've been here before?
I ﻿came here a lot of times
to receive many awards.
Can we really record the show here?
I ﻿think this is the first time a variety
show ever got to film in this place.
Jaesuk's first time filming here as well
We've got permission, right?
Right?
Of course ...
I'm just not sure if it's really okay.
Like what Jongkook said, only
really big events are held here.
Award ceremonies Film festivals
Only the biggest events
Kwonnie, have you been here before?
Yeah, I've been here before.
When?
To see a performance ~
Kwon watched performances here
Jongkook, you came here to get awards?
I've performed here as
well as received awards.
Showing off
Here?
Yes, of course.
Seriously?
I've received lots of awards here.
During the "Turbo" days?
* Jongkook was a member of the trio
Turbo and had hits like "Black Cat"
Turbo received a lot of awards
We need to choose the
'Morning Punishment', right?
What is the punishment going to be?
Today's punishment is?
Today's punishment is
taking the subway home
And take the subway
After overnight recording
No brushing
No shower
Please anticipate
Who will be punished?
Sealing exits.
Exits sealed
Let's go check out the stage.
Wow~
The pride of Sejong Center
Grand Theater
Among 3,000 theaters
this is the most sophisticated in Korea
Don't you want to sing here?
Of course.
Full of compliments...!
There are even three floors.
This is a dream stage
Yah, this is the spotlight.
Anyone who has a chance to perform
would like to be standing here...
Wow, this is very impressive.
I don't know if everyone is
familiar with the Sejong Center.
This theater is well known worldwide
It's one of the world's top ten theaters.
Sejong Center
World's top 10 theaters
Oh, really? I didn't know.
Well constructed.
Cold
Well constructed
Of course, this is very impressive.
Well constructed?
Huh?
This is really well constructed.
HaHa appraising like an architect
HaHa, did you build this?
Everyone should know that Sejong Center
is one of the places that represents Seoul.
One of Seoul's key landmarks
There are a lot of visitors, but
very few can visit the back stage.
It's a rare chance to see the backstage
For the first time every single spot
of the Sejong Center
Today Running Man will be running
in Sejong Center's every corner
Come to think about it, I have
been on this stage before ...
... but I think it is my first
time going to the backstage.
That is right, there should be a
lot of people that are interested.
What songs have you sung on this stage?
Twist King?
Sing it again.
You should perform it
once more on this stage
What year was that?
1996.
Dominated the '96
Twist King
Pretend you are back in 1996,
stand in front and perform again.
Sing there?
Right in the center of the spotlights
I am giving you a once
in the life time chance.
I have to stand there?
Why?
Yes.
If you stand there then your
fans will be in front of you.
Even to Jongkook this is an amazing stage
Wow, so cool.
Heated up the nation 14 years ago
The song The dance
Standing on this stage
once more...!
Relive the moments from your past.
Huh?
What...
It's not like that
Is this the dance we've seen before?
Completely
crazy
That ... is that really Twist King?
To the audience on the 2nd floor
Again
Starts hopping
The song from the past The dance fro the past but why...
That was very cool back then.
So the back view was like that?
I can't see the back view.
Obviously I can't.
This dance was really
cool back in the days.
Yonghwa, would you like to
sing or do something else?
Best rock idol CNBLUE's Yonghwa?
I'll sing.
This time it's a full house.
You'll have to deliver even to 2nd and 3rd floor.
Pretending the empty hall is full with an anticipating audience
Yes.
Oh, this feels nice.
You can feel it.
All the CNBLUE fans are sitting there.
Imagine
The hall is full of CNBLUE fans
Concert in the heart
I'm starting.
Yonghwa Jjang.
A dream to have a chance to sing here one day
2nd and 3rd floor scream.
Who screamed when he
said 2nd and 3rd floor?
A different scream compared to fan girls
Expected
Controls the stage like a rock star
Kwonie, do you also want to sing?
I'll dance to 1st, 2nd, and 3rd floor.
The audiences are slowing
filling up down there.
To Jo Kwon this stage is still too small
I got it.
It's all you now then.
This is really amazing.
When we watch the broadcast later, we
should add this to our personal collection.
Private collection?
Kwonie, greet the audience first.
Jo Kwon is ready
Hello, this is Kkab Kwonie here.
Hello this is
Kkab Kwon here
Started!
Jo Kwon stage!
Feels good even if it's an empty hall
Unlimited smooth movements
Eye contact with the audience
Right now
This is the real start
Second floor.
Third floor.
Big stage control
This is Jo Kwon's solo concert
Just like watching a musical...
The best
performer
Jo Kwon
Sejong' Center's
1st 2nd 3rd floor's seats filled
That was incredible.
He really got the feel.
Gary you try too.
No reason to say no
Gary
Hip-hop.
Dance?
Of course.
This stage is like a
grand award show.
Imagine again
This is a grand award show
Gary.
Grand award's main show
Gary
Gary, let's go.
Previous years dance battle winner
Gary's performance
Oh?
One! Two!
Is this supposed to be cool or funny?
But still the atmosphere is
Here it comes ~
Thomas
It's here! Difficult technique!
Here it comes ~
Gary is like this
Wah~
If you want to hear
screams again then ...
The ending with
Butterfly
Right now is
Gary's personal dance
One after another
Sejong Center's performance
Right now we will start our game.
What is the game?
* BGM: "Phantom of the opera" by Andrew Lloyd Webber
Instead of an answer it slowly comes down
Using what was prepared by Sejong Center
Gigantic photo frame
Wow, this is really Sejong Center.
First time seeing a frame this big.
Go inside the photo frame.
First mission
Photo zone
Isn't this too easy?
The team with most members
captured in the frame wins
But this is ...
Ssook~
The door dance.
Just like walking through a door
Basic hip-hop dance move
Just stand behind the photo
frame and show your face.
Ah okay.
Just as usual, we have 10 seconds.
The photo is automatically
taken after 10 seconds
We only have one
chance of the shoot.
Members must form a
pyramid inside the frame.
The team that correctly forms
a pyramid in the frame wins
Once they've captured that
on camera, then it's good.
Shocked
Pyramid?
Pyramid ~
3 people at the bottom and 2 on top.
You just have to finish the pyramid.
So we we're not just taking a picture.
Worried
Of course it won't be that easy.
Ready.
Blue team
Challenges first
Why are you holding
on my hand so tight?
I'm afraid that you might leave me.
Alright, let's do well.
Fighting ~
Fighting'
That scared me.
Holding hands and running ~
Pressed the timer
Have 10 seconds to run back to the frame
Now form the pyramid
It looks easy but it's very difficult
The V sign.
V sign.
Click
So ...
How was it captured?
Uneasy
A falling pyramid
Ah, this is funny.
Let's see it together.
The falling Jaesuk
Because Jihyo is
sitting on his shoulder
Blue team
FAIL
I'm scared of getting injured.
Sit on the top.
We kept falling back afterwards.
Easy mission but hard to complete
Starting from in there ...
Excuse me, the time doesn't start
when you're leaving the frame ...
... why did you run to the camera?
Where?
The timer doesn't start over there.
No point in running before they pressed the camera
What did you say?
The time doesn't start there,
so why did you run so fast?
We should've slowly walked there.
Realizing now...
We totally didn't know that.
Tsk Tsk
Then give us another chance.
Come on, just give us a chance.
What?
Ultimate move
Kneeling
Just give us another chance.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Just give us one more chance.
Switching leg
What is this?
Because of pride
He doesn't go down on both knees
Let us finish this first.
The man that loves kneeling down
MC Yoo
Go ahead.
Start.
Red team
Walk slowly before pressing the camera
Yah, Jongkookie, I didn't
think you would do this.
We'll start running once you press it.
Lively walks in front of the camera
Even plans a returning route
Where?
Are you ready?
Calm
1, 2, 3 ...
Pressed the timer
... go.
Now the 10 seconds start
Hurry back to the frame
According the plan
Red team
All that is left is to form the pyramid
No, that's not it.
Curse
You have to stand up.
First HaHa goes up
1, 2, 3.
Eunjung also succeed?
No, that's not it.
Smile
You have to stand up.
Peaceful
Click
How will the pyramid turn out?
No ~
Why?
You have to stand up.
That's right.
And your T-shirt is weird,
the design can't be like that.
Nitpick
Design(?) can't
be like that
In the midst of chaos
the one who's calm
We won.
Alright, we won.
Pyramid formation
Red team's faces
Okay, 1 to 0.
Red team
WINS
Blue team
Okay, now it's 1 to 0.
What shall we do next?
What's the second formation?
Become a graceful ballerina.
Follow the music and dance ballet.
At the climax of the music ...
... stand on your ﻿toes and
put your hands on the head.
The group with most members
captured within the frame wins.
I got it.
Like this?
Everyone is standing in position
So cute.
These clothes aren't very suitable.
The outfit raises with your arms and legs
Not like that.
This really can't do.
Wearing this outfit while completing
the mission is to embarrassing
Because of the outfit we cant do it.
It's getting low class.
When I raise my arms it
is just too embarrassing.
And he tries again...
Why is it like that?
He started doing that
from  a long time ago.
Witness claim:
There are other clothes you can use.
What?
For those in trouble
Clothes prepared
As if they had been waiting
I should wear a skirt.
It's better to wear a skirt.
Picking according to their own liking
Is it?
Oh?
What Gary likes
Why does Jo Kwon looks so pretty?
Beautiful
Kwon seems to have been
reborn into a female idol.
Gary, what's that you're wearing?
It fits you really well.
Feigning innocence
It's too scary.
Oh?
What...?
He looks so scary.
This person
Muscular ballerina
Why does the skirt look so powerful?
The skirts looks so powerful.
Even his muscles can be
seen through the skirt ...
We're starting now.
With music from 'Swan Lake'
The swans are slowly unfolding their wings
Full of feeling
A totally immersed swan
Awkward macho swan
The flirty grasshopper from England
Flexibility?
Outfit and flexibility are two different things
Where in the song is the climax?
Swan lake
Be in the shot at the climax
Is the climax now?
The frame is rising
Absurd
Calm
No matter what
Today's photo zone is
a moving frame
Panicking
The whole team jumps
Jump
It's getting higher.
No doubt
the calm man
The frame
Moving everywhere
The music suddenly climaxes
When are you taking the photo?
Swan lake
Going to the climax soon
Here, here. They took it.
They took it.
Click
Photoshoot over
The team with most ballerinas in the frame is?
We're in.
Where is our team?
Abruptly:
Jihyo, this expression is a little...
Is this an arm or a thigh?
Did you lift your legs up?
Aren't these your legs?
Our team, 1 2 3 4 .... 4 people.
4 people
Blue team
WINS
Gary was supposed to be this
round's main character, but ...
Gary is not in the photo
... he didn't come out.
Unhappy
Because of too much pressure.
Red team
Current score
Blue team
Please ~
Like a vocalist, make your hands
and mouth into an 0 shape.
Last round
Pose as a vocalist
in a small frame
I have a good feeling about this.
Make your hands and mouth into an 0 shape
Ah, like this?
The frame suddenly became smaller
Let's do this one last time.
We're going to start now.
There is no way we
can show up like that.
The more the frame shrinks
the more fierce it becomes
You're counted if you get into the shot
Excuse me, what are you doing?
The small frame suddenly moves
In sync with the frame
Come out
noona
Voices raises as the frame raises
Oh~
Sudden descent
Commotion
Red team
Eunjung
Dominates the center of the frame
Gary desperately tries
to get into the shot
Along with the frame
Oooh la la ~
Jaesuk can't get in
between the young people
I have to get in
even if I die
Right
Left
It only counts if both the mouth and hands are correct
Smock
Click
Finally
The result this time is?
Eunjung
Both mouth and hands are
Okay
Whose sharp chin is this...?
Jihyo's eye ...
That sad looking eye
Who was successful?
Kwonie's hands isn't shown.
His hands were blocked.
Eunjung is the only one
First victory goes to the red team
Red team
Gets the Running Ball
The fear of ringing sounds
Who is going to
escape first?
Who will be the winner?
For this race ...
... the teams will be divided
into hiding and hunting teams.
The hiding team needs
to complete a mission.
What about the hunting team?
The hunting team just needs
to capture the other team.
Hunting sounds cool.
I also like to catch.
So the catching team just
needs to get the nametags?
So just tear if off?
Just tear off all of the other
team tags and it's over.
Members without nametags are out
The hunting team has to
wear bells on their shoes.
Hunting team
Movement will be noisy
Weak point
Ah, the sound.
Cat and mouse game.
Will hiding be better?
Because you just have ﻿to hide or
run away and not let them get you.
I don't have the confidence
to catch Jongkook.
Can he...
catch...
them...?
We want to be the hiding team.
You guys want to hide?
The blue team decides to hide
We can get the other
four person's tag ...
... but not Kim Jongkook's.
So you all want to have the fear
of sounds of bells approaching?
Ah... The scary sound from the hunting team
Terrified
The thought of it gives
Goosebumps
Start over ~
No, you said you want to hide?
Didn't realize that
ringing sounds
is so scary
Ah, I'm so nervous my stomach hurts.
I'll let you have a feel of what it's like.
It's so unfair to us.
Even with 5 of us, we can't
rip off Jongkook's tag down.
Here's how it feels like ...
Imagine it coming towards a quiet place.
In a quiet place
Only you and the VJ are hiding there ...
... and suddenly I'm approaching.
Ring
...The will to resist fear...?
With my eyes closed,
it's really very creepy.
Can you handle it?
Unable to handle the fear...
The shocking battle begins
What's the mission?
Blue team
Mission
Find 5 haechis
(Duration: 1 hour)
* Haechi = A lion-like horned mythical
creature chosen as the symbol of Seoul
You have to find five of these.
Haechis?
How do we find them?
You have to find them while at the
same time avoiding being caught.
Find the Haechis without being caught
We can hide anywhere, but finding
the five haechis is another problem.
Yes, that's the problem.
The mission is to find 5 haechis
And if you are caught within
that time, it's not counted.
Among the 5 of us, we just need 1
person to not be caught and it's fine.
Blue team's message
It's here ~
The stairs behind the dance stage ...
Haechis' location
1. Backstage staircase of dance stage
2. The orchestra pit
3. Turtle boat at Chungmugong story
4. Sejong story library
5. Shin Gijeon at Sejong story
the Orchestra Pit ...
turtle boat at Chungmugong story ...
Haechis'
locations
Lets go.
Red team is on 2nd floor
They will start the chase in 5 minutes
They start from the 2nd floor.
In 5 minutes ...
Even if it's 5 minutes, it's still time.
Duration of 1 hour
Need to save time
Hurry, lets go.
1. Dance stage staircase
2. The orchestra pit
3. The turtle boat
4. Sejong library
5. Shin Gijeon
Blue team
Rushes towards the dance stage
Yonghwa goes up the stairs
Jo Kwon follows behind...
Have you seen this map?
Come over and have a look.
Found the location of the basement on the map
This is below the stage, this is the top.
The stage has floors of 43m height
This is the backstage
Where is it?
On the other side...
Red team testing the walkie-talkie
Something's here.
Red Team receives a message
It's here ~
Tear off the other teams
name-tags within 1 hour.
We only have this mission.
They don't know what mission Blue Team has
Both of you, don't go together.
Why?
Just in case.
Not sure why but afraid that something
might happen between Gary and HaHa
We got to make full use of this hour.
When we're running around ...
... sometimes we are ﻿together
and sometimes we'll separate.
One team goes up from the bottom,
one team goes down from the top.
So we'll meet in the middle.
Joongki's brain is so good.
Also, hyung ...
When using the walkie-talkie,
please don't breathe into it.
Listen to this ...
How you shouldn't use it
No, but that's not fair, how
many times have I done that?
Framed
Seriously, I can't hear
what you're saying.
How many times have I done that?
Isn't this supposed to
be a tactical meeting?
All right.
This sound is really scary.
It's scary just hearing it.
If you think that someone is
hiding nearby, then stop and ...
And then ...
The ultimate scare
Confidence is up
High desire to win
They're dead, really.
That's a good idea.
Yeah, I like that too.
Remaining time
before mission ends
Yonghwa is up there, right?
Jaesuk's afraid of height
Will never climb those stairs
Still searching for the Haechi
Found it?
They have started.
Hurry and get down.
Alarm
Emergency retreat
Hiding in the elevator
Blue Team
Where's Yonghwa?
He's here...
Where are they?
The result of climbing to high
Yonghwa was unable to retreat
In this spacious area
became a loner
Where are they?
Far away he is hearing
The bells ringing
Also becoming louder is
the evil laughter
Nervous
If they climb up these stairs
he'll be caught immediately
Nerve
wrecking
Fighting ~
But luckily
Red team is leaving almost immediately
Phew~
A sigh of relieve and then continue to search
The clue said it's
here somewhere
Found it...!
Dong!
Also pretty boy Yonghwa has his flaws
Regardless
He found the first Haechi
The rest of the blue team reaches Basement 2
There is someone out there.
Stay here ~
Feeling uneasy because they're afraid someone's there
Stay in there, but if I shout
then shut the door and go up.
Okay ~
Hide properly.
Bait Sukjin is
going to take a look
This place is
* The story of Chungmugong = Memorial hall
for the legendary commander Yi Sunshin
Toward B2 level of Sejong Cultural Arts Center
the story of Chungmugong
Right next to it is the story of King Sejong
* King Sejong (reign: 1418-1450) = The 4th
king of the Joseon dynasty (1397-1450)
Both exhibition halls links to
the Gwanghwamun underground passage
No one, right?
Now they need to find
the other 4 Haechis
Jihyo, come here with Jo Kwon.
But at the same time
Gary & HaHa enters
Why can't I contact them?
Sukjin hyung ...
The ringing of bells...!
They are here...!
HaHa, it's HaHa.
Let's go hunting.
The little rascal hunters are on the right momentum
We need to search carefully.
Yooruce Willis completely freaking out
Fearful
That ringing.
In the other section
Big nose big brother Sukjin also
The bells.
The bells!
He runs at the speed of light in the opposite direction of the bells
Vibrating throughout the quiet hall
The scary sound of the bells
HaHa
Jaesuk
The little hunter
he left
Hurrying~
Jaesuk in panic
enters an elevator
Where should I go?
He's in a hurry so he pressed the
button without much thought
3rd floor
The ringing is so scary.
It's so scary.
We shouldn't have separated.
Time before mission ends
There's something there.
Yooruce Willis managed to escape
HaHa with much difficulty
But the crisis isn't over yet...
Starts searching from the top floor
Jongkook . Joongki . Eunjung
Started their search immediately
And now going ...
toward 3rd floor
They entered the box seats
They're not here yet.
It's not the right timing.
Using his animal instincts to search
Muscle Jongkook
They're not here yet.
Jaesuk blindly going to 3rd floor
I'm going crazy.
I'm alone again.
Hide-&-seek expert Yooruce Willis
alone again
The determination of his fate
is approaching fast
Talking to himself
They don't get caught, right?
But where's Yonghwa?
Jaesuk's heart beat stops
The crisp ringing of bells
Yooruce Willis faces a big crisis
What will the result be?
It's Muscle Jongkook's attack
This is called
The fox
hiding from HaHa
The tiger
meeting Jongkook
Wait ...
Both his arms being bounded instantaneously
Okay.
Blue Team
Yoo Jaesuk
Unexpected
Yooruce Willis
for the 1st time
eliminated
You should have run faster.
That ringing is really scary.
Getting caught then blaming his VJ
That bell is really scary.
For the hid-n-seek expert
The scariest thing in the world is ringing bells
Why did I go to the 3rd floor,
I should have gone to 2nd floor.
Regretful
But Yooruce Willis' suffering isn't over
Time left before
the mission ends
You have to hide properly.
Still hunting in the basement
The little hunter
I'm In trouble ~
It's that bell again.
Nervous
It's that bell.
Picking up courage and runs to a better hiding place
Luckily he found the exit
But it's locked
HaHa reached the stairs where Sukjin's hiding
In danger
Big nose brother
Peeks
Caught
Hyung ...
Big nose brother
trying to escape
Ahsa~
Gary coming from the front
I caught him.
Big nose brother
Biggest crisis
Wait... Okay...
Okay ~
In the end
Ji Sukjin
Currently
Blue team's survivors
Yonghwa Kwon Jihyo
Remaining dolls = 4
Remaining time
Hello, Yonghwa ...
It's Yonghwa.
Yonghwa, where are you?
I found a doll.
You found one?
Yes.
Good job.
Right now, at the 2nd and
3rd level of the theater ...
... there are 3 people searching.
Jongkook, Eunjung ...
I got it.
After hearing from Jaesuk
Yonghwa is going down
But ...
He heard the bells when he reached basement 2
Ssshh
Nerve
wrecking
The little hunter
approaching
Underground ~
Yonghwa's
hiding place
From behind a thin wall he's listening
to the hunters voices
Looking for a safer hiding place
Crash
The VJ crashed into the door
We're in
trouble
...Huh?!
As it turns out...
Within a split second
after the door closed
What a timing
Are they gone?
Yonghwa survives better than Yooruce Willis
Safely sets off to Chungmugon's Story
Hello.
On the other side
a desolated Yooruce Willis
Waiting for news from his team
Seong Im?
Ah, I shouldn't have taken the elevator.
Carefully
Joongki hides the sound while creeping somewhere
Shh.
It's Yooruce Willis
Since Jaesuk hyung
is using the talkie ...
Whispers
... we can find out the others location.
Seong Im, where are you?
All he needs to do is
to say the location.
Kwon, Jo Kwon ...
Jaesuk's giving a detailed report
Can you come over here?
Our CN Blue Yonghwa
found one of the Haechis.
... found one of the Haechis.
...Haechi?
Haechi?
Up 'til now they didn't know the other
team's mission
Haechi.
Eavesdropping
Success
They're looking for Haechis.
Where are you?
Yooruce Willis left speechless
They're looking for Haechis.
Joongki reports to his team mates
I'm sorry.
Jongkook ...
Joongki ...
Jittery
You guys don't know what Haechi is.
I think Haechi is some kind of figurine.
Smart
They misheard it as Saechi.
I'll go up to the 5th floor.
Thank you hyung.
He's going to level 5.
That's nothing
In the end it was me ...
... ﻿the mission's black hole.
Today Blue Team's black hole is
the self-proclaimed hide-n-seeker
Jaesuk
Sejong Cultural Center
Chungmugong Story
Jo Kwon
Jihyo
Sejong Story
Yonghwa
Remaining time
The new
Die Hard star Yonghwa
Sets off to search in Sejong Story library
It should be hidden behind a King Sejong book
Blue Team
The second Haechi
acquired
I found the second one
On the other side
Jihyo and Kwon are searching
* Turtle ship (Geobukseon) = Large warship during Joseon dynasty
Don't miss the movie about turtle ship (The Admiral: Roaring Currents (2014))
Approaching a turtle ship
Chunmugong Story
Reproduced at 1/2 of actual size
Turtle ship
One of the Haechis is hidden here
Found it
Blue Team
Found the third
Haechi
Remaining time
Sorting out the mission's progress
Found at Stairs Warship Library
Total 3
Is it three?
We need to find two more.
We found one at the
stairs and library ...
Now only the Orchestra Pit ...
... and ShinGiJeon is left.
I will go to the Orchestra Pit and
you two find the one in ShinGiJeon.
Where is ShinGiJeon?
It's downstairs.
The bright juniors are working hard
to cover for the useless seniors
Sejong's arrow rocket. One of the most
powerful weapons in the 15th century
ShinGiJeon
is over here
They walk straight pass it
If there's anyone there
please listen to me ...
Jongkook and Eunjung are at 2nd floor.
Hold on.
Are you doing this again in a show?
* Jaesuk are teasing Jongkook again about
"dating" on a show as he started to do in X-man
What?
You two are together?
Because we're following the plan.
Jongkook falls in love again.
Expert in producing scandals
MC Yoo
Jongkook falls in love again.
In the end Jaesuk's mouth is sealed
That way the secret won't be disclosed
I've got a present for you.
A present from HaHa
Sukjin's name tag
Awesome.
As predicted, me and
Sukjin got captured.
Chatter
I hope you 3 will do well.
Huh...?
Suddenly Jaesuk grabs the VJ's hat and camera
Oh my ~
Got you again, Gary...!
What are you doing?
Why?
I'm just helping the cameraman.
Is he really naive or just slow~
Gary gets fooled every time
You can't do this, hyungnim.
He's just right next to you.
Sorry.
Hyung, where did they catch you?
The two finally meet
At Sejong Story.
They don't know what
our mission is, do they?
They do.
Shameless
They know?
They know we are
looking for Haechis?
You blew it?
Totally not me.
Lies
That bell sound is annoying.
The bell sound is getting on their nerves
It's really scary.
Yonghwa is going to
the Orchestra Pit
Time before mission ends
We have to walk up.
The elevator doesn't stop at the
floor where the Orchestra Pit is
Bell sound is coming from the lobby
They're coming this way
Gary is coming to take the elevator
Who's at B2?
Are you getting in?
Hyung, let's go down to
the waiting room first.
If HaHa and Gary goes to the waiting room
Yonghwa will be discovered
No, they're at B2.
Give up the waiting room Goes to B2
Phew~
Orchestra pit ...
Once again looking for Orchestra Pit i B1
Orchestra Pit
The underground orchestra
area in front of the stage
Orchestra Pit:
This is exactly
the Orchestra Pit
From underground
it elevates to the main stage
Carefully listening for
bell sounds ~
Blue Team
Found the fourth
Haechi
Yonghwa found 3
all by himself
Suddenly the pit moves upward
Designed to move up and
down like a big elevator
Right now I'm ...
Remaining time
Yonghwa escapes
Now there's only one Haechi left
Jihyo
discovered something
The display glass won't open
Inside the display there's
a ShinGiJeon miniature
But since it won't open it's no use
The ShinGiJeon they walked by
Kwon, ShinGiJeon.
It was there the whole time
ShinGiJeon.
This is the last thing they need to find
Sound of the bells are heard again
Emergency
They run to the restroom in panic
Too bad...
The young ones are experience the final critical moment
Something to drink?
The thoughtless old ones are enjoying their morning tea
Remaining time
And one last Haechi to find
There's only 4 min left
Now they know where the last Haechi is
Nervous
But it's very difficult to find the Haechi
At the same time ...
... he's coming
Startled
The result ...
Jihyo
Kwon
Jongkook
Who's faster...?
Time left
Muscle man is slowly moving closer
Where is it?
Coincidentally
But
just then
Yonghwa
The man who's born to race, Yonghwa
Appeared at a critical moment...!
Open here ...
Oh?
Yonghwa stalling for more time
Blue Team
Gets the last
Haechi
Found it.
Blue Team
Found 5 Haechis
Mission success
We found them all, we won.
It really wasn't easy.
It looks like we've won.
Jihyo ...
How is it going?
We found all of them.
The thoughtless hyungs are really glad
He found 3 Haechis
MVP Yonghwa
Blue Team
Got the Running Ball
It's a shame.
Meanwhile...
What's shameful?
Come here ~
Jongkook and the kids
gather
Both of you started going
up to the 2nd floor, right?
What were you doing
on the bottom floor?
Unfair
We went up.
Did you search the bottom floor completely?
Of course ~
From now on, I forbid
both of you to go together.
From the start
Jongkook was unhappy about
the Gary & HaHa combination
Then all of us should
be punished together.
Punishment?
Why should I be punished?
Unfair
Jongkook and the children separates?
Let the past go.
The new day is here Hi-Lo.
Absurd
The hands that are ready to ...
... comfort.
Comfort~
For a new day, Hi-Lo.
Can you two not stick together?
Finally exploded
Don't turn off the camera,
otherwise I might get hit.
Don't turn it off.
In the future
Jongkook and the kids' fate is...?
After everyone fell asleep...
Gwanghwamun
Everyone, time for a relaxing drink.
Mission 3
A relaxing cup of tea
This time ...
It's irrelevant to your imagination.
Stiff~
You will easily feel sleepy, so
you need to wake yourself up.
The time when dreams and reality are mixed together
To overcome everyone's sleepiness ...
Want to overcome sleepiness
To get rid of our sleepiness ...
Sorry, Eunjung please open your eyes.
Now there is no way out.
You can't be like that, open your eyes.
Oh, Kwangsoo ...
What?
Kwangsoo came?
Oh!!
What?
It's Kwangsoo.
Please open
the door
Confused
Drama filming ended so he came right away
Hello.
For Running Man he didn't feel exhausted
You came.
You came from filming?
Yes I did.
Coming is easy, but ...
Not coming is okay too.
Kwangsoo, the atmosphere
just now was really good.
HaHa jokes
Kwangsoo, it would've been
okay if you didn't come.
Everyone is teasing Kwangsoo
I'm not welcomed for my arrival.
Disappointed
Hurry and take a seat.
Kwangsoo, quickly use the microphone.
This isn't the reaction Kwangsoo hoped for
Kwangsoo arrived, he must be tired
This is not what I anticipated.
Being deceived again
I thought they would be very happy.
We'll have some refreshing lemon tea.
Now the real game will start
Today's menu
Lemon tea
That's good.
Lemon effect
The sourness of the lemon is really good for
tiredness and vitamin C can prevent the flu
Lemon tea ...
Throw this dice to determine
the amount of lemons.
One relaxing cup of tea
Throw this dice to determine
the amount of lemons.
The number that shows up on the dice ...
... be the amount of lemons for your drink.
Let's start from Kim Jongkook.
1st contestant is
Jongkook
Am I the first?
Yes.
Do we get a ball with this?
Ah, that's right.
Oh with this?
The team that drinks it the fastest will win a ball
Yes, you can win a ball.
Let's start ...
Bounce ~
11 lemons.
How many lemons will Jongkook's drink contain?
One lemon?
Jongkook gets 11 lemons
What to do?
Kim Jongkook ...
Can't even imagine 11 lemons
... so 11 lemons.
Half of the lemon is
counted as 1 lemon.
Half is one?
Luckily
Half of the lemon is counted as one
Yeah.
Is that for one person?
Of course.
100% lemon juice
Everyone, this is not the time
to be making enemies.
It seems sour.
Worried
If he drinks all 11 lemons,
his muscles will disappear.
Satisfied
Muscles will disappear(?)
Power of 11 lemons
Why did 11 lemons appear from the start?
Finished~
To all viewers, lemon tea is
really good for your health.
Muscle man
Will be full of Vitamin C
It's good for the body.
Since it's very good for
the body, then it's okay.
Evil ~
Powerful
He squeezes it clean.
Dude?
Dumbfounded
I said squeeze, not dude.
Your pronunciation must be clear.
At this time it's very easy to mishear.
Okay, done.
Before moving on, let's
congratulate Jongkook.
Jongkook's 11 lemon tea is done
This not all of it going in.
Soon the cup fills with lemon juice
A little bit more will make overspill.
It's hard to drink the lemon tea even if you get paid
There's no more space for water.
Okay.
There's no room to pour water.
Okay, throw it.
2nd contestant
Joongki
The result of Joongki's lemon amount is?
10 lemons ~
Joongki will get 10 lemons
Why is our team like this?
10 lemons or more in a row
Okay, 10 lemons.
If 10 lemons ...
All out~
Kwangsoo squeezes until it's clean
Are there any lemons left?
You came late, why are
you still enthusiastic?
Because he came late, he's enthusiastic.
Go away.
Telling the latecomer Kwangsoo to go away
Ah, Joongki ...
The two same-aged best friends
The person who was tired has
already been told to go away.
But it's annoying like that.
Look at how Kwangsoo squeezes the juice
He's well matched to make
relaxing lemon tea(!)
Joongki's lemon tea is done
10 lemons and 11 lemons
make a very Indifference.
Euah sour ~
You can't drink this.
Eunjung ...
Already worried
Eunjung's turn to throw the dice
Is it 10 lemons?
How many lemons will Eunjung get?
8?
Two.
Very lucky
Eunjung
2 lemons
Eunjung gets 2 lemons.
Oh that ...
Please don't use your bare hands.
What?
Thoroughly hygiene
Yah, you should hold
the lemon higher up.
Excuse me, but ...
Yes?
... please stop calling people by "Yah Yah".
This is not the effect of coming late
All done
by hand
Why are you like that?
I thought there still
were a lemon there.
Result from lack of sleep
Done with the 2 lemons.
Eunjung ...
2 lemons look very easy
Suddenly this lemon tea is fresh and sour
My turn to throw?
Red Team
Gary 5 lemons
HaHa 8 lemons
Yes.
I will throw it now.
Blue Team's Jaesuk
Jaesuk It's clearly 11 lemons
Devastated
11 lemons.
Satisfied~
Jongkook, why are you more ...
Jongkook His image has become more ...
Whoo, what is that?
Oh this is very sour, seriously.
Next Kwangsoo.
Aigoo, that seems sour.
What to do?
Red Team
Squeezing lemons with the force of revenge
Tired 40's generation
Sukjin throws the dice
3 lemons ~
Lucky...
3 lemons to drink
Three lemons.
I'm busy.
Kwangsoo Jihyo Kwon Yonghwa
Red Team
is at a disadvantage
You're boasting now, right?
Jongkook has been exercising
for 10 years already.
Look how he squeezes the lemons.
Muscles that won't allow a single drop of
lemon juice get wasted
Now everyone has their lemon
tea placed in front of them.
We're not going to drink it like that,
we need to add little a bit of sugar.
Time to choose the amount of sugar to add
Spoons are placed in these boxes.
Jongkook, choose from number 1 to 12.
Choose the spoon to
scope sugar with
I choose 10.
10.
What kind of spoon is in box 10?
Puha
AH!
Ear-pick
No matter what, you could
have put in a better one.
To sweeten the sour taste of 11 lemons
at least some sugar is needed
I'll scoop deeper in for you.
As small as ear-dirt
No matter how deep~ you dig
Oh, done.
Not able to see it
I choose 5.
Okay, number 5.
Aiyo, congratulations Eunjung.
Rice spoon
Later when the other team chooses ...
... switch the order of the utensils.
Yes I got it.
Like nobody's business
2 lemons plus a rice spoon of sugar
But how ...
Don't drink it yet.
Just like sugar water
Number 1.
Without hesitation
Must be the soup spoon.
Guessing?
BINGO
Soup spoon chosen
This can't be ...
Am I a master in fortune telling.
The cup must be too small for a soup spoon sugar
Aigoo.
What to do?
But he still puts it in
Oh, what to do?
Come on ...
Please turn around.
Time to change the order of the spoons
Who will be the victim.
Must be able to use
the largest spoon
How to use this to scoop.
Uneasy
Okay, it's done.
Okay stop.
Then I choose number 4.
Number 4.
What kind of spoon does
box number 4 contain?
Congratulations.
Rice spoon
11 lemons plus 1 rice spoon of sugar
To the brim
Kwangsoo ...
Kindly helps
to stir ...
It's better to let me stir.
I'm a man, I choose number 1.
Aigoo ~
Unusual reaction
A straw spoon
You can only pour it like this.
Pouring it is faster than scooping
That is for only 3 lemons?
3 lemons plus a big
This is not bad at all.
spoon of sugar
It's okay.
Mostly made up of sugar
Is this sugar added to lemons
or lemons added to sugar?
Sugar tea with a lemony smell
Jo Kwon ...
Number 10.
A big welcome
It's here
The large spoon
Doomed
I'll give you a reasonable amount.
To the brim
Number 12 was not chosen.
Now the sugar has been added.
What's in number 12?
Now ...
Jaesuk hyung, this is number 12.
Careful
Garden shovel?
A garden shovel seems a bit too much.
Serious
Please fill it up.
Now is the time to add water
A bit more~
Add a bit more.
Enough.
Quarreling over the amount of water
Just add a bit more.
It's going to overflow.
Look at this, you add so much.
Difference
Pours a lot for Joongki
How about me?
Unhappy
Ah, this is serious.
Eunjung's perfect Sugar Water
You can only see the sugar.
Just give a bit more.
Unhappy
MC Yoo's own tea also gets a full cup of water
Explodes
Oh, my bad.
Please slowly enjoy.
Everyone ...
Dessert will be served at the same time.
Perfect preparation
Still a last dessert left
Everyone listen up ...
The team that finish drinking
and eating first wins
This is a team's challenge.
All ﻿the teammates drink up the tea fast.
Fast?
Jihyo fighting.
Ready ... go.
11 lemons
1 ear-pick of sugar
1 rice spoon of sugar
Aiyo, it's so sour
Jongkook is still faster
Jongkook succeeds
Joongki
10 lemons + 1 spoon of sugar
Jaesuk finished
Now the dessert
Hurry up ~
Both sour ...
... and bitter
Jaesuk, swallow it down.
Jaesuk succeeds
Messy
Noona fighting.
8 lemons + 1 big spoon of sugar
Jihyo
Drinking it
in one gulp
Jihyo at top speed
What are you doing? Quickly drink it up.
Tight ...
competition
Joongki and Jihyo finish at the same time
2 lemons
+ 1 spoon of sugar
3 lemons
+ 1 straw-spoon of sugar
Okay, done.
Eunjung drinks it all in one go
Hurry up.
Just swallow it, no no no.
This old man still...
5 lemons
+ 1 teaspoon of sugar
Gary
Sukjin is
still eating the dessert
Oh, so bitter.
Sukjin finally finishes
Hurry ~
4 lemons + 1 spoon of sugar
Yonghwa
Eat it up, eat it.
Finishes his dessert
Gary
HaHa finishes it as soon as it's his turn
8 lemons + 1 spoon of sugar
Last one
Eat ~
Swallow it ~
8 lemons + 1 giant spoon of sugar
Last one
Kwon too finishes it in one gulp
Swallow it ~
HaHa is still eating his dessert
Actually
Gulp~
HaHa finished first
Red Team wins
Running Ball to
Red Team
Finally
Time to decide who can leave
Finally, I'm so nervous.
This is nerve-wrecking.
Having less Running Balls
doesn't mean we lose.
Yes, last we only had 2 while
you had 3, but we still won.
Last week
Dramatic victory for team with least balls
First, let's put the balls inside.
Hurriedly
Red Team
Morning's group football
they won a ball
Red Team
Balls
Blue Team
Putting all the good luck inside.
You have to come out, you have to.
Putting all his faith into the balls
He does it with abnormal behavior
Please put the balls in.
Finally the balls are put inside
Ah, we used all our
efforts to get them.
Putting the result of hard work into the lotto machine
Only if their team's ball comes out
are they allowed to go home
So whatever team's balls
come out, mean that they win?
Red Team
Blue Team
Chance of winning
The winning team doesn't get punished.
Aaahhh, please ...
Spinning
The moment that decides their fate
Who will stay ...
Who can leave
Read Team
Blue Team
The color of the ball decides who wins
Blue ball
Blue Team
Gets to leave
60% chance lost against 40% chance
The unexplainable
dramatic twisted victory
Walking to the VJ who always gets punished together
His earnest prayers...
And his desperate wishes
A long awaited victory
Today they can go home right away
Jaesuk at this moment...
Transformation complete
Since going back home
takes a long time ...
Thanks to the other team they just had to take a bus
... and last week they took care of us.
You just have to take the
train to Yeoul Island station.
Just take the train
You're not satisfied?
Arrogant
Thank you ~
Bows
Don't be too arrogant.
Walking to the train station
Yah, if the people stares at us ...
Oh~
Looking good
... ﻿we have to act like nothing is
wrong and just greet them normally.
Joongkook oppa, you're funny.
Kim Jongkook hyung, sing "One Man".
Walking round in the middle of
Sejong Center with this face
This way is in the Panghwa direction.
Have to take a train in the morning rush hour
It's here ~
Gets on the train
Subconsciously walks
towards a corner
No brushing No washing
Their barbaric side
Please act like you don't know us.
Amazingly
Citizens still recognize them
Easily bullied(?) Gary sits down
Burden
They've all woken up from dozing off
Then the citizen slowly passes something to Gary
Bread
You ate it?
Pity?
Gary doesn't seem to
look tired at all ... ?!
Eats it right away
She gave it to me, of course I eat it.
The bread drenched in tears
we must win next time