Softsubs by SamFive @AvistaZ
Based on hardsubs by iSUBS
Today's landmark
National museum of contemporary art
Where the best arts from
the whole world and our nation breathe
I'm a big fan.
Along with special guest
Chasing wars that makes you out of breath
The horror suspense thriller
starts now
Fall enters...
A breezy day in September
Right here is the National
Museum of Contemporary Art.
Loud
Today's landmark is
National Museum of Contemporary Art
Displays only world class
level of art pieces
Pushing our nation's arts development
The one and only National Museum of Contemporary Art
Enters the museum
In front of their eyes
Oh, that art work.
Baek Namjun's artwork.
The father of video-art
Baek Namjun's 'The more, the merrier'
And
the nation's top artists works
Domestic and foreign
famous artists' works
I should come with the kids,
but I'm here with you guys.
You had surgery last week.
Is your waist better now?
Yes I'm fine, no need for
the waist belt anymore.
Not long after Jongkook's waist surgery
Really?
You should take care of your body.
You still shouldn't run.
It's really ...
But you still can't run.
You should rest for a few weeks.
Using caring as a tactic
They're all looking for your spot.
Is Jongkook's injury a chance for others?
Why did you return?
Just go back.
Your spot isn't only sought
after by Gary and HaHa.
Also Sukjin is waiting for a chance.
You should go home.
Anyway, after 2 weeks
Joongki has returned.
Because of drama filming
Joongki returns after 2 weeks
Are you going to continue
to come from now on?
When I watched the broadcast
at home, I had a urge to run.
Finally our "Brain" has returned.
Smart Joongki's return makes
it perfect
When you weren't here, this team could
play the strength games with no problem.
Without Brain Joongki
something was missing
But when it came to games
that require a little brain ...
You're so funny.
Funny?
Thank you then, I am very funny.
Just
then
A strange couple enters the museum
Running Man
Today's guests
I have Jongkook within my palms
Cha Taehyun
Shines with overwhelming charm
Yoon Seah
Cha Taehyun
Today's guests
Yoon Seah
Oh, Seah.
Welcome
Aigoo, Cha Concubine.
* Cha Concubine = Cha Taehyun (a joke from Family Outing)
Nice to meet you.
Awkward
Hello.
I'm a big fan of yours.
Cold with Sukjin...
Passionate with Jaesuk
Saddened
Today we invited Yoon
Seah and Cha Taehyun ...
... ﻿to Running Man, nice to meet you
Grateful they came despite busy schedules
Taehyun's close friend Jongkook is also grateful
Just so you know, this show
requires you to stay up all night.
Yes ~
Forced
Do you hate it?
Very much.
Trying to avoid using stamina Taehyun
There's also running.
I don’t know if anyone
knows about Taehyun ...
... but this friend over here
is the master of scheming.
Taehyun's specialty is ...
Scheming?
It's not voice imitation ...
* Play with words, in Korean "imitation" sounds like "scheme"
... it's scheming skill.
He's the only one that can control Jongkook.
Earning him the name
Cha Concubine
Scheme master can control Jongkook
Within the entertainment industry ...
Come to our team.
Please, some to our team.
... he's the only one who can control Jongkook.
He is the only person who
has seen Jongkook's tears.
It'll be great if Taehyun came to our team.
The reason for Cha Concubine to be on his team?
Doesn't matter if we lose all the games,
or if all the balls go to the other team.
Using all kinds of tricks to win
Even like that we can still win the competition.
Still win without any Running Balls?
How is that possible?
I'm going to paint all the red balls blue.
Nothing can go wrong if we trust Taehyun.
Will you be serious when you have to run?
Nope.
Today
Cha Concubine's liveliness explodes
Also ﻿Seah came to our show.
Chameleon actress Yoon Seah
I saw you on Strong Heart, you're amazing.
In Strong Heart her deeply
hidden wittiness was seen
Interest
Sukjin, that's a 90's pose.
I was quite the thing back in the 90's.
90's handsome man pose?
Don't you think that's kind of old?
Why are you so concerned about my pose?
Explodes
I'll do what I want.
♪ ﻿I swear ... ♪
The audition 17 years ago
Humiliating video 'I Swear'
Seah, how are your running skills?
I got the record of around 14s
when I was in high school.
High school 100m record in 14 seconds
Jihyo, what's your high school record?
Jihyo's high school record is?
48 seconds?
Just say it, it's okay.
Stealthy~
Look at her hands.
I thought she wanted to hit someone.
To Jihyo he's getting more bold
Little rascal HaHa
A trustworthy source told me that ...
Spending every week together
discovering the new Jihyo
... this Jihyo is not the Jihyo we know.
Yes ~
Kwangsoo, I heard Jihyo went to a club.
I've heard of that rumor too, but
there are also a lot more bad stuff.
Sudden report
Have you met Jihyo before?
Today is the first time.
What do you think about this friend?
She's very pretty.
Really?
A little ~
Is she my dongsaeng?
Yes, she's younger than you.
Ah she looks older, right?
Look carefully?
Last week we competed with
the Running Man members.
For Running Man's members
A segment for them to become closer
A segment was prepared
for them to become closer.
At the end of the recording, if they
have anything they want to say ...
... they can send a message to this phone.
First week a lot of people participated.
I'll briefly go through one by one.
Ending digits with 7315 wrote ...
"I got my waist surgery today, it hurts a lot."
"I don't want to do it again."
"When can I leave?"
Are you saying that you don't
want to do Running Man?
What?
Isn't that what this means?
I meant that there aren't many
days before the show and ...
... I was worried that I couldn't
leave the hospital to do the show.
It was interesting, ﻿but it
could've been more funny.
Ending digits with 3074 wrote ...
"I've found out about Jongkook
hyung's surgery on the internet."
"﻿I was worried so I gave him
a call, but he didn't pick up."
Who was the sender of that message?
Anxious
"﻿But then he picked up the
call from HaHa and then ..."
"... he sent me a message 'It's okay ...' "
Close up
Excuse me, let me read it myself.
He's very interested in these type of things.
Scheme master's full of curiosity
Cha Concubine
You can't help but wanting to look at it, right?
"Then Jongkook wrote, 'It is
okay, don't worry about me'"
Jongkook didn't pick up the phone
but replied with a text message
"But he still picked up HaHa's call".
This is from Lee Kwangsoo.
He clearly left his name
Embarrassed
Wasn't it supposed to be anonymous?
What?
Anonymous?
It was supposed to be anonymous,
but I can see the name right there.
We should make the teams first.
First mission is a solo mission.
Teams will be set after the solo game
Through the solo game
form the team that will benefit you
Why a solo game?
The objecting two(?)
Stare
Someone said to me once ...
Retreat
... and I ﻿felt the same
when I saw the broadcast.
Suggestion from someone close to Jaesuk
Because of Jongkook's strength we need
a handicap when we are facing him.
What handicap?
Make him push a cart or some sort.
Or make him carry something heavy.
Or even make him carry his
niece and run or something.
We need to give him
some disadvantage ...
... but since he recently got his
surgery we'll start next time.
Let's start today.
One and only
As expected from Jongkook catcher
Cha Concubine
That hyung is really something.
You can't joke around about this stuff
But you want it too.
Dawn in Hongdae
Endless crowd
Today's punishment will be received here
Citizens passionate about them
Which team is getting punished?
Current time
National Museum of Contemporary Art's
7th gallery
Because we were outside, the
atmosphere is different here.
Jongkook came here before?
My home is in Anyang ...
... so I've been here a few times.
You have?
But sounds like you only go
to the horse racing derby.
Feeling like running with the horses?
Running Man auction.
First mission
Solo match Teams will be set after the auction
I will be the auctioneer ...
... and everyone else will be the bidders.
After buying the item,
use punishments as money.
Ah, not using money, but ...
... taking punishment as payment?
Yes, that's right.
The person who wins the bidding receives
the punishment they offered as payment.
I'm starting the auction now.
The item's something that everyone
needs ﻿when filming Running Man.
Auction item
They need it when filming Running Man
Got it?
Yes ~
If hesitate too long you'll miss your
chance and be at a disadvantage.
Understood?
Yes ~
Are you ready?
First
auction item
revealed
Yes ~
Show us the first auction item.
This person is?
Shocked
Surprise appearance
Jongkook's manager
He's very unnatural, but ...
Stiff and unnatural movements
... he said he wanted to be on camera.
Thank you for volunteering.
So the first item ...
Everyone ...
Shall we have a bidding
without looking at the item?
Hit the forehead once ~
Without knowing the item
Auction starts
5, 4 ...
Hit the wrist 3 times ~
Hit the forehead ~
Hit the forehead once plus a highway.
Forehead and highway?
Huh?
Highway.
Kang Gary.
Open a beer bottle using the nose.
Current bids: Hitting forehead - Hit wrist three
times - Highway - Open a beer bottle with nose
A slap on both cheeks.
Determined
Although he suggested it it heated up the place
A slap on each side?
Please suggest something we can do.
Suggest something more realistic
The given punishment is using
chopsticks to hit the forehead.
Chopsticks, 15 times.
Confident
What?
Chopsticks, 15 times.
15 times?
Punishments
It's rare in the auction world
Is that possible?
Yes, I can do it.
Kang Gary's specialty is enduring pain.
Ah~ Now that you mention it
Master of pain Gary
He doesn't feel pain at all.
Anyone bid higher?
16.
Sixteen is the current bid.
Twenty ~
5, 4 ...
Taehyun and Jongkook aren't you bidding?
I'm not doing it, I don't want to.
That guy is really ...
He really hates pain.
I don't want to
If you bid 22 we are going to bid 23.
I'm not going to.
Not trusting
You're not going to do that?
5, 4 ...
Kang Gary ~
25 ~
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
In an instant 25 hits breakthrough
In the end the first auction item ...
26 ~
5, 4, 3 ...
27.
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
28.
First auction item
Current bid Forehead hit 28 times
4, 3, 2 ...
If it ends like this
Sukjin pays with 28 hits on his forehead
Huk...
28 times is...
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
... 1.
Winning bid
Sukjin
Although the item isn't known yet
Cheering for Sukjin's punishment
Now ...
Let's have a look at the item.
What's wrapped under the veil
Revealed
Yes.
Jongkook usage voucher
Jongkook usage voucher.
Surprised
Woo hoo ...
Power and strength in games
Variety world's terminator Kim Jongkook
For one day He who controls Jongkook
has the universe in his hands
The ticket to victory
Jongkook usage voucher
Jongkook usage voucher.
But he's nothing today.
We can't use him for anything right now.
Because of his back injury and recent surgery
Jongkook won't be able to display much power
Why do I have to be
hit 28 times for that?
Oh my
Why don't you like it?
Today you can use him to your
heart's content the whole day.
I have to get hit first?
After you get hit you can use the voucher.
Kim Jongkook please come forward.
Why is he hitting me?
Because it's a Jongkook usage
voucher he has to hit you.
It's Jongkook usage voucher,
so who else will do it?
I will reveal a new rule now, but it only
applies for the men, not for the ladies.
I'm done for ...
"Aahhh!!", if we hear that ...
... the bid will be canceled.
When the men getting hit
make a sound the bid is
canceled
It's fine for the ladies, but if the men
let out a sound the bid is canceled.
So please be reasonable with your bids.
So only make a bid
that you can endure
Get ready.
Nervous
To sum up ...
Sukjin, you just maintain the same
pose as the one on your T-shirt.
Keep this kind of pose
Ready ... go.
Aahhh!
He made a sound
Bid canceled
How would you endure 28 hits?
We're canceling the bid.
Please bid your punishment in moderation.
Reminder
We'll start the auction again.
Jongkook user voucher
auction starts again
One hit ~
Kang Gary two hits.
Four hits ~
Five hits.
Jihyo five hits?
Yes.
Six.
Sukjin
6 hits
Die ~
Huh?
He wants to do it again?
Sold
Die ~
Sukjin wins the bid
successfully(?)
Will he be able to take 6 hits this time
Sukjin ... get ready.
Aaahhh!!
Failed also this time
The bid is
canceled again
The bid is canceled.
Stubborn
I was only taking a breath.
Please go back.
You went, "Aaahh".
Who breathes like 'Aahh'
I'm only breathing.
You screamed "Ah", please go back.
Jongkook usage voucher
3rd round auction
I was breathing.
We'll start the auction again.
One hit ~
Gary, two.
Three.
Die ~
Countdown, 5 ...
Four hits ~
Seven hits ~
5, 4 ...
Question ...
Does it mean that the Jongkook voucher ...
.. can be used all day long
in any way we want?
Use him the whole day as you like
Jongkook voucher
Of course.
If it ends like this
The Jongkook voucher will be Gary's
Gulp...
... 1, sold.
Gary
7 hits
Sold
We know Gary can endure pain well.
Master of pain
This is a golden opportunity for Gary
It will be a good day today ...
A chance to payback all the
humiliation in the past
... ﻿if you manage to endure it.
This voucher will be very useful to Gary.
To the Two Kids this is very precious
Jongkook usage voucher
Really useful.
I won't blink when I get hit.
Good.
Like a pro
Not making a sound + Not blinking
So if you blink ...
Yes, I won't blink.
That's good.
Okay, Kang Gary ...
I wouldn't take him even if he
was free, why are you guys ... ?
Later you will find out
how we can use him.
Get ready.
Gary fighting.
Maintaining his usual calm
Glaring
So far 3 hits out of 7 is okay
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
Would you like to turn back time?
At any time you can ring the bell to withdraw
How many did I do?
Three hits.
3 already?
Yes.
4 hits
5 hits
6 hits
Only one more hit and
Jongkook voucher will be in Gary's hands
All the humiliation in the past ...
Only one more hit and
Jongkook will be ours.
With this
Will be repaid
Only one more hit and
Jongkook will be ours.
Forehead hits
7 times Success
Jongkook usage voucher
successfully sold to Gary
Congratulations.
For your own words
be responsible at
Running Man auction
From now on ...
... you can use the Jongkook
usage voucher as you like.
Jongkook hyungnim can you hold this for me?
Jongkook's suffering starts now
Everyone ...
Shall we present the next item?
Yes ~
Please bring out the next item.
This time in the silver plate...?
The second item for auction.
1, 2 ...
Oih, everyone is so ...
Super nervous
You look like you are
watching the world cup.
1, 2 ... 3.
... 3.
Running Ball
The 2nd auction item is a Running Ball
I can confirm this is a Running Ball.
The teams haven't been decided yet, but ...
After the teams are decided
The team with the bidding winner gets the ball
... the ball will belong to the team
with the person who wins this.
Taehyun and Seah, do you
know what this means?
Okay.
Yes.
Every time a mission is won
the team is awarded a Running Ball
To avoid the punishment
the Running Ball is a must
Running Ball auction
Gary ...
Easy 3 times.
3 times?
For Gary 3 times is nothing
5, 4 ...
4 times ~
Joongki has four times.
7 times.
But you haven't tried it before.
I haven't... I'll be okay.
Seven times is not that easy.
5 ...
Yoon Seah, eight times.
Seah, eight times.
Eight times?
A lady being hit 8 times?
Have you ever been hit by chopsticks?
No.
Eight times, let's do it.
8 times for a lady is a bit too much.
Suddenly uneasy
Daeng Daeng Daeng
Seah
8 times
Sold
In the middle of the confusion the Running Ball is sold to Seah
Taking off the glove to
deliver the punishment
She was a delinquent
during school days.
Trembles
Now feeling the real
wood chopstick power
Still 7 hits left, are you
going through with it?
Give it up?
No.
Are you okay?
Jihyo clenching her teeth
That's too weak ~
3, 4 ...
Evenly, can you hit evenly please.
Can I do the rest?
Okay.
Looks like Jihyo has a soft heart.
Sukjin replacing Jihyo as the punisher
For now Jihyo please go back to your seat.
Worried
I'll be noona's black knight.
Are you sure?
Flower Joongki
Running Man scandal?
Drawn by the black knight Joongki ♥
He's so cool.
Taehyun, don't you want
to be a black knight?
I like white horses better.
You can just say you don't
want to be a black knight.
Refusing to be a black knight
Using white horses as an excuse
"I like white horses."
So will you be a white knight instead?
He prefers white knights to black knights
Black knight Joongki's noble sacrifice
Now the Running Ball belongs to Seah.
Running Ball
goes to Seah as the winning bidder
Seah now has one Running Ball with her.
You got a big one there
Now everyone ...
... we'll reveal the last item.
But Taehyun and Jihyo hasn't bid much,
so ﻿I look forward to your participation.
Is this the last one?
Please bring it out.
Again with excessive setup
Jongkook's stiff manager
Embarrassed
The last auction item revealed
Free!
Punishment immunity voucher
The awe-inducing auction item
Today's auction
highlight
Today's auction highlight.
It doesn't matter which
team you'll belong to.
The holder of this voucher will
be exempt from the punishment.
Running Man members'
The return of punishments
shower
brushing teeth
Hot pants nightmare
Earn the immunity
and be free from punishment
I really want that one.
Now this auction ...
If your team loses, only the one
with the voucher will be exempt.
Five times.
What?
Chopsticks five times.
This time even Jongkook
eagerly participate
I'll do 8 times.
8 times.
10 times ~
I'll bid 13 times.
You can't.
On this one I also want to bid, 13.
Of course
The auctioneer don't want to miss this precious item
I can't lose this.
16.
Seems like you really don't
want to do the punishment?
Trying hard to avoid the punishment
Yes.
17 ~
Anymore?
18 times.
Song Jihyo, 20.
Everyone is very participative
Stealthy
Hmm?
Finally
Taehyun is joining in
Cha Taehyun, 21 times.
An unknown participant has bid 21.
An anonymous participant.
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
Final countdown
... ﻿Cha Taehyun .
Taehyun
21 hits
Deal
He must hold back, right?
Yes, if he makes a sound when
getting hit the deal is canceled.
Making a sound while getting hit
The deal is canceled
Please hit fast.
Hit me five times in a row
No doubt
Someone who likes to take advantages
If he can bear it
Five times continuously.
I'm doing it.
If your team wins, all this is useless.
Taehyun ...
Wait, I can win without doing this.
the punishment-free coupon is useless
If the team Taehyun will be in wins in the end
If you want to give up, do it now.
Do you want to go back?
After getting hit like that
can't give up easily...
What should we do?
Again five times continuously?
This time three times in a row.
Five times is too much
Three times ... start.
If you want to give up,
do it while it's still early.
Ah, one moment.
Ah?
If that's so...
Deal canceled
"Ah, one moment"
because he said that
deal is canceled
Wait a sec ...
Why?
Couldn't endure the three consecutive hits
The deal is canceled.
Dong...
Punishment-free coupon
2nd round
11 times.
12 times.
Ah, that's too many.
12 ...
13 times.
15 times.
Kwangsoo and Jihyo won't give up
5, 4 ...
16 times.
Uishhh~
Snaps!
Aishhh ...
Scary
Maybe the Song Jihyo we
know is not the real Jihyo.
When the respectful Jihyo meets
the punishment-free coupon
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
Kwangsoo again?
Wait, 19 times.
20 ~
21.
Sneaks~
Calling once ...
5, 4, 3 ...
Wait, 22 times.
Jaesuk bids 22?
Yes, 22.
5, 4, 3, 2 ...
There's no way he won't make a sound.
5, 4 ...
Counting down again!
Why do you re-start the countdown?
... 2, 1, deal.
Deal
Jaesuk
22 hits
Deal
Joongkook ...
... let's take turns hitting him.
The energetic punishment carriers
I bet all of my family's property, that
he will make a noise within 5 hits.
If he doesn't make a sound before 5 hits ...
Not only can I skip the punishment ...
... I also will get all of Sukjin's property.
Jaesuk
Did not make a noise
Someone else made the sound
Jaesuk endured it
It's over right?
Now is the
time to give up
I'll just have to endure it 5 times.
Sukjin's property
C'mon...!
Ding
One hit and
gave up from the shock
I even gambled all my family's property.
I really want that coupon.
It must be under bearable conditions.
The bidding has to be
at an acceptable level for each one
Punishment-free coupon
3rd round
Starts now.
Jihyo, 5, 4, 3, 2 ...
Final countdown
I am ...
not doing it
Jihyo, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
This time it's Jihyo
Jihyo
7 hits
Deal
... 3, 2, 1.
Jihyo gets a chance due to her persistence
It's Jihyo.
It's 7 hits.
Yes.
Should I hit a few times in a row?
3-3-1.
Our audience must understand ...
... because of game's rules
we can't give special treatment.
A game is a game
Girls can shout, right?
When the girls are hit
making noise is okay
Yes.
I'm sorry
You shouldn't have ...
Three times in a row, just give up.
No way, I have to get it.
Three times ~
Another 3 hits OK!
Would be great to get the coupon
Just one last time.
5, 4, 3 ...
Wait, I'll take her punishment.
I'll take her punishment.
* Back ground music: "Put your head on my shoulder" by Paul Anka
Oh la la la la la ?
It's okay.
What should I do...
Unwilling to accept his kindness
His love line is broken.
Embarrassed
Endured
Jihyo gets the voucher.
Jihyo
finally got the punishment-free coupon
Unfortunately
Hope noona wins the game.
If her team loses, ﻿Jihyo can
skip today's punishment.
Use Jongkook
Gary
Running ball
Seah
Punishment-free
Jihyo
Members chosen by Seah
Special mission
Find the hidden famous painting
From now on...
We're not friends anymore
The battle between
the hiding and seeking people
Starts now
Current time
Containing the best art pieces
There are a lot of art pieces here ...
National Museum of Contemporary art
... so we have to walk around carefully.
Are not allowed to run in the museum
they have to speed walk instead
There's nowhere to hide.
The problem is ...
the museum is mostly open spaces
You can hide in the boxes.
Therefore hiding places were arranged
Can hide in the boxes
around the museum
In the boxes?
The hiding team
Instructions have arrived
Da Vinci
Mona Lisa
Self-portrait
van Gogh
Shin Yunbok
Portrait of a beauty
How do we do this?
Blue Team's
Mission
Find the three paintings
(Time limit: 1 hour)
Does this mean we have to find them?
We hung the paintings.
Oh, I see.
Three paintings, right?
Then we don't have to hide.
Let's start searching.
Down to earth Taehyun
You're thinking too lightly of it.
But his idea is not bad.
Maybe they could do as he said
Blue Team
Mission starts
Then Jihyo goes with Taehyun.
But this is the first time we met.
Awkward
Surprisingly Taehyun is shy
Then who do you feel
most comfortable with?
The only person I am
comfortable with is myself.
Unexpected Cha Taehyun
Looking forward to his performance
Meanwhile
The chasing team
Red Team
Jaesuk will definitely keep hiding.
Strategy time
Jaesuk will definitely hide
I can be HaHard Pitt.
Self-acclaimed Pitt
I could be Gaecholas Cage.
* Gae = Dog
Gaecholas Cage.
Not Nicholas Cage but Gaecholas Cage?
Angelina Seah?
Not Angelina Jolie but Angelina Seah
Angelina Seah, I like that.
Hyung should do one too.
JongK ~
Ah~
Not Hulk but JongK
Sparta Kook
Sparta Kook.
Joongki can be Joongde Law.
Joongki should also play the character game
Not Jude Law but Joongde Law
So Harad Pitt and Gaecholas Cage.
Gaecholas
Cage
Harad Pitt
The highlight of the names
is Gaecholas Cage
Received the instructions
Red Team's
mission
Tear off the name tags in 1 hour
of all Blue Team's members
Then let's load it up from here.
...What??...
No, I meant searching.
Embarrassed
Stronger than she looks Angelina Seah
Remaining time
'Beauty' and 'Self portrait' at 2nd floor
'Mona Lisa' at 3rd floor
Blue Team
Find the location of
the three paintings
Hurrying
Waddle
I'm really fast, right?
The comfortable one man team
speed walking
Why shocked...?
Entering the Paintings Gallery
Where is ...
'Mona Lisa', 'Self Portrait' and 'Beautiful Woman'?
Discovered something?
That's it
Shin Yunbok's 'Beautiful Woman' ... !
Powerful eyesight Cha Taehyun
He found one already...
Eh??
He didn't discover the paintings
but found a box for hiding
Leaving the painting(?)
A that moment...!
Ringing bells
Buzz~
Ringing from all four corners
the sound of the bells
Woah~
Stumble
If he does that
he'll be surrounded and caught
Last resort Hide in the box he previously discovered
Everyone ...
I ...
... ﻿couldn't find the artwork
It's right here
I'll rest a bit before I search again.
They don't know about this place.
Just like this...
time passed by
I ... in here ...
What can I see through my tears?
What am I doing in here?
In a tiny box with a camera
It'll become really hot
Hot
I can't stay here for long.
I'll take a deep breath
and get in again later.
Open~
Breathe
Ding dong ~
But Red Team is searching everywhere
The sound of bells are coming closer
going back in again
Therefor
Red Team's talent, Joongki
enters Portrait Exhibition
Right at this moment
the walkie talkie
Joongki gets closer to the exhibit
Was it heard...?
Joongki turns around
Stiff
Rigid
A reasonable distance for the sound to be heard
Passes by
If the walkie-talkie sounds again
he'll immediately be found
Panic
Ah...?
Just passing by...
Of course...
the lucky Taehyun
Truthfully...
His destiny is...?
Remaining time
On the other hand
Blue Team's members are...
Sukjin - Kwangsoo
2nd floor
Roof searching
A discovery?
He looks like Jongkook.
Hey, up there.
Who went up there?
I didn't see the color.
Who is he?
It is ...
Sparta Kook
Yah ~
2nd floor ~
Jongkook has power to summon them
Blue Team
This is the chance to catch two people
The bell sounds are coming closer
Red Team
Heading for 2nd floor roof
Big trouble!
Even in such a hurry they still have to power walk
No running is allowed in the art museum
Their hearts are in a hurry but
their bodies are wobbling
Suddenly
They caught on
Are they wobbling?
Don't run.
Blue Team's most dangerous situation yet
But ...
Also the seekers are only allowed to walk
Wobble
Long legged Kwangsoo
power-walks at the speed of light
Successfully escapes
But
Seah saw Kwangsoo
2nd floor, Kwangsoo is on 2nd floor.
Desperately wants to run but he can only walk
Hearing Seah's cry they all gathered up
Ambushed and surrounded
In the end
Harad Pitt
No.
Blue Team
Kwangsoo
During the commotion
Jihyo finds a place to hide
Once again Red Team catches on
Jihyo, we're here.
Catch Jihyo.
Target secured
Jihyo enters the shopping mall of no escape
Jihyo, you shouldn't enter that place.
Both of them still remembers to power-walk
There is no escape now
Blue Team
Jihyo
Time remaining
Hooo~
They are like five ghosts.
Even at the emergency corridor
the bells can be heard
Where is the bell sounding from?
Top...!
Even in the emergency corridors
there's people
Wobble
Seriously
The infamous hide-n-seek master
Super sonic speed power-walking
Vrrr~ooom !
Jaesuk at 1st floor basement A dead end
Lies ...
...down?
Ah... Won't he be seen from above?
I should've been a seeker instead.
Meanwhile...
In the boiling hot box
lies Cha Taehyun
Opens
Sweating...
As if in a sauna
There are still bell sounds around
Careful
Still haven't realized...
Runs in the opposite direction of the bell sounds
But there's also bell sounds at the opposite direction
Taehyun
Finally... Re-enters the box
Gave him a fright
Again
Enters the boiling hot box again
He continues to look down
with a strange face
Ka dong ...
Suddenly it's quiet
Taehyun comes out again
But he hears
the bells again
Go back in?
Or not?
Sigh...
I heard the bell, the bell.
The lid is shut tightly, when...
The
sound
is
getting
closer
Who's the owner of the god-forsaken sound?
Sparta!
The strongest seeker
Sparta Kook
It's here ~
Cha Concubine
His biggest crisis
Ring~
This box...
is a little...
Dun dun !
Huh?
An empty box!!
I'm to good at entertainment.
The box where
Taehyun was in before
Now he is in the
box across the hall
Gone ...
As expected
Cha Concubine the luckiest man in the world
He can finally search for the artwork
Not even one of them has been found
Blue Team
Mona Lisa - Portrait - Beauty
Seekers
Red Team keeps on seeking
Taehyun finally meets team mate Sukjin
Looks around
Hyung, come this way.
You hid inside that box?
It's so hot, you can't even breath.
Huh?
This is the 'Beauty'.
Finally...
Yunbok's "Portrait of a Beauty" is discovered
If Taehyun had been alert
he would have found it earlier
Beep
Shocked
Siren goes off
Beep
Beep ~
Behind the three artworks
there's an alarm siren device
They must run to save their lives
Seekers
Hears the alarm and starts to seek
There's an alarm on them.
But still
Found 1 of 3 paintings
Portrait of a Beauty
Cha Concubine
Escapes from the exhibit
Taehyun spotted
As soon as he escapes...!
3rd floor ~
Coincidentally Sparta Kook is nearby
Taehyun running
towards Jongkook
Bye, I won't
get caught
Cha Concubine not knowing anything
Sw... oo... sh
Captured
Sparta Kook ambush
Success
Ah, that scared me.
Seah found Taehyun
She's an outstanding helper
I caught this fool.
It's really hard to breathe, over at that side.
Where were you?
In a box, similar to that box.
But didn't I look through it?
still others hiding to be apprehended
Taehyun is caught
In that one.
Ah, the other one.
Taehyun
Blue Team
Time remaining
Meanwhile
Lying on the staircase floor
Yooruce Willis
Sukjin, where are you?
My back is cold.
Lying too long on the cold stair
Wiggle
So he won't be spotted from the top
Yooruce Willis new technique
Rolling up while hiding behind the steps
There's not much time left
Yooruce Willis needs to find the 2 remaining portraits
Elevator is dangerous
Taking the chance to ride the elevator up
Without hesitation Search from the highest floor
Realizing that
the Red Team
is nowhere in sight
Along the 3rd floor corridor hangs "Mona Lisa"
Upon hearing the surrounding's silence... Opportunity
One of the remaining portraits "Mona Lisa"
Finally discovered it
Not knowing about the alarm
Why can't I
take it out?
What the ... !!
Confused
Stopping will only cause a major problem
Have to escape and hide first
Chaser
Alerted by the siren
This time...
From where...
Red Team
Tracing the path towards the siren's location
What was that?
Anyway
Blue Team
got 2 of the 3 portraits
That really scared me.
Meanwhile
Sukjin was spotted
Stumble
Where did he go?
Sukjin hyung ~
Spotted
Hurry come here, Gary is coming.
Gary, Seah
Chasing toward the elevator
If the Blue Team gets caught their chances will vanish
Ugh!
Angelina Seah
is in front of them
Hurry and close it.
Just
then
Phewww...
Life shortened with 10 years
What did you find?
Where did you find this?
It was hanging on the middle of the wall.
What about yours?
This was also hanging on the wall.
But the title next to it was different.
It was?
The title had been replaced by the crew.
Is anyone on the first floor?
Arriving at the first floor
You go first, I will head
back up to the 2nd floor.
Yoo Jaesuk ~
2nd floor ~
Yooruce Willis
Just arrived at 1st floor
Immediately being chased
Ugh!!
Red Team is everywhere
Revealing Yooruce Willis'
speed walking escape ability
The VJ is also walking fast ~
Yooruce Willis
Tries to walk in a circle to escape
But is it possible to escape by doing that?
Harad Pitt
Covering up the tracks
Here comes Joongki
Suddenly
Hyung come and help me.
Blue Team
Yooruce Willis
Captured
What's that?
I got caught.
Blue Team
Jaesuk
He is still in the elevator.
He went down from the
2nd floor using the elevator.
Information received
Sparta Kook
Heading to the 2nd floor elevator
Its nerve wrecking.
And then the one that's going up
Very nervous.
Arrived at 2nd floor
Sparta Kook
Just in front of the elevator
Doors opening.
Huh? What...?
Please...
There's nothing else inside
Door please close...
It won't close
When did he appear?
But ...
From his angle Sukjin can't see Sparta Kook
Still pressing the close button
Why isn't the door closing?
He is ...
coming over
Because it was so absurd they can only laugh
So it's like this?
Why didn't you just come in straight away?
Given up
Hurry come over here.
I'll give you this and you let me go.
Please
How did you know I was here?
When I was going by,
the doors just opened.
The doors opened and
Blue pants can be seen in the mirror
Eventually went in and
found the last member
Why am I just so unlucky?
I wish you just could pass by.
Still ...
... giving it up like this would be a pity.
What will you do?
I'll try and escape from you.
There's no chance at all
Blue Team
Sukjin
Mission failed
Everyone
I just needed to get
that one last portrait.
Red Team
Running ball
Acquired
Current time
Leisurely tea time.
Mission 3
Time for leisure cup of tea
PD explaining the rules for the game
One person from each
team needs to be excluded.
Exclude me ~
Why does it have to be you
when there is Jihyo here?
Only thinking about resting...
The first domestic surprising(?) guest
Four members on each team have
to memorize a picture and draw it.
Memory drawing
After the excluded members see the drawings ...
... they have to go the the exhibition
hall and take a replica picture.
The fastest team with
the correct picture wins.
First we have to decide
who is going to stay here.
Who is going to stay?
Hyung, is your drawing good.
Not at all.
Jihyo?
I'm not good at it.
Jihyo what exactly are you good at?
Love, Jihyo is good at love.
Love snows on Gary.
When it comes to Jihyo's love topic
Gary starts
Jihyo, what are you good at?
Love ...
Blushing
Let us leave Gary and Jihyo
together and the rest of us go.
Others' awkwardness is our happiness
Gary-Jihyo Both of them excluded
Let the two of them get
closer with each other.
We are already close.
I'm close with oppa.
Then do you know each
other's phone number?
If close they should know each other's number
No, I don't know it.
What's the age difference
between the two of you?
Four.
4 years difference between Gary and Jihyo
Difference by four?
It doesn't seem like it
4 years difference?
By looking at their appearance
It doesn't look like they are 4 years apart?
Like four letter for love to death ?
* "Love to death" in Korean contains 4 letters
Reversal
The phenomenon of being so greasy
Becoming arrogant based on the greasy words
Ah ya, what is this smell?
I've never ﻿heard before such
a mushy thing in my life.
Gary ...
... make it look like it's love until death.
Red Team leaves Gary behind
Sets off
Where would the art exhibition be?
Blue Team follows
Also setting off
Where are you going?
What? Jihyo what's wrong?
We'll go and be back.
Jihyo, right now only
the game is important.
Not letting go
of their hands
It's okay to lose this game.
There's a punishment that needs
to be prevented from happening.
Cruel reality
We can't go against the rules.
The elders making her stay
Jihyo, you have to just stay here.
Just stay, you don't have
to talk if it's awkward.
It's already awkward.
Then...
There's only the two of them left
Ah, why is this so awkward?
During the games it's not so apparent
Ah, it's hot.
Two of them alone Really awkward
Jihyo keeps fanning herself
Gary pretend to be busy by looking elsewhere
Glances~
Jihyo also
glances ~
They secretly keep looking at each other
Will they be able to get closer?
The rest of the team members
paintings they saw earlier
Examines the
That one illustrates Gary and Jihyo.
Slave Gary
Miss Jihyo
But it's too long.
Although very nice it's very big
Wouldn't this be easy?
Has Blue Team finally decided on one?
This one is really cool.
If you put this up at home
wouldn't it be kind of scary?
You think so?
It might turn around.
Scary?
Even good painting can have weird audience
It's Andy Warhol.
The great pop artist
Andy Warhol's [self portrait]
Let's go.
They decided on the Andy Warhol piece
Chosen.
Okay.
That's good.
Meanwhile the blue team
It looks like our hyung.
One of Korea's great artists
Kim Duhwan's [self portrait]
Self portrait by Duhwan.
Jihyo can find this.
Looking carefully to remember it
Can they remember and paint it well?
Meanwhile...
Gary awkwardly walks back and forth
Guess who?
No need to overreact Jihyo.
Joking around to get closer
It was because you surprised me.
But ended more awkward...
And again silence ...
Jihyo must be really hot
Jihyo, I'm going out for a while.
I'm going out for a while.
Okay, come back soon.
He's heading to ...
Get something for Jihyo who is tired of the heat
Cold coffee machine
Can this cup of coffee
bring them closer?
Oh no, he's back.
Nervous
Did you only get one cup?
A cup of coffee
only for her
Wow, ice coffee?
I didn't have enough coins.
You can have it.
Sweetness
You're really thoughtful.
Grateful
It's nothing.
Ah, it's hot ...
Acting cool after buying her one coffee
Don't worry about me,
just enjoy your coffee.
Suddenly
...Huh?
Kind hearted Jihyo
Sharing the ice coffee
What does this mean?
With one cup of coffee the atmosphere cools down
Should we toast?
Just ...
... because we're being awkward.
Did you like the taste?
It's a bit bland.
Because there's not enough of my sincerity?
It's back!
Gary's nausea-inducing comments
I haven't been this nice
to a girl so it's awkward.
Finishing in one go
One shot!
Is it time for you to get married?
You're in your mid 30s.
I don't have plans yet.
Are you in a hurry?
... in a hurry?
Speechless...
At least with one cup of coffee
They got a little closer to each other
Can you act like we're close
so I don't embarrass myself?
Red Team arrived first
Looks like we came back too fast.
Sorry.
Slicky
Moving next to Jihyo?!
Stunned~
What does it mean?
Those two ...
When will they get closer?
Have you chosen one?
We might have chosen the same one.
Drawing from memory
I can't remember it well.
Drawing started
Speedy completion?
Kwangsoo's exactly the same.
It's a photo.
Time's up
Don't look over here yet.
Let's choose one drawing
from the opposite team.
One that's least similar.
Okay ~
I don't know if this will work.
An animated character
What is this?
Sukjin's ugly drawing
Chosen!
Red Team drawings revealed
Let's see your drawings.
Joongki's exactly the same.
The simple drawing
by Joongki is chosen
I'll be back.
The person that returns first
with the correct picture wins
Jihyo and Gary must find the actual
painting from their team's drawing
Why is this a kid's drawing?
It's exactly you. Want to see?
The rest of the team
Drawing self portraits
One drawing that stands out
from Jongkook's creations
It is similar ... isn't it?
At first glance ...
you know who it is
Why did you draw me like this?
It's exactly the same.
Match rate
I don't look like that.
You do.
They are here.
They're back?
Who came back first?
It's Jihyo ~
Blue Team's Jihyo arrived first
Our team is really bad at drawing.
Gary's back.
Also Gary arrived
Let's look at Jihyo's first.
If Jihyo's picture is correct
then Blue Team wins
1, 2, 3.
And the ...
... result
From this drawing
did she find the right painting?
... 2, 3.
Success
Even they are
amazed~
Those are
the same?
Even with a bad drawing she did find it
It's similar.
Seriously, how is this similar?
Then ... let's look at Gary's.
1, 2, 3.
Ugh!
The painting is right but why is Jihyo there?
But why is Jihyo there?
She just materialized into the picture.
Round 1 is over
Blue Team
wins
So now the losing team
will chose the spoons first.
Oh yeah, here's the cart.
Not again
Excessive setup by Jongkook's manager
Go back with a moonwalk.
Huh? What was that?
That's just a turn...
Embarrassed
Was he just nervous?
Or doesn't he know what the moonwalk is?
Everyone, for the coffee ...
Red Team
Coffee spoon selection
... make your choices.
Number one ~
You should have mixed it up well.
Shame ...
Just a normal spoon for Jongkook
Major relief to Jongkook who doesn't drink coffee
Brimful
One spoon with overflowing affection
Okay, Seah.
Number three ~
Seah loves coffee and chooses number 3
Soup...
...ladle
What should I do?
The fun and lively Seah
seems to really love coffee
Do you like coffee?
I absolutely love it.
Eyes wide open
How many cups is that for
Cut it down ~
Take off more.
What are you gonna do
to take some off hers?
Then Jaesuk
throws a surprise offer
will he take some of her coffee?
Jongkook who doesn't drink coffee
You said you liked coffee?
I can't trust anyone here...
If it's this much, it's okay.
Give me that.
In the end
Jongkook pours some of Seah's coffee into his cup
You're so cool.
Touched
He's such a hypocrite.
Backfired
Flood of criticism
Joongki's turn ...
Are you jealous of Gary?
No, I'm not.
"Love-lines are my thing".
* Teasing Jongkook about his love lines in earlier shows
Annoying
Even a good deed gets no praise in Running Man
Pick number three.
Number three.
Joongki follows Jaesuk's recommendation
He really trusts me.
Huh!
Woven bamboo spoon
Ah, what's that?
Why did you listen to him?
That one scoops a lot.
I've tried it before.
A worrying start
Next, Gary.
I'll go with number four.
Aigoo, what to do with this?
That's a spoon for drinking makgeolli.
* Makgeolli = Korean rice wine
A spoon big enough to make a big bowl of coffee
Hold on.
Isn't this the right time to use
the Jongkook usage voucher ?
The item he won at the auction Jongkook usage voucher
Why does it have to be at this time
Jongkook voucher can be used
Yes, you can use it,
Then I'll use it now.
Switching Gary's and Jongkook's cups
Tact
Sorry
He's thinking hard to save his body.
HaHa's turn.
I'll take number one.
Aigoo, congratulations.
A frying skimmer
What is that?
Won't it fall through?
But ...
The coffee powder can't pass through the net
This coffee powder won't pass through.
It won't drop ~
Make it full.
Okay.
I'll help you pour in the right-amount.
One
full cup
Hyung, it's already full.
Speechless
You can't add any water.
Not even a space for water
Put in the water.
Okay ~
This is too full.
Although there's less coffee
it's still a great amount
If it's too much, I will give
you a chance to lessen it.
Including this ear digger.
Really?
Choose one out of two.
Hold a spoon in each hands
and they choose one hand.
Choose one of my hands.
Left and right hand.
Thank you.
Yeah ~
The left-right-hand game, Jongkook.
Yes.
Which hand will Jongkook choose?
Is it ready?
Pick left hand.
Right hand.
Jongkook chose the ear picker
Didn't I tell you to pick the left hand.
Today ...
What's wrong with me?
This kid didn't even want to listen to me.
Jongkook can't make it.
Seah ...
Left hand.
Seah also chose the ear picker
What should I choose?
What's it for Brain Joongki?
Left hand.
They made the same choice
This is getting mysterious ...
Really, how could we
be so bad at guessing?
This isn't a prank, is it?
Absolutely not, I hold them in full view.
Jihyo, tell him which hand to choose.
A special hint from Jihyo to Gary
Jihyo, can you please tell me.
Oppa, choose left.
Left hand.
Choose left.
Slowly~
Had trust in her
Betrayed
Hey, it was the right hand.
It was the right hand?
Jihyo mistook
the left hand for the right hand
Why are you treating me like this?
No matter what Gary is hurt
She though it was the left hand.
Putting one scoop or not
doesn't make a difference.
I raised it like this.
Lastly How will HaHa do?
Left hand.
Ah...
Caught in a moment
There's no such thing in this world
A result no one expected
I gave you all a chance.
We were all victims.
Director, what is the next game?
The throwing coins game is next.
Everyone will stand behind the line and
throw the coins into a bowl with water.
If all members in a team
succeed, then that team wins.
Ah, that game.
A game which everyone played as kids
I played it many times in the past.
First up is the Red Team
Come over here.
You want us to hold on to you?
Jongkook success
Stop pushing me forward all the time.
That doesn't seem to help.
Will this method work?
It will work.
Hey, move your body more forward.
Slap!
Once again scolded by Jongkook
Don't you have the Jongkook voucher?
Aha!
Time for Jongkook voucher
Throw it in, don't try to be funny.
Aren't you supposed to lean
forward when you throw?
The coin rebounded from the tip of the bowl
Explodes
Seah scores with ease
Even Seah could throw it in.
If Jongkook hadn't missed they would have succeeded in 1 try
Today's unfortunate man, Jongkook
We can't do it like that?
Big Nose hyung is full of confidence
In the midst of throwing coin lesson
Do this, don't do that.
Aim and then quickly throw.
Is that hard?
Jihyo
practicing her aim
Shoo~
It counts.
Jihyo, leave it and come back here.
Immediately placing Jihyo as the first player
What do you think you're doing?
Jihyo succeeded, it counted.
A sudden conflict between the teams
Really, why are you guys like that?
Nagging
Next
Jaesuk challenges
A confirmed
success
Kwangsoo ~
An atmosphere as if they already won
You are stepping on the
line, you little mustache.
You also have a mustache.
Mustache VS Mustache
Move forward a bit more.
Kwangsoo's using his long body to help him
Shoo~
It looks similar to the painting
"Creation of the World".
Running Man
the World Creator
... the painting "Creation of the World".
Oh?
Kwangsoo failed
You idiot.
Such a pity 'You idiot' slipped out of his mouth
There was just a small distance.
Carefully think about it, Kwangsoo.
Blue Team isn't able to hide their regret
Red Team gets another chance
We can do it, finish them off.
First player
Joongki
A man capable of anything Joongki
Succeeds with ease
You stepped on the line.
Hold it like that.
Scores
Jongkook made up for his previous failure
HaHa is getting ready
After one success...
MC Muscle starts to teach the others
That team really doesn't have any strategy.
They only know how to
follow Jongkook's instructions.
HaHa can't do his own thinking.
It won't go in.
Under Jongkook's supervision
HaHa succeeded
Well done.
Throw it like this.
As expected Gary has a quick lesson
If you want to do that,
you must run from the side.
It's really uncomfortable.
Hyung, I don't feel comfortable like this.
No ...
Without a doubt, "I feel uncomfortable".
Gary.
Okay.
In the end
Gary succeeds with his own method
Seah, all you have to do is succeed.
Red Team's last player
Yoon Seah
Seah succeeds easily
Red Team
Succeeds in the 2nd attempt
In the end
the harmonious side wins
The team that drinks fastest wins
This is too bitter.
Both teams will drink at the same time
The team that finishes first wins
Really bitter.
Kwangsoo and I will drink together.
HaHa and Kwangsoo Start
Fighting Kwangsoo.
We need to win.
The reaction start once they drink
Unknowingly letting out a sigh
Using whatever time to cool the coffee
HaHa
finished
Speed gets faster with each turn
Struggle
In a mess
Red Team
2nd player Gary
1st player Kwangsoo
Blue Team
Kwangsoo, drink it all up.
Kwangsoo
Gulps it down
Drink it all up.
At last
It's Taehyun's turn
Eh?
Why did he go to the front?
Finding a good spot to sit down
Taehyun ~
Quietly~
As expected from Cha Concubine
What? You're allowed to do that?
Time out
Taehyun, good job.
Still drinking during this confusion
Taehyun, finish quickly.
Finish drinking by breaking the rules
Taehyun
Now Blue Team is in the lead
Jihyo ~
Gary
finishes
Not used to bitter drinks
3rd player Joongki
Can't stand hot drinks
3rd player Jihyo
So hot.
As expected
Okay, hurry up.
Jihyo's faster
3rd player
4th player
Battle between Joongki and Sukjin
Joongki...
Pushes his limits
Success
A fan of coffee Seah Red Teams 4th player
Pretend you are filming a commercial.
Also Seah has a difficult time
Unknowingly a close battle between the teams
Seah succeeds with her fast speed
Sukjin is still fighting the bitterness
Faster ~
Competing with a weak coffee drinker MC Muscle
This is too hot.
Sukjin resorts to pouring the rest into Jaesuk's cup
Finally the battle between
the last players of each team
Kim Jongkook ~
But...
the members have no sympathy
It's too bitter.
The bitterness is worse than the heat
Taehyun is obstruction
Jongkook from taking the lead
Taehyun's grudge toward the winner
Despite Taehyun's interference
Jongkook continues
Taehyun, you can't do that.
Compared to Jongkook the others are noisy
Eh...?!
What happened?
Jaesuk finished in one gulp
Blue Team wins
Jaesuk, unbelievable.
Should we laugh or ...
remain bitter?
It wasn't me who drank it at the end.
Who was it?
Good job ~
Jaesuk doesn't want to do a one shot
Blue Team's hidden MVP Taehyun
Blue Team
Won the last Running Ball
Taehyun, yah ...
Current time
What is the punishment for today?
Time to decide which team gets punished
Today's punishment is to go to the coffee
shop to drink coffee with make up on.
Wearing make-up and punishment clothes
and drink coffee in a crowded coffee house.
Let's put in the balls.
Red Team: 2 balls
Blue Team: 1 ball
The ball's color represents the winning team
Taehyun's luck is really good.
Seah should join our team.
Will Taehyun's luck continue?
The results are always different.
Jihyo doesn't need to
take the punishment, right?
Ah, that's right.
That's why her expression is so relaxed.
Calm
Blow faster.
Red Team
Running Balls
Blue Team
Taehyun, we can't not win.
In the midst
of praying
Taehyun, will we win or lose?
Seems like we will win.
Cheerful
3, 2 ...
Will Taehyun's prediction be correct?
Who will escape?
... 2, 1.
Who'll be humiliated
in Hongdae?
It's coming ~
Red ball!!
Red Team's
escape confirmed
Thankful
Taehyun's prediction
was inaccurate
Quietly
Jihyo naturally moves to the escaping team
My luck has been used up.
Lost Taehyun's luck~
Blue Team makeover done
Joker Jaesuk
Chick Taehyun
Going to Hongdae
in this look
Fashion tattoo
Go to the convenience store first
and eat a bowl of instant noodles.
HaHa and Jongkook help with the punishment
To do what?
Stand outside and whoever finishes
the fastest gets to go home first.
Really?
Concentrated
Heading to a convenience store in Hongdae
We all look like musical actors.
Like if we just finished performing.
A gathering after performance?
Hey Crystal.
Crystal, where did she go?
Calling you.
Musical star
Crystal
Anthony.
Jonathan.
Jonathan, Crystal, Anthony.
Jonathan-Crystal-Anthony
The 3 musical actors
Reached Hongdae
Hurry up.
Is it crowded at this time...?
Why are there so many people?
Embarrassing
Excited
Embarrassing.
I love you.
Messy
Arrived at the convenience store
Running Man, Yoo Jaesuk is there.
Messy again
Embarrassing
More and more people gather outside
A shy 'V'
Click
Already a lot of people
outside
There are even more people
than I have imagined.
There is even
Who knew there would be so
many people at Hongdae at 5 AM.
foreigners
A sea of people
Countdown.
3, 2, 1.
Time to eat instant noodles
Supper time
Just eat at your own pace everyone
They're embarrassed so they eat as fast as they can
Ah, so hot.
They all want to return home
Quiet~
Focused onlookers
Jaesuk goes home first
Leaving the set in the midst of a cheering crowd
Following is Kwangsoo
Kwangsoo's passionate fan(?)
Next to leave is Taehyun
Celebrating with an onlooker before leaving
Now all there's left is...
Only uncle Sukjin
How were they so fast?
So pitiful ...
Eating noodles at dawn
alone in Hongdae
Finally
Sukjin finished the punishment
Tidying up the dirty bowls
Goodbye.
In the center of Seoul
Seoul Post Tower
A pleasure to see Kim Jaedong
the return of Jung Yonghwa
No matter how the post tower looks
there will be games fun and laughter
And more exciting game