What happened to your clothes?
- Hello.
- Hi.
They're nice.
(Jong Kook's ready.)
- Why are you so early?
- What?
Why are you here already?
I had something in the morning.
What's up with your clothes?
You're wearing dress shoes.
What's going on?
To kick you.
(Running away)
I'm scared.
Let's get ready for the shoot.
- Let's get ready.
- Did you get bitten?
Isn't it nice?
You look cute.
You lost so much weight.
How can you spit all the way here?
I'm sorry.
Because I have a protruding mouth.
You lost so much weight.
I was talking to Se Chan,
and he spit on me.
It's amazing. It's unbelievable.
We were talking, and he spit on me.
I'm sorry.
I have a protruding mouth.
My mouth is in good condition today.
Did you want to call dibs on me
that badly?
Seriously. No matter how far we are.
How did I spit all the way there?
I saw the show yesterday.
We were very close.
Did you know...
- I watched it too.
- your hat matched my hairband?
Really?
(Matching green clothes)
(They also had a hug to celebrate
which only couples do.)
You hugged me...
like we were dating.
I was surprised to see that too.
In fact, you were doing this.
She was that happy to win.
She hugged me like
I was her boyfriend.
I worked out yesterday.
Yesterday?
- You texted me yesterday.
- The stairs? Okay.
You have to go lower...
to use your hip muscles
and hamstrings.
It rather feels heavy.
I'll teach you later.
- Jong Kook. The shoot has begun.
- What?
- The shoot has begun.
- Already?
It has?
- You should've told me.
Are the cameras rolling?
What's taking them so long?
Tell them to hurry up.
He was sitting like this
for too long.
Jong Kook.
- I was...
- You were like this the whole time.
I thought it was a calendar shoot.
A personal conversation.
What are you wearing?
- What?
- I asked the same question.
A celebrity should dress nicely.
- Haha. Your sunglasses are...
- He has something today.
Haha.
Why are you wearing sunglasses?
He's trying to look cool.
If he takes them off...
From some point on,
you stress me out.
Why?
She nags at me now.
- Why?
- The camera must've captured it.
When I look at you, you're like...
(What are you looking at?)
I used to do that.
She does that to me.
When I saw your head,
I wanted to try it.
- Hey.
- No, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- Anything but this.
- She'd really do it.
- Just wear a wig.
- Wear a wig instead.
- That's wrong.
- Don't go this far.
- Not this.
I support your hairstyle,
but that's gone too far.
- If you want to try it,
- I want to try it.
- you should join a movie.
- Wear a wig instead.
What's taking Suk Jin so long?
What's wrong with him?
Why is he late?
Because he forgot where he started.
Can you video call him?
I'll video call him.
(Jae Suk video calls Suk Jin.)
- No.
- But it's true.
He's not picking up.
He noticed it.
He noticed it?
- Is he in the elevator? No.
- I think he's in the restroom.
He'd still answer it.
He's never late,
but he's late today.
Suk Jin is full of himself now.
- Yes.
- He's...
- in the early stage.
- This is...
Nothing else explains it,
but that he's full of himself.
He's in the early stage.
The manager is nervous,
but the celeb is like, "It's fine."
"I'm supposed
to be five minutes late."
That's how it begins.
You can see through this shirt.
What are you doing?
I know.
- She touches him now.
- You can see it through.
- She doesn't hesitate.
- I can see my fingers through it.
- Still, don't put your fingers in.
- It's okay to see it through.
- Hey.
- That's wrong.
You can see my fingers.
- I mean,
- Ji Hyo's become bold.
- I love it.
- A shirt can be that thin.
- I'm a fan.
- What about his nipples?
You can't see them.
What are you talking about?
- The pockets make two layers.
- Don't take it too far.
When you act like that,
I don't want to join you.
- This is crazy.
- We were probably on the same page.
You have to show
that you don't like it.
Now that Ji Hyo is so aggressive,
I think it's time for me to move on.
- Are they breaking up?
- No.
I have to look for
another make-believe relationship.
We better try harder.
- We must work hard.
- But he's not interested in us.
You're...
I'm sorry.
(They're not his concern.)
I'm sorry, but I'm not interested
in your relationship.
We need one more person.
What do you think about
Se Chan making moves on me?
I was like, "Hey."
- He's...
- We will...
- No.
- That's not it.
When you do that, you look pitiful.
I see.
- If you do that,
- When I do that?
you look pitiful.
Why isn't he picking up?
He's in the restroom.
He has the mic on.
- Does he have the mic on?
- How could he go to the restroom...
with the mic on?
If he goes to the restroom with
the mic on, it records everything.
But no matter how much he tries,
nothing records.
- Really?
- Yes.
- No matter how much he strains,
- There's nothing to record.
there's no sound whatsoever.
He's weak. He's here.
The star is here.
- Hello.
- Suk Jin.
You were supposed to be here
by 9:30 a.m.
- You're late.
- Why didn't you tie your shirt?
Why did you cut your clothes?
- Is that hanbok?
- Wear your clothes properly.
- What's going on?
- He's wearing new clothes.
You're not supposed to tie them.
- Where do I sit?
- You know nothing about fashion.
- You can sit here.
- Just stand up.
- Stand up.
- Sit here.
- It's been a while.
- That stings.
- You can sit here.
- Move aside.
You were supposed to be here
by 9:30 a.m. Why are you late?
I was waiting in the car.
- What? I didn't see you.
- There was no place to wait.
- I parked my car somewhere else.
- Suk Jin.
You already got criticized
by viewers.
- It's okay now.
- Because I'm late?
- Tell them not to curse at you.
- From the beginning.
That's not it. Dear viewers.
It's not that I'm late. They're early.
- "Dear viewers."
- They got here early.
He's fighting with them now.
- "Dear viewers?"
- Don't curse at me please.
- I love it.
- Me too.
- "Don't curse at me."
- I mean...
"Don't yell at me."
I mean, they got here early.
- It's true that we got here early,
- But you were late.
but you were a bit late,
and the camera rolled early.
- Right.
- It was already rolling.
All those conditions made
people blame you.
- But...
- If you apologize, it'll be over.
- I was waiting.
- You have no choice.
- If you apologize, it's over.
- You have to apologize first.
- But I did nothing wrong.
- If you weren't...
If you weren't late,
it would've been fine.
- But you were late a bit.
- You have no choice.
- Apologize first.
- I'm not late.
- It was 9:30 a.m.
- You should've been here by then.
- What time is it?
- The call was...
- We had to standby at 10 a.m.
- Yes.
- The shoot begins at 10 a.m.
- It's still 9:59 a.m.
You were supposed to be here
by 9:30 a.m,
- but you weren't here.
- The call was at 9:50 a.m.
Fine. Is it over if I apologize?
Yes.
Ask for their forgiveness.
"Don't blame me. I'm sorry."
You won't blame me, right?
From the start?
That's how misunderstanding begins.
That's how it begins.
Something happened lately.
Jong Kook and So Min made...
- a YouTube clip together.
- On MBTI.
- MBTI?
- He checked his.
In the clip,
he said...
we manipulated the soccer scene.
Don't be ridiculous.
It wasn't manipulated.
- How was that manipulated?
- I think...
Let's be honest.
The shoot was manipulated.
Do you agree?
Think about it. I never said...
I was good at soccer
on Running Man before.
I never said I was good.
I always say I'm not bad.
- How can we manipulate it?
- Jong Kook.
You thought it was so unfair.
You played soccer on "My Little Old Boy."
- I was good on "My Little Old Boy."
- You were very good.
When I was shooting "My Little Old Boy."
there were some women watching us.
They all said this,
including the judge.
I shot Running Man the week before.
They said, "That was manipulated."
What are you talking about?
It wasn't manipulated.
Look.
Bad and good aren't
the only expressions.
- What else is there?
- What?
That I'm not bad.
- I'm not that good.
- Good job.
- There are various expressions.
- That's...
very positive.
- Why do you always say...
- He's making a concession.
I'm bad or I'm terrible?
- So people think I'm terrible.
- You may not be terrible.
But it's also nice
when I go play soccer.
People think I'm terrible,
so if I do well even for a bit,
they say, "You're very good."
(You're very good.)
"You're not that bad."
Everyone says that.
They're surprised.
It's good because they don't have
high expectations of me.
We say Jong Kook is terrible...
because compared to his passion
for soccer...
- and the amount of time he spends,
- So,
you should I'm not that good
compared to my passion.
- Don't just say he's terrible.
- Right.
Exactly.
- When it comes to soccer...
- I know.
- When it's about soccer...
- He's so sensitive...
- when it's about him.
- You get too sensitive.
Jong Kook.
(Glaring)
He goes crazy when it's about him.
Haha. Look here.
Don't turn your head that way.
- Everyone.
- Yes.
We have two teams...
who are coming back this summer.
- Two teams?
- Are there two?
I hear Jong Kook is releasing
a new song.
I know one.
I got the text yesterday.
It's Jong Kook and KCM.
- Kang Chang Mo.
- There are...
- KCM.
- two people who are coming back.
Let's bring them in.
- Who is it?
- Please come out.
- I hear high heels.
- Hello.
Chorong.
- Chorong.
- Hello.
(Bomi and Chorong of Apink)
- Bomi.
They're Apink.
(Chorong and Bomi of Apink
are debuting as a unit.)
Are they our guests today?
Bomi. You lost so much weight.
You lost so much weight.
- You...
- What's going on?
Long time no see.
- We'll say hello. In 1, 2, 3.
- They created a new unit.
- Hello. We're from Apink.
- Chorong.
- Bomi.
- We're ChoBom.
- Bom.
What was that?
- We're ChoBom.
- Bom.
- Do it again.
- Try it again.
- Is it ChoBom?
We're still new.
- Do it again.
- Let's try that again.
- Hello. We're from Apink.
- Chorong.
- Bomi.
- We're ChoBom.
- It's ChoBom.
- It's a new unit.
- It's a new unit?
- Yes.
Twelve years after our debut,
we debuted as ChoBom.
- We're in a live cafe today.
- Yes.
We misunderstood the theme.
You didn't know
you were singing live?
We thought we were performing
as we always do.
Did you think you were singing
with the AR on?
- You can do that.
- Do that then.
- That's what we did.
- What?
But it's a live cafe.
Just do it then.
Our new song...
- hasn't been released yet.
- Really?
So we can only show it
to you briefly.
Is this the first time?
Yes. We're revealing it
for the first time on Running Man.
- Thank you.
- Let's do that.
- Good.
- We'll reveal it here.
(Revealing ChoBom's new song
for the first time)
- This is it.
- The new song.
- Is it ChoBom?
- ChoBom.
("Copycat" by ChoBom)
Come on.
(Cheering)
(Men are excited.)
Come on.
- Good.
- Let's go.
(The key choreography is addictive.)
(Here's the bad example.)
(Cheering)
- Good.
- They're stars.
Stars. We have stars.
- They're stars from my town.
- ChoBom.
- Go, ChoBom.
- It was very nice.
- Thank you.
I liked it.
The dance reminded me
of the tyrannosaurus.
Is it a cat?
- It's a cat.
- That was a cat?
- Because...
- I liked the dance.
It's a cat.
- We'll stop here.
- That was nice.
- Thank you.
- Have a seat here.
- Apink is pretty much...
- They're pretty.
- Our family.
- our family.
Right. They worked with us
many times before.
There's another performance.
- I know who this is.
- It's another special guest.
We already said it's KCM.
- I know who it is.
- We already talked about it.
- Hang on.
- Jong Kook is...
I need to change my voice
from talking to singing.
- Change your voice.
- The singer mode.
Jong Kook wears black pants...
- for weddings or...
- He's wearing dress shoes.
You're not wearing shorts.
- He had a reason.
- You're not wearing shorts.
- Because he has to sing.
- First,
let's bring in one of the duo.
- Duo?
- They sound like thieves.
Are they thieves? A thief duo?
Hey. They sound like robbers.
He's here.
- KCM.
- My Running Man.
- Dear brothers and sisters.
- Harmonica.
Maybe not sisters. Hellucca.
(Hellucca.)
- Jong Kook doesn't like it.
- I'm sick of it.
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook doesn't like it.
- He brought a harmonica with him.
He's too cheerful.
(Upbeat)
They look like two thugs
from the neighborhood.
Two thugs.
They look like thugs from a cartoon.
They look like two thugs...
singing together.
- I'm wearing a gold necklace.
- Hang on.
- A gold necklace?
- Do you have a name?
We don't have a name.
We just do it.
You should be Kook and Myun.
- Kook and Myun.
- That's a good idea.
- Kook and Myun is perfect.
- Kook and Myun.
That's a good one.
You should go with that.
- Kook and Myun.
I don't know if I can sing a ballad
in this mood.
You should go with Kook and Myun.
How about Soup and Noodles?
Stop it, Suk Jin.
Stop what?
That was the first thing I said.
You kept saying
Kook and Myun repeatedly.
Kook and Myun is perfect.
It's the global era.
- Go with Kook and Myun.
- I love this mood.
- It's a perfect duo.
- A duo.
- Right.
- It's hot in here.
- Will you tell us the title?
- They're unexpected.
They won't even tell us the title.
I've been waiting for these two.
- It's new.
- What's the title?
- "I Luv U".
(We know it
From looking at each other)
Nice.
(I can never get enough of it)
- Good job.
- Nice.
They're perfect together.
They're perfect.
(The word we always say)
(I luv you)
I love you!
Come on.
(The thug duo sound sweeter
than they appear to be.)
- I love it.
- It's so nice.
(They already love the melody.)
(The first moment)
(We met)
- It's so sweet.
- It's sweet.
(Still excites me)
Kick him out.
(You know that feeling)
I like it.
(It feels perfect)
They're good.
(Like we're meant to be)
(We began like destiny)
Nice. I like it.
It's sweet.
(Since the moment I met you)
(All I think about)
I really like this song.
(Is you)
(I can see it from your eyes)
So Min.
(Laughing)
(She winks because she's excited.)
(The word we know without saying)
(The word we always say
I luv you)
(I luv you)
I love you.
(Sweet protein ensemble)
(Heart)
- They're good.
- Good.
- I like it.
(The song reaches the climax.)
I want more!
(The word we know without saying)
(The word we always say
I luv you)
(Someone appears.)
Who's that?
- Mirani is here.
- That's Mirani.
- Who is she?
- She's Mirani.
(Rapper Mirani)
(You are my map on a hard day)
(I hope you say the same thing,
I get excited every day, baby)
(Please stay as you are)
(I like you more each day)
(Our love gets better)
(Mirani's rap part...)
(completed the two workout lovers'
mellow performance.)
(To me)
(You're the one who shines
the brightest in the world)
(The words)
(That I can say only to you)
- I love you!
(I love you!)
I love this song.
(The song for those who wish
to fall in love this summer)
("I Luv U")
("I Luv U" by Kim Jong Kook and KCM
with Mirani)
- I love you!
- Jong Kook and KCM!
- I love you, Jong Kook and KCM!
- I love you!
- The duo!
- Thank you.
- The duo.
- Thank yucca.
- Duo, I love you!
- Jong Kook and KCM!
- That's an incredible song.
- I love you!
- It's amazing.
- I liked Mirani's part too.
- Thank you.
- That was amazing.
We should call them a trio,
not a duo.
- I really like their song.
- Oh, my.
- It's a great song.
- Indeed.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Can you put on that face
while shooting the show as well?
Right. Look at us with loving eyes
as you did while singing.
I was so embarrassed
to sing in front of you guys.
- He always feels that way.
- That's true.
Mirani,
can you perform your song as well?
- The song title is "VVS".
- "VVS"?
- Yes. I'll perform the song...
- You mean, the wheel brand?
- Pardon? A wheel brand?
- That's a famous brand.
- You don't know?
- What do you mean?
- The brand used to be popular.
- It's a wheel brand name.
- VVS.
- You don't know?
Only old people would know.
- I see.
- The popular wheel brand.
- A wheel brand.
- I see.
- It's understandable.
- Is it "You fool, I love you"?
"You fool, I love you"?
- You mean, does VVS stand for that?
- VVS?
- You guys...
- That's lame.
I see you're trying hard
to get to know her,
but you don't seem to know how to.
You're all approaching her
in such an old-fashioned way.
- Why would you do that?
- Hey.
- He's the worst of all.
- You're the most old-fashioned.
- Your hairstyle is old-fashioned.
- You're the worst.
- So are your sunglasses.
- Just talk to her naturally.
He thinks he's the hippest man
in the world.
Forget it.
Mirani is here as a guest
for one episode anyway.
- You're right.
- Yes.
- Thank you for trying.
- We're the hosts. That's all.
- Mirani.
- Yes?
- Perform "VVS" for us.
- Sure. I'll do that.
- Please, sing it for us.
- Shall I do it here?
- "VVS".
- Please go up on the stage.
- On the stage?
- Show us.
- I'm excited.
- It's a really famous song.
- Yes.
Okay.
- You look fabulous.
- Clap, everyone.
It's a great song.
(They chant
in an old-fashioned way.)
(They cheer in the wrong way
from the start.)
(I'm going to show you)
(To those who said I would fail)
(Hopping)
(Dancing)
That's hip hop.
(Mirani's trademark dance move)
(Shaking)
(Her shaking dance drew attention
as well as her song!)
This is exciting.
(Hey, new water, new VV,
I ditched work to be on this stage)
(My poverty shines in my lyrics)
She's so cute.
(They're all dancing to the rhythm
in their own ways.)
She's fabulous.
(I'm here to back-stab
the disgusting world)
(Scream louder, calling my name
Everyone gets surprised to see me)
(Mirani is on TV)
(Take off the tag
Get a new one, yeah, yeah)
Look at her.
(They try every dance move
they know to look hip.)
(She's giving
such a hip performance,)
(but the audience members can't
seem to keep up.)
(They don't know how to enjoy it.)
(Some don't know how to enjoy it
while others go overboard.)
Thank you.
(The old audience members
hit it off with one another though.)
- Awesome!
- Mirani!
(Mirani gave a great performance
in front of a difficult audience.)
- That was incredible.
- I'm impressed.
She was amazing.
- I really like this dance move.
- Exactly.
(They all pretend they enjoyed
her performance properly.)
(Mirani's signature shaking dance)
- Awesome.
- Impressive.
I saw Suk Jin checking
the water temperature.
(He checked the water temperature
before washing his hands.)
Suk Jin did it.
He checked the water temperature
while watching her performance.
(He wanted to be hip but just looked
like a man in the restroom.)
That's what should be called hip.
- "VVS" is the best.
- Right.
So Min, you seemed cold.
You were shivering like this.
- So Min does it too.
- She seemed cold.
- She had chills.
- Right, she had chills.
So Min had chills.
Why can't I do it as she does?
I looked around
during her performance.
Surprisingly, Chorong and Bomi
couldn't enjoy themselves.
- They didn't know what to do.
- I guess they've reached the age.
- Bomi was taken aback.
- You all seemed excited.
- They couldn't enjoy themselves.
- Oh, no.
And I saw KCM doing
such an old dance move.
- It was an old dance move.
- He looked like an old fossil.
- You looked like an old fossil.
- I saw him.
He started with a different move.
This is how he danced at first.
(One, two, three, and four)
- I didn't realize I was doing that.
- We all danced like that back then.
We did that move to any song.
I mean, it's such an old dance move.
- The combination of those two...
- I'm excited about them.
- We talked about it a lot before.
- Yes, we did.
- The masters of high notes.
- Their fans wanted this.
Actually, it began...
when "Do You Want to Hear My Voice?"
was released.
I had a chance to sing that song
with Jong Kook.
- Was the song for the two of you?
- Really?
- I had no idea. Yes?
- Songwriter Park Keun Tae...
- made the song for them.
- That's right.
- Did they hear the song too?
- But Suk Jin snatched it.
- Because he liked it so much?
- I went to see him.
He said he had made a song.
I asked him, right?
- Yes, you did.
- "Have you given it to Jong Kook?"
He said he hadn't.
So I said, "Then it's mine."
(- I haven't given it to him yet.
- Then it's mine.)
- He's greedy.
- You have an ear for music.
- Se Chan is right.
- He has an ear for music.
The song became a hit.
Which one of you convinced her
to collaborate with you?
- I bet it was KCM. I'm sure of it.
- It was KCM.
We were working on this song,
and I thought...
- Mirani would be perfect for it.
- Right.
So I contacted her right away...
- through her agency.
- Did you have her number?
- Of course.
- And Mirani...
- happily said yes and thanked us.
- Yes, I did.
- She willingly accepted the offer.
- Mirani made the right decision.
- This will make her famous.
- I'm happy.
What are you talking about?
- Mirani is really famous.
- Suk Jin, I'm sorry,
but she's more famous than you.
(Mirani wins.)
- Gosh, you.
- You made the right decision.
Mirani, if I were your manager,
I would've made you do it.
- I know. I'm so excited.
- Of course.
You should let more people know
about your rap skills.
She should release a diss track
against Suk Jin.
Haha is right.
You've crossed the line.
- Are you offended, Mirani?
- Not at all.
- Talk about this in your diss song.
- I'm happy.
- Ji Seuk Jin is the best.
- She called him Ji Seuk Jin.
(Ji Seuk Jin is the best.)
- Ji Seuk Jin.
- Nice.
- It's getting intense.
- Hey...
- Hey, Ji Seuk Jin.
- Ji Seok Sam!
- Ji Seuk Jin.
- I like her comment.
- Ji Seuk Jin...
- Ji Seuk Sam.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey...
"I'm getting started now."
- Ji Seuk Jin.
- Guys, stop it.
Suk Jin doesn't know
how to handle this situation.
- He's moving his hand like this.
- He doesn't know what to do.
- Suk Jin must be frustrated.
- Right.
Look at that weird pose.
He's moving his fingers like this.
What's with this pose?
What does it mean?
Doesn't it look so weird?
- Hey, let's move on already.
- Sorry?
- You've done enough.
- All right.
- Please move on.
- Okay.
I'll explain about today's race.
There are many popular restaurants
on social media...
- for the food or the atmosphere.
- That's right.
Do you guys often visit such places?
- No, we can't do that.
- No.
I never visited such places.
The hottest place I've visited was
Yeongdong Seolleongtang.
- That's a 40-year-old restaurant.
- Right.
That was the hottest place
I've been to.
We know that the members always
go to the same places.
- That's true.
- I go to the same places.
- The places I go to regularly.
- That's why today...
Since we have the guests
who are Generation MZ,
today's race will be held at places
that Generation MZ likes.
- Really?
- It's Spoon War Race.
- Spoon War Race?
- I think we'll have delicious food.
- I bet some of us won't get to eat.
- Today,
you will go to three restaurants
we've picked.
And you will be divided
into two teams.
- We'll be divided.
- Two teams?
But you will go all together.
You'll play a game,
and the winning team...
will enjoy the food.
The losing team should do something
in order to eat food.
- I knew it.
- Of course.
We'll tally each team's score
achieved in the missions.
The losing team will get a penalty.
- I see.
- We'll divide you into teams first.
KCM and Mirani are on one team.
- That's nice.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- Chorong and Bomi...
- are on the other.
- Yes.
The four of them will play
a simple game...
and recruit the members 1 by 1.
- I'd be happy to join any team.
- Us against them?
- Both teams are great.
- Any team would be nice.
- I'll join Team ChoBom.
- All right.
Here's the game that they'll play.
The members played this game
last week.
Is it the drawing game?
I'll say the last two characters
of a Chinese idiom,
- and you say the 1st 2 characters.
- It's quite hard.
(Jae Suk got jintoeyangnan right.)
Jajeon.
(Wuwangjajeon?)
(Last week, the mission threw
the members into chaos.)
- Oh, you say the last characters?
- Since he says the last ones,
- It's difficult.
- it's hard to get a correct answer.
- Will they be okay?
- No, we won't.
- Are we doing it here?
- If you get it right,
- you can recruit a member.
- It's better to go first.
- We'll go first.
- You should... That's good, Bomi.
- It's better to go first.
- You can recruit a member.
(We'll go first.)
- Go for it.
- Okay, Bomi.
Chorong, you should go first.
- There's no way I'll get it right.
- I'm not confident.
Chorong, will you go first?
Let's begin.
(Chorong decided to go first
in the end.)
- Chorong is very smart.
- I can't believe you.
- Chorong is smart.
- Yes.
Bangga.
- Goseongbangga.
- Is it "goseong"? Goseongbangga.
(The answer is goseongbangga.
She failed.)
(Even the empty heads knew
the correct answer.)
- Hey, that was easy.
- It's goseongbangga.
- It's an easy question.
- It was so easy.
- It's your turn now.
(Following Chorong who failed,
it's Mirani's turn.)
Cheonseon.
Jingak. What?
- It's "gaegwa".
- He said the last two characters.
- Gaegwacheonseon.
- Oh, I get it.
- You say the 1st 2 characters.
- No wonder...
- Gosh, I knew the answer.
- But it was close, right?
- What a shame.
- Cheonseon.
- Next up is Bomi.
(It's Bomi's turn now.)
- Daneung.
- Dajae!
(The answer is dajaedaneung.)
(Bomi pulled it off!)
- That was too easy.
- Hey, I thought...
- It was difficult for her.
- No, it wasn't.
I thought you had passed
a national exam.
- Bomi did a great job.
- My gosh.
That was a difficult question.
I'm impressed.
I just realized... Hold on.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
When she failed, you said,
"Well, that was a little difficult."
Didn't you get all the questions
wrong last week?
- I want to join their team.
- Okay.
- Now...
- It's difficult.
He's trying to impress them.
Now, please choose one member.
- Did we win?
- Yes.
- We choose Haha.
- That's great.
- Okay.
- Thank you, guys.
- He kept asking them to pick him.
- Next up is KCM.
- Yes.
- You've got this.
I don't want to join that team.
Cheomhwa.
- Geumsang.
- Geumsung.
- It's "geumsang".
- Cheomhwa.
(Geumsungcheomhwa?)
- Pardon?
- It's "geumsang".
Mirani even told him the answer.
She whispered, "Geumsang."
- I haven't heard it in a while.
- He said, "Geumsung."
- It's an old TV brand.
- I'm so embarrassed.
Next up is Chorong.
Here's your question. Hoho.
Gaga.
(The answer is gagahoho.)
(Finally,
Chorong got a correct answer.)
- Nice work.
- She got it right.
- She's so smart.
- Gagahoho.
- She must've felt rushed.
- What was that?
- Chorong.
Why did you make a weird voice?
What's with your voice?
- What was that?
- She sounded like a monster.
- You did a great job.
- Why did you do that?
- What was that, Chorong?
- She did well.
- I was surprised.
- What was that?
- I choose Jae Suk.
- Okay!
(Team Chorong and Bomi recruited
Haha and Jae Suk.)
- I'll move to that side. Okay.
- All right.
Mirani, it's your turn.
Jichu.
- This one is difficult.
- Jjangjjang?
What's jjangjjangjichu?
(Jjangjjangjichu)
- She's never watched "Running Man".
- Jjangjjangjichu.
- It's "nangjungjichu".
- It was difficult for me.
- It was a difficult question.
- This one was difficult.
Why did you give Mirani
a difficult question?
- Hey.
- It was difficult.
- How would she know nangjungjichu?
- That was too difficult.
- What was the answer?
- Nangjung...
- It's "nangjung".
- It means "an awl in a pocket".
Next up is Chorong...
I mean, Bomi.
Gowu.
- Jukma!
- That's correct.
- Great job, Bomi.
- Oh, my.
Why do you give them
only easy questions?
- Good job, Bomi.
- That was great.
I'm not sure. Whom should I choose?
- Se Chan.
- Yes!
(She chose Se Chan.)
(Disappointed)
Here's your question. Gamrae.
- Gojin.
- Great.
Gojin!
- Okay.
- Please choose one member.
- Great job.
- I pick Jong Kook.
(The first member Mirani chose was
Jong Kook.)
(The singers of "I Luv U"
teamed up again.)
Nice work, Mirani. Okay!
- Great.
- Good job.
- Ji Hyo.
- Me?
Thank you, my friend.
- He's your friend, right?
- The couple is on the same team.
Poor So Min.
(He giggles while saying,
"Poor So Min.")
- Poor So Min.
- So Min...
- So Min.
- Okay. Good.
- Daebal.
- Daebal? Nobaldaebal.
(The answer is nobaldaebal.)
They keep getting easy questions.
- It was easy.
- No, it was difficult.
The remaining members are
So Min and Suk Jin.
- Don't point at me.
- Who is remaining again?
You're not popular, So Min.
Pick one of them.
I pick So Min.
(I pick So Min.)
It doesn't cheer me up at all.
(It doesn't cheer me up at all.)
Gosh.
Can't I refuse to join the team?
- I want to be a one-person team.
- Then Suk Jin will join them.
What will Suk Jin do?
- He's on the other team.
- I see.
He's doing it again.
- His hand is shaking again.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, you're doing it again.
- Suk Jin, how about we...
How about we team up together?
I'm okay. Don't be upset
over such a petty thing.
(I'm okay. Don't be upset
over such a petty thing.)
I mean, it's not the first time.
- It's not the first time.
- If you get upset...
So he's not upset at all.
It doesn't matter.
I'm happy that I'm on this team.
Then why do you look so sad?
Please name your teams.
- Our team is Team ChoBom.
- Right.
- We're Team Kook and Myun.
- Team Kook and Myun.
- Team Kook and Myun?
- That's a good name.
- Team Kook and Myun.
- Team Kook and Myun, Team ChoBom.
- Yes.
- Let's go to the first restaurant.
- Let's go!
- Okay. Let's go!
It's over.
I'm so hungry.
- I'll eat all the food I get.
- Anything would be nice.
- Goodness, So Min.
- I'm hungry too.
Why are you sitting there?
Come and sit next to Chorong.
- Right. Go and sit next to her.
- But...
Come and sit next to Chorong
right now.
What's wrong with you?
- Thank you.
- He's being shy.
- He said, "Thank you."
- You're grateful, right?
- Earlier, in the waiting room,
- Yes?
- I asked Bomi,
- Bomi?
"Bomi, were you born in 1994?"
She said, "No, I was born in 1993."
Then Suk Jin said,
"Oh, you're from Busan?"
(Seok Sam talked nonsense
as if he were almost deaf.)
"Oh, you're from Busan?"
- It sounded like that.
- Stop it.
Go see a doctor. You might have
big chunks of earwax.
- That's enough. Be respectful.
- My hearing is fine.
- Are you sure?
- Don't be disrespectful to him.
- Don't speak rudely to him.
- It might be the case.
- I was distracted. That's why.
- Make sure...
to go see an ENT doctor.
- Stop it, Jong Kook.
- Why should I go see a doctor?
- My hearing is fine.
- I'm a big fan of Mirani's.
I watched the shows she appeared on.
She's a good daughter.
- Thank you.
- And she got good enough grades...
- I heard that too.
- to go to Ewha Woman's University.
- Really?
- Oh, that's right.
The reason why
she studied hard was...
that she wanted to make
her mother's life better.
But she disappointed me earlier.
Why?
Mirani, what was your major
in college?
I majored in
apparel industry management.
- My, that's cool.
- Really?
- You got good grades, right?
- That's amazing.
I got good grades, but...
I didn't know she graduated
from an elite university.
Mirani, is your real name Mi Ran?
It's actually Kim Yoon Jin.
- Yoon Jin?
- Kim Yoon Jin?
(Yoon Jin!)
- Yoon Jin suits you.
- The name Yoon Jin makes you...
- look really smart.
- Hey.
- Yoon Jin.
- I like that name.
It sounds like the top student
in a class.
- "Can you help me solve this?"
- Her real name is Yoon Jin.
- She must've studied hard.
- Absolutely.
Of course.
Suk Jin, don't look out the window.
Mirani is talking.
Suk Jin, Mirani graduated
from Ewha Woman's University.
Focus on what she says, will you?
- Hey, Mirani.
- Come on.
Why were you checking the bus route?
- Just get used to it.
- Do you want to go somewhere?
- You can do well on your own.
- He's ridiculous.
- Got it.
- She's doing well. What's wrong?
Listen to what she says.
She's doing well on her own.
What's the matter?
- She was giving us new information.
- Gosh, I can't believe him.
New information?
- I heard that.
- Why weren't you listening?
You got good grades, right?
And you majored in
a fashion-related field, right?
- You didn't have breakfast, right?
- Cho!
Chorong has... Rong! Long legs.
- Why did he do that suddenly?
- Why did you do that?
- That was random.
- I know.
Bo! Bomi is...
- Mi! Magnificent.
- Mi.
- That was good.
Mi! Mirani is...
- Rani.
What?
- "What?"
- That's funny.
- Good job.
- He's gutsy. He wouldn't stop.
- Indeed. He never hesitates.
- He's gutsy.
- Right. He never hesitates.
- Right.
Seok! Suk Jin is...
- Jin.
- Seriously annoying.
(Suk Jin is seriously annoying.)
That rhymes.
(It's short,
but it has the key point.)
Jae! Genuinely bored with...
Seok! Suk Jin!
(Genuinely bored with Suk Jin!)
- That was good.
- I like that.
- All right.
- I'm starving.
- I wonder where we're going.
- I'm so hungry.
Oh, my. I love the menu.
- I can't digest it.
- Since you're hungry. let's begin.
- Okay! Let's begin now.
- I'm starving.
Let's go!
People wait in line for a long time
to eat here.
It's a popular restaurant.
They serve
jjajangmyeon with truffle and steak,
mianbao xia
looking like a thick macaron,
scallop jjamppong,
and many more dishes.
- That sounds delicious.
- We prepared various dishes.
(The reinterpreted Chinese cuisine
drew a lot of attention.)
(Refreshing jjamppong
with a lot of scallops is ready too.)
- We have to win to eat food.
- You have to win the game...
- to eat food under no conditions.
- Exactly.
In the first mission,
you should get good grades to get
Generation MZ's favorite food.
It's Happiness Comes from Grades.
- Okay!
- That's nice!
(It must be a quiz game!)
I like the game name.
Happiness Comes from Grades.
I think we chose...
- I'm sorry.
- We chose the wrong members.
- Do you see the scoreboard?
- Yes.
- Pick any of those questions.
- You get the points written there.
- Okay!
- Okay.
- I see.
- Many of them went to college.
- Okay.
Look at our members
on Jae Suk's left side.
We're hopeless.
They have no hope.
We might be able to manage to win
thanks to me.
(We might be able to manage to win
thanks to me.)
- I'm serious.
- To be honest,
- Mirani is the only smart one.
- That's right.
- Chang Mo is not smart either.
- Hey!
- True.
- What are you talking about?
- About him...
- I'll get them all right.
I can't trust him anymore.
- Fine.
- Honestly,
I'm a little embarrassed
by Chang Mo.
There are two sinkholes
on that team.
- But...
- There's more.
The two teams will take turns...
- to pick a question, right?
- Yes.
But anyone can say the answer.
- I see.
- That's good.
The person who says
he or she will answer...
- will pick up that jar...
- Gosh.
and relay it to the next person
after saying the first syllable.
(The member will relay the jar
after saying the first syllable.)
- Oh, I see.
- Gosh.
That's too hard.
The other members will do the same
after saying one syllable.
- U.
- Why?
- Hey. Good.
- M.
- A.
- My gosh.
(If one member gets it wrong,
the whole team fails.)
- Then I should be the first to go.
- Right.
What about me?
- Where should I sit?
- You should go second.
Listen. Your opponent team will
decide your seats.
- What?
- Gosh.
Please decide the seats
for the other team.
I discussed it with Jong Kook
and everyone else.
We want Jae Suk to move to the end.
The rest can sit anywhere they want.
- Me?
- Yes.
We just want you to move
to the end. That's all.
Okay. So Min, come and sit here.
- And Ji Hyo.
- Here?
Chang Mo on her left side
and Ji Hyo on her right side.
- Ji Hyo and Chang Mo around her.
- Gosh.
- Okay. No problem.
- What about Mirani?
She should sit there.
- Oh, I get it.
- I want them to surround her.
This is driving me nuts.
Pick the first question.
- We pick English.
- We have one more member here.
How many points?
- How many points?
- Well...
- How about 20 points?
- English, 20 points.
English, 20 points.
If we start with Ji Hyo,
I'm the last one, right?
English, 20 points.
- Let's let them go first.
- What is it?
Let's steal the answer.
Spell out the word "December".
(English, 20 points:
Spell out the word "December".)
- Mirani!
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Oops.
- It's okay. Go ahead.
Say the first letter
and give it to the next person.
- D.
- Give it to the next person.
- Me?
- Yes.
Say the next letter.
- A.
- Gosh.
- Hey.
- Let me answer.
It's "December".
- Okay.
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
- D.
- Go on.
- E.
S.
- Great.
- Ji Hyo.
- Let me answer.
- We'll have another chance.
- D.
- E.
C.
- M.
(Please get it wrong.)
- B.
- E.
R.
- We made it!
- R.
We had a chance.
- Who was the last one?
- What a shame.
- I didn't know.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay. We pulled it off.
- What a shame.
We can get points
by getting another question right.
Let's go for 30 points.
How about Sports and Entertainment,
40 points?
- Let's go.
- What should we pick?
We pick Sports and Entertainment,
40 points.
- I like the category!
- Forty points?
- Forty points.
- Sports and Entertainment?
Let's win 40 points!
Sports and Entertainment, 40 points.
- I've got this.
- Really?
- Let's go for higher points.
- Come on!
What is the name of the association
founded by FIFA...
that registers soccer players
who have played in...
- over 100 international matches?
- Let me answer.
(The Century Club)
Go on.
What is it?
- I know what it is.
- Cen.
Tu.
(The Century Club)
Ry.
(Jae Suk's anxious.)
(The Century Club)
S.
Let me answer!
- Cen.
- Tu.
Ry.
Oh.
What on earth?
What on earth is "Centuryoh?"
- Are you kidding me?
- Let me answer.
Come on.
- Let us answer.
- We'll start from over there.
Cen.
Tu.
Ry.
- C.
- Lub!
That's how you do it.
(Team Kook and Myun scores
in the category chosen by Team ChoBom.)
Okay!
It's the Century Club.
Son Heung Min recently joined
the Century Club.
- That's right.
- That he did.
Congratulations.
Let's have them answer first...
- and listen to half of it.
- We'll feed off their answer.
It was my original strategy.
- Which category?
- Let me see.
- How about Current Affairs?
- Current Affairs?
Forty points?
Jae Suk may know the answer,
but the others won't,
so let's do this.
(The others)
- The others are clueless.
- Exactly.
(They can't really argue with that.)
- Thirty or forty?
- Let's go with thirty.
- Current Affairs, 30 points.
- Nice.
- Let's show them, all right?
- Let's do this!
Let's turn this around.
- Go!
- Let's do this!
- Here we go.
- My head's spinning.
- I need to eat this.
- The National Assembly.
- The National Assembly?
What is the debate that legally
prolongs or delays a vote...
in the National Assembly?
(So Min answered it correctly
in episode 602.)
The debate?
What is the debate that legally
prolongs or delays a vote?
The debate?
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
Fi.
Li.
Seung.
(That is incorrect.)
- Seung.
- All right.
Let me answer!
Fi.
Li.
Mo.
What was it?
I think...
You can't tell each other
the answer.
Mirani, you first.
- No, me first.
- No, her.
- Start with Mirani.
- It can be either of them.
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
- Fi.
- Slide it over.
Li.
- Bu.
- S.
(Filibuster)
(Team ChoBom still has zero points.)
(If Team Kook and Myun
gets it right,)
(they'll have 90 points.)
- Suk Jin, it's your turn.
- Me?
Ter!
(That is correct.)
Filibuster!
(They score another 30 points.)
Okay!
Filibuster!
We knew this one, didn't we?
It's not the 100-minute debate.
(Jae Suk sighs with his eyes.)
How are they that smart?
(Once again, they lost their chance
to score points.)
We're at a huge disadvantage.
How did you know the answer?
Filibuster?
Don't you know what that is?
What is a filibuster?
- He gave us the definition.
- The unlimited debate.
Explain it to us once again.
Minor parties...
- What parties?
- Do debates...
You all seem angry.
I hate how Mr. Kimchi
thinks he's above us.
- He didn't know that answer.
- Of course I do.
They shouldn't be
feeding him the answer.
No one did that.
We didn't tell him anything.
Guys, let's find our energy again.
- Let's do this!
- So Min,
- let's hear your voice.
- Don't let them intimidate you.
- But...
- So Min,
let us hear your voice.
My head's spinning again.
- I didn't know she was here.
- Hey, So Min.
- So Min.
- Why aren't you talking?
Should we turn off your mic?
What do you say?
Should we take it off?
- Please turn off the mic.
- I thought it was on purpose.
Please choose a category.
- Current Affairs, 40 points.
- Yes, Current Affairs, 40 points.
- Here we go.
- Sure.
It's the toughest question
in this category.
What do you call...
the increase of base interest rate
of over 0.75 percent...
- Do you know what this is?
- by the Federal Reserve System...
that is issued
to stabilize inflation?
- You know this one, right?
- I do.
I know this one.
- You know this one?
- Really?
(The two eldest members
seem confident.)
Let me answer. I'll kick it off.
- D.
- No, that's not it.
- Okay, good.
- All right.
- D is incorrect.
- Don't be fooled by it.
- Jong Kook and I know the answer.
- That's right.
(She doesn't seem to know.)
It won't be easy, but let's take it
one syllable at a time.
It's not commonly known.
But I'm sure we'll go
back and forth on this.
- Back and forth.
- We'll go back and forth.
We'll probably go back and forth,
- so remember the correct syllables.
- Just stay put.
- Let's try this.
- No, don't.
- They're waiting for that.
- Please go first.
(They're trying to get
the other to go first.)
- We need to wait.
- That's right.
(Silence fills the room.)
It has turned into a game of wits.
I didn't even
understand the question.
How about we sit here like this
for two hours?
We'll stay silent for two hours.
- On our team...
- Jae Suk.
- Why not?
- Only I know the answer.
- We can't afford to lose.
- No way.
- We can't tell them.
- We must win this round.
We're going to hold out.
- Because...
- We're clueless.
- Can we get some beer?
- This isn't like "filibuster."
- Exactly.
- We can't afford to lose.
- This...
- The first half is easy.
- You know these English words.
- Don't tell them.
G!
- Are we going first? G.
- Here we go.
Yes, you said the first syllable.
- But you started it off.
- Go on.
You said it first!
Let us answer.
- Go ahead.
- G.
Good.
- Go ahead.
- G.
Good.
A.
It's similar to A.
- No, don't do it.
- Let's try.
- Even if we do...
- But...
Did it come to you?
(Does Se Chan know the answer now?)
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
- G.
- Good.
What?
Can she pass it over to me?
- Of course.
- Go ahead.
Let me answer. G.
- I.
- No, you can't do that.
It should bounce back to me.
- This way?
- Yes, this way.
- Really?
- G, I...
G, I...
- And?
- Ro.
- That's not it.
- You heard it, right?
Let's form a word together.
- G.
- Good.
- I.
- Yes.
(Gi...)
Only you need to answer correctly.
- We only need you to get it right.
- It's an easy English word.
- Ri.
- All right!
(The ball is back in their court.)
Jae Suk, go ahead.
- Get thinking.
- It's all right.
- KCM, it's all right.
- Don't tell them!
- Don't mouth it to them.
- Let me answer.
- No, don't.
- Hold on.
Are they allowed to be angry at us?
Don't mouth it to them!
I mean...
- He almost cussed at us.
- You're mouthing it to them.
- They don't know it.
- This way.
Bomi, you kick it off.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead.
- G.
- I.
- An.
- T.
(Giant?)
- All right.
- You heard that, right?
- You heard it, right?
- Nice!
(You heard them, right?)
(Time is up.)
Let us answer. G.
I.
An.
T.
S.
- Tep.
- Yes!
(That is correct.)
All right!
Okay.
(Thanks to their perfect timing,
they score 40 points.)
You guys are so smart!
I mean...
Jae Suk, I knew this one.
(Just like that,
a rare opportunity vanished.)
We only knew up to "giant."
- Right, but...
- That's all we knew.
Even I knew this one though.
This team...
- They need to be separated.
- Exactly.
- Right.
- They can't sit together.
Seok Sam and Ji Hyo
should swap seats.
How far behind are we?
No winners are declared
in this game.
The points you score
will be added throughout the day.
- Got it.
- Let's answer as much as we can.
No winner is declared in this game.
Choose a category.
- English, 40 points.
- English, 40 points?
- Yes.
- Good.
- It's our last chance.
The set of 26 English letters...
starting with A, B, C...
is called the English alphabet.
Please spell out "alphabet."
Alphabet?
Let's do this.
- A.
- Alphabet?
L.
P.
- A.
- L.
- P.
Was that B?
Y.
- No?
- It's all right.
I'll take that. Let me answer.
A.
L.
- P.
- H.
A.
- B.
- E.
- T.
- She told her the answer.
- E.
- T.
- She told her the answer.
- No, she didn't.
We heard it!
(Team Kook and Myun claim
that they told her the answer.)
- Yes, they did!
- No, we didn't.
- You heard them.
- Of course you did.
- We all heard it.
- But...
- It was that loud.
- Alphabet!
- But of course she knew it.
- Of course she knew it.
- Of course.
That I know.
Okay, fine. Bomi,
spell it by yourself
and I'll let it go.
I'll accept it too.
- Do it.
- Okay.
- Everyone stay silent.
Go.
And go.
- A.
- All right.
- R.
- Seriously?
Okay!
- R.
- Seriously?
(She got stuck
at the second letter.)
Okay, it's our turn, then.
I...
Can't I answer
the questions by myself?
(Can't I answer
the questions by myself?)
I want to go home.
I'd like to go home.
Let's do this.
- You know what it is, right?
- I know I do.
- Of course.
A.
- You heard them, right?
- L.
I didn't catch it.
- P.
- She didn't hear it.
I didn't catch what they said.
Nice. All right.
- We've got this.
- All right.
- Me?
- Yes, let's start with you.
Here we go. A.
- E.
- T.
Okay!
(That is correct.)
- There we go.
- Let them feed us the answer.
- Jae Suk's in a lonely fight.
- Nice!
- This will be the last round.
- Got it.
Let's win this round.
What is the lifestyle choice
of those who wish...
to retire at an early age
through financial independence?
Financially?
Through financial independence...
- You know this one. Go ahead.
- Let me answer.
- F.
- Right.
S.
(That is incorrect.)
(She at least speaks
loudly and clearly.)
How can we let others know this?
You know what it is, right?
(Team Kook and Myun
hasn't grasped the answer yet.)
How can we let others know this?
- I know this one.
- Bomi...
I know this one!
- You do?
- Then go first.
- Let me answer.
- Have Jae Suk go next.
(Chorong goes first
since she knows the answer.)
- Let me answer.
- F...
- I...
- Re...
- S.
Gosh.
- You know it, right?
- Let me answer.
- Start from there.
- I know.
- F.
- I.
Re.
(FIRE)
(Will they lose
this golden opportunity like this?)
Movement.
(FIRE movement)
It's FIRE movement.
It's FIRE movement?
- Thank you for the "FIRES."
- They got the hint.
We could get it thanks to "FIRES."
- What's this? Is it this one?
- FIRE.
- "FIRES."
- I mean...
Is it the title of a new movie?
"FIRES."
"FIRES" sounds good though.
What is the FIRE movement?
Fire. "FIRES."
- But what's good about our team...
- "FIRES."
is no one blames
the one who got it wrong.
We acknowledge it.
"FIRES." It's very close.
- Right.
- We never blame each other.
- So...
- Well done.
they won the first mission.
Bring the food.
- Yes.
- It's nice.
I do want to eat though.
- Can we not eat at all?
- We can't.
Okay. Let me explain
how you can eat.
- What is it?
- You can eat it this way.
- Pick two from Team Kook and Myun.
- Okay.
- Send your opinions about them...
to the number you're given.
"Suk Jin's nose is too big."
- Something like that.
- Okay.
You can send anything.
It could be a malicious comment.
- The AI will read it.
- All right.
But if the opponent can't stand it
and raise the "stop" sign,
you will receive 30 points
and a chance to eat.
- What if we can't stand it?
- You can stand it.
If you raise the sign
as you can't stand it,
- there won't be more comments.
- I see.
I see.
I can just endure it
even if I'm angry.
- The food will be served.
- I might get indigestion.
Pick two people among them
as you want.
First,
the one who gets angry the most...
The one who is affected the most.
It's Seok Sam
who can't put up with it the most.
- Let's go with Seok Sam.
- You should pick one more.
Jong Kook...
- I'm fine.
- He can stand it.
- I get upset, but I can stand it.
- He can put up with it.
How about Chang Mo?
I got cursed in every possible way.
I won't be affected at all. Try it.
- I'll choose you.
- Okay.
We'll choose Chang Mo and Seok Sam.
- Chang Mo and Seok Sam.
- These two.
But they wouldn't know who wrote it.
- Right. It's anonymous.
- We won't be scolded anyway.
Okay.
Let me tease the older guys
after a long time.
I think you'll be good.
Hey, we can put up with it.
He's amazing.
Here it is.
(Surprised)
(Impressed)
(Shrimp mianbao xia
that is as thick as a macaroon)
- It looks amazing.
- It looks good.
It's not that side.
- We'll just set the table.
- You just set the table?
Thank you.
He yelled again.
(Seok Sam was surprised
that they might steal his food.)
Gosh, this is so thick.
It looks good. I want to eat it.
The mianbao xia is so thick.
It smells so good.
It looks like a macaroon.
Thank you.
This is crazy.
- I can smell truffle.
- Gosh.
- This is crazy.
- This is insane.
This is crazy.
Can we eat?
(Team Kook and Myun is enjoying
the perk of becoming the winner...)
(after crushing the other team
at the quiz.)
- I've never had something so good.
- Me too.
(Not only Millennials
and Generation Z,)
(but also Generation X
is impressed.)
The jjamppong is amazing.
(Scallop jjamppong
is the cherry on top.)
This is insane.
- It's so good.
- It looks so good.
The meat itself is so tender.
- It's not tough.
- I've never had...
something this good in my life.
It's so good.
(On the other hand,
the losing team...)
I'm going crazy.
It seriously looks so good.
(They start writing their opinions
anonymously, enduring hunger.)
(Make Suk Jin and Chang Mo angry
and raise the "stop" sign.)
This is good.
I should change the setting again.
(Everyone is thinking seriously.)
- Who is it?
- Oh, no.
We won't be shocked easily.
The sunflower tattoo
on Chang Mo's belly...
smells like dead skin
under a toenail.
(smells like dead skin
under a toenail.)
(They start attacking him
with the smell of his tattoo.)
I think he's mad.
My goodness.
Who smelled it?
(It's not his business yet.)
I think I know who wrote it.
(Glancing)
- It's so...
- Ants are coming out...
from Chang Mo's philtrum.
(What?)
(Someone claimed that Chang Mo's
philtrum is a house of ants.)
Who is it?
(Someone claimed that Chang Mo's
philtrum is a house of ants.)
Jjajang would get
on Suk Jin's nose.
(Jjajang would get
on Suk Jin's nose.)
Ji Seok Sam is such a boomer.
It's more shocking
as the AI is reading it.
(Writing a new comment on Suk Jin)
Suk Jin,
if you take your glasses off,
does your nose come off too?
(If you take your glasses off,
does your nose come off too?)
(Writing malicious comments
while hiding behind anonymity)
I can feel it a little.
Feel what?
Suk Jin, close your mouth,
open your wallet,
and go out right now.
(Close your mouth, open your wallet,
and go out right now.)
(Se Chan asked him to leave early.)
Suk Jin.
Put lipstick on Suk Jin's lips.
Suk Jin, what are you doing?
(He starts eating again
as people around him stopped him.)
He doesn't look happy now.
(The infamous netizen Mr. Yoo
who has been quiet starts typing.)
Suk Jin, these are jokes.
Suk Jin, transplant some hair.
(Suk Jin, transplant some hair.)
Hold on.
No.
Suk Jin, I said go out.
Oh, gosh.
(The persistent requests to leave
have cumulative effects on him.)
It's hilarious.
(How about this?)
I think it will hurt him.
Suk Jin, you smell like an old man.
(Suk Jin,
you smell like an old man.)
(Grandpa Seok Sam is the target
of the concentrated attack.)
- Are you okay, Suk Jin?
- Yes, I'm fine.
This is not a big deal.
(Sending another one)
Are you not leaving, Suk Jin?
(Are you not leaving, Suk Jin?)
The AI says it in the right tone.
When there's a question mark...
I think the AI makes it
ten times more shocking.
Because it's saying it
without any emotions.
(Smiling)
Suk Jin's earwax
is piled like a bowl of rice.
What?
- My earwax is like a bowl of rice?
- Suk Jin is an old fox...
who doesn't act his age.
(Suk Jin is an old fox
who doesn't act his age.)
(An old fox who doesn't act his age)
(Laughing)
(Grabbing)
- You can't.
- No.
- What are you doing?
- Leave.
No.
I should eat it quickly.
(He barely endured it.)
"Your earwax
is like a bowl of rice."
It makes me angrier as it rhymes.
Suk Jin doesn't love Su Jung.
- "Su Jung?"
- It's his wife.
(Happy)
You got five minutes left.
Oh, no.
Celebrities get cursed a lot.
- Sure.
- So this is nothing.
This is fine.
It's my feeling. This is not...
Suk Jin has been searching
for places in Cheongdam...
where pretty girls come.
(Suk Jin has been searching for
places where pretty girls come.)
No, I have not.
(Suk Jin raised the "stop" sign.)
We'll give you time to eat.
Give them to me.
- Chopsticks.
- You don't have much time.
- You got two minutes and a half.
- Grab your chopsticks.
- I raised it so that you can eat.
- Try the mianbao xia.
- Thank you for the food.
(They finally got to taste
what they could only see.)
This is so good.
- Thank you.
- This is really good.
Gosh.
(Savoring)
How is it? Is it good?
(It's so good.)
- Is it good?
- Yes.
(Having a bite of truffle
jjajangmyeon that he smelled)
The smell of truffle.
It smells so nice.
(The first bite
makes everyone happy.)
- Is it good?
- It's so good.
It's delicious.
- We don't have time.
- But the time is up.
What?
But the time is up.
(The mealtime is over.)
Let's go to the next restaurant.
- What are you doing?
- I only had one bite.
- Let's go.
- Just one bite.
- Stop eating.
- It's over.
Stop eating.
- Hurry up and proceed to film.
- Stop eating.
- For real?
- Put them down.
Stop and put them down.
Let us eat.
I will eat the next menu
no matter what.
I will eat it.
- I'm hungry.
- Me too.
- We're going to the next place.
- Yes.
What's the menu?
It's your favorite.
- What is it?
- It's a snack bar.
- Yes.
- Come on.
- A snack bar?
- It's a snack bar.
But...
- I like it.
- It's my area.
You're in my area.
It's your area.
- I walk around here.
- It's Apgujeong.
What do you mean it's your area?
Cha Tae Hyun often comes here too.
Come on.
Many people walk around here.
- I do too.
- I told you last week.
You shouldn't talk
with people like these guys.
- Okay? End of conversation.
- End of conversation?
I know so many people
who often come here.
- Let me give you a tip again.
- Many people come here.
This is a great tip for social life.
Don't have a long conversation...
with people like him.
It makes you tired.
- Talk for a short while.
- Just for a moment.
- Where is Mirani?
- Mirani.
- It got me surprised.
- Se Chan said this to me.
- That he likes Mirani.
- What?
(Se Chan said he liked Mirani.)
So I said I would say it
instead of him.
- I was going to say it later.
- Se Chan did?
Don't do it.
- He's...
- Do you have a boyfriend?
You're making it weird.
Don't try to create something
between them.
You don't even know how to do it.
Se Chan likes Mirani.
(Se Chan likes Mirani.)
(Talking about his feelings
instead of him)
- My goodness.
- He's weird.
I'll give you a mission in the car.
Okay.
- We must win.
- This...
is also popular on social media.
But we must win.
We can win this.
He said it's famous on social media.
- Seriously. Bomi, Chorong.
- Yes.
Let's cheer up.
Cheer up.
"FIRES."
- Let me explain the game.
- Okay.
Hold your laughter to try popular
food among Millenials and Gen Z.
It's a Try Not To Laugh challenge.
"Try Not To Laugh challenge."
It's simple. One from each team
would make...
a random weird noise.
Those who laugh will lose points.
Okay.
Like a sound effect?
- Just make any random noise.
- Okay.
You can make any noise.
Something like this.
Those who do not laugh...
From now on...
- But it makes me laugh.
- Oh, no.
Smiling is fine, right?
- You can't smile either.
- When he goes like this...
So...
What if someone smiles
when they're making a noise?
- That's not allowed.
- Right?
You can't laugh at yourself either?
Please allow us to smile.
No. You will lose then.
- This is not allowed?
- Do you always smile?
You can't smile either.
You should have a straight face.
How about this?
This isn't allowed either?
- Once you laugh, you keep doing it.
- How about this?
- What?
- What's that?
This isn't a smile.
Show it to me.
- You can do it.
- We'll follow our standards.
- Who wants to go first?
- I'll keep a straight face.
- Each team takes turns.
- Se Chan is strong.
- We're on the same team.
- Se Chan is good.
Among us, Chang Mo can do it.
- Chang Mo.
- If you laugh,
- your own team will lose points.
- Okay.
- Chang Mo, do it.
- Chang Mo.
- Start from Chang Mo.
- We must win.
We must win it.
- Don't worry.
- We must win.
You can't laugh from now.
(The Try Not To Laugh challenge
begins first.)
Ready, go.
(The game begins.)
Harmonica.
(Laughing)
- I'm sorry. I'm so...
- Bomi lost points.
Bomi. This is...
- Bomi.
- You could've held it.
Okay. I got it now.
- I'm sorry.
- Honestly...
You got it only now?
What's the point
if you got it only now?
Next. Who is going to do it?
This is driving me crazy.
- So Min, do you want to try?
- The captain should go.
So Min, I'll do it slowly.
- So Min, try it.
- So Min.
- You shouldn't laugh.
- Try it.
- Should our team not laugh too?
- Of course not.
What should I do?
Ready.
Go.
(Weird noises)
Gosh. What's that?
Jae Suk, you lost points.
(Jae Suk lost points.)
Why did you laugh?
He laughed.
It's too weird.
It's a sound people make
when they soothe babies.
- It's so weird.
- They make that noise...
- to babies.
- It's too weird.
- What's this?
- It was too weird.
- Jae Suk.
- It wasn't professional at all.
Next. Suk Jin.
- Me?
- Yes.
- I shouldn't laugh.
- I laugh easily.
Me too.
- You're on our team, right?
- Yes.
Try your best.
(Shouting)
(Singing)
- Don't laugh.
- How can you not laugh?
- Pass.
Next. Who is going to do it
from this team?
I'm going crazy. I shouldn't laugh.
- Should I attack them?
- Bomi.
- Se Chan, you go.
- I'll do it.
- Se Chan, let's go.
- Bomi, don't laugh.
Okay.
- I don't have any idea.
- I'll do it.
(Laughing)
Hold on.
It's always our team that laughs.
(Hold on.
It's always our team that laughs.)
- Hey.
- Don't say that.
- It's because...
- It's not creative at all.
- It's our team that always laughs.
I didn't even look.
You're so weak.
- Don't laugh.
- Why is it only us who laugh?
- We will win for sure.
- Mirani, it's your turn.
- Mirani.
There's nothing to do.
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
Try rapping with a weird voice.
No. Just do what you were thinking.
- Stay still.
- What's wrong with him?
Are you an expert or something?
- I mean...
- Stay still.
In case it will confuse her.
(Squeaking)
(Laughing)
Haha and KCM lost points.
(Haha and KCM lost points.)
Haha, what are you doing?
- Next. Jae Suk.
- Why did you laugh?
You should listen beside her.
- Jae Suk will laugh at himself.
- Should I try?
He will laugh at himself.
- I laugh easily.
- That's why.
I'll try.
I haven't laughed once.
(Singing)
(Laughing)
What was it?
(Laughing alone)
Many people laughed.
(Laughing)
- Many people laughed.
- It's only our team that laughed.
He made the noise
and he laughed at it.
- It was bad.
- My goodness.
(A bad suicide goal)
Everyone lost points except So Min.
Hey, why is it only us who laugh?
I don't know. Why did you laugh?
- What's the matter with them?
- You should understand us.
- It's funny as they're bad.
- Why did you laugh?
- It's weird.
- I almost died because of her.
It's Jong Kook's turn.
- He will be funny.
- Jong Kook.
- It's not funny.
- He's funny too.
I have nothing to do.
Try making a thick voice.
Go.
What if the sunlight
(Laughing)
- Haha.
- He's...
- Come on.
- Haha.
- Why did you laugh?
He sounded so dumb.
(He sounded so dumb.)
- Why did you laugh?
- He...
(He can't breathe.)
How can he sing that bad?
Oh, my gosh.
I mean...
The way he sang it was so funny.
- I'm sorry.
- Jong Kook made him laugh.
- Chorong.
- It's because I liked it.
Chorong, let's go.
- Chorong, get ready.
- Everybody
Ready.
- Please let's not laugh, our team.
- Set.
Go.
(Go.)
(Laughing)
- Haha.
- What's this?
- You keep laughing.
- I'm sorry.
What's this?
- I mean...
- This is...
Hey, what is it?
Chorong. She did her best.
- She did her best.
- What's the matter?
I could feel next to her
that she was doing her best.
To the point that I wondered
if I should laugh for her or not.
- Chorong.
- Overall,
- I'm going crazy.
- it's funny because they're bad.
- But...
- Everyone...
- we have low standards.
- has low standards.
- We have low standards.
- We sure do.
- The worst one is So Min.
- It's so...
(What's wrong with this?)
Why?
It's funny because it's bad.
- It's Ji Hyo's turn.
- Ji Hyo.
- Me?
- Yes.
- "Me?"
- I'm crying.
You shouldn't laugh.
(He stops laughing.)
I will not laugh for real.
I can control myself.
(Weird noises)
(A random dog noise)
I didn't think of it.
- It was a unique sound.
- Ji Hyo.
- It was so strong.
- It was unexpected.
- It's how my dog barks.
- I didn't think of it.
Ji Hyo, I couldn't think of it.
- It was funny.
- Haha is over.
- What should I do?
- The killer move.
It's Haha's turn.
I can't do it.
- Shout "Ya, man."
- I'm crying.
- Don't laugh.
- You end it later, Bomi.
- Look to the front.
- No. I'll see them.
- No.
- Look to the front.
- Don't do that.
- Look outside the window.
(Haha starts attacking them.)
(Weird noises)
It's so bad.
(It's shockingly bad.)
It's so bad that it drives me crazy.
- What is it?
- He failed for the first time.
- What's wrong with him?
- What's the matter with you?
Haha.
He laughed at himself.
- What's so...
- He's weird.
Me doing this is...
- What are you doing?
- You know what it is, right?
Oh, my gosh.
I...
(It was so humiliating
that he laughed automatically.)
I feel like dying.
- Did you lose then?
- Bomi didn't do it.
- Bomi didn't do it?
- Bomi.
- Bomi should do it.
- Should I do it?
- Did we win?
- You should do it.
- You lost.
It's okay
if you make more people laugh.
We shouldn't laugh.
Bomi, let's go.
(Go.)
Bomi has grit.
(Weird noises)
But it's a little...
It makes me not like her anymore.
(It makes me not like her anymore.)
Are you looking down on Running Man?
It was so...
- What was that?
- Bomi.
- But it...
- Even her facial expression.
- It makes me not like her anymore.
- I saw your look.
Bomi.
I'm sorry, but...
- Bomi, it makes me not like you.
- Bomi. What should we do?
- I feel dizzy.
- You ruined the game.
And you ruined this too.
What's this?
- Bomi.
- Seriously.
"It makes me not like you anymore."
(Sad)
- Why is this so funny?
- This is hard.
Them trying to be funny is funny.
Yes. It's...
- It's not the noise.
- I think...
Looking at them trying so hard
is funny.
I think it's funny
because it's childish.
- Did we lose?
- Let me count.
- Yes, we did.
- Jae Suk and Haha kept laughing.
- Did we win again?
How can I not laugh when it's funny?
I didn't want to win, but we won.
Team Kook and Myun
laughed six times.
- Really?
- It's over.
Team ChoBom...
laughed 16 times.
We have more members.
We have...
- more members and laughter.
- That's right.
We are nice.
We couldn't help but laugh.
Team Kook and Myun won points.
- What are we going to do?
- This is nice.
We lost today.
Does this place sell street food?
I didn't know this place was here.
(Sweet and spicy tteokbokki...)
(and a sandwich that contains
freshly-fried tonkatsu)
Tonkatsu sandwich looks tasty.
I have often ordered deliveries
from this place.
(Gimbap with yukhoe and
rice bowl with salted pollack roe)
It sounds tasty.
Tteokbokki with fried fish cake.
This place is famous
for tonkatsu sandwich.
I want to play this game again.
(Clucking)
(Neighing)
(Apgujeong safari opens.)
(Singing)
That came out of nowhere.
This building...
- belongs to Lim Ha Ryong.
- That's right.
(Screaming)
- Stop it.
- Does it belong to Lim Ha Ryong?
(He is imitating Maenggu.)
- Come on.
- He doesn't have anything new.
You are obsessed with this game.
- You know,
- Seriously.
he laughed all ten times.
- Let's play it again.
- He laughed all ten times.
I am dying.
Which dishes would everyone enjoy?
- Yookgaejang ramyeon.
- Ramyeon would be nice.
Can't we eat?
(Sad)
- There are so many tasty dishes.
- Are the rules the same?
I am writing comments.
Are the members KCM and Suk Jin?
No, I am writing comments
about Jong Kook.
Let's have everyone receive
the hate comments.
Shall we make everyone open
for comments?
- Let's do that.
- Sure.
You can write comments about anyone.
Let's eat by ourselves.
- It will be easy.
- Seriously.
- The comments don't mean anything.
We didn't fill our stomachs.
- Jong Kook punched me once...
- We didn't get the food yet.
and I was so surprised
because it didn't hurt at all.
(I was so surprised
because it didn't hurt at all.)
We didn't get the food yet.
Bring it on.
It didn't hurt at all.
- He throws soft punches.
- I bet Jae Suk wrote it.
Jong Kook is hopeless at soccer.
(Jong Kook is hopeless at soccer.)
Kim Jong Gukbap.
(Kim Jong Gukbap)
- It's short and strong.
- There are such comments.
There are such comments.
Suk Jin is a dirty old geezer.
(Suk Jin is a dirty old geezer.)
(Attacks on his age and smell
are always effective.)
That was funny.
Mirani.
(There is a comment for Mirani.)
It's me, Se Chan.
Do I...
like you?
(It's me, Se Chan. Do I like you?)
(Do I like you?)
(He confessed his love
like Tan in "The Heirs.")
You wrote it, right?
- You wrote it.
- My goodness.
What was that?
(The culprit is Maenggu,
the man who is obsessed with love.)
"Do I like you?"
(The fake confession of love
seems to be effective.)
The voice lacks soul.
Hold on. The food will enter.
Let's eat.
Thank you.
Tonkatsu sandwich looks tasty.
- It's famous.
- Tonkatsu sandwich is famous.
Is it over?
(Giggling)
(Which comment did they read?)
What is it? Is it for Mirani?
Hurry up.
Mirani.
It's me, Se Chan. 0, 1, 0, 9...
It's my actual number.
Don't air it.
- Hey.
- It's my actual number.
- Is that allowed?
- Mirani.
- That was nice.
- It's me, Se Chan.
- Is that allowed?
- Mirani.
- That was nice.
- It's me, Se Chan.
- It was better than mine.
- Let's go out.
I love you like crazy.
(I love you like crazy.)
(Mirani raises a stop sign.)
For goodness' sake.
(A manly confession of love
by the man with big gums...)
(leaves Mirani feeling dizzy.)
It was manly.
- It was nice.
- It was manly.
The AI voice made it funnier.
- It was so funny.
The voice was so funny.
It was insane.
How was it so funny?
She raised a stop sign,
- so Team ChoBom can eat as well.
- Okay.
That was so funny.
- That was so funny.
- "It's me, Se Chan."
That was hilarious.
What is that? Tonkatsu?
It's tonkatsu in bread.
It's really tasty.
(Sweet, crispy, and moist)
It's tasty.
The meat has been cooked perfectly.
He knows how to eat.
He dipped it in sauce.
(Impressed)
(My goodness!)
(Giving LA reactions)
I am chewing already.
What's this?
- It's tasty.
- What an idea.
It's tasty, right?
- Yookhoe gimbap.
- What's up with gimbap?
- What's inside? Yookhoe?
Jae Suk.
- Yookhoe gimbap is tasty, So Min.
- What's this?
- It's seriously tasty.
- It's so tasty.
- It's tasty.
- Yookhoe gimbap.
- Despite being street food,
it's nutritious.
The meat is so thick.
(Glancing over)
(Laughing)
Who are you looking for?
If the food is tasty,
you have to make eye contact
with the owner.
(Making eye contact)
The ingredients are fresh.
- Seriously.
- The food is tasty.
(Nodding)
(My goodness.)
Stop making us uncomfortable.
- And the meat is tender.
- What?
For real.
My goodness.
They added so much yukhoe.
They did that.
Mirani, isn't this ridiculous?
Don't they care about
other restaurants?
Hold on.
Is that a compliment or a threat?
- Which one is it?
- I mean...
(He compliments the food
as he huffs and puffs.)
It makes no sense.
Let's move to the last place
for dessert.
- Let's go.
- All right.
It's this place.
(They move to a different place
for dessert.)
Look at the chandelier.
This place is nice.
It's nice.
- This place is nice.
- Haha, sit down.
Sit down.
(Inching closer)
Would it be okay
if Se Chan sits next to you?
- Sure.
- Se Chan, I asked her.
You can sit next to her.
For goodness' sake.
You know,
I can't look at her because of you.
I have no feelings for her,
but I can't look at her...
because of what you did.
I can't look at her.
I can't do it.
I can't look at Mirani
because of Haha.
- It's awkward.
- You know,
- Mirani stopped talking too.
- Seriously.
Haha made it seem like
I had confessed to her.
Haha messed up the atmosphere.
- What's wrong with him?
- For real.
- Look at his face.
- "Do I like you?"
He ruins everything.
He should just leave people be.
This is the last place.
- With colorful desserts...
- They will be delicious.
and romantic atmosphere,
it captivated Generation MZ.
It's a bingsu place.
(There are different types of bingsu
Generation MZ likes.)
It's a bingsu place.
(We love bingsu.)
- Bingsu, patbingsu
- Everyone is happy.
We love you
Bingsu is the best.
- We should eat bingsu.
- We should eat it.
- I want to eat this the most.
- Let's eat it.
For this mission,
all team members except for the one
who will guess the answer...
will draw the given sentence
separately for 30 seconds.
- A sentence?
- Yes.
- A sentence.
- After 30 seconds,
all drawings will be revealed.
Then the one remaining member
has to guess the sentence.
We can do it.
Okay.
Sit down.
Let's win this time.
- That's right.
- We have to win.
Let's eat bingsu.
Don't worry. Draw in a relaxed way.
This team has many members
you have to watch out for.
- I am bad at drawing.
- Come on.
- We don't do that.
This is...
a matter of drawing
what comes to your mind.
Please help them stay on track.
Even if we want to help,
they won't listen.
Here comes the first question.
Don't worry and draw.
We have many members
who can draw well.
(Se Chan picks his teeth
with the N Seoul Tower.)
Please lower the level.
We have many members
who can draw well.
This is hard.
- It's easy.
- I would answer it in a heartbeat.
- It's so easy.
My goodness.
Oh, no.
- Bomi shouldn't show hers.
- Two,
- one. Hold it up.
- This is very...
Bomi shouldn't show hers.
- This is hard.
- My goodness.
- Hold it up.
- It's hard.
I am not sure about this.
Hey.
(A masterpiece)
(Two poor-quality drawings)
Hey.
That's me.
- What?
- You accentuated the teeth.
- Don't give him any hints.
- Stop sharing information.
I guess it isn't me.
- Hey.
- There are no glasses.
This person is picking his teeth
with a tower.
(Impressed)
It must be Se Chan.
(It turns into 20 questions.)
- My goodness.
- Let's see.
Se Chan is... Let's see.
- Aren't you going to count down?
- Don't give him so much time.
Say the answer now.
- Two, one.
- All right.
What's the answer?
On top of the mountain...
(Incorrect)
You were getting there.
All right.
Why did you think it was you
when I didn't draw the glasses?
- It's me.
- It's Se Chan.
It looks like "Attack on Titan."
- It isn't Se Chan.
- Come on.
It's me.
- I will get it right.
- The second question.
(The second question)
- Cue.
- Trust me.
Cue.
It's a simple game.
There will be a member's name.
(Jae Suk rides a scooter
while wearing pants on his head.)
- It's easy.
It's really easy.
- It's really easy.
- Ten seconds.
Jae Suk will get it right.
Everyone is drawing well.
Five, four,
- three, two, one.
- Bomi can draw well.
- Time's up.
Time's up.
Bomi can draw well.
(Se Chan and So Min's drawings
are ordinary.)
(She made
another grotesque artwork.)
It's me.
While wearing pants on his head,
(That's it!)
Jae Suk rides a scooter.
(Correct)
Correct.
- I did well, right?
- Good job.
- It was too easy.
Okay. Good.
How did you guys draw me?
Isn't that an alien squid?
- Bomi, you are bad at drawing.
- An alien squid.
- Listen, the two of you.
- Prince Squid.
You guys don't need to draw.
The two of you
should just draw the person.
- They will draw the situation.
- That's what we can't do.
- All right.
- That's the key point.
Let's go.
Here comes the question.
- Get the key points.
- I will focus on them.
Cue.
(Jae Suk plays the piano
with his teeth.)
What a sentence.
- It's easy.
- It's so easy.
It's easy.
It's easy. It's totally easy.
What should I do?
- For goodness' sake.
- I need to know who it is.
- You have 15 seconds left.
- Hold on.
Jae Suk.
Five, four,
- three, two,
- Why are you laughing?
- one.
- Is that a dinosaur?
Hold it up.
- Hold it up.
- That's a dinosaur, right?
- It was hard.
- That's me.
- No.
Don't say, "No."
- Don't say, "No."
- It wasn't easy.
- Se Chan.
- It was easy.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- It wasn't easy.
- Hey.
Se Chan, is that a skull?
- That's me.
- That's a skull, right?
Isn't that me?
There is no hair.
(This cheater keeps drawing
while others' works are revealed.)
- This is bad.
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
- There is no hair.
- They didn't have time.
- It's Jae Suk.
- Hold on. He wrote English.
Come on.
(He wrote English.)
- English.
- He wrote "Chi" for "Teeth."
- Hold on.
- I didn't need that hint.
But you can't read "Chi."
(She looks down on him.)
- That's right.
- It's Bomi who can't read it.
- That's not true.
- All right.
If the person
with a protruding mouth...
has glasses, it's Jae Suk.
Otherwise, it's me.
- Okay.
- The hair doesn't matter.
- The teeth matter the most.
- That's right.
- If there are no teeth, it's Haha.
- Okay.
- Understood?
- Here comes the question.
If the person is bald, it's me.
(Mirani becomes angry
because of Se Chan's confession.)
This one...
- This one is hard.
- Pay attention to who I am...
Don't write any words.
(Pay attention to who I am...)
- Who I am...
- Don't write any words.
It's easy.
He is looking at the person
too much.
(He gives a hint openly.)
That's too much, Seriously.
Jae Suk.
Keep your eyes on the paper.
I need to look at her
in order to draw her.
I am sorry,
but this is what you have.
- You stared at her for so long.
- Wait.
Ten seconds.
- That's ridiculous.
- You always draw a stick figure.
Seriously.
Three, two, one.
- Hold it up.
- Let's see it.
(They hold up the drawings.)
She drew well.
Chorong's drawing skills improved.
Chorong drew so well.
Okay. So there are two people.
She drew well.
Is this Speak with Your Actions?
- Okay.
- Speak with Facial Expressions?
Okay.
- What are you doing?
- Jae Suk, what did you tell him?
I didn't tell him anything.
Se Chan confesses to Mirani.
(Incorrect)
You were close.
(He missed the angry Mirani part.)
- What's the answer?
- You missed her reaction.
Mirani becomes angry
because of Se Chan's confession.
I drew everything.
What's that?
- Mirani is angry.
- How is that Mirani?
These fringes
should tell you as much.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Aren't those twigs?
- What are you talking about?
- The next question.
- Cue.
- Hold on.
(Team Kook and Myun goes next.)
It must be hard.
- Hold it up.
- Here.
- Time's up.
- What's the answer?
- It's hard.
- KCM...
plays the harmonica with a snake.
Right?
Hold it up.
This is a person.
(He plastered a squid
to So Min's face.)
- You are too much.
- It's "The Lion King" character.
So Min uses a squid as a sheet mask.
Okay.
(Thus, Team Kook and Myun
got 2 questions right.)
Since it's a tie,
why don't you arm wrestle?
(They will arm wrestle
to determine the victor!)
- The representatives.
- Bomi, you are good at it.
- Yes.
- Bomi.
- Bomi, are you good at it?
- Yes.
How about Bomi and Mirani?
- Okay.
- Okay. Bomi versus Mirani.
- Bomi looks strong.
- Bomi is strong.
Okay.
Bomi, show us.
- Okay.
- Show us.
- I can do well.
This match will decide
the winning team...
that will eat bingsu.
- Bomi, put your weight into it.
- We will eat bingsu.
- Let's go.
- It's a single match.
- Use your elbow.
- Let's go.
Start from the middle. Get ready.
- Get ready.
- Let's go.
Get ready. Set, go.
- What are you doing?
- It's the Top Roll.
(The end)
- What are you doing?
- It's the Top Roll.
(They lost again.)
It was the Top Roll.
- Yes!
(Bomi lost in her specialty,
a match of strength.)
Jae Suk, how did this happen?
(I don't know.)
Bomi.
You lost in every match today.
Don't cry.
You should be good at something.
- It was my specialty.
- We lost in every match.
- Hold on.
- Jae Suk.
- This team had the perfect victory.
- Okay.
(Team Kook and Myun had
the perfect victory.)
We were going to lose this time.
We were preparing the hate comments.
We were going to write
the hate comments.
We have to eat again.
(Team Kook and Myun has no choice
but to eat again.)
(Sweet and sour fruit bingsu enters.)
- It's bingsu.
- Mango bingsu.
- Is it supposed to flow?
- Yes.
It's very tasty.
My goodness.
- We don't have anything to say.
- Bomi.
- Seriously.
We had the complete victory.
We were ready to write
hate comments.
- That team...
- Shut up, Suk Jin.
I am 50,000 percent sure
Jae Suk wrote that.
How tasty.
I chose the wrong team.
(She has no words.)
Hey, listen.
If you say funny things
about each other,
I will hold up the stop sign.
You are out of things to say,
so criticize each other.
Mirani. It's me, Se Chan.
Can't I like you?
You look pretty when you eat.
(An avid fan's comment
appeared once again.)
- That's so funny.
- They are attacking Mirani.
- It's funny.
- Mirani.
It's me, Se Chan.
I am seriously going crazy
because of you.
I want to drive you home
after the shoot.
(The man who is going crazy
because of Mirani, Se Chan)
She is nearly there.
Try a bit harder.
(She is close
to raising the stop sign.)
My goodness.
(The woman who makes
Se Chan go crazy, Mirani)
- It's so funny.
- I am a fan of that story.
Mirani.
Mirani. It's me, Suk Jin.
I will give you a ride.
(The dad offers a ride.)
(The dad is worried about
how his daughter will get home.)
Come on.
(The dad is worried about
how his daughter will get home.)
- Stop.
- Okay.
- She held it up.
The Mirani series is so funny.
"Mirani. It's me, Se Chan."
"I am seriously going crazy
because of you." That was so funny.
That was so funny.
- Encore.
- It really sounded like Se Chan.
(With the manly confession,
they clear the last menu.)
It was funny
because it sounded so real.
Now, I will give you
the ending rules.
- Okay.
- The final score...
is 210 points to 120 points.
- My goodness.
- But...
the score won't decide the result.
Okay.
Remember spinning the wheel...
- for the N Number Race?
- Yes.
I remember that.
The points will give you
a certain number of slots.
It's 1 slot per 50 points,
so this team can write
the other team's name on four slots.
- Please do that now.
- Wouldn't that be better?
I had the same thought.
Let's put one here.
Never mind.
Let's keep them as they are.
All right. This team gets two slots.
All right. The wheel is ready.
You will now spin the wheel.
The team that gets picked will lose.
I see. I remember doing this.
With 4 and 2 slots filled each,
you will spin the wheel.
If you get an empty slot,
add the other team's name.
(If you get an empty slot,
add the other team's name.)
When a team gets picked,
that team will lose right away.
That team will receive the penalty.
- Spin it.
- Bomi, spin it first.
- Bomi.
- Go, Bomi.
- Spin it.
- Let's go.
- You can do it.
- What's the penalty?
It would be great if we get
Team Kook and Myun right away.
- Please.
- Then we will win.
- Seriously.
- I will win this one.
- Okay.
- I haven't won once today.
- Let's win.
- I will win this one.
(The team that gets picked
will receive the penalty!)
- Okay.
- If you get picked, we win.
That's right.
- If it's a blank, we add a slot.
- I think you will get picked.
- Team Kook and Myun.
- Team ChoBom.
- Please.
(The team that gets picked
will receive the penalty!)
- I think you will get picked.
- Team ChoBom.
(Team ChoBom gets the penalty.)
It only took one go.
Team ChoBom.
(Team Kook and Myun won
until the very end.)
(Dumbfounded)
(The big sinner)
(Bomi causes trouble in the end.)
Jae Suk. You have to do it again.
Hey.
- That's shocking.
- Get out.
Get out of here.
- Get out!
- Get out.
Leave now.
That was very close.
- Hey.
- It's perfect.
Take her with you.
Get out now!
I'm shocked.
- How is that possible?
- How could that happen?
It didn't work out all day.
- Nothing worked out.
- How is that possible?
Nothing worked.
She's worse than me.
Here's the penalty.
Among 6 balloons,
3 of them have flour.
Take one with you. It's simple.
If she doesn't get it,
that's...
(Then the winner is ChoBom.)
This is crazy.
- Are you going to sit there?
- Just sit down.
- I'll sit here.
- Then I'll sit here.
Should I sit here?
(Six stragglers are sitting
side by side.)
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Let me just see.
We'll start with these three first.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Three people here.
- I can already see it.
- Do I go?
- Does it have flour?
Wait. Do I go?
- Do I just go?
Yes. 1, 2...
(Does one of these balloons
have flour inside?)
Two, three.
(Chorong got floured.)
Hey.
(Jae Suk and So Min were lucky.)
It's annoying.
Now there are two left.
Two of them.
Two of them?
You're never this lucky.
That was awesome.
Gosh.
Do you want to switch?
- No. Let's do this.
- Will you switch with me?
- Let's do this.
- Let's switch.
What are you doing?
It'll get on him too.
- Really? Do you want to switch?
- Let's do it.
I did it already.
- You already did?
- I already did it, Bomi.
- All right. One.
- Let's switch.
- No switching?
- Two.
Let's switch.
One, two, three.
(Se Chan and Bomi got floured.)
Who is it?
Am I safe?
Awesome.
She's unlucky to the end.
Still,
I'm not even joking.
Bomi and Chorong.
- They're the worst.
- They're unlucky.
Consider you avoided
something worse with this.
- You got flour too.
- ChoBom.
Your album will be a hit.
Are you sure?
- Right. Your album will be a hit.
- It will be a hit.
- I hope that's true.
- Are you sure about that?
You got rid
of all your bad luck here.
(Thanks to Chorong, Bomi, Mirani,
and KCM for their appearance.)
I hope our album becomes a hit.
(The worst penalties...)
(wait for the members.)
(To avoid worst penalties ever,)
(they promise to stay united.)
- Right.
- There are seven.
(Step by step,)
(they carefully enter...)
(the mysterious universe.)
(Doctor, president,
judge, scientist)
(Act casually.)
(I've already done...)
(suction on that patient.)
(If you don't pay attention,
it will cause big trouble.)
The whole family is bald.
(Their teamwork is
about to collapse.)
(In the midst of
conflict and confusion,)
(seven people are on trial.)
(Before the temptation of coins,)
(will 7 people stay loyal?)
(The 2nd Sharing Playbook)