(It's the second day of
a two-day-long shoot which is rare.)
Okay. Do we keep
our shoes on in the house?
- Hello.
- What do we do in this fancy house?
I know.
My eyes are all puffy, right?
Yes. Did you sleep a lot?
No. I just had
six packs of ramyeon last night.
Why?
I had an eating show.
- An eating show?
- It's so cold.
- Hello.
- Gosh, Ji Hyo.
You're all dressed up today.
Today...
- I like your outfit.
- I dressed up.
- It's so cold.
- My gosh, Ji Hyo.
What's with my pants?
Jong Kook, see? You should
dress up like Ji Seon.
She looks so fashionable.
- Look at her.
- What's the difference?
- We look the same.
- No, you're different.
I look even better.
- You think you look better?
- Yes.
(Unusual fashion philosophy)
Did you wear
the same pants yesterday?
Yes.
They are the same pants,
but these are new.
- Ji Seon...
- With the same design.
I heard Ji Seon is having a hard time.
Why?
She feels like she's being paid
for doing nothing.
- She does work hard though.
- Really?
It's not easy. She needs to buy
five outfits with the same design.
That's not an easy thing to do.
We run out of clothes soon.
I should take a picture of this.
It has Se Chan's face on it.
This is Se Chan.
I heard he paid for this.
(Se Chan ordered a coffee truck
for the members of Running Man.)
That's right.
He should pay the membership fee
for our soccer team.
Right. And...
A coffee truck doesn't cost a lot.
Hey. My goodness.
Why would you say that
while drinking the coffee?
What's wrong with you?
You're unbelievable.
(There's a sound of grinning.)
(Se Chan and So Min were
watching the whole thing.)
What did he say?
(The evening before)
(Tomorrow, we will pick a member
who's last in the hierarchy.)
(The last in the hierarchy will
take on all the difficult tasks.)
(So Min: Difficult tasks?)
(Se Chan: My gosh. Okay.)
Hello.
Dear directors, I will order
a coffee truck next week.
I will appreciate your votes.
I love you all.
I love you, dear directors.
(She woos the crew members
with her open display of affection.)
Did you enjoy the coffee?
(Did you enjoy the coffee?)
I wish I would get all the votes.
Unanimous votes.
Like a score of 95 to 3.
Are you wearing the microphone?
Hey. Why did you get us
a coffee truck today?
I told you. It was supposed
to come yesterday.
You know this is a bribe.
- It's not a bribe.
- Seriously, this is bribery.
I didn't even know
about today's mission.
Actually, I want to be
the last in the hierarchy.
- Why?
- I like it.
But I don't want my name
to be at the end.
- I see.
- That's what bothers me.
Why would you even care about that?
Even your name?
Because it makes me...
look unpopular.
(She thinks the order of names
is based on popularity.)
- That's not true.
- You know what? Suk Jin's name...
- comes...
- Before Jae Suk's?
No. His name comes after Jae Suk's.
But Jae Suk is younger
than Suk Jin.
- That's ridiculous. Listen.
- It's not based on our ages.
But it's not based on popularity.
His name comes before Jong Kook's.
That doesn't make sense.
So there's no fixed rule.
Then it should be
So Min, Suk Jin, and Se Chan.
No, So Min. Let me make this clear.
You are going to lose today.
I think I'm losing already...
- because of the coffee truck.
- Hello.
- This is amazing.
- The other members...
don't know you are watching them.
(They are going
to have a secret poll.)
Paying for it is no big deal.
This is from Se Chan.
He got the coffee. Enjoy it.
Se Chan's fans did it for us.
- Se Chan paid for it himself.
- Se Chan got it himself.
- Really?
- Yes.
He paid for this.
That's why I said that.
I wouldn't say it didn't cost a lot
if it was from his fans.
I'm not that crazy.
(He feels dizzy
just at the thought of it.)
I thought...
I just thought you were so gutsy.
(I just thought you were so gutsy.)
- Gosh, this is...
- My goodness.
He's the one who's gutsy.
- What?
- What? Who is he?
It looks like
he's wearing a straw mat.
- He's the one who's gutsy.
- Why?
He's so gutsy.
(A beggar shows up
at a fancy house.)
- Suk Jin.
- What's going on?
I heard my stylist say something
on my way up here.
"My gosh. He looks amazing."
As I always say, for celebrities,
I wonder how Haha likes it.
it's important to have
good people around.
- Do you not like it?
- I admire the spirit of challenge.
- I agree.
- It's cool.
Honestly, I was ashamed at first.
But I've tried many unique outfits,
so this is no big deal.
You were told not to wear black.
- It brings you bad luck.
- I will break my fate.
- My fate.
- That sounds scary.
Even Jong Kook's parents can't...
- break his obstinacy.
- Right.
No one can stop him.
He will probably cave in
if he meets a woman he loves.
No. The woman he loves will cave in.
You think?
What?
Why?
- What did you say?
- Isn't that true?
- How could you say that?
Jong Kook.
Marriage isn't about
being obstinate or caving in.
Mind your own business.
Suk Jin, mind your own business.
- He already caved in.
- Mind your own business.
I don't want to hear it from you.
- You can't be obstinate.
- Speak for yourself.
Then what is marriage about?
You should be understanding
and considerate of each other.
- Mind your own business.
- But why do you...
yell at your wife
when you talk on the phone?
When we talk on the phone,
he's like, "Su Jung,
I'm talking on the phone."
(He throws tantrums.)
- Really? That's the worst.
- That's...
- what we usually say to kids.
- "Su Jung."
People might take it the wrong way.
- I wasn't throwing a tantrum.
- Yes, you were.
You might take it the wrong way.
You were throwing a tantrum.
I just said, "I'm on the phone."
But she didn't hear it
and talked to me again.
So I was like,
"I said I was on the phone."
I just said that out loud.
Gosh, this is...
Haha.
- Why are you being so quiet?
- What do you mean?
Are you like this
even on "How Do You Play?"
(Are you like this
even on "How Do You Play?")
I'm sorry, but...
Look at him.
We keep talking,
- but he's being quiet.
- "How Do You Play?" doesn't...
have a member like you.
I feel comfortable there.
You should talk more.
You were talking,
so I was showing some responses.
That's not enough. You need to talk.
You should bring up something.
(Making a funny sound)
Hey.
Isn't he acting up?
(Isn't he acting up?)
Hey.
I think he's defying me.
You're even worse than him
to your seniors.
(Meanwhile...)
This is what he always does.
(They forget about the youngest
members and keep chattering.)
He thinks it's big.
I'm not sure about that.
I have an objection.
Why aren't they talking about us
when we're not around?
They didn't ask them about us yet.
They don't even find it strange.
I flinch at a time like this.
Everything goes well without us.
You know what I mean?
This is why we should work hard.
- They don't realize our absence.
- They don't.
That's why we should try hard.
Everything goes well
even without Suk Jin.
- Are you showing it off?
- You're wearing a yellow shirt.
Are you showing off your shirt?
You're wearing yellow.
- Yellow brings him good luck.
- Right. Yellow is good for him.
- He believes in fortune-telling.
- Suk Jin.
I can break
the three years of misfortune.
He's amazing.
- I can break misfortune.
- There's nothing you can't break.
All right. Today...
- What?
- Is it started already?
So Min and Se Chan aren't here yet.
Between the two youngest members,
Jeon So Min and Yang Se Chan,
we will pick
the last in the hierarchy.
What do you mean?
That's important. We need
to have a pecking order.
- It was tricky for us.
- They are of the same age.
(The order of their names has been
a tricky issue for crew members.)
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
Haha, Ji Hyo, So Min, Se Chan)
(The order of the names got
mixed up in press releases.)
(Yang Se Chan and Jeon So Min,
Jeon So Min and Yang Se Chan)
(The youngest member's task 1:
Closing the clapper board)
(The two youngest members
did it in turns.)
(The youngest member's task 2:
Running errands)
(The youngest members did
all the difficult tasks.)
In alphabetical order,
Se Chan's name comes first.
But sometimes
So Min's name comes first.
So before we start the race,
- I'd like to hear your thoughts.
- Okay.
So Min and Se Chan are waiting
somewhere else.
Between Se Chan and So Min,
who do you think is more mature?
More mature?
I'm not sure. The thing is...
I'm feeling nervous.
My name is called.
(The members don't know
that they are listening.)
Se Chan is more mature.
- Se Chan is.
- He's more mature.
That's not true. That's just
how we look on the show.
The reason we pick the last
in the hierarchy is...
to decide who will...
take on chores and run errands.
I think it's easier
to have Se Chan do all the work.
If that's the case,
Se Chan is better
because he's quick-witted.
- We can't send So Min on errands.
- My point.
But you let her run errands.
You're the one
who always sends her on errands.
That's true.
- You know what?
- I was surprised to see him.
- He does that all the time.
- Hey.
I just asked for a favor.
This is sending her on an errand.
"Hey, So Min. Go bring that to me."
But I was like, "So Min,
will you pass me that thing?"
That's the same thing.
- He let her run errands.
- It's the same.
That's what old people always do.
"Bring that to me."
When I'm about to eat something,
Suk Jin asks,
"Are you going to eat it?"
- He wants it.
- Exactly.
- This is what he always does.
- It's the same thing.
"Are you going to eat it?"
- "Are you going to eat it?"
- You let her run errands.
Suk Jin,
you make her uncomfortable.
- She's right.
- What are you talking about?
That's the worst.
I'm really upset
when he takes my food.
He knows what I'm having.
- Let's say I'm eating jjamppong.
- Right.
But he asks, "What is this?"
You know what it is.
- We had jjamppong yesterday.
- That's horrible.
- "What is this?"
- Rice was delivered by mistake.
- But he ordered noodles.
- Right.
And So Min was there.
He said,
"Mine doesn't have noodles in it."
(I want you to give
your noodles to me.)
- He's the worst.
- And So Min said,
"You can have mine."
- So Min ordered fried rice.
- "No, it's okay."
- "I'm fine."
- He's the worst.
That means,
"Give me your noodles now."
- Right?
- So Min...
Thankfully, So Min
gave me her noodles.
And Ji Hyo was eating already.
"Does yours have noodles in it?"
(Does yours have noodles in it?)
She was about to eat noodles.
- She could see it.
- We all could see it.
Anyway, I think
Se Chan is more mature.
(The conclusion is that
Se Chan is more mature.)
The conclusion is that
you're more mature than me.
I'm more mature.
But Jong Kook and Jae Suk think
it'd be better to have me...
run errands.
Hang on. The last in the hierarchy?
Se Chan might look mature,
- but So Min is also thoughtful.
- I agree.
- She's right.
- They say good things about us.
They just don't know.
You two talked a lot
on the phone late at night.
To be honest,
neither of them looks
like the youngest member.
They are quite old.
- They are...
- How old are they?
We can't say they are young.
- They are 37 now.
- They are 37?
- To be honest...
- Are they 37?
- Se Chan and So Min...
- I said they were old.
are the youngest ones here,
- but they are not quite young.
- How old are you?
I'm 44.
(I'm 44.)
I'm 44 and have 3 children.
Will you give me a break now?
Hey.
(The 44-year-old boy is
a father of 3 children.)
- Jong Kook said...
- He's old too.
it would never happen
even if I had five children.
He would never give me a break.
- Not until he dies.
- He's old.
- Are you 44? He's old.
- He's 44.
- He's 44, but...
- You seem surprised.
- If you're 44...
- You're shocked, right?
- Hey.
- That means he's old, right?
I told you before.
When Se Chan is...
on "Comedy Big League,"
he's like a king.
- Right.
- He's like a king.
You have a commanding
presence there, right?
Kind of.
I'm different there.
- I'm like, "Hey."
- I'm curious.
- Are you like them?
- I'm like them.
I'm like, "Hey, you guys."
- "You punks."
- Little Kim Jong Kook.
When Ji Hyo goes to her hairdresser,
everyone makes a bow to her.
Jae Suk.
- Hey.
- That's true.
- Look at her. They should do that.
- That's what they do.
She looks young
because she's with us.
"Give me some water."
This place looks
like Ji Hyo's house.
I have a question.
You're not going to start
the shoot without us, are you?
This is so fun.
The opening is really fun.
I want to join them...
and be part of it.
What is going on?
We won't be on TV for long.
That's the main part.
We will be on a small screen
at the bottom, right?
You should say that on
"Invitation from Bachelor-agains."
(They are chattering
without the youngest members.)
- Suk Jin.
- I'll save it for the show.
See? They don't talk about us.
Why aren't they talking about us?
Let's go. Pick up the water gun.
- What's that water gun for?
- What's that water gun?
I'm supposed to shoot
those who say boring things.
(The 37-year-olds are upset
that they had fun without them.)
Suk Jin, I don't like your jacket.
- What's this?
- What's with your outfit?
You talk a lot
on "How Do You Play?"
- What?
- Why are you being quiet?
And a coffee truck
doesn't cost a lot?
It doesn't cost a lot?
Did you hear all that?
- We heard it all.
- In there?
- The whole thing?
- I had no idea.
I like your jacket.
It looks good on you.
I like your outfit today.
- It looks great on you.
- You know what?
Jae Suk bought me this.
- I see.
- It looks nice.
- You picked a good one.
- It does look good on you.
You shouldn't dress up
on a day like this.
What are you talking about?
Se Chan is quite a dresser.
- I don't look young today.
- That's nice.
He got us the coffee truck
today of all days.
I can't believe this.
- That doesn't matter.
- It has nothing to do with this.
It doesn't cost a lot.
(It doesn't cost a lot.)
(The stubborn voter is
not swayed by pin money.)
Thank you.
When Jong Kook said
it didn't cost a lot,
I found it hilarious.
Let me tell you about today's race.
Among Running Man's lucky charms,
So Min and Se Chan,
we will pick a member
who's last in the hierarchy.
It's called The Seniority War
of the Youngest Members,
- Who Is the Last in the Hierarchy?
- All right.
The loser of this race...
will be the last in the hierarchy.
The loser will get a penalty today.
And the loser's name will
come last in all press releases.
The last in the hierarchy.
The loser will be
the last one in everything.
- I see.
- It's good to be the youngest...
- except for having more jobs to do.
- It can be a good title.
- You'd be considered the youngest.
- Exactly.
- The order kept changing, right?
- Yes.
I couldn't fall asleep because of it
several times.
- Why?
- Are you serious?
It makes me worry for no reason.
I know that it doesn't
mean anything.
- I see.
- No way.
I'm serious. Someone must've decided
the order of our names.
- Right. Does it bother you?
- "Haven't I been doing well?"
- "Why is Se Chan before me?"
- Are you serious?
- Really?
- Such thoughts come into my mind.
- It keeps you up at night?
- Actors and actresses do care...
- about the order of the names.
- I didn't know that.
I see that she makes things
too complicated.
- The order of yours and my names?
- Yes.
Hey, if we all think as you do,
Suk Jin would've died.
- I... You should just let it go.
- I guess So Min...
- I think...
- It's not a big deal.
- She's worried for nothing.
- I've seen my name behind yours.
- Don't let it bother you.
- Sometimes it's behind Chan Hee's.
Exactly.
I felt pressured to do better.
- Really?
- It's unusual.
- It must've been stressful.
- You should let it go.
- Try not to let it stress you out.
- The youngest will get more tasks.
- I see.
- From now on...
It's easy to give you more tasks.
We'll take advantage of the title
as the youngest.
- But...
- I find it funny...
that So Min gets annoyed.
- So I'll win no matter what.
- Right.
- She'll hate being the youngest...
- True.
- and having more tasks.
- Good.
I'll enjoy watching her like that.
- That's good.
- Yes.
The loser will be the last
for all that's in order of age.
Also, the youngest will slate on set
throughout this year.
- That wouldn't be a problem.
- I want to slate on set.
- Would you like to be the youngest?
- Do you want to compete with us?
- Can Haha join the competition?
- I'd be happy to slate.
- It's easy.
- Do you want to be the youngest?
- Are you in or not?
- Do you want to compete with us?
You know I'd do anything
to look younger.
- But a crane camera can't find you.
- He's obsessed with being youthful.
- Absolutely.
- Yes.
Wouldn't you mind if we treat you
as someone younger than us?
Would you call us
a big brother and a big sister?
- You should use honorifics to us.
- It's a match between you two.
You two are so rude.
He's acting so bossy.
- He can't be the youngest.
- I'm 44 years old, you know.
- He has three children too.
- You know he acted so bossy...
- on "Music Bank K-Chart" too, right?
- Yes, that's right.
- Yes, he did.
- Jang Won Young and the other MC...
(The old fossil on "Music Bank K-Chart"
drew a lot of attention.)
- It was totally unacceptable!
- Really?
How dare you look at the script?
(Haha yelled at the MCs
while reminiscing the old days.)
Let's move on.
The youngest will do petty tasks
like slating or serving water.
And we'll ask the youngest to relay
messages to the other members.
Hey, he's the director.
And we'll ask the youngest to relay
messages...
(She shot the water gun.)
How could you shoot him
with the water gun?
I've never seen anyone
who did that to a director.
I must say, So Min can be
really crazy.
- She shot the director.
- He's the director of our show.
- During a shoot.
- I was surprised.
- Exactly, during a shoot.
- She can be really crazy.
- She does as she pleases.
- I wasn't joking.
- Why did you do that? I'm curious.
- I bet she hates him.
- I just wanted to shoot him.
- Oh, I see.
- Don't you want to shoot him?
We all do, but none of us would
actually shoot him.
We wouldn't actually shoot him.
Anyway, we'll ask the youngest
to do many things for us.
Here's how to decide the youngest.
After all the missions end,
- you'll vote for the true youngest.
- My goodness.
Each of you will have one vote.
And to be fair, a few staff members
will vote too.
- I understand.
- Okay.
The two youngest members will be
the leaders of their teams.
The other members can choose
the team leader in each round.
The winning team of each mission
will get extra ballots.
(The winning team will get
extra ballots.)
We'll give the two youngest members
So Min coins and Se Chan coins.
You two can give your coins...
- to anyone you want.
- I see.
The coins of the loser of the race
will be invalid.
The two members who have
the most coins of the winner...
will be exempt from a penalty.
(2 members with the most coins
of the winner won't get a penalty.)
(Staring)
- will be exempt from a penalty.
- Hold on. Suk Jin...
- About 30 seconds ago,
- Yes?
- He couldn't understand the rule.
- you lost him.
- He got caught.
- My gosh.
- He wasn't listening.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- Exactly.
- He seems so lost.
- You should've listened carefully.
- I admit it.
I was going to ask Se Chan
about the rule later.
My gosh.
- Honestly, I wasn't listening.
- All right.
In summary, the winning team members
will get extra ballots.
- You'll vote at the end.
- Okay.
- One of them will win the race.
- Yes.
Only two members with the most coins
of the winner won't get a penalty.
- Got it.
- Only two members?
Yes. That means you have to get
as many coins as you can...
- to be in the top two.
- We should give them many coins.
Now, it's time for you to choose
your team for the first round.
So Min and Se Chan,
please wait in your rooms.
- Okay. Please join my team.
- All right.
Okay.
I'll give away at least 300 coins.
Consider yourself informed.
Today, I'll play the role
of the youngest as I've been doing.
But I'll win this race
and no longer act like one.
Which of you will go first?
- Why are we going there again?
- To choose your team.
- "Why are we going there again?"
- I mean...
- You can go home now.
- I can't believe him.
- We're going home.
- Director,
why can't we take a break as always?
- We're going home.
- I usually ask the others...
about the rules during a break.
You just have to choose
1 of the 2 of them.
- Oh, between the two of them?
- Yes.
- The one you support... Correct.
- "I'm rooting for you."
- Okay.
- You go first.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Okay. Got it.
- It's hard to decide.
Should I choose So Min or Se Chan?
(Walking wearily)
- Look how he looks from behind.
- Wait.
(He looked unsure from behind.)
- Who wants to be the youngest?
- He looks as if he just came out...
- covering himself with a blanket.
- No one wants to be the youngest.
Oh, right. The one who doesn't want
to be the youngest...
I'm so worried.
Can he be funny on the show?
Back in my days, he would've been
scolded harshly.
How would he be funny
when he doesn't understand the rule?
(Big Nose trudges to the front
of the youngest members' rooms.)
Neither of them wants to be
the youngest, right?
And I have to choose
the person whom I support.
I'm sure that Suk Jin will join
my team in the first round.
There's no doubt.
(The 2 captains are waiting
for their supporters to come.)
(Sliding a coin)
Didn't he see it?
(She slid a coin
under the door to lure him.)
(But Big Nose couldn't see
the coin.)
He couldn't see my coin.
(He keeps wandering
without finding the coin.)
(So Min's Room)
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, didn't you see it?
- What do you mean?
- I slid a coin under the door.
Where is it?
(He received the coin
that So Min threw as well.)
- Just two coins?
- I'll throw them better next time.
- I see that Suk Jin chose her.
- I gave you three.
Okay.
(Big Nose who didn't understand
the rule joined So Min's team.)
The youngest.
We have to decide
which should be the youngest.
- Thank you for choosing me.
- Haha is here.
(So Min quickly goes
to lure another member with coins.)
I should choose one of them
as the youngest.
What's this?
(Haha found a bait on the floor.)
(1 coin added)
She already gave me two coins.
If Se Chan gives me three coins,
I'll choose him.
(He'll go if Se Chan gives him
3 coins?)
(She gave him the 3rd coin.)
I got three coins.
This is awesome.
Then I guess Se Chan should give me
four coins to recruit me.
(Right then,
Se Chan approaches him too.)
Why?
(Right then,
Se Chan approaches him too.)
- Haha, just come on in.
- Yes?
- Give me some coins first.
- I'll give you...
- I'll give you some if you come in.
- Coins first.
I'll give you ten coins
if you join my team.
I'll choose you
once you give me coins.
- I'll give you ten coins.
- Give me your coins first.
Then I'll give you five coins first.
- Okay.
- Here you go.
Will you give me five more
when I come in?
Come on in. I have five more coins
for you.
Really? Honestly, So Min would be
better as the youngest.
Do you have a thread?
I want to attach it to a thread.
(Candidate Jeon is anxious.)
Do you have any threads?
I'll give you 10 coins.
I'll give you 5 more if you come in.
- Really?
- Yes.
Let's begin with ten coins.
- All right. Come on in.
- Thank you.
I can't believe Dong Hoon.
- Dong Hoon?
- Honestly...
(Following Dong Hoon who chose
his team just to get more coins...)
I didn't know he would do that.
(Ji Hyo is about to choose
her team.)
(Rolling)
(Candidate Jeon is trying to lure
another member with her coins.)
She'll come, right?
I know she'll come.
Are you tempting me?
I can't let him talk her
into joining his team.
(She threw another one
since Ji Hyo didn't take the bait.)
- So Min.
- Come on in already.
- I have an idea.
- What is it?
Ji Hyo, can you be a spy for me?
(Can you be a spy for me?)
If you give me ten coins,
I'll sabotage the other team.
If I give you ten coins,
can you disturb him?
- I'll make the team lose.
- Really?
- I promise.
- And then join my team...
- in the next round, okay?
- Of course.
If you succeed in making them lose,
I'll give you five more coins.
- Okay.
- Can you promise me?
- Yes, I promise.
- Make sure they'll lose.
- I'll do that.
- You're my spy.
I'll be a spy for you.
- Trust me.
- I trust you.
I can always trust you.
- Ji Hyo is my spy now.
- She's a spy?
I gave her ten coins for now
as a retainer.
I'll give her five more coins
if they lose. She'll join us later.
Ji Hyo. How many coins did she
give you? How many do you have?
(Ji Hyo comes to talk
to Se Chan naturally.)
- How many did she give you?
- Give me your coins first.
How many did you get?
- I'll tell you if you give me.
- I'll give you five coins now.
Here. I'm giving you five.
I'll give you more than So Min did.
How many did she give you?
- She gave me ten coins.
- Okay.
Oh, my. You're here.
- Yes.
- Here you go.
(Will Ji Hyo help So Min as her spy
as she promised?)
- Okay.
- Good. Okay.
He's athletic too.
(Next up is Jong Kook.)
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- He didn't even get any coins.
(He chose Se Chan right away.)
- This is...
- Oh, my.
It's a given.
You must be touched, Se Chan.
I didn't even think twice.
My gosh. He went there
without even looking back.
Jong Kook said that he would join
Se Chan's team.
(Opening the door)
Where are you going?
(She's putting her coins
along the path toward her room.)
I must say, So Min is perfect
for a variety show.
(The person whom the coins are for
is here.)
I have to choose who doesn't look
like the youngest member, right?
(Chuckling)
Impressive. But I hate
things like this.
This is the worst as I always say.
(The cheesy coin path seems
to dissatisfy him.)
Gosh. She can never be
simple and nice.
Jae Suk can't seem to decide.
(Se Chan noticed it
and went to convince Jae Suk.)
I mean why...
Will you take the poison
or just join my team?
You don't need any coins
in the beginning, Jae Suk.
Take all her coins and come to me.
I was going to join her team,
but this might change my mind.
It'll put you in trouble.
You know that, right?
Gosh, seriously.
(Picking up)
The coins will be helpful though.
- He says he doesn't like it,
- He actually likes it.
but he's picking them all up.
(The coins lead him
to So Min's Room.)
(Turning around)
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk took the coins
and turned around.)
- Jae Suk.
- Why? What is it?
You can't do that.
(I'm alone with Suk Jin here.)
I'm alone with Suk Jin here.
Why?
(They could end up forming
the weakest duo.)
I'm alone with Suk Jin here.
- I've chosen your team.
- Thank you.
I chose your team because it seemed
there were so few here.
(Bowing)
- Hey, you should know...
- Jae Suk.
You would've teamed up
only with Seok Sam.
There could've been just the two
of us. He complained a lot.
- The team selection is over.
- Okay.
- I feel so confident.
- This is great.
- We're going to have fun.
- The New Zealand team gathered.
- Let's win!
- You're right.
We teamed up together again
after a long time. Great.
We'll begin the first mission
after you change your clothes.
- Okay. I'm excited.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- This is good.
Why are there so many wearing red?
- It looks intense, right?
- The red color...
Take this. One, two.
Are you happy
with your team members?
- They're just perfect.
- Yes.
We can beat them in any game.
That's ridiculous.
So Min would've been in trouble...
- if I hadn't chosen her.
- True.
I would've been alone with Suk Jin
in that room if he hadn't.
Suk Jin would've been happy.
He would've been excited.
The first mission where you can get
extra ballots is...
Musical Chairs with No Hierarchy.
What kind of game is it?
All of you will put on
special swimming goggles.
(They'll wear swimming goggles
that will block their sight.)
While holding hands,
move in a circle
to the music we play.
When the music stops,
find one of the chairs
and sit on it.
- We have to find it?
- Yes.
Until the last person finds a chair
and sits on it,
you're allowed to take
someone else's chair.
- Oh, gosh.
- Really?
- Can we push one another?
- That's not fair.
- If that's allowed,
- we can never win.
- There's no point.
- It's unfair.
- What if the four of them push me?
That's not possible
because you can't see anything.
- Oh, I see. We can't see.
- But still...
- Let's begin the first round.
- Yes.
- Please put on the goggles.
- Okay.
We're at a disadvantage.
- That's not true.
- Don't worry.
- We're not at a disadvantage.
- Right. You have a chance to win.
Suk Jin, this blocks my sight
completely.
- You can't see anything?
- Anything at all.
Oh, my. I can't see anything.
It's pitch dark.
Hey, I can't see anything.
- Gosh. I can't see at all.
- Right?
- I can't see anything.
- It won't be easy.
Jae Suk, you really look
like a locust in the goggles.
(You really look
like a locust in the goggles.)
- Indeed.
- It makes you look...
- like a real locust.
- Locust Man.
(He turned into a locust
with a simple item.)
- All right.
- You look cool.
Please stand in a circle
next to the other team members.
- I can't see anything.
- I'm So Min.
- It's me. Jae Suk, it's me.
- Okay.
- You're Se Chan.
- Jae Suk, it's me.
- Who are you?
- Ji Hyo is on my left side.
- I should hold Jong Kook's hand.
- Who is this?
- Where are you?
- Hey, Se Chan, don't hold my hand.
- Hold my hand.
- It's just a game.
- Don't hold my hand.
I have no choice.
We should move in a circle.
- Don't hug me.
- We'll play a song now.
- While the music is...
- Give me your hand.
Move in a circle
while the music is being played.
- Got it.
- I can't see anything.
- Exactly.
- Now... Play the music.
I can't see anything.
I'm in trouble.
(Round 1 begins.)
I like the song.
("Kiss Kiss" by LABOUM)
This is one of my favorite songs.
Is this LABOUM's song?
- Where are the chairs?
- Yes, it's LABOUM's song.
Where... Hold on.
You shouldn't check
where the chairs are now.
Don't do it now.
He says we're not allowed to do it.
Hey, don't drag a chair toward you.
Gosh. Stop doing that.
- That's not fair.
- Keep moving, everyone.
Move in a circle. Don't stop.
- Who are you?
- We should keep moving.
- Hey.
- Gosh.
(They have to find and sit
on a chair before one another.)
Gosh, my legs. Hold on.
Who are you? Who is this?
(Jong Kook and Se Chan found
and sat on chairs.)
Be careful. Who are you?
Two chairs are taken now.
(2 people on Team Se Chan
already secured chairs.)
There are still three chairs
you can take.
(Suk Jin)
(Ji Hyo)
There are three empty chairs left.
- Two chairs are left now.
- I can't see anything.
There are two empty chairs left.
- Two?
- Yes.
Where are those chairs?
Hey, I...
- Where are those chairs?
- Where are they?
(They got into a brawl.)
Who is this?
- I found Jae Suk.
- It's me, So Min.
- Give me your chair, Ji Hyo.
- How many chairs...
- There are two empty chairs left.
- Hey, It's me.
- Ji Hyo, give me your chair.
- Hurry up and give me your chair.
- There are two empty chairs left.
- Hey.
- You promised you'd help me.
- Hey, quiet down.
- Come on. Help me win.
- You promised you'd be my spy.
- I'll help you.
- Come on. Act naturally.
- All right.
Gosh. What was that?
Whose butt is this?
- Pass me the chair.
- Where are those chairs?
There are two empty chairs left.
- Are there empty chairs left?
- Yes.
Good. I found one.
There's one empty chair left.
I can't find it.
- Haha, hurry up.
- Where is it?
- There's only one left now.
- I found a chair.
There's only one...
(Finding a chair in the dark
made him happier than he thought.)
I can't find it. Who are you?
- Haha, is that you?
- Hey.
Who was that?
- It's you, So Min, right?
- There's one empty chair left.
It's me.
Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
Come over here. Hurry.
(The tactful Little Zombie goes
toward her right away.)
Stop. Who are you?
Whose arm is this?
I asked who you were! Who are you?
(They began to tussle
over the chair.)
Ji Hyo, they're near you.
- Take her chair.
- What is this?
(Little Zombie got more ruthless
since he couldn't see anything.)
Who are you? Ji Hyo, it's me.
- Take the chair from her.
- Jae Suk, help me.
- If you sit on it, it's over.
- Take it.
Ji Hyo, take the chair from her.
There's one empty chair left.
Hey, I already found one.
(So Min sat on a chair too.)
Okay. How did it go?
Who was it? Oh, it was Dong Hoon.
Ji Hyo is out.
(Ji Hyo is out.)
What happened? Did I take yours?
- No.
- You took mine.
- You took my chair.
- How did I end up here?
- Why am I here?
- What happened?
- Why are you facing that way?
- This is awkward.
I was sitting with my back
against them.
(While Ssaebssaeb was
talking loudly,)
(So Min whispered,
"I'll give you five more coins.")
- Sorry?
- I'll give you five more coins.
We'll begin the next round
without Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, tell us
where the chairs are.
When I find a chair,
I'll go, "Woof, woof."
This game is difficult.
My gosh. I couldn't see anything.
Can anyone see ahead
with the goggles on?
- No, not at all.
- I can't see anything.
- So Min.
- Whose hand is this?
- It's me Se Chan.
- One.
- Your hand is so big, Suk Jin.
- Dong Hoon, your hand is huge.
Play the music.
Right?
- Here we go again.
- Let's go.
Don't kick the chairs.
- Who just kicked a chair?
- Hey.
- Hey!
- Stop it.
- That hurts.
- Don't do that.
- Hey, stop it.
- I warned you.
- Keep moving in a circle.
- Keep moving.
- Let's keep moving.
- Don't stop.
(Dun dun dance)
- Keep moving.
- Okay.
(They didn't forget to dance
in the chorus part.)
Hey, don't swing your leg.
- Okay.
- Gosh. Hold on.
Who was that? Hey, who are you?
(Jong Kook and Suk Jin got
into a fight.)
(Jong Kook won.)
- Oh, isn't this...
- Gosh, stop it.
- It's me.
- These are plastic pants.
It's him. I'm sure of it.
Who are you?
Hey, who are you?
What are you doing?
(They're like a couple in the dark
joking around with each other.)
- These are plastic pants.
- I'm already sitting on it.
Who are you? It's mine.
(The spy is giving So Min a signal.)
- Who are you?
- Move.
There are three empty chairs left.
- We have so many empty chairs.
- Here.
Hey, what are you doing now?
(So Min survived again
with Ji Hyo's help.)
- Go that way.
- Jong Kook, did you find a chair?
- Hey, who are you?
- Jae Suk, it's me.
- Go to the opposite side. Go.
- I'm holding Suk Jin down.
(Ji Hyo helps Jae Suk
on Team So Min as well.)
To the opposite side.
- There must be one here.
- No. Jae Suk.
(Grunting)
- There must be one here.
- No.
(The skeptical locust ended up
falling on his butt.)
- There's nothing over there.
- What is this?
Give me those. Whose are these?
These are Suk Jin's glasses.
Jong Kook, did you find a chair?
- Yes, I did.
- Hey.
Haha, where are you?
I'm holding Suk Jin down
in the middle.
- Hey, let go of me.
- There must be one here.
- Haha.
- Hurry up and find a chair.
Haha, come over here.
- Okay.
- What is this?
It's me.
- Haha, is that you?
- Yes.
There are two empty chairs left now.
(There are 2 empty chairs left
including what Haha is holding.)
We have two chairs left?
Yes. Hurry up and find it.
Roll around.
Roll around quickly.
- Hey, it's me.
- Sorry.
I heard the noise.
(Ssaebssaeb found another one.)
(Rattling)
(I heard the noise.)
(Crawling)
- I heard it.
- It wasn't like that.
There's someone in front of me.
- Jong Kook, kick him away.
- Okay.
Knock him down.
I heard the noise over there.
It's me, Suk Jin. You came
in the wrong direction again.
Where is it? Where is the chair?
(Screaming)
(The man in plastic pants started
doing a B-boy dance move.)
(The game is over, but they won't
blow the whistle.)
Where is it?
- Why? Is it over?
- It's over.
- Gosh.
- Who got eliminated?
- Suk Jin is out.
- Great.
- There were two chairs here.
- I see.
What kind of strategy is that? Hey.
(Round 3 turned
into a mixed martial arts match.)
So Min, bite him.
- That's good.
- Good job.
That's good. Hit him hard.
(The match between the foul king
and the foul queen)
- Keep hitting him.
- Hey, stop it.
That's not my underwear.
Hey! Stop groping me!
Fine, I won't do it again.
That's not nice.
Okay.
How did it go?
- What?
- You're playing dirty!
That's not nice at all.
- Behind you.
- Turn around.
- No, not there.
- Right there.
- That's Se Chan.
- Steal his seat.
Wait.
(Slap)
(He gets thrown.)
Nice!
Sit in the chair.
He got on it.
(Jae Suk defeats
his fellow pouty mouth.)
- Okay!
- Jae Suk wins.
He slapped me!
He slapped me
while I was in my seat.
- Nicely done.
- Nice.
- He can't see you though.
- I did it.
- Now...
- He's good at this game.
Only Jae Suk remains
on Team So Min.
- This is what it came to.
- Defeat them all.
I'm the last man standing
on this team.
- Yes, defeat them all.
- Oh, no.
Is it my turn to be activated then?
Okay.
Someone has to stop Jae Suk.
(Jong Kook announces Jae Suk
as his prey.)
Jae Suk, you must make it.
- Go, Jae Suk.
- Let's hold hands.
Who's next?
- Go, Jae Suk.
- Here we go.
Cue music.
(Cue music.)
It's one of my favorite songs.
("Journey to Atlantis" by LABOUM)
Just enjoy the song, Jae Suk.
Wait.
And dance.
Did you kick the seats away already?
- Jae Suk...
- You can take on Jae Suk.
(Out of the blue)
(An uninvited guest performer)
(Laughing)
(The fake artist
takes command of the stage.)
(Peck)
(Gosh...)
He's the worst.
Jong Kook's the worst.
(The whistle is blown.)
Look.
Jong Kook has grabbed Jae Suk.
Hold on.
Seriously?
Gosh.
Oh, no.
(Groaning)
He's the worst.
Things seem too easy for Haha.
Look how strong he is.
Haha has found his seat.
I...
- It's over.
- But...
Is this even allowed?
(Jong Kook holds Jae Suk
so that he can't move.)
This shouldn't be allowed.
Jae Suk!
Let me go!
(Mr. Muscle loves
to have fun with Jae Suk.)
Darn it.
Hey.
Jae Suk, free yourself
and you might get a chance.
The round only ends
when one of you finds a seat.
- Break free and you could win.
- Really?
Is that so?
There's a seat left.
(What's happening?)
He's dragging Jae Suk along.
(Jong Kook rolls Jae Suk
along with him.)
He's dragging Jae Suk along.
- Hey!
- That's how he'll locate the stool?
But...
Haha's getting to safety.
- You...
- No way.
Jae Suk, beside you.
- Beside you. Use your foot.
- Good.
- Use your foot.
- My foot?
- His foot?
- Your left foot!
- Your foot.
- Your left foot.
His left foot.
Jong Kook, it's near your head.
Jae Suk, it's right above you.
- Above you.
- Above my head?
- Above your head.
- Your head.
My head?
Hey.
It's above his head?
Jong Kook has the stool!
He's going to sit on it.
He'll sit on it.
Go, Jong Kook. Just end it.
Hold on a second.
He hasn't sat on it yet.
It's still in his hand.
- He hasn't sat on it yet.
- It's still in his hand.
- In his hand?
- Yes, his hand.
(Team So Min loses
if Jae Suk is eliminated.)
(Will Locust Warrior
turn the tables?)
It's in his hand.
(Jong Kook goes
for the Adam's apple.)
It's over.
- Look.
- My gosh.
- You...
- Goodness.
- Nice!
- Seriously?
- He was able to tease you.
- That was fun.
That wasn't fun at all.
- He didn't have fun.
- It was the worst.
- Gosh.
- Unbelievable.
- That was fun.
- Here you go.
You finished your first game...
and Team So Min was eliminated.
Members of the winning team
will each get a ballot.
(Members of Team Se Chan
each get a ballot.)
Goodness.
- What's this?
- It's the ballot...
- you cast your votes with.
- I see.
(They'll cast their votes
with this ballot.)
- So this is a ballot.
- It's a ballot.
- This is what's important.
- We need this.
So Min, I suddenly feel motivated.
You see...
You were eliminated pretty fast...
for someone who was motivated.
I'll make sure that Se Chan
ends up beneath you.
So Min.
- I'm on your side.
- I'm worth a lot.
I'll devote myself to you.
- I'm motivated.
- You can have ten.
You already gave him a lot.
I'll give you eight coins.
What about me? Three?
No, you get four.
How about five?
Next up is...
the bonus round.
For lunch, you will play
The Food I Ordered.
- The Food I Ordered?
- The Food I Ordered.
- The Food I Ordered
You will each order the dish...
you wish to eat.
The number of ballots you receive
will depend on how fast it arrives.
Goodness.
Then Chinese is the way to go.
- Or street food.
- The faster the better.
The dish or restaurant...
- can't overlap.
- Is that so?
The one who orders it first
will receive the right to the dish.
Do we only order one each?
The number of dishes
will be selected randomly.
(The number of dishes
will be selected randomly.)
The least number of dishes
will be two.
- Right.
- The maximum will be eight...
which will be shared
among the staff.
It's over if you must order a lot...
and one has to be jokbal.
It will take too long.
Only one of us has to win.
You are not in teams.
- Really?
- It's an individual game.
Really?
So every man for himself.
We each have to order
a certain amount of dishes.
- Okay.
- What's the minimum?
- Two dishes.
One or two?
(Jae Suk only has to order
2 dishes.)
Darn it.
- I have to order 6.
- I have to order 4.
Three dishes. Not bad.
- I have to order 5.
- Does this say 8?
- Yes, 8.
- I have to order 7.
I'll order from a nearby restaurant.
Okay. You may now order...
- from your own cell phones.
- I'll use the app.
- What's the address?
- I'll write it down for you.
- Are you already ordering?
- Of course.
I only have to order
two bowls of jjajangmyeon.
Darn it.
I can order anything I want, right?
- Eight dishes though?
- That's right.
- This is bad.
- I hate this.
You can't order
two of the same dish.
- Must they be different?
- Are you serious?
Unbelievable.
- That's insane.
- Must they be different?
I can't order two of the same dish?
- Then...
- Hey.
This is crazy.
(Jae Suk is the only one
who doesn't use a delivery app.)
- Hello?
- Yes, hello.
- I'm here at Seongbuk-gu, Seoul.
- Let me order from there.
I'd like to order
1 jjajangmyeon and 1 jjamppong.
- One jjajangmyeon, one jjamppong.
- Right.
Thank you.
All right. I'm all set.
(Jae Suk placed his order,
so no one else can order Chinese.)
No one else can order Chinese.
I'm ordering street food.
No, that's mine.
What can be made in a hurry?
Cheese gimbap and tuna gimbap.
(Laughing triumphantly)
- I ordered seven.
- He's so annoying!
Darn it!
I'm done. It cost me 35 dollars.
- I placed my order.
- What did you order?
- Dumplings and...
- Street food is off the table.
How can a burger take
40 minutes to make?
I offered the cafe owner
Jae Suk's autograph...
in exchange for fast delivery.
- What?
- I offered your autograph...
- in exchange for fast delivery.
- Six dishes of jokbal...
I ordered pork cutlet!
- A rush order of 40 minutes?
- I ordered kalguksu.
It cost me 84 dollars.
(It cost me 84 dollars. Darn it.)
Call 114 and ask...
which restaurant offers
the fastest delivery.
Get the phone number from them...
and place your order.
- Are you good with sandwiches?
- Sure.
Okay, I'm done.
(Old man Suk Jin
manages to order 8 dishes.)
My order is being confirmed.
- It'll take 43 minutes.
- Okay.
I placed my order.
I'm sure that my order...
- Eight dishes.
- is being wrapped as we speak.
I bet they're on the wrapping phase.
How can Jae Suk not win this?
Chinese restaurants offer
the fastest delivery.
Who's the current
youngest member then?
- It's Suk Jin, of course.
- It's just that...
Yes, Suk Jin.
- It's just that I want some water.
- Got it.
This is what I call habitual.
(Se Chan is used
to running errands.)
This is what
the youngest member will do.
- These things...
- Go ahead and take one.
Haha.
Haha, here.
- Thanks.
- Haha,
- here you go.
- Thank you.
Here you go.
The water is cold as ice, isn't it?
The water in my van froze.
I bought a lightweight padded jacket.
One to wear indoors?
- Indoors?
- Yes, to wear indoors.
Back home,
my father wears the padded jacket
he wears outdoors.
(My father wears the padded jacket
he wears outdoors.)
(They wear padded jackets
to reduce heating bills.)
- And turn the heater down?
- Yes.
And in the summer...
Se Chan and I went to his house
to film something.
It was summer and he stepped outside
covered in sweat.
The living room
was pretty hot as well,
but he was like,
"Gosh, it's cool out here."
- He doesn't turn the AC on.
- No, he doesn't.
You don't turn on the one
in your room?
I only turn on the one in my room.
- But you will once you're married.
- Once I'm married,
that'll be up to my wife.
But you'll complain though.
"That's a lot in utilities."
Of course not.
- He'll be like that for sure.
- No way.
I'm not one to bother
with the utility costs.
- I'm not like that.
- He's frugal.
I'm saving up the money
for my wife and children to spend.
- What about...
- I have no use for it.
Does that include
the wet wipes you received...
- as a housewarming gift?
- Of course.
Even after all these years?
- We bought that for him.
- Are they for your kids too?
Of course.
What about
the toilet paper I got you?
- Exactly.
- Jong Kook...
Ji Hyo, seriously?
- What?
- That tissue.
She used it to wipe her nose
and put it back in her sack.
I saw that.
His future wife!
- Gosh.
- I can't believe it.
- Seriously?
- It wasn't a clean one either.
- She didn't throw it away?
- Like husband, like wife.
Actions speak louder than words.
- Unbelievable.
- Nothing else is needed since...
- actions speak louder than words.
- It went back in your sack?
- After wiping her nose with it,
- Good one.
she put it back in her sack.
Is this your way
of flirting with him?
Words aren't needed in this case.
You saved the used tissue.
- I can't believe it.
- How thoughtful.
- No way.
- She's just as frugal.
I'm amazed, Ji Hyo.
(Food is delivered.)
(Which dishes are first to arrive?)
- He doesn't buy it.
- So the standard is based on...
Someone is here!
(While they were chattering,
someone's food arrived.)
(Which food has arrived first?)
- Someone is here! It's pork cutlet.
- No way!
(It's pork cutlet!)
(The pork cutlet that Ji Hyo ordered
arrived first.)
- That's mine! It's unbelievable.
- The pork cutlet got here first.
For real?
That was possible because
the restaurant is right in front.
- Is that so?
- The pork cutlet got here first?
- She is...
- The pork cutlet arrived first.
She's the most practical one.
- You're right.
- Ji Hyo...
- It's the pork cutlet.
- She is the lucky one for sure.
- I even called the owner myself.
- They're not coming.
Ji Hyo, we'll give you three ballots
since you won.
That's incredible.
Mine should be here soon.
Ji Hyo, you don't mind
if I have this, do you?
Not at all. Go ahead.
- Thanks.
- They don't need to give this.
Here he goes again.
Just leave it.
- No.
- It's a waste, isn't it?
Give it to me.
Ji Hyo can use it as her pouch.
Come on. She'll use it as her pouch.
- No.
- Here. Use it as your pouch.
Use it as a reflecting plate.
There you go.
Something else is here.
It's jjajangmyeon and jjamppong.
Is it mine?
Yes! It's jjajangmyeon
and jjamppong.
Jae Suk is lucky.
Since you won 2nd place,
we'll give you 2 ballots.
All right!
I heard the doorbell ring.
(The doorbell rang again.)
It's street food.
- It's yours.
- Se Chan, you get two ballots.
That's right.
- It's Subway, Jong Kook.
- It's Subway.
(Jong Kook's healthy sandwiches
arrive as well.)
I wish it came a little earlier.
Until when will you make my food?
This is driving me crazy.
- The emoji keeps going like this.
- It keeps...
- It keeps cooking.
- The emoji keeps going like this.
The emoji.
Look at this.
Oh, I got a call.
What is it?
(Right then, Haha gets a call
from the deliveryman.)
- Hello?
- Please leave it by the front.
Just ring the bell, please.
The bell? The address says
it's a construction site.
- A construction site?
(Startled)
- There's a construction site.
- It's next to the site.
(Haha's deliveryman missed
the place and drove past it.)
Tell him it's the house
with many cars.
There's a house where there are
many cars parked.
(He's in a hurry.)
This is worth a shot.
Do I have to go down the hill
from the construction site?
(But...)
(Right then)
(Another deliveryman arrives.)
- It'll take two minutes.
- I'm waving my hands here.
Over here.
(But...)
(So Min's deliveryman
goes back the way he came.)
(Halting)
- Come to this side. Thank you.
- All right.
Hurry! You need to come faster
than that man!
Two deliverymen arrived
at the same time!
(Two deliverymen arrived
at the same time!)
- Really?
- You need to hurry!
- Sir! Please hurry!
- Please hurry!
- This won't do!
- Hey.
Sir, please hurry!
- Please hurry up!
- Please come in faster than him.
- They're...
- You need to come in faster.
(The deliveryman who enters first
will win.)
You need to come up
faster than he does.
I think it's mine.
You need to come in before he does.
You ordered a lot though.
(So Min wins.)
That's mine. All right! Thank you.
That was close.
My deliveryman came in
before the other guy.
So Min takes fifth place,
and Haha comes in sixth place.
What did you order?
Suk Jin is in seventh place.
(Suk Jin takes last place
as his food hasn't arrived.)
He's in last place.
You guys can have the food
when it arrives.
Thank you so much.
- All right.
- I think he's sullen.
Are you upset
that you spent 100 dollars?
- No.
- Why do you sound so blunt?
He'll say this to Bo Pil later.
- To pay for it?
- To wire him money?
"I'm sorry, Bo Pil,
but for the food..."
"Wire me money."
("Please make it look like
I paid for the food.")
- "Let's split the bill."
- "Bo Pil."
"Bo Pil."
(Laughing awkwardly)
Please enjoy the food.
This is a really delicious sandwich.
And we'll continue
the mission afterward.
- I'm so full.
- Look at this.
You'll need to choose your team
before the second mission.
Who should I pick this time?
- First...
- I think they'll win for sure.
- So Min is so stingy with coins.
- Is that so?
- But So Min gave me a lot.
- She's really stingy.
- How many do you have?
- Wait a minute.
He's not giving me any coins.
He's not?
- The number of coins matters a lot.
- Did he give you any coins?
Look at this punk.
- Right?
- He made us forget about it.
- He didn't give you any?
- Two, four, six, eight.
I have about 20 coins.
- You got about 20?
- Yes.
- You got about 20 coins?
- You must let So Min win.
- I got 20 or more coins.
- You need to go all-in.
Why don't we start with Jong Kook
this time?
- Shall I?
- Yes.
- This is ridiculous.
- Jong Kook, join our team.
I think we should stick to one team.
Should I join his team again
and ask for more coins?
Se Chan is so stingy with his coins.
He really is.
(He has arrived on the 2nd floor
with wrath.)
I should go and scout them.
I realized you haven't given us
any coins since earlier.
You gave us coins only once.
I'll give you ten coins
if you come into the room.
We worked hard with the game,
so shouldn't you have given us...
some coins?
- We won the game for you.
- I...
Jae Suk already has
more than 20 coins.
- More than 20 coins?
- That's right.
How come you're not giving us any?
Jong Kook, I can guarantee you
ten coins once you come in.
(At that moment)
Jong Kook.
(Fisherwoman Jeon throws a bait
while showing him the coins.)
How can you give them to me
like this? Hold on.
Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- There are 20 coins in there.
Even if you get 20 coins,
you can't win against Jae Suk.
It's better for you to get
20 more coins from me.
- I'll give you incentives.
- She won't be able to win.
So Min won't be able to win.
Okay, then.
- All right.
- There are 20 coins in there.
I... All right, then.
I choose this team.
It's snowing, and it's so pretty.
- It's really pretty.
- Right.
- It's snowing.
- The white snow is coming down
(The gangster is in a good mood
after receiving coins.)
Jong Kook, if you do well this time,
- You'll give me incentives, right?
- I'll give you more coins.
Right, you know how to boost our morale.
(Next up is Ji Hyo.)
I hope Ji Hyo joins my team.
I'm sure she'll join my team.
(Ji Hyo has been performing
as So Min's spy.)
Ji Hyo is my spy.
I'll give you coins.
Ji Hyo, you should remember this.
Even if you join that team,
you'll be short on coins.
You should join my team and enjoy
the eight coins I'll give you.
What's worse is that
So Min doesn't have coins now.
She gave Jae Suk 30 coins.
- Se Chan, did you know?
- What?
I have a lot of ballots.
How many do you have?
I got plenty.
I'll give you 15 coins to start with.
What do you think?
Why don't you show me...
I'll write her name
if you give me the coins.
- Okay. Keep your promise.
- I promise.
You'll write her name,
- Give me 5 coins since I'm here.
- and I'll give you 5 coins.
Goodness. This is...
I'm not thinking of giving Suk Jin
any coins.
(I'm not thinking of giving Suk Jin
any coins.)
So Min.
So Min, he's offering me six coins.
(Click)
(So Min blocks Suk Jin
from entering.)
Good job. He's good for nothing.
I realized he's not very helpful.
Did she just shut the door on me?
She shut the door on me?
Aren't you going to scout me?
No.
I see.
Gosh, no. I won't join your team.
You're giving me eight coins?
Eight coins?
I'll think about it.
I think he's acting alone.
- It's so obvious.
- Right?
He's acting on his own.
You're giving me eight coins?
- Eight coins?
- You see?
He should come in last
in the hierarchy.
(You see?)
He's 57 years old this year.
(He's 57 years old this year.)
And he's still faking a deal.
Who's immature here?
Look at him.
He's 57, and yet...
"Give me one more, will you?"
Did you just have a daydream?
I didn't say anything.
What do you mean by eight coins?
How many do you have?
So Min gave me eight coins.
Let me see. I'll give you ten coins.
- Ten?
- I'll give you ten.
- Give it to me.
- Come in first.
You should give it to me first.
He's inside the room.
He's done, right?
- It's confirmed.
- It's confirmed. Great.
(Suk Jin, who had nowhere to go,
chose Team Se Chan.)
- All right.
- This is great.
- I hope they give us a quiz.
- All right.
- Gosh, we're a strong team.
- Well done, Jae Suk.
- All right.
- We're so strong.
We don't need anyone else.
Shall I lock the door
since I don't need anyone else?
I'll give you 12 coins.
- I think we'll win this time.
- All right!
- All set.
- I can't help it.
- Of course not.
- It can't be helped.
Of course I should choose this team.
Let's go.
So Min must be high-spirited.
Jong Kook, how could you
join that team?
- Of course.
- I was startled.
I should test my luck on both teams.
All right. Let's move on
to the second mission right away.
The second mission with
the two youngests' pride at stake...
is called
The Youngest's Winning Game.
The youngest members,
Se Chan and So Min,
will write down five simple games
that they're good at.
Then they'll play the game
that's randomly picked.
- Between the youngest members?
- Yes.
- But...
- Between the youngest members?
When they're done with it,
the members can play the same game.
- Between the members?
- The members on each team.
We'll only count the final score.
- So this is pretty fair.
- So...
the team that acquires
four points first wins.
Let's play a quiz.
- Submit the final...
- Play a quiz.
Using the same questions from last time.
Something like this.
- The results will...
- Let's go for gonggi.
Choose a game where you can win.
- A game that guarantees your win.
- A memory game.
Both teams,
please write down the games.
Of course. I'm good at it.
I'll include jegichagi.
- Yes, go for it.
- I'll add jegichagi.
(They're after a win
with games So Min is bad at.)
- Let's choose that.
- Good one.
- Let's...
- You'll win that for sure.
A game he can win.
- Gonggi. You're good at that.
- Gonggi.
- That's it.
- That's it. That's right.
And...
(Gonggi, memory game)
- What else?
- That sounds great.
What about this?
Shedding tears fast.
- That's a good one.
- Right?
Shedding...
What if he sheds tears faster than me?
- Shedding tears fast.
- He won't be able to.
(So Min is also writing a list
of things only she's good at.)
What else is So Min good at?
(What else is So Min good at?)
How do you play that?
Keeping composure?
Keeping composure. What else?
What about boxing?
- Why don't you name comedians?
- Boxing?
- Boxing. What's wrong?
- You want boxing?
- The one whose nose bleeds first loses.
- With me?
- Boxing.
The one whose nose bleeds
loses. What's wrong with it?
I need to win to survive.
Boxing.
What about a quiz on stocks?
- A quiz related to stocks.
- That's a really good one.
You'll be...
- He'll be at an advantage.
- This is totally...
I know stocks well, so...
- You'll win for sure.
- What about this one?
It'll be funny if they use
the same questions from last time.
Gosh, what were they? All right.
Using the same questions
from the same quiz is boring.
Something like an isothermal line?
Something like
the five duties of a citizen?
Yes. Using the exact same questions.
- The exact same ones.
- I remember them.
- Do you think she remembers them?
- I just tried to recall them,
but I couldn't.
What about flicking on a forehead?
- That doesn't sound good.
- It's cute.
You shouldn't include that...
because it'll be too painful
for some.
We have Jong Kook.
What's the point of winning
on your own?
Or we should do something like
stealing a bike.
- You're good at that.
- You should do that.
It'll only take me 15 seconds.
(It'll only take me 15 seconds.)
I can steal it in 15 seconds.
It takes me 30 seconds
to steal a motorcycle.
(It takes me 30 seconds
to steal a motorcycle.)
- Drinking water fast.
- Okay.
- Hey, I got Jae Suk and Jong Kook.
- You'll win for sure.
They can cover any games.
- This is...
- You'll win these for sure.
They're too...
- They're too mean.
- Bring it on.
- That's how it is.
- They're too simple though.
- How reassuring.
- Do we have to play all of them?
I'll pick one now.
There are ten games here.
- All right.
- Okay.
(Among the 10 games,)
Which one is it?
(which game will they play first?)
It's shedding tears fast.
(Shedding tears fast)
(He picked So Min's game.)
- All right.
- You're good at acting too.
- You can do it, right?
- Okay, this is...
- Don't start already.
- We haven't started yet.
Stop it. Don't start.
You started crying
even before receiving...
- Think of that moment.
- the Top Excellence Award.
- You can start when I tell you to.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes. Ready, start.
You can do it.
Don't blink your eyes.
The first one to drop a tear
will win.
(The youngest ones get emotional.)
- Don't blink your eyes.
- The first one...
(A comedian who is
an expert in skits...)
So Min can cry right away.
(versus a great actress)
- Hey, you should imagine...
- So Min...
that you fell
into the bottomless pit.
This is my killer move.
(This is my killer move.)
Why are you doing this to me?
(Why are you doing this to me?)
(So Min suddenly talks
to Jong Kook.)
Why are you staring at me?
It's scary.
Gosh.
(So Min gets emotional
while looking at Jong Kook...)
(and sheds tears in only 3 seconds.)
(It's unbelievable.)
You're the best. So Min is the best.
- How...
- You're the best.
Ji Hyo, you should give this a try.
I seriously thought...
- You can do it, right?
- No, I can't.
- I can't do it.
- You're incredible.
How is that possible?
I killed everyone I know in my head,
but I couldn't cry.
I killed everyone I know,
You'll be able to shed a tear
if you just look at Jong Kook.
- Am I that terrifying?
- He's so scary.
- Am I that bad?
- All the things you did...
flashed before my eyes.
It didn't even take 15 seconds.
All the things he did,
flashed before my eyes.
It's one to nil.
How did she shed a tear that fast?
She's amazing.
- It's unbelievable.
- They should pick your game.
- Either jegichagi or...
- You need to play your game.
- Aren't you going to play?
- No.
- You won't?
Suk Jin and Jae Suk
should give it a try.
- I can never shed a tear.
- I can't shed a tear.
Will you play if Suk Jin does?
- I'll make you shed tears.
- You should play if Suk Jin does.
- If Suk Jin plays?
- I'll make you shed tears.
Okay, I'll play if he does.
You should play, Suk Jin.
- You should try playing it.
- I can never shed a tear.
I'll accept it if your eyes get red.
- Do you want to give it a try?
- Okay.
I'll give you a minute
and another one if needed.
- I don't think I'll shed a tear.
- We're playing it for a minute?
- I can't shed a tear.
- If it's for one minute,
you'll shed a tear
if you just keep your eyes open.
You need to open them big.
- This is...
- Open your eyes big.
You might be able to shed
a tear if you open your eyes big.
Look at Jae Suk.
- It's begun.
- I don't think he'll cry.
Ready, set, go.
(The 1 minute begins.)
Jae Suk, that's quite fast.
- Look at Jae Suk.
- Think of something sad.
I think you might shed it.
Don't blink.
Can you take off your glasses?
(They go head to head
by taking off their glasses.)
They're so ugly.
Think of something sad.
(Something sad...)
Think of your stock prices dropping.
Can you cuss at me, Jong Kook?
Try to move my heart.
I only shed tears when I'm moved.
Jong Kook, go ahead and cuss me out.
Think of your wife.
- Suk Jin, actually...
- Like this?
(Hitting hard)
(He's going to hit Jae Suk
until he cries.)
- Think of something sad.
- He's crying.
What do I do?
You have 15 seconds.
Suk Jin, make your acceptance
speech for the Grand Award here.
- Hit me one more time.
- Say your speech here.
- Then you'll cry.
- I'm grateful for our members.
You know the speech you prepared.
- "Dear my beloved..."
- I'm...
(I'm grateful for our members.
Thank you so much.)
Thank you so much.
I can't cry!
(Jong Kook is still trying
to make him cry by punching him.)
Keep going.
You can do it.
- Hit me one more time.
- Mention our names.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- Hit me one more time. Darn it!
Jong Kook, I'm...
(A rare sight of one being
overly emotional...)
- And then what?
- He's crying.
I'm grateful, and...
(The Grand Award winner
in his imagination...)
(got teary-eyed in no time.)
- He's crying.
- He did it.
- It just came out!
- It came out!
- That doesn't count.
- Mine came out too.
- It came out!
- It came out.
My tear came out.
- It did, right?
- Look at this.
(The director comes in
to verify it.)
- It came out, right?
- It came out.
- Where?
- Suk Jin wins.
(Suk Jin wins.)
(Suk Jin squeezes out a tear
while making his acceptance speech.)
(His eyes got a little watery.)
(On the other hand,
Jae Suk's eyes are dry.)
(Suk Jin manages
to squeeze out his tears.)
I told you to hit me harder.
I thought it'd hurt.
Gosh.
- I did it!
- It's one to one?
I squeezed it out.
- That really helped though.
- I should've hit you harder.
- You did shed a tear though.
- It's a tie!
- This is great.
- Here's the second game.
Please pick jegichagi.
All right. He should pick jegichagi.
- It's jegichagi.
- Yes!
(The games Se Chan suggests)
(They picked the game Se Chan
suggested, jegichagi.)
All right!
We got this.
I'll win this for sure.
- All right!
- We should play it.
- Can they play too?
- We'll make up for it.
- They could make up for it.
- I'll make up for it.
- It's jegichagi.
- We can play against them.
Is there a specific rule
for jegichagi?
We'll just count
the number of kicks.
Let's just keep it simple.
Do you want to add up
the number of kicks?
- Let's do that.
- Let's add up the scores.
We'll add up the scores.
- They have more members anyway.
Okay, let's add up the scores.
But you can't catch it.
- Okay. No catching.
- No catching.
Okay, that'll be better for us.
- That'll be better.
- They're at an advantage.
There you go. Good job.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- No!
- How come she's so good?
- So Min...
- If this is how it'll be...
- Good job. That was great.
- You're pretty good.
It must be because
I did it yesterday.
You're pretty good.
You never know. You might lose
if you make a mistake.
- No catching.
- I'm so nervous, So Min.
- All right.
- No catching.
- My shoes...
- Ji Hyo.
I'm playing first?
- Let's do this.
- You can just kick it once.
- This is really nerve-racking.
- All right.
This is the chance
you can make up for your last game.
- One will be enough.
- All right!
- It's simple.
- Just kick it twice.
- I'll kick twice.
- You can kick it once, right?
- Kick it three times.
No catching.
One.
- That's two!
- Two!
So Min. It's their turn.
- You'll take turns?
- Let's take turns.
All right.
So Min, kick it just once.
No catching, all right?
You should be nervous.
If you catch it,
you'll get no points.
So Min, kick it
like how you did earlier.
Why was I good at it earlier?
- One.
- Why was I good at it earlier?
One, two.
- That's just one.
- That's one.
One, two.
(She's back to her old skills
as soon as the game starts.)
- She only hit the feather.
- That's just one.
- I think she hit it.
- That's two.
- All right.
- Give it to me.
- You should go next.
- I should change my shoes.
- What's your size?
- No changing shoes!
- Why not?
- No changing shoes.
- You should play with your shoes.
- But it hurts.
That's none of my business.
- That's your business.
- You can't change your shoes.
- But your shoes will work well.
- No, they won't.
- No changing shoes.
(Haha gives it a try first.)
Suk Jin, I think...
- your pants are the problem.
- Two,
- three, four...
- Keep going.
That's great! Five, six...
- Seven... Gosh.
- That's six.
- Good job.
- Darn it.
- Why am I so bad at it?
- No tucking in.
- Why can't this be allowed?
- You should play as is.
- Of course.
You should play with what you got.
I'll accept any objections.
Why are you being so unreasonable?
We suggested this game.
- You should play as is.
- You're supposed to...
- hold your pants as you play.
- You can do it.
- All right.
- All eyes are on you.
- Everyone, be quiet!
- Go ahead and try it.
Jae Suk is doing the jegichagi.
Everyone, keep quiet.
- He'll kick it only three times.
- Here comes the king of jegichagi.
- The emperor of jegichagi.
- All right.
The king of jegichagi,
- the almighty of jegichagi.
- Everyone, be quiet!
- All right!
Yoo Jae Suk.
- This is nerve-racking.
- You can do it!
- Watch him.
- The almighty of jegichagi!
- Cameramen, focus!
- Here we go.
- All right.
- Everyone, focus!
(Will he be able to overcome
his nervousness?)
Everyone in the country is watching.
- Two, three, four...
- Two, three, four,
- five. That's four.
- Four, five.
(The end)
That's four.
He kicked it only four times.
I knew it.
We only needed to pressure him.
- We need to pressure him.
- All right.
- You should do well for our team.
- What's the current score?
- You should do well.
What's your current number?
- Kick it 5 times.
- It's 8 to 6.
- Kick it 6 times.
- Is it 8 to 6?
I might not need to play this round.
This is getting interesting.
- My goodness.
- Let's go.
- There are people behind you.
- He needs to do well.
Would you move further back?
- Don't stand so close to me.
- You should start...
- as we are.
- All right.
Suk Jin,
you should take off your pants.
(He moves to the side
to avoid the mischievous members.)
No way.
Two, three,
- four...
- He is done.
Move out of the way.
Hey.
What? I didn't move from my spot.
- Come on.
- He ruined it.
That shouldn't count.
- He stayed still.
- It's true. I didn't do anything.
- Still...
- I didn't do anything.
- Is my total 4?
- Your total is 4.
So the current score is 12 to 6.
Should we go next?
Should they go next?
- You should go next.
- Okay.
- You are up.
You are the last player.
- Kick it 20 times.
- Don't be nervous.
Come on, Se Chan.
- Your team is leading by 6.
- Did you say 6?
(Team Se Chan is leading by 6.)
Don't be nervous.
Your face turned red.
- This is fascinating,
- Why are you nervous?
- Don't be nervous.
- You just become nervous.
- Go.
- That's right.
One, two,
- three, four,
- My goodness.
- five,
six... That's good. Seven...
Come on.
Hey!
(Landing a kick)
What's your problem?
- Hey!
- What was that?
How could you kick me there?
- How could you kick me there?
I could kick it two more times.
You practically stepped on it.
Why did you stand there?
Are you insane?
For goodness' sake.
Kick it 14 times for a tie.
Do I need to kick it 14 times?
- Kick it 15 times to win.
- Don't grab it.
Let's go.
Aren't you standing too closely?
What?
- Hey.
- Why are you standing too closely?
Jong Kook will punch
as he kicks the jegi.
- How many times? 14 times?
- That's right.
- Are you going to stay here?
- Yes.
Hold on.
(Uppercut)
(Flinching)
Are you going to be okay?
(Martial arts jegi)
- Do you kick the jegi like this?
- Yes.
Didn't you know?
- I kick the jegi like this.
- Be careful.
- Are you going to be okay?
- He will break your jaw.
He will break your jaw.
- I kick the jegi like this.
- He will break your jaw.
- Really?
- Yes.
- So you will punch people.
- To kick it 14 times...
- My style changed.
You will get punched.
- He will break your jaw.
- Okay. I will stay here.
- Old man, be careful.
- Okay.
He will break my jaw.
If you come near,
your jaw will take a blow.
I don't want to get dental implants.
- I need to kick it 14 times, right?
- Then it will be a tie.
- Okay. I can kick it 14 times.
- Let's go.
- Yesterday,
I kicked it 25 times.
- Hey.
- That's the usual count.
- It's easy to kick it 14 times.
- That's right.
- Go.
- I bet he will kick it ten times.
- I will lose if I kick it 13 times.
- Yes.
- This is...
- Go.
This is...
One, two,
- three, four...
- That's good.
- Five, six,
seven, eight,
- nine, ten,
- Hold on.
eleven...
- Ten, eleven...
- Hold on.
(Flying)
Eleven...
(I just needed to kick it
4 more times to win.)
Thank goodness.
- Gosh.
- He got close.
Jong Kook is scary.
- It was because of the chair.
- I should have moved the chair.
- Jong Kook did it diligently.
- You did so well.
Team Se Chan won.
Okay.
- Yes!
- They are no match to us.
The score is 2 to 1.
I used to be good at jegichagi.
Here comes the third game.
I guess it requires
athletic abilities.
- A quiz on stocks.
- Okay.
(It's the game Se Chan suggested,
a quiz on stocks.)
Okay.
- It will be related to stocks.
- A quiz on stocks?
- I will answer.
- All right.
I don't know anything about stocks.
I don't invest in stocks.
That's why we suggested this game.
Unbelievable.
- You don't play fair.
- A quiz on stocks.
That's why we suggested this game.
I am so flustered.
Being a chicken breast enthusiast,
Jong Kook started
a chicken breast business.
- Se Chan decided to invest in it.
- Okay.
To his favorite member, Se Chan,
- Jong Kook gave a stock option.
- A stock option.
How do you spell "Stock option?"
Stock.
(How do you spell "Stock option?")
This is an English question.
- This isn't about stocks.
- I think I know.
- Hey.
- Don't give them the answer.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Read the question.
- It isn't "Stop."
- She thinks it's "Stop option."
I wrote down "Stop." Hold on.
- All right.
- "Stock option?"
- Just write.
- Write.
The person whose answer is closer...
- will win this round.
- Write.
- Reveal your answer.
- Hold on.
- "Option?" Hold on.
- Reveal your answer.
- Hold on.
Hold on. It takes time for me. S...
- "Option."
- O.
- Five,
- "Option."
- four, three,
- two...
- "Option."
(Glancing over)
For goodnesss' sake.
I can't believe these jerks.
- I am done.
- This is too much.
(They will have a fierce match
of wrong answers.)
You are out
if you don't reveal your answer.
Hold it up.
("Stook Oktion" and "Stock opsuen")
(Team Se Chan: Stook Oktion
Team So Min: Stock opsuen)
You jerk!
You are so cruel.
Hey.
"Stook oktion."
Show us the answer.
(The answer is "Stock option.")
Hold on. Show us the answer.
- She got "Stock" right.
She got "Stock" right, but...
- "Opsuen."
- S, U, and E are wrong.
- Her answer is much closer.
O, P, S, U, E, and N.
- So his answer is missing C.
- "Stook."
"Stook."
What?
- No way.
- "Stook."
Se Chan's answer
only has two wrong letters.
So Min's answer
has three wrong letters.
(Did Se Chan get
one more letter right?)
(Se Chan won.)
We won the English quiz.
What?
- Is it right?
- It's true.
"It's true."
"Stook oktion."
- He got I, O, and N.
- I, O, and N.
- She destroyed the last part.
- "Opsuen."
- He got I, O, and N.
So Min.
- I mean...
- So Min and I said...
- we should never do a quiz.
- It's not like that.
- This makes no sense.
I needed to savor the pronunciation,
- but I didn't have time.
- Listen.
- This answer makes no sense.
- I can't believe So Min.
- So Min, I am sorry.
You got "Stock" right.
- T, I, O, N.
- How did you lose...
to "Stook oktion?"
We won the English quiz.
How are you so athletic...
- and smart?
- You are making me blush.
- We are done, right?
- Yes.
Team Se Chan won 1 more point,
so the score is 3 to 1.
You should participate in this quiz.
- I can do it.
- You know a lot about stocks.
- I will go next.
- Go.
Okay. I got this.
- I know a lot about stocks.
- The king of stocks.
I am so stressed out.
- Quiz us on economic terms.
- So Min.
I have invested in stocks
for over 20 years.
Suk Jin has invested in stocks
for many years.
That's right.
- All right.
- T, I, O, N.
- Okay.
In the stock market,
what is the measure of halting
future and option sales...
for five minutes...
when futures prices soar
for more than one minute?
- I wrote it down.
- Suk Jin doesn't know.
Can you repeat the question?
I know this.
- Write it down.
- Don't you know the answer?
- Check their answers.
He is writing something down.
- For goodness' sake.
- You have 5 seconds. 5...
I should remember this.
This is bad.
Reveal your answer.
(Sidecar)
That's right. It's a sidecar.
He wrote "Brief pause."
- Come on.
- I...
- Why did you write "Brief pause?"
- I couldn't remember.
Isn't it "Volatility interruption?"
What's
"Volatility interruption" then?
- It's "Volatility interruption!"
- What?
- It's "Volatility interruption."
- "Volatility interruption."
- It's "Sidecar."
- What's "Volatility interruption?"
- "Volatility interruption."
- It's "Volatility interruption."
- It prevents abrupt price changes.
- "Volatility interruption."
I don't know what that is.
(I don't know what that is.)
- Hey.
- What's up with you these days?
Why are you doing this to us?
- Hey.
- What's up with you these days?
Is it "Sidecar"
or "Volatility interruption?"
It's "Sidecar."
I said we shouldn't have
another round.
(The current score is 3 to 2.)
- Thank goodness.
- It was fun.
The last game is keeping composure.
What kind of a game is it?
- Composure? We don't know.
- It's So Min's suggestion.
- Is it like the Absolutely Game?
- Absolutely Game.
You can't get mad.
You can't get worked up or mad.
- Okay.
- So it's about composure.
And you should remember
that this is...
- It's fake.
- Yes.
- It isn't real.
- No.
- Absolutely.
- Don't ruin the atmosphere.
- Promise that.
- Okay.
Promise that you won't cry...
or stop the shoot.
You lose if you show
a strange reaction.
Will you be okay?
So Min, promise me this.
If you run out tearfully
and ruin the atmosphere,
- it will be a bit...
- Let me tell you this.
I will cry.
This is about keeping composure.
This is a warning.
I will run out tearfully.
- What?
- What kind of a game is this?
You are the one
who suggested the game.
Remember that, okay?
Don't be like that.
- Let's go.
- All right.
This is the final.
- Let's begin.
- Destroy her.
How do you lose?
You lose if you lose your composure.
- We will judge by your reaction.
- You lose if you get mad.
I will be the judge.
Se Chan, please begin.
- Okay.
- All right.
You know...
that you resemble
Han Min Kwan, right?
- Absolutely. I know.
- Absolutely.
You know...
that you resemble Han Moo, right?
- Absolutely.
They are starting off light.
You know...
that you are ugly, right?
Absolutely.
You know...
that you are darn ugly, right?
(You know
that you are darn ugly, right?)
- So Min.
- Absolutely.
- How far can we take this?
- That was too much.
- She swore.
Seriously.
- Hold on.
- She lost her composure.
I am giving you a warning.
You lost your composure.
- Me?
- Yes.
- This is ridiculous.
- You lost your composure.
- Don't do that.
If she does it again, she will lose.
- So she just received a warning.
- Yes.
- She totally lost her composure.
- I am really calm.
No, you lost your composure.
- You shouldn't swear.
You lost your composure.
Isn't she well-known
for losing composure very easily?
Why did she suggest this game?
- She swore after three turns.
- Hold on.
- Why did she suggest this game?
- Seriously.
- It's my turn.
- She is brazen.
You...
are still seeing that man, right?
My goodness.
Who?
Why did you ask that?
(Who?)
- What kind of a game is this?
- You lost.
- No.
- You lost your composure.
- You can't ask a question.
- I am sorry.
- You lost.
"Yes" should be your only answer.
Why did you suggest this game?
Why did you suggest it?
- Were you testing your composure?
- What was that?
- You are number eight.
- She received her second warning.
If she messes up again,
she will lose.
- How many warnings are there?
- Two.
- All right. Absolutely.
- Absolutely.
Don't ask a question.
Is my junior from university
doing well?
What?
(He flinches a bit.)
Absolutely.
- What?
- "My junior from university?"
Did you meet up with her?
A film and theater major
at Dongduk Women's University.
Are you still keeping in touch
with the man...
who can sing well?
Absolutely.
- He got himself a new girlfriend.
- I see.
No small talk.
- Didn't she lose already?
- No small talk.
- You have a warning.
- I am sorry.
She lost already.
She lost her composure.
You will marry me, right?
Absolutely.
You can't attack him at all.
You know...
that...
(Se Chan mentioned
her ex-boyfriend's occupation.)
You know that
he is in touch with me, right?
Absolutely.
(Absolutely.)
Hold on. Are you okay?
Jae Suk, she is crying.
- That was the worst.
- She is crying.
- Come on.
- I am not crying.
- This is a game.
- So Min's facial expression...
- She is upset.
- She is crying.
- It's...
- It's obvious, right?
She suddenly lost her composure.
You...
were serious when you badmouthed
Jong Kook, right?
- What?
- Absolutely.
- What did he do?
- He badmouthed Jong Kook.
(Her attack wasn't very effective.)
When you had a kissing scene
in "Show Window: The Queen's House,"
(The drama So Min is in)
you thought of him, right?
Absolutely.
- Stop.
- Absolutely.
- Are you okay?
- You didn't answer right away.
- Jae Suk, just admit it.
- Se Chan won.
- Okay.
(Se Chan won.)
- All right.
- Hey.
- Why did she suggest this game?
- Seriously.
She has the least amount
of composure.
Why did you suggest the game?
Since she suggested it, I thought...
- I thought she knew a secret.
- Seriously.
I also thought she knew a secret.
I thought that too.
- You lost composure first.
- It's only a game.
- Don't misunderstand.
- That's right.
Thus, Team Se Chan won
with the score of 4 to 2.
I didn't even suggest this game.
- Why did you suggest this game?
- Seriously.
The back of her neck
is hot right now.
(The back of her neck
became a sauna.)
- Composure.
- Why did you pick that game?
(Team Se Chan gets a ballot each.)
- Okay.
- For goodness' sake.
We will have the last mission
right away.
- Gosh.
- That was so funny.
The last mission is very simple.
Between Se Chan's room
and So Min's room,
the room with more people will win.
Everyone in that room
will receive a ballot each.
So guess which room
will have more people.
- Okay. That's good.
- Okay.
Let's go.
- I will go last.
- Me too.
(Which team will get more teammates
and win the mission?)
I have four ballots.
I collected a lot.
Jae Suk and Jong Kook are the ones
with a lot of So Min coins.
How many coins does Ji Hyo have?
(Despite being So Min's X-Man,)
All right.
(Ji Hyo didn't receive
So Min coins.)
(It's important to secure
as many coins as possible.)
How many more do you need?
Compared to Jae Suk,
I have half the number of coins.
I will give you ten more coins.
(I will give you 10 more coins
if you come here.)
I will give you ten more coins.
(So Min suggests 10 So Min coins.)
All right.
(Ji Hyo chooses Team So Min.)
Nice.
Here.
(So Min recruited Ji Hyo
with the promise of 10 coins.)
I will give you five.
Hey.
(So Min doesn't have
a lot of coins left.)
Where should I go?
(Now comes Jae Suk,
the man with many So Min coins.)
(Jae Suk has done all the missions
as a member of Team So Min.)
(Which team will the man
with many So Min coins choose?)
(Why did he enter Se Chan's room?)
So Min needs to do some hard works.
Is So Min filming right now?
(So Min didn't show up.)
- I won't pick you.
- Don't pick me.
- I will stay with Se Chan.
- Ten coins for you.
Ten coins for you.
I gave you the coins.
She is doing something.
(Se Chan and Jae Suk
figured it out.)
- She is doing something.
- She is trying to recruit them.
(Se Chan opened the pouch as well.)
Will you give me coins?
Jae Suk.
I will give you a lot of coins.
(Thus, Jae Suk received
a lot of Se Chan coins.)
I am in your care.
How many do you have right now?
- I am not sure.
- Count the coins.
If Jong Kook and Haha come here,
- we are set.
- Okay.
(Next comes Haha,
the member So Min won over.)
Haha, I will give you ten coins.
- Really?
- Yes.
Okay.
All right.
I am sorry, So Min.
We are set.
If Suk Jin comes, we are set.
Did he go to that room?
We need Jong Kook.
He went to that room.
That won't do. We need Suk Jin.
But Suk Jin...
We need to win Suk Jin over.
Which room has more people?
I need to choose well.
Does that room have a lot of people?
How many people are there?
Both rooms got two members,
but we have a better chance.
Why?
Suk Jin, I will give you ten coins.
How many coins did she offer?
- She offered 15 coins.
- What?
- I will give you 16 coins.
Suk Jin, I will give you 17 coins.
Did you say 17 coins?
(They begin to have a game of wits.)
I will give you 20 coins.
Come on.
Really? Give me 20 coins.
- I have 20 coins.
- Let me see.
Will I have an advantage
if I enter this room?
Counting 2, 4, 6, 8... 20.
- How many coins do you have?
- I have 11 coins.
Then you will have 31 Se Chan coins.
Will I be in the top two?
Jae Suk and Jong Kook
only have 25 coins each.
Do they only have 25 coins each?
(Se Chan guarantees
that he will be in the top two.)
- Really?
- Yes.
(The outcome depends
on Suk Jin's choice.)
I'm in.
Suk Jin, I will give you 20 coins.
I received the coins.
You received many coins.
- What?
- You received many coins.
But Ji Hyo has...
- many ballots.
- You won.
- Yes!
- Okay.
- Now, the coins are important.
- All right.
I gave people a lot of coins.
Once they receive more ballots,
we will have
a fewer number of ballots.
I have many ballots.
Do you have many ballots?
(Who will be decided
as the last in the hierarchy?)
We need to write it down, right?
Let's vote.
On the ballot,
write down the name of the person
who will be the youngest.
The person who doesn't get picked
as the youngest will be the winner.
Two people with the most number
of winner's coins...
- will be exempt from the penalty.
- Okay.
The person who gets picked
as the youngest...
will choose 1 of the 3 members...
who aren't exempt
from the penalty...
to carry out the penalty together.
If So Min doesn't get picked
as the youngest,
both of them will be exempt
since there are only two members.
It's not about the team.
Two people with the most number...
of winner's coins will be exempt.
I see. So it's about everyone.
I see.
It isn't about the team.
(He understood the rules
right before the ending.)
Then I don't have much of a chance.
- What?
- Who should be the youngest?
(Who should be the youngest?)
You should have thought
about it earlier.
- Seriously.
- You came to my room.
Suk Jin.
- Why didn't you think earlier?
- You should have done that.
I did think, but...
I voted.
Me too. I am done.
Gosh, this is hard.
All the members voted.
I told you that
the staff members will vote too.
Producers, scriptwriters,
and cameramen will vote.
- I will cherish each vote.
- That's right.
So Min did well
in the beginning, but...
- Absolutely Game.
- That ruined her.
- That ruined me.
- Keeping composure...
- completely ruined her.
- Yes.
- Totally.
- Staff members got many ballots.
- Seriously.
There are about 40 ballots.
Please count them.
Okay. I will count the ballots.
(Candidate 1, Yang Se Chan
wants to escape menial tasks.)
(Candidate 2, Jeon So Min
says she makes a good big sister.)
So it's bad to get picked.
- You lose if you get picked.
- You lose.
All right.
Suk Jin voted for So Min.
- Why would you say that?
- Okay. I will remember that.
(Suk Jin got on So Min's bad side.)
Ji Hyo, show the board.
Jeon So Min.
- Please mark.
- Hold it like this.
- So Min.
- Jeon So Min.
- Two votes for Jeon So Min.
- I will do it.
Jeon So Min.
No.
- Three votes.
Jeon So Min. Four votes.
Four votes?
Jeon So Min.
I can't predict the result.
Don't be absurd.
I am getting all the votes.
Suk Jin voted for So Min.
It's natural for one
to get many votes at once.
The Jimmy Jib operator,
Yoon Hong Min voted for So Min.
Thank you.
- People think it will be funnier.
- You are cuter.
This is for Se Chan.
"Se Chan should be made to work."
"Good luck as the youngest."
Kang Seo Rim wrote that.
- Seo Rim.
- Thanks.
It's bad for you.
Oh, it's bad for you. Hey!
You know Min Hee,
the youngest scriptwriter.
- Yes.
- She voted for you.
This isn't a popularity vote,
Min Hee.
Seung Gyul of the audio team
voted for Se Chan.
(Seung Gyul of the audio team,
Se Chan)
Thank you.
I said it's bad for you.
Oh, it's bad for me.
Watch your back.
Yang Se Chan.
- So Min.
- Come on.
Yang Se Chan.
- Here it comes.
- Oh, no. Please.
(The outcome is still unclear.)
Jeon So Min.
My name keeps coming up.
There are 40 votes.
Jeon So Min.
- My gosh.
- What?
- Jeon So Min.
- What? Is it buffering?
- It's like buffering.
Jeon So Min.
- Jeon So Min.
- All right.
Jeon So Min.
I'll collect the ballot papers...
- to check the names.
- Hey.
(The voters are afraid
of the tiger moth's revenge.)
Hey.
- Burn them.
- Tear them off.
Burn them out.
- Jeon So Min.
- Tear them off.
- Yoo Jae Suk voted for So Min.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
Yoo Jae Suk voted for So Min.
(Jae Suk's ballot is revealed.)
Jae Suk.
Yoo Jae Suk voted for So Min.
- That's a lot.
- Finally...
Finally?
We have three votes left.
We don't know it yet.
They might count as five per each.
It might count as five.
- Jeon So Min.
- The last one. Please.
This is the last one.
- This one will decide the result.
- Right.
Jeon So Min.
(Jeon So Min)
- Okay.
- Thank you.
So Min, don't lose your composure.
Burn them down.
Burn the votes.
Don't lose your composure.
- Keep your composure.
- All right then.
You're the last in the hierarchy.
- Let's say I'm older than you.
- We're not sure when it will end,
but So Min is the last
in the hierarchy.
- All right.
- I'm older than you.
Since Se Chan is the winner,
what matters is...
- how many Se Chan coins you have.
- He gave you a lot of coins.
Count your coins.
I didn't get anything today.
- I have 22.
- Haha has 22 coins.
(Haha has 22 Se Chan coins.)
- I have a lot of So Min coins.
- The yellow ones don't count.
I know. These are 30.
Gosh, how many coins do you have?
Do you have 30 coins?
- More than 30?
(Those who are likely
to be exempted from the penalty...)
("Shy Se Chan" Jae Suk moved
to Se Chan at the right time.)
(He got a lot
of Se Chan coins at once.)
(A loyal supporter, Jong Kook)
(He collected Se Chan coins
over time building up trust.)
(Suk Jin was lucky
to be cast at the last minute.)
(Who are the 2 members
with the most coins?)
I have 37.
My goodness. Jae Suk,
I thought you had 33.
- I have 37.
- Jae Suk has 37 coins.
What about you, Suk Jin?
- I think I have 33.
- You have 33?
I'll count them.
- Does Suk Jin have 33 coins?
- Yes.
- How could he have so many coins?
- Two, four...
That doesn't make sense.
Jae Suk is
currently in the first place.
Okay.
Darn it. It's not 33. I have 32.
How many coins do you have?
I have less than 30.
- Yes!
- How many do you have?
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin are currently
exempted from the penalty.)
- Jong Kook.
- Darn it.
How many do you have?
I have 33.
(I have 33 coins.)
- Really?
- All right.
So Jae Suk and Jong Kook
are the survivors.
(Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, and Haha
the candidates for the penalty.)
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Hey.
- I have one more coin.
You were about to go to So Min.
Come here, Se Chan.
You calculated the whole thing, right?
- No, I didn't.
- You ungrateful punk.
Now, So Min, among these three,
you should pick one member
to get a penalty with you.
- Let me tell you about the penalty.
- What is it?
Today's penalty will be a big help
to our production crew.
- What is it?
- What?
I bet it's about cleaning.
- I think so.
- Something bothersome.
Today's penalty is...
- When this episode is aired...
- What is it?
I mean, the week before that,
the preview will be aired.
You will shoot a few scenes
that will be used...
in the preview.
(Shooting a few scenes
for the preview)
- For example,
- Like a thumbnail?
a scene where you run hurriedly.
- Where we're chased.
- Or you could look startled.
- But...
- That's the worst.
- That's a good idea.
- I like that.
- It's not so bad.
- We will use them for a preview.
All right.
You need to pick a member
to act with.
I'll get ready to go home.
He's taking off
the microphone already.
Suk Jin, who did you vote for?
Be honest. Who did you vote for?
(He lies that he voted for Se Chan.)
I don't think so.
I think you voted for me.
Right. I had three ballots.
Seriously, we supported you, So Min.
Haha and me.
Let's just decide
by rock-paper-scissors.
Our youngest member in 2022,
So Min, it's your call.
(So Min is officially the youngest
member now. Who will she pick?)
All right. Let's put on our masks.
Oh, right. My mask. Thanks.
Look at them. They're so annoying.
- We supported you, So Min.
- We supported you.
Our youngest member in 2022,
So Min, it's your call.
I supported you.
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo)
Song Ji Hyo is picked.
Okay. Congratulations.
(During the final voting)
(Ji Hyo got caught
that she voted for So Min.)
- Let's go.
- My gosh.
- I survived. Let's go.
- Let's go home.
See you.
We have two actresses here.
For the preview...
Ji Hyo voted for me.
She wrote my name.
Hey. They all voted for you.
Everyone except you voted for you.
I need to check the ballot papers.
I think we are going to run.
I'm not good at running.
What do we do?
All right. Cue.
(That's how we got
the good chase scenes.)
Move over!
(She runs away in a hurry.)
I'll leave. My goodness.
No. My goodness.
(She pretends to pass out.)
I think that was really lame.
(She even shows some sprint
which rarely happens.)
Why are they trying to kill me?
Who's trying to kill me?
(She pretends that
someone is coming to kill her.)
Don't kill me!
Jeon So Min? I can't believe this.
Hey!
This is embarrassing.
(This is embarrassing.)
(She completes her mission
and wins a lot of R coins.)
(Upclose)
I'm so happy.
(She rips off a name tag
at a crucial moment.)
Hey, you...
(It's strange that she's
surprised by what she did.)
Cut. Okay.
- Hey, what was that?
- That was nice.
- Why are you surprised?
- I don't know.
- I was just acting.
- I mean,
you ripped it off
knowing that it was my name.
You knew it was me.
I just had to do something.
I thought I had to do something.