(June, 2022)
(SBS Variety Center moved
to Sangam-dong.)
(The new home of SBS variety shows
including Running Man)
(Nice lounges for friendly talks)
(Editing rooms with
the cutting-edge equipment)
(This is where SBS variety shows
will improve further.)
(On the 15th floor,)
(at the end of the long hallway,)
(there's the new office
of Running Man.)
(And two days before the shoot...)
(The producer is calling someone.)
- Hey, Bo Pil.
- Hello, Mr. Ji Suk Jin.
- What?
- Mr. Ji Suk Jin.
- Why are you being like this?
- This is Running Man.
- Are you filming now?
- Yes.
(Laughing)
Then I should change my voice
for the TV show.
Bo Pil, I'm done.
Hello, Mr. Yoo Jae Suk.
- What?
- This is Running Man.
What is going on?
The standby
of our shoot on Monday...
will be between 8 a.m. and 11 a.m.
Between 8 a.m. and 11 a.m.?
You can come anytime
within the time.
From 8 a.m. to 11 a.m.? There's
a big difference between the two.
Is it my choice?
Yes. It's up to you.
You can come anytime you want.
This is like the Game of Wits.
Anytime within the three hours?
- Yes. You can come anytime.
- Which is better?
Going early or late?
Can you give me a tip?
Is it better to go fast or late?
Gosh, which is better?
Please tell me.
Why are you giving me
such a hard time?
Do you want me to think
of Running Man all day?
If it's between 8 a.m. and 11 a.m.,
that means 8 a.m..
No. You can come anytime you want.
That doesn't make sense.
You say it's from 8 a.m. to 11 a.m..
My goodness.
- Between 8 a.m. and 11 a.m.?
- Yes.
- And I can go anytime I want?
- I see.
- You can do as you like.
It's your choice.
You don't have to worry about me.
(He just accepts the situation
as it is.)
And our office moved to Sangam-dong.
Jae Suk, you love Running Man.
- What?
- I know you love it.
(What?)
Well... Yes. I guess.
With your love for our show,
I'd like you to bring a small gift
for our new office.
(Laughing)
- You can bring one gift each.
- Okay.
It'd be nice
if it doesn't exceed 100 dollars.
The price...
Can't I just offer my heart?
I'd like you to express your heart
with something physical.
Of course.
Then I'll see you on Monday.
Hang on.
What time does the shoot begin?
Did you talk to the other members?
I really want to talk
to someone on the phone.
My phone...
Our writer, Hyo Im
will give you a call.
What time should I get there?
I have a call coming in.
I have to go now.
Who is it? Wait. Tell me who it is.
I'm serious.
(The first morning in Sangam-dong
finally draws on.)
(The members can come anytime
they want between 8 a.m. and 11 a.m.)
Hello.
(Hello.)
(Se Chan arrives at the lobby
at around 8 a.m.)
Does it begin right away?
Se Chan, you arrived here at 8:01 a.m.
- I'll put the microphone on you.
- Okay.
- Am I going up?
- Yes. Tag the card and go up.
It's Running Man's office
on the 15th floor.
On the 15th floor? Okay.
I want to try tagging the card.
(I want to try tagging the card.)
I'm the first one to arrive.
(He's on the 15th floor
where the office is.)
Is this it?
My gosh. That's me.
(He finds the photo of him
as soon as he enters.)
Hello. Where is it? Here?
This place is really nice.
My gosh. Why is it so good?
(The country boy is impressed
by the modern facilities.)
(Surprised)
(Amazed)
(Fascinated)
(My goodness...)
Look at this. It looks amazing.
(The country boy is on a field trip
to the broadcast station.)
Is this it?
(Is this it?)
Hello. Is this it?
Gosh, this is really nice.
This place is great.
Why is it so nice?
Is this really Running Man's office?
Gosh, it has a great view.
The view relieves all my stress.
(It looks over
the panoramic view of Seoul.)
This place is so pleasant.
It's really nice.
This is why you can come up
with such fun ideas.
Seriously, you can come up
with fun ideas in a place like this.
You can't do that in a small room.
I know it because I have meetings.
You just can't. You need
a pleasant place like this.
Is it a good thing
that I arrived early?
I'll explain later.
I bet it's a good thing.
That's nice.
There was no traffic jam
on my way here.
There was no traffic jam.
The size of my gift...
I guess they will explain later.
I tried to get you something useful
that others won't bring.
It's a gift with good taste.
You can cook frozen food in this.
Like frozen dumplings.
It's not sponsorships.
I bought it myself.
We gave you the same model
as a prize before.
No. That's not true.
- I'm serious.
- No, Bo Pil.
We gave you the same thing.
No. I think I gave it
to someone else.
Seriously, I bought this myself.
I can show you the receipt.
I don't want you to doubt me.
(While the firstcomer is busy
giving an explanation...)
(The second one shows up at 8:07 a.m.)
What? Hello.
(Jae Suk arrives at 8:07 a.m.)
So this is the new office.
(He's the kind of person who
arrives early at a time like this.)
- My gosh.
- Hey.
Jae Suk.
My goodness.
- You're here.
- Hey. What?
- Did you bring an electric cooker?
- No.
It's an air fryer.
- What?
- An air fryer.
An air purifier?
I brought an air purifier.
Hang on. This costs
more than 100 dollars.
Of course it does.
No, you can't...
Then I would've brought
something more expensive.
Hey.
I was told it should
cost less than 100 dollars.
So I bought something
that costs 80 dollars.
This is a big conference room.
A model that costs 100 dollars
would be too small for this.
But that's the rule.
- It can't be helped.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
What? You're welcome.
What's going on? I was just...
This is Samsung.
- This is a good one.
- It's Samsung.
You two must be curious
about the gathering time.
- Sure.
- There must be something.
- We came early, right?
- Yes. We should get a benefit.
So I will tell you...
what we are doing today.
Good. You should tell us.
- You two came really early today.
- Yes.
Today, the time you come to work...
will decide the time
you get off work.
It's called
I’ll Get Off Work First Race.
What's that?
Just like an ordinary office worker,
you will get off work
after working for eight hours.
- Eight hours?
- Yes.
Seriously?
- But...
- Yes?
(But...)
It's not like first come,
first served.
Why not?
It's only fair that the first one
to come leaves first.
Se Chan who came here first...
- arrived at 8:01 a.m.
- Right.
- After 8 hours, it will be 4:01 p.m.
At 4:01 p.m.,
one of you will get off work.
And at the average time
of the five members,
five of you will get off work.
Lastly, eight hours after the time
the last one shows up,
one of you will get off work.
(If the last one shows up at 11 a.m.,
one of them will leave at 7 p.m.)
(That means, the time they
get off work is decided randomly.)
That's not fair.
The law says we should work
eight hours a day.
Thanks to you two, the first
and average times are moved up.
It will be the worst
if I become the last one to leave.
- If I leave after four...
- You were the first one to arrive,
but you might be
the last one to leave.
If the last one to arrive...
leaves at four,
that person is really lucky.
- That's right.
- Yes.
What about this gift?
We will open the gifts together
and use them well.
Is it just a gift?
My goodness.
I thought...
we would at least use the boxes...
to play a game or something.
So we don't have
any privileges here today.
No.
- What's this?
- What nonsense is this?
Why are we doing this?
I didn't tell you to come early.
- What's with him?
- Your voice sounds...
Why do you sound so upset?
This is ridiculous.
It's better to come early anyway.
If we come late,
the average increases.
You're right.
My goodness.
I can't believe this.
- Hey, Jae Suk.
- Suk Jin.
- Se Chan and I are here already.
- Where?
- At the broadcasting station.
- Okay.
- You have to come right away.
- You're the only one who's late.
- Where are you?
Don't lie to me.
Those who come early get a benefit.
If you come late,
you will get off work late.
- You're in trouble.
- Don't you dare lie to me.
- It's true.
- We're serious.
I was told to come by 11 a.m.
Just hurry and come.
- They just said that.
Hey, I can't fly over there.
What am I supposed to do?
You should take today off then.
- You don't sound well.
- I didn't...
tell you to come flying.
Why would you say such a thing?
Hey, it's not like
I broke my promise.
- I just didn't go early...
- Why are you yelling?
- Early in the morning...
- Why are you yelling at us?
- If you come early...
- You're ridiculous.
Why are you yelling?
Do you really think
I'll believe what you say? Hey.
(He hung up.)
Let's call...
(He just hangs up on Suk Jin
with no hesitance.)
Call someone else.
Why is he...
Why do you keep calling me?
- Jae Suk.
- What?
I was talking, but why...
(I was talking, but why...)
Gosh, Suk Jin.
I'm in a hurry now.
You take your time.
I should call Haha now.
This is really nice.
It's pretty.
It's so pretty.
Running Man.
Don't walk, but run. Running Man!
What? A plant...
- So Bal.
- What?
Gosh, a plant?
Congratulations.
Congrats on your new office.
But this is...
- They don't seem to like it though.
- Why not?
It will wither away.
They should grow it well.
You can look at it
when you have a meeting.
So Min, you just gave
the youngest staff...
- another work.
- They should water it.
- No.
- That's a lot of work.
"This is the source
of inexhaustible ideas."
"From Jeon So Min
who loves Running Man."
(She even prepared a card.)
- Did you prepare the card?
- Of course.
It blocks the camera.
Put it down here.
- Why?
- Just put it down.
- It does block the camera.
- We can't do this.
- It's blocking Jae Suk's face.
- Why?
So Min, put it down.
But it's pretty.
Hey, how much did it cost?
This is expensive.
- It has a few flowers.
- All right then.
- Should we eat some hangover soup?
- I'd love that.
- Do you want to eat here?
- Yes.
We have nothing else to do here.
It will be funny if we are
eating some hangover soup...
- when Suk Jin comes in.
- Let's eat seolleongtang.
We should order only three servings
and eat them.
Then Suk Jin would
want to eat it too.
(They will order only a few servings
to tease Suk Jin.)
- We want some hangover soup.
- He's the youngest one here.
Yes. Order only three servings.
- I want seolleongtang.
- Or seolleongtang.
There's a seolleongtang place
near here.
- Make it 4.
- Order 4 servings.
Order four servings
of Naju bone soup.
Okay. Thank you. Bye.
We should order only four.
And when Suk Jin shows up,
I'll say, "See? I told you
to come early."
(See? I told you to come early.)
All right?
- You have plans.
- Of course I do.
You've been planning
the whole thing.
- Of course I have.
- You are unbelievable.
That's your plan.
(All he thinks of is
how to tease others.)
Those who come late can't eat it.
I just can't wait. I hope
Suk Jin will come soon.
And the Naju bone soup.
- This place is really nice.
- That's a great plan.
(Ji Hyo shows up at 8:50 a.m.)
This is really nice.
- I can see Mount Nam.
- She's here.
- There's Mount Nam.
- Ji Hyo, come on in.
- What did you buy?
Did you buy alcohol?
No, I just...
What's with her?
Ji Hyo.
- Is that alcohol?
- It's a gift for the new office.
The thing is...
- What is this?
- While they work...
I bought it in different sizes.
- This is really good.
- Did you buy beer? Seriously?
They can drink it when they are
stressed out while working.
- I bought it myself.
- Did you buy it with your money?
The first four to come
will get to eat Naju bone soup.
- What about the rest?
- That's a great plan.
- Hang on.
- They have it here.
This is Ga Eun's seat.
This is so clean and nice.
Ga Eun has a lot of pencils in here.
- This is amazing. Look at this.
- So Min.
They have a lot of R money in here.
- Let's take some.
- We should take it.
(They found R money in the cabinet.)
- Hey.
- They have a lot of R money here.
- You should keep them.
- Keep these?
- Ten money each for early people.
- That's amazing.
(Master of mischief's second plan)
Your plan...
- Come here.
- I want this.
- This is really nice.
- With those R money...
This is fun.
- Here.
- Should we keep ten money?
They wouldn't believe it
if we had too many.
When should we take these out?
Suddenly...
You should pay
for the Naju bone soup with this.
After we order it?
(R money has become
the official currency.)
When Jong Kook sees this,
he will be like,
"It's all right. I don't care."
"I don't mind becoming the last."
- He's no fun.
- Congratulations.
- You startled me.
- What's this?
Congratulations.
- You startled me.
- What's this?
(Haha shows up at 9:11 a.m.)
- Hey.
- Why are you so late?
- I'm not late.
- We already have flowers.
- Haha.
- Yes?
This isn't a graduation ceremony.
What is all this?
Are you at a graduation ceremony?
- Hey.
- Why did you bring flowers?
Is Dream going to school?
- This looks nice.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
- Haha.
- You should put it here.
This is for Bo Pil.
I prepared this for you.
- Why are you flattering him?
- If you look closely,
you'll find something precious.
- Hey.
- Okay.
Hey.
Please have a seat.
- Sit.
- My goodness.
This place is really nice.
- It's nice, isn't it?
- Did you see the view?
- This is amazing.
- It has a great view.
We have something to celebrate.
(Do they have good news?)
So Min and Ji Hyo
shot a commercial together.
(Ji Hyo and So Min did
an ointment commercial together.)
Hey, you...
(The wound witches)
(They found a new job
as the wound witches.)
Hey, they took your job.
(The former wound fairy)
A lot of people asked me
if I was okay with it.
So I said...
- So Min, you should do this.
- So...
- We are the wound witches.
- I was the wound fairy!
- You will get better.
- This is not fair.
- Were you the wound fairy?
Yes. Se Hyeong and I were fairies.
And they are witches.
- We are witches.
When I saw their commercial,
I was like, "That's mine."
(I was like, "That's mine.")
I did the same thing at home.
Jong Kook is calling me.
Hey, Jong Kook.
Why did you call me
so early in the morning?
- Where are you?
- I guess he's home.
Where do you think? I'm on my way.
- Hey.
- No!
You have to hurry and come.
Who would want
to go to work so early?
This isn't about whether
you want it or not.
It's first come, first served.
The last one to come
will get the penalty. Hurry.
- Really?
- Yes.
I kind of expected that, but...
- Well...
The penalty won't kill me, you know.
- I knew it.
- My gosh.
It's not funny at all.
- He's the worst.
- He said...
- exactly what you said he would.
- Right? I told you so.
He said it nicely
because he's in a good mood.
I'll go as soon as I can.
- I'm hanging up. Gosh.
- Okay.
Gosh.
- Seriously, he irritates me.
- I know, right?
He's just so annoying. Gosh, him.
All we can do is talk badly of him
behind his back.
You should've come a little earlier.
We ordered food.
What did you order?
- Beef bone soup.
- Naju bone soup.
You can order more for me now.
- Only four can have it.
- We can't.
- It's the benefit for the top four.
- Don't lie to me.
- It's true.
- I'm not lying.
It's true. There was a time limit
for ordering food.
- That's right.
- Stop annoying me.
- You should've come earlier.
- You chose to come late.
I came...
I mean, I followed the rule.
I'm sure
this is the rule that you made.
- Why would I make a fake rule?
- No.
- Haha.
- Our staff members are right here.
- Our food is here.
- It's here.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
- I'm excited.
- Okay.
- Good.
- I think you can have coffee.
- Haha.
- Haha, move over.
- You can have coffee.
- So that we can start eating.
- Move aside.
You were lying.
There's enough food for all of us.
- No, we have four servings.
- No, there isn't.
- Just move over there.
- Are you sure?
Yes.
For real?
- Yes.
- Yes, just as we told you.
- Give me four R money.
- Okay.
- Four R money.
(He's starting to get confused.)
- You should've come earlier.
- It's a lie, right?
I'll order food too.
You can only pay with R money.
- You gave me three R money.
- Just a second.
(They're acting like
they have to pay for the food.)
(Is this for real?)
Okay.
Here are 16 R money,
4 R money from each.
You can't order food
if you don't have R money.
(Confused)
- All right. Let's enjoy it.
- Let's eat.
It looks so good.
I opened them all.
- Did you?
- Yes.
- But I... Are you serious?
I brought my old bag.
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
I guess there were R money...
- in the new bag.
- Give it to me.
- The fact that he thought...
- Young Jin.
Check inside the new bag I received.
See if there's R money in there.
(We got him.)
I brought my old bag.
- Why didn't he trust us?
- No, the new one.
- I mean, why...
- I heard there was R money in it.
- We received R money in the office.
- They gave us the money here.
- We paid for the food with R money.
- Aren't there any R money in it?
(Aren't there any R money in it?)
There's only one mask in it?
(That's so sad.)
What's his problem?
Don't you have any R money
set aside?
Let's eat.
- Good.
- Let's eat. Is it good, Jae Suk?
- My, it's good.
- It's so good.
(It tastes even better
as they're fooling Haha.)
This is so good.
Haha, your phone is buzzing.
(Haha's stylist is
calling him back.)
Yes, Young Jin.
Haha, I just heard you shouldn't
use the old bag.
And there's no R money
in the new bag.
He's fussing around
because of R money.
Do you want the props
that you used before?
I see a few.
One of them says "fifty cents."
(I see a few.
One of them says "fifty cents.")
No, but put it somewhere safe.
- Okay.
- I'll text you.
- He and his staff are the same.
- Okay.
That's funny.
- Hey, when will Suk Jin come?
- Suk Jin?
- I hope he'll come shortly.
- I want him to come now.
I shouldn't finish my food
until he comes in.
- Exactly. When will he come?
- He's coming up now.
- Is he?
- Yes.
Then wait. I'm going to
put it in my mouth when he comes in.
(Then wait. I'm going to put it
in my mouth when he comes in.)
My gosh. He's just unbelievable.
- He even had it calculated too.
- The moment he walks in...
- He knows Suk Jin too well.
- I'll put it in my mouth.
- And he...
- Of course.
(Right then)
Please come here
and put on a mic first.
- A mic?
- Yes.
Suk Jin, you came in at 10:02 a.m.
Yes.
They're going to make a fuss
over me coming later than they did.
(Jae Suk is on standby
with a big spoonful of food.)
Where is it?
(Meanwhile, Seok Sam arrived
on the 15th floor.)
Which way? That way?
I've never come up
on the 15th floor before.
Right. And you put it all
in your mouth.
Yes.
Then he'll probably be surprised.
- You went passed it.
- Sorry?
- Did I?
Where on earth is it?
- My gosh.
- What about the show?
- It got cold already.
- Just eat it, Jae Suk.
- Just eat it.
- No.
I'll wait until Suk Jin comes.
Here? Oh, this is it.
(Finally, he found the office
after a long detour.)
My gosh. I walked passed it.
What's going on?
Hey.
(What's going on?)
(Jae Suk's wish finally came true.)
What are you guys doing?
Gosh, seriously.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes? Why?
- Why?
- Did you have breakfast?
- What are you doing?
- I had some bread on my way here.
Hey, why don't you say hi?
You're gobbling down the food...
- with your head down.
- What's wrong with that?
What did you say?
Gosh, seriously.
- It's so good.
- What is so good?
Only the first four people
can have it.
But... What?
- Why...
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- Hurry up and find R money.
- You need R money.
- I'm not lying.
- Suk Jin, he's not lying. Look.
- I'll show you.
- Look.
- That's a lie.
- You should find R money.
- Stop lying.
- I'm telling you the truth.
As if.
There's no way I didn't fall for it.
- What was that?
- What? That means you fell for it.
(There's no way
I didn't fall for it.)
- That means you fell for it.
- "There's no way you didn't?"
- You fell for it.
- That means you fell for it.
"There's no way
I didn't fall for it."
(His way of speaking transcends
time and space.)
- That was so funny.
- My gosh.
He must've come from the future.
"There's no way
I didn't fall for it."
The man from the future,
Ji Seok Sam.
Suk Jin is a time traveler.
(Seok Sam's time flows backward.)
- By the way, this is so tasty.
- Indeed.
- Does it taste that good?
- It's so refreshing.
It must be a famous restaurant
in Sangam-dong.
- Did you have breakfast?
- I'm having it right now.
What's wrong with him?
He asked me if I had breakfast
while watching me eat.
Did he come from the future or what?
Why did he ask me
if I had breakfast?
- What kind of question is that?
- I apologize for that question.
I just said it without thinking.
- There's no way he didn't.
- "There's no way I didn't say so."
(There's no way I didn't say sorry.)
Hey, why hasn't Jong Kook come yet?
(While the time traveler is trying
to pull himself together...)
(The lobby is empty.)
(The elevator stops.)
(Jong Kook came in at 10:43 a.m.)
- Hello.
My gosh.
- You're here.
- Why...
- Why didn't you come earlier?
- Why did you all come so early?
- You're empty-handed.
- Didn't you bring any gifts?
I did.
I brought a cafe gift certificate.
- You can put it here, Jong Kook.
- Where?
- Oh, I see.
- A gift certificate?
- He bought a gift certificate.
- That's nice.
Before we begin,
could you tell us...
- about your gifts?
- Okay.
- Sure.
- All right.
This is... Isn't it pretty?
I bought this
because it looked so nice.
- It's pretty.
- I like the color.
- You can open it like this.
- Suk Jin, it's so pretty.
- Isn't it pretty?
- It looks sophisticated.
- Yes, it's nice.
- A trash bin? That's a nice gift.
It's really nice.
- This morning...
- What is that?
It's an air purifier.
An air purifier?
- Isn't it expensive?
- To make sure to bring this,
I put this box in front of my room.
And Ji Ho got up early this morning.
- He opened it, right?
- I saw him opening the box.
I usually don't yell at him,
but I was so surprised.
"Hey!"
Ji Ho got startled.
(Ji Ho was taken aback.)
- You put it there.
- "Don't open that box."
"I'm going to take the box with me
when I leave home."
- He asked why I yelled at him.
- He must've been scared.
I said, "It wasn't like that."
(He shared a cute incident
that happened this morning.)
- I'm sorry, Ji Ho. Sorry, my son.
- Ji Ho...
- Ji Ho must've been startled.
- Yes, he was.
- He must've been startled.
My, the air is so fresh now.
- Congratulations.
- I'll explain about the rules now.
- Okay.
Do you know what the term
"flexible working hours" means?
- Yes, I know.
- Pardon?
- No. Is it normal these days?
- "Flexible working hours."
- I don't know what it is.
- So...
- You can decide when to work.
- It means you can come in anytime,
- Really?
- work your daily work hours,
- and get off work.
- That sounds so reasonable.
That's so great.
- Can they come in really late?
- Yes.
- If they work the full shift.
- That's so nice.
- Night owls come in and leave late.
- Exactly.
That's so nice.
We're going to adopt this system
for today's shoot.
- You chose the time to come.
- Yes.
And you will stay for eight hours...
starting at the time
of your arrival.
But it's not that person
who actually goes home.
- What?
- That is...
- Gosh.
- Come on.
- I don't like this.
- Se Chan arrived at 8 a.m...
- That's right.
- Then someone goes home at 4 p.m.
- One of us will leave at 4 p.m.
- One of us can go home.
One person will leave at 4 p.m.
Five people will leave
at the average arrival time...
of the 5 members
from the 2nd to the 6th to arrive.
Lastly, eight hours
after the last person's arrival...
- It'll be 7 p.m.
- Yes.
One person will leave at that hour.
And we'll choose
the people to leave randomly.
- Got it.
- Also,
there will be group missions...
where you can shorten
the total hours to stay.
We can shorten the total hours?
- Let's do that.
(They're full of enthusiasm.)
Of course, we'll shorten it.
- Let's pull it off!
- This is fun!
We're good at group missions.
- Indeed. We're good at it.
- If you succeed,
you all can leave four hours earlier
than you're scheduled, for example.
- That's great.
- Hold on.
Since we were all getting excited,
I was going to let it go.
But Suk Jin said, "This is fun."
- I'm motivated, and it sounds fun.
- We haven't even started yet.
- What's fun about this?
- It sounds fun.
- Bo Pil hasn't told us about it.
- This is fun.
You see, he already saw
what happens in the future.
- He's a time traveler.
- Is he a time traveler?
- There's no way it's not funny.
- Will this episode be funny?
- Very much so.
- Are you sure?
- It's insane.
- Will it be okay?
- It's insane?
- Will you be very funny?
- Well, I won't be good enough.
- But Ji Hyo will stand out today.
- Ji Hyo will?
- Really?
- Yes.
He saw the future.
- Ji Hyo.
- That's unexpected.
What did you do yesterday?
- What did you do yesterday?
- I stayed at home.
You're really getting
your money's worth with your home.
- You see, I...
- She makes the most out of it.
- I think she needs a larger place.
Now, we'll bring in the board
with the getting off time on it...
and a clock.
The member to get off early can
leave at 4:01 p.m.
The members to get off on time can
leave at 5:04 p.m.
The member to get off late can
leave later than 6 p.m.
- That's the worst.
- That's too much.
- Hey, the group missions...
- I really don't want to work late.
- The last one leaves at 6:43 p.m.
- I hope I won't work late.
- The traffic is bad at that hour.
- Leaving on time is the best.
- What are the group games?
- I'll explain to you now.
Okay.
- Why are they empty?
- What is this?
- It's the map of the 15th floor.
The first mission...
that requires the ability to observe
and good memory is...
The Map
of the Variety Show Department.
- Where are we in the map?
- So Min, we saw it earlier.
- Try to remember the places,
- Oh, we're here.
and fill in the map
of the variety show department.
(The variety show headquarters
on the 15th floor of the building)
(Conference Room)
(The layout of the floor is
complex.)
(Program Office, "Master in the House")
(And more than 30 offices gathered
on the 15th floor.)
(Director's Office)
(Conference Room)
(On top of the complex layout,
many offices gathered on the floor.)
(Management Team)
(Every member looked around
when they entered.)
There it is. The room
for brushing teeth. My goodness.
Oh, my.
There's a room for brushing teeth.
(They looked around the floor
during the break as well.)
(And they even saw the map
at the entrance too.)
- Try to remember the places...
- Oh, we're here.
(How much could they remember?)
We'll let one of you go out...
to take a quick look around.
You'll have two chances.
If you fill in every blank
on the map correctly,
you'll cut your finishing hours
by 90 minutes.
For each wrong or blank answer,
you'll lose 10 minutes
from the total 90-minute reduction.
- We must fill in all the blanks.
- That is,
if you get 1 answer wrong,
you get an 80-minute reduction.
If you get 2 answers wrong,
you get a 70-minute reduction.
You will play pop-up pirate
to earn the time...
for the representative to go out
and look around.
I know four of them.
- I know a few too.
- I remember it clearly.
There's a restroom next to this.
- The teeth brushing room.
- Fill in as many as you can.
This one is
the chief director's office.
- Write it down.
- We must be precise.
- This is the restroom.
- Haha is right about this one.
There's a teeth brushing room too.
- And...
- Give me that.
- This is...
- Is this "Sleepover Club?"
I don't know. I saw it from afar...
- I saw "new variety show."
- Let me have a look.
- A match-making show.
- This is a phone booth.
- That one is a conference room.
- No, the phone booth was here.
- This one is the phone booth.
- This is... Hold on.
- A conference room and "CP 5."
- Right? Yes.
- This one is a conference room.
- I think that's right.
I didn't see the other side
when I arrived.
- Me neither.
- "Inkigayo" and...
- That one...
- No, it was here.
- It was here.
- Was it?
I think we need to send someone out.
- Hey.
- I think we should do that.
Here. You will play pop-up pirate.
For each sword you stick in
without making the pirate pop up,
- you will earn ten seconds.
- I see.
- If you stick in seven... Yes.
- Without making it pop up.
If you stick in 7 swords,
you get 70 seconds.
If you stick in 8 swords,
you get 80 seconds.
The more swords you stick in,
the longer you can look around.
- We get ten seconds for each.
- Okay. Let's do this.
Let's do this.
(The game begins.)
- Please don't pop up.
- Okay.
You earned ten seconds.
- Twenty seconds.
- Okay.
- Thirty seconds.
We need at least 3 or 4 minutes.
That's good.
- It won't pop up.
- Ten seconds is too short.
Go ahead.
- Okay.
- Good job.
- How much time do we have now?
- We have 50 seconds.
It's okay. That's long enough.
- Don't worry. We have enough time.
- No.
- We have enough time.
- Yes, we do.
- Nice!
- Sixty seconds.
- Sixty seconds is quite long.
- Let's try one more time.
Right. One minute is...
- Okay.
- One minute is...
(They obtained 70 seconds!)
Seventy seconds.
On which side do we have
more blanks? The right side?
Turn left when you go out.
- Okay!
- And go straight.
- Are we still in?
- To your left.
- Hey, this is...
- I think that's the bad one.
- What?
- Right.
- How much time do we have?
- Eighty seconds.
- Eighty seconds?
- It's okay.
Now, I'm going to choose
the member to go out...
- Your names are written on them.
- What?
- You'll pick one randomly?
- Your names are...
(The representative will be
chosen randomly.)
- You'll pick one randomly?
- That's not fair.
- Anyone but Suk Jin.
- I hope it's not me.
- This isn't fair.
(Anxious)
The first member to go out is
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk has been chosen
as the representative.)
- It's okay. Don't worry.
- You can do this.
- It won't be hard.
- I'm not observant.
- It's okay.
- He's...
- really not observant.
- What's this? Is there a room here?
- Show me.
- Oh, you have to go around.
- I'm not observant at all.
- The chief director's office...
The teeth brushing room is
next to the empty office.
- And here...
- Check the teeth brushing room.
- Next to the teeth brushing room...
- You should check these.
- Check this one.
- Check just this side...
The three offices
next to the teeth brushing room.
We'll start timing
once you walk out the door.
- Got it.
- Three offices, Jae Suk.
- I should go this way, right?
- Three offices.
- Yes.
- Yes, that way.
- Good.
- Ready. Get set. Go.
(The countdown begins.)
You don't have to run.
"Guardians of the Ecosystem."
"New Match-making Show."
A conference room.
The teeth brushing room.
"My Little Old Boy."
"CP 3."
"DNA Singers."
"Golf Battle: Birdie Buddies."
"Invitation from Bachelor-agains."
Time's up.
"Guardians of the Ecosystem",
the new program.
- What?
- The new program.
- No, it's on this side.
- No.
- That side.
- Right?
- "Guardians of the Ecosystem."
The new match-making show.
- Where?
- Here?
No, it's right next to this one.
- "Guardians of the Ecosystem?"
- Then...
"Guardians of the Ecosystem" is
here, and this is the new show.
- This one is...
- This one is Running Man.
- Yes, that's right.
- Really?
- That's right.
- Are you sure?
- Running Man.
- "Guardians of the Ecosystem."
- It's "Guardians of the Ecosystem."
- The new show is here.
"My Little Old Boy" is here.
- Oh, here?
- "My Little Old Boy" is here.
- I see.
- And...
this one is...
"DNA Singers."
- Okay.
- Next...
"Golf Battle: Birdie Buddies."
- "Golf Battle: Birdie Buddies."
And this one is "CP 3."
And this one is "CP 4."
- It must be "CP 5."
- That's... What was it?
- Come on.
- "Invitation from Bachelor-agains."
- And...
that one is a conference room.
These two are conference rooms.
- A conference room.
- You checked so many of them.
- You did a great job.
- We can go to the other side.
- Right?
- We filled in many blanks.
- It's a conference room.
Jae Suk, you have a good memory.
- We have blanks here too.
- Right.
- This time, we should turn right.
- To the right.
- We can't check all of them.
- It might work out.
- Right. You checked so many.
- Look at this.
This is how good I am.
- You did a great job.
- That's easy. You had 80 seconds.
You had 80 seconds.
- That's 1 minute and 20 seconds.
- We got lucky in terms of that too.
I focused on this side.
You should've memorized all of them.
Now, you have one last chance
to send a representative out.
Now, I'll choose the last member
to go out.
(They're about to pull it off,
and have one last chance to go out.)
Oh, man. I'm too nervous to do this.
- Hey.
- Don't be like that. You can do it.
Six swords would be enough.
- That's a lot.
- I'll just go for it.
- Just do it. Hurry up.
- Okay.
Be careful.
We should get enough time.
- We need more than 1 minute.
- I think 60 seconds would be okay.
- We need more than one minute.
- Just stick it in.
- I'm not sure.
- Just stick it in!
- We need at least one minute.
- Let's go. Five.
Hey.
- Six.
- Okay. Let's keep going.
It's over now.
(After getting 50 seconds...
They already earned 100 seconds.)
(They currently have 100 seconds.)
- Take your time.
- Okay.
You might have written
a wrong answer too.
Yes. We know that.
- Okay. We stuck in 11 swords.
- Yes, We know that.
(They earned 110 seconds.)
- We have 110 seconds.
- You can memorize everything.
- Hey.
- If you go around...
The next member to go out is
Suk Jin.
(The last representative is
Suk Jin.)
- That's great.
- Wait.
- Suk Jin.
- What's great about this?
- Should I go this way?
- He has a lot of time.
- It's not great.
- How many rooms should I check?
- You should check this one.
- Here.
- Three, four...
- Make sure to check them all.
- Suk Jin.
- Next to "Sleepover Club?"
- Yes.
Between "CP 5" and...
- Suk Jin. Listen.
- In front of the elevator...
We have just a few to check.
Don't panic.
- Hold on. It's just...
- That's not a lot.
- Why are you so nervous?
- Why are you nervous?
- I'm not. This is our last chance.
- Don't we...
- have 80 seconds?
- We have 110 seconds.
Do we have 110 seconds?
You can memorize all of them.
- Next to "Sleepover Club..."
- Check the other side too.
Go around to the elevator,
and check the two rooms there.
- Two rooms. Yes, that's good.
- Right.
- I'll get going.
- Suk Jin, good luck.
- Suk Jin, check other rooms too.
- Ready.
Make sure you're checking
the right rooms.
"CP 5" is next to "Inkigayo."
I'm glad we got enough time.
Ready. Go.
- Hurry up.
- Turn right, and...
The chief director's office... What?
Wait. This is weird.
This is for a new show.
It's weird. There should be
a hallway... The chief director...
A new show is next to
the chief director's office.
A new show... It's weird.
Where is the hallway?
Oh, this is it.
I should go this way.
This is a conference room.
What? Hang on a second.
This is so weird.
Wait. Why... "CP 5..."
(Frozen)
What's going on?
"CP 5."
(The members remembered this room
from the start.)
"Sleepover Club."
"Same Bed, Different Dreams 2:
You Are My Destiny."
On "SBS Inkigayo", you sing,
"You Are My Destiny."
(You are my destiny)
While singing,
you go to a sleepover.
"SBS Inkigayo."
(It's hard to understand
his bizarre memorization method.)
Where is the elevator? Let's go.
- Get off, and the rooms...
- Ten.
- Nine.
- It's a conference room.
- Eight.
- A conference room.
Seven. Six.
- Five.
- Four. Three.
- A conference room.
- Two.
- This is so confusing.
One, Time's up.
I spent 110 seconds already? No way.
- He'll do well.
- I'm worried that Suk Jin might...
fail to find this room.
I wish Jong Kook had been...
Jong Kook, I wish
you had been chosen this time.
- That was just perfect, right?
- When he arrived this morning,
Seok Soon went past this room.
- "Seok Soon?"
- She just called him "Seok Soon."
- Shouldn't we put a tracker on him?
- I mean, Suk Jin.
- It's so confusing.
- How did it go, Suk Jin?
I think that the map is wrong.
- Did we write the wrong answers?
- Two conference rooms on the right.
- Two conference rooms?
- Yes.
- That's great.
- What about the ones on the left?
- Next to "CP 2..."
- Next to this one.
We got that one right.
I'm sure of it.
- Suk Jin.
- What was here?
- You are my destiny...
- You saw "Master in the House", right?
- "You Are My Destiny?"
- It's here.
- We already wrote it.
- Right.
Having different dreams,
- "Sleepover Club."
- singing, "You are my destiny..."
on "SBS Inkigayo." Right?
- We already wrote "SBS Inkigayo."
- Exactly.
- You should've checked here.
- He has his own way of memorizing.
- Here. Next to "CP 5."
- I'm talking about Suk Jin.
The director's office...
The director...
- The director's office?
- The director's office.
- Wait. Was it here?
- Well...
- She must have a larger office.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- Gosh.
- Don't take a guess.
- You should've memorized it.
- Suk Jin, that's the one.
- Right.
- It's in the corner. It has a view.
- He says I'm right.
- I think that's right.
- What are you doing?
- Her office is a corner office.
- Right.
Did you see "Master in the House"
next to "CP 1?"
Did you not see "Master in the House?"
When I left this office...
- This map is not right.
- No. You're wrong.
- No, nothing's wrong with the map.
- Anyway,
- did you see "Master in the House..."
- Wait.
- next to "CP 1?"
- Are you serious?
- Can't you remember... Really?
- What about this one?
- My gosh.
- This one is a conference room.
You had a lot of time.
We should think...
that Suk Jin pulled it off
since he found his way back here.
We should be grateful.
No way.
Suk Jin, why didn't you...
- We should write "Master in the House."
- I remember that too.
We just have to figure out
these 2... No, I mean, 3.
- What's next to "CP 5..."
- You only remembered...
- two conference rooms.
- What are you doing?
I remembered
the director's office too.
- Gosh. What did he do out there?
- Try to remember the rest.
- Fill in the blanks...
- This one is "Master in the House."
- It's "Master in the House."
- All the large rooms are...
- conference rooms.
- Write it down.
- She's right.
- And...
- What are those two rooms?
- What are those?
- What is it?
- Between "CP 5" and "CP 2."
What is it, Suk Jin?
"CP 1."
- "CP 1" is here.
- I saw it before.
- Why didn't you...
- Then...
Okay. It must be "CP 6."
- There's no "CP 6."
- Suk Jin, come on.
Be precise.
- Give us one more chance. He...
- Let us try again.
- Give me ten more seconds.
- Suk Jin...
- That's not allowed.
- But he...
- Why did you pick Suk Jin?
- What is between these two?
I'll go with this.
I remembered everything.
- Show us the board.
- Okay.
A room for a new show
next to the director's office.
- I don't understand.
- I saw many rooms for a new show.
- I'm not sure.
- What's that? Is it a blank?
No, we filled in every blank.
Jae Suk filled in
a lot of the blanks.
- Right.
- Jae Suk did it all.
Suk Jin, seriously?
(Scoring)
- The right side is correct.
- The right side?
- Nice, Jae Suk.
- See?
- The right side.
- We filled in all the blanks.
- Okay.
- Nicely done.
- What about the left side?
- The left side.
- This is insane.
- How many did we get wrong?
How could he not have remembered
any one of them?
(This will determine
when they go home.)
- Exactly.
- It's impossible.
- You got four wrong.
- Four?
(4 incorrect answers.)
- That's quite a lot.
Two need to be swapped...
and one of the places
doesn't exist anywhere.
- The conference room.
- That must not exist.
- We're at 50 minutes.
- Seok Sam was no help at all!
You always have trouble
paying attention.
- What's wrong with you?
- That's not it.
The map seemed different
which had me flustered.
- Right.
- So what now?
You got four wrong,
which means you were only able
to shorten the time by 50 minutes.
It's now time for what
all workers await during the day.
You will have lunch
at the office cafeteria.
Shall we get going?
- All right!
- Okay.
We're off to the cafeteria.
It's on the top floor.
- I can smell the food.
- My gosh.
It's like walking into a hotel.
- No way.
- It's a buffet.
Check out the view.
The view is a work of art.
What a generous company.
- Nice!
- All right.
Se Chan, isn't it like a hotel?
- This place...
- Hi.
Can I buy meal tickets
and eat here when I want to?
- Here?
- Over here.
So Min, let's go in.
Ji Hyo, come on.
I love it here.
I thought we were having lunch.
(Anyone can tell
they're here to play a game.)
- So Min, look.
- Where's our food?
We came prepared for our meal,
but that wasn't the case.
We didn't invite you here on a tour.
We thought we'd be getting lunch.
- I thought we'd be having lunch.
- I'm in love.
- What a generous company.
- This is incredible.
You guys should work even harder.
My gosh. We've made it big,
haven't we?
Our lives are a success.
Why are we having lunch
so early today?
Oh, right. I arrived late today.
That's right. Jong Kook,
it's lunchtime.
I arrived late today.
I was wondering why
lunch was being served so early.
Se Chan has been here
for five hours already.
- I ate earlier, but I'm hungry.
- Really?
I had breakfast,
so I'm not that hungry.
Today,
you'll be having lunch
at the cafeteria.
- A course meal is on the menu.
- Gosh.
A full-course meal?
It'll take about five minutes
for the meal to be prepared.
If you suggest a game
that we find entertaining,
we will deduct time off your clocks.
- Really? Any ideas?
- The game...
If we find the game reasonable...
- It must be a group effort, right?
- Yes.
- Something we can succeed in.
- Right.
We'll deduct time off your clocks.
How about jegichagi?
No.
How about a drawing game?
- A drawing game?
- Yes, the drawing game!
What's the drawing game?
You know what it is.
We each add to the drawing...
and the last person has to guess
what it is.
Oh, that?
Jae Suk must've enjoyed
playing that game.
(The game they played in
episode 605 was edited out.)
(They each add to the drawing...)
(and it must be guessed
by the last person.)
(They scored zero points, but
they want to play the game again.)
Who wants to guess the answer?
- I'll do it.
- Okay.
Jong Kook's better
at drawing though.
It's not about the drawing
looking nice.
What's the category?
Will it be a movie?
- How about an idiom?
- A proverb.
- I agree.
You can't write down any letters...
- or how many syllables it is.
- Of course.
- We know better.
- We're good at these things.
- Exactly.
No one is better than us
at cooperative games.
We don't let idol singers
rip off our name tags.
- Of course.
- We come out on top.
We're absolute beasts.
Why do you always go back to that?
- K-pop idols...
- It's like a medal of honor.
It was Suk Jin and me,
- but they couldn't beat us.
- Exactly.
- Suk Jin's a beast.
- And you're too fast.
I never lose games
outside of Running Man.
- I always win the prize.
- Exactly.
- We win on other shows.
- I always win the prize.
We dominate, don't we?
(How good are they
at drawing though?)
Here we go.
You will get three seconds each.
And go.
(A sparrow will always be tempted
when passing by a mill.)
Three, two, one, next.
Give it to the next person.
- Three, two...
- Give me the pen.
- Seriously?
- Where's the pen?
- I wasn't given a pen.
- Three, two,
one. Next!
Three, two, one, next.
- There isn't enough time.
- Three...
- Jong Kook will now guess.
- Three seconds isn't enough.
- That was too fast.
- There wasn't enough time.
Show him.
Unbelievable.
We were off to
a good start, you know.
Three seconds isn't enough.
- Hold on.
- Guess it right,
and I'll call you a genius.
Guess it right,
Who drew first?
- You can't know that.
- No?
- This is insane.
- Isn't that allowed?
- Take a look.
- There wasn't enough time.
- Guess what this could be.
- Haha, that isn't allowed.
The proverb itself is quite tricky.
- This must be a bird.
- Right.
- Of course.
- That isn't allowed.
- Why not?
- Isn't that allowed?
He's allowed to talk on his own.
There are many types of birds.
Seriously!
A proverb that includes a bird.
Birds hear
what is said at night and...
- No way.
- Of course not.
It can't be that, right?
Someone would've drawn a moon.
This is Running Man, Jong Kook.
- There are many types of birds.
- That's right.
- It's one of them.
- Right.
This is exactly why
we don't do cooperative games.
- Why not?
- No one can stop you guys.
- Have the pheasant and its egg.
- What?
- How is this a pheasant?
This can't be a pheasant.
(He openly shares
his deduction process.)
How is this an egg?
- Is this a guessing game?
- No, wait.
- It's small.
- Look at it.
I'll give you 5 seconds. In 5, 4...
(He just begins the countdown.)
- Two...
- It's a sparrow.
That's it!
- A sparrow.
- What's the answer?
It's a sparrow. Five,
four, three...
- A sparrow will always...
- Yes!
Can a sparrow pass by a mill?
Yes!
- One.
- Can a sparrow pass by a mill?
Yes!
- That's correct.
- Why?
But he said the correct answer.
It means the same thing.
He didn't include "tempted."
- Just that?
- Let me guess the drawing.
- That should be a win.
- You draw it instead.
I'll guess the drawing instead.
I only say this
because it's Jae Suk.
You're not allowed
to deliberately stall.
- Don't worry.
- I won't.
We know better.
- Here we go.
- All right.
And go.
(Once on the liver
and once on the gall bladder)
Gosh.
(Once on the liver
and once on the gall bladder)
- Two, one.
- Wait.
- Three.
- That's not it.
- Two, one.
- Draw what's recognizable.
- Draw what's obvious.
- Next!
- Next.
- What on earth is that?
What on earth is that?
Seriously?
- Three, two, one.
- What's going on?
- Next.
- That's not it.
- Three, two...
- Who's the issue?
One, next.
Haha, you're out. Thee, two...
- Haha, you can't draw.
- Why not?
Three, two, one, done.
(No one listens to the director.)
Darn it. How can one salvage this?
- What on earth is this?
- Isn't it obvious?
- Show us.
- But...
- The top part is weird.
- Back and forth.
It indicates us, doesn't it?
- This is a flea, isn't it?
- What?
It's not a flea.
That's...
- Check the far left.
- You can't say that.
What's on the left?
- Se Chan.
- What's below that?
- What could this be?
- Look.
Hold on. This can't be
a potato, right?
- Of course not.
- Let me see.
- Of course it isn't.
- No way.
- How is that a potato?
- That isn't it.
- It's not a potato.
- Of course not.
This proverb describes
people like Se Chan.
- Right.
- That's right.
- All right. Five...
- But...
- When I drink...
- It's who he is.
- Jae Suk.
- When I drink a lot.
Five, four, three, two, one.
The liver.
- Three, two...
- That's it.
(He was able to figure out
that it's the liver.)
Why covet a flea's liver?
- What?
- That is incorrect!
(Why covet a flea's liver?)
- Who drew this?
- How is this a gall bladder?
How is this a gall bladder?
- It's a flea.
- Of course it's a flea.
- That wasn't me.
- This is a flea.
- I drew the liver.
- There should've been a person.
Se Chan, come on.
"Once on the liver
and once on the gall bladder."
and once on the gall bladder?"
So who drew the flea?
Who drew the flea?
That was So Min.
- This is a flea.
- How is this not a flea?
This can't be anything else
but a flea.
You should be the first one to draw.
- Swap seats.
- All right.
- We'll do one more round.
- Right.
- Here we go.
- Let's do this.
(Another's rice cake looks bigger.)
- Hey.
- Three.
- Two.
- I didn't see what it was.
- One.
- Next.
- I really didn't see it.
- Show me.
Two, one.
- I really didn't see it.
- Three, two, one.
- No, that's not it!
- Are you nearly done?
- What's wrong?
- No, that's not it!
- Are you nearly done?
- Next.
- No!
- Wait.
- Two, one.
- Draw it over here.
Three, two, one, next.
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
- What on earth is this?
- Gosh.
- Three, two...
- What on earth?
- One.
- Are you kidding me?
What on earth is this?
This was an easy one!
- How can one guess this?
- This was an easy one!
- This isn't doable.
- It was an easy one.
No, you can do this.
Why is there an inequality symbol?
- No clues are allowed.
- There's an inequality symbol.
- Don't.
- He'll know this.
- That was too obvious.
- You're almost there.
The belly button
is larger than the belly?
- That's not it.
- That is incorrect.
- He has more time.
- It wasn't an official answer.
It wasn't my official answer.
Give it another closer inspection.
- There are two people.
- Right.
That's right.
- Goodness.
- Give it another closer inspection.
There are two people.
This guy's looking at this guy.
He's looking at him.
- What?
- Suk Jin...
The grass is greener
on the other side.
(Laughing)
What's your answer?
It's not like we said anything.
(The unprecedented clue
makes Jae Suk dizzy.)
What?
But this...
You practically gave me the answer.
- What did he say?
"The grass is greener
on the other side."
(He just gave Jae Suk the answer.)
You can't just slip him the answer.
That is incorrect.
- Hold on.
- That's just wrong.
- Come on.
- Seriously?
- What was that?
- Ji Hyo, come on.
- This was Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo!
You should've drawn rice cakes
of two different sizes.
- Exactly.
- This isn't acceptable.
- Where's the inequality symbol?
- I was in a rush.
Which is why you should've
been thinking straight.
I was in a rush!
- Then...
- Let's try it once more.
You go first.
Ji Hyo, take his seat.
No, it's over.
- One more round.
- Let us try it once more.
It's time for the main event.
Just give us another chance.
- But we were having fun.
- What's the main event?
Let's make this into a show instead.
Fine, go on with the main event.
Giving out clues is just as fun.
It's funny how we give hints
to each other.
But we can't give hints
like Se Chan does, can we?
- "That's not it."
- I thought it was soft.
- Please play it fairly.
- We should.
All right. In this mission,
we'll provide a course meal.
There are six courses in total.
- Six?
- Each dish will be served.
But there are eight dishes in total.
And one of them is a random dish.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- One of them is difficult to eat.
- Oh, really?
But since there are eight dishes,
no one could get it.
- Right.
- We don't know who'll get it.
If you finish the whole dish,
we'll deduct 20 minutes per dish.
Oh, we can still try
and eat the random dish?
- Yes, you can.
- Even if we get it?
That's right.
- The chance is only one-eighth.
- Of course.
Only one-eighth?
It's only difficult to eat, right?
Not inedible?
Yes, you can eat it.
- We used edible ingredients.
- Of course.
We're better than idols
when it comes to eating.
- Yes, we are.
- Idols?
They're always on a diet.
Has he been harassed by them
or something?
We can eat anything
no matter how difficult it is.
We never lose to them.
- We can just eat it.
- Yes, we can. It'll be easy.
The first course
is fried tofu rice ball.
- This is...
- Gosh, it looks so good.
It's not much.
- We can just easily eat it.
- It's doable.
- It's fried.
- One of them is inedible?
- That's right.
- We can easily eat it.
- We can just hold back.
- Let's just hold back.
Why don't we just take them as is
without choosing?
Number two looks a bit off.
Number two?
One of them is...
Look at number five.
- Number five?
- There are grains on the bottom.
What about it?
Why is number three so big?
There are grains of rice
on the bottom for number five.
- Let's just eat them in this order.
- Sure.
- Mine is number 2.
- Then I'll get number 1.
- All right, then.
- Okay.
- You can take them.
- Here. Number one.
- Just give them to us in order.
- What about Ji Hyo?
- I'll take number 2.
- Number 2?
This is wasabi for sure.
Look at its color.
- Number five is off. Look.
- It is the random dish.
There are grains of rice
on the bottom.
- Number five is...
- Look. It's all yellow.
- You got that dish.
- Jae Suk.
- Se Chan, Haha's is yellow.
- Oh, really?
(Haha's rice ball
has become a target already.)
- He got it.
- You want number six?
- Anyone want to switch?
No, thanks. You have it.
- All right.
- I'll take number six.
- Oh, really?
You can start your meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Let's enjoy it.
Let's eat it
with a strong mentality.
(Taking a bite
with a strong mentality)
(He smells it as though
he'd eat it with his nose.)
(Then he plucks up his courage
and takes a bite.)
(They all seem to be enjoying it.)
It's good.
It's delicious!
- Mine is good.
- Mine is good too.
Let's eat it
with a strong mentality.
(Haha was a strong candidate
to get the random dish...)
(based on its color alone.)
It's good.
It's delicious!
- Mine is good.
- Mine is good too.
- What's wrong?
- Just hold it in.
- What's wrong, So Min?
- So Min.
She doesn't look too good.
- Mine is good.
- Mine is good too.
- What's wrong?
- Just hold it in.
- What's wrong, So Min?
- So Min.
- She doesn't look too good.
- Hold it in.
- What's wrong?
- You should finish it up.
- Isn't it good?
Think of happy things. What's wrong?
Is it spicy?
It's good.
So Min, what's wrong?
Why is your face red?
(So Min's face has turned red.)
So Min, you can do it.
One of the rice balls
has a white capsaicin sauce.
- So Min, be careful.
- A white capsaicin sauce?
I think she's eaten some of it.
- You can't eat it?
- Just eat it. It's good.
- So Min, you can do it.
- So Min, you should finish it.
You don't have to finish it
if it's not to your liking.
- Hey.
- Eat it.
- Push all the rice in.
- So Min.
You should eat it.
How will you survive...
in this world with such mentality?
- You're discouraging her.
- Isn't he the worst?
- He's so...
- Don't show it.
If you show, then you'll lose
to the production crew.
- Just eat it naturally.
- It's quite good.
- Of course.
- We're going to succeed.
- Okay!
- All right!
So Min, since you finished it,
you succeeded.
It's really spicy.
- We're quite good.
- You're amazing.
(Thanks to the encouragers,
she succeeded in eating it.)
Is it that spicy?
- Really?
- Oh, this is...
The second course is steamed egg.
- I love steamed egg.
- I want number six.
Steamed egg is my favorite.
Of course. As long as it's not bad,
it'll be good.
You can give them out
however you want.
- So Bal.
- She's giving them out so fast.
- I'm telling you.
- She's like a master.
I don't feel pain.
Does that mean you don't feel pain
when you're hit?
- Of course.
- Enjoy your steamed egg.
- Okay.
- What is it?
- It's steamed egg.
- I meant what's in it.
You'll find out once you eat it.
(Exclaiming)
- It's so good!
- Mine is normal.
- I meant what's in it.
- You'll find out once you eat it.
- It's so savory.
- It's like a pudding.
(They're all enjoying it.)
Gosh, it's good.
Should it be this hot?
(Halting)
(Shutting his eyes tight)
Suk Jin.
How will you survive
in this world with such mentality?
(How will you survive
in this world with such mentality?)
(The boomer spewed out a harsh
comment without knowing his fate.)
Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
- You're from the future.
Why couldn't you predict this?
Don't do that.
How will you survive...
- With such mentality...
- in this...
- In the fierce world?
- In such fierce industry?
How will you survive?
Only if you didn't say that earlier.
Gosh, it's so spicy!
I can't have it hot.
- That's how it is.
- Was it salty?
Don't drink water.
Don't let him drink water.
- The mentality!
- Suk Jin.
- You lose if you drink water.
- How will you live...
- with such mentality?
- You lose if you drink water.
Suk Jin, don't give up.
- Suk Jin.
- You're losing to the crew.
- The thing is...
- It's really hard to eat.
- No, seriously...
- Suk Jin.
- With such mentality...
- I just can't eat this!
With such mentality,
you can't survive...
- in this tough showbiz.
- Then why did you say that?
Why did you say that?
It's up to how you think.
Suk Jin, focus.
All right. He did it.
Suk Jin.
I... I'm giving up.
(With a shriek,)
(he quickly gives up.)
- No. You have to eat it.
- He's given up.
- Just eat it!
- Gosh, Suk Jin...
- Gosh, seriously.
- He's given up.
Was it too salty? Or spicy?
It'll put you in trouble
if you eat it.
- Because it's spicy?
- Why did you say that to So Min?
- Why couldn't you eat it?
- You try it.
- Then how did So Min...
- Go ahead.
- Was it too spicy?
- Just give it a try.
- Let me try it.
- You should try it.
My nose is runny.
You just can't eat it!
You see? He spitted it out.
- Gosh!
- Is it too salty?
- It's too salty.
- I swallowed some of it.
Try it. Try just some of it.
- I can eat it if I want.
- Seriously. Try it.
Try it. It smells good.
You should take a big bite.
- It's too salty.
- Gosh, it's salty.
- It's impossible to eat.
- Try it.
No, don't do that.
You should eat it.
- No, Suk Jin.
- Just try a bit.
- Come on.
- It's so salty.
Just give it a try.
(Forced to eat)
You should try and hold it in.
- You should try it a little.
- No, thank you.
- Just try a bit.
- No, I don't want to.
- Just try it.
- I tried it before.
- Suk Jin, don't force So Min!
- Stop it!
- Just try it.
- Don't force it on So Min!
- It's because...
- So Min's stomach is hurt.
Viewers, you shouldn't criticize me.
It's because some might criticize me
for not eating it...
when I scolded So Min.
- You should give it a try!
- He knows it too.
He knows that he'll be criticized.
What do you mean by
"Don't criticize me?"
Suk Jin! You are...
- Viewers!
- If you were to be criticized...
- I get it!
- If you don't want...
to be criticized, you should eat it.
He's been in this industry
for 30 years.
But he asked the viewers
not to criticize him.
I mean, it's impossible to eat this.
He's trying to rationalize
his actions.
- That's why he's feeding them.
- I know.
- I'll eat it if I get it.
- Stop it.
Stop it.
Did you see how he spitted it out?
- You can eat it if you try hard.
- My gosh.
This is cheating.
- If only he had a will.
- I know.
The third course
is spicy fried chicken.
- It looks spicy.
- It looks good.
- Is it all right?
- It's so good.
(They're all enjoying
the sweet and spicy fried chicken.)
Gosh. Did you know?
- We all got it.
- Did we all make it?
- Mine is okay.
- Your tongue must be numb.
- Is it me?
- One of us got it.
So Min.
Who got the random dish?
- Is it So Min?
- My tongue is numb,
so I can't taste anything.
(She lost her palate.)
- It was you?
- For real?
That's great.
You should eat them all.
- I can't taste anything.
- You should finish it.
All right. I finished it.
She's good. This is how good we are.
So you've succeeded
in finishing four courses.
In total, you deducted 80 minutes.
That's a lot.
- We'll be able to go home by 1 p.m.
- So now,
those who can go home early...
- Could it be 2 p.m.?
- can leave at 1:51 p.m.
(Getting off work early: 1:51 p.m.)
And the remaining five of you
can leave at 2:54 p.m.
(Getting off work on time: 2:54 p.m.)
Lastly, the last one to leave...
- will get off work at 4:33 p.m.
- It's unbelievable.
We can leave by 4:33 p.m., at least.
It'd be incredible if Jong Kook
can leave by 1:50 p.m.
- That'll be amazing.
- We came early in the morning.
You came at 11 a.m., and you can leave
after only 2 hours.
Then you should've told me
to come later too.
I'll do my best.
- Two hours?
- I'll seriously do my best.
Let's move on to the next mission.
- Let's go!
All right.
(Working overtime: 4:33 p.m.)
What is this?
- Gosh, what's this?
- What is this?
It's 1:13 p.m. right now.
One of us will be going home.
- Someone is leaving.
- One of us is getting off work.
The one getting off work early
will be leaving at 1:51 p.m.
Awesome.
- Please let it be me!
- All right.
- I want to go home too!
- They'll be leaving soon.
Let me watch "The Outlaws."
In this mission, the amount of work
will differ dramatically...
depending on your title.
It's called Today's Staff
is Tomorrow's CEO.
What could it be about?
There are five mini missions.
In each round, you'll pick
a name tag randomly.
The titles available will be
CEO, Deputy Manager, Manager,
Assistant Manager, Supervisor,
Staff, and Intern.
You'll be divided
into different titles.
You'll be carrying out according
to the title you pick.
The CEO will be doing
the easiest mission.
The staff and intern will have to...
- do a more difficult mission.
- All right.
- It must be hard.
- Intern must be the hardest.
Once you succeed in your mission,
- twenty minutes will be deducted.
- That's nice.
That means one of you can go home
right away...
if you succeed in the first mission.
- All right!
- One of us?
- Boombastic!
Boombastic!
Please pick your title
before the first mission.
- I'll be picking it last.
- Do we just pick it now?
- Yes, please pick it now.
- I want to pick CEO.
But if we get off work too early,
we won't get enough airtime.
- That's...
- Come on.
- You can't have it all.
Why are you so greedy
over your airtime?
- You can't have it all.
- Darn it.
- This is it.
- I picked Assistant Manager.
- It's not a good thing, right?
- I picked CEO.
Didn't they peek beforehand?
- Who picked CEO?
- I'm the intern.
- You're Supervisor.
- I picked Deputy Manager.
I picked Manager!
I'm second-highest after CEO.
(And...)
Assistant Manager
is right in the middle.
- He's the staff.
- Intern, please stand over here.
And the CEO will be standing
on this side.
Please stand on the squares.
I'm a staff on this show too.
Staff Ha.
- Are you the deputy manager?
- Yes, I am.
- You're the manager?
- That's right.
Deputy Manager is a higher position.
Oh, is it?
(Deputy Manager
is a higher position.)
- Come here!
- I didn't know.
- How dare you!
- I didn't know. I'm sorry.
- You're in a higher position?
- Of course.
How did the bicycle thief
become a manager?
Are you next to me?
You assistant manager. How dare you.
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- Hey, Intern Kook.
Hey, Intern Kook.
- Hey, Intern!
- Yes.
Are we doing a role play too?
- Of course!
- Of course we should.
Of course we should.
How dare these punks...
I'm so sorry, sir.
What a mess of a company.
- It's a mess. Do a proper job.
- Assistant Manager, get down.
- Yes, sir.
- Why didn't you discipline them?
Hey! Get in the square, you punk!
Wait. Companies aren't like this
these days.
There's no such company these days.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Can you behave like an intern?
- Intern Kim.
Why are you behaving like a thug?
Why are you acting like a thug?
How can you wear shorts
to the company?
I can leave the company anytime
if I don't like it here.
You can't do that.
- What is this?
- Seriously.
Interns are supposed to...
That's what interns do, right?
- Hey.
- He's like Generation MZ.
- If I don't like it...
Okay, we heard you.
Give us the jegi.
(Throwing)
He used to study
in the States, so...
That's American style.
Hey, JK. Calm down.
Okay.
- Here's the first mission.
- What is it?
The first mission...
is Walking in Place in Group.
- What?
- That'd be easy.
You'll be wearing a blindfold,
and you'll walk in place
in your square.
- What's so hard about it?
- You can check your place...
every 5 to 15 seconds.
So we must stay within the square.
You should stay in it.
The CEO can walk for 15 seconds,
20 seconds for Deputy Manager,
then 25, 30, 35,
and 40 seconds respectively.
Lastly, Intern Kook must walk
for 45 seconds.
- This is...
- It's quite simple.
- Once you're done with it,
- Of course we can all do it.
it'll be a success if you're
in the square.
- We can easily pull this off.
- What's so hard about it?
You can't do it?
Let's speak less and practice more!
(The intern from LA
gives an order to his bosses.)
- How can an intern...
give out an order?
Once I say start, you can begin.
I'll tell you where you are
every five seconds.
We must shake our arms too?
Yes, you should. Get ready.
- Intern Kook.
- Yes, sir.
Keep your mouth shut, okay?
- Get ready.
Just walk in your place.
Go!
- Left.
- You must lift your legs high.
- This isn't hard.
- What is this?
- It's not hard.
- It's not hard at all.
- We'll be in our places for sure.
That's for sure.
How is this hard?
(Everyone is walking confidently.)
(CEO Jeon takes off
her blindfold first.)
CEO, you can take off
your blindfold. You can stop.
I'm right in the same place.
- I'm dizzy.
- Deputy Manager, take it off.
I'm in the same place, right?
(Even Deputy Manager Yoo made it.)
- I could've walked out of it.
- I can hear you.
(It's Manager Yang's turn.)
Manager Yang, take it off.
I could've been in big trouble.
- Gosh.
- What do I do?
- What?
- Assistant Manager, take it off.
What do I do? Wait a minute.
- Hold on.
- I made it, didn't I?
Supervisor Song,
take off your blindfold.
I'm taking it off.
(Even Supervisor Song succeeded.)
(There are two more members
until their success.)
Staff Ha, take your blindfold off.
(They failed.)
Intern Kook,
take your blindfold off.
Those punks...
- You guys should get down.
- Those punks...
(The superiors are infuriated.)
Are you kidding me?
Staff Ha and Intern Kook failed.
- How could you not pull this off?
- Why did you fail?
You only had to walk in place.
Because you kept talking,
I got distracted.
- Who is he to scold Staff Ha?
- I mean...
Intern Kook.
Why did you do such a horrible job?
You were way out of the square.
It's not that. I'm not even joking.
Let me explain.
I walked, following his voice.
I also followed your voice.
Here's the second mission.
You'll kick jegi as many times
as you're given...
depending on your title.
You just need to kick at least
one more than your superior.
- Is that so? Okay.
- Okay.
Can I kick more than I have to?
Then the person after you
will have to kick more.
- Then it should start from one.
- So I can kick less.
- One, two, three, four...
- We should just kick one more.
So we should think of it this way.
It's better that those
who are more athletic...
- do it later.
- It gets worse.
You're a mere intern.
Can't an intern voice his opinion?
The higher-ups will make
the final decision.
We'll tell you the decision,
- so just stay still.
- Excuse me.
- So he means...
- Then why did you accept us?
Hey, you're still just a staff.
What's with this Metallica shirt?
He's such a boomer.
You can wear that for your
club activities on weekends.
What is this?
(What?)
- What is this?
- What about it?
Who curls their bangs like this?
- Wait a minute.
- What?
- There's such a company?
- Who curls...
their bangs like this?
What are you, a dean at school?
- I was just born this way.
- These punks...
I was born this way.
How dare you.
Let's start playing.
- Kick it just once.
- You need to kick it just once.
- This isn't hard.
- Just one.
Here we go.
Just kick it once.
Don't kick it twice.
- But Ji Hyo is the problem.
- I can't kick it.
Don't kick it twice.
- One. Hey!
- No, you can't do that.
I told you to kick it just once!
- I didn't know.
- Deputy Manager, kick three times.
- That CEO!
- CEO Jeon!
- That just increases the number.
The CEO is so dumb!
Why is she so dumb?
- I mean...
- Seriously!
- What was she thinking?
- How did she...
How did she become a CEO?
- Staff Ha.
- Yes. I'm sorry, ma'am.
How did you become a CEO?
She's the daughter of the founder.
- So she's from a rich family.
- Why did she kick it twice?
- She got in through connection?
- Now...
(Now...)
- It's 1:51 p.m.
- Let's go.
(One of them can get off work
as it's reached 1:51 p.m.)
- Who's going home?
- One of you...
can get off work now.
- Is that so?
- So who's going?
The highlight of office life
is ghost leg.
- Bring in the ghost leg.
- All right.
(Nerve-racking)
Are we really getting off work?
Do we really get to go home?
- We're really going home?
- We're playing ghost leg.
Can we just leave like that?
It's none other than ghost leg.
Seriously.
It's been over eight hours
for those who came early.
We came at 8 a.m.
- For how long have we been here?
- This is amazing.
But it'll be amazing
if Jong Kook gets to leave.
- I want to go home too.
- Jong Kook.
As you can see,
"getting off work" is written
behind "candidates."
Please write your names on top.
- Let's write our names!
- I want to go home.
- Then I'll pick number 2.
- Number 2?
- I pick number 4.
- Will you pick number 4?
Yes, I'll choose four,
which stands for "death."
- Jong Kook.
- Work hard to death to survive!
- So Min.
- I'll take whatever is left over.
That's so cool.
You can write my name wherever.
- I'll take number five.
- Ji Hyo.
Can we draw lines wherever we want?
- Yes, you can.
- Go ahead and draw them.
I'll draw them here.
Make sure to draw them clearly.
I won't join in since I'm unlucky.
Right. We should draw them clearly.
This is driving me crazy.
I think it's all about luck.
(It's still in the middle of the day
at around 2 p.m.)
- That's enough.
- Is this all right?
- Yes, it is.
- I think there should be one more.
There are lines
over here too, right?
- Yes.
- Let's start.
Please rip it off.
There are more lines on the bottom?
So they drew them in advance.
- They drew them in advance.
- Let's see.
You can start.
- Let's start with Haha.
(They're starting with Staff Ha.)
I want to get off work.
One of the three candidates
can get off work.
Let's start with Haha.
One, two...
- Let's go! Go that way!
- One, two...
(Let's go! Go that way!)
Go that way! Go straight!
That's great!
I'm going home!
Yes! Haha is eliminated.
(Disappointed for real)
- No.
- You lost your chance!
Haha is out.
- All right!
- You lost your chance!
- Next!
- Se Chan.
- Let's go with Se Chan.
- Let's go!
(Manager Yang has been working
for 6 hours...)
(after coming in first.)
- This is correct, right?
- No, you should go up.
- Go up and down.
- Then come down again.
- You should come down. Yes!
- Come this way.
That's it!
That's it. Push him to the corner.
Go!
(What's the fate of Manager Yang
who came to work first?)
- Go!
- You should go down!
(He's chosen
as one of the candidates.)
(Manager Yang
becomes one of the candidates.)
(Disappointed)
- I'm one of the candidates!
- How annoying!
You're one of the three candidates.
- Yes!
- So Min!
- Next is So Bal.
(Up next is CEO Jeon.)
Ji Hyo, I got lucky
thanks to the line you drew.
I don't think I can get off work.
(So Min is out.)
- Oh, no!
- Yes!
(She got eliminated right away.)
That's just like how So Min is.
So Min!
- You should stay a bit longer.
- It's my turn!
(Next is Intern Kim.)
- Jong Kook.
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
(Let's go, Jong Kook)
(Let's go home, Jong Kook)
Let's go home, Jong Kook
- No, stay.
- Let's go, Jong Kook
- Don't go
- Let's go home, Jong Kook
- No!
- No, Jong Kook!
(He's out.)
No.
- My goodness.
- It will be me.
Hey, three of us remain.
- Three of us.
- It will be me.
- One of the three...
One of the three will go here.
Suk Jin will end up here
No, I will end up there
Ji Hyo and I will take two spots
- One of the three
- No way
- One of us will get off work
One of us will get off work
That won't happen
- I will end up there
- That will happen
- Let's go.
- Like this
You will get eliminated
Like this
I will get included
(He suddenly begins.)
Up.
(Suk Jin was the second latest.
Will he get off work in 4 hours?)
Up.
My goodness.
(He is out.)
(Like this, he got eliminated.)
(Assistant Manager Ji
failed to get off work early.)
He got eliminated
- No way.
- He got eliminated
- How did that happen?
- Ji Hyo.
- I can't believe it.
The candidates have been decided.
- We are the candidates.
- We are the ones...
- who came early.
- Yes.
- We came early.
- You are right.
Ji Hyo, let's begin.
Okay.
- Next to her...
- Jae Suk is here.
- Me.
- Okay.
- Who will it be?
- This is incredible.
It will be 1 of the 3.
The current time is 1:51 p.m.
- I arrived at 8 a.m.
- You will get off work before 2 p.m.
- Let's go.
- It shouldn't be Jae Suk.
- Take off the strip.
- Here we go.
- Who will it be?
One,
two...
(Who will realize the dream
by getting off work during the day?)
Two...
- Ji Hyo is out.
- My goodness.
- All right.
- Ji Hyo is out.
- My goodness.
(Oh, no.)
Ji Hyo is out.
- Ji Hyo is out.
- Come on.
- It will be 1 of us.
- Team 8 a.m.
No.
(Whoever gets off work
won't deal with heavy traffic.)
(Who will get off work
during the day?)
No.
(Se Chan, Getting off work)
(Manager Yang won.)
All right.
(Jae Suk lost the chance
to get off work early.)
Bye, Se Chan.
- I will get going now.
- Bye.
Manager Yang will get off work.
- Get off work.
- For real?
This is nice.
- I will follow you soon.
- Okay, Jong Kook.
It's nice that you are leaving early
after coming early. Good work.
- I will get going now.
- Manager Yang.
Is he really getting off work now?
I came early.
- Se Chan came early.
- You know,
- you arrived first.
- I did.
- It's fitting.
- It's fair.
- Bye.
- I will get going now.
- Work hard.
- Bye.
Bye.
Let's go.
Okay.
(He runs off
to avoid getting called back.)
This is unbelievable.
Se Jin and I Re, let's go.
- All right.
- We will get going now.
Congratulations
on getting off work first.
La la la la la
(This is exciting.)
- Good work.
(Manager Yang
gets off work after 6 hours.)
I will get going now.
(Manager Yang arrived at 8:01 a.m.
and left at 1:51 p.m.)
The remaining members
will continue on with jegichagi.
- That really killed my enthusiasm.
- Same here.
That killed my mood.
She kicked it 2 times,
so kick it 3 times.
- All right.
- Why did you kick it two times?
You can kick it four times.
- She is the problem.
- I am the problem.
- Seriously.
- Look.
Had you kicked it once,
she would have only needed
to kick it four times.
- I have to kick it three times.
- I will move to another company.
- Hey, intern.
- Fire me.
You fire!
- "You fire?"
- Are you calling him fire?
Are you calling me fire?
Let's go.
- Three.
- You just need to kick it.
One, two...
Hey!
- Why did you kick it three times?
- I was supposed to do that.
You are right.
What was that?
- I am sorry.
- For goodness' sake.
(He got mad for no reason.)
- I am so annoyed.
- What was that?
I am sorry.
- I am sorry.
- I was supposed to do that.
- I need to kick it 4 times, right?
- Kick it 4 times. Hurry up.
- Can you kick it five times?
- No.
- Just do it.
- You can do it.
(Sudden slapstick comedy)
- What was that?
- He did that on purpose.
- You failed.
- I think he did that on purpose.
- It was so contrived.
- How will you edit this?
- That was...
- I swear...
I didn't do that on purpose.
How will you edit this?
Even elementary school kids
will know that it was contrived.
- I swear...
- Why did you do that?
- I didn't do that on purpose.
- You did that on purpose.
- You were ready to fall down.
- I didn't do that on purpose.
- You moved your foot back.
- No, I didn't.
Two, three, four.
I should have kicked it like this.
Start over then.
You failed.
(Suk Jin succeeded belatedly,
but they failed!)
I didn't do that on purpose.
It's time for the next mission.
Why...
Before we begin the mission,
- you will pick your position.
- Okay.
Jong Kook shouldn't be the CEO.
- If Jong Kook becomes the CEO...
- Guys,
- line up.
- What?
Intern has it the worst.
I can't move to the top.
Are you the intern?
- She shouldn't be the intern.
- Hey.
(She went from top to bottom.)
Go in there.
She shouldn't be the intern.
Please treat us with respect.
Respect, my foot!
Excuse me?
- Respect, my foot!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
- Watch it.
- It will be hard...
to complete the mission
since So Min is the intern.
This mission is...
Draw a Circle
the Elephant Trunk Spin.
- We are ruined.
- This is bad.
- This game made me nauseous.
- One person will go at a time.
- Okay.
After five spins,
draw a circle that is bigger
than the R mark.
I should have been the intern.
Your circle must be bigger
than the last person's.
- So we need to make it small.
- Outside the R mark, right?
Your circle must be bigger
than the CEO's.
Manager's circle must be bigger
than Deputy Manager's.
Intern's circle must be the biggest.
It sounds fun.
- I am in trouble.
- Okay.
- It's doable.
- I draw first, right?
The circles shouldn't overlap.
- Make it small.
- It will be hard.
All right.
Get ready.
Set, go.
- One,
- two,
- two...
- three,
- Already...
- four...
- Let's go.
- Go.
Five.
Three, two, one.
- Look at that.
- There we go.
- Five.
- Let's go.
- Three, two, one.
- Bigger than that.
- You succeeded.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Good job.
- Five.
- Three,
two, one.
- That's good.
- I am dizzy.
- All right.
- We will succeed.
I am worried about him.
This is bad.
I get dizzy really easily.
- Set, go.
- He gets dizzy really easily.
- Still,
- One,
- he won't mess it up on purpose.
- two,
- three,
- You are going fast. Three.
four...
(Staff Yoo has no skills
in the elephant trunk spin.)
(Will he succeed this time?)
- Four...
- Five.
- Go.
- Three,
- two, one.
- Hurry up.
Jae Suk!
One.
Why did you draw it so big?
What are you doing?
In any case, he succeeded.
- What was I supposed to do?
- How did you draw it like this?
What are you, a thug?
- Unbelievable.
- For goodness' sake.
What was I supposed to do?
- Why did you ruin the mission?
- I didn't ruin the mission.
You should have drawn it better.
I was dizzy, okay?
- For goodness' sake.
- I was about to collapse.
Still...
- It's okay, So Min.
Just make sure it doesn't overlap.
- That's too big.
- Make it big.
I haven't gone yet.
You are going after me.
- Haha!
- He is next.
- Haven't you gone yet?
- You are going after me.
- How are we supposed to do this?
- Haha.
- I thought I was going next.
- Do well.
- Here I go.
- Go ahead.
- Set...
- Set, go.
- One,
- One...
- two,
- He is fast.
- three,
- three...
- four...
- Go slower. Four.
- Three,
- Put one hand on the wall.
two, one.
- All right.
- That's good.
Intern will go last.
- See how big you can draw it.
- Practice.
- She will succeed.
- Make it as big as possible.
You will succeed, So Min.
- That's it.
- There you go.
So Min, you can do it.
Not even a small bit
of the circle should overlap.
- So Min, you can do it.
- Go.
- You are the last one.
- You know,
my higher-ups are giving me
an overweight workload.
- Hey.
- Put one hand on the wall.
You mean a heavy workload.
It's a heavy workload,
- not an overweight workload.
- Overweight.
To be honest, I didn't see
what was wrong with it.
(To be honest, I didn't see
what was wrong with it.)
I was like, "What's wrong with it?"
It's a heavy workload,
not an overweight workload.
- A heavy workload.
- If you succeed,
- you can deduct 20 minutes.
- I feel dizzy.
- You can do it.
- Make it as big as possible.
Set, go.
- So Min.
- One,
- two...
- Two...
This is bad. I am already dizzy.
- Three,
- Three...
- four,
- This is bad.
- five.
- Five.
- Three, two,
- Make it as big as possible.
one.
(Can Intern Jeon be a hero?)
- Make it as big as possible.
- Two,
one.
You failed.
- Why?
- The right side overlapped.
It overlapped.
- Hold on.
- All right.
- I was so dizzy.
- Hey.
- I am not disappointed at all.
- You failed to deduct time.
We will do the sketchbook game.
- We can do well this time.
- We will play...
- the three-syllable word game.
- We will play that game.
Skinny jeans.
- Tick, tock.
- Keep doing that.
Two, one.
- For goodness' sake.
- Don't be flippant.
You got this. It will be easy.
This is bad.
- It's easy.
- How is this jangseung?
You should know from the ears!
- Can't you see the ears?
- Why are you laughing?
All right. It's past 2:45 p.m.,
- so five people can get off work.
- Already?
(It's the regular time
to get off work!)
Can we go home?
We will bring in the item
for getting off work.
- My goodness.
- What is that?
What is that?
I would hate to work overtime.
It's simple.
- There are six cards.
- They are keys.
Only one doesn't work.
(Only one doesn't work.)
- Unbelievable.
- This is insane.
You will need to hear the sound.
(Key card sudden death game)
- Unbelievable.
- This is insane.
- Only one doesn't work?
- I have no luck in such matters.
- Me neither.
- All right.
- Pick one.
Okay.
- Who will go first?
- Take one each.
- Don't try it now.
- Die trying and you will live.
- Am I number one?
All right.
Do we go in numerical order?
- Take turns as you see fit.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
- I will get ready to go out.
I will get ready to go out.
- Number one.
- This is nerve-racking.
Being number one makes me nervous.
I am number five.
- Why was number 1 remaining?
- It can't be number 1.
Why was number one remaining?
Who will go first?
Shall we play rock-paper-scissors?
I will go first.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do that.
- Rock...
- Does the winner go first?
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- Three of us.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- All right.
- I hope mine works.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Will I go first?
- Second.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
- Jong Kook will go first...
- and I will go second.
- If my key card doesn't work,
- everyone else will go home.
- Yes.
All right. Please begin right away.
- If someone fails to open the door,
- Here I go.
- everyone else will go home.
- Please.
I hope the door doesn't open
- My goodness.
- I hope the door doesn't open
It's better to go later
so that someone else fails first.
- Work overtime
- Let's go.
- I will be heading home.
- Work overtime
- If you fail, all of us will live.
Jong Kook will work overtime
- Did it open?
- What?
(What?)
(Will the first person work
overtime?)
Overtime
- Did it open?
- What?
It opened!
(It opened!)
Home! I will be heading home now!
(Laughing)
(It opened.)
Home! I will be heading home now!
(Sighing)
(He shows the excitement
of getting off work.)
(Slamming)
Please stay
and watch their reactions.
- Their reactions.
- Right.
It will be fun to watch.
- Who is going second?
- Me.
(Suk Jin is the next person
who wants to get off work.)
Please yell, "I am off for the day."
- Okay. This is nerve-racking.
- Work overtime
- Suk Jin, work overtime.
- No.
- I am off for the day.
- Work overtime
Please make him work overtime.
Please. That way,
all four of us will go home.
- Work overtime.
My heart is beating so fast.
What should I do?
- Work overtime.
(What will become of Suk Jin?)
My heart is beating so fast.
What should I do?
(Escape)
(Screaming)
(Laughing)
I will head home.
(The two members who came last
will get off work on time!)
So Min is genuinely upset.
This is driving me crazy.
I am unsure about this one.
- I am more unsure about this one.
- I am off for the day.
Do you want to switch with mine?
- No.
- This is exciting.
I am off for the day. Bye.
- Work overtime.
- So Min looks cheerful.
- I am sure about this one.
- I am really nervous.
- Look at her face.
- I was number three all day long.
- Please.
- Work overtime.
(Ringing)
So Min.
(What?)
(Will So Min work overtime?)
So Bal.
(Ringing)
(Beeping)
(The door opened!)
That startled me.
(That's too bad.)
- How is the order so perfect?
- Bye.
- Seriously.
It sounded like
the door wouldn't open.
The sound was strange, right?
- It rang first.
- Yes.
It didn't beep right away.
- One of the three.
- I hope it's Jae Suk.
I bet it's Jae Suk.
I am from the future. You are it.
He works so much these days.
That's right.
I want to head home now.
- Go home, Ji Hyo.
- "I am off for the day."
I am off for the day.
I think I am it.
(It's about time
a nonfunctioning key card appears.)
(What will become
of the three remaining members?)
- It opened.
(The door opened again!)
It opened.
- I am off for the day.
- Hey. How did this happen?
- It opened.
(Oh my goodness.)
How did this happen?
- How did this happen?
- Seriously.
I can't believe
we chose the key cards at random.
- How did this happen?
- We played rock-paper-scissors.
How did this happen
when we played rock-paper-scissors?
Is this for real?
How did four people pass?
It's unbelievable.
I have a bad feeling
about key card number five.
- Hey.
- Who is going next?
- Me.
- What's your key card number?
Mine is number 5
and his is number 6.
Haha, if yours work...
It will be unbelievable.
- Jae Suk wouldn't need to try.
- I arrived first today.
- Please.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- We played rock-paper-scissors.
- Haha isn't exactly lucky.
- I am off for the day.
- Please.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Please let it be him.
- If it's Jae Suk...
- I am so nervous.
- This is really nerve-racking.
Thank you for your hard work.
I am off for the day.
He has a 50-percent chance
of getting off work.
Think about what you will do
for an hour and a half.
- Please.
- My goodness.
- Please let it be him.
- He raised it.
- Please.
- Let's hear the sound.
- Please let it be him.
- He raised it.
- Please.
- Let's hear the sound.
(Please.)
Let's hear the sound.
I will try again.
(His heart dropped.)
Hold on.
- I think I did it wrong.
- Hold on.
The sensor is here, right?
I put the card here.
Okay.
Good work.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Please let me go home.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- I am off for the day.
- All right.
- Thank you for your hard work.
Let's see what happens.
(He put it on the sensor.)
I think it will work.
(Who will work overtime
without getting paid?)
Okay.
(The door opened!)
Let's go.
This is unbelievable.
(Jae Suk will work overtime.)
We played rock-paper-scissors.
- No way.
- How...
Try your card.
How did this happen?
Let's go.
I am off for the day.
(Tapping)
My goodness.
It's strange.
How did Jae Suk pick that key card?
I told you
that I am from the future.
Let's go.
Five members will get off work
and Jae Suk will work overtime.
- Okay.
- Thank you for your hard work.
We will get going now.
- He has so much work.
- This is the absolute worst.
- I thought it would be me.
This is the absolute worst.
Jae Suk, work hard.
We will get going now.
- We will be leaving for real.
- Leave.
- Jae Suk, we are off for the day.
- Thank you for your work.
- What will he do now?
- This is nice.
- I thought it would be me.
- No way.
What am I supposed to do by myself?
We can't help you.
I had a bad feeling
about key card number five.
You picked first.
(He picked the bad key card first
and lost in rock-paper-scissors.)
- How strange.
- It's unbelievable.
- You can't even plan this.
- Seriously.
You must be from the future.
I told you so.
I told you that
Jae Suk would be it.
- What will happen in my life?
- Jae Suk is it.
(Jae Suk is it.)
- Gosh.
- Can we go home now?
Bye.
- Do I head to the basement level?
- Thank you.
- Fifth floor.
- I will be heading home now.
- This is electrifying.
- Bye.
I have no luck.
Jae Suk, please slate...
so that some cameramen can go home.
Is that so?
Do I need to slate
for them to go home?
Then I will do it later.
For goodness' sake.
One, two, three.
All right.
The first group of cameramen
will head out.
Only those who are working overtime
will remain.
This is the absolute worst.
For goodness' sake.
I couldn't open the door.
My goodness.
Can I take off the camera?
Go ahead.
Out of the two...
(The staff leaves except for those
who are working overtime.)
(I want to go home too.)
What am I supposed to do
for an hour and a half?
Seriously.
This is the absolute worst.
We have a small task
for the remaining people.
(Chuckling)
Let me explain.
- I never asked for a small task.
- You are working overtime.
I will lie down and kill time.
We told you that there will be...
- a simple task.
- What is it?
Until the ending time,
receive signatures from 18 people.
- Then you can get off work faster.
- Did you say 18 people?
Yes. For each signature,
we will deduct five minutes.
- Please take a look.
- Who are these people?
(An overtime mission
to get off work faster)
"Due to his lacking job performance,
this person is working overtime."
"He is in need
to shorten his work time..."
"as he lacks capabilities."
"Receiving signatures
from people in charge..."
"can help him get off work faster,"
"so we ask for your cooperation."
"An information desk employee
on the first floor,"
"a cafe employee,"
"a woman whose last name is Lee,
a man whose last name is Park..."
For goodness' sake.
There is even
"A producer of a famous TV show."
I know that there are many.
(A woman whose last name is Lee)
Lee? Hold on.
Hyo Im, isn't your last name Lee?
It's Yang.
Isn't your last name Lee?
- No.
- Isn't your last name Lee?
(No.)
I am sure it is.
You should say
that your last name is Lee today.
A blue top.
Everyone is wearing khaki clothes.
You watch Running Man.
(He captures an assistant director
who was passing by.)
You watch Running Man every week.
- He doesn't count.
- He watches it every week.
An avid watcher
can't be a staff member.
(An avid watcher
can't be a staff member.)
Let's go to the first floor.
(He takes an elevator
to go to the 1st floor.)
"A person whose MBTI is ENFP."
Is your MBTI ENFP?
MBTI changes all the time.
What's your type?
- She is an I type.
- I type?
But you could be an E type.
(The elevator stops
on the 4th floor.)
Come on in. It's okay.
Hello, producer.
You're a producer, right?
You must be a producer.
- I'm a manager.
- Are you a manager?
Is your MBTI ENFP?
- I'm ENFP.
- You're ENFP!
All right. Please sign here.
I'm glad that I found an ENFP here.
Nice to meet you.
Whose manager are you?
- I'm Seung Guk Lee's manager.
- I see.
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
- Thank you.
All right. Hey.
Hello.
- My gosh.
- You're wearing a mask, so...
I'm Hwang Yoon Sung, a trot singer.
Oh, hello.
I'm glad to meet my colleague here.
What is this?
Please sign here.
I'm so lucky.
- This is Running Man.
- Really?
I guess you're here for work.
Yes. I am.
(Jae Suk's colleague
signs the document befuddled.)
- What's your name again?
- I'm Hwang Yoon Sung.
You're Yoon Sung. Nice to meet you.
- I'll see you later.
- See you around.
- Thank you, Yoon Sung.
- Thank you.
Have a nice day.
I didn't expect to meet
my colleague here.
- Are you sure he's your colleague?
- Of course he is.
You know he's Yoon Sung.
He looks uncomfortable around you.
No. That's because
we didn't meet often.
Yoon Sung, what's your song?
(If you have to go)
(If you have to leave after all)
I love your song. See you, Yoon Sung.
Thank you. Bye.
"If you have to go."
That's perfect for me.
Is this the information desk?
I appreciate your hard work.
Please sign here. Please.
Does anyone want
to go to the restroom?
Hang on. I need to go
to the restroom. Can I...
I really need to go.
Hang on. Is there...
Don't you want
to go to the restroom?
No.
(No.)
He's so...
(The cameraman just
wants to go home.)
Hang on. The restroom...
(An employee who was born
in the Year of the Tiger)
Were you born
in the Year of the Tiger?
- I was born in the Year of the Rat.
- The Rat?
Are we of the same age?
(Someone who is your age)
Wait. Were you born in 1972?
- I was born in 1996.
- I see. In 1996.
(He added 24 years.)
He's nice.
He has a nice personality.
- Hello.
- He's our staff.
Do you like to watch Running Man?
- I'm the staff.
- Do you like Running Man?
- Still.
You can still like
to watch Running Man.
Wait. Just say you love our show.
(Just say you love our show.)
All right. He's our viewer.
(He keeps talking
to the wrong people.)
Ju Eun. Wait in there.
- What?
- Do you want me to wait in there?
Just stay there for a while.
Excuse me. Please sign here.
- Who is she?
- What?
- She works at the cafe.
What are you talking about?
She's obviously your stylist.
No.
She's my stylist,
but she works here.
Do you know how to make coffee?
- Make what?
- Can you make coffee?
No. We can drink it.
- Are you a writer?
- Me? No.
- Aren't you a writer?
- No.
Is there anything
that works for you?
Aren't you riding a bicycle?
Isn't this a bicycle?
We can say this is a bicycle.
- If she goes home on it, it counts.
- It has wheels.
- Do you live in Sangam-dong?
- Yes.
She's riding a bicycle now.
I'm riding it now.
Hang on. Bicycle...
Aren't you a teenager?
- No.
- Do you like to watch Running Man?
I live in Sangam-dong.
- Do you live in Sangam-dong?
- Yes.
Then please sign here.
The Sangam-dong resident.
Please sign it.
(He finally gets her signature.)
Thank you so much, Nam Young.
She even rode this
pretending it's a bicycle.
Thank you, Nam Young.
She's the Sangam-dong resident.
An acquainted producer.
We are acquainted.
Were you born in 1992? My goodness.
Please sign here. It's 11.
You got signatures
from 11 different people.
- You can get off work.
- Okay.
It will happen if you work hard.
All right then.
- I'll get off work now.
- Okay.
(I'm getting off work now.)
- Bye.
See you.
(For you who are afraid
of the hot summer...)
(We are going on a vacation
that's cool to the bone.)
(For you who believe
that there's no place like home...)
(We will enjoy everything
you tell us to enjoy.)
- Hang on.
- Look at this.
We are to do this without tools.
(Something to eat)
(Something to play)
(And something to see.
They try all these for viewers.)
(The viewers' vacation comes true!)
Stop spinning it.
(When everything was going well...)
(It must taste terrible.)
(Go away!)
(What nonsense is this?)
(They end up bursting into rage.)
(Is the vacation...)
(going to be all right?)
(The 1st Running Man
Vacation Service)