(January, 2022)
(February, 2022)
(March, 2022)
(April, 2022)
(May, 2022)
(June, 2022)
(July, 2022)
(August, 2022)
(September, 2022)
(October, 2022)
(November, 2022)
(December, 2022)
It's done.
It's the luxury street.
- It's Christmas.
- My gosh.
- This is cute.
- Gosh, this is...
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hello.
Your hair looks so cute.
Suk Jin, I like your outfit today.
- You do?
- But your pants...
- Your compliment is unexpected.
- I like the top, but the pants...
Don't you think
his pants don't look right?
They are pretty.
The pants are the key, you fool.
They are the key.
Why do you call her a fool?
So Min is not a fool.
I'm not a fool.
- You're a fashion fool.
- She's dressed like a fool.
- Hello.
- Hi, Dong Hoon.
- Hello, Haha.
- Hey, Haha.
- You're simply dressed today.
- You look nice today.
- I like that.
- It looks plain.
- Right.
- You're like a lord today.
- It's just fine.
By the way,
Ji Hyo's dress is really...
- It's like hairtail.
- It really stands out.
This is just like
what you wore last week.
- Yes, it's the same.
- Right.
I wore something like this.
It's my dress,
but it's too dazzling even for me.
It looks pretty though.
We can't see it anyway.
Why are you suddenly shy?
- This is Christmas Special today.
- Okay.
So we are opening
at a cafe where you can feel...
the spirit of Christmas.
- That's right.
- It's Christmas already.
- This is nice.
- How time flies.
Merry Christmas.
- Time goes by so quickly.
- It flies so fast.
Now I'm as old as Santa Claus.
I'm so old.
We prepared some refreshments too.
- Please enjoy them while you talk.
- Okay.
- This place is very famous.
- The food is good here.
You have to make a reservation
before coming here.
- It's Christmas.
- This looks delicious.
This looks like luxury goods.
- This is cute.
- It's so pretty.
- When I'm at a place like this...
- Can we eat this now?
Yes, please enjoy it.
- Can we eat? That's surprising.
- Just like this?
- It's a party.
- Because it's Christmas.
My gosh.
- Can we really eat this?
- We can't just eat this...
- without Christmas carols.
- Right.
But we have to play
only Jukjae's songs today.
- I see.
- Oh, right.
(The reason they should play
Jukjae's songs instead of carols...)
- What?
- Start.
(Last week,
Jukjae got his wish granted.)
(Play the songs from
Jukjae's 2nd album last week.)
(Jukjae's wish)
- This is great.
- It's huge.
- I see.
- Oh, right.
Can't we listen
to Christmas carols then?
His new songs?
- Then Jukjae's songs...
- His songs are...
- somewhat gloomy.
- Aren't they ballad songs?
- His new songs.
- There's no dance song.
Maybe we will need some other songs.
I should talk to Jukjae
and work on his songs.
Tell him to sing bright songs.
He should change the lyrics.
He's such a playboy.
I looked through
the lyrics of his songs.
- He's not pure.
- He's not that pure and innocent.
- It's quite erotic.
- It is. He's a player.
- Right?
- He's really funny.
Gosh, this is so delicious.
- It's good.
- He's funny.
This is good. Try it.
- What? There's nothing left.
- Just try it.
(What? There's nothing left.)
- There's nothing.
- Just scrape it off the plate.
Eat this? Suk Jin...
Suk Jin tells me to try this.
But he ate it all.
- There's nothing.
- You should just taste it.
Just taste it.
Oh, right. It was
Se Chan's birthday last week.
What did you do on your birthday?
I did a TV show with your girlfriend
on your birthday,
and she worried about you a lot.
- Who's my girlfriend?
- So Min.
- Hey, who else would it be?
- I was surprised.
Of course, it's So Min.
- I was startled.
- So Min.
This looks like the bait
on "The Fishermen and the City."
(Halibuts and rockfishes will like
her hairstyle.)
- To catch yellowtail amberjack.
- This is...
- Yellowtail. A fishing lure.
- A fishing lure.
I'm trying to fish with my hair.
Take the bait. Bite it.
I think So Min likes...
- Se Chan a little.
- Why?
Because So Min adores him a lot.
Today, she kept saying
Se Chan was cute and adorable.
- Hello.
- This is so cute.
(Before the opening)
Isn't Se Chan cute?
I should say as So Min says.
(Rudolph Yang got a lot of love
as soon as he got here.)
Actually... I told you before.
If Se Chan asks So Min out
with an enthusiastic attitude,
she's ready to open her heart.
When they first started
the business couple,
I honestly thought it was ridiculous
and So Min could do better.
But I don't feel that way anymore.
I think you could
probably do better.
(I think you could
probably do better.)
- And...
- I'm saying...
- It's not like that.
- Se Chan could do better?
I'm just saying this because...
If you think about the looks,
you are a lot better.
But he has such a good personality.
- What about So Min?
- I don't have a good personality?
- What is he saying?
- You do have a good personality.
After spending some time, I realized
he's a really nice person.
I know what you mean.
You're right about that.
- He's nice, isn't he?
- Yes, you're right.
In the long run,
he can make a good husband.
Does that mean you realized
that I wasn't so good?
That's not it. Why are you being
so extreme? That's your problem.
See? This is what I'm saying.
- Don't be so extreme.
- Don't get him wrong.
You're a nice person too.
I just think...
he can make a good husband.
- Right.
- What makes you think so?
- Looks aren't everything.
- Exactly.
As I said, this episode will
go on air on Christmas.
And we can't talk about Christmas
without mentioning gifts.
- Right.
- That's true.
So I'd like to give you gifts
to thank you for your hard work.
- Really?
- It's really okay.
- Are you serious?
- We will go to a mall soon.
- Seriously?
- We will?
You can choose any gift you want...
up to the purchase limit
of 300 dollars.
- Really?
- I need to buy some plates.
- Are you serious?
For myself, not for the members?
- Yes. Whatever you want.
- Seriously?
You can buy
windshield wiper fluids if you want.
- Okay.
- You can buy daily necessities.
He buys windshield wiper fluids
every time he goes to a mall.
- Why is that?
- I always buy...
- razors, batteries...
- Right. Batteries.
- I will use them eventually.
- He's very frugal.
He's really nice.
I will use them eventually.
It's not a waste.
What do you want to buy, So Min?
I'll buy chicken towels.
I mean, kitchen towels.
Chicken towels?
(Chicken towels...)
(Kitchen towels!)
(She realized it a little too late.)
- Gosh, if you didn't know that...
- That was close.
That's what Empty Heads find
most confusing. Chicken and kitchen.
- Kitchen.
- Chicken towel?
- What is it for?
- Is it for goose bumps?
- Is it made with chicken skin?
- I mean kitchen towels.
- I need kitchen towels.
- Chicken towels must be greasy.
What is a chicken towel for, So Min?
- What's wrong with me?
- It can happen.
- It sounds similar.
- Right.
A lot of people find it confusing.
Ji Hyo, what will you buy?
I'll buy some vegetables.
- Vegetables?
- What's with her?
- She's unique.
Will you buy
300 dollars worth of vegetables?
- I will...
- They all are strange.
My dog is...
My dog is a vegetarian.
- So I'll buy vegetables for my dog.
- A vegetarian dog.
- Let's play rock-paper...
- Suk Jin, what do you want?
I want...
- I have no idea.
- I think 300 dollars isn't enough.
He wants to play rock-paper-scissors
so the winner takes all the money.
- He wants more money.
- He's unbelievable.
That's your problem.
- Because I want good headphones.
- That's right.
- You can buy one for 300 dollars.
- I gave you wireless earphones.
You can use them.
I'm using them now.
But I want something thick
to use at home.
But we can't just give away
the gifts.
- That's not Running Man.
- Right.
While you shop around
and buy gifts for yourselves,
you have to carry around
Yoo Jae Suk...
who was selected
as the children's idol in 2022...
so his feet won't touch the ground
the whole time.
(They have to carry
around Jae Suk.)
(Jae Suk's feet aren't supposed
to touch the ground all day.)
- My goodness.
- It sounds all right.
- Hang on.
- Wait.
Why does it have to be me?
Was he selected
as the children's idol?
Yes. Since this is Christmas,
- we're doing this for children.
- Thank you so much.
When will he stop coming in first?
"When will he stop coming in first?"
When will it end?
Every time the children's idol,
Yoo Jae Suk's feet touch the ground,
the shoot of our first episode
in 2023...
- will be moved up by ten minutes.
- What?
(The first shoot of 2023
will be moved up by 10 minutes.)
- Ten minutes?
- Hang on.
- The first shoot of 2023?
- What time does it start?
We usually start the shoot at 10 a.m.
- Then...
- We're fine with that.
It's good that we're doing this
with me.
- I'm easy to carry around.
- Right. You're light.
Yes, I am.
If Jae Suk's feet touch the ground,
and he takes a step,
- that makes it 20 minutes.
- Is it 20 minutes per step?
No. It's ten minutes
for touching the ground...
and another ten minutes
for taking a step.
- So that makes 20 minutes.
- This is going to be tough.
Then we will probably
have to come at dawn.
I know.
So we thought it would be good
if we could...
if we could watch
the sunrise together.
- What?
- The sunrise? Hey.
Sunrise?
- Don't be ridiculous.
- She finally reveals her desire.
So you're doing this
to make us watch the sunrise.
You started showing
your true colors now.
- I will stay up all night.
- She's out of her mind.
- She's crazy.
- We can finish early then.
I'm okay with it.
I have no problem waking up at 5 a.m.
If he loses his mind
and walks around like crazy,
we have to catch him.
- He might go wild.
- We have to make him pass out.
Then we have to
catch him right away.
- So don't provoke me.
- If he gets carried away...
You know what I'm like.
- If I get carried away, I'll...
- I know.
You know that, right?
- Then we will knock you out.
- Okay.
We should be careful.
Or we should just let him go around
and start the shoot at night.
- I'd love that.
- I like it.
Move it up to the previous night.
But I don't want
to stay up all night.
So it's up to me.
- It's up to him.
- It depends on me.
We should keep him with Jong Kook.
- What do we do with the prankster?
- Right.
- Like a backpack.
- I can...
carry him around the whole time.
He's not that heavy.
- "He's not that heavy?"
- Right.
Then we will move to a mall.
- We will start counting now.
- Raise your legs.
It starts now?
Hang on.
If I walk around now, you will...
That's right.
Why are you threatening us?
That sounds threatening.
- So Min, I...
- No, Jae Suk.
- Let's carry him.
- Don't move.
- Just stay still.
- We can carry him.
- Don't lower your legs.
- Carry him on your back.
- He's light.
- I'll carry him.
I shouldn't step on the couch.
Is that why?
Rise on your knees.
- Wait.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Hang on.
All right.
Gosh, what's this?
You're so light.
- This is nice.
- He's really light.
I'm on Jong Kook's back.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- You're really light.
- Don't drop the prankster.
- All right.
The prankster.
This is the luxury alley.
- Gosh.
- All right.
- Jae Suk is really light.
- I'll carry you on my back.
- Let me carry you.
- Forget it. No thanks.
- Come on.
- Here.
All right.
- Gosh.
- He's so light.
- This is...
- It's nice to be on his back.
- By the way...
- We have a good worker.
Jae Suk is as light as a feather.
- Aren't I light?
- Yes.
My gosh.
I weigh only 61kg.
Right.
- Do you weigh 61kg?
- Yes.
You are just like an idol artist.
- So Min, where are you going?
- Where are we going?
I want to go to Jimmy Choo.
- Yeongdeungpo.
- Jimmy Choo.
Are we going to Yeongdeungpo?
- So Min, where are we going?
- How did you know?
So Min said Yeongdeungpo.
Who told you that?
No one told me. It was my guess.
I will find out who it is.
- We're headed that way.
- Seriously, we should...
catch the spy.
We should narrow down the suspects
and interrogate them.
Actually, we don't have to do
anything about it.
It will only tire her out.
Why do you want to know?
It's not that I want to know.
I just...
Once she starts checking
her boyfriend's phone,
- she can't stop it.
- Right.
She knows it's wrong,
but she can't control herself.
- My wife...
- That's not right.
Like many, I keep my phone locked
because I work.
It could be a pattern
or a fingerprint.
But it unlocks when I get home.
- Why?
- How?
- My wife set it up.
- How would you do that?
- It's possible.
- How?
You can set it
to unlock automatically...
- when you go to certain places.
- Is that like a hack?
- What?
- A hack.
- Your phone has that function?
- That doesn't make sense.
- You can.
- Is it something you can set up?
So I just...
- I just feel comfortable this way.
- I see.
Suk Jin.
- Even in your car.
- You shouldn't do that.
Right.
(Sighing)
- You just sighed.
- I know.
(His story about the high-tech system
ends with a sigh.)
Do you fart in front of your wife?
Of course, he did.
He's been married...
- for over 30 years.
- Fart?
You can hear the roaring of guns
at his place.
It happened that way
for some unavoidable reasons.
- It sounds like an interceptor.
- Right.
(Boom)
Is it like an earthquake?
(Guns firing)
It's so loud.
Really loud.
I heard it was like a runway.
- It's really loud.
- With thrust.
A 3,000cc motorcycle.
- It's really loud.
- That's funny.
So Min.
- It's hilarious.
- I know.
(It's always fun
to talk about farting.)
- What do I need at home?
- For Dream,
I want to buy stuff like
a fish tank, a heater, and a filter.
You can buy a complete set.
I should buy a blanket.
How are you going to carry it home?
Hey, you always...
- I need a blanket.
- Why do you always...
try to buy household goods
on this show?
That's very useful.
- Hey, it's...
- Those who live alone do that.
- A winter blanket.
- They need something useful.
It's 300 dollars per person,
so it's 2,100 dollars in total.
- My gosh.
- Okay?
- I'll just buy some body lotion.
- I'll buy groceries.
You can't buy
300 dollars worth of body lotion.
- That one cost about that much.
- That one's a good brand.
Toothpaste?
I have enough toothpaste.
If you buy 300 dollars
worth of toothpaste...
- I can buy other stuff too.
- I can buy groceries.
- Once we get there,
- You'll know when we get there.
you will want
to buy a lot of things.
You can buy some beef.
- Right.
- What do you want, So Min?
- I'll go see.
- Wine.
- I can buy groceries or...
- So Min, I don't want you...
- to buy Se Chan a sweater.
- Can I get you anything?
- What?
- Do you need anything?
Then you should buy me a blanket.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Why do you need a blanket?
- I need one.
(Why do you need a blanket?)
(She blurts out something strange.)
She thinks it's a blanket for us.
- What's with her?
- No.
What's wrong with her?
- So Min is funny.
- Jeon So Bal.
I like it when he's flustered.
"Why do you need a blanket?"
- What will you buy?
- I'll...
- I'll buy my wife a gift.
- Cash...
Come on, Suk Jin.
- All of a sudden.
- Don't lie to us.
- Stop it.
- I'm serious.
I want to look like a good husband.
- My gosh.
- Do as you please.
What will you buy
for your wife at a mall?
- What will you buy?
- Perfume.
- I'm just curious.
- That's what I meant.
All right. I'll buy a perfume.
They also have some lotions.
And a Bluetooth...
Does your wife want
a Bluetooth product?
He's lying.
- He made that up.
- My wife is using earphones...
- that are relatively cheap.
- I see.
So I want to give her
something nicer.
Then you should give her
the ones I gave you.
No, that's for me.
That's mine.
- I gave it to you.
- Right.
Okay.
- We have to carry him.
- That's right.
We should carry him now.
Thank you.
Don't forget to carry
Jae Suk on your back.
- Let's carry him in our arms.
- Carry him on your back.
- Thank you.
- Let him sit on our arms.
- I can take just two steps.
- No.
- You can't do that.
- That's 20 minutes.
- No.
- We should try our best for now.
Then you can run away or something
at the last moment.
That's up to you.
- We'll try our best for now.
- My goodness.
We have to do this for now.
I'll carry you on my back, Suk Jin.
This is really comfortable though.
It's not hard.
You're not heavy at all.
This is comfortable.
It's not hard
carrying Jae Suk around.
This is nice.
Wait. I'll go see
if there's a cart we can use.
Okay. Go see if there's a cart.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Is there a cart or something?
We should find a wagon.
I bet there's something we can use.
- It's so nice to be here.
- I know.
Let's go eat a hamburger.
Shall we go eat a hamburger?
- We can eat later.
- Nice.
Jae Suk, wait here
while we're shopping.
No, we... I mean, I should go too.
- He needs to shop too.
- That's right.
- Let's look for it. Yes.
- A cart...
- Oh, that'll work. Can we use this?
- Yes.
No, this one. Let us use it.
Good. They found a cart.
- Oh, that's a trolly. Good.
- They found a trolly.
Guys, let's use this.
Let's borrow it.
Wait. You're doing it wrong.
- Is it ours?
- It's our team's.
- I see. That's great.
- I'm sorry. Please let us use it.
- Come here.
- I'll stand on it.
- But what about our staff?
- Hey, sit on it.
- Wait.
- Okay.
- Nice. This is much better.
- This is nice, indeed.
- Sit down. It's dangerous.
- Sit on it.
This is nice. It's much better.
- We need Jae Suk to stay healthy.
- Our dear Jae Suk.
We only have 30 minutes.
We need to hurry.
- Where? That way?
- Yes.
- They're carrying cameras.
- Let's go...
and check out some toys first.
- We'll need a shopping cart too.
- You're right.
Jae Suk, what do you want to buy?
Let's pick that up first.
(The members split up
and start shopping.)
Jae Suk, I see toys like LEGO.
- Where are those?
- I'll take you there.
- Hey, wait. Stop.
- Why?
I'm sorry, but can you turn me
around so that I can face forward?
- This is what you want, right?
- Yes.
- Over there.
- Okay.
Let's check out the toys.
(They found the toy aisle.)
Jae Suk,
aren't you going to buy LEGO?
Toys are the best gifts
for Christmas.
(The paradise of children
with a Christmas vibe)
My, those look so nice.
I wish I could walk around
to have a look.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Next to us... That looks nice too.
- Look at that turtle ship.
I used to buy a lot of these.
- You mean, these?
- Yes.
(Singing)
I used to play a lot with Ji Ho
with this.
- That looks fun.
- This one?
"The Zombie Attack
on Police Bureau."
- Oh, my.
- Nice.
- I'm a bit hesitant to pick this.
- Why?
My children like playing with this,
but I have to do all the work.
- That's true. You'll have to do it.
- Oh, I see.
- I wish I could walk around.
- Jae Suk, sit down.
Wait. A fish-shaped bun store?
(A fish-shaped bun store toy
caught his eye this time.)
- They like making stuff,
- Do they like it?
but I have to be a customer
in their role-play.
(He'll have to role-play
with the kids.)
You know what I mean, right?
If I buy a cooking toy like this,
then I'll have to be their customer.
You see, toys like these
don't interest me at all.
- Really?
- I don't even know what they are.
Then go somewhere else
to choose your gift.
Then keep looking around here.
- I'll pick one and come back.
- Okay. Go on.
- Stay here for a while. Okay.
- I'll look around and ask for help.
This one looks nice.
(While looking for a blanket,
he got fascinated by a vacuum cleaner.)
Excuse me.
Anyone... Excuse me.
(The strange customer
asks for someone to help him.)
Is this not for sale?
(He keeps raising his arm like he's
looking for a restaurant owner.)
Excuse me. I'd like to buy this.
Who...
Is there no one in charge of this?
(While he's desperately looking for
the owner of the store...)
Oh, my. What should I buy?
A long sleeve shirt in a solid color
like this would be nice.
I have nothing to wear
for my YouTube videos.
(In fact, he's in workout clothes
in most of his videos.)
Oh, these sweat pants
look so comfortable.
I can't have enough of them.
This is an extra large?
My, it's so nice.
(Jong Kook's only luxury,
buying black workout clothes)
Right? It looks really nice.
(He picked the black sweat pants.)
What? Oh, my.
It's very soft. I like it.
Soft pants. I like it.
It's nice.
Oh, it's a new product? Nice.
Oh, my. This one is made of
a different type of fabric.
- What are the differences?
- What's funny?
- It's different.
- I don't see any differences.
No, you're wrong.
It's different from the other pairs.
The color and the fabric
are different.
Right. It's made of
a different type of fabric.
Look at this one.
It's different too.
What's this? It's quite different
from the ones I saw.
Okay. I'll pick this one too.
Let's go.
(He picked four very different pairs
of pants.)
They're different from one another.
They're made of
different types of fabrics.
Let's go.
(All black pants are different
from one another.)
I can buy gold too, right?
(So Min can't seem to leave
the gold store.)
Right. I didn't think of that.
Look at that. I want that.
That's what I want.
Is there anything worth 300 dollars?
How much is this piggy?
It's worth over 300 dollars.
- I see. The smaller one too?
- Yes.
How much is the smallest piggy?
- It's 330 dollars.
- I see.
I guess there's nothing I can get
within 300 dollars.
Oh, my. I feel like I'm in paradise.
My goodness. It's so cute.
What should I do?
What should I do with this?
Should I just...
Shall I get one?
This cushion is so cute.
(She finds the cushions so cute.)
This one is so cute. It's a unicorn.
What should I do? It's so cute.
My, it's so cute.
It's so cute. What should I do?
How cute.
I'll keep this one
and give the rest away as gifts.
Did I pick too many of them?
Are they expensive?
I think they are.
I pick LEGO.
(Ji Hyo chose a LEGO product
that's around 260 dollars.)
Shall I pick up some beer too?
How nice. I wish I could live here.
(The scent of alcohol
relaxes her mind and body.)
These are so cute.
(She has an unusual taste
and finds beer cans cute.)
These cans are so cute.
Look at these cans.
Aren't they cute?
(To her,
beer cans are cuter than dolls.)
My little princess likes
sweet potatoes.
Pumpkin sweet potatoes.
Chestnut sweet potatoes. Found them.
(She picks vegetables for her dog
instead beer.)
(The vegetables that her dog likes)
I'm done.
I need to get a fish tank.
But how will I carry it?
(Haha said
he would get a fish tank earlier.)
I found fish tanks. Here they are.
Look at those fish tanks.
(It's a good chance for him
since he needed one.)
My, these all look nice.
Hold on. How do I get one?
How does it work?
Okay.
(He calls his wife Byul.)
- Honey, I'm shooting Running Man.
- Yes.
And I found a nice fish tank here.
- Oh, but I already ordered one.
- Did you?
Since it'll be delivered tomorrow,
it'd be great
if you pick up a heater...
and some ornaments.
Okay. Got it.
Then... A heater.
(He starts shopping
now that he got her approval.)
It's too cold for our pet turtles.
(Starting with a fish tank heater
for his cold turtles)
We also need a sturdy filter.
Filters are easily broken,
so I'll get two of them.
I'll get a rock too.
For the turtles to go up on it.
Oh, my.
The kids will love this, right?
I found a filter.
(A message from his wife arrived.)
"Soonsoo Signature Toilet Paper,
Huggies Soft Pants..."
She wants me to pick up diapers?
(While Haha received a request
for additional items...)
Oh, dear.
"Catch! Teenieping."
(Jae Suk is moving by himself.)
(His arms are full of gifts
for Na Eun.)
Oh, I should buy some books
for Ji Ho.
I think
I picked enough toys for Na Eun.
There aren't many toys
for kids around Ji Ho's age.
This is so uncomfortable.
(He has less than ten minutes left
to shop.)
(Jae Suk is left alone
as no one cares.)
Where are the other members?
They must be busy
choosing their own gifts.
- Thank you.
Okay. I'm done shopping.
Where is Jae Suk?
Jae Suk, where are you?
Jae Suk.
Hey, what is all that?
I didn't go down.
- I heard you came down.
- What did you get?
Pajamas.
(He picked gifts only for Na Eun
while he only got pajamas.)
Suk Jin, I didn't know
you wanted a hat like this.
No, this is for my mother.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Push the cart for me.
- Okay.
I mean, they all left me alone...
Oh, gosh.
Sit down.
(Seok Sam with no skills
drags the cart wildly.)
Suk Jin, that's not important.
I need to go that way.
(No, I need to go somewhere else.)
- No, I need to go somewhere else.
- Gosh.
- I want...
- I'm not going that way.
- Hey! Get back on the cart now!
- I mean...
- No, I need to go somewhere else.
- Gosh.
(Jae Suk's feet touched the floor.)
Get back on the cart now!
- I have no choice.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- Oh, no.
(Oh, no.)
- What's with these stickers?
- Suk Jin.
- Na Eun likes them.
- Put your other foot on the cart.
- Then pick that up for me.
- Put the other foot on the cart.
- Put it on the cart.
- Why...
- Stay seated for a while.
- That's not the point.
- I'm sorry. I'll be back shortly.
- No. I need to...
(His feet touched the floor again.)
Let me look around just for a while.
(He takes small steps.)
- I need to go there.
- Gosh, seriously.
- What's wrong?
- Hey!
- Why are you running around?
- Help me...
- Get back on the cart.
- I wasn't running around.
I don't want to go that way.
Jae Suk,
hurry up and get on the cart.
Suk Jin tried to take me
to another aisle.
- I need to go there, So Min.
- I'll take you there.
- Oh, these must be for Na Eun.
- I haven't...
- All right. Let's go.
- I haven't picked a gift for Ji Ho.
- These are all for Na Eun, right?
- Yes.
- So Min, come here.
- I need to check that out.
- Suk Jin, come and take me there.
- Okay.
- How much time do we have left?
- While we were arguing,
we wasted so much time.
- Where do you want to go?
- That way.
- Just go. I'll walk there.
- No.
- Let's go there just for a second.
- No way.
- I just need to check this one out.
- Over there,
- I just need to see that.
- there are Bluetooth earphones.
- Then just go.
- Just one product. No.
I can't leave you alone.
- What is it? Let's take a look.
- Take me that way.
- Darn.
- What's this? Electronic target?
I want to find something for Ji Ho.
But I have to...
- I have to go to that aisle.
- Go. Hurry up.
This is 210 dollars?
It's 17 years old.
Hey, Se Chan, there you are.
I've been looking all over for you.
How much is that?
This is it. I'm done.
I should take that out.
So it's 200 dollars...
(He chose a bottle of whiskey
instead of daily necessities.)
I'll return these two.
Oh, no.
My precious windshield wiper fluids.
(He returns
the windshield wiper fluids too.)
Done.
I've been meaning to buy that.
Oh, my. He chose his stuff
very carefully.
- Should I put them in a box?
- A box?
- Yes, I'll put them in a box.
- Okay.
Oh, my. What did you buy?
- LEGO?
- Yes.
- Will you do it by yourself?
I'm not sure about the total price.
(He got four completely different
pairs of pants.)
(The things that Jong Kook
and Suk Jin purchased)
- It's 144.30 dollars.
- Yes. Here you go.
Hello.
I have to buy things
that are worth 300 dollars in total.
- Yes.
- You only picked toys and stickers.
- How much is it?
- Give me a moment, please.
It's 234.97 dollars.
- Then 70 dollars are left.
- You have 70 dollars left.
Okay. Then that's all for me.
Let's get going.
- He can move around by himself now.
- Indeed.
- He's a master now.
- Thank you.
You can move around by yourself.
Kyung Eun will probably give me
an earful.
He bought a lot of toys.
- Probably.
- She'll say I bought too many toys.
- Yes, she will.
- That's all worth 230 dollars?
- Really?
- This is worth 230 dollars.
- I'm like Santa Claus.
- Oh, my.
- Se Chan, can you help me?
- Sure. What do you need?
- Can you put them in this?
- Okay.
I'll give it to you later.
Why would she...
So Min bought a suitcase.
- Se Chan, put them in this...
- How much is it?
- It's a little over 130 dollars.
- I'm like Santa Claus.
- Yes. I'll give you.
- Just a moment, please.
- My gosh. What's this?
- I don't know if I can afford it.
I need to think about it.
- Why would she buy so many dolls?
We said the same thing
at the same time.
- That's funny.
- Why would she buy so many dolls?
I mean,
she has to carry them around.
How sweet.
Her boyfriend is helping her.
- He's doing all the work for her.
- Right.
That's because it's hers.
It's her suitcase.
I know.
- So Min.
- Yes?
I don't want to criticize you
for what you bought, but...
I mean,
why did you buy strawberries?
- Why did you buy this?
- Why strawberries?
Is this a bag?
- Her boyfriend is so nice.
- Right.
- We'll get going now.
- Shall we?
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
You bought all you needed, right?
- Yes.
- Now, I'll tell you the real rules.
- What?
Today's race is actually...
the Christmas special,
Santa Yoo and Six Rudolphs.
- Santa Yoo?
- The things you just purchased...
are actually Christmas gifts for citizens,
not for you guys.
- That'll warm our hearts.
- Those are Christmas gifts...
(Haha will have to give citizens
the fish tank items as gifts.)
- I have to order everything again.
- But...
This is...
Hold on. I canceled
all my same-day delivery orders.
(Oh, dear)
- No way.
- This is...
- Excuse me.
- I picked what my kids would like.
- Come on. I bought pajamas.
- I have...
- a gift for the cameraman.
- My gosh.
- I can't believe this.
- I mean...
I don't know who will receive this,
but today it's their lucky day.
- They are so lucky.
- But...
- I feel the same way.
- She even bought a suitcase.
(She'll have to give away the food
in the suitcase as well.)
- I mean, hey.
- My gosh.
It's so disappointing.
Since you chose those gifts
after much thought,
I'm sure that citizens will be
very happy to receive them.
Yes, of course.
I chose all of them carefully.
You will visit several places
with a Christmas vibe...
and carry out missions
with the citizens you meet.
Every time you fail,
the number of gifts you can give
to the citizens will decrease.
- So please do your best.
- We must complete the missions.
We should do our best
to give away all the gifts we have.
Like earlier, Santa Yoo must
keep his feet off the ground.
- Suk Jin and I argued earlier.
- Right.
- He tried to take me elsewhere...
- It wasn't like that.
- You guys caused a ruckus.
- Yes, we did.
- Let me explain.
- I saw Jae Suk running around.
- How many steps?
- I didn't run around.
- He ran around for so long. Yes.
- He ran around?
It's been moved to 7:30 a.m.
- Did you say 7:30 a.m.?
- Yes.
That's too early.
At this rate, we might have to...
- do the opening at 4 a.m.
- That's the worst.
We'll move to the location
for the first mission.
Okay!
No one will like my gifts.
I only bought black pants.
- Hop on my back.
- Gosh.
This is it.
What? A treadmill?
- What's going on?
- Why is a treadmill here?
(A treadmill is placed
in the middle of the mall.)
What's this treadmill for?
What's that?
The first mission is...
- Santa Rides A Treadmill.
- Jae Suk, be careful.
- A treadmill?
- Santa Rides A Treadmill.
You have to invite two citizens.
Nine people in total...
- have to work together.
- Got it.
Each must run on the treadmill
for one minute...
and read the given text
in one breath.
- Gosh. That sounds hard.
- When you're out of breath,
the next player will run
on the treadmill...
and read the rest of the text
starting with the next word.
- It won't be easy.
- That's...
If you read through to the end,
you succeed.
If you succeed on your first try,
you can give away all your gifts.
Every time you fail,
you will lose two gifts.
- Two gifts?
- Yes.
We'll randomly choose the gifts...
- to take away.
- Understood.
Santa Yoo is allowed to put his feet
on the ground when his turn comes.
I see. Okay.
Now, go and find two citizens
who will help you with the mission.
- Two citizens.
- Physical ability is important.
How about those who are watching us
from the Pilates center?
- Pilates?
- They exercise on a regular basis.
- They exercise...
- Se Chan is going there.
- There he goes.
- Go, Se Chan.
- You can do it, Se Chan.
Namaste.
- "Namaste?"
- They don't say that.
- That's for a yoga class.
- Exactly.
- He became so active suddenly.
- Those exercises are similar. Yes.
- That's nice.
- Shall I go?
There's a gym over there.
Ji Hyo, you go to the gym.
- Me?
- Invite one of the trainers there.
- Lately, Ji Hyo is...
- Yes.
- She's the casting queen.
- so good at casting.
- Exactly.
- There she goes. Ji Hyo is going.
(Chuckling)
- Did they refuse to come?
- I got scolded.
- Why?
- They said they couldn't do it.
- They scolded me as they refused.
- You...
Did they refuse to come
because of your appearance?
I think so.
- Do you want to go with me?
- Yes. Let's go.
Okay. Let's go.
- You see...
- Jae Suk...
- can be very persuasive.
- Hey, don't leave Jae Suk alone.
Stay with him.
- Gosh.
- Oh, there's... No.
Hey.
- Gosh.
- Oh, there's... No.
Hey.
Your feet touched the floor
three times.
- We'll move it up by 30 minutes.
- What did you do?
- The starting time is 7 a.m. now.
- It's dangerous.
- Just stay here, Jae Suk.
- But...
- Stay here, Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk...
- I think...
- That cord...
- Stay seated.
- I'll stay seated.
I thought we could go over it.
- Gosh. I can't believe this.
- That was... My gosh.
- Do you run often?
- Yes.
That's great. I'm relieved.
- Hello.
- Hello. Are you busy?
- Are you busy right now?
- Not at all.
- Can you help us with a mission?
- Sure.
- Great. Are you good at running?
- Thank you.
Do you often run on a treadmill?
- I saw the young ones over there.
- Yes.
- Young ones?
- Hey, young lads.
- We're back.
- Good job, young lads.
- That's funny.
- We brought one person.
- That's right. He's here.
- Hey, young lad.
- It's good that he's young.
- He doesn't look so young.
I don't think he's so young.
- How old are you?
- I'm 38.
- Oh, he's 38.
- See? I knew it.
He's 38.
- But you're much younger than me.
- He was born in 1985.
- Hey...
- I'm 44. I'm much older than him.
He's being bossy again.
- He's so bossy, indeed.
- Indeed.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- I work there.
- Oh, you just came to work?
- It's nice to meet you.
He has a muscular body as expected.
- Are you...
- It's nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
- Are you subscribed to his channel?
- Yes, Gym Jong Kook.
- Mr. Trainer.
- I watched every video. I'm a fan.
- Gym Jong Kook.
- Is he a fitness trainer?
- He represents all trainers.
- Oh, my.
- He looks like...
a soccer player
looking at Lionel Messi.
- That's a good comparison.
- How do trainers...
What do fitness trainers
think of Jong Kook?
He's like Lionel Messi.
- Lionel Messi.
- Oh, my.
Thank you so much.
- He's the father of fitness.
- He must be a huge fan.
- The father of fitness?
- He's the father of fitness.
- I'm so grateful.
- The Bang Jeong Hwan in that field.
Fitness trainers are...
- really amazing.
- Of course.
You said you came to work.
Where do you work?
I work in the store over there.
- Oh, I see.
- He works here.
- It's good that you two came.
- Yes.
- We prepared gifts for you.
- Yes. We'll give you a gift.
- We prepared really nice gifts.
- Thank you for joining us.
- If you receive Jae Suk's gifts,
- I should've bought them.
- you'll be very happy.
- Absolutely.
Do you like "Catch! Teenieping?"
- Pardon?
- "Catch! Teenieping."
It's very popular.
You have to decide
on the order first.
When it's your turn,
run on the treadmill...
and read the text here
right after running.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- Let's go! We've got this.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- Now...
- Seok Sam, you go first.
- All right. I'll do that.
- Suk Jin.
- Listen, everyone.
- I'll read the whole thing.
- Go, Suk Jin.
- Let's do this.
- Seok Sam.
- Go up, and we'll set the speed.
- Okay. Go on, Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- Seok Sam.
Here I go. I've got this!
Show them how healthy you are.
- Right. Show them.
- Of course. I'm very healthy.
Show them
how healthy and vigorous you are.
I'll do that.
(The vigorous man is confident.)
Okay. How fast will it be?
- That's too fast.
- How fast...
- What?
- It'll be 15km per hour.
Did you say 15km per hour? Hey!
- Did she say 15km per hour?
- You can do it.
- My gosh.
- It'll be hard.
It's so fast.
- Start.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my. It's so fast.
- Gosh, that's...
- How many seconds have passed?
- Do you think we can do it?
- It has begun.
- I played soccer yesterday.
- We'll get hurt if we fall.
- This is no joke.
- We should be careful.
- How much longer should I run?
How much time has passed?
Twenty-six.
I have to run for one minute?
- It's fast.
- Fifteen seconds have passed.
Seok Sam, are you okay?
(Stiff)
- You look worried.
- No, I'm not worried.
Do you exercise often?
- Well... Not that often.
- I see.
- How many seconds have passed?
- So Min is up next.
(He's practically hanging
on the treadmill.)
Okay. You're almost done.
You should hold the bars
while running.
- How much longer?
- Almost there.
It's fast.
(One minute has passed.
The treadmill stops.)
You can come down
and read the text now.
(The sentences
that they have to read out loud)
- Ready. Go.
- Go now.
- In one breath.
- Ready. Go.
- "2022..."
- Gosh.
- Suk Jin.
- Ready. Go.
(2022...)
- Come on.
- My gosh.
What's wrong with him?
- I'm sorry.
- What was that?
- I'm sorry, but...
- What's wrong with you?
- Suk Jin, you're a pro.
- He did his best.
- Let me explain.
- You're a pro.
That ended so quickly.
Listen to me.
You should know
that I'm not joking around.
- Gosh. Then next...
- Who goes next?
Should we begin after "2022?"
Yes, right after "2022."
Can you mark the word?
Who's up next? So Min?
- It's after "2022."
- I'm not sure if I can do this.
- Start after that.
- The weak ones go first, right?
It's better if I go next
because I'm not good at it, right?
- I just ran,
- So Min.
and I barely read one word.
We'll set the speed to 13km per hour
for female members.
- To 13km per hour?
- So Min.
- Hold the bars while running.
- Or else, I'll fall, right?
For now...
- Seriously, I'm not...
- What is she doing?
You can hold the bars while running.
Hold the bars while running.
- Right. Or else, you might fall.
- Okay.
(Screaming)
- Gosh, it's too fast!
- She's not running properly.
- So Min isn't running properly.
- Why are you stomping on it?
- Hold the bars.
- Hold the bars. It's dangerous.
I can tell
that she's never run before.
She hasn't done any running before.
The sole of her feet. Right?
So Min hasn't done
any running before.
- She's stomping the soles.
- This might kill her.
- She might die.
- Grab the handrail.
- This seems like a challenge.
- Absolutely.
- This looks hard.
- This isn't easy.
- My gosh.
- So Min.
Hang in there.
(So Min's running has them
assuming a negative result.)
Five, four...
One. You're done. Stop it yourself.
Go, So Min.
- To the side.
- Step on it.
- So Min, go ahead.
- Step down.
"Is coming to an end."
"Around this time of year,
a song is brought to our ears."
"It's the carol White Christmas."
"It means a snowy Christmas..."
"and this song made in the US
became the first popular carol."
- Gosh.
- No way.
"And this song made in the US
became the first popular carol."
(So Min's did quite well.)
- Nice.
- You should've taken...
- a big breath first. Did you?
- Did you take a breath?
- There wasn't time for that.
- Gosh.
She did really well
which means I was terrible at it.
So Min did a great job.
- You did really well.
- Good job, So Min.
This is the game she's the best at.
- Dong Hyub.
- Yes?
- Will you be all right?
- Sure.
You'll be reading from...
- "The romantic mood of the snow."
- Sure.
If he hasn't worked out before...
Judging by his legs,
I doubt that he has.
It doesn't look like
he's been working out.
Will he be all right?
Be careful.
Please be careful
and grab the handrail.
- Wait.
- Hold on a second.
Dong Hyub.
Hold on a second.
He hasn't done any running before.
- Yes?
- Are you all right?
Please grab the handrail.
Dong Hyub, my gosh.
He...
It's like he's running like this.
His legs have lost their way.
- His legs have lost their way.
- Are you all right?
It's like he's running like this.
- Dong Hyub, are you all right?
- Yes.
He's flustered.
Have you tried running for a minute
any time recently?
- Yes, I have.
- Really?
It doesn't seem that way.
Please be careful.
- Please be careful.
- You'll trip.
Please be careful.
- Call an ambulance.
- Don't try to look cool.
- Don't be flustered.
You can do this.
- Five, four...
- He could have good lung function.
Three, two, one.
- Stop.
- Stop the treadmill for him.
- Step to the side.
- Stop the treadmill.
- Stop.
- Step on it.
- All right.
- Ready, get set,
- go.
- Take a deep breath.
"The romantic mood of the snow
fits the song..."
"which is why many enjoy
singing it or listening to it."
"Singing it or listening to it."
(Singing it or listening to it.)
How lackluster was that?
"Gosh, they sing the song."
- You did well.
- Good job.
- That was great.
- Dong Hyub, you did great.
- "Singing it or listening to it."
- To it.
(They're having
the time of their lives.)
"Singing it or listening to it."
He did great though. Meanwhile, I...
- Jae Suk, why don't you go next?
- Maybe I should.
- You have good stamina.
- Jae Suk, go next.
Let's do this.
To be honest,
I got dizzy after I stepped down.
- Three of you need to finish this.
- So, I...
Can you stop fishing
for compliments?
- Want to go again?
- You did well.
- How many times must I say it?
- I said I got dizzy.
- The compliments weren't enough.
- It's not like that.
You want more.
It's not like that.
I just want you to listen to me.
- Even though you were dizzy...
- Gosh.
All right.
(Fitness fanatic Jae Suk
gives it a try.)
I should've tied
my shoelaces tighter.
You can grab onto the handrails.
He's as light as a feather.
He must've been dying to run.
Bring it on!
He's loving it.
- This is great.
- He has done some running before.
You definitely know how to run.
Does it show?
- This is bad.
- What is it?
I want to pee.
(The sudden stimulation
has his bladder sending a signal.)
- Unbelievable.
- Just like that?
- He's fit except for his prostate.
- Hold the handrail if you want.
- I haven't been to the restroom.
- You can grab onto it.
All right. Five,
four, three, two, one.
Press the button.
One. Press the button.
- Stop the treadmill.
- Take a deep breath.
- I should've taken a breath too.
- Ready, go.
"This song of four verses
is set in a lyrical mood..."
"and is loved by everyone..."
"regardless of age, gender,
nationality, and religion."
"White Christmas was composed..."
"for the musical film
Holiday Inn..."
- That was close.
- Good job.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk, that was great!
- I should've...
- There's not much left.
- Nice.
- Because I went first,
I was clueless.
Exactly. Suk Jin shouldn't have...
- I should've been prepared.
- Let's do this.
It's all because I went first.
Can I go to the restroom?
- Sure, go ahead.
- Suk Jin...
Your feet can't touch
the ground though.
What?
My feet can't touch the ground
when I'm going to the toilet?
- Should I take him?
- Then...
How am I supposed to relieve myself?
You need to get it done
while seated.
Maybe you can turn around.
Place him on the toilet.
- You need to pull your pants up.
- Why is a cameraman coming with us?
Why are you filming me
when I'm off to the restroom?
Ji Yeon, go away.
(The cameraman and director
are professionals.)
I couldn't see anything at first.
- That's how dizzy I was.
- But you still did a good job.
I don't mean that, you jerk.
You want more compliments.
I know I'm right.
The compliments earlier
weren't enough.
- I'm telling you how it was.
- You're... Fine.
- I didn't mean it like that.
- We complimented her,
- but she's fishing for more.
- That's not it.
- I'm saying it was hard.
- How much will be enough?
How far do you need us to go?
Did they film you taking a leak?
It was done quite stably.
- Really?
- He did it from up here.
From higher ground?
While standing on it?
He got a taste of what it's like
to be Seo Jang Hoon.
We'll now move on to Haha...
- who is the fifth runner.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- Good.
- Go, Haha.
- This is really fast.
- It is.
"It was written for the movie."
"The Russian American musician
Irving Berlin wrote it..."
"while dreaming of
the hot desert state of Arizona..."
(His legs are short,
but he managed to say two lines.)
- Good job.
- You looked great, Haha.
Will Ji Hyo be okay in her dress?
I'm more worried about my shoes.
Your shoes don't seem appropriate.
- My shoes.
- Will they be okay?
- Are the shoes okay?
- Yes.
The fitness trainer can go next.
- This can be done.
- It should be a ten.
- Does it need to be at 12?
- No, 13.
- It's one paragraph.
- Look at Ji Hyo run.
She's quite the runner.
- Her running seems stable.
- She's light on her feet.
My shoes.
I told you to change shoes.
My shoes, darn it.
- My shoes, darn it.
- Forty seconds.
What did she just say?
Her shoes? That startled me.
- Three, two.
- Hold the handrail.
One, and you're done. Come down.
(A minute passed
while she got angry with her shoes.)
You'll do it right away. And go.
"Covered in snow on Christmas."
"It is said that Bing Crosby
made it a Christmas classic."
Good.
- Good job.
- You did well.
Okay, good.
- It's not bad.
- We're doing great.
The trainer's next.
- Don't you need sneakers?
- No, these are fine.
The trainer will probably read
all that is left.
Jong Kook,
I doubt you'll get your turn.
- He'll complete the mission for us.
- Nice.
Get ready.
- We...
- Hold on.
Suk Jin didn't do anything
to help us out.
It was as if
I didn't participate but...
And he's off.
Jong Kook,
I doubt you'll get your turn.
His feet are light.
That's what I'm talking about.
His running is different from ours.
He keeps his mouth shut.
- He just breathes through his nose.
- Right.
He must not be out of breath.
He might be able
to run for two hours.
- Five, four.
- Four.
- Three, two, one.
- You can step down.
- Nice.
- Stop the treadmill.
This is great.
- Take a deep breath.
- Ready, get set, go.
"Many adore his version the most..."
"due to his deep masculine voice
that warms the heart."
"His version of White Christmas..."
- Gosh.
- What?
(Stops to take a breath)
- Did he take a breath?
- What on earth?
- That's fine though.
- It sounded so lifeless.
- It sounded soulless.
- Jang Dong Min!
(The Jang Dong Min of Yeongdeungpo
couldn't hold his breath.)
- Did you hear his tone?
- His running was on point.
- I should've read some more.
- Se Chan could finish this.
Okay.
- Se Chan, end it for us.
- Go, Ssaebssaeb.
There's no need for me to run too.
Se Chan's the worst
at reading though.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
That could be an issue.
Hold on. So Min, look.
- Doesn't this impress you?
- You look good, Se Chan!
- Doesn't he look cool?
- You're so handsome!
How manly of you.
- Right.
- Here we go.
Five, four, three,
two, one. Stop.
- Okay.
- Ready, get set, go.
"Became the top-selling single
of all time..."
"earning it a spot
on the 2008 Guinness World Records."
(Mission complete)
- Gosh.
- Okay!
- Good.
- Nicely done.
- All right.
- Jong Kook didn't have to compete.
- Okay!
- Nice.
You can count Suk Jin out too.
We managed it without
having me or Suk Jin compete.
It's all thanks to So Min.
She won it for us.
So Min, you did so well.
- You were incredible.
- Nicely done.
- It's not gratifying though.
- Thanks, So Min.
I'm not too happy with that.
You managed it on your first try,
so no presents will get taken away.
(No presents will be taken away.)
How will we give out the gifts?
The citizens
who participated in the mission...
will receive the presents
that you chose.
Please pick out a number.
- The numbers...
- Please step forward.
There are a lot of presents...
that will be worth taking home.
- There's...
- There's alcohol.
- Alcohol?
- One that's worth 270 dollars.
It's whiskey, right?
That's right.
One of them is whiskey.
It'd be amazing if you get it.
- Do you have a child?
- Yes.
Well, then...
- Do you have a daughter?
- Yes.
- There are many items for her.
- It's perfect.
- We got many gifts for children.
- Jae Suk's is...
Is it a raffle?
- Here we go.
- Let's go for it.
- That's how they draw it.
- Okay.
- There's a lot.
- Pick one each.
- I hope they get good ones.
- If they get Royal Salute...
It's 27.
- Nice.
- Mine is good as well.
(What will they choose
out of 46 gifts?)
- What's the number?
- It's 31.
Give us gift number 31.
- Number 31.
- Number 31 is...
a dog plushie So Min got.
Thank you.
(The first gift is quite cute.)
(Thank you.)
- It's for your daughter.
- Yes.
- You can give it to your child.
- There's a handle on the back.
That's cute.
Put it...
- Thank you.
- next to your child...
on the bed to keep her from falling.
So that she won't fall.
Wash it before giving it to her.
Now, the gym trainer.
- I got 26.
- It's 26.
Okay. Number 26.
What is it?
Congratulations. You'll get two
volumes of comic books Jae Suk got.
(Jae Suk's
2 volumes of comic books)
- Thank you.
- It's...
- I like comic books.
- It's what Ji Ho likes.
Ji Ho likes this.
- Take a selfie with me,
- Okay.
holding the books.
I have a nephew.
- He'd like it.
- Yes.
He's still eight months old.
If he's eight months old...
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- It's a nice gift for a child.
- Let's take a photo quickly.
You might start feeling hungry now.
- Yes.
- Let's go and eat.
- Okay.
- All right.
Where are we going?
- We're there.
- Okay.
Be careful not to let
his feet touch the ground.
- Oh, right.
I got it.
All right.
(Ji-dolph is here in Yeouido.)
Come out.
Yes, I'm Ji Suk Jin.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Be happy.
- Can I take a picture?
- Sure.
- My goodness.
- Yes. A peace sign.
- Hello.
- Oh, my gosh.
My goodness.
- Oh, gosh.
- Do we have to take out the gifts?
- Yes.
- We should carry them on our backs.
Wait.
We should take out the gifts too.
Let's go.
Guys, this is Jong Kook.
(Making a fuss)
Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is getting off.
- Guys, Jae Suk is here.
- Hi.
- Hello.
You say something nice to them.
What nice thing?
- Are you sick?
- Hello.
- No, I'm not sick.
- It's a mission.
She asked me if I was sick.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
- Let's go.
- We should go.
- Bye.
- Take care.
This is a hotel.
You're right.
- Yes.
- For hungry Santa and Rudolphs,
- It's done.
- we prepared a fancy hotel buffet.
Jae Suk.
- Yes.
- You should eat what we give you.
Right. You should give me the food.
- I want to walk.
- It's great many people like us.
This is the best buffet...
that is fully booked
during the Christmas season.
(It's filled with various delicacies
the members like.)
Hotels have the best Christmas vibes
as expected.
Yes. Hotels are the best.
- I love this kind of buffet.
- I've never been here.
I've never been to this place.
This is nice.
So Min, let's have snow crabs.
It sounds good. There's salmon.
Oh, my.
Where should we let Jae Suk sit?
Let him sit here.
- Santa.
- This place is so nice.
Jong Kook carried him.
- This is great.
- Good job, Jong Kook.
No worries.
Precious Jae Suk...
Jong Kook must be sweating now.
It's good for both. You don't have
to walk and you get to exercise.
The one who is carrying is tired,
but the one who is carried is...
- Right. It's tiring.
- You should strain your body.
- I should strain my arms.
- It's tiring.
- It's very tiring.
You can forget
about the mission here.
As long as your feet
don't touch the ground.
You can enjoy it freely.
- You told me to forget.
- We'll get the food for you.
- We'll get what you want.
- All right.
- We know what you like.
- Don't get too much food.
- Ssaebssaeb, you know what I like.
- Yes, I know.
- A little bit of many things.
- We'll be back.
- Yes. See you.
This is very heart-warming
at the end of the year.
Coming all the way here,
it's too harsh to ask me
to stay seated.
- The buffet is nice.
- It looks incredible.
- There's so much food.
- I know. I don't know what to get.
There's a lot of food here.
- It's lamb, isn't it?
- Yes.
One for Jae Suk.
Jae Suk doesn't like it.
It's lobster.
(The lobsters are full of meat.)
There's a lot of delicious food.
Where is protein?
I think there would be steak.
It looks delicious.
Should I try one of each thing?
Is that it?
- It's for Jae Suk.
- For Jae Suk?
- Take that and... Come here.
- Yes.
Should I get something that's not
easy to eat? Like crabs?
Get him crabs.
- Jae Suk doesn't like crabs.
- I'll get shrimps and crabs.
Get shrimps too.
This one and this one.
It's what Jae Suk hates the most.
Good. That looks good.
- Give it to him.
- Yes.
You're a very muscular Rudolph.
- Right? The headband is...
- Are you the server here?
- Yes.
- I see.
Do you like it?
- No, you eat it.
- There's too much protein, right?
- Yes. It looks too dry.
- It's mine.
I always eat like this at a buffet.
- Do you eat like this?
- Yes.
- They'll get you coffee...
- There's so much nice food.
when you ask at the table.
There are so many kinds.
I need to know
what they have to get...
- Jae Suk.
- Come here.
I need to know
what they have to get... Jae Suk.
(Realizing)
- Come here.
- Why?
- I don't like peeling those.
- Just eat.
You gave this to me on purpose,
didn't you?
- No.
- You're telling me to walk.
(You're telling me to walk.)
No. That's your favorite.
I can't eat this.
- Why not?
- I don't like peeling.
I might run out. For real.
(He's about to go off,
seeing the shellfish.)
- Hey.
- Let's not provoke him.
- Right. Don't provoke me.
- I'll give you a piggyback ride.
- Do you want to get what you want?
- Yes. Carry him around.
- Can you show me around?
- Okay.
Se Chan, follow us.
- If he points at the food...
- No, you do it. I'll eat.
I mean we can't get the food.
He wants to film footage
for the show and you're saying no?
Right. I want to film it
for the show.
- So Min, you...
- Yes.
- Can you carry him on your back?
- I'll carry him.
- Are you okay?
- In 1, 2.
My gosh.
(Staggering)
- My goodness.
- So Min.
- Who didn't eat? Come here.
- I'll go.
- I'll pick the food.
- If he points at the food...
(Wearing the gloves slowly)
So Min, can you put them on quickly?
- Let's go.
- Gosh.
- The mask.
- Don't we have to wear masks?
We should wear masks.
- My mask is over there.
- So Min. Put a mask on him.
The lamb is really good.
Put it in the middle
so that we can share it.
(Let's go now!)
- Hold on. The mask.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
- My goodness.
- Jae Suk has started it.
- Don't choke me.
- I should wear a mask.
- My gosh.
(He used half of his energy
even before getting near the food.)
Go.
Go, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin is in good condition today.
Seriously, why...
Why are you giving me
such a hard time?
I should see what they have.
- Hello.
- Hello. Pick the food.
Suk Jin, put me up a little.
There you go.
- Be careful.
- The food is here.
Short ribs.
- Webfoot octopus.
- So Min.
Can you get some webfoot octopus?
- Don't choke me.
- All right.
- Lobster.
- I don't want lobster.
- Can you get the lobster?
- Never mind.
- No.
- I'll eat it.
- You can get it later.
- Put it on the plate.
- We don't have time now.
- I'll get what Jae Suk wants now.
Hello. The kimchi jeon.
Can you get two?
(He gets webfoot octopus and kimchi
jeon instead of lobster and beef.)
- Two pieces of kimchi jeon.
- Who gets kimchi jeon at a buffet?
That's enough, So Min.
- Who has kimchi jeon at a buffet?
- Suk Jin. That's what I want.
You should get something nice.
- Can you get pumpkin jeon?
- Pumpkin jeon?
- Why would you...
- Thank you, So Min.
I don't need soy sauce.
- So Min, get some fritters.
- How many times...
What kind of fritter?
So Min, can you get fish and chips?
Sure. I almost dropped it.
- Let's go now. Where should we go?
- This way.
- Let's go now. Hurry up.
- So Min.
Can you get some eggplant for me?
Why would you get eggplant
at a buffet?
Why would you...
- I just need two pieces.
- get eggplant at a buffet?
- That's all good now.
- So Min, hurry up. I'm tired.
- That's enough.
- I'm about to faint.
(He's groggy.)
We should take a look
at the left side as well.
This is...
("I Might Disappear" by Jukjae)
- Let's do this.
- So Min. Right. The spaghetti.
(It's a perfect song
for this situation.)
Don't go down.
- So Min. You should switch.
- Don't go down.
- What's the matter?
- What is it?
- He can't carry me.
You got this.
It's good. Go.
Why did you say you would do this?
- What is he doing?
- You do it.
What is he doing?
(Tilting)
- What's wrong?
- I'm so tired.
- Why are you tired?
- It wasn't even a long time.
- Why do you have no energy?
- Seriously.
Why did you volunteer?
I'm so tired.
- This is delicious.
- The kimchi jeon is good.
Why is he eating kimchi jeon
and pumpkin jeon at a buffet?
- What's wrong with it?
- I'll enjoy the food.
You need to get something like this
if you think about the price.
Why do you get lamb only?
This is so good.
It's incredible.
Once you acquire the taste of lamb,
you can't resist it.
Ssaeb, eat this.
He's not eating this. Let's eat it.
- Jae Suk is not eating it.
- Right.
Thank you.
(Crunchy)
This is delicious.
We couldn't have a meal together
at the end of the year.
- But they gave us the opportunity.
- Right.
- It really feels like Christmas.
- Yes.
- Can I take the plates?
- Can you?
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
Can you take my plates too?
What are you doing on Christmas?
I'm busy on Christmas too.
That's good.
- Right. Tell him to pick a gift.
- You can pick a gift.
Yes. What are you doing
on Christmas?
(Asking the staff member behind him)
You'll be working, right?
- Then come here. This is good.
- Oh, my.
- This is good.
- I hope they get good ones.
- I'm Santa today.
- There are gifts for you.
And they are Rudolphs.
We have...
bluetooth earphones.
Pajamas for couples too.
- What's your name?
- I hope they get nice ones.
I'm Lee Han Bi.
- Miss Han Bi.
- Yes.
- You can pick one.
- You need luck.
- You quiz?
I hope she picks a nice one.
- What would you like to get?
- Your choice?
Bluetooth earphones?
- I got that.
- What number did you pick?
(What present will go
to the hardworking staff?)
- It's number 9.
- Number 9.
- What's number 9?
- I hope it's a good one.
- Whose is it?
- What is it?
- Congratulations.
You'll get chestnut sweet potatoes
that Ji Hyo got.
(Number 9 chestnut sweet potatoes)
- Would that be okay?
- I'm sorry.
- I don't think she's happy.
- Why did you get that?
- Is that all right?
- Yes, it's all right.
- Oh, dear.
- But Ji Hyo.
- Sweet potatoes are fine...
- It wasn't supposed to be that.
- Sweet potatoes are fine.
- What's your name?
- She likes it, fortunately.
Mr. Dae Hee.
- You can also pick one.
- He will pick.
I wanted Miss Han Bi
to choose a nice one.
- I like it.
- Mr. Dae Hee.
- It's number 45.
- Number 45.
- Number 45?
- I think it will be a nice one.
You will get a large Nike bag
that So Min got.
That's a nice one.
How nice for Mr. Dae Hee
and Miss Han Bi.
It's this one.
- It's not much, but So Min got it.
- Yes, it's not much.
That's for...
- Miss Han Bi.
- Choose one more.
- No, it's all right.
- Sweet potatoes are nice, but...
there are some more nice things
prepared.
(Will it be a nice present
this time?)
- It's number 43.
- Number 43. That sounds good.
Number 43 is a gift
that Haha prepared.
- His gifts are bad.
- Pebbles for fish tanks.
(It's a gift of stones.)
(The hermit crab is out.)
- I like it.
- No, it's not nice.
- I'm sorry.
- Just one more.
- Pick just one more time.
- Sorry, I didn't get it as a gift.
- Why did you get pebbles?
I got it because I needed it.
- Pick one more.
- I'm really sorry.
- Should I pick now?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
- Seriously.
But I'm glad Mr. Dae Hee got a bag.
- I hope you can use it.
- Do you like it?
- It's number 34.
- Number 34.
Please.
Number 34...
Please let it be a nice one.
is a gift that Jae Suk got.
- What is it?
- His gifts are all useless.
- They're all children's gifts.
- It's a 3D sticker maker.
It's okay.
Stick them on your phone.
- It's nice.
- It's pretty.
- You can make stickers with it.
- It's nice.
- It's pretty.
- Do you really like it?
- I like it.
- You've never bought it before.
It's cute.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Merry Christmas.
I really needed the fish tank sand.
- Then...
- It's number three.
- It's a good one.
- Number three.
You get knee pads...
that Jong Kook got.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- It's better than toys.
- Congratulations.
It's a little disappointing.
- This...
- You have to lie down.
- It's like a crib.
- You're like a baby.
- What's that.
- Hello.
Merry Christmas.
Jae Suk isn't ill or anything.
It's a mission.
He isn't sick.
- A drone is up too.
- We're just carrying him.
- Our Santa is being carried.
- A drone is filming us.
I never thought I'd cross
the crosswalk while lying down.
- Nice.
- It must be nice.
This is very nice.
Look at that.
This is Yoo Jae Suk.
Don't do that.
Jae Suk.
Peekaboo.
Jeon So Min.
You'll be a good mom.
Peekaboo.
If you can do that all day,
I'll approve.
You'll raise a baby well.
He's like a baby.
It's right there. We're here.
- Hello.
- Merry Christmas.
Have a wonderful day.
- We're being welcomed.
- Hello.
- Merry Christmas.
- Don't walk, but run.
- Are we doing something here?
- I'm lying down.
Sorry I'm greeting you while
lying down. I should wear a mask.
- It's right here.
- Anyway,
we're doing something here.
Stay like that. Keep lying down.
Shoot while lying down.
I've been on TV for a long time,
but I've never been so comfortable
while moving to another place.
I was in a crib.
- It looks very comfortable.
- Is it perfect for you?
- It's perfect.
- It's perfect?
- It looked comfortable.
- It's the best.
The second mission is
Initial Consonant Quiz on Christmas.
Two citizens and Running Man members
will work together...
and respond with the right word...
from the initial consonant
under the given keyword.
I can do this well.
You succeed if nine of you,
including two citizens,
get the answer right continuously.
- Good.
- Okay.
As you've seen earlier,
we will make this.
We make things work.
- The MZ generation is good at this.
- That's right.
- We can do this.
- It's easy for us.
You can invite two citizens
who will join the mission.
Two people?
Who is good
at initial consonant game?
- Initial consonant game.
- Anyone good at it?
Who is good
at initial consonant game?
- Someone is coming.
Are you good at it?
You can come.
- But...
- Are you good at the game?
I'm good at it.
Have you ever played
the initial consonant game?
- One more person.
- What's PY?
- Sorry?
- PY.
Please wait.
Please wait?
- Find someone good at it.
- Prayer.
Is there a penalty
if I don't do well?
- You should do well.
- If you don't do well,
you have to lie down and get hit.
You have to get hit by me.
(The nightmare of Christmas)
- What's your name?
- Kim Ah Reum.
- Ah Reum.
- Ah Reum is here.
- She's an MZ generation.
- An MZ.
You're an MZ generation?
- MZ.
- Are you an MZ generation?
- She is.
- Nice.
- Great. She is an MZ generation.
- She is an MZ generation.
- You know how to do this.
- She is.
She is an MZ generation.
Are you an MZ generation?
Okay.
What's your name?
My name is Ah Reum.
- Ah Reum.
- Her tone says she's an MZ.
Ah Reum.
- What's your name?
- Oh Jung Hoon.
- Jung Hoon.
- Okay.
- Jung Hoon. Okay.
It's like I'm at their wedding,
- and I'm officiating.
- Are you the officiant?
Okay.
If you get it wrong,
- we'll remove one gift immediately.
- Okay.
- I want to get it.
- We give you gifts if you do this.
- They're nice gifts.
- Do you want to get a gift?
We have one Royal Salute left.
I want someone to take that.
- Royal Salute?
- Yes.
- We'll start from the left.
- Will you change the order?
- You can change places.
- Would you like to start?
- That's nice.
- Okay.
Would that be all right?
- You can try.
- Try it.
- You said you're good at the game.
- You can try.
He wasn't good.
Ready, start. Three,
(Living thing, WM)
- two.
- Watermelon.
- It's a living thing.
- It's correct.
It grows from the ground.
- It grows.
- It's correct.
- But it has no life.
- Then what is this?
- It grows from the ground.
How does something grow so big
if it doesn't have life?
It grows because it's alive.
- It's alive.
- It should breathe.
It grows up because it breathes.
Aren't plants alive?
I'll remove a gift.
They're too strict.
- I can't think of anything.
- Number 36.
- It's the luggage bag.
Oh, dear.
You said you're good.
- You can start.
- You can do it.
- Okay. I'll start.
- I'll start, then.
- It's difficult.
- I'll go again.
- Good luck, Haha.
- Let's collaborate.
- One, two, three.
Three, two,
- one.
- Jelly.
(Living thing, TT)
- One.
- Jelly.
- It's a turtle.
- Turtle.
- Why are you swearing?
- Turtle!
- You said you're good.
- Come out.
- Turtle.
I'll remove one gift.
A black trouser that Jong Kook got
will be removed.
What a waste.
- Jong Kook.
- That's a comfortable one.
I've not spoken yet.
- Try. Give it a go.
- I'll start. Let me go.
This has wheels.
- This is scary.
- Okay.
Okay. Let's go.
Good luck!
- Good luck!
One, two, three.
Three, two, one.
It's a Shiba dog.
- Shiba dog.
- I can only think of bad words.
- It's so difficult.
I'm sorry, but only bad words
come to mind.
Why are all the words like that?
I only thought of bad words.
This is driving me crazy.
I'll start.
- Okay.
- I'll start.
- Start.
- Three.
- Pepper.
- That's right.
- Let's give them gifts.
- Start.
- Three, two,
- Mushroom.
- one.
- Stop.
- Start.
Go on.
Three, two, one.
(Living thing, SB)
(Whatever.)
I mean...
- So Min.
- But...
- We're being recorded.
- What else is there?
- What other word is there?
- They're all recording.
But it's not watermelon.
- What was it earlier?
- Watermelon.
SinB.
There's SinB of GFRIEND.
- SinB.
- SinB of GFRIEND.
- We'll start with Suk Jin.
- I'll go first.
- Seok Sam.
- It will end with Haha.
Shall we succeed it?
I'll get it right. I'll start.
- Okay.
- Could you cheer for me?
- Good luck!
- Cheer for me, please.
Good luck.
- Good luck.
- Go on.
- Let's go.
- One, two, three.
One, two,
Good job.
(It's a poor answer
compared to the cheers he got.)
- Sam Kim.
- What's "good job?"
What living thing is there?
- Sam Kim!
- Sam Kim.
We should think of people's names
first.
- We should think of people's names.
- Suk Jin,
- there's a way to play this game.
- I know now.
Think of people's names first.
You realized it just now too.
What?
We got to know now.
I'll remove number 24,
the fish tank set.
That's mine.
- Se Chan can start.
- Let's start from Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
- Count the numbers slowly.
- One, two, three, and go.
- Three.
Start.
- One,
- Go Soo.
- That's right.
- Right.
That was great.
- The question is...
- It's Jung Hoon.
One, two,
BE'O. The singer.
- BE'O.
- Okay.
- Singer BE'O.
- Good.
- BE'O.
- It's So Min.
One, two,
- Frog!
- Okay.
You got a good one.
- One, two, three.
- She's an MZ generation.
Three, two,
- Bibimbap.
- Okay.
- I thought of Bibibik.
- Good.
Good job.
- It's me. I'm so nervous.
- Go on.
Ah Reum will be the last.
- It's here.
- Ah Reum will be the last.
Three, two,
Stingray.
- Gosh.
- What was that?
- Stingray.
- Gosh.
- Cat.
- You didn't know, honestly.
- You didn't know.
- Couldn't you tell?
He didn't know either.
- I'm allergic to cats.
- He didn't know.
- But it's a cat.
- It's Haha's gift.
What's removed?
What?
- Is the liquor out?
- What is it?
- Liquor.
- Johnnie Walker.
- My goodness, one liquor is out.
- It's a nice present.
One liquor remains.
- This won't do.
- Should I go first?
- In that case...
- Give it a go.
- I will give it a go.
- Okay.
- He became confident.
- I got this.
- Okay.
- Let's begin.
One, two,
- three.
- Obangtteok.
Obangtteok.
- Obama.
- Where did "Obangtteok" come from?
Don't do it. You should go last.
- Obangtteok.
And obangtteok isn't alive either.
Obangtteok is food.
- Seriously.
- Were you that nervous?
He embarrassed himself.
Why are you so intimidated?
- This is driving me crazy.
- All right.
- It's so hard.
- I will give you an easy one.
- Give us an easy one.
- Is there an easy one? Okay.
- Suk Jin.
- It's an easy one.
- Suk Jin, let's go.
- Let's go.
Let's begin.
Three, two...
- Momo.
- Momo of TWICE.
- Momo is correct.
- Good job.
- You did a good job.
- Momo of TWICE.
- Let's go.
Let's begin.
Three, two...
Jaws. Juice.
- Juice.
- Juice works.
- Juice, not jaws.
- Let's go.
- Let's begin.
- Three, two, one.
- Meat-ri.
It's "Frog."
(Incorrect)
Three, two, one.
Meat-ri.
It's "Frog."
- Frog.
- What on earth is "Meat-ri?"
- We had it earlier.
- He is bad at this.
- Boo.
- Hey.
What was that?
Why did you do that?
- Again?
- "Goguri?"
- Why did you do that? It's "Frog."
- I am sorry.
- I see that Jae Suk is popular.
- We had "Frog" earlier.
You know,
it drives me insane
that Suk Jin asked people...
- to boo at me.
- I realized...
that you are popular.
They didn't boo at you.
My goodness.
- This is so hard.
- They didn't boo at you.
- Go ahead.
- Frog.
- Four, five...
- It's... What's this?
- One.
- Willow.
- Park Gi Rin.
- What?
- Five.
- Mushroom stew.
- One.
- Chocho?
- It's "Tuna."
We did "Tuna" earlier.
- Tuna.
- This is so embarrassing.
- It's over.
We are out of questions.
- However,
- It's okay.
- we will give a present...
- It wasn't half bad.
- to the citizens who joined us.
- Okay.
- Please pick a number.
So we didn't succeed in completing
the mission.
- It feels awkward.
- You should aim for number 21.
- Number 21?
- Number 21.
"Miracle in Cell No. 21."
- It's number 12.
- Number 12.
- The numbers are the opposite.
- Number 12. Congratulations.
You got a pair of black sweatpants
Jong Kook picked.
(Black sweatpants)
They aren't half bad.
- Wear them to bed.
- They aren't half bad.
- She likes them.
- Didn't he take them out earlier?
- They aren't half bad.
- I feel sleepy already.
Didn't he take them out earlier?
- They are pretty nice, right?
- He bought four pairs.
- They are comfortable.
- Four pairs?
- They are comfortable and nice.
- I asked them,
"Didn't he take them out earlier?"
- Apparently, he bought 4 pairs.
- Did he buy 4 pairs?
- He said he will take them out.
- Why did you take out three pairs?
They were different.
- Four pairs of black pants.
- They were different.
Congratulations.
You got the item Jae Suk picked,
- the talking Heartsping.
- What?
Kids love it.
- It's cute.
- Na Eun loves it.
It's cute.
Jung Hoon, would you sell it to me?
Na Eun loves it.
- They worked hard.
- The citizens joined us...
for the second mission.
- Thank you.
- Take care, Jung Hoon.
- Enjoy the pants.
- Be happy.
- The talking Heartsping is cute.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- My goodness.
You failed to complete
the second mission.
- Now, 24 presents remain.
- Are there any presents left?
We still have many presents.
I didn't know
we were so bad at games.
It was hard.
You did much worse than us.
- You messed it up.
- You got five questions wrong.
- What's "Chocho?"
- I don't know.
- I don't remember.
- You messed it up.
- I don't know why I said "Chocho."
- Why couldn't I think of "Tuna?"
- What was "Meat-ri?"
- Jae Suk messed it up.
- Meat-ri.
- Meat-ri...
- The last location is inside.
- Shall we go?
Is it inside? Let's go.
- We should put on a mask.
- Sit down.
Everyone, merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
- Thank you. Be happy.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Bye.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- This is a nice department store.
- It's really big.
- Hello.
(They begin to stroll around
with Jae Suk in a kid's wagon.)
People will think
that Jae Suk is sick.
Jae Suk isn't sick.
There is no need to say that.
- Jae Suk isn't sick.
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, for goodness' sake.
- I want to clear up...
- There is no need to say that.
- any misunderstandings.
- Look. This place is incredible.
Is it an amusement park?
- Is this the location?
- It's so pretty.
Is it an amusement park?
It's so pretty.
It really feels like Christmas.
Ji Hyo, it's so pretty.
(The Christmas village in Yeouido
is popular on social media.)
(There is a fancy Christmas tree
of an enormous size too.)
- It's insane.
- This is cool.
(Santa Yoo and the six Rudolphs
arrive at the fairy tale village.)
This department store is amazing.
(So Min goes wide-eyed.)
It's a teddy bear.
What's this? It's sleeping.
Are you sleeping?
It's sleeping. It looks real. Hello.
Gosh, what's this?
I feel like I am in "Home Alone."
(The Christmas vibe excites
even the cool-blooded Jong Kook.)
It's pretty.
- Isn't it fascinating?
- It's cute.
It's fascinating.
It's so nice.
(Jong Kook is filming.)
- It's so pretty.
- It's pretty.
Move out of the way.
(So Min entered
Jong Kook's camera angle.)
Take photos of me, Jong Kook.
(Take photos of me, Jong Kook.)
- It's so pretty.
- All set.
Thank you.
- I trust you. You take nice photos.
- I will help you.
Se Chan takes bad photos.
I am moved to tears.
It's so pretty.
Look at So Min.
Ji Hyo doesn't disappoint.
- She is calm.
(Ji Hyo looks around calmly.)
- It's so pretty.
- I don't have that sentimentality.
No, you don't.
One, two, three.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
I feel so touched.
- You have 23 presents left.
- Yes.
The last mission that will decide
the fate of the presents is...
the As Many as You Can Jegichagi.
- What's that?
- Jegichagi.
- Jegichagi?
- I am bad at it.
The rules are simple.
Recruit two citizens...
- and kick it a total of 80 times.
- A total of 80 times.
- Okay.
You will be given three chances.
If you succeed at once,
you can give away
all the remaining presents.
With each failed attempt,
we will take out three presents.
Okay.
Since this mission involves
the feet,
Jae Suk's feet
can touch the ground.
- Can I get off the wagon now?
- Yes.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
- There we go.
- You feel comfortable, right?
- Recruit two citizens.
- Rudolphs, get to work.
- Okay.
So Min, let's go.
(Galloping)
Give me a mask.
- Who is good at jegichagi?
- By any chance...
- Are you good at jegichagi?
- Jegichagi.
- Me.
- Are you good at it?
- How many times can you kick it?
- About 20 times.
- Okay. Come here.
- Who is good at it?
- Here.
- Come here. We are set.
- All right.
- Hello.
- Hello. Please come this way.
Hello. Please come this way.
Are you good at jegichagi?
A little bit.
- Okay.
We got Generation MZs.
What's your name?
My name is Cho Bak Seung.
- Bak Seung. How about you?
- Yes.
- My name is Song Sang Won.
- Sang Won.
Shouldn't they practice?
Kick the jegi.
- Let's see how good you are.
- Okay.
- Good.
- He is the real deal.
- He knows how it's done.
My goodness.
- Hold on.
- Get out.
(What?)
- Hold on.
- Get out.
- Hey.
- When was the last time you did it?
- What was that?
- Less than a month ago.
- Really?
- Try it again.
- There was a competition at work.
- Was there a competition?
- Try it again.
- Maybe you are nervous.
- It's plausible.
He did badly for someone
who entered a competition.
How well did you do
at the competition?
I kicked it about 15 times.
He did pretty well.
- One.
- What?
Bak Seung, what was that?
- We need to talk.
- Oh, you are Bak Seung.
- Bak Seung, give it a go.
- I am under so much pressure.
- You can't do it well.
- The left foot.
- For goodness' sake.
- Bak Seung.
- What's up with you guys?
- Get out.
- How old are you guys?
- Hurry up and get out.
- Who recruited them?
- What was that?
They are really bad at this.
- Since they are here...
- It can't be helped.
- Really?
Meat-ri will do well.
I am in good condition today.
(Practice time earlier)
- Two.
- You are in good condition today.
- He is on fire.
- He is stable.
- Good, Meat-ri.
- We are set.
- Meat-ri has the skills.
- He is on fire.
- We are set today.
- Santa will give out presents.
- Let's bring our hands together.
- Let's go.
- One, two, three. Let's go.
- Up or down?
- Please begin the first attempt.
- Who will go first?
- Among us...
- I will go first.
- Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- Just do two.
- Two.
Hairtail, do five.
Hairtail.
- I will kick it when it comes down.
- Okay.
- One, two.
- There you go. Two.
- Two.
- All right. Two is a good record.
- Good.
- I kicked it two times.
- Kick it as you did earlier.
- You did 4 earlier.
- I usually can't do 4.
- Kick it as you did earlier.
- You did four earlier.
Then today will be
her day of success.
I usually can't do four.
Don't disturb her.
- One, two.
- Two.
- The total is four.
- Two is a good record.
- Suk Jin.
- Should I go next?
- I can't kick it.
- It's hard.
If you catch it, you can start over.
- Okay.
- I should have done that.
Jae Suk is in good condition today.
- I am in good condition today.
- You should kick it 50 times.
I am in good condition today.
- Suk Jin.
- Kick it over ten times each.
- You are wearing good shoes for it.
- Pull up your pants.
- Should I pull them up?
- Pull them up. There you go.
- I won't get nervous.
- Pull up your pants more.
Pull up your pants more.
- There you go.
- They are up here.
- That's good.
- You are set.
Just take off your pants, Suk Jin.
Okay.
(Number 3, Suk Jin, Total)
You caught it.
(He caught it!)
- He caught it.
- Good job.
Good job.
- He caught it.
- Good job.
- This is nerve-racking.
- Go ahead.
- Relax.
- He must be under pressure.
Two, three, four.
- Catch it.
- You got this.
- Suk Jin.
- Catch it.
- He was doing well.
- No, he was in danger.
- He needs to do ten or more.
- He did well to catch it.
- Suk Jin,
you look a bit like a man
who works at a circus.
- You are right.
- I...
- A man who works at a circus.
- This is...
I want to succeed in it.
How many do you want to do?
- Ten.
- You were like Son Yeon Jae.
- You need to kick it ten times.
- You are like a rhythmic gymnast.
(Number 3, Suk Jin, Total)
- That's good.
- He is relaxed.
- Four, five,
- He got this.
- six, seven...
- He got his.
- Eight.
- Eight. Okay.
- Your total is 12.
A total of 12 is too...
- Give it a go. We have three tries.
- Yes.
- Bak Seung.
- Should I go first?
- Yes.
- Bak Seung, please do well.
- Okay.
(Number 4, Bak Seung: 0, Total: 12)
You got this.
- There you go.
- Five.
- Five. Okay.
- Okay.
- This is bad.
I will go next.
(Number 5, Jong Kook: 0, Total: 17)
One, two, three, four.
- Hey.
- Four.
- That was too bad.
I did so well during practice.
Why did I kick it four times?
- I will go first.
- Haha.
(Number 6, Haha: 0, Total: 21)
- One, two.
- Catch it.
(Number 6, Haha: 2, Total: 23)
- Haha.
- Two.
(He tied with So Min.)
What's up with you today?
Do you want to go next?
- Go next.
- Give it a go.
Look. He pulled his sock
over his hem.
- Okay. You are set.
- I can see it.
- Good.
- Do what you did...
at the competition.
Do more than five.
Kick it 15 times. Counting 1...
(Number 7, Sang Won: 2, Total: 25)
- My goodness.
- Hey.
No. This one is better.
That one is bad.
- That one is bad.
- You need to say, "Here I go."
- Why are you so nervous?
- Did you say, "Here I go?"
- "Here I go."
- You didn't, right?
- I didn't say it.
- You need to say it.
- Say, "Here I go."
- That one is bad.
- Two, three. "Here I go."
- Here I go.
(The citizens
are allowed to try again.)
(Number 7, Sang Won: 0, Total: 23)
- Good. He got this.
- Yes. This one is more stable.
- Five, six,
- The previous one was faulty.
- seven, eight, nine,
- Good.
- ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen,
- Eleven, twelve, thirteen,
- fourteen, fifteen, sixteen,
- seventeen, eighteen...
- Okay.
- That was incredible.
(He kicked it 19 times.)
Good job.
- We are set.
- There you go.
- This one is faulty. Don't use it.
- We are set.
We are set. It's game over.
You did so well.
- Good.
- How many people remain?
- Let's go.
- A round of applause.
- Se Chan, let's go.
You look dandy today.
You need to kick it 20 times.
- One, two, three, four.
- Two, three, four.
- Catch it.
- Okay.
Good job.
- The tassel is falling apart.
- Hey.
- Is it balding?
- It's balding.
- How hard did you pull it?
- Give me a new one.
- This one would be better.
- Okay.
- It's falling apart.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Here I go.
- Go ahead.
- One, two, three, four,
- My goodness.
- five, six, seven, eight.
- You are good.
(Number 8, Se Chan: 8, Total: 50)
- I did my best.
- Good job.
- Your total is 50.
- Did you say 50?
- Do I need to kick it 30 times?
- That's right.
It won't work.
- Here I go.
- Let's go.
- How many do you need to do?
- Thirty.
- You can do it. Perform a miracle.
- Here I go.
If he gets the hang of it,
- he will be able to do it.
- That's right.
Just get into the flow.
(He threw it in the air.)
- One, two, three, four,
- Three, four...
- five, six, seven, eight,
- He is doing well.
nine, ten,
- eleven, twelve, thirteen,
- Eleven, twelve, thirteen...
- fourteen, fifteen,
- He is good.
- sixteen, seventeen,
- Sixteen, seventeen,
- eighteen, nineteen, twenty,
- Good.
- twenty-one, twenty-two,
- twenty-three, twenty-four...
- That's good.
(Number 9, Jae Suk: 24, Total: 74)
(Will he be able to kick it
30 times?)
Twenty-five.
- So close.
- He kicked it so well.
- Gosh, it was so close.
- You saw that, right?
- We only had five more to go.
- It was so close.
- In that case,
- I should have done five more.
three presents will be taken out.
Then you can begin the second try.
- Okay.
- Take out three presents.
- Let's do it again.
- Okay.
I came close to kicking it 30 times.
- You came so close.
- Numbers 6, 15, and 38 are out.
- Let's go.
- Se Chan.
- Let me give it a go.
- Se Chan, what's that?
(Se Chan borrowed a shoe
from somewhere.)
- Se Chan, what's that on your foot?
- One.
What's that on your foot?
My goodness.
His skills improved with a new shoe.
- We are set.
- Good.
- We are set. There you go.
- We are set.
- Good.
- Kick it like that.
- It depends on the shoes.
- Is it yours?
- We are set.
- It depends on the shoes.
- Let's kick it 80 times.
- Let's go.
- Let's bring our hands together.
One, two, three.
- Let's go.
- I put my hand down.
- Why did you do it by yourself?
Here I go. I will begin.
- One.
- My goodness.
One.
My goodness.
- I am sorry.
- One.
- Can I start over?
- Ji Hyo, it's okay.
- That's right.
- It's okay.
- I am sorry.
So Min can kick it three times.
- Three times?
- So Min.
- Kick it 3 times.
Kick it three times for me.
My instructor told me
to keep my body low.
(Number 2, So Min: 0, Total: 1)
(Number 2, So Min: 1, Total: 2)
- Hey.
- I couldn't do it.
(So Min kicked it once too.)
Get rid of her.
She kept her body low
and kicked elsewhere.
(They have a bad feeling
about the second attempt.)
I keep getting worse.
Here I go.
(Number 3, Suk Jin: 0, Total: 2)
- He got this.
- Three, four,
- five, six...
- He got this.
He got this.
- Don't react. Catch it.
- Go slow.
- Catch it.
- You can kick it.
(Number 3, Suk Jin: 15, Total: 17)
- You kicked it 15 times.
- Okay.
Suk Jin.
- All right.
- Well done.
Let's go. Who wants to go next?
- Haha.
- Let's go.
(Number 4, Sang Won: 0, Total: 17)
You need to practice.
- There you go. Three, four.
- Five.
- It's okay.
- Jong Kook.
- I will do it properly this time.
- I will kick it over 15 times.
- Okay.
(Will they turn the tables
in the second half?)
There is no need to be nervous.
- You got this. Go slow.
- Three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
- nine, ten,
- There you go.
- eleven,
- You will do over fourteen.
twelve, thirteen, fourteen,
- fifteen, sixteen,
- You went over the number.
- seventeen, eighteen, nineteen,
- Good.
- twenty, twenty-one,
- He will kick it 30 times.
twenty-two, twenty-three,
- twenty-four, twenty-five,
- Let's go.
twenty-six, twenty-seven,
twenty-eight,
- twenty-nine, thirty, thirty-one.
- There you go. Good.
All right. Okay.
(Number 5, Jong Kook: 32, Total: 54)
(He kicked it 32 times.)
- Okay.
- Good job.
- Merry Christmas.
- Good.
- We got this.
- You did it.
Thirty-two.
- We are set.
- You are the best.
- Jong Kook kicked it 32 times.
- I focused on it.
- Your total is 54.
Did you say 54?
We are set. We can do it. Let's go.
All right. Let's go.
- Our total is 54.
- We are set.
- One, two,
- There you go.
- three, four, five, six...
- Good.
- It's okay.
- He kicked it six times.
- Good job.
- Okay.
Your total is 60.
You need to kick 20 more times.
- How many people remain?
- Se Chan, can you do it?
- Twenty? Haven't you gone?
- Okay.
- I haven't gone.
- We can do it.
Kick it ten times.
Se Chan's skills improved
with the new shoe.
All right. Se Chan, kick it
more than 20 times.
- Just finish it.
Do it as you always did.
One, two, three, four,
- five, six, seven, eight, nine.
- There you go.
- Nine.
- It's okay.
Who are the remaining members?
- Haha.
- Thank goodness.
- Jae Suk, finish it.
- No, go first.
- Go first.
- Haha, go ahead.
- Good.
- Just kick it three times.
- I think Jae Suk should go first.
- It's okay.
- Two, three,
- All right. He will finish it.
- four, five.
- He got into the flow.
- We are set.
- Just kick it six times.
- Six.
- Jae Suk.
- Here I go.
Finish it neatly.
- There is no way I would fail.
- That's right.
- I kicked it over 20 times.
- But Jae Suk gets nervous.
He should have gone 1st.
Just kick it 6 times.
- It's 6.
- Just kick it 6 times.
- Earlier, you kicked it 25 times.
- You can do it without looking.
Look elsewhere.
Don't get nervous.
One.
(Number 9, Jae Suk: 0, Total: 74)
My goodness.
- You know about my condition.
- Yes, I do.
- I have a condition.
- It's okay.
It's a nerve-racking situation.
- Six.
- You are good.
Okay.
- One, two, three, four...
- Good. Three, four...
- We are set.
- Five.
(Santa Yoo's foot holds
the fate of dozens of presents.)
(What will be the result?)
- three, four...
- Three, four...
- We are set.
- Five.
(Number 9, Jae Suk: 5, Total: 79)
(Number 9, Jae Suk: 6, Total: 80)
- Six. Okay.
- Six, seven, eight,
- nine, ten.
- Okay.
- Catch it.
- Catch it. Twelve.
You are doing well
since you aren't nervous.
- Fifteen.
- Okay.
You succeeded in completing
the mission.
We did it.
How nice. Okay.
- Number 2.
- Pajamas.
- It's a good present.
(The jegichagi soldiers
get a present each.)
Give it to your mother.
I bought it for my mother.
It's nice. It cost 100 dollars.
Number 19.
It's this one.
This one is a bit...
Tell him to pick another one.
It must be a sticker.
I love it.
- I bought it for my daughter.
- I love it.
- I like it.
- Heartsping.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- The two of you, thank you.
Merry Christmas.
Thus, the Christmas Special
came to an end.
Merry Christmas.
I said the 1st shoot of 2023
will be moved up by 10 minutes...
every time Jae Suk's feet...
- touched the ground.
- I forgot about that.
How much did it get moved up?
The usual time is 10 a.m.
The time got moved up by 3 hours,
so we will meet at 7 a.m.
Then I will need to leave home
by 3 a.m.
- I guess 7 a.m. isn't too bad.
- I will need to leave home by 3 a.m.
You will be fine,
but some members visit
the beauty salon beforehand.
Will we meet at 7 a.m.?
Ji Hyo, we will need to leave home
at 3 a.m.
And you can choose one gift each.
Can we do that?
- Yes.
- That sounds nice.
- What is mine?
- Number 32.
Number 32.
- This is number 32.
- This is it.
This is a nice one.
I like it.
A hip sack.
- Gosh.
- Number four.
- It's beef. Nice.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- This is nice.
- Wine glasses.
- That's a good one.
Gosh, this is...
- Hey, Jeon So Min.
- That's mine.
- I bought it. A toilet brush.
- My turn.
- All right. Haha.
- Number 46.
- Olive oil.
- It's olive oil.
- That's nice.
Pick number 21, Se Chan.
- That's what you picked.
- The whiskey.
- We never know.
- You should get what you picked.
The variety deity
might do something for you.
Number 21.
- My gosh.
- I don't think that's number 21.
- What is it?
- Number eight.
- Number eight?
- What is it?
- Pants.
- It's the pants.
- It's your pants.
- How many of these are there?
How many did you buy?
- These pants...
- You can wear them when you sleep.
- The pants...
- They are really warm. Touch them.
- This is scary.
- Aren't they nice?
- The pants keep coming out.
- How many of them are there?
They fit you perfectly.
- I like them.
- It looks perfect. My gosh.
- I'm scared.
- My gosh.
I want
the Secret Jouju sticker book.
(Na Eun's dad wants
a sticker book for his daughter.)
I bet you'll pick number 21.
That's the worst gift for me.
You can give it to him.
- Number 23.
- It's number 23. It's Jordan.
- I bet it's Jouju. It's Jouju.
- My goodness.
- He got it.
- Really?
(He really got it!)
- That's amazing.
- You got a good one.
This is so nice.
My gosh. I can't believe I got this.
I got a good one.
All right. Thanks to you,
the end of the year will be warm.
- Are you sure it's warm?
- It is.
We will give out
the rest of the gifts to citizens.
(The rest of the gifts were
given out to citizens.)
(We thank all the citizens
we met throughout Seoul today.)
You may go home now.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
We will see you on January 1, 2023,
at 6:20 p.m. Bye.
- Thank you.
- Be happy.
- Merry Christmas.
(December 17, 2022,
the SBS Entertainment Awards)
And we have another reason
to run even harder next year.
Yes, starting on January 1, 2023,
(Starting from next year,
Running Man will air at 6:20 p.m.)
I'll make it
a ferocious battlefield.
(And they prepared a small gathering
to develop a special bond.)
(And the next shoot)
(We have to spend the night here.)
- It's really cold here.
- It's so cold.
(It's a village
where the snow has not melted.)
(A place with a snowstorm?)
(The members arrive at
the ferocious battlefield with ash.)
(I told you
not to put in the newspaper.)
You keep showing off your
experience from "Family Outing."
(Episode 1, Running Man Outing)
(Running Man Family Outing?)
(Cinderella Woo is invited
to the family occasion.)
(Scolded)
(Looking away)
I'll add
the ramyeon soup powder anyway.
(Surprisingly, the three meals
taste just the same!)
(Putting in the whole bag)
(Will the fools be able
to have a decent meal?)
Is the rice ready?
I think we should cook rice again.
(A family is...)
(someone you want to give
your everything to.)
(A family is...)
(is someone to be happy with.)
(When you're
with your family all day...)
(You want to go home.)
(Running Man Outing)