Hello
- Hello.
Gosh, look at you.
We have a thug here.
- Hi, Mr. Thug.
- I like the pavilion.
My goodness.
- I hate summer.
- Hey.
Jong Kook, Haha stole my coffee.
Is he a beggar or what?
Do you like my coffee?
(He stole So Min's coffee
before the shoot.)
Gosh, this is nice.
Drink it and
get out of my sight, Haha.
(Haha steals So Min's coffee,
and she tells on him.)
- My coffee was like...
- She has nothing else to say.
What's the big deal
about some coffee?
You're a witness.
It's not like I just gave it away.
- I hate summer.
- Don't call me before the shoot.
- What?
- I said I hate summer.
- Don't you like summer?
- I hate it.
I like summer
because I can wear light clothes.
- And the laundry dries quickly.
- I see.
So I love summer.
My bag is light
when I go to the gym.
The reason I hate summer is...
- I hate it because it's too hot.
- What's wrong about that?
And I don't like that I sweat a lot.
It's hot because it's summer.
(It's hot because it's summer.)
We never understand each other.
Why not?
I'm not supposed to talk
with him for a long time.
- It's hot because it's summer.
- I should just avoid him.
You know what I mean.
- Jae Suk, and...
- A guy like him...
- I'll give you a tip.
- Don't even try...
- to talk with a guy like him.
- Just come here, Jae Suk.
It will do you no good.
- I'll give you a tip.
- Okay?
- Do you agree?
- In summer...
You don't want to bother
with a guy like him.
- "A guy like him?"
- Hello, Suk Jin!
"A guy like him."
Hey, Seok Sam.
You're here, Mr. Ji.
You're wearing pink shoes.
I know. It's pink.
You don't need the microphone today.
- Today...
- Just come here.
They will use the boom mics,
so you don't have to wear one.
They will?
This is new.
You should just speak loud today.
- Why?
- You don't need a microphone.
You have to talk loud like this.
- You all are wearing one.
- You must be hot.
You all have puppies.
Puppies?
- Are you wearing a school uniform?
- It's a school uniform.
He looks like an elementary
school kid in Japan.
Today, you two look good together.
- Do we look good together?
- Yes.
- I'm hot.
- Hey, you look like his mom.
(You look like his mom!)
- He's an elementary school kid.
- So Min is...
Don't say that to So Min.
It looks like
she's taking you to school.
Don't say she's a mom.
It just looks that way,
don't you think so?
- Just accept it.
- I'm his mom,
- so I can hold his hand, right?
- Yes, take his hand.
Son, come here. My dear son.
There you go.
Pat me on the back.
Move to the back a little.
- It's summer now.
- This is nice. I like the shade.
Do you guys have any vacation plans?
- I don't. I have to work.
- That's ridiculous.
Where would we go?
So we prepared something
for the vacation season.
We will have the
1st Running Man Vacation Service.
- "Vacation service?"
- I saw something...
on our YouTube channel.
- That's what it is.
- Right. We asked our viewers...
- to suggest...
- You should've talked to us first.
Without even telling us,
they post things like that.
- I don't want to go on a vacation.
- Me neither.
It's not like you're doing
what you want to do.
You will try things
that our viewers want to enjoy...
on behalf of them.
- On behalf of our viewers?
- Yes.
- We are like substitutes.
- I see.
We asked our viewers to recommend
things to enjoy on vacation.
And we picked out the ideas
that were realistic enough to try.
We made a roulette with those ideas.
You will spin the roulette
to choose 2 activities and 1 food.
There's food too?
- It's good that we have food.
- We get to eat.
We have to enjoy
good food on vacation.
That sounds nice.
Before you spin the roulette,
- I'll give you a simple mission.
- Right.
And you will fill out the roulettes
according to the result.
If you succeed, you'll get to write
what you want on the roulette.
- Really?
- Yes.
And you can get rid of one thing...
- that you don't want to do.
- What about just laying around?
- You can write what you want.
- All right.
- It doesn't matter.
- A vacation is nothing special.
- We can just sit here...
- You're right.
- Right. Just give us young pollack.
- That will be the best.
Just give us some young pollack
so we can have a talk.
- We can chat for like three hours.
- Right.
- All we need is some watermelon.
- Exactly.
Even when we go abroad,
we just stay in the room drinking.
- We don't go out.
- That's true.
And apart from
the vacation roulette,
we also have this penalty roulette.
- It's for a penalty.
- If you like roulettes that much,
we should just go to Las Vegas.
- We're spinning so much.
- Why do we keep spinning roulettes?
You will pick one member
as you please...
and write the person's name
on the roulette.
- Really?
- Let's do that.
You can play rock-paper-scissors
or anything.
- Okay.
- I get it.
All right. Please bring in
the vacation roulette then.
- This is the important thing.
- This is important.
- What's Increasing Lung Capacity?
- What could it be?
That sounds strange.
- That doesn't sound good.
- What's that?
- What's Increasing Lung Capacity?
- Let's see what it is.
Whac-A-Mole With Jong Kook in Water.
- I hate it.
- It's the worst.
(Activity 1)
- I hate it.
- It's the worst.
- Actually, all of us are...
- good at holding our breath.
- I hate it so much.
- But we get hit.
- You do get hit.
Thrilling Game.
What is it?
Hide-And-Seek at a Very Big Place.
No. That doesn't sound good.
- That's a lot of work.
- We will sweat a lot.
It's summer.
I bet we won't want to do
any of these.
We will spin the roulette
and do some of them anyway.
- What's next?
- Diversion sounds good.
It says diversion. That sounds nice.
Giving Each Other a Makeover.
- My gosh.
- That sounds horrible.
I hate it.
- I like that. It sounds fun.
- I hate it so much.
That's horrible.
- I hate this.
- This is...
- Hey, let's get rid of this.
- This is the worst.
None of us have
a good sense of fashion.
- This is the worst.
- I don't want to do this.
- I hate it.
- I still hate the thing we tried.
- It went viral online.
- What?
I hated the personal color test.
Right. Let's not do this.
- I don't like my personal color.
- We don't like it.
- I just wear the colors I like.
- Right. It's your choice.
- Of course.
- I hate it.
- I know.
- Recreation?
- It's a special recreation.
- Special recreation sounds good.
The Yoo Jae Suk Show by
Recreation Instructor Yoo Jae Suk.
- That's tiring.
- No, I'm too tired for this.
(The Yoo Jae Suk Show by
Recreation Instructor Yoo Jae Suk)
- It's really annoying.
- It must be tiring.
- It will be annoying.
- I like it.
We will have to dance for two hours.
- I like this one.
- We will dance for two hours.
- It will never end.
- I like it.
Whac-A-Mole With Jong Kook in Water
would be better.
- That's better.
- I'd rather do that.
- It will end soon.
- This is better.
- That's better.
- All right.
- I like this one.
- Playing hide-and-seek is better.
Going On Scary Rides at Lotte World.
- I like that.
- I hate it.
(Activity 5)
(The cowards are terrified
to hear that.)
- That's the worst.
- No, I don't like rides.
- I can't ride them.
- I can't.
- It's all right.
- I'm not doing this.
- I can do it.
- All you need to do is sit.
- It will be fun.
- I can't do that.
- You should just sit there.
- But I can't do it.
All right.
It's Finding Childhood Innocence.
Having Fun at the Water Park
Like Eight-Year-Olds.
- My gosh.
- It must be tiring.
(They start groaning right away.)
- It's all about a water park.
- It has something to do with it.
- Is this product placement?
- What is it?
No. Our base camp...
has a sauna and swimming pools.
But I get exhausted
after playing at swimming pools.
It's a Leisure Activity.
- That sounds good.
- What is it?
Enjoying the Most Popular
Water Sport, Surfing.
- Indoor surfing?
- Surfing sounds good.
- I've never tried it before.
- You can get motion sick.
- You can get sick from surfing.
- You might fall down.
- You might fall.
- Right.
- And you get motion sickness.
You really do.
I don't want to do anything
among these.
We are so weak.
- There's nothing.
- I'm sorry,
but can we just lie around
at home...
- and watch Netflix?
- Sounds good.
- I agree.
- I hate this the most.
- But I bet it's the easiest one.
- Removing Waste Products.
- I thought it would be horrible.
Mythomania Game
to Get Out of a Sauna.
We can't do this.
- None of this is fun.
- It's too hot.
We can't even call it a vacation.
- It's just painful.
- Aren't they penalties?
- I think so.
- This is...
what our viewers want us to do.
I guess they picked the ideas
that we can use on the show.
So do we have to try
at least two among these?
You will pick two things. But...
you might pick
what you wrote instead.
- I see.
- Okay.
It kind of breaks my heart though.
Our viewers don't know
how to have fun.
They have no idea.
- Hey.
- I guess he went on a vacation.
You're blocking two cameras now.
- I don't know...
- Move over.
- where you are looking.
- Move.
That's because
I can't see the roulette.
- Take off your sunglasses.
- Take them off.
- That's because I'm standing here.
- Your sunglasses aren't cool.
Do you know how I feel?
You two might not know because
you always stand in the center.
- By the way,
- I just can't see it.
- you look like...
- I just go with my feelings.
- a middle-aged man at a festival.
- What?
Doesn't he look like ET?
(He looks like a middle-aged man
at a festival.)
- He doesn't look hip anymore.
- I know what you mean.
- He does look like ET.
- He's just a middle-aged man.
- He wants to look young.
- Seriously.
All right.
Let me give you the first mission.
What is it?
You guys are...
- so into drawing these days.
- That's right.
So we will have
the Running Man Drawing Contest.
- I love to draw.
- I don't like drawing.
It's your favorite game.
- You will take turns drawing.
- That's the game.
- We like it.
- We just need to have good sense.
(Each member will draw
in turn for 3 seconds,)
(and the last member guesses
what it is.)
- This must be a bird.
- Right.
(They use all kinds of tricks
to share hints about the answer.)
(The grass is greener
on the other side.)
(But despite all the hints,)
(they have never gotten
the correct answer before.)
- All right.
- I like the game.
- I will give you 10 questions.
- We get 10 questions.
If you give more than
five correct answers,
- you'll get to replace four items.
- That's a lot.
- All right.
- Four items?
The category is important.
(If they get 5 or more questions right,
they replace 4 items.)
- Okay.
- All right.
The first member should be good.
We are good at this game.
- All right. Let's begin.
- Okay.
- The category is important.
- Should we take off our shoes?
- Who will answer?
- What's the category?
- Jae Suk, will you answer?
- Do you want me to go?
- You can do that.
The category is proverbs
and Chinese idioms.
- Okay. I should answer.
- It must be difficult.
And Suk Jin and Jong Kook
should be the first ones to draw.
- You and me...
- But you guys should know...
Chinese idioms to draw something.
Stop bragging.
- They have to know what it means.
- Just do it.
- Come here.
- Do you know Chinese idioms?
- So you should be the first one.
- Ji Hyo.
- We know.
- Are you serious?
- So Min.
- I know Chinese idioms.
So Min, you three...
You three don't have to draw anything.
(You three don't have to draw anything.)
Seriously, I'm going...
to kill you today.
What's with him? We can do this.
- We have to show them.
- If they draw first, it'll be fun.
- Hey, sit down.
- Will you answer?
I will answer.
I want you to play fair.
If you don't pass it in time,
you fail.
- How many seconds?
- You get three seconds.
- Only three seconds?
- In a variety show,
- that's not enough.
- How would we...
Don't count the numbers too fast.
What about we do this?
- Mr. Producer.
- Let's just do it.
Can we use the time
for Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and So Min?
No.
- What?
- I'm going to beat you up.
- I won't let it slide.
- I'll teach you a lesson.
- Or give them a white marker.
- Let's give it a try.
- Let's just do it.
- Ready.
Start.
(Don't count your chickens
before they hatch.)
- All right.
- Three,
two, one. Pass.
- No, it's not over yet.
- Three.
- It's not three seconds.
- Go ahead.
Two, one.
Pass.
- What's that?
- Three, two,
- one. Pass.
- Stay calm.
Three.
- Pass.
- Stay calm.
(Don't count your chickens
before they hatch.)
Two, one.
Pass.
- Three, two, one.
- Just erase it.
- Pass.
- Gosh, this can be confusing.
If it's not good, just erase it.
Two, one. Time's up.
- Haha, stop drawing.
- Hang on.
Right. I mean...
Is this a proverb?
It's a proverb.
- I mean...
- You can't give him a hint.
My goodness.
- You should've drawn only two.
- What is this thing?
We need only two.
- My goodness.
- We just need to draw...
only two things from the proverb.
Don't give him a hint.
- Is this a person?
- This proverb is...
- No hint.
- You spoil...
You spoil a good dish
with ill sauce.
- Gosh.
- Don't rush.
(He gives the wrong answer
in haste.)
- Gosh.
- Don't rush.
- You don't need to rush.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- Don't rush things.
- You should say two things.
Who drew the rice cake?
- I drew the first one.
- Suk Jin drew it.
- Is this rice cake?
- It looks strange.
It's rice cake.
How else would I draw it...
- in three seconds?
- I'm sorry but draw one yourself.
- How would you draw it?
- This is a rice cake.
(This is a rice cake.)
- Like this.
- Is that rice cake?
- This is bar rice cake.
- Right.
Let me tell you something.
A proverb has two main things.
Jong Kook is right about that.
We should draw
only rice cake and kimchi.
Right. They are the main things.
Just do that.
- We will do that.
- This time, it's a Chinese idiom.
- It's not bad.
- All right. It's here.
- Don't draw anything strange.
- A Chinese idiom? Okay.
Or let's draw
about one syllable at a time.
- Let's do that.
- That sounds like a good idea.
Let's say it's sapilguijeong.
- You should draw a lion.
- Right.
- Lion for "sa."
- I see. A lion?
- Only the first syllable. Okay.
- Yes.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
- Okay. I get it.
Let's begin.
- You go first.
- Here's the question.
You will see the order.
(Seomseomoksu)
I just need to know
if it's a Chinese idiom or not.
Pass it. Time's up.
- Three, two, one.
- Draw the same thing.
Pass it.
- What is it?
- Three, two, one.
(Answer: Seomseomoksu)
One. Pass it to her now.
Three, two...
- He pronounces "pass" weirdly.
- One. Pass it.
- Pass it.
- That's good.
- He pronounces "pass" weirdly.
(Answer: Seomseomoksu)
- Good. Just add details now.
- Right.
- It's good. Don't touch it.
- Don't draw anything else.
- Don't touch it. No.
- Three, two...
- Just add details. Don't touch it.
- One.
- Don't draw anything.
- Don't even touch it.
- Hold on.
- Two, one. Time's up.
- He told me not to touch it.
- Don't touch it.
- That's good.
- Two, one. Time's up.
- That's good enough.
- Don't touch it.
- Haha.
- That's good enough.
- I'm giving you a warning, Haha.
- Got it.
- You've been warned.
- It looks weird.
- It's easy. You can get it right.
- We drew it wrong.
- We did a good job.
- We did well.
- No, that's not it.
- What could be the first thing?
- It's up to him now.
You're not allowed to give him
any hints.
- I should figure out what this is.
- But...
- Do not give him any hints.
- What could that be?
- Jae Suk, that's easy.
- What is this?
- Guess what it is.
My, I'm craving this.
You're not allowed to give him
any hints.
- Sweet potato.
- Don't give him any hints.
- It's perfect for summer.
- Hey.
- You eat it in summer?
No, that's not the point.
What place is that?
- No, wait.
- Come on.
- That's not it.
- Gosh.
- I mean...
- Jeju Island.
Five, four...
- Jae Suk.
- Three.
- Just give me a minute.
- I can't give you any more time.
- They keep giving you hints.
- No, they didn't give me any hints.
- We won't say anything.
- If you don't say a word...
- We won't say a single word.
- We'll be quiet.
It's meaningful only if you get it
right without cheating.
- What is this?
- It's not easy.
- Jeju Island.
- But Jae Suk,
- you know the answer for sure.
- What is Jeju Island?
- Stop. Listen.
- Tamra?
You're not allowed to chat.
Jae Suk.
We were talking
about something else.
He asked me
if I had been to Jeju Island.
He asked me if I was planning
to go on a trip to Jeju Island,
- so I said I'd be happy to.
- That wasn't what it sounded like.
- He said he'd go to Tamra Island.
- No.
- I said I wanted to go there.
- Three.
Two.
(The final countdown)
One.
You failed.
- What is this?
- It's easy, Jae Suk.
- We'll reveal the answer.
- Okay.
- It's an island.
- Gosh. Come on.
You just had to guess the first one.
You know ."eomseomoksu."
- "Seomseomoksu" is too easy.
- But...
Couldn't you draw the map of Korea
any better than this?
I only had three seconds.
- Try to draw it in three seconds.
- I mean...
- Draw it. One.
- Suk Jin, Jeju Island is...
- This is what Korea looks like.
- Two. Three.
- That's right.
- This is better.
But you figured out
that I drew Jeju Island, Jae Suk.
- You figured it out.
- I failed anyway.
- Right. Good job.
- Okay. I get it.
- I see how you draw things now.
- Give it a try.
- I only had three seconds.
- I get it.
- Give us an easy question.
- It's a proverb this time.
- We draw only two words.
- For a proverb...
- Two words.
- We'll draw only two words.
- The two most important words.
- Okay.
Ready. Here's your question.
(Answer:
To follow a friend to Gangnam)
- Gosh. How should I draw this?
- Three.
- Two, one.
- I can't do this.
- Pass it. Three, two...
- Really?
- I know what it means, but...
- One.
Pass it. Ji Hyo, your time is up.
Three, two, one.
Pass it. Jong Kook, your time is up.
- Three, two, one.
- What should I do?
- Don't ruin it.
- Pass it.
- Hey.
- Three, two...
- Two, one.
- Wait.
- Don't ruin it.
- Pass it.
- Three, two, one. Pass it.
- Draw faster.
What is he doing?
- Three, two, one. Time's up.
- What is he doing?
That's even weirder.
- What did he do?
- Han River.
What did he draw in the middle?
- What is it...
- Han River.
- Hey.
- What's that thing in the middle?
(Jae Suk checks the drawing.)
Is it a proverb?
- Yes.
- Gosh. What is this? Darn.
This is almost like interpreting
Na Eun's drawing.
Well, this is...
- It's so difficult.
- This is a person.
There are two people here.
- Yes.
- What is this on the left?
Who drew this?
- That's not important.
- Ignore it.
- You can ignore it.
- This is not a deduction game.
Wait. Hold on.
I see water flowing...
- Do not give him any hints.
- Okay.
There's a reason for this.
I could also...
"One cannot see through
another's mind."
- This must not be it, right?
- Take your time.
("One cannot see through
another's mind.")
(This must not be it, right?)
That's not the answer, right?
- That's a good strategy.
- Take your time, Jae Suk.
I'm going to take my time.
He's so funny.
"One cannot see through
another's mind."
- I'm sure that's not the answer.
- Take your time.
Okay. I'm sure it's not.
- Why did you wipe your sweat off?
- What?
- Why did you do that?
- That has nothing to do with this.
- That's not a hint.
- You got the wrong idea.
- That means nothing.
- Just forget about it.
- We're not allowed to do that.
- My friend, that was nothing.
- No?
- No.
This person is giving something
to the other.
What do you mean? That person is
giving nothing to the other.
(No, that's not what it means.)
- That person isn't giving...
- It's not about giving.
- If that's the case...
- Is it about moving?
(Yes. It's about moving.)
It must be friendship
that was given to this person.
Guys, please. Listen, everyone.
I'll give you five seconds.
- Five.
- But...
(The director starts a countdown
hastily.)
- Four.
- Wait.
- Where do you live?
- Apgujeong.
- Three.
- Come on. Wait.
- Two.
- Hey.
One. What's the answer?
- Let me answer. Wait.
- Okay.
He figured it out.
- He figured it out.
- Could he get it right?
Please.
(Did he figure out the answer
from all those hints?)
- I think I know what it means.
- Okay.
- Good.
- It means "to follow."
- Oh, my.
- That's right.
(Did he really figure it out?)
"To follow a friend to Gangnam."
This is...
(He managed to get the answer
in the end.)
- Recognize it as correct.
- He's right.
- He got it right.
- This is the river.
- Gangnam is south of the river.
- Great job.
- Right?
- That's correct.
- "To follow."
That's the only proverb
that includes the word "follow."
The answer is
"to follow a friend to Gangnam."
And you guys mentioned
"Apgujeong, friendship, and moving."
But he actually lives in Apgujeong.
- What's wrong with mentioning that?
- What's wrong with that?
- What's the problem?
- I only asked him where he lived.
- You mentioned other words too.
- Is Apgujeong in Gangnam?
Yes, it's in Gangnam,
but he didn't say "Gangnam."
- That's not the same.
- I got it right.
- He got it right.
- You should accept it.
- We'll accept it this time.
- Okay.
Good.
Bo Pil is so nice.
The next question is
a Chinese idiom.
- A Chinese idiom.
- Let's do this.
Here's your question. Ready, go.
(Answer: Hyeongseoljigong)
Five. Three.
(His hands are shaking.)
- Two, one.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- Pass it. Now.
- It's okay.
- Three, two, one.
- You said, "Five, three, two, one."
- Pass it.
- No. What?
- Three, two...
- Let me...
(Each of them draws one syllable
as they planned.)
- Let me draw the last one.
- Two.
One. Pass it.
Let me draw the last one.
- Three, two, one. Pass it.
- Why?
- Fix the first drawing.
- Three.
- Two.
- Fix the first drawing.
- One.
- That looks like poop.
- Three, one.
- That doesn't look like it.
- That's just poop.
- Exactly.
- My gosh. I told you to draw snow.
- One. Time's up.
- It's over. Haha, your time is up.
- Snow.
(He's adding details
to describe "Hyeong.")
- Is it a Chinese idiom?
- Yes.
Why did you draw poop?
But you can get this right,
Jae Suk.
- I see. He's right.
- Look at the last two drawings.
You only need the last two drawings
to get it right.
- "Gong."
- Yes, that's right.
- "In."
- No.
- A person has grown up?
- Look at the last two drawings.
- Don't tell him if he's right.
- Just the last two drawings.
- Look at the last two drawings.
- "Hyeon."
- No, ignore that drawing.
Gosh, seriously.
- I told you to ignore them!
- Look at the last two drawings.
Just the last two drawings.
(The last two drawings are easy
to guess.)
It must not be "Hyeongseoljigong."
(It must not be "Hyeongseoljigong.")
(Surprised)
(Chuckling)
(That's it!)
Is it "Hyeongseoljigong?"
(Correct)
- That's an earthworm for "Ji."
- Right.
You were supposed to draw
the last one.
- That's "Seol."
- He...
- Jae Suk was...
- Why did you draw poop, you punk?
- "Seolsa" as in "diarrhea."
- That's nonsense.
- Let me try this time.
- Okay.
- Come over here.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
- You got lucky this time.
- I did well, right?
- You were lucky.
- That was good.
- I did well, didn't I?
- Everyone was lost for words.
- I was so surprised.
(Everyone was taken back as no one
expected him to get it right.)
We were all surprised.
- All of us were surprised.
- Indeed.
- Let's begin.
- What is the category?
- I think we'll do well.
- It's a proverb.
- Since it's a proverb...
- Okay. That's good.
- Look here. I divided it.
- Don't be nervous.
- We know.
- We'll draw two words, okay?
- Okay.
- Got it. Let's go.
Here's your question.
(Answer:
A hungry belly has no ears.)
- I know that.
- Three.
(Answer:
A hungry belly has no ears.)
- Good. This is easy.
- We can draw it.
- One. Pass it.
- Focus on the main words.
- Three, two, one.
- We don't even have to draw it.
- Pass it. Three.
- Just add a few details.
Two, one. Pass it.
I'll just draw this.
- Pass it.
- Grapes.
- Just finish this up well.
- Three.
- Two.
- This is...
- He'll get this right.
- Pass it.
- Is it easy?
- You'll definitely get this right.
(The grapes become more realistic.)
- That's good.
- One.
- This...
- Three, two. one.
- Time's up.
- That's good.
- I bet he'll get the answer right.
- Of course, he will.
- He'll definitely get it right.
- What is this?
- No talking.
- That means nothing.
- I'm sure of it.
- Of course I know the answer.
The answer is
"A hungry belly has no ears."
Of course I know the answer.
It's "A hungry belly has no ears."
(He got the correct answer
as soon as he saw the drawing.)
- It was easy.
- Yes.
- We did a good job.
- But Haha.
Didn't you say "grapes"
while drawing it?
- No, I didn't.
- No.
- He didn't say that.
- I swear I didn't hear that.
I clearly heard him saying that.
- He didn't say that.
- He can't hear us.
- Check the recording.
- He didn't say that.
- I couldn't hear it.
- He couldn't hear it.
- Please erase his voice.
- As the director,
I request Haha to move
toward the other end.
- Okay.
- Move toward the other end.
No, not you, Jae Suk.
Someone else should sit there.
- Ji Hyo, switch seats with him.
- I'll do it.
No, we picked Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook has bad hearing.
- He knows us too well.
- My gosh.
- We're the best at group games.
- Don't look down on us!
Here's your question.
- Three, two...
- It's okay.
- One. Pass it.
- Two words, okay?
- Three, two...
- Just describe the words.
One. Pass it.
- It's a proverb.
- Three.
Two, one.
Time's up. Pass it.
Jae Suk, your time is up.
What's that?
- What's this?
- He wrote an English word.
- I'm worried.
- One.
- Isn't an English word allowed?
- No.
- I'm worried.
- One.
(He wrote "good"
as in "harden" in Korean.)
- Three, two...
- You should erase the English word.
- One.
- Erase the English word.
- Pass it.
- Erase it.
Cross it off roughly...
so that he can see it.
- Two, one.
- Cross it off roughly...
(She crosses off the word roughly
so that it's barely visible.)
- Time's up. It's over.
- Don't cover it up completely.
- It's over.
- Hey, that...
- Hey.
- Is it a proverb?
Yes, it's a proverb.
Don't think about the colors.
The English word that I wrote...
You can see it right there.
(They're starting
to give him hints.)
- Let me see. It's raining.
- Okay.
This is an umbrella.
- Don't make a noise like that.
- It's raining.
(They're not allowed to make a noise
to confirm his guesses.)
What?
After it rains...
(Did he figure it out?)
- No way.
- He's incredible.
- The weather is so nice.
- Get ready to stand up.
It means that after it rains...
It means that the ground is good
after it rains, right?
I mean... Hold on.
- Give me a second.
- Whatever you say is your answer.
I mean... Wait.
Hang on.
Give me a second.
He doesn't know the proverb.
- He's close to the answer.
- This is frustrating.
Gosh, I'm frustrated.
I know... Just wait.
- Hold on.
- This is your last chance.
I mean,
this is what I'm trying to say...
- After it rains...
- I'll give you five seconds.
- Five, four...
- After it rains...
- Wait. I think I know it.
- Three.
- Two. One.
- "After it rains,"
"the ground is harder?"
(After it rains,
the ground is harder?)
- "The ground hardens."
- "Hard..."
"It's hard ground?"
- Hey!
- "The ground is harder."
- What does that mean?
"The ground hardens."
- "The ground is hard."
- You should accept it.
- "The ground hardens."
- "The ground hardens after rain."
- Oh, I see.
"The ground is harder."
- "The ground is harder after rain."
- But...
It's
"The ground hardens after rain."
Are we allowed to write
an English word?
- That was good.
- Jae Suk, you did great.
- Good.
- Yes.
- We're good at this.
- How many did we get right?
- We're doing well.
- You already got three empty slots.
- Okay!
- That's great.
- This is the last question.
- Let's get this right too.
Can we change four slots
if we get this right?
(They'll get four empty slots
if they get this right as well.)
- Is it a proverb?
- Yes.
- It's a proverb. Draw 2 words.
- A proverb. We'll draw 2 words.
- Here's your question.
- It was easy.
- Gosh, it's difficult.
- Gosh.
Three.
(Answer: To sow the wind
and reap the whirlwind)
- This one is difficult.
- Two.
One.
(Answer: To sow the wind
and reap the whirlwind)
- It's a proverb. Two.
- Okay.
- One. Time's up.
- Just draw two words.
- Three, two...
- Just two words.
- Time's up.
- What's that "X" mark?
- It's difficult.
- What is this?
- Indeed.
It was hard to draw.
Why are there two arrows
pointing opposite directions?
- Oh, it moves back and forth?
- Right. Yes.
I think I know the answer.
- That's good. Okay.
- I think I know the answer.
(He thinks he knows the answer?)
- Yes.
- "Word travels..."
Gosh.
("Word travels...")
(Gosh.)
Why? What's wrong?
- He reacted to make the show fun.
- Come on.
- What's wrong?
- He did it without realizing it.
I didn't imply anything
about his answer.
- What's wrong?
- This is a horse for sure.
- Yes.
- And it goes back and forth.
That's right.
- The horse is behind this thing.
- Yes.
- And it moves back and forth.
- Hey.
- Is this a bowl?
- Gosh, you.
- Yes.
- Do not respond to his comments.
- It looks like...
- a bucket.
- If I acted like that,
- that would happen.
- Forage for the horse?
I think this is...
If I did it to Jong Kook...
Exactly.
- Three.
- Gosh.
- Oh, I get it.
- What is it?
Gosh, you guys. Okay.
- Did you figure it out?
- What is it?
- It was an easy question after all.
- Yes.
"To sow the wind
and reap the whirlwind."
(They got the last question right.)
(They practically deduced
the answers through conversations.)
- Yes!
- I told you so.
- This game is so fun.
- Hey.
- I think we're really smart.
- Good.
We did an amazing job.
Now, we have our own strategy
for this game.
I guess we won't ever play
this game again.
- Why won't we play it again?
- Why?
- But it's such a fun game.
- We did incredibly well, right?
- We're so good at this, right?
- It's so exciting.
- That's not fair.
- We'll play it no matter what.
- Say goodbye to the game.
- That's not fair.
- No. This game is so fun.
- Don't say that.
- We're good at this game.
- Anyway, you did well,
so you can get rid of
four activities.
- That's great. We did really well.
- Let's get rid of them.
Please choose the activities
you want to get rid of.
That's good.
First, let's get rid of
Going On Scary Rides at Lotte World.
But I like that...
- It's too scary.
- It's scary.
- I'd pull muscles.
- I hate that too.
- I can't ride scary rides.
- And...
- Giving Each Other a Makeover.
- We don't like that either.
Right. Let's not do that.
- Get rid of it.
- We've done it too many times.
- And let's not do this either.
- Get rid of the surfing.
- We might get hurt.
- Okay, the surfing.
- You get seasickness.
- That's right.
- Let's remove Whac-A-Mole too.
- Really?
Now, you can write any activities
you want to do in the empty slots.
- It's probably...
- Hey, why don't we play this again?
- Or...
- It won't be fun.
- I like this game.
- Let's play another round.
- Playing another round?
- Or 30 minutes at the pavilion.
- Relaxing for 30 minutes.
- For 30 minutes,
- we can eat...
- Just chilling.
Chatting at the pavilion
for 30 minutes. Okay.
- That's good. I love to chat.
- That's a great idea.
Chatting right here.
Chatting at the pavilion
right behind us.
- "Right behind us."
- Yes, not far away from here.
- We'll have a nice chat.
- A nice chat.
- Great.
- I'm excited.
- A vacation should be like this.
- This is what it should be like.
- Exactly.
- For how long?
- For 30 minutes.
- Is it too short?
- It's too short.
It'll end as soon as we start.
- How about an hour?
- It should be at least an hour.
- We'll get coffee delivered too.
- Right.
- He's right.
- Yes, an hour sounds reasonable.
- Nice.
- And...
- Let's go to Suk Jin's house.
- Okay.
(Taken aback)
- That sounds great.
- I like the idea.
- I really like the idea.
- Don't do this to me.
- It sounds great.
- Let's go.
- It's a great idea.
- We can see Hyun Woo too.
Come on. Let's go.
- I'll agree if we go to yours too.
- It's a great idea.
- Fine. Then...
- Let's go to his house.
Instead of Suk Jin's house...
Or let's go to Jong Kook's house.
Sure. Let's do that.
My mother is home.
- But I don't really want to go...
- It's too cold in his house.
- to his place again...
- It appears every week.
- It's not cold in my house.
- because it's too dark.
- It's hot. My gosh.
- It's too dark.
It's bright with the blinds open.
- In his house...
- He never turns the AC on.
I had never felt oppressed
in anyone else's house before.
You get frostbite
if you visit his house in winter.
- Having ramyeon at Jong Kook's.
- It could cost you a fortune.
- Okay.
- That sounds good.
Having ramyeon at Jong Kook's house.
Do you have ramyeon at home?
We should buy some.
(What?)
- Why?
- What is it?
What did you mean by saying,
"Do you have ramyeon at home?"
(What did you mean by saying,
"Do you have ramyeon at home?")
She asked that
because we're going to eat ramyeon.
- We're going to eat ramyeon, so...
- You visited his place recently,
- and there was no ramyeon, right?
- There was no ramyeon there.
- No, she was just curious.
- What's the truth?
Hey, defend yourself more actively!
Jae Suk.
- Are you a prosecutor or what?
- I don't want to.
- "There was no ramyeon, right?"
- Let me explain.
- It's not like that.
- You look suspicious.
- What's going on?
- You look so suspicious.
"Do you have ramyeon at home?
You never eat ramyeon."
- Anyway...
- Detective Yoo.
- What's the truth?
- What's important is...
that there's no ramyeon...
- at his house.
- You're being unreasonable.
- That's not it. Listen to me.
- We're not being unreasonable.
- You see, usually...
- He's defending himself actively.
- "Do you have ramyeon at home?"
- many people think...
that I never eat ramyeon.
That's why she asked,
- "Do you have ramyeon at home?"
- Ji Hyo isn't saying anything.
- So I...
- I have nothing to say.
Hey, just be quiet.
Just be quiet.
- She says she has nothing to say.
- Right.
Having no ramyeon at home...
- is unusual.
- It's normal.
- I have no ramyeon at home.
- What's going on?
We should buy some on our way.
- Oh, I have an idea.
- What is it?
Watching Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
having a date...
- for one hour.
- Watching them.
(Watching Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
having a date for one hour.)
- I like that.
- Wait. What is your problem?
- Don't write it down.
- That sounds fun.
- I love this idea the most.
- It's a good idea.
- Why would you do that?
- I like that.
- "We Went on a Date."
- What?
- It has nothing to do with that.
- Why?
An hour sounds great.
- An hour is okay, right?
- That's great.
- An hour, right?
- Why would you write that down?
- "We Went on a Date."
- It has nothing to do with...
today's theme.
It does. Watching you two together
brings us joy and happiness.
This isn't...
- We'll just observe them.
- related to the vacation theme.
- Like a reality show.
- I really want to see it.
- I want to see it.
- It's not hard.
- Then let's visit that place.
- What place?
The terrace
that Suk Jin told us about.
Hey, that place...
- Right. You should go there.
- That's a good idea.
But what are we going to do...
- Hey, not long ago, I saw...
- Yes, Suk Jin.
people taking photo booth photos
near colleges.
- You mean, four-cut photos?
- Oh, that?
I really want to take those photos
with you guys.
- Really?
- I like that idea.
- Taking four-cut photos.
- I've never done it before.
- Right?
- Me neither.
(The activity
that Seok Sam suggested)
Seok Sam takes a photo alone.
- For his funeral?
- Let him do it alone.
- And the members...
- "The Ji Seok Sam Show."
(Watching the Ji Seok Sam Show)
- The Ji Seok Sam Show.
- Hey!
- I like that.
- The Ji Seok Sam Show.
- I put on a show in front of you?
- You can do some impressions.
- Or tell us jokes.
You can do impressions,
tell us jokes, and host an event.
- Seok Sam used to...
- That sounds great.
host events at Everland
when it was called Yongin Farmland.
- He's...
- But I had...
- a script back then.
- He's good at hosting fun events.
- He's a great host.
- You can do it.
- Cross it off.
- The rose festival...
- I don't have any ideas for that.
- Okay.
- Let's take four-cut photos.
- I think that's a good idea too.
This will be...
- Right. It'll be meaningful.
- It'll be meaningful.
- Taking four-cut photos.
That will be so fun.
Okay. We're done.
You see, I'm pretty sure...
that all of our viewers want us...
- to do this.
- This activity.
- The one-hour date?
- Right. I really want to see it.
- What's so interesting about it?
- It'll help us get high ratings.
- Our ratings will go up.
- Definitely.
- There's no doubt.
- I wonder what they'll talk about.
- We'll choose our first activity.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Please, Jae Suk.
- Please pick an easy one.
- Here we go.
- Okay. I'll spin it.
- The date.
(Many people want to see
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo on a date.)
I'm so curious.
Please.
- It's the date.
- Okay. Great.
It's the date.
- It's the date.
- No, it's not.
- Oh, it's not that one.
- No.
- Is it taking photos?
- Okay. Great.
- What are you doing?
(The passionate fan interferes.)
- Stop spinning it.
- A little more.
Stop it already.
It's stopping.
- It's stopping. Okay.
- It's almost there.
- Wait. I'll spin it again.
- Go ahead.
Besides,
did anyone tell me to spin it?
- No one did.
- Right?
- Why didn't you stop me?
- That wasn't fair.
- Suk Jin should've done it.
- Why didn't you stop me?
- Right.
Let's make the decision this time.
- Suk Jin will spin it.
- Let Seok Sam spin it.
- Okay. Let's end it here.
- Seok Sam will spin it.
- I'll end it once and for all.
- Let's make the decision here.
This is for real.
- We'll make the decision.
- Okay.
- To be honest...
- Hey.
- My gosh. Look at that.
- That's it.
(The roulette starts to slow down
near the slot for the date.)
- It's stopping.
- It stopped...
Okay.
(The Yoo Jae Suk Show)
(It stopped at the Yoo Jae Suk Show
one slot before the date.)
(Disappointed and upset)
- Let's pick it next time.
- Okay.
- We have no choice.
- You can do whatever you want.
- Congratulations.
Jae Suk, you can do a talk show...
or anything you want to do.
- Got it. Then...
- Will we do it at the pavilion?
- Are we going to the pavilion?
- First...
We booked a large venue
just in case.
Do you want to go there
or stay here?
- Let's go there.
- Would you prefer that?
- Let's go there and continue.
- Okay.
Let's move to the next location
and begin the Yoo Jae Suk Show.
- Let's get going.
- Is it a large place?
- Let's go.
- We sure know how to have fun.
- During the Yoo Jae Suk Show,
- Yes.
I'll try various things
that I've always wanted to try...
along with other activities.
Are you planning
a variety of events?
You know what I've been saying...
- these days.
- What's that?
I've been making suggestions.
- Sure, go ahead.
- I've made suggestions.
I'd like that.
- I'll give it a try.
- Sure.
- Haha, they're adorable!
- I love that we have a park here.
Who is it?
- Did you take your kids out?
- Yes.
Raising kids is tough, isn't it?
I'd be lying if I said
that it wasn't hard.
- But it makes you happy.
- That's right.
- What do you mean?
- I know that, but...
- Of course we're happy.
- Of course.
- When will your song be released?
- Haha...
One will be released in the summer.
- Haha.
- Run it by us first.
- Your song...
- Run it by us.
Run it by us first
before releasing it.
Why? My previous song wasn't so bad.
- As if.
- Haha!
He releases songs
like we go shopping.
- What? Like a luxury item?
- Like we go shopping?
- Of course.
- "Busan Vacance" was a good one.
- Right.
- Jong Kook,
- you...
- Not this time around.
- You'll be releasing one too.
- Right.
- Yes, with KCM.
- A new song?
Yes, with KCM.
- Really?
- He suggested we sing a duet.
He felt bad about losing out
on the previous opportunity.
- How about a duet with Ji Hyo?
- That sounds nice.
Don't be ridiculous.
- You see...
- I quite like that.
We haven't had married couples
sing duets in a while.
(Duets by married couples
are a thing of the past.)
With just the affection
we have for one another
(The next big hit
by a married couple)
Like Hong Seo Beom
and Jo Gap Gyeong.
Why did you have to sit next to me?
Their song is "My Love to You."
- My love to you
(She tries to get him
to sing a duet.)
- My love to you
I've come up with a title
for your song.
"There's No Ramyeon at Your Place."
- There's no ramyeon at your place
(An enchanting melody)
It's a trot song.
- The market
- I checked last night
My favorite ramyeon
Is the one I share with you
- Then...
- Is the one I share with you
- There you go.
- And after having ramyeon
You've got to be kidding me.
Cook it deliciously
If you like me
If you truly like me
You would cook me ramyeon
for the rest of my life
Kiss
Is this the so-called
Yoo Jae Suk Show?
- Gosh.
- Has it begun?
Has it already started?
- The Yoo Jae Suk Show.
- Right, the Yoo Jae Suk Show.
Will it go on for an hour?
The Yoo Jae Suk Show has begun.
"Kiss, kiss, kiss" had me laughing.
He sang that
while looking straight at me.
(He wanted to yell,
but ended up laughing.)
He tried his best to sound annoying.
That was him trying really hard.
Was that the kissing sound?
That's right.
- The kissing.
- Unbelievable.
I can't believe him.
- Then...
- There's no ramyeon
At your place
Cook it
It really feels like
we're going on a vacation.
Of course I remember this place.
I know this place too well.
- Really?
- Red Velvet.
- That's right.
- We met Red Velvet here.
We had the name tag elimination
and Kwang Soo kept running.
- That's right.
- Kwang Soo kept running away.
In the final moments,
he went into the pool.
- We played a game here.
- That's right.
- What was the game?
- You're right.
I don't remember,
but one at a time...
I'm sorry,
but please sit down and stay quiet.
Shut our mouths.
Yes, and please sit.
- Let's all be quiet.
- And sit.
- What now?
- Sorry?
- What's next?
- Jae Suk.
How about Chinese idioms?
- Let's do it again.
- The one with the drawing.
I'm in!
We did that one too many times.
- So for an hour...
- Yes?
- It's currently 11:58 a.m.
- Right.
- How about lunch?
- Sorry?
It's time for lunch.
- I mean...
- Please sit at the far end.
Mister.
- Mister, get over here.
- But...
I don't appreciate
your annoying comments.
Sit at the far end.
- Unbelievable.
- I'm trying to run a show,
- so why...
- I wasn't trying to annoy you.
Anyway,
if I'm being honest,
- I don't have anything planned.
- Of course not.
- Right.
- So what should we do?
(Well...)
- Let's play for some food.
- Hold on.
Are you now thinking about
what to do?
- I am.
- Seriously?
- You have nothing planned?
- What?
- Why aren't you prepared?
- You thought of nothing?
I'm now thinking about it.
- You had more than enough time.
- The viewers wanted a show...
where Jae Suk does
anything he wants.
- That's right.
- Really?
- Like I said...
- Do whatever you want.
It's my time to do something
that I've been meaning to try.
- Like what?
- What do you have in mind?
- I would like...
- Yes?
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook to...
Don't.
(He'd like to force them on a date.)
Don't!
- Just so that you can have fun...
- Wait!
- I'd love that.
- You're being selfish.
- Don't.
- I second that.
- But it's the Yoo Jae Suk Show.
- But...
I'm allowed to do anything.
No, don't.
So you'll have them do that here?
- Then...
- A segment within the show.
I won't force anything...
since it will only put pressure...
- on Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
- Right.
- How about...
- So go ahead...
- and get us some snacks.
- Yes!
- You're making us run errands?
- That's not it.
Once we have food...
- Look at her.
- She's getting ready to go.
- She's up for it.
- But...
- I love this about Ji Hyo.
- I can't be bothered, that's all.
Getting something to eat
isn't hard at all.
Don't forget the eggs
and the sikhye.
- Sweetie.
- Your girlfriend's ready to go.
- That seems unnatural.
- What do you mean?
- Why call her my girlfriend?
- She's just someone she knows.
- Let's go!
Stop forcing it on us.
- I...
- Let's go!
Come on, let's go.
Let's go. Get up.
- Let's go.
- What...
- What's with you?
- Jong Kook.
Why are you being this way?
- Let's go.
- Don't read too much into it.
What's with you?
- Come on, Ji Hyo. Let's go!
- Then...
Get us some snacks.
- As in what?
- Pay with this.
Sure, got it.
- I'd like some mild coffee.
- Got it.
Ji Hyo, let's go.
- Sikhye?
- They have it here.
- Sikhye and...
- Sikhye and eggs.
- The rest of us...
- What game should we play?
- We should have a plan.
Can you lie down?
- On our backs?
- Really?
Suk Jin,
you can stand up.
I'm loving the Yoo Jae Suk Show.
- This is hilarious.
- Why only me?
Why should I stand
when the others are on their backs?
And now...
Give us a massage.
- And...
- The amusement park MC.
(You can be the amusement park MC.)
We hired you
to keep us entertained today.
- So...
- But I want to rest.
- You can keep talking.
- Suk Jin, keep us entertained.
I'm sorry,
but is this the King Game?
- I...
- What on earth is this?
- It's the Yoo Jae Suk Show.
- No, it's the King Game.
- Relax if you want to.
- I know
Can we also get some eggs?
How about three per person?
- That's too many.
- Is that so?
- Sorry.
- We have to have our lunch.
I wanted to eat some protein.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Which snacks should I buy?
The Homerun Ball for starters.
(Look at that.)
- What...
- Things are looking good.
- That was sweet of you.
- This may come true.
You can't carry all of that.
Let me help.
No, I can carry them all.
There still is some room left.
It's fine. You don't have to.
- Still.
- Don't.
There's no need to carry anything.
This isn't efficient at all.
Don't you agree?
- There's no need to...
- I want to help, that's all.
But it makes no sense.
What's with those two?
Is there something
going on between them?
(Beats me.)
- Goodness.
- Here you go.
- Take your pick.
- Did you buy some eggs?
- Of course.
- Eggs are the best.
- Thank you.
- Here.
- It's plum juice.
- Good job.
- Gosh, that's sweet.
(Slap!)
- You...
- Watch.
(They start messing around
with the eggs.)
It hurts, doesn't it?
(This looks like fun.)
It hurts.
(Crack!)
(Startled)
- It hurts.
- That was my fist.
- That really hurts.
What in the...
I saw how Se Chan
just used his fist.
(He gets revenge!)
It really hurts.
Stop it.
Stop it, misters!
Get back here.
(Third segment: Tag with Seok Sam)
(Chuckling)
Look at them having fun.
Is this what you wanted for
the Yoo Jae Suk Show?
Get back here!
(Most segments are created
to entertain the show host.)
I'm going to crack your skull open.
He's so annoying.
- Jong Kook, please.
- What?
Please catch him for me.
Do it yourself.
Catch him for me.
- You're the one who wants to.
- Catch him for me.
I want to crack this on his head.
(It's funny though.)
What are you laughing at?
(He takes his anger out
on Haha instead.)
It's quite hard to peel the shell.
(He takes his anger out
on Haha instead.)
(Jae Suk cracks another egg.)
(Seok Sam keeps letting his head
get hammered.)
(Once again,
he fails to catch Jae Suk.)
This is so annoying.
- So annoying!
- Here.
How is this the Yoo Jae Suk Show?
It's Yoo Jae Suk's Prankster Show.
I keep watching it though.
(It's funny for some reason.)
It's funny.
So what did you two talk about?
- Not much.
- Not much?
That's why you haven't been
successful in love.
Unbelievable.
- What are you talking about?
- I...
We let you have some alone time.
Feed the person next to you.
(Fourth segment:
Feed the one next to you.)
We're doing this
to witness one single scene.
- They're your main targets today.
- Gosh, no.
Forcing things to happen
isn't something...
- the viewers like.
- Exactly.
- It'll only pressure them.
- The viewers hate that.
Is this really the Yoo Jae Suk Show?
You both...
Jong Kook's highly irritated.
He's scoffing.
(Sweetie!)
(Ji Hyo plays the game
in "expert" mode.)
(They're loving it.)
Ji Hyo's hilarious these days.
Ji Hyo,
I get what you're doing, but...
Are you getting extra pay?
Finish it now!
We're running out of time!
Hey!
- Hurry up!
- You don't like chocolate, right?
I'll remove it for you.
Are you getting extra pay?
Are you shooting a different show?
Gosh, he's...
Why is he being so shy?
- It's hilarious.
- This is nice.
- They're lovey-dovey.
- This is great.
- Today,
- Yes?
we're here at a dry sauna
after a long while.
I know this is the Yoo Jae Suk Show,
but let's talk about the things
we've wanted to tell each other.
Right.
All right.
- Let's do that.
- I have a question.
- Yes.
- Is this the Yoo Jae Suk Show...
- or the Kim Jong Kook Show?
- Stop it already!
- He got hit!
He got hit!
He got hit at the crown of his head.
(The host got hit
while teasing Jong Kook.)
We can say
whatever we've wanted to say.
- For whom is this show for?
- I mean...
You don't have to participate.
I'll talk to her.
I've always been grateful
for everything you've done for me...
for the past 12 years.
All right.
It's over?
(End of the segment)
As soon as Suk Jin started...
That's it?
How can a segment end so fast?
- How many segments are there?
- It'll be continued.
Are there any fun games you know of?
Nothing's more fun
than a drawing game.
- I love that game.
- A drawing game...
- Me too.
- It's so fun.
We must choose four candidates
for the penalty.
We can play a game and decide that.
We can decide that right away?
Let's play a game and decide.
Let's do that.
The loser gets the penalty.
There's this classic game
we played...
- we had so much fun with.
- What is it?
What is it?
The game I prepared...
is Towel Tug of War.
- Towel Tug of War?
- That's right.
(The sixth segment
of the Yoo Jae Suk Show)
(Towel Tug of War)
One player will be holding
the ends of a towel,
and the rest of the players
will pull the first player.
- And you must win.
- Will it be a 2-on-2 game?
Sorry? It'll be 3 on 3.
- Three on three?
- That's right.
When the score is 2 to 0...
or 2 to 1,
one of the members
of the losing team...
will be a candidate for the penalty.
What about the host?
Will you be exempt?
I'll have to host the game
since it's a 3-on-3 game.
- Then you won't even play?
- What will your role be?
I know.
I mean...
All of us can be a candidate
for the penalty.
This is the Yoo Jae Suk Show.
- We can vote for you, though.
- Even so...
We have that right.
The voting is up to us.
- Then...
- We'll play the game,
and if it turns out...
- If it's 6 to 1...
- If it's not that fun,
- Then he'll be the candidate.
- then he'll be chosen.
Let's do this. Okay.
Let's put these away.
Okay, but do we have to?
I think we can play it on the mat.
- Let's play it on the mat.
- Put them away.
So it's this song.
(Suddenly playing a theme song
for a sports day)
(Weren't you guys
going to play a game?)
- A sports day!
- In 2, 3, 4.
Now, we'll divide into teams.
- Think of it as a sports day.
- All right.
- It'll be a best-of-three-race.
- A best-of-three-race.
Towel Tug of War.
Are you ready for Towel Tug of War?
- Yes.
- All right. First...
I don't want to play
Towel Tug of War.
Me neither.
- What is this?
- I really don't want to play.
Let's just...
No, let's give it a shot.
- I really don't want to play it.
- Why are we playing it?
I don't want to!
Why are we playing Towel Tug of War?
Let's warm up first
since we need to.
How do we warm up?
- We'll follow you.
- Follow after me.
Why is the Yoo Jae Suk Show
like this?
- Gosh, seriously.
- Can you change your move?
He's like a thug.
Gosh, seriously.
(Moving to the side)
Don't stall for time!
You're stalling for time
because you think it won't be fun.
Now, spin.
Spin.
What is this?
(The host carries on
despite the complaints.)
(He's run out
of things to do already.)
I can't help but laugh
because it's ridiculous.
Let's put our arms
around each other.
- It's funny.
- Let's do it.
What do we do now?
- What are we doing?
- What is this?
What is this?
- Mister!
- Seriously...
- Hey!
- We need to warm up.
- It's already warmed up.
- We must warm up.
We must warm up.
But it's not making me feel better!
Are you ready now?
- What?
- What do you mean if we're ready?
What did we even do?
- The Tug of War will begin now.
- Okay.
- How...
- Ji Hyo and So Min...
- So Min.
- will decide the teams.
All right.
Round One will start
with these members.
- What about you?
- I need to host it.
- You'll be the host?
- Get ready.
- What do I do?
- Stand in the front.
- I stand in the front?
- Grab over here.
The one who's good at it
must stand in the front.
Watch your pronunciation.
Mister, what's funny is that...
she's grabbing my waist, but...
She should grab it tight.
- But it's...
- It's up to you guys.
- You should figure it out.
- But they're grabbing the towel.
You guys should figure it out.
- What?
- You told us to grab the waist.
- That's up to you.
- We can beat them.
The rule changed?
We can do whatever we want?
(MC Yoo clearly told them to grab
the member's waist and pull.)
(But when the game started,
he went back on his word.)
The rule changed?
We can do whatever we want?
It's up to us, but we can only
hold on to it this much?
- What is this?
- I'm sorry,
- It's just a game!
- but what's this supposed to be?
That's a reasonable complaint.
- It is reasonable.
- Right?
- I get everything else.
- Let it go.
But why are we given only this much
and why did they take that much?
Let it go.
This is why I told you
to grab the waist.
- It's better to hold the waist.
- But...
what about you?
What are you doing?
I'd be beaten to death at this rate.
It's not that.
(The host will be beaten to death
for a terrible game.)
- What are you supposed to do?
- Let it go, will you?
What about you? What's your role?
I get it, but...
- What do we get out of this?
- It's the Yoo Jae Suk Show.
I know that it is,
but why are you so...
- Hey!
- Let's start already.
- Jong Kook.
- Get ready.
I'm holding the center.
- Hurry.
- It slipped.
- He's practically lying down.
What about it? You're supposed to
lie down in a Tug of War.
- We can do that? Okay.
- You can lie down too.
Get ready.
- We can do that? Okay.
- You can lie down too.
Get ready.
- Set...
- Hey. You can't lie down yet.
But you said we could.
- Set...
- Hey. You can't lie down yet.
(The game starts right away.)
- You told us it was allowed.
- Hold on.
- Why did you start the game?
- We won.
It's over!
You should start when we are...
- We won. We're the winners.
- Team So Min wins the first round.
We won.
- We're the winners.
All right. This is great.
- Why did you do that?
- You shouldn't host like that.
It's not fun!
It's not fun at all.
It's so boring even though we won.
It'll get fun when we have
the candidates for the penalty.
Don't worry.
- Then what's going to happen?
- For the first round...
You'll be in a different team
for the second round.
We'll choose our teams again?
- Yes, for Round Two.
- How will this work?
(What? We're switching teams?)
We're going to warm up again.
Get ready.
- For Round Two...
- The person...
who loses the most
will be a candidate?
What? I already told you.
- If the score is 2 to 0,
- Then it'll be over.
then one member of the losing team
will become the candidate.
Oh, really?
But we can't tell
which team is winning or losing.
Shouldn't we stay on the same team?
- Sorry?
- That way, we have a candidate.
No, that's not it.
I told you it'd be random.
- Random?
- So that Jong Kook...
- That's right.
- You can join Jong Kook this time.
- That way, it'll be 1 to 1.
- Is it just me who doesn't get it?
Yes.
The one who was on the losing team
must remember it.
- How many times must we lose?
- That's right.
- I have one win.
- I have one win too.
- Right.
How many rounds are we playing?
No idea.
Shouldn't we stay on the same team?
Isn't that how it works?
- We'll play until we pass out.
- Is that so?
- Let's begin Round Two.
- Okay.
For Round Two,
we'll divide teams again.
- They all sat down.
- Since Suk Jin sat down first,
so you take him.
- It's okay. That's how it works.
- All right.
- It's okay. We can win.
- It's doable.
We can still win.
- All right.
- I don't think we can win.
It's doable, right? It is doable.
- You should go second.
- This is doable.
Lie down as soon as it starts.
Hold the center.
We should hold the towel
as much as we can.
Their part is longer.
- Get ready.
- This is making me competitive.
- We don't stand a chance...
- Get ready...
because we only have female members.
- You never know.
- Let me lie down a bit.
- We should lie down too.
- Hold on.
- My gosh.
Goodness. He's strong like a bull.
Get ready. Set...
(Who will be the winner
of this game?)
Set,
go!
- It's 1 to 1.
- Okay!
I got two points. I won twice.
Sorry?
It's not 1 to 1.
That doesn't matter.
It's still 1 to 1.
Why doesn't it matter?
- Wait. Hey.
- It doesn't matter.
But I won.
- It's confusion. Think carefully.
- It doesn't matter.
I told you.
I have one win. What about you?
- I won twice.
- I won twice too.
- It's confusing.
- It's 1 to 1.
No, they lost twice.
- Exclude those who lost twice.
- This team won earlier, right?
- Yes.
- And you guys won this time.
But the members changed.
Let's beat him.
So what matters is which side
we are standing.
Then we just need to focus
on the last round.
The winning team of
the last round will be the winner.
No, what matters is where you stand.
- Isn't that right? The winner...
- No, it's neck and neck.
It's neck and neck
with a score of 1 to 1.
I hate Tug of War. It's not fun.
- You don't like it?
- No.
Then...
What about this?
- What is it?
- Lie down on your stomach...
- and see who goes the farthest.
- Like curling?
(Pushing yourself on your stomach)
Doesn't it look fun?
It looks painful.
- Oh, gosh.
- Be careful.
It's burning.
- It'll burn your skin.
- I have an idea.
You must include a relay race
when it comes to a sports day.
- A relay.
- That's right.
Whatever happened
to the Tug of War, then?
Sorry? You got two wins.
- Two wins.
- It's still valid?
- You got two wins.
- All right.
Since this is a team match.
We'll play a relay race
from that point to here.
- That'll be fun.
- How about we run on our stomachs?
- We'll run.
- We're going to run?
- This could be a lap, right?
- Come on.
The area next to the pillar.
You're going to tap it and run back.
Like a baton?
- Yes, that's the halfway point.
- Two must stay there.
Two here and one over there.
Let's divide into teams.
Ji Hyo and So Min will decide.
Paper.
- All right.
- I pick Se Chan.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
(She picks Jong Kook.)
Okay!
Pick one more member.
So Min, should you pick Suk Jin?
Who do you think is faster?
- Still, Haha must be faster.
- I run really fast.
I pick Jae Suk.
He can play too?
(She picked the host?)
Then...
Then Suk Jin should host it.
- Then I should...
- Yes, you should host it.
I can host the game, then.
- I'm on your team, then.
- This is great.
- Hey.
- All right.
- I never imagined it.
Why is Jae Suk playing
all of a sudden?
That's because So Min...
- suddenly picked me.
- He was chosen.
- The team...
- Then how many wins do you have?
Since it's 1 to 1,
the members of the losing team
in the next game will be a candidate.
- How strange.
- Yes.
I won't get punishment then.
- Why not?
- I won't receive punishment.
I won't lose because I'm the MC.
But I can play...
- instead of you.
- Right.
You can?
Then I would have to root for you.
Yes. You should be rooting for me.
You should be biased.
Gosh.
- Are you ready?
- Are you the first one to go?
- Yes, I'm the first.
- Is Ji Hyo the second one to go?
Gosh. I won the flag-grabbing game
in "Let's Go! Dream Team."
I was number one.
The one who grabs this wins.
So Min. You should be barefooted.
- Barefooted?
- Yes.
You got this.
(1 member from the losing team will
be a candidate to get punishment!)
- You should go then come back.
- You got this.
(Which team will win?)
Ready.
Go.
So Min is slow. Gosh.
(Haha is faster as expected.)
(After So Min, Jae Suk will go.)
- She's slow.
- Hurry up.
- So Min is slow.
Hurry up.
(Ji Hyo who received the baton
from Haha goes first.)
(Jae Suk chases her from behind.)
Hurry up, Ji Hyo.
(Jae Suk is coming after her
at an amazing speed at that time.)
Hurry up. He caught up with her.
- The last one.
- Okay.
(The last runners,
Se Chan and Jong Kook, run.)
- Good!
- Se Chan!
- Good.
- Beat him.
- Catch him.
- Hurry up.
(Se Chan barely gave Jong Kook
who tried to stop him the slip.)
Hurry up.
(They start spurting
for the last time.)
- Hurry up.
- Go.
Hurry up.
Okay!
(Se Chan went in.)
(Jae Suk, Se Chan, and So Min won.)
This is fun.
This is thrilling.
(Zooming)
We won.
Are you his girlfriend?
- Gosh.
- Nice.
We had a good strategy.
- Isn't it fun?
- It hurts so much.
The soles of my feet hurt so much.
- Isn't it fun?
- The soles of my feet hurt so much.
- How is it? Isn't it fun?
- Does it hurt?
It hurts.
It's fun to watch.
It's fun.
- They're fast.
- Hold on.
What are the rules?
So they will have a candidate, not us?
- The other team has a candidate.
- It's weird.
As far as I know,
it's the first time...
- for Haha to lose.
- They will have a candidate.
Gosh.
He's unlucky.
- Isn't it weird?
- Jae Suk's Thug Show.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
- Shoot.
(Ji Hyo is picked as a candidate
for punishment in the end.)
Okay.
(Okay!)
He likes it so much.
He's annoying.
- Ji Hyo is mad.
- Ji Hyo.
She won't receive
the punishment anyway.
We should do it now.
But we still got some time left
for Jae Suk Show.
- Stop.
- We got more time?
We don't have to do it
until the end.
No.
Let's talk.
- Sit down for now.
- Yes. We can talk too.
Sit down, everyone.
Let's have a talk.
That's random.
If something fun happened
last week...
or had an interesting experience...
- Something bizarre?
- Hey.
- Like "Incredible Moment."
- An interesting experience.
Something like
an out-of-body experience.
- If you have something like that...
- Let me think about it.
Think of a horror experience
or something like that.
- What should I talk about?
- A unique experience.
I have a bizarre experience.
It doesn't make sense.
Tell us.
- Two weeks ago,
- Okay.
I appeared on a golf channel
with In Gyu.
I was hit by the ball
Joon Ho hit with a 4-iron golf club.
- Who was hit?
- Me.
Where?
On my side. But fortunately...
You have a lot of fat there.
I was hit on my side.
But if it was a little higher or lower,
- I would've injured badly.
- It could've been dangerous.
- I went to a doctor.
- Okay.
I was lucky because I had belly fat.
The bruise is healed a lot now.
- For real? Did you get a bruise?
- I can show you.
- Did you get a bruise?
- But...
- As the ball spun.
The ball...
But you really have
a thick layer of fat.
Fortunately, before I got hit,
I had two bowls of hangover soup.
I shouted when I was hit.
- I screamed.
- Gosh.
I will stay chubby.
I want to know what Ji Hyo did
last week...
so bad.
What were your days like?
When do you wake up?
- I wake up at 12 p.m.
- Okay.
I go to the kitchen
to organize stuff.
And I prepare
something to eat later.
Around at five,
I go out to take a walk with my dog.
What do you do for those five hours?
- Do you not eat?
- Five hours is a lot of time.
- For those five hours...
- Do you not eat?
What do you do for those five hours?
- It doesn't make sense.
- I don't eat at that time.
- I eat at seven.
- What?
- You eat your first meal at seven?
- Yes. I eat my first meal then.
- It's not good.
- You eat once a day.
I don't know how it happened,
but I adjusted my life to my dog.
- So you eat.
- I eat.
I clean up,
watch TV, then go to bed.
- What time?
- What time do you go to bed?
- At 12 a.m.
- What time do you wake up?
- At 12 p.m.
- Then you sleep for 12 hours?
- Yes.
- You sleep for 12 hours?
Do you not wake up
not even once in the middle?
No. I don't wake up in the middle.
How can you sleep for 12 hours?
It's like you have six hours less
than me in a day.
Let's listen to Seok Sam's
daily routine.
- Yes. Let's listen to his story.
- Let's listen.
- I wake up at 8:30 a.m.
- So?
All my family members are sleeping.
- Then?
- Then I watch YouTube...
- by myself.
- Then?
When I get hungry,
I have a cup of coffee with a toast.
I spend my day like that until 11 a.m.
Your story is so boring.
Can you say something fun?
Do you eat your toast with jam?
What we want is...
"I was trying to get jam,
but I stepped on it and fell."
- "I passed out for a moment."
- Do I have to make it up?
- Yes.
- At 11 a.m.,
I do bungee jumping at a veranda.
(Bungee jumping at a veranda
at 11:30 a.m.)
That's too much.
You exaggerated too much.
- You know the rubber band, right?
- Yes.
- I do bungee jumping with that.
- You do bungee jumping?
That's exaggerated too much.
- It's funny.
- I do bungee jumping.
I live on the 12th floor.
I was hanging on the 7th floor once.
That's enough.
(Jae Suk Show abruptly ends.)
Let's eat now.
Finally?
The vacation food...
recommended by the viewers.
- Good.
- Bring it.
We're eating what the viewers
gave us?
We got the exact food
they wrote in the comment.
Do you think the viewers
sent the food?
They won't just give it to us.
- What is it?
- What's this?
There's something Se Chan
should make.
"Without a tool?"
(We chose 8 out of many food ideas
from so many comments.)
"Bean noodles made with millstones
by yourself."
We should make
bean noodles made with millstones?
This will take 3 to 4 hours.
"Handmade jjajangmyeon."
It will take 3 to 4 hours for us.
This doesn't make sense.
We brought the exact food
they mentioned in the comment.
- Among them...
- What's this?
"Food from a restaurant
with a long line?"
Does it mean we should eat
lining up?
One of you should get the food.
- We can't eat it either.
- No. I don't want to eat it.
It will take two hours at this hour.
What's this?
"Made by Se Chan without a tool?"
- With his hands.
- Without a tool.
He should make watermelon punch
with his hands.
How can we eat that?
Will he scoop out the watermelon
with his hands?
It's disgusting. We can't eat it.
I don't know about the others,
but I can't eat what he made.
He can't do it.
He touched his feet a lot earlier.
Get ready.
"Pepper ramyeon made by Ji Hyo"
is the best.
- Right.
- It's the best one.
"Pepper ramyeon made by Ji Hyo"
is the best.
Yes. Ramyeon.
This one is nice too.
Crabs are easy to shell.
- Right.
- I can't shell crabs.
(Hating)
- It's bothersome.
- So Min...
can make great pot rice.
- But it takes time.
- She's a good cook.
Ji Hyo's ramyeon,
So Min's pot rice,
and snow crabs are the best.
- Yes.
You can cover the roulette
through a simple mission again.
- Okay.
- It's Look Into My Eyes and Say It.
We can test how Running Man crew
who have been together...
for 12 years can read
each other's minds.
"Look Into My Eyes and Say It?"
We'll show you ten words.
One of them is the answer.
I'll show it
to the first member only.
The first member should describe
the word...
to the next member...
only with their eyes
and facial expressions.
- That's the rule.
- No way.
- So there are ten words.
- Yes.
Among those ten words.
- Among ten words.
- We can use eyes, right?
- Yes.
- As long as we don't say it.
You can't read lips.
We won't.
- We don't do stuff like that.
- We're not like that.
We're good. We won't do it.
We hate it the most.
We're veterans.
Sit in a row in the front.
The one at the end
will make a guess.
I think you should be the first one.
- It'd be better that way, right?
- Yes.
- You go after him, Ji Hyo.
- You go first, Jong Kook.
- Me?
- I'll go first.
- Yes.
- Start from there.
- I'll make a guess.
- So Min, you make a guess.
Wear your eye mask.
- We'll show you if you take it off.
- Let's go.
I'll wear it.
You should tell me what it is.
They will show me the answer.
- You should do well, Se Chan.
- Don't worry.
Let's go.
Don't try to do a trick, guys.
These are the words.
(Shampoo, butter, desire, massager,
fish, Yoo Se Yoon, crocodile,)
(monkey, Yoo Hui Yeol, lamb skewer)
Gosh.
- Take off your eye mask.
- This is hard.
It's hard.
- You can take off your eye mask.
- Okay.
- Let's see.
Okay.
"Shampoo." This is hard.
Monkey or Se Yoon?
- How do you describe Se Yoon?
- Go.
I'll just describe the key elements.
The key elements.
(Shampoo, butter, desire, massager,
fish, Yoo Se Yoon, crocodile,)
(monkey, Yoo Hui Yeol, lamb skewer)
It's over.
(Shampoo, butter, desire, massager,
fish, Yoo Se Yoon, crocodile,)
- Pass.
- "Desire" is so hard.
Just do as you always do.
I don't know what it is.
Just copy what I did.
You can't give her a hint.
Just copy what Jong Kook did.
(Ji Hyo tries to mimic what Jong Kook did
as closely as possible.)
Do it again.
What's the last facial expression?
Jae Suk, you can't watch.
(Glancing)
Jae Suk.
Why do you keep cheating?
- Why?
- I'm not cheating.
You should be fair and square.
It's over. It's Haha's turn.
Okay.
(It's Haha's turn.)
(Shampoo, butter, desire, massager,
fish, Yoo Se Yoon, crocodile,)
(monkey, Yoo Hui Yeol, lamb skewer)
Time's up.
Isn't it you?
I think he would know.
You can tell by a glance.
What is it? All of them are hard.
Okay.
No. He can get it
if he gets the point.
(Confused)
Isn't it you?
- You can't watch.
- Time is up.
(Shampoo, butter, desire, massager,
fish, Yoo Se Yoon, crocodile,)
(monkey, Yoo Hui Yeol, lamb skewer)
(His tongue moves are much louder.)
(Confused)
- Time's up.
- There's no word like this.
There's no word like this.
Think about it.
- There's no word like this.
- Watch closely.
- Take a close look.
Someone said "disgusting."
(Lastly, it's Se Chan's turn.)
- What is that?
- I don't know.
What is that?
- Come on.
- What is that?
- Guess.
- It isn't among the options.
- You can get it right.
- Do it again.
- It is among the options.
- You can get it right.
- There is one.
- What is that?
You can get it right.
What is that?
It isn't among the options.
- You can't give a hint.
- Okay.
- You can get it right.
- Yoo Se Yoon.
- No! It's a lamb skewer!
(They failed to use telepathy.)
- It's butter.
- It's greasy.
The answer is butter.
Why did you stick out your tongue
if it's butter?
Haha did that.
Ji Hyo did that.
- Ji Hyo, what did you do?
- I did this.
- It's greasy.
- Butter.
- You should have done this.
- For greasiness...
What is that?
- What would you do for butter?
- What?
- Go ahead.
- How would you act it out?
- Butter?
- What was that?
- Your tongue came out too.
That's disgusting.
- I get it now.
- What was that?
- You should have guessed.
You should have done this.
- This is fun.
- The next one.
- Let's change seats.
- All right. I will guess.
- Okay.
- I will go first.
- Go ahead.
- Please get ready.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk will go first
and Jong Kook will go last.)
All right. Jae Suk.
(Answer: Headache)
Don't add any elements
that could be confusing.
- Okay.
- Please take off your blindfolds.
I bet Jae Suk will make it
very confusing.
- I will guess the answer correctly.
- Squid.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
(Headache)
(Groaning)
- You can't make a sound, Jae Suk.
- Give him something big.
- You made a sound from the start.
- Something big.
You can't make a gesture.
Something big.
(He openly destroys the rules.)
- Start over.
- Why?
You can't make a gesture.
- Start over.
- Why?
He used his hands freely
and gave me all the clues.
He shouldn't have done this
for headache.
- I mean...
- You can't use your hands.
You can't do this for headache.
My glasses fell, so...
- Start over.
- You should look up and...
Add a slot for Jae Suk
to the wheel.
For goodness' sake.
You are overly strict.
- All right.
- Let's begin.
- That was so funny.
(Ear swab)
- Done?
- Take a look.
(It's pretty hard
to act out an ear swab.)
Let's look at the options.
- Gosh. Cat.
- There are many candidates.
- Look for a fitting option.
- Don't worry.
- Act it out to Se Chan.
- Find something similar.
Here I go.
- Don't use your hands.
- I won't.
Ear swab and earphones
will be confusing.
Pass.
He spoke.
(Laughing)
Why?
(He cheated again.)
- Why?
- Jae Suk.
Hey.
Why did you speak?
What did you do?
- I didn't give the answer.
- What did you do?
Jong Kook talked about ear swab,
so I went, "He mentioned it."
What's wrong with you?
- Seriously.
- For goodness' sake.
Change seats.
Don't be ridiculous.
- Se Chan.
- So Min, go first.
- I will be the first one to see it.
- Se Chan.
- So Min, go first.
- For goodness' sake.
Don't change anything.
Keep it as it is.
All right.
Gosh.
(Answer: Bottle opener)
- Use facial expressions only.
- Hold on.
You can look now.
Show Se Chan.
Loneliness, rice ball, Dooly...
This is hard.
How will you act out a rice ball?
- Rice ball?
- You got it, right?
Pretend to eat then.
(Just like So Min,
he uses his mouth.)
Pass.
All right.
- This is too easy.
- Go.
- That's the only option.
(This question is relatively easy.)
(Pop)
Bottle opener!
- Bottle opener!
- Bottle opener, right?
- I got that from the sound.
- What's wrong with you?
Why did you do that?
- I mean...
- Why did you ruin it?
I didn't mean to make a sound.
Why did you make a sound?
It just came out.
Why did you make a popping sound?
- Why did you do that?
- This is so frustrating.
Why did you do that?
Just act it out.
- Gosh.
- For goodness' sake.
- Isn't it pain?
- That's right.
- Nice!
- Okay!
- It's pain.
- Why is it pain?
- Is it pain? How did you know?
- It's pain.
- I will guess.
- It's the last question.
- Okay.
- Let's begin from that side.
- We should do that.
- I will give it a go.
We need to take out the bean noodles
made with millstones.
We need to take it out.
Green onion kimchi too.
I really want
the pepper ramyeon Ji Hyo made.
- I hope Jong Kook helps her.
- Pepper ramyeon.
(The answer gets revealed.)
How am I supposed to act it out?
You can look.
- Let's take a look.
- So Min, you can do it.
- It's the last question.
- You can do it.
- Hold on.
- You can figure it out.
- Passion.
I will send a telepathic message.
Look into my eyes.
(I will send a telepathic message.
Look into my eyes.)
(Passion, cheese, tie,
snake, rabbit)
Jae Suk, you can look
at the options.
(Joy, straw, Pepero,
ramyeon, candle)
- What?
- You get it, right?
- It can't be joy.
There is an option
that suits what I did.
- Think about how my eyes moved.
- Do exactly what she did.
(He kept it similar
to what So Min did.)
Don't speak.
What's that?
- Pass.
- Why don't you know?
- Are you done?
- What's that?
Nothing comes to mind.
Just do what you need to do.
(Upset)
What's that?
(He diligently relays what he saw.)
Jae Suk, it's your turn.
- It isn't among the options.
- I relayed what I saw.
Jae Suk, show it to Haha.
What's this?
Go ahead.
- Do you know what it is?
- Of course.
- What is it?
- Haha.
It's obvious.
- How did you figure it out?
- What's the answer?
(Did Haha figure it out
unlike Jae Suk and Suk Jin?)
Rabbit is an easy one.
- What is that?
- Rabbit is an easy one.
So it can't be that.
Jong Kook,
I will show you exactly what I saw.
Oh, is that it?
(She relays exactly what she saw
to Jong Kook.)
What's the answer?
- I know what it is.
- What is it?
- Three...
- You will be surprised.
- If you get it right...
- Please.
- What is it?
- Ramyeon.
- No!
- It's a tie.
- A tie.
- No!
- It's a tie.
- A tie.
- Is it a tie?
- You wear a tie like this.
- That's right.
- Haha.
- You push it up like this.
Haha, you got it.
- I got it, right?
- You got it.
You could have acted out
a tie differently.
I thought it was a candle.
- You could have done this.
- No.
- She acted out tying a tie.
- That's right.
So Min didn't know better
since she never wore a tie.
- She could have done this.
- Yes.
(He uses his hands.)
- You can't use your hands.
- For goodness' sake.
- By that logic,
- you can do this for a rabbit.
- Hey.
- You can do this for a snake.
- You can do this for ramyeon.
- As for Pepero...
- It's prohibited.
- You could have done this.
- No.
- I couldn't have done that.
- A tie was an easy one.
Let's have one more question.
- You can cover one slot.
- A tie was an easy one.
So Min did well.
What should we cover?
It should be the worst one.
In that case...
- This is fun.
- All right.
We covered it.
Write anything on top of it.
- In that case,
- In that case...
- shall we eat ramyeon?
- Let's eat ramyeon.
- Cup noodles.
- Ramyeon.
- Add eggs.
- Egg ramyeon.
- There you go.
- It's done.
Now, spin the wheel.
- Okay.
- You should do it.
- Let's go.
Good luck.
Millstones won't be so bad.
- We need to get ramyeon.
- Ramyeon.
(Out of the outrageous options,
which dish will they eat?)
- No.
- Let's go.
(What?)
- Hold on.
(Please!)
No.
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
- Yes!
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
- Yes!
(They covered 1 slot
and got what they wanted.)
- I...
- The pepper couple.
- Egg ramyeon by the pepper couple.
- We will make it.
- Yes!
- Let's go.
- Since it's ramyeon, I will do it.
- Make it tasty.
- Of course.
Make a lot.
(They happily begin
to prepare for lunch.)
Will you beat the eggs...
- or add them as they are?
- There is a method...
- of adding everything at once.
- That's a good method.
You add all ingredients at once...
when the water is cold.
- I used to make ramyeon that way.
- I hear that it's the best method.
It's the best method
for making tasty ramyeon.
A professor proved it.
I love ramyeon.
The pepper couple will cook it.
Move out of the way.
- Leave them to it.
- Add everything.
- Let's listen to music and relax.
- Okay.
- Add four to that pot.
Shall we add kimchi as well?
- Kimchi.
- Kimchi?
- How do you add it to kimchi?
- Don't you remember?
We added it right away.
Did we add it?
- I don't remember.
- We added a bit of it.
(Jong Kook adds the noodles
to cold water.)
You should add the noodles...
- when the water is boiling.
- Wait for it to boil.
No. It has been proven
that this method is better.
- Give me chopsticks.
- Who proved it?
- Don't do it so carelessly.
- But ramyeon...
- This is a good method.
You should add them
after the water boils.
- But ramyeon...
- No.
This is a good method. Look it up.
We are cooking them in two pots.
You shouldn't add noodles
before the water boils.
For goodness' sake.
- Excuse me.
- This ramyeon will taste bad.
Please move out of the way.
Haven't you heard of this method?
- Who cooks ramyeon this way?
- You are soaking the noodles.
- It has been proven to be the best.
- Who proved it?
- Look it up on the Internet!
Who proved it? It makes no sense.
- For goodness' sake.
- It has been...
- I should have cooked it.
- It has been tested.
I am good at cooking ramyeon.
I should have cooked it.
You wanted us to cook it.
(The cold water couple bickers.)
- Still
- What are the two of you doing?
- I call for you, I miss you
- Hurry over here.
Let's ask for snow crabs.
Let's add the snow crabs to ramyeon.
The power is off.
- We...
- Hey.
- Would you give us snow crabs?
The older members
can remove the meat.
You can have them
if the older members work on them.
- Jae Suk, remove the crab meat.
- Let's add it to the ramyeon.
- Let's do it.
Don't add it.
- Just eat it as it is.
- It will be tasty.
- Please do it.
- We will give you snow crabs.
- No.
- Remove the meat.
- I don't eat snow crabs at home.
- Do it just once.
I hate removing crab meat so much...
that I don't eat snow crabs.
- Please do it.
- It's too much work.
Please do it.
Give us watermelon punch
as a dessert.
I will make the watermelon punch.
I hate removing crab meat.
I will make tasty watermelon punch.
It's too much work.
Our hands will smell fishy too.
(Snow crabs appear.)
- Thank you.
- Only the older members can do it.
- Don't I count?
- No.
I won't do it. If we don't do it,
they won't eat the crabs.
- I won't do it.
- Me neither.
- Jae Suk.
- I won't do it.
Remove the meat.
Hurry up.
These gloves aren't fitting.
Just add the legs.
- I won't do it.
- Gosh.
It's too much work.
Don't do it.
The younger ones want to eat them.
Please do it this once.
- Please do it this once.
- I will make the dessert.
That's a nice watermelon.
- This...
- Jae Suk.
The taste will improve
if you add the innards.
- Snow crab ramyeon.
- Ramyeon turned into udon.
Jong Kook, ramyeon turned into udon!
It's ready now.
- Can we eat now?
- It's ready now.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- It's done already.
Water didn't even boil in this pot,
but my ramyeon is done.
(Cooking ramyeon in cold water
shortened the cooking time.)
It's a scientifically-proven method.
Stop making a fuss!
(He suddenly shouts.)
It's scientifically proven.
- Go home.
- It's done.
- Let's film some other time.
- Don't eat.
Let's just order deliveries.
- It's done.
- Go home.
- This is why I don't come outside.
- It's done.
- Don't be so cocky.
- Come here.
- Pack up.
- Remove the meat.
- Pack up, Ji Hyo.
It's done.
- Look. The noodles are firm.
- Go home.
It's done.
I cooked it so fast.
- That isn't what's important.
- It's tasty. Try it.
- Jae Suk, sit down.
- Eat.
- Eat what?
- It's done. Ramyeon.
- Try it.
- Get out.
Why did you come here?
Get out.
Don't make things worse.
Why are you filming it?
Get out.
Why did you come here?
- Eat.
- This isn't a cooking show.
Eat before the noodles become soggy.
- Seriously.
- I need an insert shot.
Really?
(Jong Kook tries
the cold water ramyeon.)
- He is hot-tempered. "Let go."
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, hurry up and try it.
- For goodness' sake.
- Try it.
- Aren't the noodles soggy?
- No. Hurry up and try it.
- The noodles aren't soggy.
- In that case,
I will divide them into big pieces.
Don't fake it. Try it for real
and see if the noodles are soggy.
- Here. Eat.
- Try it.
Jae Suk,
that's not how you open a crab.
Get the legs first.
Try it. Hey.
Try it.
Get the legs first.
(Suk Jin got some crabmeat.)
Try it.
Me too.
Is it tasty?
Suk Jin.
Jae Suk, try the snow crabs.
Hurry up and remove more crabmeat.
- In that case...
- It's tasty.
Snow crabs are really tasty.
Look. I finished cooking,
but she hasn't even begun yet.
Jae Suk, ramyeon is tasty.
- Really?
- It's tasty.
Jae Suk. It's so tasty.
I wasn't going to eat it
because of pride.
Listen to me.
Someone famous tested the method.
Try it.
- It's tasty.
- Jae Suk, ramyeon is tasty.
The noodles are tasty and firm.
- I cooked it in no time.
- You should know this.
- I am a ramyeon expert.
- Thank you.
A university tested this method.
I am a ramyeon expert,
so I can judge it right away.
- I will be objective.
- Try it.
- They tested this method.
- It's so tasty.
Try it first.
(My goodness.)
The noodles...
The noodles are firm.
It's the perfect method.
It boiled in no time.
- How are the noodles firm?
- Is it tasty or not?
- It's tasty.
- Right?
It's very tasty.
(He admits it in the end.)
(It's a happy ending.)
- It's so tasty.
- Try it.
- The snow crabs...
- Yes.
(While everyone eats,
Suk Jin sits before the crabs.)
- The snow crabs are delicious.
- Take off the legs.
Can't we touch the snow crabs?
Try it first.
(Sad)
(He removes the crabmeat
by himself.)
Put it in Ji Hyo's mouth.
- Ji Hyo, try the crabmeat.
- Ji Hyo.
It's so good.
The snow crabs are so tasty.
Suk Jin, would you work on
another crab?
(Suk Jin looks after the young ones
like the head of a household.)
- I am a ramyeon expert.
- Thank you.
Look at this.
Suk Jin gave it to me.
- I will cook another one.
- Gosh.
Look at this. Who wants to eat it?
- Me.
(He answered his own question.)
- Suk Jin.
- Hold on.
Suk Jin gave us so much crabmeat.
Why did you say, "Me?"
Try it.
Seriously. Can't we touch the crabs?
Can't we touch them?
I can remove the meat in no time.
Do you want to do it then?
- It isn't allowed.
- Why not?
Then Se Chan can be
the bigger brother...
from now on.
Ramyeon is really tasty.
That's a good idea.
Big brother.
- Hey, Jae Suk.
- Please remove the crabmeat.
All right.
I will do it for the young ones.
I will give you tasty crabmeat.
- Big brother.
- Okay.
- Please remove the crabmeat.
Don't worry.
I want to eat the crabmeat
you removed.
For goodness' sake.
Ramyeon is ready. Go ahead and eat.
It's tasty.
- Ji Hyo, it's so tasty.
- Let's try Ji Hyo's ramyeon.
Jong Kook's ramyeon has
firm noodles.
- Of course.
- It's tasty.
But compared to the one that's made
with care, it's different.
It's different.
(He inhaled
Jong Kook's ramyeon earlier.)
I did it earlier.
Here.
- This kimchi is tasty.
- Yes.
(The man who made
the cold water ramyeon is upset.)
You glared for a long time.
- Gosh, this is...
- It's incredible.
(Meanwhile, the master pulls
the snow crabs apart.)
- Can you do it fast?
- Of course.
Look at him.
How do you remove the crabmeat?
You need to take off the legs first.
Se Chan is an expert.
- You are good.
- Hey,
you once stole snow crabs
from a fish tank, right?
- Don't treat him as a younger one.
- He is a big brother.
- Big brother, you are good.
- He is the bigger brother.
- Suk Jin.
- Se Chan is the bigger brother.
Look. This is it.
(A thick piece of crabmeat
over the firm ramyeon noodles)
Jae Suk, this is it.
Please put it here.
Gosh, this is...
I didn't know
snow crabs were so tasty.
- Didn't you know?
- No.
This is a proper vacation.
- That's right.
- This is happiness.
- This is happiness. I am happy.
- That's right.
Eating ramyeon is enough
to make me happy.
Se Chan, would you make
the watermelon punch first?
- Of course.
- Work on the watermelon.
- Do you mean big brother?
- Se Chan.
Treat him as someone who is older.
He actually is older than me.
He is older than the producer.
I see.
- He is older than the producer.
- I am pretty old.
How will you do it with your hands?
Can you break it?
Do what you need to do
without any tools.
This comment got
the most number of likes.
I get to make watermelon punch
for the younger ones. Thank you.
Not bad.
Gosh, the sound is nice.
(The watermelon is ripe.)
- It isn't working.
- You will die at that rate.
- Use your head.
(The watermelon is
as hard as Se Chan's head.)
It's working.
All right.
(He knuckled the watermelon
and got a small crack!)
(He tries to rip it apart.)
Let's get the juice.
- Hey.
- We can't eat that.
Are you a primitive man?
How are we supposed to eat that?
I can't use any tools!
- It's almost done.
- How are we supposed to eat that?
(Se Chan diligently follows
the viewers' request.)
For goodness' sake.
(The watermelon opens.)
Hey.
How will we eat that?
Hold on.
Put on gloves. Seriously.
- It's tasty.
- Seriously.
You didn't go
to the restroom today, did you?
- No.
- You did.
Did you wash your hands afterward?
- Yes.
- You didn't.
I washed my hands.
(He squeezes the watermelon
for the juice.)
Juice is coming out.
I didn't touch that.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
Would you eat that?
(The sight kills their appetite.)
The watermelon smells incredible.
It looks pretty good.
He has to make it
without using any tools.
It's what the viewers wanted.
Pour Sprite.
- Ice.
- Watermelon.
(Ice is essential
to the watermelon punch.)
Doesn't it feel like
you are on a vacation?
- It will be good without sugar.
- Is that Sprite?
- Yes.
- You add Sprite.
- You need to add a bit of milk too.
- But it really does feel...
like a vacation.
Don't lie.
Now that he split a watermelon,
it feels like a vacation.
We are on the third one.
- Me?
- If you use your fingers...
If you use your fingers...
I didn't want to add too much.
Just pour it into the bowl.
Hey!
- Hey!
- I had to take some out.
I didn't want to add all of it.
Your fingers...
Stop using your fingers.
You picked your nose earlier.
That watermelon punch will be salty.
I will mix it like this.
(Se Chan's watermelon punch
will be salty.)
All right. It's ready.
(Chef Yang's watermelon punch
is ready.)
I mean...
- Hey.
- The viewers will be unhappy too.
(He already has a bowl ready.)
Try it.
Try it, Jae Suk.
Give it to me.
I have a strong stomach.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
I won't die.
Who is next?
Give it to me.
I should try the punch Se Chan made.
It's especially sweet.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Did you add salt?
(Eating)
(Jae Suk tries a bite as well.)
Is it good?
Is it tasty? What do you think?
(Choking)
He got poisoned.
How does the watermelon punch taste?
- It's bland.
- I will try it.
Hey.
- What?
- You shouldn't have blown...
on the bowl.
- You...
- Why did you do that?
- Did you do it to remove the dust?
- He did it without thinking.
- The dust.
It was my attempt to make it clean.
Hey, Se Chan.
You should eat that one.
- Okay.
- You should eat that one.
Dust will be cleaner...
- than your breath.
- Although it's tasty...
Se Chan.
- It's tasty.
- We should share the punch. Look.
(We should share the punch. Look.)
(He suddenly decides to share
the watermelon punch.)
That's right.
It's sweet and good.
Mr. Park, have a bowl.
He must be hot.
Give it to Hyung In and Bo Pil.
That's right.
- That's right.
- Give me more bowls.
- Give us more bowls.
- Yes.
- It feels like a holiday.
- It's pretty good.
- Should I make more?
- The staff members work hard.
- Make more.
My goodness.
Have a bowl.
Have a bowl. Come on.
Hey, you should have some.
Just try it. Hey.
We can't do that.
Hey, have some.
That's nice, Se Chan. I like it.
Do you like fruit?
Do you want more?
Just say stop when you have enough.
- We should give this to him.
- He should try this.
Say stop. Do you want me to stop?
Hey, it's not bad. It tastes good.
- It's tasty.
- Mr. Park. It's delicious.
But why aren't you eating?
- It tastes good.
- But...
- why aren't you eating it?
- I'm eating. It's good.
It tastes really good.
- You're just pretending to eat.
- I like it.
I just tried it. It's really nice.
It's really good.
Gosh, this tastes good.
- I like it.
- Me too.
Why do you put your thumb in it?
(Putting his thumb in it)
That's just...
- It's just...
- It's all right.
You did a great job.
- It's nice.
- I have no tools.
But you don't have to put
your thumb in it.
This is my sincere heart.
That's what they do
when they serve seolleongtang.
Mr. Park, have some. It's hot today.
Try this.
Put down the camera and eat this.
- We're family.
- Of course.
Gosh, this is nice.
- It must be cool.
- All right!
We should give it
to the assistant directors.
Here. Try this.
- Se Chan made it for us.
- We couldn't...
eat it without you guys.
I washed my hands. It's all right.
I liked the ramyeon and everything.
This is really nice.
Now we will move to our
last destination to have fun.
- Okay.
- Let's pick the quiz.
- I want the quiz.
- Having Fun at Water Park.
- Okay.
- Okay. This is it.
- I like it.
- Having Fun at Water Park.
What's the water park? Is this it?
- We're eight years old.
- Jae Suk.
- Eight years old.
- Can you do that?
So Min.
This is the last one.
Our viewers want to see you
find your childhood innocence.
- I like that.
- All right.
The eight-year-old Running Man
members are on a school trip.
Are we eight years old?
You are all of the same age.
- We're of the same age.
- We are friends.
There you go.
I want to be my eight-year-old self.
So Min, what are you doing?
What kind of eight-year-old boy
has age spots on his face?
Why does he have long hair
on his face?
I'm eight years old.
My mom got me a new bag.
Hey, you can't put anything...
- in your bag.
- Teacher.
(Feeling dizzy)
Eight-year-old boys can speak well.
Teacher.
Suk Jin wet his pants.
I didn't wet my pants. They're dry.
What kind of eight-year-old boy...
An eight-year-old boy
wouldn't wet his pants.
(The 8-year-old members
go to the water park.)
This is a vacation.
(The 8-year-old members
go to the water park.)
This is a water park.
- This is nice.
- I love it.
We're...
- at a water park!
- This is a water park.
(This isn't product placement,
but they are making an ad.)
(Shouting)
(Screaming)
My goodness.
So Min, what are you doing?
Is this your first time
at a water park?
You have to get wet
under the huge bucket first.
- All right.
- Let's do this.
Here we go.
We can't call it a vacation trip
without getting wet.
This is a vacation trip.
I will never fall over.
I won't fall over.
Let's have fun!
Swag!
- Bring it on!
- It's coming.
(Getting doused with water)
(Falling on their buttocks
pathetically)
- Darn it.
- My goodness.
You got me. You're the best.
(A surprise attack from the back)
(The Nevis Swing Brothers are
slaughtered by the water.)
(What the heck!)
No.
I'm scared, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo and So Min try
the water slide.)
Gosh, So Min.
(Starting)
It's scary.
- I'm so scared.
- My gosh.
Hey, this is so fast.
(She gets soaked in shock...)
(and slides into the hole.)
(Screaming)
(Turning over)
(While the two girls are busy
enjoying the water slide...)
It hurts.
Okay.
(Jong Kook is trying
the single slide.)
Like this?
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
(Starting)
(Shouting)
What? It's too dark.
What's happening?
(What's happening?)
(It ends
after going straight ahead.)
(He just douses himself with water.)
What was that? It wasn't fun at all.
Darn it!
(Jong Kook is bold,
but he is grumpy.)
It's not fun at all!
- There you go.
- Gosh, already?
(Shouting)
Gosh, it's too fast.
(They go back to their 8-year-old
selves having fun in water.)
Yes. I like this one.
(They go back to their 8-year-old
selves having fun in the water.)
(Like little kids,)
Come here.
(they frolic in the water
shouting out loud.)
(They enjoy the vacation
on behalf of the viewers.)
He's coming.
(The seven grownups forget about
everything and have a lot of fun.)
(You can watch the full version
on Running Man's YouTube channel.)
Please gather around.
(You can watch the full version
on Running Man's YouTube channel.)
You need to fill in the blank now.
Write down the name
of the person who's not here.
- Let's do that.
- Who's not here?
It's Seok Sam.
(Seok Sam is still
having fun in the water.)
Hey, this is really fun.
(It seems like he doesn't
want to go home.)
- What is he doing there?
- He's not here yet.
He never listens to us.
- I'll put your name on it.
- Go ahead and put it.
No.
I'm riding the waves.
This is today's penalty.
You will put
on the vacation outfit...
and hand out 50 fans to people.
(Hand out 50 fans to people
in the vacation outfit.)
- Okay.
- This is harsh.
(They have to find 50 people
under the scorching sun.)
- All right.
- Spin it?
- Yes.
- No Penalty.
(They will spin the roulette to pick
1 member to get the penalty.)
(The roulette will decide
the members' fate.)
Pick No Penalty.
It will complete today's vacation.
I'll spin it. If we get No Penalty,
it will complete our vacation.
- I agree.
- One, two...
(Spinning the roulette)
Please.
(Who among the four members
will get the penalty?)
No Penalty.
- Please.
- No Penalty.
(Who among the four members
will get the penalty?)
- Look.
- Okay!
(No Penalty?)
- Yes!
- Hey.
- I can't believe this.
(They picked No Penalty
with a 50 percent chance.)
- No Penalty.
- That's nice.
- We don't get a penalty today.
- This is a real vacation.
The grand finale of the vacation.
- You're the best, Jae Suk.
- We did it.
- Nice.
- I knew it.
- I didn't know why I was tired,
but I just realized
that we played Tug of War.
I'm so tired.
- We had a long day.
- And we ran.
- We ran a lot.
- It was really exciting.
Tug of War, running, and rides.
And we ate many things.
We will fall asleep right away
as soon as we get home.
- I'll fall fast asleep.
- I know.
All right.
The Running Man Vacation is over.
- Bye.
Bye.
- Thank you.
- So Min, ride that one again.
- Nice.
I want to ride it again.
(The place that has
a lot of rumors flying around)
(This is our matrimonial home.)
(They finally go into...)
(My Little Old Boy's place.)
(The VIP guests show up
without an invitation.)
(In this place where they
stress each other out...)
(Relieve your stress.)
- Do you have a personal trainer?
- Watch.
(Those who cry because of stress...)
(are the third class.)
(Biting the bullet.)
(Your home?)
(Those who endure it
are the second class.)
(Like son.)
(Like son running around?)
(Those who laugh off the stress
are the first class.)
(Seal your anger...)
(and be happy.)
(I control my mentality...)
(Slapping)
(Laughter brings you good luck!)
(House Jong Kook)