(Monday, 7:30 a.m., Deungchon SBS)
(The producer is waiting
for someone in the waiting room.)
Aren't we shooting yet?
(At that moment...)
Hello.
(Se Chan came an hour early
as a punishment from last week.)
- What's going on?
- Hello.
Are we having a test?
I don't know.
Is this a test?
I'll get everything wrong
if I take a test.
First,
choose a uniform you want.
- Anything?
- You can pick anything you want.
A color I want? I pick purple.
- The purple one.
- Yes.
- Today,
- Yes?
we will have a complicated mission.
So we need to explain it
before we start.
- Okay.
- I'll explain it to each member.
All right.
Please listen carefully.
Today, we are having
The 1st Division Game.
We will pick the luckiest one
among the members of Running Man.
(We will pick the luckiest one
among the members of Running Man.)
So the seven members will...
decide the ranking
through missions...
- where you need good luck.
- Okay.
And the last of each mission
with the worst luck...
- will be eliminated.
- Okay.
(The security guard
suddenly shows up.)
And the last of each mission
with the worst luck...
- will be eliminated.
- Okay.
That means a member will be
eliminated in each round.
And the one who survives
till the end will be the winner.
I see.
If you are eliminated
after a mission, a penalty ball...
I see.
(What's going on?)
with your name on it will be added.
We will draw a penalty ball
at the end...
to pick a member to get a penalty.
(Laughing)
If you're eliminated, you will
just get an extra penalty ball.
You still can take part
in the next missions.
What is he doing?
- But from the following missions,
- Okay.
(Looking straight at him)
You have to make the top three
not to get an extra penalty ball.
(Flustered)
If you fail to make the top three,
you'll get an extra penalty ball.
- Please focus.
- I'm sorry.
And we have special rules
for today's race.
- Our 100 staff members will join.
- Our 100 staff members?
They will vote for a member
whom they think will survive.
If the member survives,
the staff who voted for the member
will also survive.
If the member survives,
(He suddenly takes off his shirt.)
the staff who voted for the member
will also survive...
and advance to the next round.
- Okay.
- If the member is eliminated...
My goodness.
(This is just the beginning.)
(Warming up)
(He starts dancing in earnest.)
What is going on? What is he doing?
- Hey, he will take off his pants.
- You need to focus.
My goodness.
If you advance to the next round...
What?
(He can't believe his eyes.)
If you advance to the next round,
they will cast a vote again.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, I do.
The race is
called the Division Game...
because the winner and those who
voted for the person will...
(Giggling)
- I get it.
- divide up the money.
We will divide up the money.
Can you please stop him?
Please stop him.
- I need you to focus.
- Okay.
And you will get a prize based on
the number of coins you win.
So in the final...
What about the finals?
(His dance confuses
even the producer.)
You can just give it away.
- This is an important rule.
- Okay.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, I do.
There will be 100 staff members.
- Share the money with 100 people.
- They will take a vote.
The one who loses
the race will be eliminated.
And the winner and those who...
voted for the person
will share the money.
- This is the rule.
- I'm sorry,
but will he be
doing this seven times?
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
- I'm done explaining the rules.
- Okay.
- We're doing it with 100 people.
- And this was...
- the preliminary mission for today.
- I see.
We measured the time...
when you were distracted
by the dancing security guard.
(They measured the time when he was
distracted by the security guard.)
We will announce how long...
you stared at the security guard
as I was reading the rules to you.
Now you will move
to the monitoring room...
and watch
how the other members react.
This is hilarious.
I almost cried.
This is unbelievable.
Hello.
(He enters the monitoring room.)
My gosh.
That was so funny.
It was unbelievable.
It's hilarious.
I've never seen a man
who looked so sexy while dancing.
I mean, his pelvis came this far up.
He shook his hips like this.
I bet So Min will keep...
staring at him
once he takes off his shirt.
But the dancer might change
depending on the color they choose.
The color?
(He made a choice
before the preliminary mission.)
The color of the uniform?
(He made a choice
before the preliminary mission.)
(Se Chan was told to choose
a uniform when he entered the room.)
(Se Chan chose purple
among punk, mint, and purple.)
So will there be three dancers?
I mean, three teams?
Hello.
(In the meantime, Jae Suk
arrived early as a penalty.)
What?
- What is going on?
- Hello.
- What are you doing, Bo Pil?
- First,
choose a uniform you want.
- A uniform?
- Yes.
(If he picks purple, the dancing
security guard will enter.)
Well...
I don't like this one.
I'll go with either mint or pink.
- I want pink today.
- Pink it is.
Just put it there.
- Put it here?
- I'll get you one.
Okay. Pink.
We will have
a complicated mission today.
So I'll explain it to each member
before we start.
Please listen carefully.
- What is it?
- The name of today's race...
is The 1st Division Game.
We will pick the luckiest one
among the members of Running Man.
- The Division Game?
- Yes.
Then I'll be eliminated right away.
The last of each mission with
the worst luck will be eliminated.
(A man with a big bag?)
That means a member will be
eliminated in each round.
The last of each mission with
the worst luck will be eliminated.
That means a member will be
eliminated in each round.
- Yes.
- And the one who survives...
till the end will be the winner.
(Rustling)
One member will be eliminated
after a mission in each round.
If you are eliminated
after a mission,
(He takes out a tennis racket.)
a penalty ball with your name
on it will be added.
- A penalty ball?
- Yes.
- The one who comes in last...
- Who is he, by the way?
will get an extra penalty ball.
- A penalty ball.
- We will draw a penalty ball...
at the end...
We will draw
a penalty ball at the end...
to pick a member to get a penalty.
- Draw a penalty ball? Okay.
- Please stay focused.
- Okay. I'll focus.
- You'll get an extra penalty ball,
but you can still take part
in the next missions.
- So I get an extra penalty ball?
- Yes.
- An extra ball in each round.
- Okay.
That's Mr. Tong Dance.
Gosh, Bo Pil.
He's doing Mr. Tong Dance.
(Carried away)
(He can't believe what he's seeing.)
Please focus.
From the following missions,
you have to make the top three
not to get an extra penalty ball.
If you fail to make the top three,
you'll get an extra penalty ball.
- I have to make the top three.
- If you fail to do it,
you'll get an extra penalty ball.
And we have special rules
for today's race.
Our 100 staff members will join.
- Right. I saw them wearing hats.
- Exactly.
(Giggling)
- Please stop.
- If the member they voted for...
advances to the next round,
they can also survive.
Gosh, look at him.
(Struggling)
I can't focus because of him.
He can't do it,
but he's forcing himself.
The rule is important.
If the chosen member is eliminated,
they will be eliminated as well.
- Okay.
- When the next round begins,
they will cast a vote again.
Let's say you voted for Suk Jin,
and he got eliminated.
- Then you're out as well.
- I get it.
So...
- Then you're out as well.
- I get it.
- So...
- Why is he going into the bag?
The race is
called the Division Game...
because the winner
and those who voted...
for the person will
divide up the money.
What is he doing?
And you will get a prize based on...
(He can't help
but watch him struggle.)
- Darn it.
- the number of coins you win.
- I see.
- We prepared expensive gifts.
Okay. So this is like a random game.
There will be missions.
And the next round...
He might get hurt.
(He ends up turning his head again.)
Please stop it.
That's enough, sir.
My gosh.
- So you will share the money.
- Hello, Writer.
Yes.
- I nailed it.
- All right.
Yes. I'm going out.
And you will win the prize.
(Flustered)
Gosh, what was he doing?
What was that?
Why would he tell the writer
that he nailed it?
All right.
Do you understand the rules?
I think I do. But because of him...
This was
the preliminary mission for today.
- You picked the pink uniform today,
- I chose pink.
so the guy came in.
We measured the time
when you were distracted by him.
He was making a fuss
right next to me.
How can I not watch him?
I asked you to focus.
But he fell over and everything.
How would I not see that?
Please move to the monitoring room.
I can't believe this.
- How would I not watch it at all?
- Jae Suk.
I laughed myself to death.
I had someone else in the room.
- Who was it?
- It was a different man.
A security guard came in...
and started dancing Zero Two.
And he took off his shirt.
Right in front of me,
he was dancing like this.
You just can't help it.
- How would you ignore it?
- I don't know.
I don't understand the rules.
He did Mr. Tong Dance.
(So Min is coming next.)
Hello, Ji Yeon.
There's a camera. Hello.
(She says hello to the camera
even before entering the room.)
- Hello.
- No one's here.
- Come in.
I'm lonely
I want to meet someone nice
- Hello.
- Today...
- Where's everyone?
- Pick a uniform you want.
- We have three?
- Yes. Pick one of the three.
(So Min picks a uniform
as soon as she gets in.)
- Well...
- Pick purple.
I'll pick the color I look good in.
Purple. I knew it.
I knew she'd pick it.
You'll see.
She can't get away with this.
We will have a complicated mission.
- I'll explain it to each member.
- You don't have to do that.
Please listen carefully.
And why do you have walls like that?
Do you think I can't see
the camera behind the wall?
All right. Let me explain.
She can't focus from the beginning.
The first...
We will pick the luckiest one
among the members of Running Man.
And the last of each mission...
(A security guard enters the room.)
And the last of each mission with
the worst luck will be eliminated.
Why do you have to...
You have to listen to it first.
Do you have to explain all that?
The last of each mission with
the worst luck will be eliminated.
That means a member will be
eliminated in each round.
- If you are eliminated...
- What?
(What?)
And the one who survives
till the end will be the winner.
- Please focus.
- Well...
What is he doing?
- Please focus.
- Well...
(He starts dancing.)
What is he doing? All of a sudden...
- If you are eliminated...
- What?
A penalty ball... Please focus.
- I mean...
- A penalty ball with your name...
- on it will be added.
- He's dancing.
- Okay.
- You will get an extra ball.
We will draw a penalty ball
at the end...
- Please explain it again.
- to pick a member to get a penalty.
- Can you explain it again?
- Please focus.
We will draw a penalty ball
to pick a member to get a penalty.
From the following missions,
you have to make the top three
not to get an extra penalty ball.
If you fail to make the top three,
you'll get an extra penalty ball.
- He's feeling hot.
- It's hot.
So you should try your best
to complete the missions.
And we have special rules
for today's race.
Our 100 staff members
will join the survival.
- A hundred staff members?
- Yes, they'll choose the member...
they think will survive
in each round.
- The chosen member...
- My gosh!
(Genuinely screaming)
What is he doing?
(She reacts loudly.)
- What is he doing?
- Why would he take his shirt off?
- I don't know.
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing? Gosh!
- The members will advance... Focus.
- Please focus on this.
- My goodness. What is he doing?
Gosh. I have goosebumps.
- What are you doing?
- And...
Why did he remove his body hair?
- And if the member...
- What is he doing now?
- Please focus.
- My goodness.
How can I focus on
what you're saying?
If the member they chose
gets eliminated,
- So Min doesn't bother to listen.
- the staff members will...
I was so surprised
that I almost peed myself.
Why are you doing this? Gosh.
- It's called The Division Game...
- Who...
- for a reason.
- Who are you?
The winner and the staff members
who voted for that member...
will divide the prize money evenly,
and receive a gift
that's worth the money they won...
after dividing the money evenly.
- Do you understand?
- Wait.
Who...
- One more thing.
- He... The man... Who was he?
This rule briefing was
the pre-mission.
- No, wait.
- You chose the purple uniform.
And we measured the time you were
distracted by the security guard.
The measured time is your record.
Wait. Hold on.
I mean... My gosh.
He took me by surprise.
- You can leave now.
- I should've looked closely at him.
- What was that?
- So Min.
What was that?
You barely listened to him.
- But...
- Hey, So Min.
- You were amazed by his dance.
- Come on in.
Actually, I want to see it again.
- Why?
- I couldn't see it closely.
- You saw it closely.
- Come on. Stop lying.
You didn't even look at Bo Pil.
I saw that your eyes were open wide.
- Jae Suk, I was so surprised.
- I was surprised too.
That was shocking.
What could be done
if anyone picks the mint green one?
The mint green... Suk Jin came in.
He's wearing a bright color today.
First, please choose the color
of the team uniform.
This one looks better... Okay.
I pick this one.
- He picked the pink one.
- I chose that one. Yes.
The title of today's race is
The 1st Division Game.
I bet
he won't be able to concentrate.
Suk Jin is already distracted.
Look.
- It's called The 1st Division Game.
- The 1st Division Game.
We'll select the luckiest member
of Running Man.
(Big Nose is known
not to listen to mission rules.)
- Testing our luck?
- In each mission,
the unluckiest member
in the last place gets eliminated.
- The last place gets eliminated.
- The unluckiest member fails.
(He turns his head around.)
That is, one member gets eliminated
in each mission.
And the last member remaining
wins the race.
- I see.
- He's indifferent to others.
Each time a member gets eliminated,
a penalty ball...
with that member's name on it
will be added.
(Then Suk Jin looked at him.)
That means the eliminated member
gets an additional penalty ball.
- At the end of the race,
- Hold on a second.
we'll randomly pick a penalty ball
to pick the member to get a penalty.
(Suk Jin saw the Mr. Tong.)
- Who is he?
- But the last place...
- I couldn't hear anything.
- can play the next game.
- Wait. Can you repeat it?
- Do you understand?
- But from that mission,
- I mean, he...
if you failed to be
in the top three,
- you get another penalty ball.
- A penalty ball?
- Gosh, I didn't hear anything.
- You have to do well...
even after getting eliminated.
- We have an unusual rule this time.
- What is he doing?
- Hang on. I missed this part...
- All right.
What is he doing?
Hang on. I missed this part...
(Exhaling loudly)
He's not good at doing that dance.
That makes it even funnier.
He's hilarious.
Goodness.
- The staff members get eliminated.
- What is going on?
One member gets eliminated each time
until we have the winner.
- Do you understand?
- I couldn't hear anything.
- Since he came in...
- Let's move on.
The winner and the staff members
will divide the prize evenly.
(Inhaling)
- Since they divide...
- The winner...
(He starts the funniest performance
while exhaling loudly.)
the last member remaining...
- How do you expect me to focus?
- The winner...
He won't stop it.
- If...
- It's impossible to hold back.
(It's hard to see the intention
of his performance.)
- You can't hold back laughter.
- You can't.
- I want to see him closely.
- How can you not laugh?
They will receive a gift as well.
That is, the staff members' fate is
in your hands.
Please focus.
- How am I supposed to focus?
- Their fate is in your hands.
(He's too distracted
to think about the rules.)
- Hello? Writer, hello. Yes.
- I can't...
- Yes, I pulled it off.
- No one can focus despite that.
- That's what this game is about.
- Yes. I'm on my way.
- Come on. I couldn't hear anything.
- Try hard to win the race.
What did you say
we'll divide evenly?
- Gold?
- You just had a pre-mission.
Then the rules are fake too, right?
- I'm relieved.
- They're real. I'm done explaining.
- You're done explaining?
- You listened carefully.
I listened,
but I didn't understand anything.
(He'll play games without knowing
the rules as always.)
Hi, guys.
(Next up is Ji Hyo.)
- What's going on?
- Hello.
Hello.
- Ji Hyo came in.
- What's going on?
Why is no one else here?
Please choose
one of the team uniforms.
Should I choose one of them?
(We don't know anything about
the mint green uniform yet.)
Well... I pick the mint green color.
- You can leave it there.
- Okay.
- He didn't laugh.
- None of us chose that color.
- That's right.
- This is the first time.
- Is this the first time?
- Yes.
- The mint green color.
- She's the first one to pick it.
We're going to select
the luckiest member of Running Man.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
In each mission, the unlucky member
in the last place...
(Giggling)
Baby, my legs hurt.
- Your legs hurt?
- They're a couple.
- They're role-playing.
- This will be funny.
- They're a couple?
- The member gets eliminated.
- One of you gets eliminated...
- Baby, my legs hurt.
- in each round.
- Your legs hurt?
- Yes.
- There's a bench here.
- It's a bit chilly in here.
- The last member remaining...
- Right?
- wins the race.
- Got it.
- Come here.
It's so warm.
Come here.
(What are they doing?)
- I'll make you warmer.
- I see.
- Come here.
- They can move on with the others.
They can move on with the others.
- They get eliminated as well.
- You're so handsome, baby.
- You're so pretty.
- Got it.
- Give me a kiss. One more time.
- Again?
- I bet they're not a real couple...
- Give me a kiss.
- They actually kissed.
- They just kissed.
- My gosh.
- They actually kissed.
- Did they actually kiss?
- They kissed.
Look at her. She's laughing.
(They're a real couple.)
- Give me a kiss.
- What's wrong with them?
- Hey. Excuse me.
- My darling.
- One member gets eliminated...
- Why would they do that in here?
- in each round.
- Baby, you made my heart flutter.
- The last one remaining wins.
- Are you okay?
Baby, that woman just looked at me.
That's because you're very handsome.
- Excuse me. This is crazy.
- She has good taste in men.
- It's The 1st Division Game.
- Don't look at me.
- What about pork cutlets?
- Pork cutlets?
- I love it.
- I like pork cutlets.
- Here you go. Open.
- Yoom. Feed me.
Ji Hyo won't look at them.
- She won't look at them.
- Exactly.
- She's amazing.
- She won't look at them.
- She's completely focused.
- She's incredible.
- Give me a kiss.
- Again?
(Even when they kiss, she won't
turn around to look at them.)
- Shall we go out now?
- Okay.
They will divide
the prize of 100 R evenly,
- Baby, can you open the door?
- and receive a gift...
- Okay.
- that's worth the divided money.
- Try to win the race.
- Gosh.
- I don't understand a word you say.
- Do you understand?
No, I don't.
The members will be ranked
through games that require luck.
The unluckiest member
in the last place gets eliminated.
(Haha focuses on the briefing
right after glancing at him.)
- That is...
- It seems like a mistake at first.
- Up until this point.
- Right, I thought...
he was a real security guard.
- He must not know yet.
- Got it.
- That person wins the race.
- I see.
Each time a member gets eliminated,
a penalty ball...
a penalty ball will be added.
Your phone is ringing.
At the end of the race, we'll
randomly pick one penalty ball...
to choose the member
to get a penalty.
(Haha's eyes are fixed on him.)
The eliminated member will
get a penalty ball,
but he or she will still be
in the race.
(He starts giggling.)
He's good at dancing.
- He's a great dancer.
- Indeed.
You get an additional penalty ball
if you're not in the top three.
Wait. What is he doing?
What on earth is he doing now?
You get an additional penalty ball
if you're not in the top three.
(The security guard has improved
his dance skills.)
- They'll vote for 1 member.
- I see. There will be 100 of them.
- In each round...
- What are you doing now?
In each round,
the staff members will choose...
- He must've lost his mind. Look.
- Please focus.
(Dancing topless)
If the member they chose...
- He's good. You can't ignore him.
- He's good, indeed.
He's really good.
- He's so good.
- He looks like...
He looks like a gymnast.
He looks like someone I know.
They survive as well.
- He removed his body hair.
- Likewise,
those who chose the eliminated
member get eliminated too.
Look how thin his waist is.
So Min will get so excited.
That member wins the race.
You should bounce
your pelvis harder.
I'll show you.
You should put your knees together.
Like this. That's good.
Yes, you're doing great.
(Haha even gives him feedback
without worrying about the rules.)
Yes, you're doing great.
That's it. Do you understand?
- I knew it.
- He'll be in the last place.
- Haha is doomed.
- He was watching the whole time.
He'll be in the last place.
The time you got distracted is
your record.
- But I heard everything.
- The longer, the worse.
I was listening
while looking at him.
- I can explain the rules to you.
- Even so...
I watch TV while using my phone.
Please move to the other room.
I had to respond to that
as an entertainer.
Please move to the other room.
My gosh. You have changed a lot.
That hurts my feelings.
Go to the other room.
(Bo Pil firmly asked him to leave.)
This is how you should do the dance.
(The orange thimble leaves
after enjoying the concert.)
I wonder what we'll do today.
(The last member Jong Kook appears.)
Hi, guys.
Gosh. What is this?
- Hello.
- Hi.
(He enters the room
with a wary look on his face.)
What are you doing so early?
- He's suspicious about everything.
- Right.
Hello.
Good morning.
- First...
- We're shooting later than usual.
- First, choose the color you want.
- Yes.
I like the mint green color. Okay.
- Today...
- Yes.
- I like the mint green color.
- The mint green color?
- He picked mint green?
- There's no way he knows.
- Today, in each mission,
- Yes.
the unluckiest one
in the last place...
- gets eliminated.
- I see.
Baby, aren't you cold?
I'm a little cold.
- I feel cold too.
- Please focus.
- How about we use our body heat...
- One member gets eliminated.
- to keep each other warm?
- Got it.
- Okay.
- If you get eliminated,
- When did you get your hair permed?
- a penalty ball...
- It looks beautiful.
- Yes.
- Really? You look so handsome.
- When you're eliminated,
- I got dolled up. How do I look?
- you still can play the next games.
You're all mine.
- Am I all yours?
- Yes.
- Then give me a kiss.
- Here.
(They began the kiss attack.)
- I see.
- I'm cold. You're cold too, right?
- Jong Kook won't look around.
- I'll make you warm.
- Yes.
- How is it?
You're the best.
- Am I the best?
- Yes.
- I can make you warm.
- I see.
- Really? How?
- Come here.
- Oh, I see.
- We've become one.
Nice. It's so warm.
- Baby, it's so warm.
- Really?
Actually,
I can make you even warmer.
- How?
- I have...
- a heat pad on my lap.
- Really?
But if I sit on your lap,
- you'll be too tired.
- Oh, really?
Come on.
You're as light as a feather.
- Am I as light as a feather?
- Jong Kook won't look at them.
- Of course, you are.
- He's holding his temper.
He's like a robot.
- He's focusing on one thing.
- That's right. He just wants...
- to understand the rules.
- He knows that it's a mission.
- He's ignoring them.
- He won't look at them.
- I'll kiss you as a prize.
- They'll divide the prize of 100 R.
- Really? Kiss me.
- I'll kiss you.
- Again.
- Okay.
(Even the kisses can't
distract him.)
- You'll receive a gift.
- I see.
- How about a human amusement ride?
- Their fate is in your hands.
- I see.
- Do you understand?
The 100 staff members...
- How about a human amusement ride?
- I see.
(The human amusement ride
performance.)
The 100 staff members...
They divide the prize?
Yes. I mean, no.
- Those who survived to the end.
- The ones remaining at the end.
Those who voted for the last place
get eliminated too.
- Baby.
- Try to win the race.
- Those who didn't...
- Yes.
- survive the round.
- Shall we get going now?
- Okay. Let's go.
- The staff members survive too.
- They vote in each round.
- Correct.
- Those who survive to the end...
- That's right.
- win the race.
- To the end, yes.
The winner and the staff members
will divide the prize.
- Right? I understand.
- Yes, that's correct.
My gosh. He's so competitive.
- You see...
- I won't listen anymore.
I wish he had picked
the Zero Two dancer.
- Why is he so serious about it?
- He would still be like this.
Can't you send the Zero Two dancer?
- Hi, Jong Kook.
- Hey, how could you...
- keep ignoring them like that?
- Jong Kook.
- I can't believe you.
- What?
- Why didn't you look at them?
- They even kissed each other.
- They kissed in front of you.
- They didn't fake it.
- I listened to him as I was told.
- You ignored them.
- I always listen to Bo Pil.
- Jong Kook.
- You're amazing.
- He said I should listen carefully.
- Did you understand the rules?
- Of course.
- I heard everything he said.
- Gosh.
You all heard about the rules
of today's race, right?
- Yes.
As I told you earlier,
today's race is called
The 1st Division Game.
- The 1st Division Game.
- We are going to select...
the luckiest member of Running Man.
- I see.
- There will be six missions,
and one member will be eliminated
in each mission.
The last member remaining will
win the race.
(The last member remaining will
win the race.)
But today, 100 staff members will
take part in the race as well.
I guess
the staff members had a poll.
They predicted
the result of this mission?
- Our records?
- Our rankings?
Each of the staff members will vote
for one member...
they think will survive the mission.
Oh, my. I'm excited.
The 100 staff members already voted
before this mission began.
(The 100 staff members voted
before this mission.)
Everyone, please gather around.
As you know the basic rules,
you have to vote for the member
you think will win before each game.
And put the sticker...
of the member you chose on your cap.
If Suk Jin gets eliminated
in that round,
those who voted for Suk Jin...
must take off their caps.
If you lied to move up,
it'd take too much time to wrap up.
So please follow the rule.
That way, some of you get eliminated
after each round,
and the ones remaining at the end
receive a prize.
You will actually receive a prize.
Please think wisely
when you vote for a member.
Thank you.
(So before the shoot began...)
(The 100 staff members voted for
the member to survive Round 1.)
Just so you know, the 100 voters
include your managers and stylists.
- Really?
- They're all wearing a cap.
They voted for one of you.
Many of them voted for Ji Hyo.
Most of them voted for Ji Hyo...
- Many chose Ji Hyo.
- and Jong Kook.
- Really?
- They're mostly lucky.
- Hyung In chose me.
- Really?
- No one chose me.
- Clearly,
- you don't know me.
- No one chose me either.
- Only one person chose me.
- No one chose me.
- I'll announce your records.
- Okay.
- Really?
- I'll announce the time...
- you got distracted.
- This is so funny.
The member who came in first
by a huge margin is Jong Kook.
- He didn't look at them at all.
- Ji Hyo placed second.
- But I looked at them many times.
- Suk Jin placed third.
Jae Suk placed 4th,
and Se Chan placed 5th.
- Se Chan must have...
- I looked at him so many times.
Two members are left.
I bet Haha is in the last place.
- So Min and Haha.
- It's definitely Haha.
Haha looked at him
longer than I did.
But he was so funny, you know.
He seemed so patient too.
First,
I'll announce So Min's record.
(So Min's record will be
revealed first.)
- One minute and five seconds.
- See?
- So Min looked at him...
- Did you keep looking at him?
- She made eye contact with him.
- Yes, I did.
You enjoyed his performance.
- I couldn't take my eyes off him.
- I knew she'd do that.
Next up is Haha.
One minute and 27 seconds.
- He...
- I knew it.
- You can say that he saw...
- He didn't even look at you.
- a whole performance.
- He enjoyed the performance.
- He didn't even look at you.
- I mean, he even...
- taught him how to dance.
- I want to see his dance again.
- Me too.
- I want to dance with him.
He didn't look at you
even when he walked in.
As a result of the mission,
(As a result of the mission...)
we have the first member
to be eliminated.
Hey, that's not fair.
- It's Haha.
- All right.
I'm relieved.
(Haha is eliminated
in the first round.)
- Here. Put this on your clothes.
- Oh, no. Goodbye.
Hey, it matches
the color of your hat.
- Haha is out.
- Right. Today...
- Your outfit is perfect.
- His shirt matches with his pants.
- It looks like a prison uniform.
- You look great.
For your information,
the staff members
who voted for Haha...
- also got eliminated.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- Out of the 100 voters,
- nine people voted for Haha.
- I see.
- Right.
- I feel bad.
- So...
- I'm relieved.
they got eliminated from the race,
and lost the chance...
to win a great prize.
Just wait, you guys.
I'll make you win a prize.
We have another chance
in the next round, right?
- No, you're out.
- I'm out?
You got eliminated from the race,
and got a penalty ball.
Then can't I take part in
the next missions?
You can.
But if you're not ranked high
in each mission,
you'll get more penalty balls.
Hey, just leave the set
and cut meat at the restaurant.
- He's right.
- Just go and grill meat.
- You know...
- Get ready for the dinner rush.
- Score the meat, Haha.
- You should...
- prepare to open it.
- Right.
- And there's a fun fact.
- What is it?
Among the nine people
who voted for Haha...
There are Haha's staff members
Oh Young Jin and Choi Sung Woo.
- Obviously.
- And unexpectedly,
Jeon Chan Se voted for Haha too.
- Really?
- Chan Se?
- Jae Suk's manager?
- Jae Suk's manager.
- I like Chan Se.
He has a strong ego.
That's great.
- That's true.
- Chan Se.
So he got eliminated.
- Right. It serves him right.
- Did he...
- He didn't vote for you?
- He got what he deserves.
- Have some loyalty, will you?
- Gosh.
- It will be changed, right?
- Yes. They'll vote again.
Right?
Okay.
- I apologize to the nine voters.
- This is fun.
I'm sorry.
The first mission is over.
Those of you who got eliminated,
please take off your caps.
Vote for the second mission
and replace the sticker.
(The 91 voters who survived
voted for the 2nd round.)
(Who will be the second
to be eliminated?)
Everyone, please gather around.
(This is where The Division Game
will officially begin.)
What's this?
- It's huge.
- My gosh.
I like this.
My, look at that.
What is this? They did a great job.
(The division mansion)
My, this is huge.
I'm impressed.
(The division mansion)
They all voted for Jong Kook.
- I don't see my name.
- They all voted for Jong Kook...
or Ji Hyo.
So Min, none of them chose us.
- Hey, how could you?
- They all voted for him.
- So Min.
- I see a few...
- Come here. Let's be partners.
- Let me check.
- Mr. Kang Chan Hee.
- Right.
- Mr. Kang.
- Mr. Kang, how could you?
- You voted for him.
- I mean, how could he...
- My gosh, Chan Hee.
- Chan Hee, I thought you'd pick me.
- Look.
- Mr, Kang, you can't do that.
- That's unexpected.
- Okay.
- I'm disappointed.
(They're quite conscious about
the voters' decisions.)
I think everyone
in the managers' seats chose Ji Hyo.
- Look. I Re voted for her too.
- Right.
I Re voted for her?
- Are those who voted for me shy?
- You see...
- Why are they all hiding?
- We...
I see one person
who voted for Suk Jin.
- He chose you last time as well.
- Found one.
- I see.
- But I think...
he didn't replace the sticker
because it felt like a hassle.
- No. You have faith in me, right?
- "Put anyone's sticker on my cap."
Right?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
You can see your stickers
everywhere in the studio.
You must be under a lot of pressure.
I feel burdened.
- Of course, you do.
- Oh, man.
- Right.
- They all chose Jong Kook...
- because of that cylinder.
- I agree.
- You see, I hope...
- There are only a few who chose me.
that those who voted for Jong Kook
will all be eliminated.
Right.
I hope you all get eliminated.
- That would be fun.
- Yes.
- I hope you all get eliminated.
- Let's not let him win.
- Let's get him eliminated.
- Right.
- It's possible.
- Yes.
- You never know who'll get lucky.
- That'd be so funny.
The second mission where the
next member will be eliminated...
is Luck Across the Cylinder.
- The cylinder?
- Luck?
- You all have surnames.
- Right.
- Surnames?
- Kim, Yang, so on and so forth.
There is a roulette with
your surnames...
written in six different languages.
After spinning it,
you will cross the cylinder
and write it on paper.
(Cross the cylinder
and write down the surname.)
You will only have
five minutes though.
Out of the six remaining contestants
other than the eliminated Haha,
the one with the worst record
will be eliminated.
If you get the Korean surname,
write it down in Korean.
- "Ji" in English.
- Yes, Ji.
It's in other languages too.
If it's one you don't recognize,
you'll have to memorize it.
We'll have to memorize it?
- What's with the cylinder though?
- Beats me.
It isn't as stable as you think.
- Must we cross it?
- Will we be eliminated if we drop?
No, you'll just have to try again.
We'll be timed.
In Haha's case,
a penalty ball won't be added
if he finishes in the top three.
If he doesn't,
a penalty ball will be added.
- But he can never win the race?
- Never.
- Has he already been eliminated?
- You must not be motivated.
Why is he even here, then?
- There's no pressure though.
- This isn't fun at all.
Just head to
the barbecue restaurant early.
My run ended because
I enjoyed the Zero Two dance.
Unbelievable. Where did he go?
Here we go.
- This...
- I wonder how challenging it'll be.
- It won't be easy.
- Is it unstable?
- If you lose your balance...
- Of course.
Must we write while
standing on the cylinder?
- That's right.
- Hold on.
- While standing on the cylinder?
- Yes.
- I'm scared, Ji Hyo.
- While on the cylinder?
What's that? I don't know Japanese.
- It's in Arabic.
- Arabic isn't easy to write.
We have to memorize it.
- We have to go back and forth.
- Jeon.
- Can we look at it and copy?
- This...
Yes, but you'll have to turn around.
If you drop, you must restart.
It's not as easy as it seems.
Can you write
while standing on the cylinder?
- Okay.
- How can one write while on it?
- Please spin the roulette.
- I'll spin it in 1, 2, 3.
Arabic!
- Arabic.
Give her the Arabic word.
- The staff is just as focused.
- Arabic is perfect for So Min.
Arabic.
Give her the Arabic word.
The Arabic word.
- Please... Oh, no.
- Getting the Arabic word...
- It's impossible.
- Please, no.
- Japanese?
- No, that's too easy.
- She got an easy one.
- It's too easy.
She got an easy one.
You'll write the English word.
- Ready, get set...
- But...
So Min must be able
to cross the cylinder.
- She's not usually that lucky.
- Crossing it isn't easy.
- She must be able to cross it.
- Go!
(Go!)
All I need to do is cross it?
- That's it, right?
- Yes.
- She needs to stand to write.
- She can cross it like that.
That's even more dangerous.
Oh, no. How do I do this?
- Walk across it.
- She found her balance.
So Min, add weight to the right.
On your right foot.
Bye!
- Have confidence.
- This is impossible.
- Bye!
- So Min, you'll fall at this rate.
The cylinder will rotate.
The cylinder...
- It's about to rotate.
- Bye, So Min.
Bye!
Bye, So Min.
- Squeeze your core.
- It'll rotate.
- Bye!
- It's about to rotate.
It's funny to see her hips sway.
(It may be at a slow pace,
but So Min moves forward.)
She managed to hold on.
- It's a decent strategy.
- Look at her go.
(She's at the halfway point.)
- Nice.
- She's doing a good job.
- This is good enough.
- It'll rotate soon.
- Bye, So Min.
- It'll rotate.
She needs to stand up
in order to write it down.
- Yes, you must stand.
- Got it.
Got it.
- She'll stand at the far end.
- I'll do it on my first attempt.
You can't step on the platform.
- Bye!
- Why did you make me speak!
- She'll stand at the far end.
- I'll do it on my first attempt.
You can't step on the platform.
- Bye!
- Why did you make me speak!
- Be quiet, will you?
- Hurry and try again.
- It'll be impossible to stand.
- Get back here.
- Bye, So Min.
- She can't stand up properly.
Bye.
Those who voted for So Min...
can give up on winning today.
Don't get your hopes up.
- Please give up.
- You can even go home.
Not many seem agitated.
- Not many are on her side.
- There aren't many rooting for her.
- I was almost there.
- You should walk across it.
But standing...
- A minute has passed.
- A minute?
Try walking instead.
It's getting...
How about another
Zero Two dance performance?
- You won't make it.
- Not you.
You'll never make it.
You can't.
No way.
So Min, you should stand.
I bet your legs are shaking
from the idea of standing.
- So Min...
- Yes!
- Good job.
- Nice.
Time is ticking away.
What can she do?
So Min, just walk across it.
Those who voted for So Min.
Do you still have your hopes up?
The staff doesn't seem agitated.
(Tortoise Jeon won't give up.)
Yes, that seems like a good idea.
It won't be easy
since she'll have to stand.
Yes, she has to stand.
She'll have to stand in the end.
- It's a good plan though.
- It's not bad.
She has to stand up though.
- I can do this.
- You have to stand.
I can do this.
- That was fast.
- Everything else was perfect.
- But it's hard to stand up.
- Bye!
I bet you'll fall standing up.
Stand up.
Even if you do stand,
you won't remember
how to spell your name.
Of course.
Should I just kill them?
Stand up.
Can't she grab that in front of her?
You won't be able to kill us.
Do you know why?
- It can't be done.
- You won't be able to stand.
- You...
- Suk Jin will probably die first.
(Trembling)
Your legs must've given out by now.
That's it, So Min. You're doing it.
- You've got this.
- Now, stand.
- Stand up.
- Once she shifts her weight...
She'll fall in five seconds.
Five.
- Four.
- Three.
- Two.
- One.
Bye!
(But...)
(She managed to stand
and is now writing.)
What on earth?
(Frantic hand movements)
- What is that?
- What are you writing?
It's a success.
I did it.
(The rise of the weakest link)
J, E, O, N.
It took you four minutes.
Four minutes?
I know what to do now.
I finally know how to win.
- Who's next?
- Me.
Ji Hyo, who would you like
up there with you?
Jong Kook, please.
(She chooses Jong Kook
to hold the paint for her.)
Let's do this.
The words for "Song" won't be easy.
Gosh, these look difficult to write.
(What words must Ji Hyo
have to write?)
- These are insane.
- They're difficult to write.
It can't get harder than this.
These aren't easy at all.
- Unbelievable.
- She needs to get the Korean word.
- The Korean word.
- You should spin it yourself...
since these are
all difficult to write.
- I have the trickiest words.
- How can one write this?
The Arabic word, I mean.
These are insane.
Ji Hyo has spun the roulette.
Please let it be the Arabic word.
No way.
Arabic.
- Arabic.
Give her the Arabic word.
- I think that's it.
- The Arabic word.
- It's the Arabic word.
- The Arabic word!
You have been given the Arabic word.
I won't accept it
unless it's properly written.
Ji Hyo, my gosh.
I bet this will be hard for you.
You'll have to check it again
before you write it down.
Please get ready.
This is impossible.
- She has to go and see again.
- How can one write that down?
So Min's way is better. It's faster.
You'll have to turn
and check it again.
That's it. Find your balance first.
Mama!
(Mama!)
- It's not easy, you know.
- Did she call for Jong Kook?
- No, her mom.
- Her Mom.
- Her mother.
- It must be his nickname.
- Jong Kook's, I mean.
- As in Mama Kim?
- Mama Kim.
- I must say that...
Mama Song.
Who did Ji Hyo name
as her ideal guy?
Jong Kook.
- Her?
- Jong Kook?
She likes someone
who's like Winnie-the-Pooh.
Yes, someone like a teddy bear.
- Who likes teddy bears?
- Ji Hyo.
Look how interested he is.
He responded almost immediately.
- Yes, like that.
- She likes someone with a belly.
Maybe Jong Kook...
will stop watching what he eats.
Ji Hyo, you need to stand up now.
Standing up is the hardest.
That won't be easy at all.
Ji Hyo, you won't be able to do it.
You won't be able to stand.
Is your tongue already twisted?
"You won't be able to stand."
Because the cylinder
will roll to the side.
I'll give you 100 dollars
if you manage to stand.
Then I'll receive it.
He's offering you
half of what he'll earn today.
Have you never been offered a raise?
- All this time?
- Shouldn't he get a raise?
Suk Jin has been receiving
a fixed income.
They never offered me a raise.
- He receives more than I expected.
- How can it still be the same?
Do you even remember
how to write it?
- She needs to see it first.
- We should let her see it.
- Ji Hyo, that's my concern.
- Let her see it.
- Jae Suk...
- Take a look.
- Here.
- Okay.
There we go.
How can one memorize this?
Standing up is the hardest part.
Ji Hyo, time is ticking.
Two minutes and 30 seconds
have passed.
Place your feet first
and then stand.
Women can squat low, right?
Place both your feet
on the cylinder first.
Time will run out
while you remain seated.
- That would be funny.
- You won't be able to stand...
since your legs aren't that strong.
She's doing it.
She's standing!
- She's on her feet.
- Really?
She'll manage it.
- Look.
- She's doing it.
You've got this.
Let me hold the paint for you.
Make sure it's the Arabic word.
- Do you have it memorized?
- Check it first.
- Try copying it down.
- She's not even looking at it.
No way.
(Please...)
- Make sure it's the Arabic word.
- Check it first.
Try copying it down.
- She's not even looking at it.
- Be certain of it.
If not, they won't accept
your answer.
- Ji Hyo.
- I think it's right.
- It's not.
- Wait!
I think it's right.
(Ji Hyo has written something down.)
- It's right.
- That's not for you to decide.
- If you look at it...
- It seems similar enough.
- There are two dots.
- Hold on a second.
- I, I, C, and an L.
- She missed something.
But there's something missing
up top.
- Yes, this symbol.
- This.
- Darn it.
- Get going.
Why rush it
when it wasn't easy getting here?
Why did you lose
your patience at the end?
I forgot.
But the time...
- That's too bad.
- Five minutes.
(Ji Hyo missed a stroke
and time ran out.)
Your five minutes are over.
- Then...
- The way I see it is...
- Okay!
- Which language is this?
Isn't that the Chinese character
for number eight?
Haha has to finish in the top three.
- The penalty ball.
- Or a penalty ball will be added.
See?
- Seriously?
- Darn it!
Imagine an alligator
drooling over your leg.
Is it here or here?
On your left.
Are you tight roping?
That...
- Your five minutes are up.
- It's not easy, you know.
- Nice!
- How can he be so bad at this?
- Tell me about it.
- Can I get one?
- I wasn't trying to be funny.
- Is it that difficult?
- Is it tricky?
- I couldn't find my balance.
Seok Sam's next.
- Why don't I hold his paint?
- Sure.
- Get up there.
- No, wait.
Jae Suk!
Ji Hyo has done enough.
Jae Suk, you're getting started
right away.
How can I pull a prank with this?
- It's impossible.
- You can't.
I just can't.
It's not like you can slap him
with ink on your hand.
Suk Jin has to cross it though.
- That's right.
- I know that.
He'll be able to cross it.
Ji! In Korean!
- It's in Chinese.
- Nice.
Here, Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin's manager
is disappointed.)
Yes! He got Chinese.
- I think he'll be able to do it.
- It's a difficult letter.
It's a difficult letter.
- It's too...
- Let's go, Seok Sam!
I thought Chinese
wouldn't be as difficult.
There used to be a show called,
"Fight! Running Sunday".
I know that show.
- It aired on Sundays.
- That's right.
- There were singers...
who sang in the middle of the show.
What's wrong with him?
- That's right.
- They sang in the middle.
(A delayed slapstick comedy
before he even began crossing it)
You haven't started, have you?
- I feel bad for him.
- I haven't started yet.
You won't be able to get up
at the end...
- because...
- This isn't easy.
- Suk Jin.
- You won't be able to cross it!
- You should walk instead.
- I have to walk?
You won't be able to get up.
- because he's not flexible.
- Get ready.
- You're doing great!
- It's easier for women to get up.
You're still healthy!
- Here comes Suk Jin.
- Health!
Health, blessing,
happiness, long life!
- Here comes Suk Jin!
- Youth is now!
Youth is...
- That's it!
- Now!
- Here he comes.
- Youth is Suk Jin!
- You're doing great!
- That's a good idea!
- Okay! Nice.
- The tteokbokki guy!
(Not a chance.)
YIN!
- Youth is now!
Success!
Finally,
- He will lower our standard.
- Suk Jin is playing.
Some of the stylists and managers...
- started watching.
- He will lower our standard.
(Seok Sam's slapstick comedy
caught the audience's interest.)
(Super focused)
Ji Suk Jin. Who is this guy?
- He's going forward!
- That's great going!
To the left!
This isn't working.
Why don't we make a bet on this?
Will he fall on his left side?
- I think he'll fall to the left.
- I agree.
- I bet on the right.
- You know why?
- Why?
Because the camera is on the left.
I knew it. He's indeed amazing.
- Suk Jin, you can do it!
- I bet on the left.
Suk Jin!
- To the left.
- To the left!
Will he fall
on the left or right side?
- Youth is...
- To the left.
- He'll fall to the left.
- on this side or the other side?
- This side?
- Let's clap for him.
- I'll make it.
- It's like we're hypnotizing him.
- We're hypnotizing him.
- A dad's challenge!
He'll fall.
(The frivolous son distracts his dad
when he's giving it a try.)
(Cheering)
(You can do it, Dad!)
We're so distracting.
(He decides
to lie with his face down.)
He's trembling.
- That was the left side.
- It was on the left.
He fell on the left side.
- How did you guys cross it?
- You can never cross it that way.
How did you do it?
Did you walk across it?
You've used four minutes so far.
- He's already used four minutes?
- Suk Jin.
- I can't even smile anymore.
- He didn't even make halfway.
- You have 1 minute left.
- Give me 1 more minute.
- What's with his pronunciation?
- "Give me 1 more minute."
- "Please give me another minute."
- "Give me one more minute."
"Give me one more minute."
Suk Jin, just run across it.
Be brave.
- Suk Jin.
- Just run across it.
Run as you say, "Youth is now!"
Imagine that your wife would die
if you fail to cross it.
- You must save her.
- I bet he won't cross it.
(Su Jung...)
(The romantic from Jamwon-dong
runs toward his wife.)
(He fails to save her.)
That was quite cool though.
I praise you for your bravery.
- You have to save your wife.
- You can do it.
You should've kept going.
(Time's up.)
- He fails to save her!
- He fails!
- Next player.
- Is it Jae Suk?
- It's me.
- Is it?
It's Yang Ssaebssaeb.
- It must be in Arabic.
- Yang!
- Arabic.
- It must be in Arabic.
- Yang!
(He got Arabic.)
At least it's
easier than Ji Hyo's name.
It's Arabic.
It's easier than Ji Hyo's.
Get ready.
- He's coming!
- That's it.
I think he'll do well.
(Moving forward
like he's walking on a tightrope)
You're there, and I'm here.
You're there, and I'm here!
They're exchanging lines.
You're there?
I'm right here!
(Drawing a heart)
Hold on. Stop...
Guys, I can't get a grip!
I must've seen it wrong.
- So Min is amazing.
- She is.
- She's really amazing.
- She's one amazing woman.
- I'm right here!
- She's amazing.
- We should give her an award.
- We should.
(A cheesy girlfriend who attacks
her boyfriend's mentality)
(He quickly moves forward
with small steps.)
He's coming.
- He's dying to win her love.
- It's the power of love.
- He's good.
- Wait.
He managed to cross it.
This is great. I did it.
- All right.
- He crossed it. Good job.
- He got it.
- How did it go again?
(He'll succeed in the mission.)
How did it go again?
He's good.
- All right.
- Let's see.
That's it. He's doing great.
- That's it. He's doing great.
- Another stroke here.
- Here. I'm done.
- He balances himself well.
- All right!
- Yes!
He balances himself well.
(He finishes it neatly.)
He's good.
His record is
1 minute and 40 seconds.
(Final record:
1 minute and 40 seconds)
You should join my team!
(Shout out Se Chan!)
- He's good.
- I might get eliminated.
We should've watched them first
and learned the tips.
If he makes it,
then you'll be eliminated, Suk Jin.
Where is it? Let me see.
You'd be safe
even if you just draw a dot.
This is...
- As long as you're not eliminated.
- Please spin it.
- Is it his turn?
- Let's do this!
(Which one does Jae Suk
have to write?)
- I want to get a simple one.
- This one looks easy too.
Get the Chinese letter.
- The Japanese letter.
- It's the Chinese letter.
- Get the difficult one.
- Yoo!
Gosh, that'd be too easy.
(He got Korean.)
(It's in Korean!)
(Sighing)
This is great news
He's happy.
It's in Korean
Gosh, what an eyesore.
- Get going!
- All right.
(The reason Jae Suk
is so confident)
- This is...
- How difficult must it be?
- It looks difficult.
- Does it spin a lot?
This is...
You're good.
- It looks difficult.
- It's not bad.
It's doable.
But you must do it well.
But you did well.
(He managed to cross it earlier.)
- Get going!
- All right.
(How will he do in the actual game?)
How did you cross it so well?
- He should cross it first.
- How did you do it so well?
Jae Suk will cross it in no time.
He's good.
(Going forward quickly)
- Look at that.
- What is this?
- How can he hop like that?
- He's going forward like that?
(Showing off his skills
from his practice)
The way he's moving forward
is weird.
He's good. Look at that.
- He's good.
- What is this?
(Right then, Ssaebssaeb meddles in.)
(Startled)
- You can't hold on to her!
- He's falling!
(He runs back quickly
after pulling a prank.)
That was so close though.
- You can't hold on to Ji Hyo.
- Don't hold on to her!
- But he ran on it earlier.
- All right, then
How did you run on that?
(He falls again on his own.)
- I'm in trouble!
- He's in a hurry now.
He's in a hurry.
- He's in a hurry.
- I must hurry.
- Hurry up.
- He's in a hurry.
He was being playful.
- Hurry up.
- He's in a hurry.
Hurry up.
You should get your record.
- Okay?
- That's a new stunt.
This is a party!
- Here comes the grasshopper!
- It's a party!
Keep going!
- Here comes the grasshopper!
- Move!
(The crowd is going stirred.)
- Here he goes.
- Hurry up!
- Let's go!
- I'm in trouble!
His heart is racing!
- What is this?
- He's nervous!
- Will he make it?
- Let's go!
- Earlier...
- No!
He did well during practice.
It's spinning!
- The cylinder is spinning!
- It's spinning!
You can't help it. It's spinning!
It's spinning!
The ink...
(Drawing orchid on her face)
- That was hilarious.
- Hey.
- Look at Ji Hyo's face.
- Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo's face is messed up.
- Ji Hyo.
- It's not going to work.
- Jae Suk!
- I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
His heart is racing.
Here's a celebratory performance!
Here comes the Zero Two dance!
(Celebratory performance
of the Zero Two dance)
The Zero Two dance!
(In the end, his legs gave way.)
- Time is running.
- Here it comes.
- What is she doing?
- What's wrong with you?
Go ahead.
(Right then, the grasshopper
gets back on his feet.)
All right, now.
Let's see.
(He's used up most of his time
because he got nervous.)
He'll make it at this rate.
(Will he be able to overcome it?)
But it won't be easy.
The cylinder...
(Spinning)
It's spinning!
The cylinder...
(He gave her a mustache.)
- My goodness.
- What did Ji Hyo do wrong?
Why is it so difficult
for you to write Yoo?
- I'm so sorry.
- I might win first place.
- Please stay balanced.
- Thirty seconds to go.
- What?
- Thirty seconds?
- Thirty seconds.
- He's out of time.
- It's his last try.
In the end, we'll play
rock-paper-scissors.
I'll be able to do it this time.
In the end, we'll play
rock-paper-scissors.
- I'll be able to do it this time.
- He will.
From what I see...
He was close to it though.
(The grasshopper got back in the
game with 30 seconds remaining.)
He's in a hurry, that's why.
- He still has time.
- He can do it.
From what I see...
He's in a hurry, that's why.
You can't hold on to that!
- He grabbed onto the platform.
- He grabbed it.
- I got it, right?
- He did it!
He did it!
(He succeeds dramatically
with only 5 seconds remaining.)
- We used a foul, so...
- Right.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
(Jae Suk survives after
successfully finishing the mission.)
The last player, Jong Kook.
You're up next.
(The last player, Jong Kook)
It looked quite hard.
It's Jong Kook again.
- Jong Kook is going to win again.
- Let's go!
(He's got the most support
from the staff members.)
After he's done playing,
we'll have the final result.
- Jong Kook will...
- You should spin the roulette.
- I'll spin it now.
- It's impossible.
I'll spin it now, Jong Kook.
(Korean, Chinese, Japanese, English,
Greek, Arabic)
- Here we go.
- Jong Kook...
(They spun it.)
The letters are rather easy.
As long as I don't get
the Arabic letter.
Let him get the Arabic letter.
- They all look easy.
- All right.
(Many staff members' fates are in
his hands. Which one will he get?)
- It must be easy for him.
- Just not the Arabic letter.
- It's in Chinese.
- It's Japanese.
- That's easy.
Three strokes...
(If Jong Kook succeeds
in the mission...)
Get ready.
Does it go like this?
It's this one.
(The final round with everyone's
fate on the line starts.)
- You should get going.
- I'm quite heavy.
- I'm in trouble.
- You should get going to write it.
- That's right. He should go.
It's disadvantageous
for those who are heavier.
It'll spin faster.
- That's right. He should go.
- You should get going to write it.
It's disadvantageous
for those who are heavier.
- That's right.
- You should get going to write it.
- Look at her.
- What is that?
(What is she doing all of a sudden?)
What are you doing?
Is that a heartfelt message?
- What are you doing?
- What's going on?
What? What are you doing?
"Song Ji Hyo."
- That's...
- Hurry over and give her a hug!
Hurry over and give her a hug!
Run!
(My goodness.)
Hurry over and give her a hug!
Run!
(The muscular boyfriend was faltered
by the girlfriend's confession.)
- That was...
- You must've gone crazy.
- He got up!
- My gosh.
Is this "Love Studio" or something?
- Hurry over and give her a hug!
- Darn it.
(Come here!)
- Gosh.
- Give her a hug!
- She's amazing.
- Come on.
Everyone must've gone insane.
- This is nice though.
- He's in a hurry now.
- Everyone must've gone insane.
- This is nice though.
- My gosh.
- He can't cross over.
That's...
- He's panicking.
- It's spinning a lot.
(He falls again
after taking a few steps.)
(Jong Kook's supporters
are stirred by his performance.)
He's running out of time!
- I'm in trouble.
- Jong Kook will fail!
It spins so well.
- I'm in first place!
- You're all eliminated.
Those who supported Jong Kook
will be eliminated.
- Get ready.
- You'll all be eliminated.
- Jong Kook will be eliminated.
- It's over for him.
- I'm done for.
- About 40 people...
voted for him, right?
- I almost gave up.
- Hey.
- You're in second place.
- I'm in first place.
No, you're in second place.
I have a better record.
- Let's go
- Goodness.
- Hop.
(Darn it.)
- Darn it.
- Bye!
(Jong Kook's supporters
are slowly turning pale.)
Hey, Muscle, what happened?
Muscle.
- Jong Kook.
- They'll all be eliminated.
- Hey.
(They're getting parched.)
You can cross it
with the dance of "Loveable."
- You should go fast.
- Like this.
(Back when he used to move forward
with cuteness)
(Will he be able to move forward,
reminding himself of those times?)
I'm so proud
(He fails again.)
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm so proud
(Even the "Loveable" dance
didn't work.)
- Poor Jong Kook.
- Darn it.
It's a party!
We have another dropout!
They'll all be eliminated
if Jong Kook gets eliminated.
Almost two-thirds of them
will be gone.
- They're in panic.
- They're all stirred up.
Everyone, make some noise
at the count of three.
- In 1, 2, 3!
- Yes!
- Gosh.
- He's done.
- Yes!
You can do it!
- They're cheering for him now.
- "You can do it!"
- He's in a hurry.
- You got this.
"We believed in you."
- Four minutes passed.
- Four minutes?
(He has only one minute.)
Four minutes?
Almost 30 of them
will get to go home.
Hyung In is his supporter too? Okay.
It's over for you.
(In order for him to avoid
getting eliminated,)
(he must reach the point
where Suk Jin touched.)
No, there are about 45 of them.
I can just run like this.
(A sudden sprint)
What?
(Impressed)
What just happened?
That's it. Hold her!
(He fell right before
reaching the end point.)
They were all disappointed.
- They're all stirred up.
- They were all sighing.
No one said anything
when I was doing it.
(They forgot that
they're in the middle of a shoot.)
Hold on.
(He has only 30 seconds left.)
- Here we go.
- Why don't you crawl on it?
Jong Kook, stay calm.
(This will be his last try.)
(The last chance where many people's
fate is at stake)
(Will he succeed this time?)
- Why don't you crawl on it?
- Jong Kook, stay calm.
Jong Kook, stay calm.
(A big twist)
(He runs out of time.)
- We never know who'll win.
- He's eliminated.
- Jong Kook is eliminated.
- Okay!
- We never know who'll win.
- He's eliminated!
Come on!
No one chose me, did they?
It's a party!
Congratulations, guys.
- What do we do?
- I couldn't do it.
- You couldn't.
- Everyone.
There was a big twist.
- It really is a big twist.
- Forty people got eliminated.
- All right, then.
The major shareholder, Jong Kook,
- All right!
- got the worst record...
- and got eliminated.
- How many got eliminated?
Forty-two people got eliminated.
(Forty-two people got eliminated.)
(Almost half of them
got eliminated.)
You can all go home now!
They're all going home?
- Director Kang, go home!
- They should stay.
(Serves him right)
All 42 people who voted for him,
take off your cap,
and leave the chatroom.
- Leave the chatroom.
- Okay!
A high dividend is gone!
They're throwing away their caps.
This is the fun of it.
There should be twists
to make bets fun.
All right, then. Haha,
you're in the lower ranking,
so you get another penalty ball.
Jong Kook,
you get a penalty ball too.
(The staff members who survived)
Staff members, please vote
for the next round...
and stick the sticker on your cap.
Are they voting in every round?
Of course.
(They're done voting.)
Gosh, I should play
with no pressure now.
- I didn't know.
- As long as I don't get penalties.
They're all speaking ill of you.
(They're all speaking ill of you.)
- Right.
- That's understandable.
- They're all speaking ill of you.
- Don't you feel relieved though?
It'd have been better if I got
eliminated in Round Three.
I know.
We'll get to see who is lucky now.
- It's a twist after twist.
- It all depends on luck now.
In the next mission,
you must find a clip
with the highest views...
using your name.
It's called the View Count of Fate.
Using my name?
The laptop in front of you...
- is connected to YouTube.
- Okay.
You can use your name
and any word of your choice.
The member
with the lowest view count...
on the first clip they find
will be eliminated.
- The lowest view count?
- Yes.
(The member with the lowest
view count will be eliminated.)
But I can purposely choose
a specific word, right?
- I can choose the word, right?
- Yes, you can.
- If I...
- But it has to be...
- the view count of the first clip.
- The order...
Sometimes, the most recent clip
is on top,
and it'd have only 100,000 views.
Oh, it'll be the first clip?
He said it'd be the first clip.
For your information, we didn't
touch the setting at all.
Then it'll show the result
of recent ones. It's no joke.
I have one with a high view count.
But all their clips
have high view counts.
If I survived the previous round,
I'd have won this mission.
I recently saw one of my clips.
Gosh, I remember seeing one,
but I don't know the title.
There's one with five million views.
All right, then. Who'll go first?
No one will be able to beat mine.
We only get one chance?
You get only one chance,
and it has to be the first clip.
The thing is, the clip I want
should be on top.
So Min, tell us your keyword.
(Search)
Jeon So Min and Ha Suk Jin's
kissing scene.
All right. It's Jeon So Min
and Ha Suk Jin's kissing scene.
- You must have...
- Please type it in.
- seen it recently.
- No, that's not true.
It has a really high view count.
- Which one?
- With Ji Suk Jin...
- With Ji Suk Jin?
- Gosh, that startled me.
(A horrifying slip of the tongue)
- It's with Ha Suk Jin.
- Jeon So Min and Ji Suk Jin?
It's Jeon So Min
and Ha Suk Jin's kissing scene.
- The number of views compiled.
- I said it was with Suk Jin.
I remember its view count
being high.
(It seems like she regularly checked
her performance as an actor.)
The one with the lowest view count?
- Please!
- Let me see.
- We have it.
- How high is it?
Please!
(Ha Suk Jin and Jeon So Min's
kissing scene on a sofa)
It has 12.07 million views.
(12.07 million views)
How many?
(They got a clip with 10 million
views from the start.)
It has 12.07 million views.
(They got a clip with 10 million
views from the start.)
I'm sorry, but none of my clips
have more than ten million views.
The one on top?
- Who is going next?
- Gosh.
I'll go.
Those with ten million views
should go first.
You can't search any
unless you've seen those clips.
Kim Jong Kook, Lee Su Hyun,
"Addiction."
- What's that?
- I think it'll be high.
Kim Jong Kook, Lee Su Hyun,
"Addiction."
- You got it, right?
- "Addiction?"
- Oh, it's a duet performance?
- It was on "Fantastic Duo."
The one on top.
It has 22.87 million views.
- Gosh.
- Jong Kook. Who can beat that?
(22.87 million views)
(Gym Jong Kook leads in
first place.)
- How can we beat that?
- Wait. I'm in trouble.
I might end up in last place.
(His clip's view count
intimidates everyone else.)
How can we beat that?
I'll give it a go.
Do you guys look up these clips?
How do you know these things?
- I...
- No one can beat his.
Look up
"Song Ji Hyo, Kim Jong Kook, kiss."
(Look up
"Song Ji Hyo, Kim Jong Kook, kiss.")
I think there could be one.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- You typed in Song Ji Hyuh.
It says Song Ji Hyuh.
It's not "Hyuh."
- It's not "Hyuh."
- Why did you mention it?
Why did you have to mention it?
Because I felt bad.
Type in Song Ji Hyo.
Why would you feel bad?
Song Ji Hyuh...
Gym Jong Kook.
- That'd have a high view count.
- That has a high view count.
(Ji Hyo chose Gym Jong Kook,
her cheat code.)
- That'd have a high view count.
- That has a high view count.
- The first clip.
- It should be the first clip.
It has 16.01 million views.
Right? Okay.
(16.01 million views)
(Ji Hyo survives.)
(So Min is still in last place even
when her clip has 10 million views.)
Then let me lower the standard.
- I'll lower the standard.
- Go ahead.
Se Chan, there should be a clip
with three million views.
Somewhere between 3 million
to 5 million views.
There's no clip of me
with ten million views.
I don't look up my clips.
- Ones that guarantee high views.
- Maybe a clip with So Min.
You know how I did
collaborations with many artists.
- With EXO.
- EXO.
- Yoo Jae Suk and EXO or...
- That must have a high view count.
I recently did something with BTS.
You did something with BTS?
They were on
"You Quiz on the Block."
Right! Those clips must have
a high number of views.
There could be clips
with a high number of views...
- if I type in Ji Suk Jin and BTS.
- It must have a high view count.
It's because Jin mentioned me.
- Right.
- It went viral.
- Really?
- It was really popular.
Wouldn't you win first place
with clips with BTS?
- You can beat everyone with that.
- Right.
- This is...
- I've never met them,
but will it count
if there's a clip about me and BTS?
- Yes, it will.
- With your name alone...
If there's no result
with those keywords...
No matter what you type in, we'll
check the first clip's view count.
No matter what I type in?
Should I type in Bangtan Boys
or BTS?
- BTS.
- Give it a try.
- Yang Se Chan and BTS?
- I can't wait to see it.
- Have you ever met them?
- Sorry?
- Still...
- No, never.
Should I write in all caps?
There are some results.
Yes, there is something.
Press enter.
- Once you press enter...
- Go ahead.
It's a competition.
(The keyword
depends entirely on BTS' fame.)
(What will be the result
of using BTS blindly?)
Go ahead.
- Go ahead.
- It's a competition.
The number is 260,000. Gosh.
Gosh.
I will beat that.
- I can beat that.
- I will beat that.
- I will just look up my own name.
- He is out.
I will win even if I look up
"Yoo Jae Suk poop".
- Oh, no.
- "Yoo Jae Suk poop".
They did play a game on Running Man.
- I can beat that.
- Suk Jin.
- Any keyword will beat that.
- Seriously.
To be honest,
I have a surefire keyword.
- Use it.
- Go ahead.
- Use a different keyword, Suk Jin.
- I won't use it.
- All right.
- To be honest...
- I won't use it.
- Go ahead.
- What?
Here is what I will do.
I will beat you
with "Ji Suk Jin BTS".
Okay.
"Ji Suk Jin BTS". Search it.
- I will beat you with the keyword.
- Okay.
You will easily beat 260,000 views.
Of course. BTS.
- There they are.
- There are related keywords.
(There are
even two related keywords.)
I will beat you
with the same keyword.
- It was BTS, right?
- Yes.
Suk Jin.
Don't make a typo.
What is it?
You got it right, Suk Jin.
- Take a leap of faith.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- Hurry up.
- Let's go.
(What will be the view count
with BTS in the keyword?)
- Take a leap of faith.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- The number is 220,000.
- It's 220,000.
It's 220,000.
("Yoo Yaho Takes on Modern Songs,
Shocking BTS")
It's 220,000.
(Se Chan miraculously survived.)
- Suk Jin.
- What was your view count?
It was 260,000.
He got fewer views than me.
(Se Chan's supporter survived.)
I...
I shouldn't have overdone it.
You should look up
"Yoo Jae Suk BTS" too.
- You had a safe option.
- Yes.
- Jae Suk.
- You had a safe option.
- Why didn't you go with that?
- Just look up "Yoo Jae Suk legend".
- This is the third round of BTS.
- Yes.
"Yoo Jae Suk BTS" is
a different matter.
I am nervous about this.
- I was nervous too.
- You don't need to be nervous.
- The view count is 1.74 million.
All right.
Should I do the same?
(Suk Jin remains
at the very bottom.)
Should I do the same?
For the video underneath,
the view count is 12 million.
The view count is 12 million.
You use the topmost video.
- You use the topmost video.
- We know.
Still.
- Here I go.
- Go.
Why?
I should use lowercase letters.
- No.
- Come on.
(The cowardly man
obsesses over the smallest thing.)
- Lowercase letters.
- What's wrong with you?
- Gosh.
- He is so fussy.
Back in the day on Mnet...
Mnet?
We met.
The view count is 1.11 million!
Thank goodness.
Really?
The view count is 1.11 million!
Thank goodness.
(Suk Jin ranked at the bottom
even when he used BTS.)
What a twist.
Okay. With a view count of 220,000,
Suk Jin is...
- out.
- Suk Jin is out.
Out.
He is unrelated to BTS.
(Suk Jin's shy supporters
lament the result silently.)
- Four supporters...
- Four. Thank you.
- of Suk Jin are out.
- Did you survive?
- Of course.
- They are still in.
Continue to support me.
- Okay.
- I will survive.
I should have picked
a different keyword.
I want to thank my four supporters.
Suk Jin...
Staff members, please vote.
Thank you, everyone.
(The 4 surviving members)
So Min.
- Please gather around.
- Okay.
- Now comes the lunch mission.
- It requires luck and mobility.
- Mobility.
It's the 7 People, 7 Colors
Lunch Mission.
What is it?
You will pick a random color...
and procure food of the same color
from the surrounding area.
- The surrounding area?
- Yes.
Procure it
from the surrounding area.
- The surrounding area?
- Yes.
- What?
- It isn't the color of the wrapper,
- but the food.
- The color of the food.
You will have that food for lunch.
- Really?
- Yes.
In here are seven colors.
Take a pick.
Show your color
once I blow the whistle.
One, two, three. Show it.
- My color is green. It's bad.
- Darn it. I got yellow.
- Black.
- It's white. I am in trouble.
- Red.
- Yellow.
You can set off now.
Green? What kind of food is green?
- Pink.
- Where is black food?
I should go to a convenience store.
What kind of food is pink?
There are many tteokbokki places.
I will eat tteokbokki.
I picked an easy one.
I just need to get instant rice.
My color is white.
My six supporters picked well.
You guys are the best.
I will place first.
(Haha)
Hello.
Please give me gimbap...
- without slicing it.
- Gimbap? Okay.
- What are my options?
- Green.
Is there green food?
(Suk Jin's color)
What's your color?
Black.
- That's an easy one.
- What's your color?
- Green.
- Green?
What kind of food is green?
Here...
(Green food is nowhere to be found.)
- Please don't slice it.
- All right.
Thank you, sir.
(Haha's gimbap is nearly ready.)
- With perilla leaves,
- Perilla leaf gimbap?
would you make me
perilla leaf gimbap?
Please put the perilla leaves
outside.
- The white shouldn't be showing.
- No.
It needs to be green.
- Please put them on the outside.
- Okay.
On the outside.
(Se Chan's color)
It's blue. Doesn't this work?
It works, right?
The ice cream inside
needs to be blue.
Does it need to be blue?
(The ice cream inside
needs to be blue.)
What kind of food is blue?
What kind of food is yellow?
What's that?
"The sweet food that will sate
your curiosity". What's this?
Is it yellow?
Yes. It's yellowish-brown.
So it isn't completely yellow.
Hold on.
Then please put a lot of mustard
on the corn dog.
- Mustard?
- Yes.
Will it take long?
It will take about seven minutes.
It takes long. Seven minutes.
Hold on. Seven minutes.
It takes long.
(While Jong Kook waits
for the corn dog,)
(Ji Hyo looks
for a tteokbokki place.)
(She spots a tteokbokki place.)
(Ji Hyo's color)
It's closed.
(The restaurant is closed.)
Is there no tteokbokki place?
There it is.
(She spots a sign
for a different tteokbokki place.)
What? It isn't here.
(Ji Hyo is focused on tteokbokki.)
No way. How is there
no tteokbokki place?
(While Ji Hyo searches
for tteokbokki)
- Coming.
- A member is coming.
(Someone enters the studio.)
- Coming.
- A member is coming.
(Who will place first in Round 4?)
Is everything okay?
(The man who picked pink,
Jae Suk, enters.)
- What did you buy?
- Something pink.
- You succeeded. You placed first.
- Okay.
(He succeeded with strawberry milk.)
Am I the first one?
(Haha enters next.)
It isn't sliced.
You succeeded.
(He succeeded with black gimbap.)
- What's your color?
- White.
(So Min succeeded with string cheese
and instant rice.)
- Gosh.
- That counts.
I thought it would be white,
but it's brown.
- Hold on. Seven minutes.
- Please roll it...
- so that rice doesn't show.
- It takes long.
- Haha, what was your color?
- Black.
(Now, only one more member
can survive.)
- Thank you. Enjoy.
- Thank you. Take care.
I bought it. I bought red food.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
(Ji Hyo looked for tteokbokki
and Se Chan looked for blue food.)
Does it work?
(One of them will be eliminated.)
(The supporters eagerly wait
for the members.)
Let's go.
(Which member will enter first?)
Move.
I got it. I bought red food.
(Which member will enter first?)
The man with a view count
of 260,000 did it.
(Se Chan appears.)
The comedian who is related to BTS
and has a view count of 260,000.
- This counts, right?
- You succeeded.
- I totally succeeded.
- Yes.
(Se Chan survived thanks
to the blue candy and ice cream.)
- In any case...
- You bought tteokbokki.
What's your food?
Here. It's red.
All right. Ji Hyo's food counts.
- It counts.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook switched from a corn dog
to pumpkin soup.)
It's perilla leaf gimbap.
(Mr. Perilla Leaf Gimbap
arrives last.)
Perilla leaf gimbap.
- It's my favorite kind of gimbap.
- Is it?
- Yes. I love it.
- Let's see it.
What's that?
I haven't had it in a while.
- My goodness.
- It looks delicious.
How is it?
It tastes incredible.
(Coughing)
You are coughing.
- It's okay.
- Thus,
in Round Four,
Ji Hyo got eliminated.
There were 45 staff members.
- This time,
- I bet many of them got eliminated.
twelve of them got eliminated.
(12 out of 45 people
got eliminated.)
- That's a lot.
- Seventeen supporters.
I have a lot of supporters now.
- The number of my supporters rose.
- Let's do this together.
- My 6 supporters, let's go.
- So 33 people remain.
- Okay.
- That's incredible.
It's time
for the staff members to vote.
(The remaining staff members
vote for Round 5.)
- Please gather around.
- Okay.
What are these?
There are balloons in the back too.
I bet we have to run around.
- What are these?
- I bet we have to pop balloons.
I really want to participate
in this game.
What could it be?
You will participate.
- I know,
- Of course.
but my participation
will be meaningless.
- I helped Se Chan survive.
- It won't be meaningless...
- if you get rid of penalty balls.
- You are right.
What was that?
I forgot about that.
My goodness.
He got convinced so quickly.
The next mission was submitted...
by the frequent guest
and family member of Running Man,
- Ha Do Kwon.
- Do Kwon?
Ha Do Kwon?
Does Do Kwon submit games too?
Doesn't he have things to do?
He asked the production crew
to have you play this game.
- He should have visited the show.
- He is so nosy.
The producer put up with it
because he is nice.
- Balloons are in the lobby too.
- Lobby.
Start in the lobby
and follow the route...
as you burst the balloons
of your color.
- All the balloons?
- Yes.
You need to use your hands for some
and your butts for others.
- I see.
- In the last section,
you will throw a dart
on the count of three.
You will win if you burst
the white balloon.
We will meet at the end.
(You win if you burst
the white balloon.)
- The four of you won't participate.
- Why not?
(The 4 eliminated members
can't participate in the game.)
- What?
- Instead, you will guess...
the three members' rankings.
If you guess incorrectly,
you will receive penalty balls.
- Se Chan.
- Give us...
- the rankings.
- Se Chan.
Se Chan, Jae Suk, and So Min.
Se Chan, Jae Suk, and zom...
He said "Zombie".
(She is like a zombie
when it comes to athletic skills.)
I will pick Se Chan, Jae Suk,
and So Min as well.
Why?
(Se Chan, Jae Suk, and So Min)
- Why? Give a different guess.
- Se Chan, Jae Suk, and So Min.
Ditto.
- But...
- How about you, Suk Jin?
Our guesses should be different
in order for a competition to work.
- All right.
- Do you think So Min will win?
Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk, Se Chan...
- Jae Suk, Se Chan, and So Min.
Jae Suk, Se Chan, and So Min.
I have to pick you. I am sorry.
Since this is a luck-based race,
the level of difficulty differs...
as each color has
different numbers of balloons.
- Really?
- You will pick a color.
- Please pick one.
- My color is...
- So Min, give me what's left.
- blue.
The difficulty level is hard.
For goodness' sake.
- Okay.
- The difficulty level is medium.
- I will win.
- Okay.
- We guessed perfectly.
Her difficulty level is easy,
but it will go as we guessed.
The difficulty level is medium.
- Okay.
- Does the difficulty level differ?
- Se Chan got medium.
- I will get penalty balls.
- We guessed perfectly.
- Make me the winner.
- How much will you pay me?
- What?
- Cash.
- I will give you 200 dollars.
- That's a lot.
So Min offered us 200 dollars
for making us the winner.
Don't use money like that.
Make me the winner this once.
I don't see my name anywhere.
You guys are so annoying.
You didn't think
I would survive until now, right?
Let's go.
I will show you.
Today, I am determined.
I am determined.
I will teach them a lesson.
It looks so much fun.
One, two, three. Start.
(He falters from the start.)
Start.
(So Min also falters
from the start.)
(Se Chan gets ahead!)
They are going.
The race must have begun.
(Se Chan is the first one
to clear the lobby.)
(He quickly enters
the next section.)
Hurry up. Gosh, they don't compare.
Okay.
They got different numbers
of balloons.
Hurry up!
(Jae Suk gets the hang of it
and moves on to the next section!)
(Even with the low difficulty level,
this contestant can't win.)
(Thank goodness
she is enjoying the race.)
- Hurry up!
- Se Chan will place first.
Hurry up!
(Jae Suk quickly chases
after Se Chan.)
- Hurry up!
- Hurry up. Run!
Don't go easy on them.
(So Min arrived late,
but she doesn't have many balloons.)
Don't run like a fool.
Let's go.
All right.
(Jae Suk continues
to chase after Se Chan.)
Don't run like a fool.
Anything can happen.
Good job.
Why didn't it pop?
(Jae Suk gets caught up by So Min
after two misses.)
Hey, don't let So Min catch up.
There you go.
- Hurry up!
- Come on.
(Will Se Chan place first?)
(Nervous)
(Se Chan enters the last section
with the darts.)
He is bad at this.
(Missing)
(Missing again)
- Hey.
- He is bad at this.
(Se Chan struggles
with the last section.)
Hey.
- This is...
- Hey.
(Se Chan's supporters
become anxious.)
He is bad at this.
(Jae Suk picks up the speed.)
(Popping)
Okay.
(So Min's supporters wish
for an unexpected ending.)
Let's go.
- He is bad at this.
- Hey.
(A balloon finally bursts!)
- He is bad at this.
- Nice.
Okay.
(Jae Suk finally enters
the dart section!)
(Will Se Chan win?
Will Jae Suk come from behind?)
Okay.
(Se Chan will win
once he pops the white balloon.)
- Let's go.
- Anything can happen.
(Jae Suk gives his last spurt!)
Let's go!
- You punk.
- Anything can happen.
Let's go.
- So Min.
- Anything can happen.
(It's hard to it the white balloon
since it's far and up high.)
- You punk.
- Anything can happen.
(It's entirely possible
to come from behind.)
Anything can happen.
- Let's go.
- Do it slowly.
(Jae Suk only has
the white balloon left!)
Anything can happen.
(Jae Suk, the master hitman
is close behind.)
- Let's go.
- Throw higher.
- Anything can happen.
- Okay.
- Throw higher.
- Anything can happen.
(Se Chan popped the white balloon.)
(Se Chan won Round 5
by a close margin.)
Se Chan, you did it.
(So Min is eliminated
because she placed last!)
(Everyone cheers except
for a few So Min's supporters.)
That was great.
You scared me.
I was close.
- You scared me.
- You were close.
- Se Chan.
- I survived until the end.
- Good job.
- You did well.
- I was close.
- You were close.
- I needed one more try.
- My heart almost burst.
Okay. I won't get
more penalty balls.
- Suk Jin will get a penalty ball.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- All right.
Since So Min arrived last,
she will be eliminated.
- Okay.
- Investment is...
- all about probability.
- Probability.
For your information,
six people had bet on So Min.
- Okay.
- Now, 27 people remain.
- Twenty-seven.
- That's right.
Se Chan's era has come.
Staff members,
please vote one last time.
Thank you, everyone.
(The 27 staff members
have the last vote.)
Please finish voting.
Se Chan's era has come.
Thank you.
You never know.
You never know what I will do.
The last mission will determine...
the fate of 27 staff members
and 2 cast members.
The final round,
the Lucky One Wins Anyway.
(The Lucky One Wins Anyway)
- It must be a random game.
- Okay.
There will be
a roulette with 16 sections.
(They will begin with their names
in one section each.)
In the beginning, you will have
your name in one section.
- I see.
- Fourteen sections will be blank.
- Then you will spin the roulette.
- Okay.
If your name gets picked,
you are out.
You are out.
But if a blank section gets picked,
you add your opponent's name.
(But if a blank section gets picked,
you add your opponent's name.)
The sections with names
will multiply.
And if a name gets picked,
that person is out.
- It's a random game.
- This is...
(The last round
depends on luck by 100 percent.)
It will be fun.
- This will be so...
- It sounds fun.
- It's a matter of luck.
- It's a random game.
This is...
- It might end in one go.
- Yes.
Please place a bet.
Raise your hand
if you think Jae Suk will win.
- Jae Suk should get eliminated.
- Yes.
I usually do badly
if the game is big.
That's right.
- That's right.
- Jae Suk.
- I will tell you that.
- He does badly in a big game.
I usually do badly
if the game is big.
- Will you choose Se Chan?
- But Jae Suk gets big breaks.
- I will choose Se Chan.
- Will you choose Se Chan?
Then I will choose Jae Suk.
- I will choose Jae Suk too.
- Go ahead.
- All right.
- Se Chan.
- Okay.
- It has to be Se Chan.
- Let's go with Se Chan.
- I bet Se Chan will win...
on the first try.
- The first try.
- So Min.
I bet Se Chan will win
on the first try.
- In one go.
- Jae Suk, let's do this.
- Se Chan.
- I think I will lose.
Jae Suk thinks he will lose.
(His voice shakes
even before the game begins.)
- See? He is drinking water.
- I have never won in such games.
Jae Suk won't win. I know him.
You lose if your name gets picked.
- I hope Jae Suk loses in one go.
- Jae Suk gets big breaks.
The order is important.
Play rock-paper-scissors
to decide on the order.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Suk won.)
He'll win. See?
He won in rock-paper-scissors.
That's right.
You lose if your name gets picked.
- Let's see.
- Hold on.
(Jae Suk
will spin the roulette first.)
Let's go.
- Jae Suk, you can do it.
- Ji Hyo and...
You lose if your name gets picked.
- Se Chan's name will make you lose.
- I lose if my name gets picked.
- I hope you get Se Chan's name.
- Please get Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, you can do it.
(Will Jae Suk get a big break?)
Please.
- Let's go.
- Let's see Yang Se Chan.
- I am wrong.
- Let's end it fast.
We should see Yoo Jae Suk.
- I am wrong.
- Please give us Se Chan's name.
- Let's end it fast.
- Se Chan.
- Give us Jae Suk's name.
- Jae Suk. Let's end it.
- Let's end it.
I think it will work.
It's here.
- This might be it.
- It's here.
(Is it over on the first attempt?)
(What?)
I bet Jae Suk will be picked
on the first attempt.
It's here.
(It's right next to Jae Suk.)
- That was close.
- It's here.
That was close.
- My goodness.
- That was close.
- Oh, dear.
Isn't that it? Let's try it again.
- That was really close.
- My gosh.
- My goodness.
- That's...
- Isn't that it? Let's try it again.
- My gosh.
You fool, you should've gotten it.
Jae Suk, put Se Chan's name
on a place you want.
- Go ahead and put it.
- That was so close.
- It should go right next to you.
- A place you want.
- That was really close.
- Right next to your name.
- Should I put it here?
- No, not there.
Jae Suk, next to your name.
My gosh.
It should go here.
See? It already feels like
Jae Suk will lose.
- That's how it feels.
- I'm so scared.
Things are getting heated here.
This is amazing.
Make some noise
if you're on Se Chan's side.
(Shouting)
(The supporters are absorbed
in watching the last round.)
- Se Chan.
- It's spinning.
Yoo Jae Suk.
- By the way...
- Yoo Jae Suk.
Again, I Re is...
Does I Re have my name?
Did you not pick me?
Gosh, I Re...
I Re picked me.
I Re...
(The managers are just as
stubborn as the members.)
All right. Let's begin.
Spin the roulette again.
- In 1, 2, and 3.
- It will be over.
It will be over this time.
It will be great
to have Jae Suk's name.
- Right.
- My goodness.
(Things are going well for Se Chan.
How will it go this time?)
- No.
- This is going well.
- Gosh, it went past.
- It went past.
Put it on.
Se Chan, you should put it there.
- Here?
- Yes.
- Yes. Put it there.
- Good. That's a good idea.
- Don't be nervous.
- We should put it somewhere else.
Why would you be nervous?
- You can put it there next time.
- No, Jae Suk.
- You can turn this around.
- I don't think you will lose.
- Wish me good luck.
- Good luck.
- We don't have many spaces left.
- All right.
It might be me.
Jae Suk's name
will be picked this time.
Yoo.
Good luck.
- He has bad luck.
- Don't be nervous.
- He's out of luck.
- It might be him.
I don't think it will be me.
Se Chan!
Don't be nervous.
It didn't feel right
when he spun the roulette.
- This feels...
- It's here.
(Please...)
- This feels...
- It's here.
(It slows down around their names.)
- My goodness.
- It's here.
- No.
- My goodness.
(It is becoming a close game.)
- Put it on there.
- This is so close.
It's going this way.
(Yoo Jae Suk)
(Se Chan's name is put up.)
Good luck, Se Chan.
Let's do this!
- Yang Se Chan!
There aren't many people.
They are not shouting your name.
There are only a few of them.
- There aren't many.
- It's all right. You can still win.
It shouldn't be over.
It has to be over.
You should get your name picked.
Please.
- Just imagine that you won.
- Please.
In 1, 2, and 3. Let's go.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk can turn this around.
It's done.
It's not Jae Suk.
Just relax. Put yourself at ease.
- It's coming.
- It's here.
(The roulette slows down
around the names.)
It's here.
(What?)
It's happening this time.
- Yang Se Chan!
- It's Se Chan!
It's happening this time.
(Yang Se Chan is eliminated
in the final round.)
- Yang Se Chan!
- It's Se Chan!
(The 1st Division Game,
Winner Yoo Jae Suk)
Yang Se Chan!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yang Se Chan!
(Shouting)
- Yoo Jae Suk!
(Se Chan is sadly defeated
on the verge of victory.)
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- It was just one.
- Jae Suk.
- Yang Se Chan.
- Jae Suk, you turned this around.
- This is what I told you.
- I did it.
- It stopped right here.
- My goodness.
- Okay.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
All right.
(Throwing)
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
They are throwing their caps.
He never won when I voted for him.
(He never won when I voted for him.)
Jae Suk, I will announce
the survivors.
All right.
(Jae Suk meets with
the supporters who believed in him.)
- Ju Eun.
- Look at I Re.
- Hey, I Re.
- Gosh, I Re.
Hey, Ju Eun.
So Suk Jin's bad luck...
outdid Jae Suk's bad luck.
- I guess we lost because of me.
- Right.
- He is...
- This was so close.
They are the ones
who made me who I am now.
I'm sorry for all this.
(Yoo Seon Myung, Gang Seo Rim,
Choi Ga Eun, Jang Ye Bin...)
There were 13 supporters...
who voted for Jae Suk.
That's a lot.
It's almost half.
That was a close game.
All right then.
A total of 100 R are divided
by 13, so you get 7 R each.
- Okay.
- Here are the gifts for today.
If you get 100 R to yourself,
you will win a gold bar of
37.5 grams.
With 31 to 50 R, you get designer
sneakers worth 1,000 dollars.
With 21 to 30 R,
you get a bladeless fan.
With 11 to 20 R,
you get the prime Korean beef set.
Today, the winners won 7 R each.
With 5 to 10 R,
you get the J perfume.
So the prize that Jae Suk
and the 13 staff members...
won today is...
the J perfume.
- The J perfume?
- For all of them?
- Yes.
- My goodness.
(Only the 13 survivors
get the high-end perfume.)
Congratulations.
Nice.
And for those who supported me,
- I will prepare some gifts.
- My gosh.
Don't do that.
- Why would you do that?
- They supported me.
I can't get you anything.
(I can't get you anything.)
Now we should
draw the penalty balls.
I will announce the numbers
of your penalty balls.
Ji Suk Jin has 4.
Kim Jong Kook has 3.
(Suk Jin: 4, Jong Kook: 3)
Haha has three.
- So Min has 2.
- I have only 2 balls.
Se Chan and Ji Hyo have one each.
- Okay.
- Good.
- This is...
- If we pick Se Chan or Ji Hyo...
I bet we will get So Min's name.
- No.
- I'm glad to hear that.
Shall we begin?
Who will get the penalty today?
Let's begin.
- One, two...
- It can't be me.
(Who is the member
with the worst luck?)
- Gosh.
- I'm nervous.
- Is it out?
- It's out.
- Is it out or not?
- I bet it's me.
- We have one ball.
This is the ball
that came out afterward.
- It's Haha.
- Gosh, I'm relieved.
But I still have some balls left.
I hope it's Haha again.
- I know.
- Two balls came out.
And the one that came out first
will get the penalty.
The ball that came out first is...
(Suk Jin 4, Jong Kook 3, Haha 3,
So Min 2, Se Chan 1, Ji Hyo 1)
- Jeon So Min.
- Yes!
(Jeon So Min will get the penalty.)
I can't believe this.
(So Min had fewer balls,
but she got picked for the penalty.)
Why? Why me?
- Are you serious?
- Great.
- Seriously?
- You have a good hunch.
- Did you have two?
- You were right about this.
Hey, Haha and...
- Suk Jin had so many balls.
- I can't believe this.
I was winning.
I was about to win the race.
I do have a good hunch.
Today is Jae Suk's day.
It's your day.
So Min, ready.
(Today's penalty: Fresh cream bomb)
So Min has the worst luck today.
- She's a frog.
- The worst luck.
After playing all the games...
This is a mess.
(She's getting the penalty
after playing all the games.)
One, two, three.
(The fresh cream is fired.)
Okay.
Gosh, So Min. That was amazing.
- Thank you.
- Look at So Min.
("The lucky day"
for the 13 staff members)
(If someone asks
about the future of faces,)
(let them take a look at ASTRO.)
(If someone asks
about the future of comedy,)
(let them take a look
at Yang Se Chan.)
(Yoon San Ha, Cha Eun Woo, Moon Bin)
(I have a secret about my body
that others don't know of.)
(A natural born comedian...)
(fights against idol stars.)
(The heinous two shots)
(Where is the rose going to?)
(Action)
(Comedy)
(Romantic)
(Romantic comedy)
(Musical)
(Musical comedy)
(The war of roses
that covers a wide range of genres.)
Why is your voice shaking?
(User's Guide
to Black and White Roses)