Hello, everyone.
Aren't we starting the shoot yet?
(So Min always comes
before anyone else and says hi.)
Hello. Let me show you
something interesting.
All right.
(So Min wants to show something
even before the cameras are set.)
I can walk.
I'm walking.
(Jeon So Min walks
with her two feet again.)
It's a miracle.
I'm recovering quite quickly, right?
Don't you think so?
I'm glad to hear that.
I know who today's guest is.
(I know who today's guest is.)
(She looks depressed
talking about the guest.)
I'm very upset.
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
I've been on TV shows for 20 years,
but I still feel nervous.
- This is crazy.
- Really?
- I'm always nervous.
- You don't seem that way.
Why is he the only guest?
Is Sae Ho that popular?
This is what Jae Suk did.
Sae Ho was in home quarantine,
and I've been staying at home
because of my leg.
Jae Suk wanted us to be friends,
so he gave me Sae Ho's number.
So I contacted him
with no hesitation.
Jae Suk is our mutual friend.
So I kept...
talking to him with no pressure.
But Sae Ho called me one day.
"So Min, Jae Suk is making
things awkward for us."
"I know you are
a nice and lovely person."
He kept saying that
when I didn't say anything.
What does that mean?
It felt like I lost.
I have high standards.
You got rejected.
- I do have high standards.
- You lost.
When can I dance again?
I'm really worried.
(Street Dancer So Min
wants to dance again.)
Hello.
- Are we starting right away?
- Haha.
Hey, it's been a while.
- Hey, So Min.
It's been a long time.
Se Chan, we haven't seen
each other for a month.
- Really?
- Yes. We were...
You've become
a lot prettier in a month.
(You've become
a lot prettier in a month.)
What was that?
I'm just saying that to be nice.
- Should I leave you two alone?
- No.
Stop it already, Haha.
- Are you two...
- Hello.
Where's everyone?
- Jong Kook.
- Have a seat, So Min.
I saw them only on the screen.
(The members of Running Man
had video calls all week.)
- Haha.
- It's been so long.
- Se Chan, long time no see.
- Jong Kook.
Hey, you can walk.
All right.
You can walk now.
- Se Chan.
- It's good to see you again.
Let's sit.
- My gosh.
- We are of one mind!
We are one!
So Min, you didn't catch
COVID-19 though.
So you can't be one of us.
We have our own chat room. I'm sorry.
- Without her...
- A chat room without me?
- Yes.
- Sure.
- We beat the disease.
- Hello.
How are you feeling?
- I'm fine.
- Hello.
- Jae Suk.
- We're all gathered.
- Hey.
- Your leg.
Ji Hyo.
So Min can walk.
- Good for you.
- Suk Jin.
You're walking.
- Hey, you're here.
- Hey.
- We're finally here.
- Mr. Ji.
(Hugging)
We're here.
We've overcome the disease.
- Yes!
- We got over it!
We've overcome the disease.
We got over the epidemic.
It's Ji Hyo who beat the epidemic.
She's amazing.
She's the strongest one.
It's Ji Hyo and So Min
who beat the disease.
I'm glad that So Min
got her cast off.
- Me too.
- I'm trying to toddle.
I know.
Is it okay to walk?
- Of course.
- That's great.
- Don't walk though.
- Stop it.
But I'm not sure
when I can dance again.
- Why would you dance?
- I want to dance.
She's...
- You're not a singer.
- Hey.
You can dance sitting down.
- Let's sit.
- You can dance while sitting down.
- This is really nice.
- I know.
She should get us water since
she's the last in the hierarchy.
- But she hurt her leg.
- I can do the clapper.
- No.
- He brings just one.
He's the worst.
People never change.
- He's unbelievable.
- He never changes.
He's the worst.
He wants you to bring it yourself.
I didn't know you were thirsty.
You don't drink water
only when you're thirsty.
- You should keep yourself hydrated.
- Sure.
- That's good for COVID-19.
- You know what?
This is really funny.
When I caught COVID-19,
this is what Jong Kook said.
"I actually..."
"talked to someone with the virus
for an hour, but I'm totally fine."
(I talked to someone with
the virus, but I'm totally fine.)
"I don't get sick."
- "I've survived."
- It's not like that.
- So I said,
- I was wearing a mask.
"Anyone can catch COVID-19."
And he said this the next day.
"I feel great after a workout."
Then he suddenly said this
on the third day.
"I don't smell anything."
(I don't smell anything.)
You know what it is.
My nose was stuffy.
I hated that feeling.
So I worked out really hard.
I sweated a lot.
And my nose was all cleared up.
And my sense of smell was gone.
- They were gone all together.
- You know...
I kept calling all of you.
And you guys had
one thing in common.
- You all pretended to be fine.
- Jae Suk.
- "Hello?"
- We didn't know.
"Hello? It's me."
"Yes. I'm fine."
- "Hello, Jae Suk."
- Suk Jin was hilarious.
"What a relief."
"I don't have any symptoms."
And the next day,
"Are you all right?"
"Yes, I'm fine."
(Yes... I'm fine...)
(He denied the reality
with a hoarse voice.)
He sounded horrible.
He showed more symptoms over time,
but he kept saying he was okay.
"My throat hurts a little,
but I'm fine."
It wasn't serious though.
- I know.
- I just had a sore throat.
- And you had a slight cough.
- Right.
I lost the sense of smell,
but I had a good appetite.
- Really?
- I had a really good appetite.
- You've gained weight.
- I ordered delivery food.
I checked the delivery app
on my phone after ten days.
I spent over 700 dollars.
I spent over 700 dollars
on delivery food.
- You spent a lot of money.
- I ate a lot.
You should eat well though.
- You live alone.
- I live alone.
Actually, I always
order the same menu.
But I had
nothing else to do at home.
- So I read the menu carefully.
- Exactly.
And I tried many dishes.
You finally understand
what I went through.
- That's true. I agree.
- You spent two weeks.
- How could you put up with it?
- For 14 days.
I can't do that for 14 days.
And those you live alone
can use your whole place.
- But I had to stay in my room.
- That's what I did.
Like the movie, "Oldboy."
It wasn't so bad though.
I liked being alone.
You said you were
having a hard time.
- What?
- Why are you saying that?
I really liked it.
I enjoyed being in quarantine.
- Really?
- You wanted to be with your wife,
so you said you'd kiss her.
(You told me
that you'd kiss your wife.)
Why are you lying?
Why are you lying to us?
Did he say he'd kiss her?
- Why would you do that?
- Why?
- Why are you lying to us?
- What's with him?
Why would you do that?
And when we first
had our group video call,
So Min called the five of us.
- I guess he didn't know about that.
- Why?
- He wasn't wearing a top.
- Right. He wasn't wearing anything.
(Suk Jin didn't recognize
the camera angle.)
- He was naked.
- There was So Min,
but he was talking to us like that.
- My gosh.
- It only showed my face.
- Do you know what's funny?
- "What are you doing?"
I was so hot.
We couldn't reach Ji Hyo...
when it was confirmed
that you caught COVID-19.
And Ji Hyo called me back
in the late afternoon that day.
"Jae Suk, why did you call me?"
"I'm sorry. I was out,
so I missed your call."
"Is something wrong?"
"Do you not know?"
(Do you not know?)
She had no idea.
- "Did something happen?"
- She didn't know.
"Jong Kook caught COVID-19."
"Did Jong Kook catch COVID-19?"
(Shocked)
- "Hey! Did you not know?"
- She had no idea.
- "No, I didn't know."
- She didn't know.
I got a call from her
after five days.
She called me
the day I was released.
"Are you all right?"
(Ji Hyo is a little late,
but she is warm-hearted.)
Because of Jong Kook,
two of us got infected.
- Hang on.
- What?
On "How Do You Play?"...
(It's finally happening.)
- They blamed us.
- That's right.
Bong Sun said she would kill us.
Speaking of which,
our shoot has been...
delayed two times
because of Running Man.
I won't let Running Man
get away with this.
Running Man!
Bring it on!
("How Do You Play?" was
furious at Running Man.)
I can't believe this.
Hang on.
- I heard...
- Unbelievable.
- the team producer is from Anyang.
- Yes, he is.
- How old is he?
- "How old is he?"
I was going to teach them a lesson.
Jun Ha and Bong Sun want to kill us.
Say something.
Producer Park Chang Hoon wants...
to fight with Bo Pil sometime.
(Producer Park Chang Hoon wants...
to fight with Bo Pil sometime.)
(No one's going to get hurt
in the battle though.)
We have to talk about this.
Haha did a shoot by himself.
- What?
- For "How Do You Play?"
You...
(During the quarantine period,
he made a home video himself.)
Goodbye, COVID-19.
(His love for MBS gives them
a good excuse to nitpick at him.)
Hey, you know what?
- We have to talk about this.
- There you go again.
- Did you do it alone?
- Listen.
He filmed "How Do You Play?"
even in his quarantine.
- You didn't do it for Running Man.
- Listen to me.
Running Man is...
Gosh, look at your faces.
- Do they pay you more?
- You punk.
Do they pay you better money?
Did you get an extra 50 dollars?
What is it?
- He filmed a video?
- They had...
nothing to air at all.
But we had a new episode here.
- What do you mean?
- They didn't have anything to air.
- An episode with you?
That's why they were mad.
That's why...
They are just ridiculous.
(That's why...
They are just ridiculous.)
(He shifts his position to survive.)
Listen.
You should think
about it, Jong Kook.
- About what?
- I'm not trying to side with them.
- They just...
- You're siding with them.
- What?
- You're on their side.
- What are you doing?
- You're taking their side.
Do you not realize
where you are now?
The members of Running Man
got criticized for no reason.
All right. They don't want me there,
and you don't want me here.
What about me?
Last week, a producer
of "How Do You Play?"...
- joined our soccer club.
- Really?
And he kept tripping and falling.
How hard is he working?
Anyway, I'd like to say this again.
The thing is,
they say Omicron causes
only mild symptoms,
- but it's still COVID-19.
- Right.
I was sick.
- We should be careful.
- Exactly.
Anyway, we've finally gotten back
all together after five episodes.
That's right. We had a few episodes
without some of the members.
- It's been a really long time.
- I've missed you.
We weren't even sure
if we could get together...
- Right.
- because things change every day.
So we invited a guest just in case.
- Who?
- A guest?
- Is he the only guest?
- Yes. I asked him a month ago.
- Yes.
- He must be someone famous.
- I think so.
Is Park Bo Gum discharged? Is he?
- Woo Do Hwan is discharged too.
- Really?
- Is it Zo In Sung?
- I guess he is discharged.
Is ZICO discharged?
(They talk about popular stars
to undermine today's guest.)
That means he's quite popular.
- But...
- There he is.
What?
- What?
- Hey.
Sae Ho.
- What...
- My gosh.
- Are you here to watch our show?
- What?
- Are you stopping by?
- What do you think?
He's...
(Without getting up to greet him,)
(they just stare at him sharply.)
- Do you want me to leave?
- By the way,
what's with the atmosphere here?
- Who are you bringing?
- I don't mind.
- I'm just...
- What's with the atmosphere?
I'll just...
- go to the terrace.
- Hey.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- What's with you?
- I didn't see this coming.
- Hello.
He's got a lot of wrinkles.
I mean, what's with...
Did you suffer from COVID-19...
- with your face?
- What?
- Did you catch it with your face?
- I'll talk more over time.
- Let's sit.
- Do you have to be so...
Is he today's guest?
Aren't you...
supposed to give a hand
to your guest during the opening?
- You should greet me.
- Is he a wingman?
- Did you bring a guest?
- Your face is a lot funnier now.
Your face is interesting.
- Hello.
- Sit in the middle.
- Okay.
- Sit.
This is uncomfortable though.
- Have a seat.
- Sit.
- Sit here. I'll sit here.
Just sit there.
- Sit here?
- Yes.
So Sae Ho is...
Do we have to ask
what's new about him?
It's not like that.
- Gosh, Sae Ho.
- We know him so well.
- What perfume are you wearing?
- Gosh, that's strong.
- My gosh.
- That's really strong.
Jong Kook, can't you smell it?
I've lost my sense of smell,
but I can smell his perfume.
I'm here to help you.
Gosh, what's this?
- Is this a kind of training?
- It's hard to put up with it.
I put it on
because this is a big show.
Are you wearing expensive shoes?
Yes. They are Chanel.
- He's wearing Chanel.
- Right.
- I wear them for this show.
- Are these...
- They are Chanel.
- By the way,
- Chanel?
- is the rumor true?
- What rumor?
- That Chanel warned you.
Warning?
There's a rumor,
but that's not true.
Actually, there's
something upsetting.
- It's about Jae Suk.
- What about him?
- It was 11 p.m. last night.
- Was it last night?
It was 11 p.m. last night.
I was doing lower-body bathing,
and he made a video call.
- I was sweating a lot.
- He's always naked.
So I answered.
"I heard from Bo Pil."
"You're joining
Running Man tomorrow."
So I said, "Yes, I am."
"I don't want you to come."
Just one day before.
It wasn't like a week.
- Keep talking.
- With only a few hours left,
I'd been working out
for three days to come here.
"It's a little late, but you should
call Bo Pil and tell him..."
"that you can't make it tomorrow."
"Is that your decision?"
"Tell him that it's your decision."
I told him not to talk about me.
Don't talk about me.
"Don't talk about me. I'm just
saying this to help you."
Sae Ho, if you didn't
catch COVID-19,
weren't you supposed to go
on a date with So Min?
- No, it's not a date.
- It's not a date.
Were you going
to make a video together?
- With Jae Suk...
- Let me explain.
I tried to set them up
together three years ago.
- But they didn't like each other.
- Right.
So it just ended like that.
- To be honest...
- Why do you not like her?
It's not that I didn't like her.
You asked what I thought of her.
And I said, "I think she's nice."
"Why don't you go
on a date with her then?"
"Maybe there's
someone better for her."
Really?
I said...
Please don't get me wrong.
I have my position.
And I have my own standards, you know.
- You have your own standards?
- What...
- Nonsense.
- What are you...
- Hold on a second.
- He's talking nonsense.
- He's ridiculous.
- Your own standards?
- I mean, I have my own preference.
- Maybe that's because...
there are many beautiful women
around Sae Ho,
- and he knows many of them.
- I guess he's quite popular.
- But he never dated any of them.
- It's understandable.
- True. He didn't date any of them.
- Why...
What makes you think
I never dated any of them?
I've seen
Sae Ho's girlfriend before.
- How did she look?
- Sae Ho's girlfriend?
- You've seen his girlfriend?
- Rumor has it...
that Sae Ho always lies that he has
a girlfriend when he doesn't.
But I've actually eaten
with his girlfriend.
- Really?
- When I met her,
I couldn't understand why she was
dating Sae Ho.
- Really? Was she pretty?
- She was incredibly gorgeous.
He tends to spend a lot of money
on his girlfriend.
My goodness.
(He tends to spend a lot of money
on his girlfriend.)
- Let me explain.
- I get it. Okay.
- True. I do spend a lot of money.
- I see now.
- The mystery has been solved.
- It's beyond your imagination.
- He spends so much money on a girl.
- I know that.
- I know.
- No wonder why he can't save money.
- He's a generous man.
- Indeed.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
Now, I'll tell you about
today's race...
with the sole guest Cho Sae Ho.
The presidential election will be
held later this week.
- Really?
- Yes.
Oh, really?
Sae Ho, who will you vote for?
The ruling party or one of
the opposition parties? Tell us.
- I can't believe...
- Answer me.
- Must I reveal that right here?
- We all shared it at the opening.
- Just make a hand signal.
- We all revealed our thoughts.
- I'm sorry to disappoint you,
- A hand signal.
but I don't even know what
the ruling and opposition parties mean.
- He avoided the question smoothly.
- That was cool.
With the presidential election
right around the corner,
we're going to choose the captain
of Running Man through an election.
What? We'll have an election?
(There will be an election to choose
the captain of Running Man.)
- Running Man Presidential Race.
- I see.
It's an individual competition.
All of you are the candidates
for the captain.
The winner of the election will
lead the team...
- as the captain for the next month.
- Really?
- For one month?
- That's amazing.
- I know, right?
- For one month?
The captain will get various
benefits during his or her term.
The captain's name will be added
to the logo that appears...
in the top left corner of the screen
like "captain's name's Running Man."
- That sounds great.
- That's tempting.
- That's amazing.
- Nice.
(The 1st benefit will improve
the captain's reputation.)
Also, only the captain's photo will
appear on the screen...
with the TV rating
right before the show begins.
For the next month, we'll prepare
any food that the captain wants...
- for lunch.
- That's great.
(Benefit 3: Choosing the menu
for lunch regardless of the price)
- I really like this one.
- We'll provide the captain...
with E water during a shoot.
- Really?
- Oh, my. That's so nice.
The captain will get a pay raise
during his or her term as well.
However, the increased amount
will be paid in R money.
- R money?
- Yes.
We'll give the captain extra R money
before every race.
- That's good.
- It's a great benefit.
However, this kind of glory always
comes with great responsibility.
Since the captain will represent
this show,
during his or her term,
with a sense of responsibility,
the captain must attend
the staff meeting...
- more than once a week.
- Gosh. I don't want that title now.
(The captain's duty: Attending
the staff meeting of Running Man)
- I don't want to be the captain.
- I won't do it.
- The captain must offer ideas too.
- That's a penalty.
- That's a penalty, not a benefit.
- I'll never be the captain.
- The staff meeting? Gosh.
- That's ridiculous.
- The captain must...
- I'll just do as I want.
- come by our office in Mok-dong,
give your approval of our plans,
and offer some ideas.
All of us said we didn't want to be
the captain except for Sae Ho.
- Does all of it apply to me too?
- Yes.
- Of course.
- Really?
- How does it work?
- The same rules will apply to him,
but he won't be on the show.
- Does that mean...
- Should he attend the meetings too?
That's good.
Cho Sae Ho's Running Man...
- without Cho Sae Ho?
- I support Cho Sae Ho!
- I'd go to the meeting once a week?
- That's a hassle.
- Actually, it's a good opportunity.
- It's a hassle.
- Your ideas will be used.
- Exactly.
The title will be Cho Sae Ho's
Running Man for a month. It's good.
- That would be great.
- If Sae Ho wins the election,
wouldn't people talk badly
about him?
- Even so, I would...
- What do you think?
The footage of the meeting...
- will be included in the show.
- It'd help you get some attention.
- The footage of the meeting?
- That sounds great.
That means you'll get paid too.
That'd be nice, but it'd be
meaningful to be part of the show.
That's right.
You will fight with one another
for this glorious title.
- I don't like it. It's a penalty.
- It's a harsh penalty.
- Gosh. And it lasts for a month.
- I don't like it either.
- It sounds like a hassle.
- I don't want to do it.
- I hate it the most.
- It's the worst.
- So Min, you should be the captain.
- But the meetings...
The meetings...
So Min, your eyes are sparkling.
No. You're all mistaken.
So Min seems quite ambitious.
No, I'm not, Jong Kook.
Ji Hyo, what do you think?
Do you want to be the captain?
It'll be Song Ji Hyo's Running Man.
Well, I'm a little indifferent,
to be honest.
That's an honest answer.
Obviously, getting as many ballots
as possible is very important.
- We should get as many as we can.
- I'll explain the rule to you.
Absolutely.
We'll give each of you a map...
- divided into electoral districts.
- Yes.
Divide ten ballots you'll be given,
and place them in any region.
For example, you can put
four ballots in Gyeonggi Province...
- and two in Jeolla Province.
- I see.
The winner of each mission will pick
a region and obtain the ballots.
(The winner picks a region
on someone else's map,)
(and obtains the number of ballots
allotted in the region.)
The remaining ballots after the race
will be yours.
- I shouldn't let the others know?
- Correct.
- Don't show your map to the others.
- Yes. Don't let them know.
My gosh.
- Make it advantageous to yourself.
- Okay. I understand.
- First off...
- This is...
- just like real-life politics.
- We need to be ambitious.
- Just like real-life politics.
- Should I just...
Should I put all in the same region?
What should I do?
- My, this is not easy.
- I have no idea.
- Should I put all in one place?
- There are six regions.
(Each candidate plans a strategy
to win the fierce competition.)
If you want to reduce the chance of
losing ballots,
- putting all in one area isn't bad.
- You're right.
- It's difficult.
- Then picking the right area...
can be an advantage, right?
- Sae Ho, can you quiet down?
- Pardon?
- That was the only thing I said.
- Sae Ho.
- You should be quiet now.
- Oh, I see.
Chungcheong Province...
Oh, I get it.
Se Chan must've put some
in Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
- Why are you saying that suddenly?
- I just saw you take the area off.
You have to take off every sticker,
so you can put them on your map.
I'm going to take off Jeju Island.
- Suk Jin...
- He doesn't understand the rule.
- He doesn't know the rules.
- What's wrong with him?
- You have to put them on your map.
- Don't let the others see your map.
- Make sure no one sees it.
- Right. Be careful.
It'd be funny if Sae Ho wins, right?
Yes. It'd be nice if he wins.
- We have three missions today.
- Don't worry.
- Those who place from 1st to 4th...
- I didn't see it.
will get to pick two regions
on someone else's map.
(After each mission, the top 4 will
pick 2 regions of another member.)
The person in 1st place can choose
2 regions of 1 of the 7 others.
So can the one in second place.
And they get the ballots.
- The remaining ballots are yours.
- Okay.
All of you finished
dividing your ballots.
- Now, please change your clothes.
- Okay.
Look at the view. It's beautiful.
(The 1st mission will be held
in a place with a great river view.)
What an amazing view.
- Oh, my.
- This place is so nice.
We can see the Han River from here.
- Sit down.
- Right.
- That was smooth.
- Can I sit?
- Yes, please.
- All right.
"Can I sit?"
- I must say, I can't stop laughing.
- What was that?
I'm surrounded by
Se Chan and Sae Ho.
- What do you mean by that?
- Don't make it a love triangle.
(She tried to make it
a love triangle.)
- You see, that's So Min's problem.
- The three of us?
- This is what they call...
- That's right.
- You guys are already here.
- You see...
(You guys are already here.)
- Sorry. Please don't interrupt.
- I'm sorry.
- How come you all came so early?
- Please don't interrupt.
- She wants to create romance.
- That's right.
- She keeps sending mixed signals.
- Exactly.
- She tries to create her own story.
- In fact...
I want you to act like that
only when your feelings are genuine.
That's exactly my point.
- Then you might have a chance.
- Yes.
- So Min seems...
- I know, but you keep...
- So Min looks...
- Right.
- As if she had feelings...
- She looks disappointed.
You know how So Min approaches a man
when he keeps a distance from her.
- Yes. She feels disappointed.
- So Min tends to do that.
- Is it because you're sad?
- I just want...
a certain level of intimacy.
- I see. Can you elaborate?
- What do you mean by that?
- Then...
- I want us to be close friends.
Would you not mind
if I drove you home after the shoot?
I don't want you to do that.
Would you not mind
if I drove you home after the shoot?
I don't want you to do that.
That's ridiculous.
- I mean...
- That's just weird.
- Gosh, I hate it.
- That's so weird.
- He's so bad at dating.
- That's the worst.
- That's disgusting.
- I hate it so much.
- What's wrong with it?
- But So Min...
- She seems excited.
- Yes.
- I'd prepare flowers for you.
- She's finally smiling.
- He knows how to make her smile.
- I'd put the flowers in my car.
- So Min likes things like this.
- Yes, she does.
- She likes it.
- "This is for you."
- And then I'd drive you home.
So Min, you're smiling
in a flirty way unlike usual.
- I just like comments like this.
- She likes such comments.
- It makes your heart flutter.
- Yes.
- She sure likes such comments.
- Say something like that too.
- Right.
- But I don't have a car.
(Chuckling)
You know that he has a car, right?
I can't believe he told such a lie.
He didn't tell me
that he had moved either.
I'll tell you
about the first mission.
The first mission...
where the candidates' weaknesses
may be revealed is...
- Okay.
- Say Yes! Variety Show Hearing.
- We've played this game before.
- Right. You must say, "I admit it."
- Is it a hearing?
- It was fun.
In Episode 574 where we had
the Elegant Western Road race,
you played this game with some hard
comments for you to admit...
- that the viewers sent to us.
- That's right.
(They could score points
only when they raised "Admit.")
(Everyone was confident.)
(I admit all of my body secrets
often mentioned on TV shows.)
(I've actually dated a guest
on a variety show.)
(I'm actually 168cm tall.)
(I'm 171.5cm tall. Gosh.)
Based on what I've seen
for the past four years,
(I don't understand why Jae Suk is
called the best MC in Korea.)
(They have to admit
such harsh comments.)
It was so much fun. I remember that.
- It was really fun.
- She wasn't there?
- At the donut place, right?
- Yes.
- That's right.
So Min couldn't be there
as she was a close contact.
(So Min missed the shoot
as she was a close contact.)
Sae Ho wasn't there either
as the icon of absence.
- Why didn't you come?
- I wasn't even invited.
- You should've come anyway.
- You should've come.
- We had a shoot in Gangnam.
- I'm disappointed.
- Why didn't you come?
- I apologize.
- Don't ever do that again.
- I was wrong.
- Yes.
- You were wrong.
- You should stay focused.
- I'll check the schedule.
- We were at Apgujeong.
- I won't let it happen again.
- Apgujeong Rodeo Street.
Since the two of them didn't get
a chance to play this game,
- we prepared it again.
- That's good.
Each of you will
listen to a question.
It's not difficult.
If you admit it,
your team wins one point.
- Okay.
- It's that easy, Sae Ho.
- All you have to do is admit.
- That's right.
- So this is...
- There may be weird questions.
- That's good.
- But I can score a point...
- if I admit.
- That's correct.
- You have to explain why as well.
- Okay.
You will be divided into two teams.
- Team So Min and Team Sae Ho.
- Yes.
So Min and Sae Ho will be given
five questions each.
- The others will be given only one.
- Okay.
- It must be a hard one.
- It'll still be hard.
- All right.
- We also picked the team members.
- Yes.
You'll be with the same members
as the last time.
Jong Kook, Suk Jin, Haha,
and So Min are on the same team.
(Team So Min)
- We're on the same team.
- And...
- Se Chan, Ji Hyo, Jae Suk...
- Great.
You see, after playing this game,
a lot of news articles about us
came out.
- True.
- That's the thing about this game.
- If you admit something...
- It made the headlines.
- Of course.
- That's true.
- You just have to overcome it.
- But they wouldn't pick easy ones.
- All right.
- Just admit whatever you hear.
- First up is So Min.
- Make sure to admit everything.
- Admit everything.
- Don't worry. It's not hard.
I bet So Min will deny
the comments so easily.
- Don't lose your temper.
- She's quite sensitive.
- It's not hard.
- Indeed.
Here's the first question.
- Stay calm.
- "To be honest,"
"I'm afraid to ask Se Chan out
because he might reject me."
(Question: I'm afraid to ask
Se Chan out...)
(because he might reject me.)
You've told me that before.
You remember that, right?
- Hey.
- You were afraid.
Be honest. You're afraid.
- Really? Hey, So Min.
- That's not true.
"What? No. I don't like you."
- Do you think I'd say that?
- That's not true.
- "I don't find you attractive."
- It's not like that.
- Just admit it.
- You were afraid.
- That's not the reason...
- It's not that hard.
It wouldn't feel great
if he rejected you.
- Is it because it's harder...
- If you thought that way...
- to make him fall for you?
- Is it not the reason?
Then deny it.
- Listen.
- Deny it.
Listen to me. Even if there's...
- a one percent chance, admit it.
- So Min, deny it.
That's not why I won't ask him out.
- Deny it first, and then explain.
- Why are you getting upset?
- Stay calm.
- Then what's the reason?
- Why won't you ask him out?
- Is there a particular reason?
- Tell us.
- She's tearing up.
It's because I'm not into him...
- Deny it first, and then explain.
- Deny it.
- Deny it first.
- You can explain after denying it.
- Just deny it.
- Say that you deny it.
- So Min, listen to me.
- You should say it.
- Come on.
- I guess I'm irresistible. Tell us.
- Admit it. Don't get upset.
- So Min, say you deny it.
- You won't ask him out... Good.
- Okay. She admitted it.
- She admitted it?
- Asking him out...
- Do you think I'd reject you?
- doesn't necessarily mean...
- Do you? Explain yourself.
- she's head over heels for him.
- Exactly.
- Right. Go ahead.
- I'll explain.
- Why do you think I'd reject you?
I think he'd reject me...
because he wouldn't believe...
that I really like him.
That's why I think he'd reject me
if I asked him out.
- So I admit it.
- Okay.
- That's not true.
- No way.
- That's not what the comment means.
- You should deny it.
- She practically denied it.
- Good job.
- This is what it means.
- Yes.
"I like him so much,"
"but I'm afraid he might reject me."
- No!
- She just denied it.
(No!)
- Hey, stay calm.
- She denied it.
- I told you, it's not like that.
- This is just a game.
- It's just a game.
- Let's say you have a crush on me.
- You ask me out, but I reject you.
- No one would believe it.
- I'll be honest.
- No one would think that way.
- It's true that she liked you.
- It's just a game.
Some of us knew that,
but we kept it a secret.
- When did I like him?
- There's nothing wrong with it.
- Haha, don't say anything.
- I didn't like him that way.
- Tell us, So Min.
- She practically denied it.
- Are you afraid I might reject you?
- Just admit it.
- No.
- She'll deny it.
- You won't admit it?
- I deny it.
- She denied it.
- Okay.
- Really?
- I knew it.
- Se Chan...
- It's okay. We can make up for it.
Maybe he gained weight
during the quarantine.
Yes, I did. You can see that, right?
Honestly, I could never admit it
because he looked like that.
- Exactly.
- It would've hurt my pride.
- He looks unusually ugly today.
- Exactly.
Sae Ho looks handsome
because of Se Chan.
- It's great. You should thank me.
- Things are going well for you.
- Sae Ho, don't cross your legs.
- Pardon? I shouldn't cross my legs?
He just told me
not to cross my legs.
Earlier, I left to change my mic,
and he scolded me...
for leaving during the shoot.
Where did you go?
- Right. You shouldn't do that.
- You shouldn't.
- Don't leave during a shoot.
- You shouldn't leave the set.
Sae Ho, your right nostril is
running.
Oh, thanks for telling me.
I admit it.
- I admit it.
- Why is your nose running?
- Are you okay, Sae Ho?
- I'm fine. I admit it.
- It's because...
- Instead of tears...
He has a runny nose
instead of crying tears.
- But this is...
- She denied it.
- It was nothing to be upset about.
We can make up for it
if we admit ours.
But we already know the truth.
"I have called
one of the male guests..."
"who appeared on Running Man
for a personal reason."
- You have. Admit it.
- You'll admit it, right?
(I've called 1 of the male guests
for a personal reason.)
(You'll admit it, right?)
- She'll admit it.
- Be honest with us. Admit it.
- You have done it before.
- I know it's true.
- I know that.
- You should admit this.
It must be easy for her to admit it.
- You'll admit it, right?
- This one is easy.
If she admits it,
she has to tell us whom she called.
- I bet she'll admit it.
- She has to reveal the guests.
- Or say you deny it.
- That's not fair.
- Why must she reveal their names?
- Should she?
- She doesn't have to do that.
- She has to.
- What are you talking about?
- She doesn't have to do that.
(My head hurts.)
- Why must she?
- Or she can say she denies it.
- Answer me.
She doesn't have to do that.
- Why must she?
- She should tell us who they were.
- Why?
- Or she can say she denies it.
- Then...
- She doesn't have to reveal it.
- She should if she admits it.
- Or just deny it.
- Just deny it.
- You don't have to do that.
- There's nothing wrong with it.
- She can deny it.
Just deny it.
- It's not a bad thing.
- Just deny it, So Min.
I've called some of the guests too.
Just deny it.
- Suk Jin, it's not the same thing.
- Why?
It's the same thing.
- It's different.
- Nonsense.
I've called some of the guests too.
- It's okay.
- Admit it.
- She denied it.
- Why would you deny it?
(So Min denied it.)
Why did you tell her that
to make her deny it?
- Nice.
- It's not like that.
- You chose to protect your image.
- Nice.
That's not why I denied it.
I have never gotten the phone number
of any guest.
- I'm so disappointed.
- Okay. So Min denied it.
- We won't ask you any questions.
- I'm so disappointed.
- We'll pretend we don't know.
- So Min.
Let's move on.
"If Jong Kook were younger than me,
I would've taught him a lesson."
- Hey.
- So Min.
- You should admit this.
- That's true.
You should admit it.
(She admitted it so quickly.)
Hey, you admitted it too quickly.
- Hey.
- Of course, she admitted it.
Look at you wearing pants
that look like tiles on a bathroom floor.
She admitted it. Why?
- Of course, she admitted it.
- Just like bathroom floor tiles.
Of course, she admitted it.
Tell us why you admitted it.
If he were younger than me...
I only refrain myself out of respect
since he's older than me.
But if not, I would've taught him
a lesson with harsh words.
- With harsh words?
- He's so much stronger than me.
(Is that so?)
I'm no match for him.
He'd be intimidating
even if he were younger than me.
Right. He would still be
intimidating.
- That's true. You see...
- If that could work,
Suk Jin would've already
taught him a lesson.
- He's younger than me, but...
- He would've done it a while ago.
He's younger than me,
but it's not easy.
- But Suk Jin... Still...
- He's very fond of me.
- But still, Jong Kook...
- We get along well together.
Yes, we do.
That's because Jong Kook...
would never treat older people...
- with disrespect.
- I would never do that.
They get along well
because Suk Jin is...
- always nice to Jong Kook too.
- Exactly.
He bends over backwards
for Jong Kook.
We get along well together.
- He's very polite to me.
- Of course.
- We take care of each other.
- He bends over backwards for him.
While Jong Kook was in quarantine
at home,
- Suk Jin was...
- Suk Jin is so nice to him.
- so worried about his health.
- That's true.
- He was worried about Jong Kook...
- Of course.
- while coughing badly.
- He asked if Jong Kook was okay.
He asked, "How are you feeling?"
- He was coughing...
- I'm the best, right?
- You're the best.
- Of course.
- And he's cute too.
- That's right.
- He acts cute in front of him.
- Indeed.
- He's cute.
- He's a cutie.
Here goes the last one.
"To be honest,"
"I'm dumber than Se Chan."
- If you admit this...
- Why are you doing this to me?
- It's not a hard one.
- Explain why you think you are.
- For example, you think...
- you lack general knowledge...
- You can just admit it.
- Honestly, Se Chan...
- Just admit it.
uses more sophisticated words
than you do.
What are you talking about?
- He does seem smarter than you.
- You should admit it.
- I mean, I think Se Chan is...
- He knows a lot of English words.
- a little bit smarter than she is.
- Se Chan is smarter than her.
- In fact...
- But...
- I admit it.
- Good.
- Explain why you think that way.
- I have something to say.
- Why do you think you're dumber?
- I mean...
I believe there's a wide range of
factors to determine...
- Then you should've denied it.
- No.
- I admit that he's smarter than me.
- Are you more empty-headed than me?
What? You little...
(Are you more empty-headed than me?)
(The empty head's attack)
- It's a better way of putting it.
- That's funny.
"Empty-headed?"
- Is your head completely empty?
- "Empty-headed?"
(Is your head completely empty?)
- You have no brain in there?
- That's hilarious.
It's completely empty.
There's no brain in there.
- That's right.
- A part of your skull fell apart?
So you have to walk around
looking like this?
- Tell me.
- How does she walk around again?
Like this. With no brain
in her head.
- You admitted it.
- Do you want to deny it?
You're more empty-headed than me.
- You're completely empty-headed.
- She's bad at multiplication.
- She's bad at it.
- There must be a little difference.
- A little difference.
- It's not embarrassing.
- Just admit it.
- No. Way dumber than him.
- He said, "way dumber."
- Admit you're way dumber than him.
- You can do this.
- He didn't say, "way dumber."
- It's okay.
- Admit you have no brain.
- Se Chan knows...
- Just admit it.
He knows more about
social and cultural trends...
- Just say if you admit it or not.
- Be honest.
Yes, I'm completely empty-headed.
(Yes, I'm completely empty-headed.)
There's no brain in here.
(She admits she's an empty head.)
- Happy now?
- Stop it. What's your problem?
- You just can't stay calm.
- Right. Hey.
- And...
- I admit it.
- You still admit it?
- You know more about sports...
- than he does.
- She already admitted it.
- Okay.
- I admit it.
- She's so dumb.
- That's okay.
- I'm smarter than her.
- But she's a better referee.
- She's much better than you.
- Okay. She's dumber than me.
- I'm done, right?
- Yes, you're done.
- Good.
- We still have a chance to lose.
- It's easy. Just admit everything.
- There will be five questions.
- For the team's sake.
- Okay.
Here's your question.
"I have talked about Jae Suk
behind his back in real life,"
"not for a TV show."
- It's true.
- I admit it.
- Okay.
- It's easy.
(I've talked about Jae Suk
behind his back in real life.)
(He admitted it right away.)
- I heard about it from others.
- It's true.
- It wasn't for a TV show.
- You heard about it?
I actually said that I was
uncomfortable around Jae Suk...
Where? To whom?
I was chatting with Lee Kwang Soo
at the gym.
- Okay. That's good enough.
- "He calls me too often."
- I said that to him.
- That's understandable.
- It's a true story.
The trainer at the gym told me
that story.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- There's nothing wrong with it.
Although I like him so much,
I don't like some things about him.
- That's natural.
- Yes.
- There's nothing wrong with it.
- That's cool.
- Good.
- Let's move on.
"Neither So Min nor Ji Hyo is
good enough for me."
I admit it.
(He admits it?)
(Hitting)
- I'm being honest.
- He admitted it.
(Sae Ho's answer will anger
all Koreans.)
It was an honest answer.
I have my own standards.
- Right. Okay.
- Hey.
- He does have high standards.
- This makes me upset.
- They're not good enough for him?
- He has high standards.
- They may not be his type.
- Who do you think you are?
- They're not good enough for you?
- How dare you say that about them?
Don't you dare say mean things
about them.
I have no choice but to talk about
you behind your back.
- You're leaving me no choice.
- He's right.
- But how could you say that...
- Try to think in my shoes.
- about the members I care about?
- Listen.
- Don't even think of dating him.
- I know...
- that you care about them.
- But...
- That's right.
Who's to say
that I'll go after them?
That's different from them
not being good enough for you.
- To be honest...
- They're not good enough?
If So Min told me
that she was dating you,
I would throw a fit.
- We'd be against it.
- I won't let it slide.
Why is that?
It just can't be you.
You're just pushing it
for no reason.
That's a lot of vigor.
- Just admit it.
- I admit it.
I'm sorry to say this,
- but they're not good enough.
- They're not your type.
Him saying that is motivating her.
- She seems desperate.
- Of course not.
I could treat So Min to a meal
if that's what she wants.
- Well, of course.
- Beef?
- It can be anything.
- Even Japanese omakase?
Japanese omakase?
Wait. I guess that's too expensive.
- Not that?
- Korean beef or omakase...
- will cost you 500 dollars each.
- For how many people?
- Four. Including her friends.
- Four?
Four people, 500 dollars each?
Make it six people
since that's the limit these days.
- Six?
- Yes, six.
You can easily spend
3,000 dollars, right?
- That's 3,000 dollars.
- I'll think about it.
Really?
- And Japanese omakase.
- As long as there are no drinks.
- Sounds good.
- No drinks.
- Okay.
- I love how he admits everything.
- Question number three.
- He admits everything.
I hesitated before
when coming onto Running Man...
because Jong Kook is an eyesore.
(I hesitated before
when coming onto Running Man...)
(because Jong Kook is an eyesore.)
I admit to that.
(He admits to it
at the speed of light.)
- I...
- Why is he an eyesore?
- Well...
- Why?
He calls me out for losing my touch.
"Sae Ho, why aren't you
funny anymore?"
Not even encouragement
can help me sometimes.
- So you hate his demeanor.
- He tears me down from the start.
That's his way of being nice to you.
- Exactly.
- That's him showing love.
One's encouragement
should sit right with me.
No matter how good...
Just look at Suk Jin.
He doesn't do anything to fight it.
I'm just saying that...
Jong Kook must be hurt
to hear you say that about him.
He finds you suffocating.
- But...
- You know,
you should seem more reluctant...
and only hold it up
because you have no other choice.
- But I...
- You're being too serious.
But I'm present, aren't I?
I may have hesitated, but I'm here.
Which floor do you live on?
Me? The 17th floor.
Check out the window
from time to time.
You'll see someone
looking up at you.
The 17th floor? Which neighborhood?
- Mapo.
- Mapo? Got it.
(Information received)
Jong Kook will find you.
- You admitted to it.
- He'll be there.
Sae Ho admitted to it.
- You should seem more reluctant.
- Go ahead.
I may have
more experience in the business,
but Se Chan is better...
at hosting variety shows
and improvising.
(Se Chan is better at...)
(hosting variety shows
and improvising.)
Just admit to it.
- Well...
- These days...
Yes, of course.
- Absolutely.
(You're not immediately agreeing?)
- What...
- But why?
Sae Ho meant
every word he said so far!
- He meant every word.
- He was being serious.
You've been telling
the truth so far.
- You need to think about this?
- Shouldn't I?
This is what you need
to think about?
Were you serious about
me making you uncomfortable?
- This I need to think about.
- It's what he believes.
- I'm younger, so...
- Hear me out, guys.
If you can't admit to it,
it means that
you're serious about Jong Kook.
- Let me think for a second.
- Sure.
You told us to just admit to it.
Se Chan's been on a roll these days.
He's hilarious these days.
He's been killing it.
You see...
(Se Chan is better at hosting
variety shows and improvising.)
- He's pondering.
- I admit to it.
- Really?
- Because...
- You agree with this?
- You see,
I've been learning a lot from him.
(I've been learning a lot from him.)
I admire
the spirit and confidence...
- he displays in comedy shows.
- His spirit?
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but he's way better
at comedy sketches.
Yes, exactly.
Starting from his days...
playing Big Eyes' father.
You can't possibly
compare yourself with him.
We'll comfortably say
what's on our minds now.
- Se Chan's way better.
- Yes, of course.
I couldn't be honest with you
because he's your junior.
So you see...
This is the side of you
that I hate the most.
(What an eyesore!)
The way you talk.
- This tone?
- Yes.
- Is this the one?
- I get it.
That I agree.
He's been telling
nothing but the truth.
- He meant everything he said.
- He wasn't lying.
This wasn't just for fun.
Here's your last question.
Suk Jin is my idol and role model.
(Suk Jin is my idol
and role model.)
- Must you think about this?
- What?
- He's thinking about it.
- What's there to think about?
During quarantine,
you called and said you admired me.
Don't you agree with this?
How can you...
- You said you admired me.
- Your role model?
- He's your hero!
- Unbelievable.
Calling him my hero...
He's a great man, that's all.
Do I have to be able
to wear your face on my arm?
- Of course.
- Absolutely!
- Suk Jin's face.
- Right here.
You need to be able to have
a photo of his big nose on your arm.
Just like people have photos
of Charlie Chaplin, right?
People do that, you know.
- I'll go with this for starters.
- Really?
(He admits to it for starters.)
- Look at Suk Jin.
- He...
- You must keep your word.
- You must.
- Are you insane?
- Back when I was young,
you were the reason
why I wanted to become a comedian.
- Really?
- Yes.
Don't you lie.
Jeon Yoo Seong was your mentor.
He wasn't active
when you were an aspiring comedian.
- You looked up to Nam Hee Suk.
- Wasn't he?
No, he wasn't.
How can I put this, then? He...
(Eyes quivering)
Even at this age,
- he shows vigor and...
- He's now telling lies.
Anyone can tell.
You don't sound like yourself.
This isn't how you seemed
when you said I was an eyesore.
It's like you don't want
to agree to this.
- But honestly...
- It's nice to hear this though.
I search my name online
every morning.
- What about Suk Jin's?
- And then Suk Jin's.
What came up
when you looked up his name?
That it's another
cheerful day for him.
- That's a lie.
- He's lying.
- Are you lying or not?
- I'm not.
What's the name of his son?
I couldn't possibly
say his noble name out loud.
What's his name?
Is it Ji Seok Sam?
You...
- That was nicely improvised.
- I'm sorry.
- Wasn't it great?
- Seok Sam?
- Ji Seok Sam?
- Do you know his wife's name?
- What's her name?
Mrs. Ji, you mean?
- Mrs. Ji?
- Yes, Mrs. Ji.
- My gosh.
- My hero.
- Thank you, Sae Ho.
- Okay, fine.
- You'll get a tattoo.
- Next week,
Sae Ho will get himself a tattoo.
- Of course.
- A henna at least.
- Yes, a henna at least.
- At least.
- Right.
- He's your hero after all.
Get a henna tattoo of my face...
- and post it on social media.
- That's right.
(On social media?)
He's your hero, isn't he?
With your best Tom Hardy impression.
Right.
- If you don't...
- Post it on social media.
- Exactly.
- With a Tom Hardy impression.
- On social media.
- Rather than a henna,
I'll go with a realistic drawing.
- There are artists who can do that.
- Right.
- I'll get myself a drawing.
- And?
- With a Tom Hardy impression.
- Post it on social media.
- Show us.
My hero.
- That's what I'll do.
- And post it on social media?
- Yes.
- Then you'll pass.
I'm not kidding.
This is my first...
(He ended up keeping his word.)
This is my first tattoo.
My role model.
I'm excited to get a tattoo
of my role model.
This is why you should
watch your words.
Aren't I the first in Korea
to get a drawing of Suk Jin...
on a body part?
I'll be the first and last.
(My role model Ji Suk Jin)
He admitted to all the questions.
You receive five points.
- No way.
- Good job.
We'll only be asked once,
so admit to them all.
- You have to.
- Let's make a pact.
- Let's promise each other.
- Of course.
- You have to.
- Let's admit to them all.
- We need to do so too.
- All of us.
- We must.
- There's no reason not to.
We'll start with Jong Kook.
- Sure.
- Why me?
You'll only be asked
one question each.
Admit to whatever he says.
- Just admit to it.
- That's all you have to do.
- It's not that hard.
- Just admit to it.
Bring it on.
I'm the worst at soccer.
(I'm the worst at soccer.)
- Say it.
- Admit to it.
I'm the worst at soccer.
This...
- Admit to it.
- Just say it.
- You must admit to it.
- I admit to it.
- Jong Kook.
- You see,
although he loves the sport...
If anyone's going to admit to this,
it'll be me!
- Wait.
- Who are you to answer for me?
But...
Why are you angry at me?
It's my question to answer.
- Why are you worked up?
- Who are you to answer for me?
- Keep at it!
- Why are you angry?
- How dare you.
Even if this is wrong,
- for the team...
- This is a sensitive topic.
You could admit to it for the team.
For someone who loves
soccer so much...
Shut it!
Shut it
and let me answer his question.
He's not as good as he says he is.
The worst at soccer?
- The worst at soccer.
- He does miss his kick at times.
He's not that good
of a soccer player...
for someone who's in a club
and plays every week.
(Roaring)
He frequently makes mistakes.
Don't you love
how cheeky Jae Suk is?
- He...
- He'd rather...
hear people say he's a bad singer.
- That's all right.
- Say he's a bad singer instead.
But Jong Kook's a great singer.
It's not like you even
played a game with me before.
Join us for next week's game.
Join us next week.
I don't have soccer cleats.
I'll lend you mine,
so just be there.
- They won't fit.
- They will. You wear 275mm.
No, I wear 270mm.
(The newbie-to-be
talks back to the team owner.)
- He's dead serious.
- Just admit to it.
- Anyway...
- Right.
- I see this isn't easy.
- Of course not.
- It's not easy at all.
- It isn't.
- It hurts his pride.
- It's a matter of pride.
- He is the owner of the team.
- Of course.
- It's for the team.
- Right.
I'll admit to this.
Okay, nice!
- Why though?
- You're the worst at soccer.
Can I tell others
that you're the worst at soccer?
- Of course.
He said so himself.
Do you start trembling
when the ball comes near you?
When the ball rolls close,
do you say...
"Don't pass it to me.
I'm the worst at soccer!"
"Don't pass it to me!"
He must say that
for this to be true.
Don't you run a soccer team?
- Do you feel the pressure?
- Se Chan's being mean today.
You haven't been to practice lately.
- If you admit to it...
- Do you...
- admit to it?
- Yes, I do.
I'm fine with it.
Can it not be remedied
with hard work?
- Aren't you on my team?
- Sure, of course.
We're on the same team, darn it.
- We're on the same team.
- I'm sorry.
You should be more careful.
Jong Kook, I'm sorry to ask,
but do you know...
how many players
are on a soccer team?
(Do you know how many players
are on a soccer team?)
Why you...
Are you teasing him?
- Of course I know.
- I was just checking.
Explain why you're
the worst at soccer.
- Why are you the worst at it?
- Well...
What makes you a bad player?
What do you lack as a player?
- Everything, but...
- Well...
He could be better at dribbling.
You!
It's true.
It's me who's admitting to this,
- so who are you to butt in?
- Have you seen him play?
Yes, of course.
- It's not like that.
- He's Jong Kook's spokesperson.
Well...
- It's...
- He hates this situation.
Don't admit to it, then.
Change your mind.
- We wouldn't ask.
- Don't admit to it.
I...
Yes, I feel like dying
every time someone passes the ball.
- When the ball comes near me...
- Can't you dribble it?
- I can't.
- Of course not.
But it's not like you shoot well.
Right, his shots aren't good.
We're on the same team.
Jong Kook is the worst at soccer.
- It's so...
- He admitted it.
All right.
Jong Kook is the worst at soccer.
Jae Suk, it's your turn.
- It's my turn?
- Yes.
- I'll admit it no matter what.
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk, everyone admits it.
- Let's do it.
What's there not to admit?
It'd be strange not to.
Right. You should just admit it.
He's the most generous man.
- I'll hold it before hearing it.
- All right.
"I..."
"have a lot of money."
That's true.
- That's true.
- This is...
- Of course I admit it.
You have a lot of money.
You must tell us how much you have.
- He must reveal all his assets?
- Yes, he must.
I must reveal my assets?
- All the real estate.
- Tell us.
- The list of your real estate.
- You must tell us.
- Starting with your real estate.
- Tell us the exact amount.
- Tell us everything.
- I'm certain...
- It could be over 100 million.
That's a given.
- I must reveal my assets?
- You should.
Reveal your assets.
I'm certain he has as much as
the prize money from "Squid Game."
You mean 45.6 million dollars?
- What are you doing?
- It's just that...
What do you think you're doing?
Don't you have that much?
- He has about 45.6 million dollars.
- I mean...
- Is it higher or lower than that?
- I need to reveal that too?
- You can use comparison.
- We must know a certain amount.
- So we can accept it.
- Or you can deny it.
- Then deny it.
- Then I'd be lying.
- You have a lot of money.
- So tell us how much you have.
He must tell us.
There are many people
who lie about their assets.
Then can you buy an imported car
right away if you want to?
- Of course!
- That goes without saying!
Why would you ask that?
You're talking about my assets.
I know that.
So tell us how much you have!
- Just tell us roughly.
- Set the boundary and tell us.
- Or you can deny it.
- Deny it?
- I can't deny it.
- Jae Suk.
Let's say you went shopping,
and you loved all the items.
"Give me everything
from here to there."
- I can't do that.
- But...
- Why not?
- Yes, you're capable of doing that.
"Give me everything
from here to there?"
- "Give me everything."
- That's right. The luxury goods.
It's because
he doesn't lavish his money.
- I don't think it's necessary...
- He's capable of that.
- He does have that much money.
- He's capable.
You can buy a rack of Chanel goods.
- Of course. He can do that.
- "Give me all these bags."
- Jong Kook, it's my assets.
- Yes?
You can do it, can't you?
- Then say that you deny it.
- Why are you so upset?
Then say that you deny it.
I roughly calculated,
and you have enough money for that.
Let's say you're at a supercar shop.
"Give me everything
from here to there."
- Can you say that or not?
- He can!
- I can't.
- Yes, you can!
- You have that much money.
- I don't.
- Why can't you do it?
- Then deny it.
Then say it like this.
Just tell us how much you got
for your down payment and end it.
Don't even ask him
how much he has in all.
- Hey.
- How much did you receive?
- He can do it.
- If you don't want to say it...
Then just say you deny it!
- Say you deny it!
- You should admit it.
- But seriously,
- Say you deny it!
he's really amazing.
A few days ago,
we went to an electronics store.
He got a tablet PC
with the best specifications.
He paid for it in a lump sum.
- I can buy that much, you punk.
- Sae Ho, that's...
- Even I can buy that much.
- Hey!
- Anyone can buy that much.
- You can?
- Sae Ho.
- Even we can buy that.
- Are you kidding me?
What about getting a new one
when you already have one?
Of course I can buy it.
- I can buy that much too.
- Really?
- Even I can do that.
- You can?
If you're not going to...
- tell us the rough amount,
- I mean...
- don't admit it.
- What are you telling me to admit?
Admit that you can buy
30 supercars...
at once.
I told you. I am rich!
Can you buy that much?
I am rich!
So can you buy...
If I say I'm not rich...
- Can you buy 30 supercars?
- He's rich.
They'll criticize me!
So can you buy 30 supercars or not?
I don't need 30 supercars!
How much did you get
for your down payment?
Can you buy them or not?
- Can you buy them or not?
- "Give me all the supercars here."
- Tell us if you can or not.
My goodness.
Why can't you say it? I even said...
(I said I shake like this
when a ball comes to me.)
I shake like this
when a ball comes to me.
(He strongly admitted
that he's terrible at soccer.)
Jae Suk, So Min admitted
she's empty-headed.
- I even said I shake like this!
- I'm empty-headed!
- This is driving me crazy.
- You can't share that?
- You can buy that much.
- Deny it if you can't.
- Right. Deny it.
- No, you must admit it.
- Deny it.
- You can spend that much.
- You can buy that much.
- There are many rich people.
Imagine giving the supercar
to each one of us.
- Deny it.
- One for each one of us.
That's...
I can't give them to all of you.
- Why not?
- Why must I buy supercars...
for some of you?
Don't lie!
- That's how much money...
- I can't give them to all of you.
you have.
- You have that much.
- We're talking about your assets.
So do you have...
- enough money or not?
- Listen.
You're capable of buying that much.
Are you capable or not?
- Then tell us this much.
- What?
What's the first digit
of your bank account?
- That's not important!
The number of digits
is more important.
- I mean, we can ask...
- You should take a break.
- Remove his mic.
- Go rest there.
Come here.
- He's talking nonsense.
- So what I'm saying is...
It's because he likes you.
- He's giving you time to think.
- I admit that I'm rich.
I know that you admit it,
- but you should share us...
- I admit I'm rich.
how much you have to admit it.
- So...
- Tell us...
- Did you just push me?
- You pushed me?
- How much do you have?
- Hey.
- I'm also curious.
(Candidate Yoo's hearing
ended up leaking his privacy.)
(They're all saying
groundless rumors.)
- So how rich are you?
- How much do you have?
I'm also curious.
- So...
- How should he tell us?
- He should...
- I deny it.
- We did it.
- He denied it. We did it.
- He's poor.
- We did it.
Seriously...
- He's penniless.
- How could you...
- What?
- You're penniless.
- Hey.
- What did you call me?
Jae Suk is penniless.
My car is better than yours!
- He has no money. He's penniless.
- Sit down.
- He denied it. All right.
- My gosh.
How much do we need to have
to be called rich?
Do we have to go this far?
You should've admitted it.
- Isn't this too much?
- Jae Suk,
call me if you're struggling.
I can lend you some money.
I can treat you to a meal.
My goodness.
Jae Suk denied it.
What does that make us?
That means we're poor.
- It's Suk Jin's turn.
- All right.
- "I..."
- I can just admit it.
- Just take it easy.
- I'll admit it.
- You must admit it.
- That way, we can win.
- "I..."
- They added a twist.
Right.
"I want to quit YouTube,"
- "but I missed the timing."
- That's it.
- You must admit this.
- I can tell.
- You should admit it.
- He's...
- You haven't been uploading.
It seems like
he's not been uploading.
It's because he's not getting
that many views.
Isn't this too easy? Thank you.
- You must admit it.
- Thank you.
- You're not getting many views.
- Hey.
- He's not getting that many.
- You're not.
I have more than
500,000 subscribers. How can I...
Suk Jin, even if you admit it,
- nothing will happen.
- That's right.
- No.
- That's true.
- If you talk about it here...
- Something will happen.
more strategically,
- That's true.
- you'd have more subscribers.
- You'd have more by now.
- That's true.
- Then you should admit it.
- But in a way,
- Let me remind you.
- that's not what he's saying.
- Once you admit it, you must tell.
- Tell what?
When you started
thinking of quitting it.
- It's just how you felt.
- You knew about this.
- You must tell us why.
- This is driving me crazy.
Then you should deny it.
If you admit it, you must tell us
when you thought of it...
- and upload an apology video.
- You just don't like it.
- How can I upload that?
- You should.
- You should wear a suit and do it.
- I can't.
- You must upload it.
- Because you admitted it.
- How can I...
upload an apology video?
- He should wear a suit.
- You should wear a suit too.
- You should do that.
- On a black background,
- To be honest...
you should say,
"I'm sorry for everything."
- That's right.
- I'll watch that for sure.
- The top of your head should show.
- That's right.
You can just say it.
- Actually...
- That's right.
See for me how it looks.
Hello. I'm here to apologize...
You should either admit it
or deny it.
- Let me try it first.
- No, you can't.
Actually, it's been over two years
since I started my channel.
But I've been wanting to quit.
- That's it.
- "I knew it! What a jerk!"
"I knew he'd quit!"
- "Ji Suk Jin, that..."
- What did you say?
This could happen.
- It's because he's not educated.
- This could happen.
I deny it! I can't admit it.
All right. He denied it.
It's Ji Hyo's turn.
"Just like I said in the past,"
"I can seduce every man here
with a flick of my finger."
You should admit it.
- I admit it.
- All right!
- Try it.
- Show it to us.
It makes no sense.
Why would you be mad, Suk Jin?
- It's not that I'm mad.
- Don't be mad.
That's it!
(With a flick of her finger,)
(he smiles from ear to ear.)
- He smiled.
- Don't be mad.
Don't be mad.
- "Don't be mad."
- But...
Ji Hyo.
It's Haha's turn.
It's your turn.
You must admit it no matter what.
- What could it be?
- Admit it no matter what.
"If you want, I can measure
my height here."
Come again?
"If you want, I can measure
my height here."
- Of course he can.
- Didn't he say he was 173cm?
- Just do it.
- Haha.
- Let's measure it.
He's over 170cm.
- Didn't you say you were 173cm?
- Hey.
- You're over 170cm.
- He even shaved his hair.
(Height: 168cm)
(Who wrote that? I'm 171.5cm tall!)
(When I'm in good condition,
I'm 172.5cm tall!)
(There's a 4cm difference
depending on his condition?)
(Curious Stories R,
A man affected by gravity)
He's over 170cm.
- Didn't you say you were 173cm?
- Hey.
- You're over 170cm.
- He even shaved his hair.
- I'm 171.5cm.
- He can't be that tall now.
- Because you cut your hair...
- You don't have hair right now.
- You can do it.
- He's shorter than 170cm.
When I measured my height
on "Infinite Challenge,"
- That's five years ago.
- I was 172cm,
- so they pushed me down.
- But you don't have hair now.
If you measure it now,
- you must take off your socks.
- Just show it to them.
"Infinite Challenge"...
- The thing is...
- is over ten years ago.
I'm in bad condition.
The Omicron variant...
- Hey!
- It damages your sense of smell,
- but it also shortens your spine.
- Haha.
- I mean it.
- Just deny it.
- It's better to deny it.
- Let's measure your height.
- He should deny it.
- You can do it, Haha.
- It's nothing.
- I'm not that short.
- Just measure it with no excuses.
- I'm over 170cm.
You see, I contracted
the Omicron variant.
- So I'm in bad condition.
- So what if you're not over 170cm?
- Because I was in bed...
- Then deny it.
- Deny it.
No, I can't deny it.
Deny it.
- Seriously.
- I'm over 170cm.
- Then admit it.
- I bet it'd be positive...
if I got tested again.
- Should I bring it?
- Just deny it.
- I'm still sick.
Don't bring it.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm in really bad condition.
- Just measure it!
- I'll go bring it.
- I'm in bad condition.
- Deny it.
- Seriously...
- I'd measure it with no trouble.
- What are you trying to do?
- Okay, let's do it.
- I'm obviously over 170cm. Look.
- Just deny it.
- Gosh, this is...
- No.
- Just deny it.
- You guys are so mean.
Is my mic okay?
Suk Jin,
do you want to measure your height?
- Suk Jin.
- Me?
- You should measure it.
- Of course I can.
Try it, Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin is tall.
- You should take off your shoes.
- I can do it. It's nothing hard.
- How tall are you?
- I'm 177cm tall.
- He's 177cm.
- He's 177cm?
- He is?
I don't think you are.
Stand straight.
(Hitting)
(Darn it.)
Wait.
- You punk.
- Jae Suk.
You just wanted to do this.
- Jae Suk...
- It was 153cm.
- You just hit his head.
- You wanted to do this.
- Please smile.
- What?
I can't smile.
He must be less than 170cm.
- No, I am.
- You can just...
- You're 165cm, right?
- That's not true.
- I'm over 170cm.
- Just deny it quickly.
- Deny it.
- Okay. It's because I'm sick.
- Okay, he denied it.
- You denied it?
I'm really sick.
- I'm serious.
- If you were 171cm before,
you can't be taller than that now.
- I'm really sick today.
- I'm 171cm.
- Se Chan, you're the last one.
- Me?
I'll admit it no matter what.
"There's a young woman
who frequents..."
"the new place
I recently moved into."
Why that...
- Just admit it!
- What did he say?
Just admit it!
(During their new year
fortune reading,)
(Se Chan's type of woman
was revealed.)
- Stop it.
- There is.
There is!
- He told me so.
- Hey.
- You said there is.
- Sae Ho.
Tell them what you told me.
Tell us about it.
- Gosh, I'm getting goosebumps.
- Well...
The question itself
got me goosebumps.
Why would you add
the description, "young?"
- Young woman?
- Admit it.
A woman can visit your place.
Tell me the limit of age
to call her young.
As long as she's younger than you.
Think about it.
If she's younger by a year,
that means she's young.
- That's right.
- She's younger than you.
After Se Chan moved
into the new place,
- I video called him.
- Right.
He wouldn't show me
the master bedroom.
- That's right.
- I asked him to show me his house.
But he didn't show me
the master bedroom.
You think there was a woman in there?
That's nonsense.
Who knows?
When we asked him
to show us his house,
he turned around,
and I saw that his place has a terrace.
- I saw...
- That's right.
someone hanging there.
- My gosh.
- Oh, come on.
- Hey.
- You're so...
- Because of him...
- I'm right.
- You saw it, right?
- Nothing works out because of him.
- The fingers?
- Her arms were shaking.
Those were a woman's fingernails.
So we said,
"Your terrace is really pretty."
- Your face is so red now.
- There's nothing to explain.
- Deny it, then.
- This part is very red.
- I deny it.
- Because he denied it,
- it makes me want to know more.
- He has a girlfriend.
- He does.
- It's so funny.
- He could admit it if there wasn't.
That's right. He has a girlfriend.
- So you had a girlfriend.
All right.
That was really intense.
Team Sae Ho wins seven points.
It's not easy to admit it.
Team So Min wins four points.
- Team Sae Ho wins.
- All right!
So Min should've admitted hers
in the beginning.
I would have admitted mine too if...
- They're the winning team.
- We are?
Decide 1st to 4th place
through rock-paper-scissors.
- All right. Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Yes!
- He won again.
- All right.
- I...
Starting with Sae Ho,
you get to steal two slots...
from their maps.
Two slots from their maps?
You can take two slots
from any one of them.
You can take one from your teammate.
- It's an individual match, right?
- It is.
- I want to take Haha's.
- Go ahead.
Take them right away.
If you look over there,
he removed Gangwon Province...
and Jeju Island. That means
he contemplated between the two.
I think it'd be fun...
- to take Suk Jin's.
- You should.
Take Haha's.
Take one from the guy
who is shorter than you.
I think it's either
Gangwon Province or Jeju Island.
Can't I do it on my own?
- He's a better host than you.
- He's better than you.
- He's a better host.
- Oh, right.
- You should listen to me.
- My apologies.
- You should listen to him.
- All right, then. I pick...
- Suk Jin's.
- Which one?
I'll take Jeongseon
of Gangwon Province.
- Jeongseon.
- Come on.
Okay.
Jeongseon? I wouldn't put it there
since it's my hometown.
- I think you did.
- Let me give you another chance.
I pick Jeongseon, Gangwon Province.
- Can I take it?
- I'll give you another chance.
- Another one?
- All right.
Then I'll take Jeongseon
of Gangwon Province.
Gangwon Province? Okay.
I gave you so many chances though.
All right. I'll take it now.
That's my hometown. Think about it.
- I got 8 ballots.
- There were 8 ballots?
(Sae Ho steals 8 ballots
from Suk Jin at once.)
That was so obvious.
I got eight ballots.
- That's amazing.
- You got eight ballots?
- Sae Ho takes eight ballots.
- All right.
- He took eight ballots?
- I thought otherwise.
- Why didn't you twist it?
- I didn't think you'd pick it.
- Suk Jin didn't add a twist.
- Next.
- You should pick one more.
- Then I'll lightly take...
- So Min's.
- All right. So Min's.
(Jeon So Min)
- You want to steal her heart?
- So Min.
- You live in Ilsan?
- Sae Ho, don't use this to...
So Min's parents live in Ilsan.
Ilsan. Gyeonggi Province.
I'll just pick it.
Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
Please think again.
- Is there something behind this?
- No.
I pick Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
- The way people think...
- All right.
I pick Seoul and Gyeonggi Province
above Chungcheong Province.
(Sae Ho doesn't get swayed and picks
Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.)
Did she put a lot here?
(10 ballots!)
(He steals all of So Min's ballots.)
- What was that?
- I'm sorry.
It's already
Cho Sae Ho's Running Man.
- Gosh, what is this?
- You took almost all the ballots.
- I...
- He already has 18 ballots.
This makes it no fun.
That's why I told you
to think again.
Sae Ho earned her ballots.
- What do we do?
- It's Cho Sae Ho's Running Man.
He took all my ballots.
I might be disliked by many.
(Sae Ho quickly becomes
unlikable by sweeping all ballots.)
How did he choose this?
- Who was in second place?
- Me.
- I'll take Jong Kook's.
- Okay.
Go for it.
- I'll take Gyeongsang Province.
- His hometown.
- Jong Kook's hometown.
His hometown is Hapcheon.
Rip it! I bet he divided
his ballots into different slots.
- There's none.
I wouldn't put them in my hometown.
But Suk Jin did.
- What?
- I put them in my hometown too.
- I know.
- Haha.
Go for Jeju Island.
- Jeju Island.
- I think Haha put it there.
- He must've put it there.
Because he likes Jeju Island.
He left it open
for the others to rip it.
- I knew it.
- That's quite a lot.
(She manages to steal 5 ballots.)
- She took 5 ballots.
- She took 5 ballots?
- Ji Hyo took 5 ballots.
- Who is in third place?
- Me!
- Can I pick one too?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
This is fun.
(Jae Suk's target is Sae Ho
who earned many ballots.)
- I'll pick Chungcheong Province.
- Chungcheong Province? Okay.
I have a good feeling about it.
- There's none.
I'm sorry.
(Sneaky Sae Ho avoided
getting his ballots taken.)
- Why are you...
- Let me take another one of his.
- I should take Sae Ho's too.
- Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
- Three.
- You divided them like this?
- Yes.
That's still a lot, Jae Suk.
- It is.
- That's a lot.
I bet Jae Suk...
- Eighteen ballots are a little...
- put all ten ballots together.
You should check his face
as you test each slot.
Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
It's in Gyeonggi Province?
Gangwon Province.
Chungcheong Province?
Your tone got a little lower.
Gyeongsang Province.
Jeolla Province.
Jeju Island.
I see. It's in Gyeongsang Province.
- Is it Gyeongsang Province?
- It is.
Then I should pick Chungcheong.
Can I pick it now?
- Yes.
- Is it Chungcheong Province?
Should I pick Chungcheong Province?
- I think it's there.
- It must be Chungcheong Province.
- Se Chan is good.
- I'll pick Chungcheong Province.
Oh, no.
- You earned one though.
- Jae Suk divided them.
Then...
That's so unlike Jae Suk.
- This time...
- He divided them.
It looks like he divided them.
- It could be Seoul and Gyeonggi.
- Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
- Seoul and Gyeonggi Province?
- It could be Jeju Island.
- I don't think so.
- You like Jeju Island?
- Of course he does.
I love Jeju Island.
Then I'll pick Jeju Island.
- They're clenching their fists.
- It is Jeju Island.
I'll pick Jeju Island.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Four ballots!
- I told you.
- That's a lot.
- He put a lot of them there.
- I placed four ballots there.
All right.
All of you earned extra ballots.
He got 18 ballots.
Let's move for the next mission.
- Okay.
Gosh, what is this?
Are we doing a race?
Here's the second mission.
It's called King of the Race.
You'll be divided into teams of two.
You'll assemble the mini cars
we used to play with...
when we were young.
- Mini cars are fun.
- I'm really good at it.
You'll race and decide the ranking.
You'll need to race two rounds,
and in the order of arrival,
we'll give you
40, 30, 20, and 10 points.
- That sounds fun.
- After racing two rounds,
you get to overhaul
for exactly two minutes.
Then you'll have a second round
and earn points.
- We get to overhaul too?
- We'll probably change batteries.
Right. Because if they race far...
It's like F1.
Depending on that,
the speed changes.
The full marks are 40 points
in each round.
We'll give you 40 points
for the designs.
- Designs?
Depending on how well
you decorate your mini car...
There are stickers too.
Those details...
The directors who used to play with
mini cars when they were young...
will give you points.
Starting with this mission,
the winner gets a special benefit.
You can either resign
or unify candidacies.
- Unify candidacies?
- Can we do that?
We can unify candidacies?
The winner of the race...
may force the candidate
of your choice...
to unify their candidacy with yours.
That person will only earn
extra ballots...
and be exempted from candidacy.
- That's a good thing, then.
- It is.
It's supporting other candidates.
- That's great.
- We should support others.
Do you not want to be the captain?
- It's because...
- Of course not.
- we need to attend meetings.
- It's troublesome.
Actually,
it'll be meaningful for you.
It'll be Cho Sae Ho's Running Man.
I know that, but I'm not
a regular on Running Man.
That way, you can become
a familiar guest.
- Hey, there's an open spot.
- Through this?
- We have an open spot.
- Oh, really?
- He likes it.
- We have an open spot.
You came to the show
without knowing that?
- Gosh.
- We have an open spot.
The fact that I'm here
as the sole guest...
- That's right!
- My gosh.
You must make your own path.
No, that's not the case.
- No, Sae Ho.
- He's saying no.
- That's not the case?
- He's in bad condition.
So you want to become the captain.
- What did you say?
- From Gangnam to Mok-dong.
Once a week.
- Despite your busy schedule,
- Hey.
- you'll attend the meeting?
- I don't get a day off.
- I'll help you become one.
- I don't get a single day off.
- You should take good care of him.
- Take care of Jae Suk.
- He should become the captain.
- Stop it.
- I'll make sure...
From lunch to a meeting.
- That'll be great.
- I'm too busy for that.
Sae Ho can make him the captain.
Before the mission starts,
we need to decide one thing.
The inner lane is more advantageous.
So we'll play Pirate Roulette
to decide who takes the inner lane.
The inner lane is more advantageous.
- It's a lot more advantageous.
- For sure.
But if you make your mini car well,
it can turn the corner well.
- Is that so?
- The motor matters a lot too.
The wheels matter too.
We divided you into teams
in advance.
The first team
is Jae Suk and Se Chan.
- We'll win for sure.
- That's not fair.
- Protruding mouth brothers.
- All right.
The second team
is Jong Kook and Haha.
Do you know how to make it?
They're like brothers.
I've made it before.
The third team
is Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
- What about me? What?
- It's okay.
What about me?
- What?
- The fourth team...
(Automatically,
So Min and Sae Ho form a team.)
- Hold her hands!
- I don't want him!
What is this?
- Is this a date?
- Take her home after this.
- Drive the mini car home.
- Why? What is this?
- What is this?
- Take her home.
What is this though?
- What is this?
- We're at a disadvantage.
Sae Ho likes it.
What's this?
Did you tell them to?
Why would I do that?
We're at a disadvantage.
Let's play the game
to determine your lanes.
Okay.
It'll pop out.
- Yes! You see?
- He killed it.
(The faster the pirate pops out,
the further their lanes will be.)
- We got this.
- Okay. Second lane is good enough.
It's good for us.
Gosh, they look so fancy.
We're supposed to assemble these?
I don't think we can.
Guys, we'll give you 30 minutes.
If you feel lost
while assembling them,
you can use one of your ballots
to ask for help.
- And we'll help you for a minute.
- Is that so?
Please sit separately
and start assembling.
- Get ready.
- We're in trouble.
You've never played with these, have you?
We will make it in no time.
Is it possible
to make it in 30 minutes?
I make it these days
because of Ji Ho.
My goodness.
Let's finish it in 20 minutes.
- I will work on the wheels.
- That's right.
I haven't seen a motor in a while.
We should be thorough
and make the ends smooth...
because any parts that stick out
create wind resistance.
Gosh.
I am sorry,
but do you have reading glasses?
- I will work on the wheels.
- What am I supposed to do?
(The instructions
make him complain.)
We need to work on the motor too.
- This is so much work.
- Seriously.
When I messed it up in my childhood,
- I broke everything and cried.
- I did the same.
I didn't cry, but I got annoyed.
Are you good at something like this?
Do men seem charming
if they can do something like this?
Of course.
Men who can assemble furniture
are charming.
Let's do this.
- You guys look affectionate.
- That's right.
- Hey, Sae Ho.
- They are so mischievous.
- Yes, Haha?
- Women find this trait charming.
- They are so mischievous.
- I will do my best.
They like it
when men build things with ease.
You will hurt your hands.
Don't do anything.
- Don't do anything.
- What are you guys doing?
"You will hurt your hands."
He is such a good actor.
(Giggling)
He has no interest in her.
He is ugly.
(They badmouth him
in a childish way.)
- We are so one-dimensional.
- He is ugly.
He was much cuter
when he was chubby.
I completed the wheels.
- Did you complete them already?
- You didn't complete them.
- Gosh.
- I am making them nervous.
I completed the wheels already.
Did you complete them already?
I completed the wheels.
We are putting in the motor now.
- Stop it.
- You are lying.
- What are you playing at?
- Why would we lie?
- For goodness' sake.
- Hey.
Unlike you guys, we are experts.
Here comes the motor.
- Ji Hyo, you are good.
- We need A8.
Why would you talk about every process?
For goodness' sake.
All right. The front wheels.
The rear wheels are ready.
(He assembles the parts
after the announcement.)
- Will you boast every time?
- Okay.
Gosh, we are doing well.
We are about to start the car.
- We get it. You are good at it.
- Vroom.
They are so loud.
- Seriously.
- Why would you brag so much?
You will place last anyway.
- All right.
- The car is ready to go.
We are fastening our seatbelts.
It's ready to go.
- Vroom.
- Don't be ridiculous.
I need what's behind you.
- All right.
- This is good.
- We need A4.
- Jae Suk.
- Did you say A4?
- It's incredible. Look at it.
It looks amazing.
It's for the points.
- It's incredible.
- Does it go?
Does it go?
- Put it down.
- Which one should we use?
- There it goes.
- Okay. This is great.
- Did you make it already?
- Sae Ho, be careful.
- You made it well.
- Be careful not to crash it.
When did you make it?
- It's so pretty.
- It is, right?
(A car by So Min, the designer,
and Sae Ho, the engineer)
We need to paint it.
It works.
Please change the wheels.
(Many of them switch the wheels
after putting in the motor.)
- They spin.
- Shall we switch the wheels?
(Many of them switch the wheels
after putting in the motor.)
Let's do that.
(They tune the mini car
for design points.)
Yes. A pink car.
Please wrap it up.
- Hold on. We need to add this.
- I didn't know.
Jae Suk,
the new wheels we put in...
don't spin.
- What?
- Jae Suk, these wheels don't spin.
What do you mean?
- Can't we use them?
- It must be because we used...
homemade wheels.
(The homemade wheels
have a crucial problem.)
They don't spin.
- Spin them like this.
- Let's ditch it.
- Okay.
- Let's ditch the top.
(They decide to ditch the top.)
- Jae Suk.
- We just need to be fast, right?
Jae Suk, let's put flowers...
on the top.
That's good. Okay.
- It's not very pretty.
- Simple is the best.
- Good.
- It's white.
This is our car.
Team Suk Jin and Ji Hyo
in Lane One,
please introduce the car.
The design...
represents Ji Hyo's car.
Ji Hyo is a pink princess,
so we made a pink car.
It's a very pretty pink car.
These wings have a function.
Please listen.
- Hey, listen.
- Okay.
These wings have a function.
They divide the wind
and set direction.
That way,
they make the car go faster.
The wings play a big role
in the Pink Car.
Yo!
This car is way above those cars.
Our car has various colors
and gold wheels.
These are 24K gold.
The name of this car is...
- Rainbow 401.
(Rainbow 401)
Rainbow 401.
Why did you add "401?"
It has various flavors.
We added 401...
- because 4 wheels will become 1.
- Okay.
- They will become 1 forever.
- Sae Ho.
- Okay.
So Min came up
with the overall design.
We focused on the design.
It looks like a festival...
because it will bring us
a private festival.
The name is...
Love...
In the Lane.
- Love in the Lane.
- Sae Ho suggested the name.
Yes. It's like
"Singin' in the Rain."
If you look here,
there are Sae Ho and me.
(94 percent for parts
and 98 percent for nuisance)
Are you guys dating?
Wouldn't the car be too heavy?
So Min, isn't the car too heavy?
It isn't heavy. Trust me.
- Jae Suk.
- Our car is...
- Simple Is the Best.
- Vroom.
- Show us.
They want to see it.
It isn't simple at all.
It's so crude-looking.
- It's so crude-looking.
- We focused on speed.
I am sorry, but isn't that a jegi?
- Vroom.
We switched the wheels...
and decided to focus on speed.
Simple Is the Best.
You removed the top.
In Round 1,
the cars will make 2 laps.
Start the car
and hold it over your lane.
- Standby.
- I think it will get caught.
- Start the car.
- Here we go.
Here we go.
Get ready.
(Lane 1: Suk Jin and Ji Hyo
Lane 2: Jong Kook and Haha)
(Lane 3: So Min and Sae Ho
Lane 4: Jae Suk and Se Chan)
- Get ready.
Jae Suk, your car
went over the starting line.
- Set,
- It went over the starting line.
- go.
- All right.
(The race begins.)
- Oh, no.
- That's good.
- Oh, yes. They are out.
- My goodness.
- Go.
- All right.
- Oh, no.
- That's good.
(Pink Car stops
as soon as the race begins.)
- Gosh.
- It stopped.
- Oh, no.
- That's good.
Oh, yes. They are out.
(Simple Is the Best
flies out while cornering.)
- Look at that.
- What happened?
(Se Chan puts the car
back on the lane.)
That's good.
Oh, yes. They are out.
- Let's go.
- It's so fast.
Our car is so fast.
- Okay.
- Our car is so fast.
- Look at that.
- It's so fast.
- Okay.
(Completing the 1st lap)
(The engineers become excited.)
- It's on another level.
- It's so fast.
(Pink Car is still moving slowly.)
- Look at this.
- What happened?
- It's so fast.
- Okay.
- It's on another level.
- It's so fast.
- Okay.
(The leading car is ahead
by one lap.)
(3rd place, 1st place)
- We are ahead by one lap.
- Why is their car so fast?
- Hey.
- The motor is malfunctioning.
(The race continues.)
- We are ahead by one lap.
- Why is their car so fast?
- It's so fast.
- Look at our car.
- We are ahead by 1 lap.
- We are on our 3rd lap.
- We are in 2nd place.
- We completed the 2 laps.
- We are ahead by 1 lap.
- We are on our 3rd lap.
- We are in 2nd place.
- We completed the 2 laps.
What happened?
Why did our car fly out?
(1st place, Rainbow 401)
(2nd place, Love in the Lane)
- No?
- Simple Is the Best.
I will announce
the result of Round One.
- Team Jong Kook placed first.
- Okay. That's us.
Team So Min placed 2nd
and Team Jae Suk placed 3rd.
I mean...
What are you looking at?
I wasn't looking at you.
You will have two minutes
to make repairs.
- Let's go.
- What should we do?
- That was incredible.
- Let's add something big.
We need to remove the bottom.
Let's hurry up.
- Let's hurry up.
- This is...
- Our car is really fast.
(Laughing)
It's on another level.
- Rainbow 401.
Throw it on the track.
Let's try it one more time.
(Team Jae Suk has a test drive
instead of making repairs.)
- It flew off here, right?
- That was incredible.
(It completes a lap this time.)
What?
It flew off here. This is good.
This is so much fun.
- It's so fast.
- All right.
It's Lane Four.
Why did you put your hand
on Lane Three?
Ji Hyo, let's use
the homemade parts.
- So those are homemade parts.
- Yes.
That's right.
Move out of the way, So Min.
Hold it like this.
(Se Chan steals batteries.)
Our car is incredible.
I brought all the batteries.
What are you doing?
Why are you changing batteries
after each lap?
Simple Is...
- What was the name?
- Simple Is the Best.
Simple Is the Best or Vroom...
will teach you a lesson.
Jae Suk, let's go.
- Hey.
- Let's do this.
- Love in the Lane is good too.
- Love in the Lane.
- Yes. I am serious.
- I agree. It's a formidable car.
This time, you will make three laps.
- Three laps.
Jae Suk, don't we need to change
the batteries?
- Let's change the batteries.
- Hey.
It won't do if the car sways.
- It's okay.
- It can't stand the Mach speed.
Best of... This car can't...
- Simple of the Best.
- Get ready.
- "Simple of the Best?"
All right. Let's go.
- What are you saying?
- I don't know the name.
- Let's go.
- Excuse me.
- Get ready.
- Please hold on.
Get ready.
Let's go.
- Set...
- Your hand is shaking.
(Lane 1: Suk Jin and Ji Hyo
Lane 2: Jong Kook and Haha)
Go.
It's going well.
- Okay.
- It's going well.
(The cars are off to a good start.)
- Okay.
- It's going well.
- That's it.
- Our car is fast, Jae Suk.
- Our car is fast.
- That's it.
It's going well.
- Our car is fast, Jae Suk.
- Our car is fast.
- That's it.
- It's okay.
- That's good.
- Our car is leading.
(Pink Car comes to a halt
once more.)
What's wrong with it?
- Our car is fast.
- That's it.
- It's okay.
- That's good.
- Our car is leading.
- Simple Is the Best. Okay.
- Simple Is the Best.
- That's good.
- It's okay.
- Our car is leading.
- That's good.
- It's okay.
- Our car is leading.
Simple Is the Best. Okay.
(Rainbow 401 and Simple Is the Best
are competing.)
- Our car is leading.
- It's okay.
Simple Is the Best. Okay.
- What was that?
- No!
(At that moment)
- Simple Is the Best. Okay.
- Simple Is the Best.
- What was that?
- No!
- What?
- Simple Is the Best.
(A crash follows an overturn.)
(Rainbow 401 crashes
into Love in the Lane.)
It entered a different lane.
(Team Jae Suk seizes the chance.)
- Simple Is the Best. Okay.
- Simple Is the Best.
(Racing)
- That's good.
- Okay.
(1st place, Simple Is the Best
2nd place, Love in the Lane)
It entered a different lane.
Why is it so weak?
(Pink Car is dead.)
(3rd place, Rainbow 401
4th place, Pink Car)
Team Jae Suk placed first.
Okay.
What happened?
The car flipped over.
(Simple Is the Best finishes!)
Team Sae Ho placed second.
- We placed 2nd.
- Team Haha placed 3rd.
- We placed first, right?
- Yes.
(1st place, Simple Is the Best)
(2nd place, Love in the Lane)
(3rd place, Rainbow 401)
Simple Is the Best.
Okay.
We placed second.
The batteries keep falling off.
You should have built it
to withstand the Mach speed.
Do you want some batteries?
Why do the batteries fall off
during the race?
Gosh, Rainbow 401.
Why did you go easy on them,
you fool?
The result is out.
You combine the points, right?
- Yes.
- That's good.
That's too bad.
In first place are
So Min and Sae Ho.
(1st place, So Min and Sae Ho)
In second place are
Jong Kook and Haha.
- Okay. Good job.
- Good job, Rainbow 401.
Rainbow 401, good job.
As you did before,
you will steal ballots
from someone else's slots.
Like I said before,
one member of the winning team can resign.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Resign?
- Yes.
(One member can resign.)
It's bad news for Sae Ho.
- Do you want to be one?
- It's bad news to you.
If you resign
and choose someone to support,
that member will receive votes.
(That member
will begin with 3 votes.)
You have a lot of ballots,
so I will resign.
You have 18 ballots.
I do, but you...
- I will resign.
- No.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
That's right.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Yes.
The winner will resign.
- The winner will resign.
- Yes.
I might not want to resign.
I want to resign.
(Candidate Jeon wants to resign,
but Candidate Cho doesn't want to.)
Do what you want then.
I will play rock.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
(The winner will resign right away.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Why did So Min lose?)
Okay! Wait, I messed up.
I messed up.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Okay! Wait, I messed up.)
- Candidate Cho resigned.
- No.
- Are you a fool?
- What are you doing?
- It wasn't like that.
Wasn't I supposed to lose?
You should have played paper.
- All right, So Min.
- Wasn't I supposed to lose?
Sae Ho resigned.
- What?
- It was an unwanted resignation.
I know.
You really wanted to do it, right?
Sae Ho resigned.
You can vote,
but other people can't vote for you.
The candidate you support...
will begin with three votes.
In that case,
I can still have some fun.
Some members
wouldn't welcome the unification.
I am reminded of those
who didn't welcome me warmly...
when I came here as a guest.
- It's understandable.
- I welcomed you.
Through meetings,
he or she can build solidify.
- You mean "Solidarity."
- Solidarity.
- You said "Solidify."
- "Solidify?"
- Hold on.
- He said "Solidify."
- That's a bit...
- You are laughing.
- Seriously.
It seems like
you are looking down on me.
- Support him.
- Are you looking down on me?
- I just found it funny.
- That's the undertone.
- I will support one member.
- Okay.
I was displeased last night...
- because...
- Last night?
Yes.
I couldn't help but be displeased.
I wanted to sleep well
for the shoot.
"You are joining the shoot
tomorrow."
- "I don't want you to come."
- My goodness.
What kind of a man says that?
So I will support Yoo Jae Suk.
(So I will support Yoo Jae Suk.)
Congratulations.
It's a good reason.
The first promise
of unifying candidacies surfaced.
(Candidate Cho Sae Ho resigns.)
- It's a good reason.
- He always tells me,
"You need to have affection
for the show you are on."
By joining the meeting once a week,
he can aim to bring
the second heyday to the show.
Jae Suk and Sae Ho
unified candidacies.
Jae Suk, you will begin
with three votes.
(Candidate Yoo secured 3 votes.)
- Gangwon Province?
- Jeju Island?
Gyeonggi Province.
(Team So Min and Team Jong Kook
acquire ballots in others' slots.)
Since Ji Hyo placed first,
she can unify candidacies.
Which candidate will you support
before you resign?
You can resign.
I will support Haha.
(Candidate Song supports
Candidate Haha.)
- You will support Haha.
- Yes.
- Good job.
- Good job, Ji Hyo.
- It could be Haha's Running Man.
- Nice.
It's your last chance
to steal the ballots.
Please hold it up.
- Not many ballots remain.
- I have five ballots left.
- Five ballots.
- Ji Hyo has many ballots left.
Does she have many ballots left?
(Ji Hyo still has 10 ballots.)
Ji Hyo isn't the type to think much.
She is simple.
She probably chose
the places she lives in.
- Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
- Ilsan and Seoul.
It's not like that.
I will take
Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
- Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
- Okay.
(Seoul and Gyeonggi Province)
(9 ballots)
Jae Suk is a genius.
He is really good.
He stole nine ballots.
Where is the remaining ballot?
He knows Ji Hyo so well.
- All right.
- You put them in one place.
Third place, Jong Kook.
Sae Ho, hold up the map.
- Okay.
- Do it nicely.
- Here you go.
- Okay.
Hold it up nicely.
There you go.
Someone took
Seoul and Gyeonggi Province.
Many people around you
are from Gyeongsang Province.
What?
(Slapping)
- What?
- What was that?
Many people around you
are from Gyeongsang Province.
- What?
- What was that?
- Hey.
- So Min.
- What was that?
- Hey.
- She slapped his head.
- Why did you laugh so loud?
- What was that?
- I...
That came out of nowhere.
- What was that?
Seriously.
Why did you do that?
I think she likes him.
Doesn't she like him?
- Right?
- It was so strange.
There must be a reason.
Seriously. Are you a lunatic?
- Sae Ho is happy.
- What was that?
- Doesn't she like him?
- That came out of nowhere.
- You know,
- She likes him. She slapped hard.
she made my heart flutter a bit.
- She made my heart flutter a bit.
- Right.
Do you know what So Min said to me?
She said, "Jae Suk, look."
"Isn't the back of his head
perfect for slapping?"
I didn't think much of it,
but she suddenly slapped him.
Why did you do that?
I was going to act like you did it,
but I failed because you laughed.
It would have been impossible
for me to slap him.
I don't feel bad about it,
so there is no problem.
I get that,
but I think she likes you.
It felt like she was trying
to get me more screen time.
It made my heart flutter.
Did you take off Gangwon Province...
and Seoul and Gyeonggi Province?
- Of course I didn't.
- I see.
- You have friends on Jeju Island.
- It's such a funny incident.
- I have friends on Jeju Island.
- Why did she slap him?
It's so funny
that she couldn't hold back.
It's a bit strange.
Okay. There we go.
There were five ballots
in Gyeongsang Province. Okay.
- Fourth place comes next.
- Me.
Jae Suk is
the only one who is left.
- That's right.
- Look him in the eye.
His wife is
from Jeolla Province, right?
- I will take Jeolla Province.
- Jeolla Province.
- Yes.
- Will there be ballots?
One ballot.
- That's too bad.
- They are in other provinces.
- He used...
- He spread out the ballots.
- a cheeky method.
- I wanted four ballots.
Thus, the ballot distribution is over.
I will reveal how many ballots
each member has.
If So Min becomes the captain,
the producer won't be happy.
- It will be tiring.
- She will be a lot of work.
Jae Suk has 16 ballots.
Suk Jin has two ballots.
Jong Kook has ten ballots.
Haha has two ballots.
Ji Hyo has five ballots.
- Don't I have more than 10 ballots?
- Se Chan has 5 ballots.
- I used them earlier.
- Yes.
Sae Ho has 22 ballots.
So Min has zero ballots.
Sae Ho.
Does So Min have zero ballots?
Please talk among yourselves
to create a consensus.
So Min suits the position the most.
- She does.
- She likes doing such things.
- Please listen.
- She likes coming up with plans.
I don't need to be the captain.
And think about the votes
the members have.
Haha and Jae Suk already have
three votes each.
So Min is the closest
to the staff members.
If So Min becomes the captain,
- things could get a bit annoying.
- That's right.
So Min would contribute
her various ideas.
When I watch the show,
I sometimes think about...
how Se Chan's Running Man would be.
That's a good idea.
Se Chan suits the position.
He would like it.
- If I become the captain...
- He would do well.
- He is a good worker.
- Things will become very annoying.
- If he becomes the captain,
- I will make sure it happens.
the penalties will be intense.
- I will make them intense.
- He has good ideas.
We have a former host
of "Star Golden Bell."
- Let's go retro.
- I recommend Suk Jin.
- Me too.
- As the oldest member,
- But I...
he persevered without a complaint
for 12 years.
Did you forget about how he tried
to quit in the beginning?
- Thus...
- My love for the show...
isn't that great.
How could you say that
when the fans are watching?
It's just that your love
for the show is much greater.
What is this? Are you still waiting
for a chance to quit?
- Here is the thing.
- I am not qualified...
to be the captain.
If it weren't for the requirement
to attend the weekly meeting,
Suk Jin would have really wanted
to be the captain.
- I am not qualified.
- Suk Jin has good ideas.
I don't have any ideas.
- Also, Suk Jin is a gourmet.
- That's right.
- He is picky.
- Yes.
How about this?
Haha could show us
which show he likes better...
between "How Do You Play?"
and Running Man...
- by becoming the captain.
- I gave my answer already.
- He should become the captain.
- I said...
that I like Running Man better.
- Really?
- Why don't you show us?
I want to see him pour his love
into Running Man.
- Haha's Running Man sounds nice.
- No.
I am a lacking man.
I personally think...
it would be nice to make Jae Suk
attend the meetings.
- That isn't a bad idea.
Yoo Jae Suk's Running Man
sounds the most appropriate.
If Jae Suk goes to Mok-dong
every week,
people at the TV station
will be energized.
I am disappointed in you guys.
Why is no one bringing up Jong Kook?
- Come on.
- There is a reason.
I am afraid he will throw a fit
during the meetings.
- I would definitely do that.
- Right?
(The political thug
threatens to throw a fit.)
So you don't want people
to vote for you.
To be honest,
seeing the members
brainstorm ideas...
makes me a bit jealous.
- Why? We do it together.
- You...
Yes. You brainstorm ideas together.
- When you are together...
- We are like a family.
- Yes. It's so nice.
- Thank you for coming today,
but I feel uncomfortable
that you keep saying such things.
- What did I do?
- My goodness.
It's not like I asked you
to let me join the show.
I am well aware of my position.
- I feel a bit uncomfortable.
- Can't I gather up my courage?
I will hand out your ballots.
You know where to go, right?
- Yes.
- Are we voting right now?
So Min.
Who should be the captain?
- Who should it be?
- Please make a wise decision.
- Can I ask?
- When it comes to meetings...
- It's an actual vote.
- So Min doesn't want to do it.
Of course not.
- That's surprising.
- The captain is...
- This is really hard.
- That's too much pressure.
The captain from Yongsan
who's the last in the Hierarchy.
- That sounds so cool.
- Jeon So Min.
- Gosh, So Min.
- Move out of the way.
- That's beautiful.
- I'm the captain.
- I don't want to attend meetings.
- But...
I hurt my leg, so I can't go around.
If I become the captain,
I'll send someone
who voted for me to the meeting instead.
- Because I'm the captain.
- Can he do that?
No, you can't do that.
I'll vote for Suk Jin.
That's not the attitude...
- No, I mean...
- You can't do that.
You can't become the captain
with that attitude.
Who should I vote for?
I have no idea.
- I bet I'll get a lot of votes.
- Darn it.
Seriously, I can't do this.
- Hey, I have no time.
- I don't like being a leader.
I don't have a day off.
- Suk Jin sounds upset.
- Why are you upset?
- Suk Jin is...
- You guys are framing me.
My gosh.
He says he never gets upset,
but why...
"I don't have a day off."
He's sulky.
Go ahead and vote for me.
- Here.
- All right.
- We don't know who will win.
- We don't know.
Let me count the votes.
The winner will be...
the captain for the next four weeks.
- That sounds amazing.
- He gets to decide what to eat.
And he should attend meetings.
- Attend meetings.
- Four times.
(The captain should attend
meetings of the production crew.)
Let me start counting the votes.
Two for Jong Kook, two for Haha,
two for Se Chan,
and ten for So Min.
So Min got ten votes?
(Jae Suk gave
his 10 votes to Candidate Jeon.)
Three for Suk Jin,
and two for Haha.
(Ji Hyo voted
for Haha and Suk Jin.)
I bet it was Se Chan.
- No, it's not me.
- Three and two.
(Pretending to be innocent)
- You had five votes.
- No. You'll see.
One for Jae Suk, Suk Jin,
Jong Kook, Haha, and So Min.
(Se Chan gave one vote
to each except himself.)
One for each.
- We don't know the result yet.
- Right.
- This is so thrilling.
- I'm so nervous.
(The votes counted are 41.9 percent,
but they have no idea who will win.)
Ten votes for Haha.
- What?
- Okay.
(10 votes for Haha)
What's that?
- It must be Jong Kook.
- What?
- It's Jong Kook.
- No.
Two votes for Haha.
- Haha got...
- What?
Haha has won...
Are you counting the votes?
Haha's Running Man?
One for Suk Jin and one for So Min.
We don't know who will win.
Haha might win.
Has Haha gotten the most votes?
It's up to Sae Ho after all.
This is Sae Ho's decision.
One for Jae Suk,
one for Jong Kook, one for Haha,
one for Se Chan, one for So Min,
and 17 for Suk Jin.
One for Se Chan, one for So Min,
(17 votes for Ji Suk Jin)
(What?)
(Cho Sae Ho)
I just like him so much.
- I mean...
- It's nice.
It's settled.
- Well done.
- I like him a lot.
It can't be helped.
I just like Suk Jin a lot.
- This week...
- This is a penalty.
I'll get a henna tattoo this week.
- You...
- This is a penalty.
No, it's not a penalty. You are...
- my captain forever.
- Sure.
He just did it for Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Please accept my heart.
- Okay.
All right.
You also got the three votes
during the unification.
(The 3 votes
from the unification are left.)
- Right. There are more votes.
- That's right.
- Haha won.
- It must be Haha.
Haha got three votes,
- and Jae Suk got another 3 votes.
- Right, 3 votes.
- Three votes each.
- And there were...
- I had ten votes.
- ten votes.
- Because of them...
- We don't know it yet.
We have no idea.
The winner was decided
by only one vote.
- What?
- It must be Haha.
- It should be Haha.
- What do I do?
- One vote?
- One got 22 votes...
while the other got 21 votes.
- Who is it?
- Are they 21 and 22 votes?
I don't think it's Suk Jin.
The captain...
who won 22 votes is...
(The captain who will lead
Running Man for 4 weeks is...)
Congratulations.
Ji Suk Jin.
(Ji Suk Jin is elected
with 22 votes.)
Why did you make me anticipate it?
Haha got 21 votes.
All right. Captain Ji.
We should toss him into the air.
If you gave me only 15 votes...
Why did you do that?
- I told you.
- You're the captain of Running Man.
- Suk Jin.
- This is obviously a penalty.
Why is it a penalty?
I just like you so much.
Ji Suk Jin's Running Man.
You know what?
I'll tell you about
a few good restaurants.
Pick our lunch from there.
(Eye contact)
- Well... Today.
- You're a great man.
- Suk Jin is my role model.
- This is crazy.
Just take off the microphone
and run away.
With Captain Ji,
we will work hard for the next four weeks.
Congratulations. Don't stop.
- Captain Ji!
- Ji Suk Jin's Running Man!
Ji Suk Jin's...
- Running Man!
- Thank you.
- I should enjoy this.
(It is like a movie.)
(The two youths meet again.)
(Jin Ji Hee and Cha Jun Hwan)
(Hello.)
(They have to be the captains...)
(and lead the old team members.)
(Blind and deaf)
(The old fossils are
throwing tantrums.)
(Embarrassed)
(Someone shows up at the moment.)
(The ultimate boss)
(How dare you talk back to me?)
(Spending some time
with the members of Running Man...)
(they learn the bitters of life
from experience.)
This is how life is.
You are learning about life here.
(Do you know who he is?)
(He's figure skater Cha Jun Hwan.)
(Sorry.)
(Whoever wants to be a captain...)
(must endure the weight
of old fossils.)
- I'm here.
- Are you here?
(Because This Is
My First Time to Be a Captain)