(Last week)
(You have spiritual power.)
(The members had their fortunes
for 2022 read last week.)
(The fortune-teller suddenly found
So Min's spiritual power.)
If you hadn't become an actress...
(She is an up-and-coming
fortune-teller.)
(She is blessed
with a special ability.)
(So she opened
a small fortune-telling house.)
(Comedian Yoo Jae Suk)
Excuse me. Is this the place
where I can meet...
the fortune-teller Jeon So Bal...
who sees through everything?
- Forehead Fortune-teller
(Top Secret Revealed,
Forehead Fortune-teller)
(Forehead Fortune-teller)
(The unlicensed fortune-teller's
first client shows up.)
We're like Mabbaki.
Isn't this Mabbaki?
(The fortune-teller is excited
to see the big-time client.)
She's good.
Let's go.
- Forehead Fortune-teller
My goodness.
Aren't you the girl who seeks
revenge in "Show Window"?
Hey.
You're supposed to carry him
on your back.
Oh, dear.
Hey.
- That was too hard.
- You hit him really hard.
I heard the cracking sound.
- Gosh.
- Does it hurt?
How does it stick?
Did you not hear
the sound of a breaking gourd?
- Hey.
- It was loud.
Hey.
(She shows her fake supernatural
power using double-sided tape.)
All right. This is... I see.
(You live up to your name!)
You live up to your name!
- That's too soon.
- It's not over yet.
- You should wait.
- Really?
You live up to your name!
You're the best MC in Korea.
- Korea's... I'm nervous.
- Korea's best MC.
- The best entertainer.
- Let me try it again.
It's okay, So Min.
You should enjoy this.
You seemed really good
in the drama, "Show Window".
He's the best entertainer.
Okay.
You are Korea's best entertainer
who lives up to his name.
- The master of variety shows.
The pride of Korea and Running Man.
Korea's friend.
Korea's forever best friend.
Yoo Positive.
Yoo Jae Suk.
I've missed you.
I see.
(The nation's beloved MC,
Yoo Jae Suk's first talk show)
That's right. I'm Yoo Positive.
(I'm Yoo Positive.)
- Yoo Positive.
- He's back.
- I'm back.
I'm Yoo Recovery.
Welcome back.
I can tell...
that you got it.
Pardon? What did I get?
The booster shot.
- What?
- The booster shot.
- How did you know?
- My goodness.
(How did you know
that I got the booster shot?)
- I know everything.
- The booster shot?
- I know it.
- How did you know?
- How did you know that?
- And...
you had a chicken breast sandwich
when you were home.
- How did you know?
- How did you know? Is that true?
Well... Your family...
- who lives with you...
- She called me every other day.
(She called me every other day.)
It's impossible not to know.
How dare you say such things
about the fortune-teller?
- Hey.
You know what?
- So Min actually studied psychics.
- Right.
Back in college.
She's interested in stuff like that.
- She reads people's palms.
- So she sometimes...
reads our writers' palms.
You know that, right?
- I have superficial knowledge.
- She does it on the side.
She's amazing.
I'm not sure if I can say this.
It's fake.
- She's a fake.
- You look much better now.
- Pardon?
- You look great.
Yes. I'm doing well.
What have you been up to?
Did you just get some rest?
- I'll make it short.
- Okay.
I got up early in the morning.
At around 6:30 a.m. or 7 a.m.
That's when I woke up.
And I had some friends
who were in self-quarantine.
- Your quarantine colleagues.
- Your colleagues.
Colleagues.
Your colleagues you could talk to.
They were like,
"Jae Suk, what are you doing?"
"Jae Suk, are you up yet?"
"You got up early."
"How are you doing?"
"I'm doing fine.
I feel great today."
"Have a nice day."
"I'll talk to you later."
I talked to them like this
and had breakfast.
Then it was about nine o'clock.
I watched "AM Plaza" every morning.
(He watched "AM Plaza" at 9 a.m.)
I watched "AM Plaza" to see
who the guests on the show were.
Then Sae Ho called me
at around 9:40 a.m.
- He did?
- "Jae Suk, what are you doing?"
So I talked to him on the phone.
- At around ten, Bong Sun called me.
- Bong Sun.
And So Min called me at around 12 p.m.
- So Min did?
- She called me.
So until around four
in the afternoon...
You were busy.
- I was very busy.
- That was a tight schedule.
Seriously, I made a lot of calls.
So I got a hoarse throat
at around four.
That sounds very tiring.
You should take
good care of your throat.
Seriously, I got a hoarse throat.
And he got like four calls on
the line while I was talking to him.
I'm serious. I was shocked.
- I found this funny.
- Were they collect calls?
"What are you doing, Jae Suk?"
"Well, I'm alone in my room again."
He was alone in his room.
- Like the movie, "Oldboy".
- "Oldboy".
- That's hilarious.
- Kyung Eun left...
- some food...
- She left food?
in front of my room.
- You just reached out your hand?
- In disposable containers.
Then I put on plastic gloves...
and sprayed some sanitizer.
- My gosh. It must've been tough.
- It wasn't easy.
- My family went through a lot.
- I guess so.
Then tell us
why you're here to see me.
Right.
- Already?
- I bet something's bothering him.
We don't have time.
Oh, right. I watched
the SBS Entertainment Awards.
I was really heartbroken.
It's not just about
winning an award.
Without me, the atmosphere
there was a little...
- Because you weren't there...
- It didn't feel right.
It felt like something was missing.
I should've been there
talking and everything.
The most fun part of the awards
ceremony was texting you.
- Right. That's what he did.
- We kept exchanging texts.
I thought Jong Kook and Ji Hyo
would win the Best Couple Award.
- Me too.
- That's what I expected.
- We presented the award.
- Right.
If they kissed,
they would've won the award.
They have to do it this year.
And we also want to win
the award this year.
- We need to plan a strategy.
- We will...
try to win the award this year.
- Which one?
- The Best Couple Award.
- Really?
- We will win the Best Couple Award.
Then we will have to kiss on TV.
- Seriously.
- I need to think about it.
- We have no choice.
- She wants to kiss.
- Then we will definitely win.
- Are you really a fortune-teller?
You seem too superficial
to be a fortune-teller.
But I told you about that.
You two don't make a cute couple.
- You think?
- It's not like...
- I like all couples.
- Right.
I have my likes and dislikes.
I'm not interested
in couples whom I don't want.
- You're not interested at all.
- Who do you think I should be with?
- What?
What do you think you're doing now?
You're supposed
to read his fortunes.
- All right.
- Have some charisma.
- You should ask about his concerns.
- About So Min...
(So Min's drama,
"Show Window" made a big hit.)
So Min's drama,
"Show Window" made a big hit.
- That's true.
- I told you.
I knew this would happen. I said
Jae Suk would do all the talking.
She was right about that.
- Hey. You know what?
- He can talk for a whole week.
I had nothing to do at home,
so I kept watching TV.
- Did you watch my drama?
- Sure. I watched "Show Window".
- So Min's acting was impressive.
- She's really good.
Right before you kissed
a guy in the storage,
- Song Yoon A found you.
- You watched it.
I was watching it with my
mother-in-law, so I rushed out.
(I was watching it with my
mother-in-law, so I rushed out.)
It's awkward to watch it alone
and to watch it with someone else.
You know what?
- It feels weird.
- I know.
It feels strange to watch it alone
and to watch it with someone else.
I can't watch it with my family.
Actually, I can't even
start watching it.
It feels like
I get caught doing something.
I feel somewhat guilty.
Oh, no.
I should watch it alone.
All right. What's your concern?
- Pardon?
- What's your concern?
The thing is,
I couldn't join you last week.
- So I didn't have my fortune read.
- Right.
Are you here
to have your fortune read?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes.
- Born on August 14, 1972.
- Your nose is all sweaty.
She's nervous. So Min,
- don't be nervous.
- Just do what you want to do.
- Be yourself.
- What's wrong?
The thing is,
I can't be absorbed
in the fortune-teller character.
You don't have to do anything.
Just be yourself.
It doesn't matter.
Just do what you want to do.
- All right.
- She seems solemn.
- The Yoos of Gangneung.
- Yes.
Your show size is 270mm.
That's right.
- Well...
- Is this Naver?
Is this Namu Wiki?
Your father was born in 1943,
and your mother was born in 1947.
Your father and mine are
of the same age.
- Are they?
- The year of the Sheep.
- That's right.
- We should make them friends.
(We should make them friends.)
Your fathers will be friends.
My father is shy, so he doesn't
take up with just anyone.
My father is ENFP.
I bet my father is an I.
Jae Suk, you're ISFJ, right?
- We're an I.
- I'm ISFP.
You're ISFP. I guess you're...
- the curious artist type.
- We're the same.
- I'll read your fortune then.
- All right.
Jae Suk,
you were born with a weak fortune.
- I was?
- It's weak.
You weren't born under a lucky star.
But you've overcome your fate
with your relentless effort.
- You're timid and distrustful.
- That's right.
Is it his mind that's weak?
- Something else?
- Or is it something else?
- What is it that's weak?
- I bet it's my mind.
- My mind is weak.
- His mind is weak.
(Jae Suk is weak.
What is it that's weak then?)
And his lower body is weak too.
(And his lower body is weak too.)
So he's weak all over.
You just see through him.
There you go again.
- She's unbelievable.
- She sees through him.
- Hey.
- Forehead Fortune-teller
Forehead Fortune-teller
What should I do to prove myself?
- Do you have anything to show?
- My goodness.
You can't show anything though.
You won't have more children.
- Not anymore?
- It's over.
Actually, that's what
Kyung Eun and I planned.
And those who were born
in the Year of the Rat...
will be caught in three years
of misfortune next year.
I think you drove away the bad luck
by catching COVID-19.
Your fortune changed for the better.
- Really?
- He overcame misfortune already?
- I did?
- So it's all over now.
He overcame it again
with his relentless effort?
Of course. And he is
destined to be a celebrity.
Your great fortune began last year.
- Me?
- Hey.
His great fortune started
20 years ago.
It's been a really long time.
- Will it be even greater?
- Jae Suk... Yes.
- Jae Suk maintains...
- Are you serious?
his great fortune
with his effort and hard work.
I guess that's what it is.
Next year, you will have trees.
They will make a big flame.
Trees mean work.
- Work?
- Yes. Trees mean work.
- Really?
- Jae Suk...
I'll have a lot of work to do
starting from January.
Are you starting a new show?
I'm starting something.
- That's unbelievable.
- That's what's happening.
And he's so lucky...
that he can break
the three years of misfortune.
Then it's not misfortune.
- So it's all about popularity.
- What?
We can't call it misfortune.
Will I break
the three years of misfortune?
He even changes his fate.
- I'll break off my misfortune.
- His lower body is weak,
- His lower body is weak.
- but he has this energy.
- He has a strong upper body.
- That's amazing.
- He has energy.
- He has a weak lower body...
and strong arms.
So he breaks off his misfortune.
I usually work out my upper body.
So he will break off his misfortune.
Since Jae Suk is perfect,
there are people
who want to disturb him.
- They are jealous of him.
- Are they his colleagues?
- His colleagues or strangers?
- That's possible.
- Someone in here?
(Who is jealous of Jae Suk...)
(when he can
even break off his bad luck?)
It might be an older comedian
who made his debut after you.
(An older comedian
who made his debut after Jae Suk)
There's Suk Jin.
Seok Sam?
- I'm not sure who it is.
- Myung Soo.
- Jun Ha.
- I don't know who it is.
- Myung Soo.
- You know what?
I know that Myung Soo talked
behind my back a few times.
- He does that even on TV.
- Right.
He does that even on TV.
He talked to a few producers
behind my back.
I actually heard about it.
- But it didn't bother you, did it?
- What?
- Not at all.
- Never.
I even called Myung Soo
and told him this.
"Why are you talking
behind my back?"
("Why are you talking
behind my back?")
- What did he say?
- "Who told you that?"
"Who said that?"
He asked, "Who said that?"
So I told him who it was.
"I heard this from him."
"That's true."
("That's true.")
He admitted that he talked
behind your back.
"That's true."
(Myung Soo was caught
feeling jealous of Jae Suk.)
You should be careful too.
I'm sorry. My apologies.
- Be careful.
- I did it only once.
Just be careful.
You two don't have good chemistry.
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
you two are like enemies.
- We are?
- Yes.
- The fate of these two?
- But we overcame it.
- Haha is...
I talked about this before.
He, of all people,
will always be there for me
no matter what.
- Of course.
- For my whole life.
- I will.
- Until he dies.
I can guarantee
that he's a loyal friend.
Thank you.
Your great fortune has begun.
I'm not sure if it's okay
to say this, but Haha is...
like a fetus in my belly.
(Haha is like a fetus in my belly.)
How many months pregnant are you?
When is your baby due?
Suk Jin is a toddler.
Yes. I hold his hand.
- But Haha is still in your belly.
- I wipe his nose.
That's right. He's in my belly.
I'm not even fertilized yet.
- You're not fertilized?
- I want to be fertilized.
I want to be fertilized
after Haha is born.
I'm not fertilized yet.
You found a new agency last year.
- What?
- That's unbelievable.
It's been over six months.
How did you know that?
You had movement
in your fortune last year,
- and it's the same for this year.
- Again?
I guess you're planning to move.
- Is that right?
- True.
Seriously?
- Yes.
- That's what your fortune says.
- Transfer?
- The thing is,
your new place will...
Hang on.
It's not like
I don't believe in you,
but this is
what I told you on the phone.
Excuse me.
Are you a journalist or what?
Well...
You can't just repeat what he said.
- What are you doing?
- You need something new.
I said Jae Suk has
the fate of a weak fire.
- You should avoid black clothes.
- I should?
- Black has the energy of water.
- He doesn't wear black.
You should avoid black
for your underwear or house.
- I rarely wear black.
- Right.
- Red is good for you.
- Why?
And yellow which symbolizes wealth.
- Yellow is good for you.
- I like yellow.
- He likes green and yellow.
- So I...
bought a yellow cardigan before.
You should wear
yellow underwear too.
But I don't wear underwear
in primary colors.
Why are you swinging the fan?
- Why would you do that?
- Excuse me.
- Ma'am.
- It's...
- It might upset him.
- When you choose your underwear...
- Don't point it at me.
- Your underwear...
- Stop it.
You should wear underwear
and socks in those colors.
It will give you good energy.
But I don't wear yellow underwear.
Do men wear
skin-colored underwear too?
I...
- Do you?
- Yes.
- I wear all kinds of colors.
- Why?
- Skin colors?
- I love underwear.
Do you wear thongs too?
- A thong.
- Some men wear a thong.
A thong? I don't wear it.
- He can't wear it.
- Even out of curiosity?
I once bought it though.
Some wear a thong...
- not to show their underpants.
- Some guys do.
I can't wear it though.
It would feel like
sitting on a tightrope all day.
(It would feel like
sitting on a tightrope all day.)
I mean, all day...
It would feel like...
sitting dangerously on a tightrope.
It would feel like
someone is poking me like this.
I would be shaky all day.
- Sitting on a tightrope?
- Yes. Sitting on a tightrope.
I don't like it.
This year, you will be a good match
with certain Chinese zodiac signs.
- Like what?
- Certain Chinese zodiac signs.
Jae Suk will be...
(Thinking carefully)
The Year of the Tiger.
(The Year of the Tiger)
- Tiger?
- And the Year of the Ox.
We were born
in the Year of the Tiger.
- We're Tigers.
- The Tiger and Ox go well with you.
- Tiger and...
- It's the Year of the Black Tiger.
This is the Year of the Black Tiger.
We are Black Tigers.
Growl!
Go away.
I mean, those who
will be born this year.
- This year?
- The newborn babies of this year.
- Tigers have different colors?
- What are you doing?
You guys are not the Black Tigers.
The coming year will be
the Year of the Black Tiger.
- You fool.
- The year 2022.
- I didn't know.
Watch your words.
This year,
Jae Suk,
you will meet someone important.
If you are nice to the person,
- you will make it big.
- Who is it?
Who is it?
Well...
The name has an "S" in it.
An "S"? Like So Min,
Se Chan, or Suk Jin.
And...
(And...)
Let me see.
- Yong...
- Yong?
Yong?
The person lives...
in Yongsan.
- You live in Yongsan.
- And you too.
Look at her.
She's a fraud.
Just get up.
You shouldn't listen to her.
- You're a fraud.
- We should kick her out.
- You're a fake.
- You...
- You don't have to pay.
- When I talked...
to So Min on the phone,
she was upset with you.
Because you moved to Yongsan,
- but you didn't even tell her.
- He didn't tell me.
- The thing is...
- I was really upset.
I'm not done moving my stuff.
But you know what?
There's a misunderstanding.
Some people think...
I like Se Chan.
Of course I do.
But it's not like
I have feelings for him.
- Of course not.
- Let me make things clear.
It's not like So Min
has feelings for Se Chan.
She just thinks he's a nice guy.
If Se Chan expresses his affection
and asks her out,
she's willing to go out with him.
- That's it.
- There's a possibility.
Right. It's possible.
"What are you doing on Sunday?"
- Right.
- Something like this.
- "Do you want to go for a walk?"
- Right.
("What are you doing?
Do you want to go for a walk?")
If you do that...
for about a couple of months,
So Min will think
about going out with you.
"Do you want to have some
gimbap at a convenience store?"
Something like that.
That sounds sentimental.
I have a lot of...
fellow comedians around me
including Se Chan.
So Min is a nice person.
So some of them could've asked me
about So Min.
- But...
- He means...
- But no one asked me about her.
- Me, Chang Hee,
Sae Ho, Se Hyeong, Byung Jae...
No one asks me about her.
That's surprising.
It really is.
The guys you mentioned
aren't my type. I don't like them.
- Sae Ho and Chang Hee...
- That's good.
Sae Ho doesn't like her either.
- I don't like him.
- I once thought...
about setting up So Min with Sae Ho.
I was going to set them up together.
Honestly, I was
surprised to see Sae Ho.
I've never seen him have
such a serious look on his face.
Sae Ho seemed so serious.
- But...
- He lost some weight.
I know a guy
who does leather crafting.
- A three-generation business.
- Leather crafting?
- That sounds great.
- Is he single?
He's single.
Is he single?
Of course he is.
- It's like...
- He has to be single.
- I mean...
- That's because of the drama.
- It's the drama.
- I see.
She's like that
because of her drama.
I'm sensitive about it.
That's what I've been
seeing and hearing lately.
You feel like it can happen to you.
Anyway...
Please make a conclusion.
- Right.
- A conclusion?
A conclusion of what?
Why don't you read his palm?
This is what I learned in college.
Your left palm shows...
the destiny that you were born with.
And the right one shows
what you have carved.
So I should compare them.
Jae Suk, you are...
- You have to compare the two.
- You were very sensitive.
He was born sensitive.
- But he's become not sensitive.
- He changed.
- Seriously?
- He tried to change himself.
Clench your fist.
- Does she want to see the bumps?
- Yes.
Hey, this is...
- This is what little kids do.
- I did it when I was little.
This is what
elementary school kids do.
No. I can tell how many
sons and daughters you have.
- Seriously?
- This is what little kids do.
Clench your fist.
- This is for little kids.
- Right. A son and a daughter.
- That's right.
- A son and a daughter.
- That's ridiculous.
- And...
you have good luck with money.
- This is interesting.
- What?
You have the lines
that popular people have.
- Really?
- I know what it is.
Those who have
two separate lines here...
are very popular
with the opposite sex.
He was asked out a lot
after he became famous.
No one asked him out
before he became famous?
Of course not.
So it's all about popularity.
Hey.
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
- How dare you...
- I'm serious.
A lot of people around me...
- liked him a lot.
- He was very popular.
There weren't a lot of people
who asked me out.
There were a lot. I know that.
They just had a secret crush on you.
- Really?
- That's probably the case for me.
- Who?
- Me.
People don't talk about it,
but they have a crush on me.
- On you?
- Yes.
No. He seemed very serious.
Can you have Sae Ho on our show?
We should invite him over.
I'm serious.
The fortune-teller opens up easily.
She talks about herself a lot.
- I...
- She's humane.
- She is tender-hearted.
She's easily hurt.
She's not strong-minded at all.
I'm tender-hearted.
- I know.
- I'm soft-hearted.
- What about me?
- You?
Let me take a look.
- Why would you have yours read?
- I'm curious.
Haha is a very sensitive person.
- Why? I wasn't sensitive before.
- You're such a sensitive person.
You've always been sensitive.
- Was I born this way?
- Yes.
- My parents fought very often.
- My, you'll meet so many women.
- Did you hear what she said?
- He was born to meet many women.
- She said you were born that way.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
- Get lost. Just get out of here.
- Listen.
- Just get out of here.
- You were meant to be a flirt.
- I'm happily married. Leave now.
- Let me explain.
- That's not what I meant.
- My gosh.
- I guess he hasn't changed.
- I said to leave.
- That's not what I meant.
- Stop it.
Anyway, I'm so happy.
I felt this way yesterday as well.
- It's so good to be on set again.
- It's fun, right?
This is where I belong.
- That's right.
- Of course.
I felt like a prisoner.
- We waited so long.
- It's so true.
- And honestly,
- Yes.
it feels as if the entrance
has changed.
- What do you mean by that?
- You feel like you should leave?
Exactly. I feel like I'm the guest.
"Goodbye."
- But still, Ms. Fortune-teller,
- Wait.
you should tell him the conclusion.
- Please tell me the conclusion.
- Right. Ouch.
I'll tell you the conclusion.
All right.
You seem so distracted somehow.
- She's all over the place.
- Now, here's the conclusion.
Jae Suk, reading your fortune...
- made me realize this.
- What is it?
Jae Suk, the pillar of Running Man,
is meant to have good luck
this year.
And that means that 2022 will be
a great year for Running Man.
For the sake of Running Man
that relies greatly on Jae Suk,
I pray...
Long live, Jae Suk!
- Thank you!
- Forehead Fortune-teller!
Thank you!
(Has Jae Suk's worry been solved?)
(The fortune-teller gets
the most excited when she's dancing.)
(Forehead Fortune-teller solved...)
(the pillar of Running Man
Jae Suk's worry.)
Let's go!
- Forehead Fortune-teller
(The fortune-teller was reported
for unlicensed practice right away.)
- That was good.
- Princess Aurora!
Jae Suk, I missed you.
This is not good enough.
- Today,
- Yes.
we're shooting the first episode
of 2022.
Now that Jae Suk had
his fortune read as well,
every member has had
their fortune read.
Okay.
(Last week, the cast members had
their fortune read.)
(Haha will have good luck
from 2022.)
(Haha will become extremely focused
this year.)
(It's good for entertainers
as they need acting abilities.)
It happens in 2022.
(Next up was Suk Jin.)
(He's like a piece of gold
that's frozen.)
(But his wife is there for him,
melting the frozen gold.)
(Without his wife,)
(he would've been arrested
while running a business.)
(Suk Jin will be very lucky
in 2022.)
(The general on the battlefield
finally found his horse and sword.)
(On the contrary, Jong Kook...)
(You were lucky until 2021.)
But unfortunately, in 2022...
(Jong Kook won't be as lucky as
he was in 2021.)
(Since you won't be so lucky,)
(you'll become very short-tempered.)
(I'll be good to you, Jong Kook.)
(He'll get a new business offer
in the new year.)
(But starting a new business won't
be good for him.)
(It might ruin the reputation
he's been building.)
All seven of you had
your fortune read.
So you should pay for the service.
The total fee for all 7 of you is
7,000 dollars.
- Seven thousand dollars?
- What? Are you serious?
- That's too expensive.
- I think that's too expensive.
We prepared today's race
to start the new year off right.
It's Pay Fortune-teller's Fee Race.
You have to pay the fee by 3 p.m.
You will work together
to make money...
and pay the fee by 3 p.m.
If you pay the full amount,
none of you will get a penalty.
- Oh, my.
- That's good.
- Let's work together.
- We've got this.
- Of course.
- We can do this.
- Let's work it out.
- We've got this.
- We can pay it all.
- We can do anything together.
- Absolutely.
The less you pay,
the more of you will get a penalty.
- Okay.
- Got it.
There are several ways
to pay the fee.
In the place upstairs
you will go to later,
you can complete a mission
or finish labor tasks.
You can try the mission
up to ten times.
(Complete a mission in 10 attempts
or finish labor tasks)
At the end of the shoot,
we'll use penalty balls
to pick the ones to get a penalty.
The number of your penalty balls
has been decided...
based on the scores
of your fortune for the new year.
The person with the highest score
who got 95 out of 100 points,
Haha will be the captain
of the team.
- He has no penalty balls for now.
- Captain Ha.
- I knew it.
- It's time for him to be one.
- He got 95 points?
But Haha said that he didn't believe
in fortune-telling.
- He said he didn't believe in it.
- How was it on "How Do You Play?"
Did it say that he'd be lucky
on "How Do You Play?" too?
We heard that he'd be very lucky
for the next ten years.
- Really? But he doesn't believe it.
- You all should be good to me.
- You don't believe it, right?
- For the next ten years.
- Jong Kook keeps saying...
- You don't believe it.
- that he doesn't believe it.
- He doesn't.
- Haha, you should have...
- He said that.
You should've released
your new song "Get" this year.
- It's "Gap".
- That's not the song title.
- Suk Jin, you're unbelievable.
- You should've released it...
- It's not "Get".
- this year.
- Suk Jin, it's "Gap", not "Get".
- I'm working on another song.
- Dynamic Duo.
Haha, you should play
your new song for me...
- before releasing it.
- Right.
Why didn't you play it in advance?
- Gosh, seriously.
- To be honest,
- I liked the song, but...
- I was quite shocked that day.
Everyone, zip it!
- Sadness and loneliness
- Haha.
I'll produce your next song.
- I'll think about it.
- I just can't believe him.
- Remake your song as we suggested.
- Right.
Mix it with "Sunny Day".
Haha, as today's team captain,
- you can cast a curse...
- My goodness.
on anyone you don't like
up to five times.
I can cast a curse?
(He can cast a curse...)
(on anyone he doesn't like.)
- I can cast a curse?
- They just teased him.
Can I curse a person five times
at once as soon as we begin?
Oh, no. Jong Kook is in trouble.
- He can cast a curse on any of us.
- You know who that is, right?
(You know who that is, right?)
I'm sure that that person knows.
- He always makes me uncomfortable.
- This is so funny.
- I wonder who that is.
- What?
- Who could that be?
- He doesn't know...
that he makes others uncomfortable.
- I wonder who that is.
- Curse him before we begin.
- Who could it be? I'm curious.
- It's not that I hate him.
- I'm just uncomfortable around him.
- Who could it be?
This is so unexpected.
- Who is he?
- Hey.
- I'm sorry, okay?
- He might be cursed.
I just hope things will work out
well for you.
The member who gets cursed
by Haha...
will get
additional ten penalty balls.
- Oh, gosh. That's so many.
- Ten penalty balls?
- For each time he curses someone?
- He has absolute power.
(They will get 10 penalty balls
each time they get cursed.)
However, there's a way
for the other members...
- to cast a curse.
- Really?
I'll explain it after we move
to the next location.
Got it.
The 2 people tied for 2nd place...
who got 90 points are...
Jae Suk and Se Chan.
(2nd place with 90 points:
Jae Suk, Se Chan)
- Five penalty balls?
- Yes.
Suk Jin came in fourth place...
with 85 points,
so he has 10 penalty balls.
The rest 3 were tied for 5th place...
with 80 points and will begin
with 15 penalty balls.
Fifteen penalty balls? Okay.
We'll gather upstairs again.
- Okay.
- Got it.
I'll cast all five curses
at the end.
(The members gathered again
after changing their clothes.)
- Had I had any gaps
- Let's cast some curses.
I'm ready to cast a curse.
- In my life
- That's good. I like you.
I would be so happy
- Good. Great job.
- Thank you.
Had I had any gaps
- Good job. Okay.
- In my life
I won't curse you two. Sit down.
- Good. Great job.
- What is this?
- That's the main camera.
- Which camera is this connected to?
- So Min.
- Which is the main camera?
Hey, come and sit down.
Don't block the camera.
- Move. You're blocking us.
- I'm so sick of it.
- Do you want to be cursed?
- Hey.
I told you to move.
You're blocking us, you brat.
You're going to get beaten up
by Ji Hyo if you keep doing that.
What is she doing?
(So Min won't give in.)
Haha, cast a curse on her.
(She's returning
while making a weird noise.)
(The childish frog gets motivated
as she's been told not to do it.)
You have to repay your debt now.
We never borrowed any money.
Why are you saying
that we owe you money?
Nothing is free in life, you know.
Suk Jin is an honorary employee.
- He should be exempt from it.
- Exactly.
I'm an employee.
- Why would you charge me?
- True. That's cool.
- Great. He reacted as he should.
- Yes, he did.
- That's so cool.
- Doesn't he get paychecks?
- I'll get my paycheck soon.
- He should be paid.
Give him just ten R coins.
- We'll pay you with R coins.
- Great.
Anyway, you have to pay off
7,000 dollars.
- Some of you may get a penalty.
- I see.
You'll get additional penalty balls
in only two situations.
- First, when Haha curses you.
- Yes.
Here's how the others cast a curse.
If you go downstairs,
you'll see a dartboard.
(There's a dartboard
to cast a curse downstairs.)
If you successfully hit the center,
you can curse a person.
But if you fail, you only end up
getting additional penalty balls.
(If they hit the center, they can
give anyone 10 penalty balls.)
- Here's the list of what to do.
- Okay.
- What is it?
- You can do work anytime you want.
But you have only ten chances
to try each mission.
- Why do we have to work?
- We should do it...
- to repay the money.
- We have two different lists.
- Let's check it out.
- We have a lot of options.
(Game Research Lab,
Contribution in Production Cost)
"Bobbling Basketball,
1,000 dollars."
"While one member keeps bouncing
on a gym ball under the hoop,"
"the other makes the ball bounce
on that person's head..."
- "and get through the hoop..." No.
- What?
- Next up is Pirate Roulette.
- If you just throw it...
"Every member sticks a knife twice."
"You succeed
if the pirate doesn't pop out."
"Singing".
"Set your target score
before singing."
"Sing the 1st verse and get a score
within a 1 point margin to pass."
- One point?
- One point more or less, right?
- Yes.
The most common score range is
from 80 to 89 points.
- "Immortal Chan Hee".
- "Chan Hee"?
"All the members must
stand together..."
"in the frame of Chan Hee's camera
within three seconds."
- We can do that.
- In the frame?
- I think that's possible.
- Of course, we can do it.
All right then. You can try those
missions only ten times.
Check the list of the works now.
What kind of works should we do?
Let's take a look.
- First up is Game Lab.
- I see.
We can get up to 500 dollars
from it.
"Come up with a fun game
using objects you can find."
"Play the game you created."
"The staff members will evaluate
the game."
"Based on the quality of the game,
you can get..."
- "up to 500 dollars."
- Up to 500 dollars? Okay.
- That sounds great.
- But it's up to them.
- I see. We have to...
- It won't be easy.
- create a game.
- We can make a game they'd like.
But he seems to let his mood
affect his decisions these days.
Let's not try that one.
We'll only get upset.
I bet they won't give us
a high score.
"Support Production Cost".
"Eat the chicken dish we have
for an indirect advertisement..."
"and describe the taste
with your faces and exclamations."
- I specialize in this.
- Let's try this one several times.
Can we have cooked rice with it?
I'm like an expert.
- Make faces and exclamations. Good.
- Yes.
There's also New Year's Card
on the list.
"Write New Year's cards
to the hard-working staff members."
- That sounds meaningful.
- We get 50 dollars for each card.
- I like that one too.
- "Feet Washing Ceremony".
"Get 100 dollars by washing
a member's feet."
"If you wash Se Chan's feet,
which must be hard,"
- "you get 200 dollars."
- Come on. It's worth 500 dollars.
We deserve to get more than that
for washing his feet.
You should pay at least 500 dollars.
We'll have to wear a protective suit
to wash Se Chan's feet.
- A protective suit?
- The smell will get on the clothes.
You may start trying anything
you want with some other members.
Let's think. What kind of game
could we make?
Shall we start with Pirate Roulette
to test our luck?
- Okay.
- Let's try Pirate Roulette.
- We'll bring you the toy.
- Let's do that.
- Let's play Pirate Roulette.
- Do two people play it?
We win if we all stick two knives,
and the pirate doesn't pop out.
- We have a chance to win.
- We've got this.
All right. Let's begin.
Okay.
Let's take turns
starting with Jae Suk.
If the pirate pops out,
- Yes.
- I'll cast a curse on that person.
- Good.
- Okay.
Are you ready?
- Of course.
- We're ready.
- Is it worth 500 dollars?
It's worth 500 dollars.
- I'll give you two knives each.
- Two knives?
- Okay.
- I didn't know you would go first.
- I'm done.
- You have one more knife.
You win if everyone sticks two,
and the pirate doesn't pop out.
- I put one in it.
- Okay.
- I'll stick one in it too.
- Well...
I'm sure we'll succeed
because Kwang Soo isn't here.
- Next.
- Who's next?
Are you done?
(Their 3rd attempt...)
- Great. You did it.
- Okay.
It's loose.
- Next up is the award winner.
- The Honorary Employee Award.
I'll show you how I won
the Honorary Employee Award.
Wait, Suk Jin. Are you confident?
- Then put it right below...
- Gosh. What was that?
(The honorary employee failed.)
Suk Jin.
- How could that happen?
- It popped out.
I can't believe you made it pop out.
- You're an honorary employee.
- Exactly.
He deserves to be cursed.
- He deserves a curse.
- You should curse him.
- I don't understand...
- Why did he...
- Let's try again.
- Gosh. I'm so upset.
- We failed too quickly.
- Some didn't even get to put it in.
We don't lose 500 dollars, right?
- No, but you lose one attempt.
- Let's try again.
- Why would you get so mad?
- Gosh, seriously.
- Hold on, everyone.
- You have only ten attempts.
- Ten attempts.
- Oh, really?
- We didn't know that.
- We'll start over. We didn't know.
- Oh, really?
(What? We didn't know that.)
- You failed on your first attempt.
- You should've told us...
- before we began.
- We didn't know.
- We really didn't know.
- You should've told us before.
- This is so unfair.
- We really didn't know.
Exactly. You should've told us.
- We didn't know about that rule.
- Right. We really didn't know.
I told you about the rule
four times.
- When did you tell us that?
- I didn't know.
(As they always do,)
(they forgot about the rule
as soon as they heard.)
(They were so distracted that they
barely continued shooting.)
Let us start over again.
- You should've told us.
- You didn't tell us.
- Trust me. We didn't know.
- I clearly told you...
- Give us some slack just this once.
Just this once.
I'm the honorary employee.
- Right. He's the honorary employee.
- How about Jae Suk...
kicks a jegi 20 times?
- Okay.
- We accept it.
- If he kicks it 20 times, okay?
- Okay.
- That's a promise.
- Who will do it?
- I'll kick it 20 times in a row.
- If he catches it, he can continue.
- Okay. Let me catch it only twice.
- If he catches it...
- Just twice.
- That's allowed...
- in the traditional game.
- You can kick it 20 times?
- Of course, I can.
- So if he catches it...
- I mean, if he succeeds...
- We'll get to start over again.
- If I kick it 20 times, okay?
- It'll be good for us.
- He can catch it.
- Jae Suk, make sure to succeed.
- Okay.
- You can do this.
(An extra attempt is on the line.)
(Could he be able to pull it off?)
- Okay.
- You can do this.
- One, two, three...
- He's good at it.
- Four, five...
- Six...
- Darn.
- I knew it.
- Jae Suk.
- Gosh.
- Five...
- Six... Darn.
(He couldn't kick it
any more than 6 times.)
- Come on, Jae Suk.
- He's so bad at playing games.
You did a great job
when you were practicing.
- Hang on. Why were you so tense?
- Were you nervous?
- Why were you tense again?
- Why would he be nervous?
- Why were you tense?
Even his lips are dried out.
Why did you get so nervous?
- What's wrong with him?
- Why do you always get nervous?
- What is your problem?
- Give me one more chance.
- No. You failed.
- Give me just one more chance.
- Try kicking it.
- Okay. How about he kicks it...
- twenty-five times?
- He's the honorary employee.
- Come on. Give me another chance.
- He just finished his quarantine.
- I'm back now.
- That's right.
- Right. Give him another chance.
- I'll try again.
- What was that?
- He sounds so bossy.
- Give him another chance.
- Let me try again.
- I'm the honorary employee.
- He sounds bossy.
- I couldn't even attend the awards.
- He's bossy only on variety shows.
- Only on variety shows.
- Okay.
- Twenty times.
- This is your last chance, okay?
- Sorry?
- I won't ask for any more chances.
- Jae Suk, make sure...
- I think I should...
- He's getting nervous.
- I should put this on.
- Just don't get nervous.
- Okay.
- Why are you intimidated?
- Just relax. Stay focused.
I just have to do
as well as I always do.
- Just do as you always do.
- Okay.
- Think that no one is watching you.
- Okay. I'll do that.
- You can kick it 20 times.
- Think that there's no camera.
- Think that you're just practicing.
- Okay.
- You're quarantining in your room.
- One, two, three...
(You're alone in your room.)
- You're quarantining in your room.
- One, two, three...
(Surprised)
- He said it was practice.
- You're quarantining in your room.
(His fear of playing games
came back.)
- He said it was practice.
- You failed.
No, he said it was practice.
- I told you to relax.
- He said it was practice.
- He didn't say he'd begin.
- I'll begin now.
- Catch it if you think it'll fall.
- He didn't say he'd begin.
- Now...
- I'm ready.
- Go.
- I'll begin now.
- Catch it if you can't kick it.
- Jae Suk, don't get nervous.
- He did well when practicing.
- You see...
- Don't pressure him. Move back.
You're getting so worked up.
Why couldn't you even catch it?
- Just catch it.
- I'll kick it 20 times.
- All right. You can do this...
- I'm ready. I'll begin.
- He'll begin now.
- This is so funny.
- Here we go.
- I don't think he can make it.
- One, two...
- I don't think he'll pull it off.
- three, four, five...
- Good.
- Great. You're doing well.
- six, seven...
(Catch it!)
- That's it.
- Catch it!
(He received it.)
Nine, ten...
- Catch it.
- Eleven... Gosh.
(He missed it.)
I told you to catch it!
Didn't I? I told you to catch it.
- What a shame.
- Darn it.
- Fail.
- Gosh, seriously.
That means what we did still counts.
- Cast a curse on him.
- Yes, you have nine attempts left.
I told him to catch it.
Listen, everyone.
I'll cast a curse...
- Let it slide just this once.
- on one of these two.
He's the one to blame.
I did nothing to deserve it.
- You acted up too, Jae Suk.
- He failed.
- You had your chance.
- He failed to kick it 20 times.
- Why did you say you could do it...
- No, I mean...
- in the first place?
- I thought I could do it.
- But I was wrong.
- So you were not sure.
Then should we play
rock-paper-scissors?
Staying at home would be better
than being treated this way.
- My gosh.
- You said you could do it.
I would rather chat with you
over the phone at home.
- Why did you say you could do it?
- He's right.
Hey, you said such kind words to me
during my quarantine.
- I know, but it ended.
- But you're back now.
- Why did you get nervous?
- Darn it.
Why do you get nervous
every time you play a game?
- Both of you...
- Yes.
I'll let you slide if you write
ten New Year's cards each.
- Let me do something else.
- I promise.
- Writing ten New Year's cards...
- That's too much work.
- Hurry up and start writing them.
- I'll do it.
We can write up to 100 cards, right?
- I'll write 10 of them.
- Each of you write 10 cards.
Good. Write ten cards.
- Are 10 cards worth 500 dollars?
- You must write...
the name of a staff member
on each card.
- Their names?
- Yes.
I'll write one to Chan Hee.
Then I'll write a card to Bo Pil.
"Bo Pil, don't live your life
like that."
- "Dear Chan Hee."
- The message...
"Bo Pil, I wish you..."
"Chan Hee, thanks to you,"
"a happy New Year."
"I look younger."
(Thank you. I wish you
a life full of happiness.)
"Thank you."
Here you go, Bo Pil.
Thank you.
(Remaining time: 2 hours and 55
minutes, Fee: 6,900 dollars)
It's okay.
I bet he doesn't know
ten staff members' names.
- Next... Hold on.
- Yes.
Jae Suk's handwriting is bad.
Hey, is it Kang Hyo Im?
(He's asking the name of the writer
who's been on the team for 7 years.)
He just asked me for your name.
- No, I didn't.
- He asked...
He asked if Hyo Im's family name was
Kang.
(He can't send the card
even if he wants to.)
(Meanwhile, the others are
practicing another mission.)
- No, that didn't work.
- It won't work.
- He can't aim it in that position.
- How about I don't move?
- Just make it bounce on my head.
- That's a good idea.
- Go ahead.
- You must keep bouncing on it.
- Oh, I see. He must keep moving.
- Hey.
- Let's try again.
- This is too difficult.
- No, not like that.
- Gosh, you punk.
Jong Kook.
- Throw it...
- He just wanted to hit you.
- and let him head the ball.
- Hey, did you...
- Did you hit me hard intentionally?
- No, it wasn't intentional.
- Go on. Try again.
- Okay.
- This is...
- Hit the back part...
No, it didn't work.
(He stood up
as he couldn't stand it anymore.)
That wasn't my intention.
Trust me. I'm not lying.
I didn't do it on purpose. I swear.
Didn't you just throw it to hit him?
- No, never.
- He threw it like this.
- That was not intentional? Really?
- It wasn't intentional.
- Let's give it a try.
- Se Chan, sit on it.
It was close.
- Jong Kook will shoot the ball.
- Watch me.
- I hope he'll make it.
- Wait.
Let's see how lucky the winner
of the Top Excellence Award can be.
Watch me.
- That's good.
- You should throw it like this.
- You almost succeeded.
- You should hit the right spot.
You're good at throwing the ball.
It's difficult.
- Great. That's how you should move.
- I see.
- Again.
- It's so difficult.
- Try to hit it to the back. Great.
- Great.
- That's good. You almost did it.
- That was great.
- Remember how you headed it.
- Hit it with your forehead.
- Where? Here?
- Right here.
- Good.
- I think they can pull it off.
It'd be better if I didn't...
I should just...
- Start.
- Head it with your forehead...
- They did it.
- Okay.
- Start.
- Head it with your forehead...
(The ball went into the hoop.)
- Okay.
- We did it!
- He said, "Start."
- He wasn't the player.
- He said it.
- He said, "Start."
It doesn't count because I said it?
- He's on our team.
- Why not?
- Why doesn't it count?
- He just finished his quarantine.
- He's on our team.
- Why doesn't it count?
- Why?
- What?
- You said it, right?
- Then...
- It doesn't count?
He'll kick a jegi 20 times.
- Okay.
- If he kicks it 20 times...
- Make it count if I succeed.
- But we made it.
- Kick it...
- Make it count if I succeed.
- If he kicks it 20 times.
- Okay.
- It counts if I kick it 20 times.
- Just relax.
- Okay.
No one is around you.
Last time, you did it
for another chance, but this time,
- we'll actually complete a mission.
- If you fail again,
you'll have to write
20 New Year's cards.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- You've got this.
- You can catch it.
- Don't worry. You can catch it.
Catch it if you can't receive it.
- Catch it.
- I think he'll succeed this time.
- Look how his legs are shaking.
- He did some practice.
(His legs are wobbly too.)
He did some practice.
He'll pull it off this time.
(After tidying up
the jegi carefully)
- One, two...
- I caught it.
- Good job. Well done.
- Jae Suk.
- Relax.
- You got better.
- I'm sorry, but Jae Suk,
- Just relax.
have you ever succeeded in
kicking it 20 times?
Yes, I have.
- You have?
- Of course, I have. I can do this.
- You've done it before, right?
- Of course.
One, two, three...
- Good. Four, five...
- Great. Keep going.
- You're doing great. Keep going.
- six, seven...
- Good.
- eight, nine...
- Catch it.
- Ten.
- Eleven, twelve.
- Yes. That's good.
- Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen.
- Keep going. That's great.
- Sixteen, seventeen.
- Eighteen.
- You'll make it.
(Will he succeed?)
- Eighteen.
- You did it.
- Nineteen.
- You're there.
(He manages 20.)
(An opportunity was obtained
through constant protesting...)
(and the jegi boomer
didn't let it go to waste.)
I did it!
I actually did it!
I did it.
(He powered through
his performance anxiety.)
- Nice.
- I did it.
I did it.
- Nice.
- You did it.
- I did it.
- You did it!
- Nicely done.
- I did it.
- You succeeded.
- You paid back 1,000 dollars.
We paid back 1,000 dollars.
I've never kicked it
20 times in a row before.
But...
- It's a first for me.
- Well,
you said "start"
at the perfect moment.
- Nice.
- At the right timing.
It was right before you began.
I can't believe
you managed to say "start."
I'm amazed.
We paid back 1,000 dollars.
- This is hilarious.
- What next? Some singing?
- Right.
- Yes, let's sing.
- Look.
- What do we need to do?
You'll have to sing
one of your favorite songs.
- So 99 points...
- Plus or minus a point.
- A score of 99 would be the best.
- No way.
The best option would be
a score of 85.
Let's sing one for a practice round.
We'll put it to the test.
- Which song should we sing?
- Hold on a second.
- We need to check the settings.
- How about "At Andong Station"?
- "At Andong Station"?
- Sounds good.
("At Andong Station" by Jin Sung,
popularized by Yoo San Seul)
This will be a test run.
- Here we go.
- Let's see how we do.
The train is leaving Andong Station.
Please get ready for departure.
Your support gave me the strength
to come out of quarantine.
Once again, I extend my gratitude.
The fact that
you're back to full health...
I wish the same
to all of you as well.
All right.
(Gone with the wind)
(Oh, gone)
(The wind whisked it away)
(Was it only an empty promise?)
(What an empty promise)
(Backup singer Big Nose
gets lost in the tune.)
At the entrance of Andong Station
(We promised to meet)
(That person)
(The one I love)
(The snow that fell all night)
(Not rain, but snow)
Now reaches my knees
(Check out the snow,
it's up to my knees)
(Are you not coming?)
(That must be the case)
(Or is something stopping you?)
No, that's not it
(Big Nose
is running out of ad-libs.)
Hurry over here!
(The song is now almost over.)
(Suk Jin can't think
of anything else.)
On this night where now
the last train has left
(The song ends with
a bad impression of a train horn.)
Let's check out the score.
- Let's see.
- I call 90.
- See?
- No way.
- I knew it.
- You're right.
- Trot songs get you 100 points.
- So a trot song of 99 points.
The score's higher than I expected.
- If we go for 99 points...
- It has a generous scoring system.
I bet we'll get 100 points.
You're bad at ad-libs
even as a backup singer.
Wasn't I incredible?
Suk Jin, go ahead.
- I'm not sure.
- Choose a recent song.
- "Meant to Be" could be good.
- It didn't get me dancing though.
- "Meant to Be"?
- Or maybe...
- "Wrongful Encounter."
- How about "Southbound Train"?
- "Wrongful Encounter"!
- Let's go with "Southbound Train."
- "Southbound Train"?
- But those...
They were all released decades ago.
- But they get you dancing.
- How about that one?
- Which one?
- "Jintobaegi"?
- No.
- Then what?
"Youthful You."
- Which one?
- "Youthful You."
- "Youthful You"?
- Hold on.
Youthful you
Hold on a second.
Did you all just hear that?
It's what I sang
during my teenage years.
- Wouldn't it bring down the mood?
- It's by Kim Soo Chul.
- No way.
- I think it will.
Then "Youthful You."
- It won't bring down the mood.
- No?
- This...
- It cheers you up.
Can you get a full score?
- Of course.
- A full score?
Are you taking on the challenge?
(He hesitates for a bit.)
Go ahead.
- Or pass...
- I'll give it a shot!
- Really?
- What's the estimated score?
- What will be your goal?
- A score of 99.
- Okay.
- Then you must get from 98 to 100.
The song's number is 1, 2, 3, and 8.
(The song's number indicates
how old the song is.)
I have never punched in a number
this low before.
- It's an upbeat song.
- Of course.
How does it go?
- All right!
- I'm loving the beat.
(Intro)
His dance moves are just as old.
(He vocalizes the beat.)
- The beat's lost on me.
- This...
- I'm finding it hard to sway to it.
- Was...
Was the song always this slow?
I remember it being a faster beat.
(When Seok Sam used to strut down
the streets of Bangbae-dong.)
What's with this slow song?
- Was the song always this slow?
- Why...
- Why is it this slow?
- We see TWICE on screen though.
- This song...
- There's TWICE.
- It used to be a fast song.
- Why is it this slow?
(He remedies the situation
by turning up the tempo.)
I turned up the tempo.
- Let's run to
- No, not yet.
- No?
- And go!
(Let's run to the rough plain)
- All right!
- Let's run.
Keep running!
(Drink in the sun of youth)
Drink it in!
(He acts like
he's drinking in the sun.)
- This isn't getting us to dance.
- More blissful than jewels
(They begin to pull back
from participating in the song.)
- Should I turn up the tempo again?
- This isn't fun at all.
Tomorrow's
Hey, stop fidgeting with that.
It calls for us
- It picks up from here.
- Then let us party.
All right!
(Those in their youth, wake up)
Don't you dare sleep!
Wake up!
(Those in their youth, wake up)
(Even he's embarrassed
by his poor ad-libs.)
What are you talking about?
Get him out of here!
Get the honorary employee
out of here.
(He tries his best
to seem young and cool.)
(However, it's painful to listen
to this old man's song.)
- You are youthful and like the sun
- Haha, stick one on him.
(He keeps singing
unaware of the pain he's causing.)
(A curse gets stuck on him.)
(The old Suk Jin
receives 10 more penalty balls.)
(A score between 98 and 100
is what he needs to succeed.)
(So what's his score?)
Wasn't he too old for that song?
- What?
- Does it say 47?
- You know you deserve it, right?
- No way.
You know you deserve it.
Here you go. What would
you have done without this?
- I can't believe it.
- How can he get 47 points?
That song should
be called "Old You."
How is that "Youthful You"?
That was "Old You."
- How was that youthful?
- It's only because...
you guys didn't have fun with me.
Was it too slow?
- The machine...
- It wasn't fun at all.
You need to sing a trot song
to get 100 points.
Anyway, you failed this round.
How about this then?
Can I sing one? I really want to.
- Go ahead.
- Go for it.
- Is it a trot song?
- No.
- I want to sing "Daring Woman."
- What?
"Daring Woman" by Suh Joo Kyung.
Exactly.
- So Min only wants...
- I'm shocked by my score of 47.
I bet you want
a certain someone to see this.
- Of course not.
- I'm sure of it.
It's a song I like.
- Go for 100 points.
- You know, it suits you.
Men like this song as well.
Are you going for it?
- Go for it.
- Yes, go for it.
("Daring Woman" by Suh Joo Kyung,
performed by Jeon So Min)
- I didn't call out a score.
- Go for it.
What should be my goal?
- What should it be?
- Decide on one now.
- Around 80.
- I'll go for 82.
- How about 85?
- Okay, 85.
All right, 85.
Is it 85?
A score of 90 wouldn't be so bad.
Really?
Aim for 90 instead.
I'll go for 90.
- Is this on purpose?
- Isn't 99 better?
(She already begins
with her daring steps.)
- Is it 90?
- Yes, 90.
The only difference...
is that I'll be
the backup singer again.
No, don't do it.
We're done hearing from the old man.
(You're forcing yourself
not to smile)
Absolutely!
(You're only cold toward me)
- Absolutely!
(The fake backup singer is gone
and enters Psychorus.)
(A big fuss)
(That is what makes
you charming though)
- That's right!
(Your nonchalant gaze and words)
- Your gaze!
- But I can still feel your gaze
- Nice!
(She gets the part going
after the "Youthful You" fiasco.)
I'm throwing in my jegi performance.
- Are you on your way home?
- That's right!
The weight of the world
seems to be on your shoulders
It's a festival!
(They're having a blast.)
(Would you buy me a drink?)
- Nice!
- Any time!
Yayaya, look at me
(They all show off
what they can do.)
(Saying that you
were waiting for me)
(Doesn't make you
lose out on anything)
It does!
(The gummy backup singer is thrilled
to be back at his day job.)
Say that you want me as yours
(They're having fun
regardless of their mission.)
This is great.
(Despite all the distractions,
she managed to finish the song.)
- All right.
- Let's see.
That was great.
- I have a good feeling about this.
- Give us 90.
- Right.
- Give me 90.
- We guessed correctly.
- I did it!
- I did it.
- Really?
(Changing the goal at the end...)
(led them to a victory.)
- It was 90.
- Yes!
No way.
Ji Hyo suggested
that we change it to 90.
- I'm glad you said so.
- Our goal was 90.
- Amazing as always.
- We actually did it.
The machine knew
that I was singing from the heart.
No way.
I can't believe we actually did it.
I bet you're punching in the scores.
There is no way I'd get a 47.
Who gets a karaoke score of 47?
What's more insane is
he got a score in the forties.
- How can that be?
- It's giving me the chills.
A score of 47
doesn't make any sense.
Manual labor is always an option.
- Washing the feet or...
- Of course.
Let's come up with a game.
(Game Lab, Worth up to 500 dollars)
You can come up with a game.
- It's worth more money.
- Sure. What should it be?
Let's think about it.
- There's a jegi...
- I saw many props...
including an eye mask.
Yes, and a jegi.
There are a lot of props.
- Game Lab?
- How about blindfolded hacky sack?
When we can't do it
with our eyes open?
We can't even do it
with our eyes open.
But I did 20 a few minutes ago.
- But...
- How about this?
- Go ahead.
We'll stand in a circle...
- and toss the jegi around.
- It'll be a team mission.
- That sounds good.
- Everyone must kick it.
- So we'll go around in a circle?
- And when...
- the seventh person kicks it...
- That's like...
It's like a trapping drill
in soccer.
- Absolutely.
- That's what you mean.
But we'll do it with a jegi.
- Who will go first?
- Let's give it a shot.
Go ahead.
What on earth? Keep a steady rhythm.
- Why didn't you use your left foot?
- This is the problem.
- This can happen though.
- I know.
What do you think
of the game we came up with?
I'm sure they approve.
What kind of games do you prefer?
It may not be fun,
but it'll be rewarding for us.
It's not the most creative idea.
- They must value creativity.
- Not the most creative idea?
Come up with one yourself then.
Don't be like that.
- How about this then?
- We'll just do it.
Someone will stand here
with his or her mouth open.
A snack will be thrown
from across the room...
and someone can eat it from here.
- What do you say?
- That's impossible.
- That's weird.
- What?
- That won't be easy.
- That's weird.
- It will be so much fun.
- Or...
(Or...)
How about we keep kicking...
- and the last person scores?
- The last person scores?
That will be so hard.
- I think we've done that before.
- That's hard.
Give it a try.
The seven of us kick,
and the last person must score.
- All seven of us?
- Yes.
- Will that work?
We have to keep passing.
It doesn't matter who's next.
- Let's kick once.
- That's so hard.
That's funny.
- One. Two.
- Okay.
- Suk Jin.
- You can kick again.
- You'll have to kick again.
- Right.
- Let's try it again.
- One.
It's fine
as long as we don't drop it.
(Crazy jegi skill)
Wait.
- We got it.
- I don't want to do it.
- You can play jegi with both feet.
- You're good.
- Why am I so good?
- Young jegi.
- Aren't you the young jegi?
- He's using both feet.
It doesn't matter how many times
you kick.
You just have to keep kicking
until you score.
- Okay.
- Just pass it.
Pass it.
- Okay. Good.
- Why am I so good?
- I was surprised.
- Okay.
Is there a magnet? One. Two.
- Keep it going.
- I'll take over.
- Save it.
(It's a mess.)
Save it.
- Are we doing this?
- You should...
What do you think? Is it fun?
- You can get it evaluated.
- Do you like it?
We should give it a try.
- Let's get it evaluated.
- How much is it worth?
The jegi game.
How much?
(1.50 dollars,
there is a similar game.)
I thought that said 15,000 dollars.
- There is a similar game.
- There's a similar game.
So we have to come up
with something new.
What about guessing
whose hair it is?
Who guesses it?
It.
- Who's it?
- The loser.
We all pull out a strand of hair.
Isn't that new?
We have to guess whose hair it is.
- Is this a DNA test?
- Guess whose hair it is?
- Is this a CSI game?
- Is this a DNA test?
- Is that from CSI?
- How is that funny?
- From the smell.
- Who films strands of hair?
How are we going to film it?
She's still suggesting an idea.
We're having a meeting.
Stop being an old fossil.
- That's not it.
- Oh, I have one.
How about pot tennis?
- Let's see if it works.
- Let's try.
(It's the best idea so far.)
- Did you hear that?
- It works.
Do I catch it?
(Do I catch it?)
- Hey.
- Is this a catch ball?
- Are we supposed to catch it?
What are you doing?
- Is this a catch ball?
- You have to hit it.
- Do I hit it?
- He didn't hit it.
- What are you doing?
- Why did you catch it?
- Hit it.
- Hurry up.
- Hit it and grab it.
- Give it a try.
Give it a try.
Just wait.
- It should be a rally.
- Hit it.
It's supposed to be a rally.
- Hey!
- Hit it.
(Jegi catch ball won't
become a rally.)
- You have to hit it.
- I will.
- I'll hit it.
Why can't you hit it?
How many times
do you have to do it to succeed?
- Ten times.
- What's the rule to win?
But,
he's funny.
- What's the rule?
- Why do you blame me for trying?
- We should draw the line.
- Jegi tennis looks fun.
- Yes.
- What do you think of jegi tennis?
- Try.
It's so fun.
Come on.
- It's only fun for you?
Hey.
Hey. It's not fun for us either.
- What are you talking about?
- We're forced to play.
Jae Suk. How about this?
Since you're having a snack,
we'll all close our eyes...
and guess which one you're eating.
- Awesome.
- That's so fresh.
I've never seen anything
like that before.
- We'll guess what you ate.
- I swear...
that will cost like 15 cents.
- Eat any random snack.
- It'll be 15 cents.
What if he writes,
"Only the person eating enjoys it."
- We're not enjoying it either.
- How about...
you put five in your mouth,
and you have to explain it
until you finish eating.
Like a speed quiz.
Because you can't talk properly.
You have to eat it fast.
A speed quiz.
- Eat it fast in time?
- While answering,
you have to eat it fast.
If you whistle after eating,
you win.
(Punching)
- Wait.
- Why are you talking to me?
What's that reaction?
- It won't work.
- What's that reaction?
What else is there?
- Hey. We have the best teamwork.
- That's right.
Hey. Why are you all running away?
(Running away)
- Look at them.
- That's ridiculous.
- Is it fun or not?
- How about...
one person stands here
and the rest line up.
We pass the ball with a header.
- Let's try.
- With this?
If the last person grabs it
and says,
"Go, go, let's go." Then we win.
That's so fresh.
What do you think?
Like Pac-Man game.
Something that involves
product placement.
Let's eat fried chicken
for product placement...
- and have a speed quiz.
- A speed quiz.
Until you finish the fried chicken.
- And we measure time.
- Let's do product placement.
And the number of answers.
What do you say?
You have a speed quiz
while having fried chicken.
We set the time and finish
fried chicken within that time.
Hurry up and write it.
That's worth more
than 1,000 dollars...
because it involves
product placement.
- Hurry up and write it.
- That's worth more than 500.
It also involves product placement.
It's nice.
- It will be worth 1,000 dollars.
- Write it already.
(Whispering)
Write what you think.
Don't ask the person next to you.
It's okay. We can make money
from product placement.
(200 dollars)
- Really? 200 dollars?
- I still got 200 dollars.
- Let's try it.
- Yes. Let's try.
You don't have to do it.
Just share your ideas.
- Only the ideas?
- It's a good idea.
- Really?
- We only have to share our ideas?
- We don't have to do it?
- I earned 200 dollars.
- Really?
- Only the idea.
- Hey.
- Line up.
- Everyone. Jump off.
What if we jump off
with our heads down?
Wouldn't that be fun?
No variety show has ever tried that.
How about we all line up...
and slap each other with a smile on?
The person who cries has to pay
a dollar.
- Let's do it.
- What?
The person who cries has to pay
a dollar.
(They demonstrate it right away.)
- Stand here.
- What do you think?
- We didn't have to try?
We only have to explain it.
- It's a popular computer game.
- A lot of people play it now.
- What's this?
- What is it?
It's pretty simple.
You use the mouse to move it.
Are we playing the game?
You can play it at any time.
(A jar game where you have to
pass the obstacle using the mouse)
- I see. Okay.
- What?
You just have to pass that tree.
- Here?
- Yes.
(If he passes that tree,
he wins 500 dollars right away.)
- How do you do it?
- How does it work?
- You have to hang it.
I see.
Or you can't pass the tree?
- Just like that.
- Do it one more time.
There.
(It may look easy,
but it will upset you.)
Oh, gosh.
It's not easy to pass the tree.
(He slowly gets frustrated
and angry.)
I'm actually pretty good at games.
- Really?
- Yes.
I don't use it in the gym.
Wait.
Do you even know how to play?
It doesn't seem like
you know how to play.
It's my first time.
You said...
- you feel confident.
- Yes.
You have to go up.
You have to get on the tree.
That's right. You finally hung it.
Bite the branch with your teeth.
How did this guy end up in a jar?
What's wrong with him?
- Just do it.
- I don't understand this game.
He can just break the jar with it.
Exactly.
Why did he go in there
with a hammer?
He can just break the jar
with that hammer.
You shouldn't take that long.
- You got it.
If you let it go,
he'll get stuck in it.
Yes.
- Let go of his arms.
- I got it.
- You did it.
- I'm up here.
You got that far.
You just have to hang it right.
- You did it.
- It went up.
Now hang it. That's right.
Now, go over it.
I should move.
Take it slow.
You can go up.
Hang it.
(Jae Suk becomes nervous when he
just needs to go over the tree.)
- You did it!
- I went over.
(He went over the tree.)
(He wins 500 dollars.)
- I went over the tree.
- You got 500 dollars for that.
Jae Suk.
- Good job.
- Well done.
If you pass the next round,
you get another 500 dollars.
Do I get 500 dollars for this round?
- If you pass the rocky mountain?
- How much do we have left?
- Hey. What's that?
- No.
Fried chicken is here.
This must be the fried chicken.
- It must be new.
- That looks good.
Amazing.
How are we supposed to do it
without saying any words?
Use your expression...
- and exclamations.
- Only exclamations.
(Support Production Cost:
Worth up to 500 dollars)
It smells so nice.
(Only facial expressions
and exclamations are allowed.)
It smells so nice.
- Is it good?
- It's good. You should try it.
Describe it only with your facial
expression and exclamations.
(Cock-a-doodle-doo)
(A philosophical reaction to
represent the sacrificed chicken)
Did you become a chicken?
Are you a chicken?
(Peep peep)
(Everyone's making facial
expressions and exclamations...)
(with no specific words.)
- It's still warm.
- It's sweet.
It's savory.
(The small fortune-teller
seems to be possessed.)
I like it.
(The small fortune-teller
seems to be possessed.)
Here.
- Yes.
- It's really good.
It's stuck.
(Laughing)
Do you understand
why people play that game?
If you pass it, you get 500 dollars.
(The delighted middle-aged man
is totally into the game.)
Jong Kook. Calm down.
(Totally immersed)
(What's the definition
of game addiction?)
(How do we decide it?)
(Kim in his 40s chose the game
over the muscle loss.)
- No.
- He has a game machine at home...
and spends over five hours
on the game on weekends.
(Kim in his 40s chose the game
over the muscle loss.)
I went up so high.
It's unbelievable.
(Kim in his late 40s)
This is unbelievable. I got so high.
- Jong Kook. Are you playing a game?
- Yes.
Jong Kook. This is not a real fight.
(Everyone is worried
about Jong Kook.)
- Nice.
- It's delicious.
(He hung the hammer.)
(Nervous)
Did you get there?
I went down and climbed up again.
That's worth 500 dollars.
(If he passes the rocky mountain,
he'll get 500 dollars.)
You must pass it.
(If he passes the rocky mountain,
he'll get 500 dollars.)
- You got it.
(You must pass it.)
I'm not used to using the mouse.
(What's the result
of Mr. Kim the game addict?)
(He barely saves the jar man
who almost fell.)
- You got it.
You can do it.
(Almost there)
Hurry up.
- Gosh.
- Hurry up.
- You did it!
- Yes! I did it.
(Jong Kook did it!)
(The impressive result
of the game addict)
That's another 500 dollars.
(The impressive result
of the game addict)
(Remaining time, Remaining fee)
(Jong Kook won 500 dollars.)
Do you understand
why people play that game?
If you pass it,
you'll get another 500 dollars.
(Laughing)
Oh, no. Where are you going?
Well...
Can we have a Feet Washing Ceremony?
But we just ate.
Feet Washing Ceremony?
- Come on.
- What?
- Don't you think that's too much?
- That's too much.
You're going to wash your hands
anyway.
Oh, come on.
Let's have a Feet Washing Ceremony.
But we just ate.
How much is
the Feet Washing Ceremony?
- How much is it?
- It's 200 dollars.
- That's not enough.
- Only 200 dollars?
- That's never enough.
- Only 200?
- That's so cheap.
- Medicine will cost more.
You could wash your loving friend's
feet without getting paid.
- That's not it.
- Here's what we should do.
Make it 200 dollars per foot.
His feet stink so bad.
I'll clean between his toes.
Count each toe.
You should do it.
You can do it for him.
Do we have latex gloves?
I can't do it without gloves.
It's the best
after having fried chicken.
How can he be so shameless?
This is great. My feet are actually
in a bad condition.
Do we have to hold
the Feet Washing Ceremony?
My goodness.
- I'll be right back.
- What floor is it?
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk and Suk Jin
move to curse.)
- I'm ready.
- Can I wash my hands?
(Doctor Jeon is in charge
of the Feet Washing Ceremony.)
Pour water first.
- Water first.
- Your toenails are so ugly.
Hurry up and pour water.
(She tries to get rid of bacteria
with hot water.)
My goodness.
Both of his big toes are rotten.
(His two feet are perfectly ripe.)
It's warm.
Can you pour water up to here?
I think we need to soak your feet,
Se Chan.
I can't wash them now.
We need to soak them first.
Something's floating.
I'm not joking.
Something is floating.
- Something is floating, Haha.
- That's called dead skin.
(That's called dead skin.)
- Try.
- Don't curse me.
- I won't.
- How can he do that after this?
But you're doing this
because you love him.
No. This is too much for me.
We're colleagues.
I can wash your feet too.
(Grabbing)
Gosh.
(Grunting)
(Locking her fingers with his toes)
What's going on?
(Delightful Feet Washing Ceremony)
- You see,
- This is disgusting.
that's what a married couple
looks like.
Whatever.
- This is disgusting.
- My goodness.
(Locking her fingers
with his toes again)
Poor So Min.
(She massages each of his toes.)
(He expresses how nice it is
by exposing his gum.)
Lift it.
So Min. Thank you for doing this
in the new year.
My colleague is washing my feet.
I'll wash your feet too.
I'm good.
- I'll wash your feet.
- No, I'm good.
Right. You should wash
each other's feet.
- No, I'm good.
- Let me do it please.
- I'm good.
- Erase her makeup with that water.
- For 500 dollars.
- For 1,000 dollars.
I'll kill you then.
(She locks her fingers
with his left toes.)
(He's going crazy
with his colleague's love.)
Poor So Min.
- Hey. So Min.
- Yes?
My goodness.
Can you smile?
(Forced smile)
Hey.
Thank you.
To the end. One foot at a time.
(She even dries his feet.)
- The towel. Done.
- Thank you.
It's my first time
to wash anyone's feet.
I've never done this before.
This is my first time
aside from my mom. That's good.
Wait. There's dust.
Is this dust or what?
- That's good.
- Is that dry skin?
Thanks.
- Is that 200 dollars?
- Yes.
My hands feel weird. They're dry.
Is this okay?
What's wrong with my hands?
Do you want to touch it?
It feels really weird.
This is strange.
I'm getting heated up.
What?
He's arousing.
- It turned you on.
- Watch your mouth.
No. That's not it.
He's turned on.
- No.
- Gosh.
Jong Kook. Don't be mad.
(He tries to calm down
while playing the game.)
I got it.
Oh, I got it.
(His control skill improved
so much.)
Are you really playing it?
This is why Jong Kook never plays
any games.
He's afraid he'll go crazy.
(The venomous snake never lets it go
once he bites it.)
- Yes. Once I'm into something...
- He finds the way.
That's right.
It seems his muscles have
gotten bigger.
- He worked out.
- He bulked up.
He worked out.
- Come on.
- That's amazing.
Come on.
What's this? How does this work?
(The dartboard shrine
where you can curse someone)
Throw the dart
at the target in front of you.
If you hit the center, you succeed.
The person you choose
gets ten penalty balls.
However, if you hit anywhere
other than the center,
you'll get penalty balls
according to the number on it.
Only here?
Yes. But you can practice
as much as you want.
My goodness.
You have only one chance.
(You can practice
as much as you want.)
(But once you go for it,
you only get one chance.)
This isn't going to work.
Before you try, you have to say
the name of the person...
you want to curse.
He got it.
- You didn't say you'll go.
- I know.
I used to play darts so much
in the past.
Can you get out of there?
(He used to be
the king of dart in Apgujeong.)
Gosh.
(Bull's-eye)
- You should've said you'll go.
- My gosh.
My. I did it again.
(He hit the center twice in a row.)
I used to play darts so much.
I should try.
All right.
(He decides to give it a try
right away.)
Say the name of the member
you want to curse and say go.
Who should I curse?
Let's curse the same person.
- Yes.
- What about Haha?
- Yes, Haha.
- I'll curse Haha.
I'll say go before I try.
This is a practice.
- You have to say go.
- I'll say go before I do it.
When it's time.
(He plans to practice
and say go when it's time.)
When I finally get it.
I'm getting there.
Okay. I'll go.
(I'll go.)
(Will the old king of dart
save his only chance?)
(He fails.)
(He hits 5.)
Suk Jin.
You get five penalty balls.
- I almost had it.
- What are you doing?
(The king of dart cursed himself.)
I almost had it.
- How do you play?
- What?
Hit the center?
Do you see the circle in the center?
You have to hit that.
Gosh. This isn't easy.
(Jae Suk keeps missing the center.)
(I'll go.)
I'll go.
(Glancing)
Now is time.
Haha?
Suk Jin.
(He curses Suk Jin
in front of him.)
Hey.
(Laughing)
How could you?
How can you do that?
Fine. Go ahead. Do it.
You're going to fail anyway.
(Bull's-eye)
(Shocked)
Jae Suk did it.
Suk Jin gets ten penalty balls.
(Suk Jin gets 10 penalty balls.)
- Ten?
- I never thought I'd do it.
- That was awesome.
- How does that happen?
- That was amazing.
- I concentrated so much.
You missed it 9 times out of 10,
and yet you hit it?
(Suk Jin gets
15 penalty balls alone.)
I'll go. Whose name should I say?
Suk Jin.
- Say you'll go.
- Suk Jin. I'll go.
I'll go. Suk Jin.
- She keeps failing.
- I'll go. Suk Jin!
- Hey.
- That's all yours.
- That's a negative ten.
- She gets a negative ten.
- Is that all on me?
- Yes.
You cursed yourself.
If you miss it, it goes to you.
Come on. Yes.
Yes.
Somebody stop Jong Kook.
He's going crazy.
- He's about to...
- He's about to spend money on it.
He's going crazy.
- Jong Kook. You should stop.
- I said he can stop, but he won't.
- Stop playing.
- Come on.
The man in the jar is begging us
to save him.
If he gets on the red bar,
he gets 500 dollars.
(If he passes the red bar,
that's an additional 500 dollars.)
Hang on. That punk.
(Pro Gamer Kim moves the mouse
a few times.)
- He did it.
- I got it. I'm on it.
(He succeeds easily.)
- I'm on it.
- You get 500 dollars.
(He gets additional 500 dollars.)
- How much...
- I know what to do.
- How much have you earned?
- What?
- Didn't you earn a lot?
- I earned a lot.
- Please stop playing.
- Shall I stop?
I got the hang of it.
It's such a difficult game.
We earned more than 1,000 dollars.
- How much did we pay off?
- You paid off 4,100 dollars.
That's good.
What can we do now?
- You can either work or...
- How about missions?
Five chances remain for missions.
- Shall we try Immortal Chan Hee?
- Immortal Chan Hee?
Let's try it.
- We should try all the missions.
- That's right.
The camera will move this way.
I remember playing this game
in the early days.
- That's right.
- We played this game.
Once you say, "Start..."
All of us need to be in the angle...
- once the camera moves.
- That's right.
- Left.
- Let's practice.
- Right.
- It's just our faces, right?
It's just your faces.
As soon as the camera stops,
- I will count down three seconds.
- Okay.
You succeed if all of your faces are
in the angle.
Wouldn't we succeed if we move back?
Tall people should move back.
- Ji Hyo and I...
- I think it will be easy.
The time frame will be very tight.
- So Min should go down.
- I just think...
you should look at the angle
and judge for yourself.
- So Min.
- Let's go.
Once you yell "Start,"
you will lose one chance.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Start.
It's going to the right.
- Down.
- Look at the top.
Look at the camera.
It's going to the right.
Up. Down.
- Down.
- Look at the top.
- Look at the camera.
- The camera.
- Three,
- It stopped.
two, one.
Three, two, one.
(Se Chan's facial features
aren't visible.)
You failed.
- Why?
- We were in the angle.
My knees.
My knees hurt.
- We were in the angle.
- My knees hurt.
Chan Hee, you made this
impossible for us.
- Seriously.
- Chan Hee.
We were in the angle.
- That was too difficult.
- We were in the angle.
Chan Hee, you are too much.
Chan Hee.
You completed the mission too late.
- Did we complete it too late?
- You should look at the angle,
not the screen.
For goodness' sake.
You lost one chance.
I think this is doable.
- I know.
- Does that mean...
- we lost a chance?
- Yes. Four chances remain.
Only four chances remain.
- We need to complete this mission.
- Shall we try again?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Say, "Start."
- Start.
Look at the camera. That's better.
- Okay.
- Look at the camera.
He tends to point the camera
to a corner.
Go!
- Three, two, one.
- Is my face showing?
He tends to point the camera
to a corner.
(The camera pointed to a corner.
What will be the result?)
One.
- I fell down.
- You failed.
- Why did we fail?
- Hey.
- Go!
- Three,
- two,
- Is my face showing?
one.
(On the floor)
You failed.
- Why did we fail?
- Hey.
- She fell down.
So Min, I am sorry.
I slipped.
- My goodness.
- Are you okay?
I slipped. I am sorry.
I thought we were successful.
Didn't we succeed?
So Min was nowhere to be seen.
So Min wasn't in the snapshot.
So Min, were you nowhere to be seen?
So Min even washed Se Chan's feet.
(Giggling)
"Were you nowhere to be seen?"
(She makes him quiet
with a forced fist bump.)
- In that case...
- We were close.
Right.
It can't be helped. Let's stop.
Let's try it one more time.
- Really?
- Let's try it one more time.
Let's try it one more time.
I will do well this time.
We tried it multiple times already.
- We are invested. Let's try it.
- Okay.
Just look at the camera.
- That's right.
- Just look at the camera.
(They try it for the third time.)
- Say, "Start."
- Start.
- Just look at the camera.
- Look carefully.
If he points the camera upward...
- That's impossible.
- Spider-Man.
We can't go midair.
Just look at the camera.
- Three,
- Down!
two, one.
- Where am I?
- We succeeded?
- You failed.
- Why...
- So Min, where are you?
- Where am I?
- You failed.
- Why...
- So Min, where are you?
- I am here.
- Why didn't you look at the camera?
This is driving me crazy.
- The camera.
It's impossible to like her!
Why did you hide from the camera?
Why did you hide your face?
Why did you hide?
Are you an X-Man?
- So Min, don't look at the screen.
- Don't look at the screen.
Look at the camera.
Why did you look at the GoPro?
Hold on.
Shouldn't So Min be a referee?
Are you an Ax-Man?
- Ax-Man?
- That was obviously intentional.
Ax-Man?
That was obviously intentional.
- You keep doing that.
- Do you admit it?
- My goodness.
- Don't be ridiculous.
You are an Ax-Man.
(He tried to make the fourth video
about his verbal blunders.)
- That was so obvious.
- You are embarrassed, right?
Seriously.
"Ax-Man" was obviously intentional.
Do you keep in touch...
with the person who is in charge
of the official YouTube channel?
"We need two more verbal blunders
to create another video."
(We need two more verbal blunders
to create another video.)
Ax-Man.
- Let's try it for the last time.
- The last time.
I will use a curse
on the member who fails this time.
- Okay.
Aren't we out of chances?
Two chances remain.
I think we will succeed this time.
- Let's do this.
- After this,
- we can make money through labor.
- Yes.
- Will we be able to succeed?
- I am so nervous.
We can do it.
(They try again with perseverance.)
Chan Hee.
- Down.
- Hey.
- Three, two,
- I am in the angle, right?
one.
- Down.
- Hey.
- Three, two, one.
- I am in the angle, right?
Are they in the angle?
(What will be the result
of their last attempt?)
- Okay.
(They finally succeed.)
You succeeded.
I lifted up your face.
We struggled because of the Ax-Man.
Ax-Man.
It's okay.
We did it. We succeeded, So Min.
I am happy that you succeeded.
You made 4,600 dollars so far.
I can't believe
we only made 4,600 dollars.
Is that all we have?
I will slice the rice cake.
- So Min and I will slice the rice cakes.
- Which game can we play?
We need to hurry up and work.
Only one chance remains.
There is a simple game we recommend.
Okay. That sounds good.
It's the last chance.
All seven members need to take turns
to bounce the ball once.
Then the seventh member
needs to score a goal.
- That sounds simple.
- We can do it.
- Okay.
- I think we can do it.
- You can't bounce it twice.
- Just once.
We need to go in the right order.
- Who will score a goal?
- You don't need to go first.
- I will go first.
- So Min.
- Sit next to her.
- To do it like Ji Hyo,
bounce it high.
There you go.
- Do we bounce it twice?
- Once.
- It's my turn.
- Ji Hyo.
There you go.
Put it in there.
- That doesn't count.
- Doesn't it count?
- Why not?
- It went in.
- It was a dunk shot.
- Why not?
You held the ball for two seconds.
We didn't say, "Start."
It was a practice round.
- Let's do it like that.
- Okay.
- Pass.
- Let's go. Start.
- Start.
- Already?
- Pass it over.
- Go.
Is this an actual round?
Let's practice once more.
- Let's practice once more.
- Once more.
Is this a practice round
or an actual round?
- Start.
- Which one is it?
All right. We told you.
- It was a practice round.
- A practice round.
- Yes.
- Jae Suk told you.
- We told you.
It's an actual round
when we say "Start" together.
What?
- It was a practice round.
- We didn't say, "Start."
What's the problem?
- Start.
- Why are you so sensitive?
- Go.
- Start.
- Is this an actual round?
- Shall we go?
- Start.
Let's say it together.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Start.
Go. That's good. Slowly.
Hey.
(Suk Jin's toss was shaky.)
Put it in there.
(They failed.)
(They can't even protest.)
- We failed.
- That was...
- Suk Jin, sit here.
- You messed up.
- Suk Jin.
- It wasn't like that.
- Listen.
- Ji Hyo passed it badly.
Here.
- You need to keep it short.
- Bounce it like this.
- Like this.
- That's right.
You need to keep it short.
If someone gets five penalty balls,
I will let you try again.
- Suk Jin.
- Why me?
- You send it far.
- Ji Hyo passed it badly.
- Let's have a vote then.
Who should receive
five penalty balls?
- In 1, 2, 3,
- You.
- It's you, Suk Jin.
(Swearing)
Come on.
You got picked.
- You made everyone vote for me.
- What is your problem?
- Let's have a fair vote.
- Come on.
- What is your problem?
- Suk Jin, do well just this once.
- What are you talking about?
- Aren't you an Ax-Man?
- Just this once.
- What are you talking about?
- You seem like an Ax-Man.
- Ax-Man.
- I will receive five penalty balls.
- Let's go.
- Ax-Man.
(They resume after Suk Jin receives
5 penalty balls.)
All right.
- I will pass to Haha.
- Ji Hyo.
- Haha.
- All right.
- We did it.
For goodness' sake!
We didn't say, "Start."
- We didn't say, "Start."
- No.
We didn't say it.
- They are incredible.
- We didn't say, "Start."
Keep the ball in here.
- Here.
- Let's go.
- Start.
- in 1, 2, 3.
- in 1, 2, 3. Start.
Go ahead.
Keep going like that.
- Keep going like that.
- There you go.
- That's good.
- Good job.
- We got this.
- It will go in.
(They failed again.)
- We didn't say "Start" properly.
- We didn't say it.
We didn't say it properly.
- This is our strategy.
I wanted to see
how you would react. Good job.
If someone gets penalty balls,
- I will give you one last chance.
- One last chance.
Haha should get them since he said
he is good at basketball.
If I had said
that I am good at soccer,
I would have gotten
the penalty balls.
- It goes without saying.
- Haha?
- I would have gotten them.
- No!
- You deserve five penalty balls.
- Go ahead.
Then I will give you
two curses each.
- That's 20 penalty balls each.
- Don't be like that.
- Go ahead.
- From here...
- Jong Kook should go last.
- Jong Kook.
- It's difficult.
- I will do it.
- Because of that hole,
it's impossible to score a goal.
It's too small.
What are you doing?
Can't I stretch it?
- Don't do that.
- Leave it as it is.
- It won't go in.
- Let me stretch it.
- Leave it as it is.
- It won't go in.
- What are you doing?
- Come on.
- You know,
this is exactly why
Suk Jin can't win the Grand Award.
I can't believe him.
- It won't work.
- It won't go in.
It went in. Watch.
It was much harder
when the opening was like this.
- It didn't go in.
- You are doing it wrong.
(He hit it hard on purpose.)
You hit it hard.
Come on.
I am telling you
it's better this way.
- Watch.
- Even if we succeed...
See? It's nearly impossible.
Even if we succeed,
you will get criticized.
It works better this way. Trust me.
- See? It goes in more easily.
- Sit there.
- Try it.
- It goes in more easily.
- It doesn't matter, right?
- It doesn't matter.
- It's because...
- Try it.
I will give you a curse if you fail.
- This way,
- It's the last chance.
the ball will bounce more.
- Start.
- The edges...
It will bounce off the edges.
- It's better this way.
It's science.
Use your hands only.
(It's the last chance.
Will they manage to succeed?)
Hey.
Pass it.
All right.
(Ax-Man had a grand plan.)
(Will he succeed?)
- Gosh.
- You failed.
(He failed.)
You failed.
- What was that?
- You tossed the ball wrong.
You should have bounced it
on the spot.
- Let's slice rice cake.
- It's impossible.
- Gosh.
- The current time...
- is 2:40 p.m.
- For goodness' sake.
Let's do labor.
We will slice rice cake.
- We will slice rice cake.
- Let's slice rice cake.
How do we slice the cake?
We will pay you 50 dollars
for every bag of sliced rice cake.
Every bag?
The rest of the members
should write New Year's cards.
Let's be happy always.
In the new year...
You currently have 5,700 dollars
and 10 minutes remaining.
- What?
- Did you say ten minutes?
If the race ends this way,
three members will get the penalty.
(Remaining time: 10 minutes
Fee: 1,376.50 dollars)
(They need to make 300 dollars more
to lessen the number by 1.)
Hold on. In that case,
why don't we kick jegi 100 times?
That's a good idea.
In total?
We will kick jegi 100 times
in total.
We will do that for 300 dollars.
I will let you do that.
Okay. Clear the table.
- Clear the table.
- Let's kick jegi.
We need to kick jegi
100 times in total.
How will we do that?
- Did you say 100 times?
- It's doable.
- You came up with a good idea.
- Clear the table.
- There are seven of us, so yes.
- Did you say 100 times?
- There are 7 of us,
- so it's doable.
- Of course.
- You can't catch it.
- Good.
We can't catch it?
Se Chan is good at it.
Then I am a bit nervous.
- Then...
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Hey.
It's the last try of the day.
- Let's say, "Start."
- In 1, 2,
- three.
- Start.
One person can catch it once.
- Okay.
- You can't catch it afterward.
I will go first.
- This isn't a practice round.
- Okay.
- No more practice rounds.
- One.
One.
(She kicked it 1 time.)
(Oh.)
Good job.
It's okay. Good job.
- So Min.
- It happens.
- Gosh.
- All right.
- So Min.
- I think I will kick it once.
So Min kicked it
three times earlier.
Three. Good job.
- How many times did she kick it?
- Three times.
The total is four.
Currently, the total is four.
- You need to kick it 96 times.
- That's not a lot.
(They need to kick it 96 times.)
How many times? 96 times?
- Here I go.
- We can do it.
Good luck.
- This is nothing.
- You are right.
- You can kick it 50 times.
- How many times?
- You need to kick it 96 times.
- The remaining number is 96.
- Will it be okay?
- You can kick it 100 times.
- Jong Kook, kick it 30 times.
- Will it be okay?
- Give us some screen time.
Viewers won't like it
if I succeed at once.
Of course not.
Will it be okay?
Jong Kook, the more you talk,
the more nervous you seem.
- I will kick it 50 times.
- Okay.
There won't be any suspense
if I kick it too many times, right?
- All right.
- How do I usually kick jegi?
- Just kick it.
- I don't remember.
Okay. Here I go. This is nothing.
- There you go.
- Counting 3, 4,
- five...
- There you go.
- Four, five...
(The end)
Hey!
(What was that?)
Gosh.
(Hey!)
What? Didn't you say 50 times?
I should have known
from the way he talked too much.
- You know,
- Seriously.
I overdid it in the beginning.
- Five.
- It wasn't my usual rhythm.
The remaining number is 91.
Fourteen. He is just doing it.
- You are good.
- Counting 16, 17,
- eighteen, nineteen, twenty,
- Why didn't you do that earlier?
twenty-one, twenty-two,
twenty-three.
- For goodness' sake.
- You are good at it.
All right.
The remaining number is 91.
(Suk Jin is up next.)
You are the king of jegi.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Darn.
- Seriously.
- He is the real deal.
- You are young.
People who pull up their socks
can kick jegi more than 30 times.
- That's what uncles do...
- More than 30 times.
- during the holidays.
- Always.
Yes. They do this
before they show off to the kids.
The honorable and young Ax-Man.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Why am I so nervous?
- It's nerve-racking.
- You are sporty.
I am so nervous.
You are sporty.
- Here I go.
- Go.
- Start.
- Okay.
All right. He is good.
- He is steady.
- That's good.
Go slow.
- Go slow.
- He doesn't disappoint.
- Take this to the end.
- That's good.
- Don't give up until the end.
- His record is 19.
- Good job.
(The Honorary Employee
defended his honor.)
- Uncle is the best.
- Good job.
- You know...
- You did so well.
- Good job.
- I kicked it 19 times.
- That was incredible.
- Good job.
- You did so well.
- The last kick was off.
- Good job.
- The remaining number is 72.
- What?
- Did you say 72?
- You can do it.
- Se Chan is good at kicking jegi.
- Se Chan is good at it.
- Se Chan, do what you want.
- That's right.
- Se Chan.
- My goodness.
Just kick it 40 times.
You will look cool
if you kick it many times.
- He looks cool already.
- He is good.
- You are going too fast.
- Counting five,
six, seven, eight,
nine, ten,
- eleven, twelve...
- Gosh!
(The remaining number is 72,
but he only kicked it 12 times.)
I really did my best.
- I am serious.
- Hey!
What was that?
- It should be a close call.
- I think...
Haha should go next,
and Jae Suk should go last.
I should have kicked it more times.
What have I done?
- I could have done better.
- That broke the rhythm.
(Haha steps up
in the moment of crisis!)
Will you be able to kick it
30 times?
The remaining number is 60.
- Did you say 60?
- You never know.
- He might do well.
- Counting one,
- two, three,
- Never mind.
four...
- Two, three,
- Never mind.
four, five...
- Hey.
- Five...
(Swinging)
Why did you give up?
Give him a curse.
How could you do that?
Why did you give up?
You have messed up
multiple times today.
- Bring a curse.
- You said you are good at this.
Why did you decide to go later?
Why did you do that?
Give yourself a curse.
Your belly is sticking out.
- Only Jae Suk remains.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk, kick it 65 times.
- What's the remaining number?
- It's 55.
- What?
- You can catch it once.
- It's a bonus.
- We will step back.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk.
- Don't look.
- We won't look.
- And...
- Don't talk.
- Just count the number.
- I messed up because you looked.
- Don't say, "Go slow."
- We don't need to count.
- He will count himself.
- Let him count.
- Let's leave it to himself.
- Let's be quiet.
- All right. Be quiet.
- Let's go.
- Kick it 30 times right away.
- Okay.
- That's right.
- I need to do that much...
- to make it doable.
- Kick it 30 times smoothly.
Heroes are born
out of turbulent times.
Okay. I will kick it 55 times.
You should do this much
after the quarantine.
- All right.
- We won't say anything.
Be quiet!
(Be quiet!)
He looks nervous.
Who is being loud?
(He is shouting at the air
because he is nervous.)
He is in a good condition.
His voice is strong.
(He overcame his nervousness
regarding games earlier.)
(Will he be able
to overcome it once more?)
All right.
- Hey.
- Why did you laugh?
Why did you laugh?
(Chuckling)
(Jong Kook's laughter
broke his concentration.)
- Why did you laugh?
- Hey.
- Why...
- Why did you laugh?
- Why are you blaming me?
You should let me start over.
- Why did you laugh?
- Why are you blaming me?
- Hey, he laughed.
For goodness' sake.
- You were nervous.
- Jae Suk.
- I mean...
- Give him another chance.
It's Jong Kook's fault.
You failed.
Since 2 minutes remain,
2 people should write a card.
Let's write a card.
Go ahead and write it.
(If they write 2 cards,
3 people will receive the penalty.)
I don't know the name.
It's 2:59 p.m. One minute remains.
Gosh, nothing goes our way.
Why is that? What's wrong with us?
- It's 3 p.m.
- Okay.
The total amount of money
you made is 5,523 dollars.
We made a lot of money.
I will now announce
the final number of penalty balls.
- Jae Suk has 15 balls.
- Did you say 15?
- He doesn't have a lot.
- Haha has 25 balls.
- Why?
- That's not a lot.
Jong Kook has 45 balls.
He has a lot.
Se Chan has 28 balls.
- I thought I would have more.
- Ji Hyo has 25 balls.
So Min has 32 balls.
You don't have a lot.
Suk Jin has 52 balls.
- What?
- Did you say 52?
Did you say 52?
- It's close to your age.
- Isn't that his age?
- It's less than his age.
- Really?
Did you say 52?
Let's do this.
Hey, about ten more balls went in.
No.
- Let's see.
- You will get electrocuted.
- For your information,
one person will receive the penalty
if three balls have the same name.
- Hey.
- This is bad.
- My ball might not come out.
- Let's go.
- That's all that matters.
- This is how you win at life.
Okay.
I don't think I will get picked.
A ball came out. Two balls came out.
Okay.
(Who will receive a penalty
in the new year?)
Two balls came out.
Okay. It's fine
as long as I don't get picked.
- It's the New Year.
- Kim Jong Kook.
(The first member
to get a penalty is Jong Kook.)
- Yang Se Chan.
- Se Chan!
(The second member is Se Chan.)
Okay.
(And the last member
to get a penalty...)
Yang Se Chan.
(It's Se Chan again.)
- You two will get a penalty.
- How many balls did Se Chan have?
I didn't have many balls.
I can't believe
Suk Jin's ball wasn't picked.
My ball wasn't picked.
I can't believe this.
So Se Chan and Jong Kook
will get a penalty today.
- I'll announce today's penalty.
- Okay. What is it?
This is the first day
of the New Year.
And we're shooting
this episode on Sunday.
So we picked something
you can do only on Sundays.
- What is it?
- Cooking Chapaghetti?
- Is that it?
- Seriously?
You will watch our show
that will begin soon.
My goodness.
You will make a video of one minute.
I have to go to the gym.
You should laugh out loud
every time your face is on TV.
- That's horrible.
- Excuse me.
You should laugh out loud
watching yourself on TV.
For how long?
For about 30 seconds to 1 minute.
You should wait
until our show begins.
Okay.
(The shoot ended like that.)
(It was 5 p.m. that day.)
(Gym Jong Kook works out
at the gym watching Running Man.)
Okay. There it is.
(When his face is on TV...)
(Laughing)
I'm not supposed to take
a break for over a minute.
(He watched the show to the end
working out his muscles.)
(Se Chan is
getting the penalty too.)
(Laughing)
There he is.
(He just laughs out loud
for the penalty when no one's on.)
Hide!
Good.
(A mansion in Seongbuk-dong)
(Senior Candidate A Jeon So Min)
(In a corner of the same building)
(Empty Head is the future,
Senior Candidate B Yang Se Chan)
(Between Yang and Jeon,
who's last in the hierarchy?)
(Which one is more mature?)
(How to avoid being
the last in the hierarchy?)
Which one?
(They can't fall
for the false propaganda.)
(Defeat your rival no matter what.)
(And there's one more way.)
(Buying votes with money.)
(You should be a spy.)
(The youngest members...)
(keep betraying the members.)
(Once they escape from
being the last in the hierarchy,)
(they can become free
from the old fossils.)
(Who will be
the last in the hierarchy?)
(The Seniority War
of the Youngest Members)