(The morning of the shooting)
It's raining a lot this year.
(Unlike the weather forecast,
it's raining hard.)
We were going to shoot
today's episode outdoors,
- but it's raining hard.
- I know.
(So they are looking for an indoor
place where they can shoot.)
- Jong Kook's place...
- If it rains this much,
- it won't be a problem.
- It's no problem.
(So they decided
to walk around in the rain.)
- When do we start?
- Do I look okay?
We don't have to...
wear a mask in the open air anymore.
So some of our production crew...
often take off their masks
during the shoot.
It feels strange.
They look like strangers.
I will need some time
to get used to this.
For the past few years,
we only met wearing masks.
Now that I see their whole faces,
some seem a little unfamiliar.
We will get used to it over time.
(Laughing)
He seems to like it.
- Hello.
So Min, you are pretending
to be Generation MZ.
He will make fun of me today.
- Attention
- I'm not wearing a wig today.
- You came early.
- Hello.
Of course, I did. So Min, gosh.
- Jae Suk, please.
- Gosh.
(He messes up her bang.)
- She just went to the hair salon.
- So Min...
I know how it feels.
I'll piss her off.
- So Min...
- I just got my hair done.
I'll make her really upset.
- Are they shooting the opening?
- My gosh.
- Hello.
- Hey, why are you...
Aren't you supposed
to shoot the opening together?
You're from FIFA.
FIFA?
- Pass.
- This is...
Pass!
- Are you a ball boy?
- You're wearing the same thing.
- You're from FIFA.
- Pass.
- Shoot.
- The World Cup...
- will begin soon.
- The World Cup is beginning soon.
- It's 10 p.m.
- Right.
(Korea!)
(Singing)
Korea!
- Hey, shut it.
- The Taegeuk warriors
- You're from FIFA.
- Hi, Ji Hyo.
- Hello.
- Your hair has grown a lot.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hello.
Jae Suk. That's a cool-looking hat
you have on.
- I do?
- Because it's raining.
By the way, why does your hair
look like a thatched house?
- Because of the rain.
- No.
This is what I intended.
- That's not it.
- A thatched house.
That's because she's trying
to let her hair grow longer.
So it looks awkward
before it gets long.
What about you?
- You just look awkward.
- What's with your hair?
- Hey.
- You look like a hobo.
- You're just...
- A hobo.
You're just a bum.
- Hey.
- You always look that way.
You're just a hobo.
(He sowed the wind
and reaped the whirlwind.)
"You're just a hobo."
- Hey.
- What's that?
Hi.
- Don't act like you're young.
- What are you doing?
- No one does that anymore.
- It's like this.
If Haha does this,
it means it's outdated.
- Haha, young people do this.
- Hello.
- This is what they do.
- What's that?
They do this.
- Hello.
- Hi, Haha.
- Hello, Suk Jin.
- Let's do this.
- One, two, three.
- Hi.
- Let's do "Yappi."
- What's "Yappi?"
It goes like this.
- Everyone.
- Everyone. One, two, three.
- Yappi.
- What's that?
- What are they doing?
Kongsuni.
- What's that?
- Kongsuni.
- That's really old.
- What's that?
- It's so outdated.
- Kongsuni.
- What's that?
- Do you not know this?
- This is what they do now.
- I know.
- This is funny.
- Today,
we have the FIFA chairman here.
- Hello.
- Pass!
- The World Cup is coming.
It's November 24. Let's watch it.
Go, Korea!
(The chairman works hard.)
It's November 24.
What will you do?
Will you watch it together?
Is your house empty that day?
Suk Jin.
You can come over
to my place if you want.
- You just want to bet money.
- You said you'd bet money.
No.
- Hey.
- The FIFA chairman can't do that.
- It's just 20 dollars.
- He's the FIFA chairman.
- We will bet only 20 dollars.
Suk Jin, you can't do that.
- Didn't your wife go to the States?
- What?
- Didn't she go?
- She didn't go.
- She didn't go to the States.
- She went to Jeju Island.
- Jeju Island.
- I knew you were in a good mood.
- Right.
- I look energetic, right?
- Yes.
Last night,
I drove her to the airport.
(He can't hold back his smile.)
So Min, did you enjoy
your trip to Singapore?
- It was really fun.
- I know.
Seon Myung told me.
You just drank all day.
She didn't do anything in Singapore.
- She only drank.
- She just drank all day.
- She didn't even eat crabs.
- I didn't drink a lot.
- Seon Yoong was...
- It's Seon Myung.
- Seon Myung.
- Seon Myung is a picky eater.
- You spent five days with her.
- You went on a trip with her.
- But you don't even know her name.
- Jae Suk.
You know what?
They caught me when I went
through immigration.
- Why?
- Because you don't speak English?
No. I was standing
at the immigration checkpoint.
And they told me to come.
Seon Myung already left,
but I was called
to the investigation room.
And they kept checking
my departure date.
- How long did you stay there?
- Five days.
- You should just say, "Five days."
- I did.
I don't think she didn't know that.
- Just say, "Five days."
- So I wondered...
why they cared so much
about my departure date.
- It turns out...
- Why?
You should write down your departure date
on the immigration form.
I was supposed to write
October 2, 2022.
- But I wrote October 2, 2202.
- My gosh.
Oh, dear.
So they probably thought
something was up with her.
You should've said this.
"I'm sorry."
- "I'm Empty Head."
- Empty.
They seemed very serious.
They kept asking when I'd leave.
"Are you sure you're
going back to Korea?"
They could've thought
it was just a mistake.
- Jae Suk, did you hear the rumor?
- What?
When Seon Myung and So Min...
- went to Singapore...
- Of course, I did.
- Did you hear they went clubbing?
- No.
- Did you go to a club?
- It's a secret.
- People would recognize you.
- Actually,
So Min said she'd bring
some outfits for that.
She brought a dress.
With the low-cut back.
Please.
- Don't do that.
- Then we should have...
So Min and Seon Myung dance
during the opening.
- Hey.
- As if they're in a club?
- The thing is...
- We see her dance all the time.
The thing is...
Actually, I was...
with Suk Jin
when So Min video-called him.
- Right.
- I was right next to him.
So Min was wearing a pretty bikini.
- Stop it!
- No!
- Enough! Stop talking!
- Stop it!
- Hey. Ahn Chang Ho is here.
- But Seon Myung was...
- Dosan Ahn Chang Ho is watching us.
- Her bikini was more revealing.
- Seon Myung...
- Stop talking about Singapore.
Seon Myung's bikini was all strings.
Stop it!
- I don't want to hear it.
- That's enough.
Seriously...
I'm sorry,
but I don't want to hear it.
We have to work together.
I don't need to know
too much about Seon Myung.
Stop talking about Singapore.
- I have one question for you.
- Okay.
What do you think is
the most famous thing in Seoul?
- Mount Nam.
- Seoul Tower and 63 Building.
- Gangnam-daero.
- The 63 Building.
- The 63 Building and Seoul Tower.
- Myeongdong. The Bank of Korea.
- The Han River.
Gangnam Station.
The skyscraper in Jamsil.
Famous restaurants in Hongdae.
- It's 401.
- He means 401.
If you pick only one,
I'll explain the rules.
Where should we go?
I don't want to go far.
Let's pick something close
from here.
- Let's do that.
- Jae Suk.
If we say, Mount Nam,
we'll go there.
A cruise boat.
- If we say, Mount Nam.
- A cruise boat on the Han River.
- Dosan Park.
- Seoul is famous...
- for the Han River.
- Right.
- Most people know the Han River.
- But...
The Han River is famous,
but the symbol
of Seoul is Mount Nam.
It's Mount Nam.
- That's the symbol of Seoul.
- The Seoul Tower on Mount Nam.
- Let's go to Mount Nam.
- The National Assembly Building.
- Taekwon V.
What else, So Min?
The hair salon that did this to you?
It's a famous place, everyone.
The hair salon that made
your bangs look like this.
Let's go there.
- The symbol of Seoul.
- People would want to know.
The symbol of Seoul.
You should visit
the hair salon near Dosan Park.
Hairdresser Lee.
So...
We have Kang Chan Hee here.
Gang Gam Chan, tell us one thing.
Where do you think we should go
when you think of Seoul?
The Seoul Tower.
I think only people of our age
say that.
- Let's ask Generation MZ.
- It feels like...
We should ask young people.
Seoul is where
the 1988 Seoul Olympics took place.
- Jamsil! The hoop boy.
- And there's Hodori.
The 1988 Seoul Olympics.
- Hodori.
- Because...
we have to pick only one thing
that represents Seoul.
Hey, will you stop that?
It's out of date.
- Even I know that.
- Stop doing it.
I'll try this instead.
So are we going to Mount Nam?
One, two, three.
- Mount Nam.
Han River.
All right. You think
the most famous thing in Seoul is...
- the Seoul Tower.
- Yes.
Before I tell you the secret,
I'll explain the rules of the race.
- Race?
- We are having a race today.
Today's race is called...
A Walk Around
the Famous Neighborhood.
That sounds nice.
If you try three different dishes...
before you take
20,000 steps collectively,
you will complete the mission...
and will be allowed
to go home right away.
(Try 3 different dishes before
taking 20,000 steps.)
If the number of steps
exceeds 20,000...
before you try
three different dishes,
you fail the mission,
and you all will get a penalty.
- We should try to walk less.
- How do we do that?
Are you going
to tell us what to eat?
You can eat any dishes you want.
Let's eat pork cutlet there.
Let's eat pork cutlet on Mount Nam.
We should go to Mount Nam
and eat pork cutlet.
(That's simple enough.)
However, before you eat,
you need to go to
a particular neighborhood...
and ask the people
to recommend a menu.
- That's what we did in Okinawa.
- Right.
It's something like that.
(It was the Okinawa Special
aired in April 2017.)
(She asks the driver
to recommend a menu.)
(In the mission
where they needed to hear "steak,")
(they heard something else...)
(and had to eat
the recommended dish.)
(And they ended up eating
noodles five times in a row.)
It's something like that.
- We only got to eat noodles.
- We only ate noodles back then.
This is the question you can ask.
"What's the most famous thing
in this neighborhood?"
- This is easy.
- They will say pork cutlet.
- Definitely.
- This is good.
- And udon.
- If we go to Sinsa-dong...
- Soy sauce marinated crab.
- That's right.
- We can go to Sindang-dong...
- Tteokbokki.
- Right. This is what we should do.
- Right.
If they recommend
a dish or a restaurant,
you can go
to the recommended place and eat.
But if they recommend
a famous place or attraction,
you need to go there
and take a photo.
Then you can ask another citizen
the same question.
I see. If things go wrong,
we'd walk more than 20,000 steps.
If you keep failing to find
someone who recommends food,
you can go to another neighborhood.
But you will have to
move on your own.
- On our own?
- You can either walk,
take a taxi,
or use public transportation.
We don't have a van?
If you get to eat,
we will take you
to your next destination in our van.
- Okay.
- Only when you succeed.
Earlier, you said
the most famous thing in Seoul...
- was Mount Nam.
- Right.
You will put on a pedometer now...
and move to Mount Nam
to start the race.
Should we go to Mount Nam?
Can we check our pedometers
during the race?
- You can check it anytime.
- Can we do that?
- Then we can control it.
- We can do that.
- Sure. It's no big deal.
- Put on the pedometer first.
- Okay.
- Pedometer.
- Are we going to the Seoul Tower?
- I wonder how Man Bok is doing.
The pork cutlet restaurant
is very far from it.
We should go to the entrance.
The pedometer is really big.
I think the count will go up easily.
(The pedometer is in a hip sack.)
This is the pedometer.
- When do we start?
- I think it's there.
- It has begun.
- Can I press it now?
- If I move...
- It's 30 already. I'll reset it.
It's 30 already. I'll reset it.
- Why?
- You can't do that.
- No, I should do this.
- Don't move.
- It should be less.
- Less than 20,000.
It shouldn't be high.
(Ji Hyo already got 85 steps.)
- It shouldn't be high.
- Mine says 66 already.
- It shouldn't go up.
- Mine is 12.
- It starts counting right now.
- It's 66 already.
You can take a taxi or public
transportation to Mount Nam.
- Please begin.
- Okay.
- Do you know how to get there?
- I do.
- We should take a bus first.
- Let's do that.
There's a bus-only lane.
I'll check the bus route.
There is a bus
that goes to Mount Nam.
- Shall we ride the cable car?
- That sounds nice.
The pork cutlet restaurant is
near the cable car station.
You're right. We walk less
if we ride the cable car.
We should walk like this.
- You don't have to do that.
- No, that's weird.
- What's weird?
- It's weird.
- You don't have to do that.
- Not now. When it's close.
- You don't have to try so hard.
- We can do this when it's close.
- You darn brat.
- Jae Suk.
We have to take
two buses to get there.
- Do we have to transfer?
- Yes.
- That sounds cumbersome.
- It takes an hour.
It's a 48-minute route.
- How about we take a taxi?
- Let's do that.
- Let's take a taxi.
- It takes an hour.
- Then let's split into two teams.
- Shall we do that?
- Then 2 teams of 3 and 4 members.
- Let's choose our teams randomly.
Then let's all choose
between a bus and a taxi.
- Which one do you want to take?
- I'll take a taxi.
Gosh, you.
- Let's choose what we want.
- No.
- Why? This is a democratic country.
- Point at the one to take a bus.
- Let's do that.
- Let's pick one person for now.
- One person to take a bus.
- Say, "You take a bus."
- One, two, three.
- You take a bus.
- No! I'm taking a taxi.
- You've been chosen.
Don't push me.
The number keeps going up.
- We should get there quickly.
- Yes.
- So let's all take a taxi.
- Okay.
It might take us too long
if we take a bus.
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
- I should go to the restroom first.
- Haha, no. Stop.
- I'll be right back.
- Hey, where are you going now?
- It's over there.
- You can't go right now.
- It's too far from here.
- Hey.
- Haha.
- Hey!
- Just pee here, you punk.
- Do you want me to pee in the bush?
- No, wait until we get there.
- Gosh.
- What if I need to go on our way?
- Hold it in for a little while.
- Wait until we get there.
- Just hold it in.
You should've gone to the restroom
before the shoot.
I did, but I have to go again.
- He must have prostate problems.
- I guess that's the case.
- Hurry up and come.
- Right.
Why would you assume
that I have prostate problems?
- Just hurry up and come.
- Come back already.
If you go there,
you'll add up to 300 steps.
- We're wasting our time.
- Let's get going already.
Would it be better if I peed myself?
Or...
- Go ahead and pee yourself.
- That'd be better?
- Of course.
- Okay. Fine.
- I'll actually pee myself.
- Yes.
- That'd be crazy.
- Let's get going now.
- We can go now.
- Can we start walking now?
- Let's go.
- We're all walking slowly.
- We're all walking weirdly.
- Like this.
- We're walking awkwardly.
(Dosan Ahn Chang Ho Memorial Hall)
Gosh, it's pouring.
(It started raining more heavily
when they had to leave.)
It's a shame that it's pouring
when we have to move around outside.
You should have pork cutlet
when you go to Mount Nam.
Why does it have to rain? Gosh.
- You said it several times already.
- It's annoying. Just three times.
Do we have masks?
- You're right. We need masks.
- Yes.
- We should wear masks in a taxi.
- We need masks.
We're wasting so much time
trying to hail a taxi.
(On top of the rain, it's a holiday.
So it's hard to catch a taxi.)
What's going on?
Are we leaving now or what?
(Bored)
Today is a holiday, right?
(The staff members can't just wait
for them to leave either.)
It's hard to catch a taxi...
- because of the rain.
- Yes.
So we'll give you a ride
to Mount Nam.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- There aren't any taxis.
- You'll give us a ride?
And it's a holiday.
- Sounds great.
- Oh, today is a holiday.
- Let's go to Mount Nam.
- Sounds great.
- Then please drive us to Mount Nam.
- Okay.
- You can get in now.
- Let's hurry up and get in.
- We should hurry.
- Haha, we're leaving now.
- Right. Jae Suk, you should drive.
- I can drive.
Let's go.
(Driver Yoo will drive.)
- Because it's pouring right now.
- All encounters
- Okay.
- And farewells
We'll use this vehicle
just to get to Mount Nam.
- Yes.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- I wonder why. It's odd.
- What do you mean?
- What's odd?
On rainy days when our show airs,
we get higher ratings.
- That's right.
- True.
- But it rains when we shoot it.
- You're right.
- My point exactly.
- What weird timing.
And it's sunny when it airs.
- Right. It's always sunny.
- It drives us crazy.
- People go on an outing.
- They all go out.
- That's life.
- Lately...
Gosh.
I really want it to stop raining.
I guess it'll be sunny tomorrow
seeing that it's pouring.
It'll be a beautiful, sunny day.
I'll turn on my TV...
You see,
I like Western-style pork cutlets.
- The pork cutlet there is so tasty.
- It's delicious.
- With bread and soup.
- Or udon.
- I like to have it with soup.
- I like it so much.
- I go crazy.
- Right.
I really like it.
- Add some pepper to the soup.
- Jong Kook!
- I like it very much.
- I like it too, Jae Suk.
- I'll have it with the soup.
- I'll have the fish cutlet.
- When I first tried it,
- Me too.
I was surprised by the size.
I'm having the fish cutlet.
- No, don't eat the fish cutlet.
- Why?
- Let's order a combo platter.
- No. Just have regular pork cutlet.
- Let's share it.
- No. Order the regular pork cutlet.
- Why?
- I'll have the cheese pork cutlet.
- Let me eat what I want.
- No. Have the regular pork cutlet.
Should I?
- It's taking me to Seongsu Bridge.
- I'll have a combo platter.
- You should make a left turn.
- I should turn left.
I think someone entered
the wrong destination.
No. You can cross Seongsu Bridge
to get there.
I'll figure it out.
You can go toward Hyatt...
Come on, Suk Jin.
Let me figure it out.
- I'm giving you advice.
- Just stay quiet if you don't know.
- I went to a school in this area.
- Don't butt in if you don't know.
- I'm giving you advice.
- Just stay quiet if you don't know.
- I went to a school in this area.
- Don't butt in if you don't know.
I used to pass by the place
on my way to school every day.
I said not to butt in
if you didn't know anything.
- Observe only Jong Kook.
- I went to Mount Nam...
- He speaks only when Suk Jin does.
- so many times.
- Suk Jin.
- I can see it from my house.
- Suk Jin, don't butt in.
- I can see Mount Nam from my house.
- Just be quiet if you don't know.
- Right. Don't butt in.
- Why do you keep butting in?
- You can go straight.
- Jae Suk knows what he's doing.
- Exactly.
- Just worry about the World Cup.
- Right.
The GPS is telling you to go...
Assist him since you're sitting
in the front seat.
Gosh, seriously.
- Like an assistant. Assistant Ji.
- I can't believe you guys.
You're sitting in the front seat.
- Assist him as the MC's aide.
- Assist him?
- Not an assistant, but an aide.
- The MC's aide.
- We shouldn't go up there, right?
- Of course.
I just realized...
that you guys are sitting
in the back,
- and we're sitting here.
- The youngest members are here.
- We're young enough to do this.
- Right.
Hey, So Min is considered young
when she's with us,
- Exactly.
- but she is...
I realized
that you guys weren't so young.
- No. We're the youngest here.
- We're still young.
- We're in our late 30s.
- You guys are old.
- Hey, you guys are quite old.
- That's right.
Se Chan is treated like a teacher
on "Comedy Big League."
- Yes. He's like a school teacher.
- No. He...
- They'll turn 40 soon.
- That's right.
You're right. We'll turn 40 soon.
But we're the youngest here.
Yes, we are.
The youngest members are almost 40.
Jae Suk, I'm 42.
- I know that.
- Of course, we all know that.
Ji Hyo, you're the same age
as my wife Kyung Eun.
Yes, I am.
- Really?
- If you think about that... Yes.
(The youngest members are not
so young anymore.)
Suk Jin is... I mean...
- I attended a wedding recently.
- Yes.
I found out that Suk Jin was
older than Kim Kwang Kyu.
- You're lying. Really?
- Yes, it's true.
- He came on this show before.
- Right, he did.
- But I didn't know that.
- He came on the show.
I realized this once again that day.
Jae Suk and I have worked together
at so many weddings.
- At a lot of weddings.
- True.
- Do they have good chemistry?
- Jae Suk hosts, and he sings.
- Jong Kook and I...
- They come in a set.
- sang at and hosted...
- A lot of weddings.
the weddings
of many producers and writers.
And Suk Jin performed
his signature Oswa Dance...
- at all of those weddings.
- Yes, he did.
- His dance...
- Hey.
- Stop making me do that.
- He does that...
- all the time.
- It's included in the package...
for weddings
of the employees of SBS.
Oswa!
(This is the footage of him
performing the Oswa Dance.)
Oswa for love!
(The shamanic dance
to bring blessings)
Oswa for fertility!
They will have
as many children as they want...
- Yes. It's a tradition.
- I do the Oswa Dance...
at any SBS employee's wedding.
It's like touching the nose...
- of a stone statue on Jeju Island.
- Exactly.
- That's what it's like.
- Like a rocking stone.
Then when I get married,
I want Jae Suk...
- to officiate my wedding...
- If he's still healthy enough.
- Get married before he dies.
- You should hurry.
- You never know. Hurry up.
- "Grandpa."
- Hey, So Min.
- Yes?
Of course, we'd do it for you
when you get married.
I want him to officiate it
and you to host it.
- You want me to host your wedding?
- Yes, host my wedding.
Then can Haha and I be
your bridesmaids?
- Sorry?
- Is it called a floral kid?
- Yes. A flower child.
- A floral kid.
- Is it "flower child?"
- My gosh. What's "floral kid?"
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, right. It's "flower child."
- Gosh. He said "floral kid."
- What was that?
- You know...
- When I said that, Ji Hyo said,
- You drive me crazy.
- "Right. A floral kid."
- A floral kid.
- Well, it doesn't matter...
- A flower child.
since we all understood.
- That day,
- My gosh.
- Haha's daughter impressed me.
- That's cute.
- I see.
- Song Yi. Didn't you see her?
- She looked gorgeous.
- I was busy hosting the wedding.
- She can make facial expressions...
- She's so cute.
that suit different types of music.
Each of the members had a photo
taken with Song Yi.
As she walked toward Suk Jin,
she said,
- "Grandpa."
- "Grandpa is here."
- Hey, she didn't say that.
Why are you lying?
- She whispered.
- I kind of talked her into it,
- She did say that. "Grandpa."
- but she actually said it.
- You guys called me a grandpa.
- She called you that.
Come on.
And Suk Jin liked it
when she called him that.
- Before that...
- Song Yi likes elderly people.
Suk Jin, I think
you should let her call you that.
- She made me want a daughter.
- Right?
- Having a daughter is different.
- Right. That's true.
That thought crossed my mind.
It's like a comic book.
- So Min.
- Yes?
Your father came home early
to see you, right?
- She looked cute as a little girl.
- Of course, he did.
- Right?
- My dad adored me so much.
- Right? You did a cute act...
- So Min was so cute.
When did it become awkward
between you and your father?
I think it was
when I was in elementary school.
- When you were in sixth grade?
- Really? Darn it.
- That was so early.
- Didn't it happen too early?
My dad isn't the type...
that shows his affection often
as you guys do.
- Is he blunt?
- Yes, he's blunt.
I'm not the type
that shows his affection often,
- but I do it to my kids.
- You do that, right?
- I do it often.
- To your son too?
- I don't think he does.
- Ji Ho? I did when he was little.
- What about now?
- He's not a baby anymore.
- Now...
- If he's treated like a baby,
- he would get upset.
- He seems to nag you a lot.
- Right. He nags Jae Suk a lot.
- He wouldn't get upset, but...
Ji Ho seemed to be really something.
He's really something.
- Ji Ho...
- He can be a match for Jae Suk.
Ji Ho is famous for being polite
in our apartment complex.
- That's right.
- Oh, he's popular.
- Jae Suk, I heard...
- That's nice.
Ji Ho greeted your acquaintances
at the beauty parlor too.
- Yes, that's true.
- I've met him, Jae Suk.
He's very polite. That's right.
- Se Chan has seen him.
- Did you teach him to be polite?
Se Chan,
do you go to a beauty parlor?
- Come on, Haha. Of course, I do.
- Hold on.
- What?
- You go to a beauty parlor?
- Yes, I do, Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- Chae Young cuts your hair, right?
- I work with a hairstylist.
- It's Chae Young, right?
- Did she put a bowl over your head?
A bowl?
We're here.
Let's ride the cable car here.
- Okay. Then we'll stop here.
- Right. Keep going this way.
- Suk Jin, see? I took you all...
- Yes?
to the right place without a hitch.
I could find my way here easily too.
- It was so quick, Jae Suk.
- Here...
- I could...
- Right?
- It was smooth.
- I mean, I'm in the back.
Anyone would take the same route.
It's not just you.
No. You told him
to take a different route earlier.
- You could move backward.
- He reacted.
He never misses a thing
Suk Jin says.
- That's...
- He's like...
- true love.
- the best damage dealer.
(It must be love.)
- You're here for a shoot, right?
- Yes, we are.
He seems so surprised.
(What a surprise.)
He got so startled.
"My goodness. Yoo Jae Suk is here."
(My goodness. Yoo Jae Suk is here.)
He got startled so much.
- Indeed.
- He was shaking like this.
- He almost had a heart attack.
- He got startled so much.
We're here on Mount Nam!
I haven't come here
for almost ten years.
It's so crowded here
since today is a holiday.
This is nice. It's been a while.
- We've arrived at Mount Nam.
- Yes.
As you said Seoul Tower,
take a photo in front of it...
- before you begin.
- Right.
Then should we go up there
to take a photo?
- Can we take a photo here?
- But we can't see the building.
- Gosh. I can't see it from here.
- I want to ride a cable car.
We can take a photo here,
but it's not visible.
- It's totally invisible from here.
- I can't see it.
(Seoul Tower is not visible
from here anyway.)
- Then should we go up there?
- Of course, we should.
- Let's go.
- Who wants to ride a cable car?
Let's not waste our time.
- We can't walk there.
- Really?
- We can't walk...
- I have an idea.
- I think I can walk there.
- How about...
two of us go up there...
while the rest of us wait
at the pork cutlet place?
When I said I could walk up there,
Hyung In chuckled like this.
- She didn't like the idea.
- She didn't want that.
- Most producers would've said,
- Right.
- "Really? That'd be nice too."
But Hyung In chuckled cheerlessly.
- She was afraid you might do it.
- She didn't think you'd do it.
- Let's get going.
- Let's go.
- We should buy tickets first.
- Suk Jin, buy tickets for us.
Okay. That's easy.
I'll buy the tickets.
They'll pay for the tickets.
For seven adults.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Goodbye.
- Jae Suk.
- I'd like a cup of coffee.
Jae Suk,
can't we hang a padlock too?
- Oh, my.
- Let's just go.
- He's right. Let's go.
- A padlock?
- You can do it some other time.
- So Min.
- Come back with your boyfriend.
- Let's just go, okay?
- It's not necessary.
- He's right.
But still...
Just to commemorate this moment.
It says we should go
to the platform on the third floor.
- So Min, do it with your boyfriend.
- Shall we take the stairs?
- I want to save this memory. No?
- No.
Oh, the pedometer...
Guys, try to walk lightly.
Don't walk with loud, heavy steps.
Our steps are being counted.
(Suk Jin: 90 steps)
Maybe we should've taken
the elevator. Our steps will go up.
- Haha.
- Yes. I'm almost there.
(Haha: 175 steps)
Haha must have walked
a lot of steps.
- It's unbelievable.
- It's one floor above us.
It's a lot of steps. Is this okay?
We should've taken the elevator.
- Right, we should have.
- Oh, our steps are being counted.
We should've taken the elevator.
Suk Jin, I don't think
we'll take more than 20,000 steps.
- We won't, right?
- Because this is...
- It's been a long time.
- I've never ridden it in the rain.
I haven't ridden it
in the rain either.
I haven't ridden a cable car
in almost ten years.
When you get up there,
take a photo and ask,
- "What's most famous around here?"
- We can ask the question, right?
- We should say the exact words.
- Oh, I see.
But it's okay for us
to say something like this, right?
"We've arrived at Seoul Tower."
- Yes. That's good.
- What's wrong?
- It's time...
- Exactly.
- We can say that much, right?
- It's time...
- Are we allowed to say this?
- I mean, it's afternoon.
- "I'm hungry." Is that allowed?
- It doesn't matter because...
I'm sure we're allowed to say this.
"Oh, perfect timing."
- "It's almost noon..."
- "It's time for lunch."
- No, that's not allowed.
- Really?
- Why not?
- "It's time for lunch." No?
(All sorts of petty tricks are not
allowed.)
How about we ask the question...
to just one person over there
for practice?
- For practice?
- Good. Go ahead and try it.
- I'll give it a try.
- Okay. For practice.
- That will be helpful.
- Right, Ji Hyo.
- That's a great idea.
- You know the exact words, right?
- "What is most famous..."
- That's great. I like that.
"on Mount Nam?"
Excuse me. I'm asking you this
purely out of curiosity.
You can tell me
what pops into your head.
What is most famous on Mount Nam?
Well, pork cutlet is very famous.
(- What's most famous on Mount Nam?
- Well, pork cutlet is very famous.)
(She heard "pork cutlet"
at her first attempt.)
- Oh, yes.
- He must've said it.
She asked for a high five.
I think he gave her the answer
she wanted.
- Hello.
May I ask you a question?
What is most famous on Mount Nam?
- Pork cutlet.
- Giant pork cutlet.
Thank you.
(Her second attempt was
successful too.)
Thank you.
(Reporter Song Ji Hyo did
a great job.)
- That's impressive.
- She's as good a reporter.
She's good at interviewing people.
- She's good enough to be one.
- I'm impressed.
- I've never seen her like this.
- She has talent.
- Ji Hyo, what did they say?
- How did it go?
At least ten people said,
"pork cutlet."
- That's great.
- It's true.
- We'll pull it off.
- That's great.
Okay. Great job.
I'm sure
we'll get to have pork cutlet.
- I'm glad.
- But we always fail...
when the game begins.
You know I'm from the streets.
Don't worry.
- You're from the streets?
- I can tell.
- You just admitted it.
- Sorry?
- You admitted it.
- He's from the streets.
I'm from the streets.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
What did you say?
How many people did you ask?
- Okay.
- I asked about ten people.
- Ten? They all chose pork cutlet?
- Here we go.
- Yes, they all did.
- That's awesome.
- And they did this.
- I see.
- I didn't realize that.
- Oh, my. It's moving.
- Here we go.
- It's moving. My gosh. I haven't...
(The unusual scenery on a rainy day
outside the window)
My gosh. How many years has it been
since I last rode a cable car?
You already said
it had been ten years.
- Did you hear that?
- Of course, I heard it.
Hey, they might edit that part out.
It's magnificent.
This reminds me
of a rainy autumn day...
This is nice.
when I was in school.
Did you go to a school in this area?
- I came here very often back then.
- I see.
I rode the cable car here
with three of my ex-boyfriends.
I think I rode it three times.
(She shares her old memories.)
- Did you lie you'd never come here?
- Of course.
There are three padlocks
that I hung here.
- You hung three padlocks?
- Yes, three.
- I hung just one.
- She hung three padlocks here.
She pretended it was
her first time here every time?
Can't you find them?
It's because you throw the key away
after hanging it.
- I see.
- Isn't that a scam?
- This is so nice.
- What did you say when you arrived?
- "Oh, my. What is this?"
- Sorry?
No. "Oh, my. I've never ridden this
before. It's so beautiful."
- You did that three times?
- Some of the guys...
probably tied the key with a string
before throwing the key...
- It's moving fast.
- so that they could get it back.
(The cable car in the rain starts
moving faster.)
- Gosh. Why is it moving so fast?
- I've never ridden it in the rain.
- It's beautiful.
- I'm anxious.
We're going right into the fog.
It feels like
we're in "Jurassic Park."
- Gosh.
- Come on.
- Look out the window. Look at that.
- My gosh.
("Jurassic Park"
in Yongsan-gu, Seoul)
- Look at the forest.
- "Jurassic Park," my foot.
- That's ridiculous.
- "Jurassic Park."
- We're on Mount Nam.
- I mean...
- Look at those autumn leaves.
- We're in Yongsan-gu.
- Finally.
- It's beautiful.
We'll be able to see the tower
when we get there, right?
- Yes, I'm sure of it.
- Maybe not the top of it.
- Anyway,
- Yes?
we have to take a photo
in front of the tower...
and ask the question.
- Here...
- How about a cup of coffee?
- Sounds great. I'll treat you all.
- Look at that.
And if you go up, there's a place
where the floor rotates.
- What place is that?
- The rotating restaurant.
- Yes, the rotating restaurant.
- But it's too expensive.
They copied the rotating lounge...
at the Westin Bonaventure Hotel
in Los Angeles.
- Come on, Jong Kook.
- That's not true.
How do you know
who came up with the idea first?
He talks about Los Angeles
all the time.
Why would you talk
about Los Angeles?
It suddenly crossed my mind.
That's all.
Jong Kook is so nice.
Since I complained, he said,
- Yes, of course.
- "It suddenly crossed my mind."
- You brat.
- I know.
- I must say, he's so gentle.
- Yes, I am.
I must listen to you.
- He's so gentle.
- I respect your opinion.
He couldn't be more gentle.
- Even a wild beast can be tamed.
- That's right.
- He's really meek.
- You're so adorable.
His attitude changed completely...
after you appeared in a video
on his YouTube channel.
He's so meek.
Right after your appearance
on his YouTube channel.
Whatever I say to Jong Kook,
he says yes.
- We're here.
- Let's go.
We're here.
I really love this place.
Hello.
- Hello.
- I wish you all happiness.
Why is he acting like that suddenly?
- Look at the fog.
- I see a lot of elderly people too.
The fog makes the scenery beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Let's breathe in some phytoncide.
- Right, phytoncide.
- Oh, my.
- It's beautiful.
- The trees in the fog...
- The fog looks magnificent.
- How beautiful.
- Look over there.
- It's so beautiful.
- There're a lot of stairs here.
- It's no joke.
- It's incredible.
- I love this scent.
- It's so nice.
- My lungs feel refreshed already.
Why didn't you guys come here often
to enjoy this scenery?
- You should come here more often.
- You said it'd been ten years.
- It looks beautiful in the rain.
- Exactly.
- I've never seen it like this.
- The rain creates a mystical vibe.
- So Min, isn't this your padlock?
- No.
- It says "So Min and Min Jun."
No?
Mine is up there.
I hope we can see the tower.
- You fail if you can't see it.
- We fail?
- Why? You didn't say that before.
- Hey, don't say such a thing.
- That's not fair.
- It'll be visible if we get closer.
- There's a photo spot here.
- Of course, it's visible.
- Hyung In.
- Yes?
Can we have a cup of coffee here?
- No.
- Don't be so strict.
- Why can't we? We'll pay for it.
- There's fish cake over there.
- Of course, we can't eat...
- Fish cake.
anything but the three dishes.
Hey, can you give me an umbrella?
Hold on.
(It starts raining heavily.)
Hey, can you... An umbrella...
He returned his umbrella
saying he wouldn't need it.
- An umbrella...
- Don't give him an umbrella.
- Jae Suk, we can eat here too.
- Come on.
- Sorry?
- They serve pork cutlet too.
- Really?
- Let's eat here.
- They have the owl pork cutlet too.
- It's closer to the tower.
- Like the place in Hongdae?
- Yes. It's written in there.
(They're fighting for an umbrella
in the rain.)
Hey, did you walk
all the way up here?
Yes. I mean, no. I rode a cable car.
I see.
- You got rained on, kid.
- You're soaking wet.
Really?
- Yes.
- Kids find it fun to get rained on.
Kids these days are so friendly
and good with words.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- I wish you happiness.
- Thank you.
- It's nice to see you.
- I'm a fan of yours.
She said hello to Jae Suk,
but Suk Jin said hello back to her.
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hey.
- I have a lot of good memories.
- I can't see it.
- Haha, so do I.
- Me too.
- I see the pavilion.
- I can't see it.
- And Suk Jin...
- Can I say just one thing?
- What is it?
Please don't say hello
to people when they don't seem...
- excited to see you.
- And don't drop the honorifics...
when you say hello
to middle-aged ladies.
- He's right. That's rude.
- "Hey, hi."
- When did I say, "Hey, hi?"
- You said that.
You said that to a middle-aged lady.
(Hello.)
(Hi.)
(He did it for sure.)
(They managed to come up
after many twists and turns.)
- Guys, it's still invisible.
- I can't see it.
We'll be in trouble.
I can't see it at all.
I'm sure we can see it.
- Oh, I can see it, Suk Jin.
- I can see it too.
- I can see it.
- I can see it. It's over there.
Yes, I can see it.
- I can't see the top of it though.
- It's not visible.
- I'm worried.
- It's really tall. This is it.
- I can't see the top of it.
Now, you can see it, right?
- Let's take a photo here.
- We can take it from a low angle.
Would it be visible?
It's slightly visible.
- Let's take a photo first.
- What's that?
- We should take it here.
- Right. It's visible from here.
It's slightly visible from here.
- Let's stand here.
- What's that? I mean...
- I think it's from a high angle.
- You can say it's visible.
Of course,
it should be considered visible.
To be honest, I don't see anything.
I don't.
- Just the tip of the feet...
- So Min.
- Can you not go off on your own?
- Exactly.
What's wrong with you?
- Let's take a photo.
- What does she even talk about?
Let's lower our umbrellas
for the shot.
- I can see it.
- Right.
- It's there.
- I see it. Hurry.
- Right.
- Who's going to take it?
I can see it.
- Really?
- You can see it.
- Hurry.
- Who's going to take it?
(The fog clears
and the tower is visible.)
- Hurry.
- Who's going to take it?
- Who'll take it?
- I can see it.
- The staff...
- You're blocking us.
- Over there.
- Who'll take it?
- I can see it.
- Who's going to take it?
(He suddenly acts weirdly.)
Who'll take it?
Shouldn't it be one of us?
- There.
- Hyung In's taking it.
- Will Hyung In take it?
- We should take a selfie.
- What will it be?
- Right?
- The MZ pose?
- Let me have it.
Suk Jin, you're the worst
at taking selfies.
- What's the matter with you?
- Seriously?
- To splash water.
- Stop joking around.
- You can see the tower.
- There it is.
- Get in the shot.
- Lower it.
- Can you see it?
- Should I rotate it?
- No.
- Yes, like that.
- You can see it.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Nice.
- It's good.
- Okay.
- Let me see that.
Gosh, that was hard.
- It's good.
- Let me see that.
(They hand in the photo
of them at Seoul Tower.)
It's right there in the photo.
- We took the shot.
- That's a success.
All right. Who should we ask next?
I think I smell pork cutlet.
Who should ask the question?
(They must ask the question
to another citizen.)
Jae Suk, how about this?
Jae Suk.
Let's ask the question
at a pork cutlet restaurant.
Don't you think that's a dirty move?
Of course.
"What's most famous at Mount Nam?"
That's all we can ask.
- Right.
- I met a fan earlier.
Let's go with someone older.
- How about a family?
- A mother and daughter.
- Someone who's with family.
- A father and daughter.
- I see a family ahead.
- Over there.
- Hold on.
- Who?
- Are families better?
- Have we made a choice?
- Yes, a family.
They'll definitely
grab a bite to eat.
- Over here.
- Goodness.
- Hello.
- Over here.
- We want to ask you a question.
Can we ask you something?
- Hi.
- The both of us?
- Sure.
- You can answer us instead.
Who's going to ask her?
Jae Suk, go ahead.
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
(What's most famous at Mount Nam?)
(Jae Suk musters up the courage
and asks the question.)
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
(Will they say "pork cutlet"
like the others did...)
(during the practice round?)
(Anxious)
(What's most famous at Mount Nam?)
What do you think?
The padlocks.
(What's most famous at Mount Nam?
The padlocks)
So that's what we'll be doing.
(They'll be securing padlocks
at Mount Nam.)
The padlocks.
(Jae Suk's first attempt
is a failure.)
So that's what we'll be doing.
- That padlocks.
- Let's hurry.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Bye.
- Take care.
- Let's take a photo of it.
- Jae Suk, wait.
You have to take photos
in front of the padlocks.
We'll take a photo of those.
There are a lot of them up there.
- I'm glad they're close by.
- They're up there.
- Let's not be serious about it.
- Exactly.
- So...
- Keep it casual.
Us being serious
is why they answered us seriously.
- Right.
- We should keep it casual.
"What's most famous at Mount Nam?"
"Gosh, I'm hungry."
- That's not allowed.
- No?
Why isn't anything allowed?
We can't even say we're walking.
Nothing's allowed.
- Here are the padlocks.
- Let's take a photo.
(They walk to the padlocks while
adding steps to the pedometer.)
Still... Here they are.
Let's take a photo.
Gosh. Look at all of these.
We have these many couples in Korea?
- Se Chan.
- All these couples...
(Walking around meaninglessly
adds steps to their pedometers.)
So many couples loved
and fell out of love.
Let's hurry and take a photo.
We took one
during our second episode.
- That's right.
- Really?
- Did we?
- Get in the shot.
Get in here.
- The padlocks should show.
- Over here.
Let them show.
Why on earth are you doing that?
(He's at it again.)
Just take the photo, Jae Suk.
I'm trying to splash Hyung In.
- The padlocks.
- One...
- I can see them now.
- In 1, 2, 3.
In 2, 3.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Let's go.
- We did it.
You succeeded in taking
the selfie with the padlocks.
Please go ahead
and ask the question again.
- Let's not be serious about it.
- We'll be nonchalant.
- Why don't I ask?
- Sure thing.
Hey!
- Hi, kids.
- It's good to see you.
(Haha moves swiftly
to nonchalantly drop the question.)
It's nice to see you.
- Do you know us?
- I do.
We're from Running Man.
Your favorite TV show.
All right.
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
(After breaking the ice,
he drops the official question.)
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
(Will they hear
"pork cutlet" this time?)
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
The padlocks at the Seoul Tower.
- We already took photos of it.
- All right.
The padlocks. That means you failed.
The padlocks.
Please take another photo.
What's wrong with you?
What's the matter with you?
- What's your issue?
- What's the matter with you?
You pressure the kid too much.
Why...
- You pressured the kid.
- Why burden the boy?
- Haha.
- You did great.
- Let me ask the question.
- We'll take another photo.
Kids their age don't know you.
(Kids their age don't know you.)
- Let's take a photo.
- But he's a celebrity of 30 years.
- Take the photo.
- Over here, guys.
- Over here.
- Two!
- Three.
- One...
In 1, 2, 3.
(How many photos will they take
before this is over?)
- Okay.
- Are we all in it?
I'll ask this time around.
You asked the last time,
- so let me ask instead.
- Sure, go ahead.
- Try someone young.
- How about that kid?
- Yes, him.
- All right.
He seems to be a fan.
- He wants to talk to us.
- Would you like to talk with us?
- Sorry?
- He's leaving.
Would you like to...
Would you like to talk to us?
- Sorry?
- He's leaving.
Would you like to...
- He has his hand up.
- Over there.
The kid has his hand up.
- Yes, over there.
- That kid.
- Suk Jin.
- Hold on.
Would you like to...
(He's the only one
who hasn't spotted the kid.)
Excuse me.
He has his hand up.
The kid has his hand up.
- Yes, over there.
- That kid.
- Suk Jin.
- Could you join us?
Sure thing.
- He's the worst at interviews.
- He's so bad at this.
I know from experience.
He's terrible at this.
- Hello.
- At Mount Nam...
- Yes?
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
- At Mount Nam...
- Yes?
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
(What's most famous at Mount Nam?)
(What will be said by the man
Suk Jin invited over?)
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
The Seoul Tower.
- Gosh.
- I see. Thank you.
Suk Jin, come on.
(They got
the Seoul Tower this time.)
I see. Thank you.
You must head to the Seoul Tower.
- Come on.
- The kid has his hand up.
How many photos must we take?
Take one.
- We can take one right now.
- Just a second.
Can you wait for us?
We need to be inside the tower.
- We have to get up there.
- The tower?
Earlier, why...
(Jae Suk heads forward
to purchase tickets.)
Seven adults, please.
- Seven?
- Yes.
- Seven tickets?
- That's right.
(He's trying to pay
for seven people.)
That'll be 112 dollars.
Did you say 112 dollars?
Why did you ask that way?
Can you pay it with your phone?
- People won't say pork cutlet.
- Got it.
(Jae Suk makes
the unexpected purchase.)
- This...
- It's 112 dollars.
- But that's cheating. What is it?
- I paid 112 dollars.
- What?
It costs 112 dollars
for seven adults.
- Is it that expensive?
- For seven adults.
- We won't be able to see anything.
- We'll come right back down.
- It's fine.
- Did you purchase the tickets?
- Did you say 112 dollars?
- That's what it cost.
For seven adults?
Hurry, will you?
We're walking way too much.
- And I'm starving.
- What is my pedometer at?
I'm at 900.
Mine is already at 900.
(Suk Jin past the 900 mark.)
What was that?
- My pedometer is already at 900.
- This is bad.
Suk Jin, this is all on you.
It'll be too foggy to see anything.
We'll add a lot of steps
once we reach the observatory.
Check out the Seoul Tower.
(They enter the Seoul Tower.)
Is there a restaurant here?
No, just the observatory and a cafe.
- I can't see a thing.
- You can't when it's foggy.
What on earth is this?
How can we take a photo here?
I thought screens
had been pulled down.
I can't see a thing.
We're at Seoul Tower,
so take the photo.
Hurry and take the photo.
- We all need to be in it.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(At an observatory with no view)
- Okay.
- Let's ask the couple over there.
No, slow down.
- We need to take this seriously.
- Hey.
- Gather around.
- Let's not...
- pressure the people.
- Don't rush this.
Jae Suk, let's keep it casual...
and go to them at once.
No, we'll stay here.
- Right.
- Approach them by yourself.
- But here...
- "What's most famous at Mount Nam?"
I doubt we'll hear
what we want though.
Are you okay with that couple?
Go ahead. I have
a good feeling about this.
I'm sure they're going
to grab a bite to eat next.
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
(He approaches them casually
not to intimidate them.)
What's most famous at Mount Nam?
- Pork cutlet.
- Okay!
Okay!
(Someone finally said pork cutlet.)
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
This is insane.
Nice and casual.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- You're our savior.
- The pork cutlet.
Someone said pork cutlet,
so you may go ahead and eat it.
- Pork cutlet.
- Let's go.
- My friend.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
- No way.
Just casually
dropping the question...
We got the answer
by keeping it casual.
- That's how we got the answer.
- Se Chan.
That was fast of you.
Why don't we grab some coffee
while we wait?
Hyung In, can we get some coffee?
Sure thing. Go ahead.
(They take a break
while waiting for their coffee.)
Seven iced Americano, please.
- Seven?
- Yes.
What's this? Come over here.
What is this?
This must be new.
- What is it?
- It must be new.
- Time capsules.
- What is this?
- Time capsules?
- They have time capsules now?
- Does it last a year?
- This is nice.
You probably get to open it
when you want to.
(So Min's pedometer)
Se Chan...
Jong Kook, check that out.
Today's mission isn't an easy one.
Those over there are time capsules.
Putting an engagement ring there
and proposing later on...
- I'm intrigued.
- Imagine proposing to someone...
two or three years later
after placing a ring in there.
It would mean a lot.
This is fascinating.
What if I placed a gift
for my wife here?
She'd love it.
(So Min is a very curious child.)
I want to sit next to you.
(It already exceeded 1,800.)
It's so hard to eat three meals.
It's going to be hard
to eat three meals.
- Let's have pork cutlet quickly.
- That's so pretty.
Let's check the pedometer.
It's 582 for me.
(This is a normal range.)
It's 582.
Oh, no. I'm in trouble.
Oh, no. It's 1,872.
Why did you walk around so much?
- Why is it so high?
- Look how much you got.
It's delicious.
The coffee is good too.
- The coffee is so good.
- The atmosphere is also good.
It's raining harder.
(They're going to a pork cutlet
restaurant in the pouring rain.)
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
During 13 years
of doing Running Man with you...
Isn't it the first time
being this kind?
What?
Kindly sharing an umbrella
like this.
Yes. I think it's the first time
to share an umbrella like this.
It'll become sweet memories.
I know.
Come here, So Min.
I don't mind getting rained on.
I'm wearing a raincoat.
It's a sentimental day.
(To you, I)
(Like a sunset glow)
- Become
- Sing a random song about rain. Go.
- A beautiful memory
(When it rains)
(And the song plays)
(They became sentimental
and excited in the pouring rain.)
Hello.
(They're soaked with the sudden rain,
but they're just excited.)
It's raining heavily.
This is serious.
- You worked hard.
- Yes.
(They're going to take a cable car
to go down and walk.)
I'm completely soaked.
Hear the sound.
Pork cutlet would be so delicious.
- In this chilly weather.
- Pork cutlet after this...
would be crazy.
Having soup after some noodles...
- With black pepper.
- But...
- I want to have soup.
- you can't eat too much.
We should eat two meals in a row.
- No. I'll eat a lot.
- Me too.
Because I'm in a rush.
My stomach is...
What did you write? "Running Man?"
- Can you see it?
- Of course.
Why would I not be able to see that?
- I can see it well.
- You have bad eyesight.
- My eyesight is better than yours.
- Suk Jin has great eyesight.
You can just say yours is good.
Don't say it's better than hers.
- These glasses don't have lenses.
- It would hurt her feelings.
- You don't have to compare.
- Right.
How is your eyesight?
It's 1.2 and 0.9.
He has to have good eyesight at least.
Everything else is bad.
How do you know
everything else is bad?
- I'm perfectly healthy.
- I can just tell.
This is not a joke.
- Why?
- You are always arguing.
- I...
- You're always arguing...
- with someone.
- How do you know?
I'm going to make a content soon.
"I'm Going To Beat Up
Kim Jong Kook." That's the title.
Kim Jong Kook."
- When?
- I got a content material too then.
"It Was Self-Defense."
(Kim Jong Kook, Ji Suk Jin)
That would be it.
- Don't do that.
- Then I'll be a commentator.
- A commentator.
- I'll be a commentator.
- Is it okay to finish real quick?
- It's okay.
I'll try to film enough content.
All right.
Grabbing and shaking.
- Let's walk. The rain is not heavy.
- Pork cutlet.
It won't take long.
I often came here
when I was a student.
- You must have memories.
- Hello.
- You must have memories. Hello.
- So many memories.
I don't get to walk that much
if it weren't for a shoot.
You?
- Isn't it the same for you?
- I walk a lot.
Do you like walking?
Yes. I won't have
many chances to exercise otherwise.
- I should walk at least.
- Right.
I walk a lot too.
I walk for four hours.
You do? You just said
you don't get to walk that much.
- I do on some days.
- Which one is true?
What's your true side?
- When I walk, I walk a lot.
- When will you show it to me?
When will we get close?
Suk Jin lies too often.
What on earth is the truth?
- What do you mean?
- Suk Jin...
What he said today and what he'll
say tomorrow are different.
He can't say something contradictory
to what he said five minutes ago.
You should check the pedometer.
- I'm in trouble.
- It's so...
That's why they found a restaurant
that is far. It's the pedometer.
Oh, no.
- Why?
- It's 3,050.
What?
- It's 4,000?
- It's 3,050.
Why is it so high?
Were you shaking while walking?
Why is it so high for me?
- I've been here.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Udon.
- It's wet.
- Let's share it.
- It's soup.
(The soup will warm them up
after being soaked in the rain.)
It's the soup
you were talking about.
Right. This is the soup
I was talking about.
Thank you for the food.
(The appetizer soup at a casual
Western restaurant is great.)
Thank you.
This is it.
Black pepper.
Did you order udon too?
- Yes.
- It's so good.
(They're having soup sprinkled
with pepper after a long time.)
- Isn't it good?
- Yes.
This is it.
- You should have bread rolls too.
- It's so good.
- Should I remove this?
- I...
So Min, you look so pretty.
Soaked in the rain...
You look so...
- That's unusual for you to say it.
- Your bangs are wet and stuck.
It's actually better...
(Laughing)
That's cute.
So Min, you're the prettiest now.
You look good.
- You look good.
- It's the best.
- We're amazing guys.
You look good now.
Good for you, So Min.
She's making it entertaining
with her hair.
She's trying her best for the show.
Gosh. I should cut my bangs again
if I want to make people laugh.
- What?
- I should cut my bangs again...
- when I want to make people laugh.
- No. It's perfect now.
- You look the funniest now.
- I'm good.
- "You look the funniest."
Ji Hyo and you look almost
equally funny with your hair.
It would be delicious.
We're hungry for real.
But we should have three meals.
Don't we have to restrain ourselves?
- But...
- You can't do that.
- We came to have nice food here.
- We should eat three meals though.
- You punk.
- We should've shared.
When did we ever plan
for our future?
Or instead of something heavy,
- should we have...
- Okay.
- Like a dessert?
- Like a dessert.
- That sounds good.
- Yes.
If you go to Ikseon-dong,
the cakes are amazing.
- Ikseon-dong?
- At small bakeries and cafes.
If you go there, it's usually...
I think you should keep it down.
Yes. Speak quietly.
Keep it down.
- They don't even care about us.
- Suk Jin, please.
This is quiet.
Yeppi.
Yappi.
- Kongsuni.
- Gosh, he's so...
- How about the corndog?
This is the corndog.
He's a trendy grandpa.
I'm very trendy.
- A trendy grandpa.
- Something like this.
But in my opinion,
it's so cool that Suk Jin
tries to keep up with the trend.
- It's cool.
- And...
that's how he's getting old
in a trendy way.
It's so cool.
My grandpa died like that too.
What's wrong with that?
- Right.
- As long as it makes him happy.
It makes him happy.
I'm confident that I'm
the trendiest guy in his 50s.
- Right.
- I acknowledge that.
I acknowledge that too.
Here it comes.
It's here.
- It's the giant pork cutlet.
- Giant pork cutlet.
Look at the steam.
It's so...
I can already feel the crispiness.
The cheese is insane.
- Gosh.
- Pork cutlet.
It's been a very long time.
Look at the steam.
For me, it's cheese.
I can already feel the crispiness.
She likes cheese.
Yes.
- Eat.
- My gosh.
I'll eat after you guys
because I'm the youngest.
It's more delicious
as we were desperate.
It's not a joke. It's so good
as we were desperate for food.
(They were desperate for Namsan
giant pork cutlet more than ever.)
(They're gobbling their first meal
as they're relaxed now.)
- Oh, my goodness.
- Gosh.
It's so good.
At what age will I stop liking
pork cutlet?
I still like it so much.
Old men usually
don't like cheesy pork cutlet.
Right. I want to know. At what age
will I stop liking pork cutlet?
But we're in trouble.
How can we have three meals?
I had breakfast,
but this is still so good.
We should have something delicious
that has a small portion next.
Let's move to the next spot.
- I enjoyed the food.
- Here we go again.
Where are you going?
I ate so much. I'm worried
about the next meal.
We can't have food
for the next mission.
Why is it yours so high though?
- What do you mean?
- Walk slowly.
It's not about walking slowly.
- Hey.
- Are you taking small steps?
No.
- It's over 3,000.
- Why is it so high?
Jong Kook. It's not
that I'm taking small steps.
- Why is it so high?
- Seriously.
It's because I like moving around.
That's true.
It's over 3,000 for So Min as well.
- Jeon So Man.
- Why is it over 3,000 for me?
- So Man.
- Why is it over 3,000 for you?
I think my heart is beating fast.
What does it have to do
with your heart rate?
Everyone,
be careful with your steps.
You be careful.
Gosh.
- It's 1,600 for me.
- I mean...
It's different.
You're just unable to walk a lot.
What are we going to eat now?
I can't eat. I'm full.
The staff members picked one for us.
- They picked the area.
- We didn't choose it.
Yes. If we could choose, we could
have tteokbokki in Sindang-dong.
It'd be nice
if it's a famous area for desserts.
I don't want to go
to Sindang-dong now.
- Tteokbokki?
- That is true.
When I'm this full.
I want to go to Busan.
The seed hotteok in Busan.
It sounds great.
- It sounds great.
- Hotteok sounds nice.
- Right?
- Blueberry hotteok in front of SBS.
That's nice.
- That's in Tanhyeon.
- Tanhyeon.
Going to a famous coffee street
and having coffee would be nice.
- I want some cake.
- I want to have something sweet.
I want some macarons.
Thick macarons.
Suk Jin really
keeps up with the trend.
- He's like a younger generation.
- Why?
People your age
don't talk about macarons.
I like macarons.
I always liked something like that.
- That's awesome.
- I think we're like that.
- What? Because we don't drink.
- Because we don't drink,
- That's why I like it.
- our taste stays the same.
Yes. It's the same.
- Like a child.
- I think that's part of the reason.
Suk Jin looks younger
considering his age...
- because he doesn't drink.
- Because I don't drink.
Right.
- It's definitely a reason.
- Yes. If he were a drinker...
Jong Kook.
- It's nicely said.
- It would be bad.
- Okay. Listen up.
- Listen to him.
- Listen what?
- Jae Suk is talking.
- The grown-up is talking.
- Hey.
- Jae Suk is talking.
- What's up with you two?
- Jae Suk is...
- I'm talking right now.
- You little punks.
- I mean...
We didn't finish talking, old men.
Those in the back row, be quiet.
People around me...
You have a loyal friend.
Jong Kook is docile.
Go ahead.
- Go ahead.
- He's such a nice one.
He settles everything.
You're too nice...
to survive in this harsh world.
A person like me
is unexpectedly nice.
(A kind of worry
they've never heard before)
- Keep going.
- Yes.
Let me tell you this.
Those who drink a lot
look much older.
- Right.
- Those who drink?
- That's true.
- Yes.
- Those who drink less...
- That's true.
- That's really true.
- Their face...
becomes droopy.
- Because the skin gets dry.
- Yes.
- And guys,
- you should have a good sleep.
- He's talking, you punk!
I'm talking.
- Let us talk as well, misters.
- I'm talking.
Does he get paid for this?
- Do you receive a salary?
- He...
- Jong Kook is a nice guy.
- Does he pay you?
- He's docile.
- Why are you doing this?
He's leading the talk.
- He's saying something nice.
- Yes.
- We need to talk about this.
- Yes, we must listen to him.
Jong Kook is almost like
my guardian angel.
You should listen to him
when he initiates his talk.
He changed completely...
right after you made an appearance
on his YouTube channel.
- That's exactly when he changed.
- That's not true.
I've always been this way.
- We're here.
Isn't this Namdaemun?
What's famous here?
What's in this area?
Isn't this Myeongdong?
It's the Sungnyemun Gate area
near Myeongdong.
- It's Namdaemun.
- Oh, it's Namdaemun.
Isn't this area famous
for braised hairtail?
- I'm full though.
- I don't think...
we can have another meal.
We're headed toward
the Sungnyemun Gate area, right?
What are we having near Namdaemun?
I haven't seen Sungnyemun Gate
for a while.
- I've never seen it up-close.
- Really?
It's Namdaemun!
You've completed
your first food mission.
The second spot is Namdaemun.
- It'll be hard.
- We're in trouble.
- We won't be able to find anything.
- We won't find any food here.
- What could we find here?
- We won't be able to find anything.
I'll let you ask
"What's famous near Sungnyemun Gate?"
When we ask that,
they'd say Sungnyemun Gate.
Do we have to keep
taking photos here if we get that?
- Oh, gosh.
- Gosh.
And currently...
Are you planning
not to send us home today?
You've walked 12,000 steps so far.
- We'll be done with it soon.
- You should walk less.
- We need to ask the passersby.
- We could get it at once.
Wouldn't it be better
to ask someone who works here?
Who?
The one standing behind us.
Then they'd recommend
the Sungnyemun Gate right away.
What do you think we should do,
Jong Kook?
I think you should give it
a thought...
and tell us what to do.
- All right.
- They're having a blast together.
- You're good with such decisions.
- He's...
- He's really sharp.
- Right.
You don't need to hear
many people's opinions.
What's wrong with you two?
- You should just decide.
- It's because...
- he's gentle.
- Then just tell us what to do.
- He's gentle.
- Of course.
You might start living with him
if he appears on your channel again.
- You might start dating him.
- He's...
- He's so gentle.
- He's gentle?
He's gentle?
I don't know when Jong Kook
will start dating,
but I can't let him
date just anybody.
I'm serious.
- I'll have to see them first.
- Of course.
He can't just date anyone.
- It's not allowed.
- That's right.
- Let's start asking around.
- Let's do that.
- As long as they mention food.
- Right.
Excuse me.
May we ask you a question?
- Are we starting right away?
- May we ask you a question?
(He goes straight to the person
passing by them.)
- Do you know...
- Wait.
what's the most famous
near Namdaemun?
Wait. He's holding
something delicious.
(Wait. He's holding
something delicious.)
- Do you know...
- Wait.
(Glancing)
(What's the most famous
near Namdaemun?)
- Goodness!
- King-sized dumplings.
King-sized dumplings?
(King-sized dumplings?)
King-sized dumplings!
Really?
- Haha asked if he was holding food.
- Come on.
(The director)
(It doesn't count
because they cheated.)
- Come on.
- You can't say such things.
- Why did you do that?
- Why did you?
Why did he have to act up?
- Where did you get it?
- Near Namdaemun.
Over there?
That's a bummer.
- Hey.
- Just don't cheat.
- Who said it? Was it you?
- Why did you have to add words?
- Why did you ask that?
- Because it looked like food.
I wasn't the one who asked.
Why do you do that?
- You didn't have to add words.
- You did.
No, I didn't. It was Jae Suk.
You should abide by the rules.
Why did you have to run your mouth?
- It was a rare chance.
- This is a variety show!
I had to say something.
We got the answer
that was hard to get.
Since we're on a roll,
let's ask someone else right away.
- Let's go.
- Guys.
If we walk, the number of steps
will increase.
- You're right.
- Let's walk a bit...
toward Sungnyemun Gate.
Let's go.
Guys, let's target those
who are holding plastic bags.
- That's right.
- The one who's holding food.
- We can ask them a question.
- And we could...
look at the bag
when we ask the question.
- We'll look at the bag only.
- We should...
look at the plastic bag.
As we look at the bag,
we could go...
Can you answer this question
as you walk by?
What's the most famous
near Namdaemun?
(Running away)
They ran away.
There's no one around here.
Listen. If people walk by
with food in their hands,
then you should go, "Goodness!"
We can ask them a question.
All right. The staff
would let that much slide.
"Wait a minute. This is..."
(However,)
There's no one around here
to ask a question.
There's no one on the streets.
(the streets are empty
because it's a holiday and raining.)
There's no one around.
- But the thing is,
- Because of the rain.
we must ask anyone who comes by
since it's Namdaemun.
There are so little people
walking around in this area.
I like dumplings, though.
- I love dumplings.
- What's the most famous near here?
It's been a while since we
came out like this...
to shoot on the street.
Shouldn't we ask the question now?
- Should we cross?
- Let's ask the question...
to the people who cross the street.
- There are elders here.
- No.
They're not holding any bags.
Jae Suk.
(Right then...)
(Here he is.
He's holding a plastic bag.)
Here he is.
He's holding a plastic bag.
Over there.
- My gosh, hello.
- Hello.
- Let us ask a question.
- May we ask a question?
What's the most famous
in the Sungnyemun Gate area?
(Their eyes are fixed on the bag.)
(What's the most famous
in the Sungnyemun Gate area?)
The Sungnyemun Gate area?
They sell hotteok over there.
- Hotteok?
- Yes.
- Where?
- Over there.
- This is incredible!
- They sell hotteok over there.
(Hotteok?)
(It's Hotteok!)
No way! I mentioned earlier
that I wanted to have hotteok.
- Thank you so much!
- No way!
No way!
- Thank you.
- He said hotteok.
We... Did you get their hotteok?
No, this is a toast.
- It's a toast?
- Hotteok!
Hotteok!
I mentioned hotteok on the way!
- We mentioned hotteok earlier.
- You completed your mission.
- Hotteok is allowed, right?
- You can go eat hotteok now.
No way. We even mentioned hotteok
on the way.
- This is perfect.
- I want to go to Busan right now.
- I really mentioned seed hotteok.
- It's perfect.
You said you wanted to have
seed hotteok in Busan.
- That's right.
- This is great.
Thank you!
Stay happy!
(Thank you.)
- We're on a roll today.
- This is great.
- It's amazing.
- Let's go.
- Hyung In.
- How did you think of asking...
at that timing?
They're having a blast again.
- You're incredible.
- Good!
I picked him.
- I picked him.
- Well done.
- Hey, the sound of music...
- Move away.
I picked the guy, but Jong Kook
told Jae Suk good job...
for picking him.
Of course.
What happened?
- They're on the same side.
- He's so annoying.
Jong Kook.
It's not that.
- He's just annoying.
- The thing is...
He's so annoying.
You should stay still today.
How is he any gentle?
- He's gentle.
- He's leaning on one leg.
- What?
How so?
- Let's go!
- Let's cross first.
- Us four should hang out.
- Yes. We should do that.
I can't hang out with them.
The young people
should stick with each other.
- That's right.
- You can include me, right?
They'll shoot another show.
They'll shoot a show like
"Grandpas over Flowers."
We haven't filmed the show on the
streets of Seoul for a long while.
- I know.
It'd have been so nice
if it didn't rain.
I love browsing stuff like them.
It looks like fun. Look at that.
(Singing)
- What are you doing?
- Stop walking like that.
(So Min, Jae Suk)
Hey! You'll increase the count!
Oh, right. It'll increase the count.
You two have the highest count.
- Right.
- But it's so exciting.
Mine is half of yours.
Look around, though.
- They're all here to have hotteok.
- She's making hotteok.
So this is where they sell hotteok.
- It's Namdaemun hotteok.
- Here it is.
It's hotteok.
Goodness. It's Namdaemun hotteok.
Gosh, this hotteok is perfect.
Hotteok is famous here.
It's filled with fillings.
It looks so good.
- Se Chan.
- This is the line for hotteok.
Oh, this is the line?
- Is this the line for hotteok?
- This is the line.
We'll be here. Go and get it.
- This is the line for hotteok.
- Is this it?
- We can be standing here.
- This is the line.
Let them go and get it.
Their hotteok is popular.
It's a specialty.
- We get to try Namdaemun's hotteok.
- It must be really famous.
- I know.
- I didn't know...
- hotteok was so famous here.
- Me neither.
Wait. They have vegetable hotteok.
I'll have that.
- I'll have honey hotteok.
- I want to have that too.
- What would you have?
- I'll have half of each.
Four honey hotteok...
- and three vegetable hotteok?
- That's right.
(Singing)
Jae Suk, why did you have to
start singing this song?
- Singing in the rain
- It keeps repeating in my head.
(Jumping)
Don't take small steps.
- Stop taking small steps.
- Don't forget the pedometer.
- When it rains...
- You're too excited.
- Stop it.
- I like it when it rains.
(The grasshopper
is super excited in the rain.)
One, two. Left foot first.
(They can't stay still
like dogs in the rain.)
- They'll complain about our steps.
- Is that so?
Stop moving.
Stop making small steps.
Just stay still.
Why do you two keep moving?
Our step pedometers
have the highest count...
- I'm so excited.
- It can't go over 3,000.
I'm just so excited. What do I do?
- How many steps have you walked?
- Me?
Mine is 2,017.
Mine is 3,187.
- Mine is 2,017.
- Why did you walk so much?
What about you?
- Mine is 1,215.
- You walked so little.
You know how old men
walk in small steps, right?
- You know how grandpas walk?
- Mine is 2,017.
- Foreigners...
- It's not raining anymore.
What?
It's basically stopped raining.
I think it'll start raining again.
Then I can unfold it if it does.
It'll be inconvenient.
- It's not inconvenient at all.
- It's better to just hold it.
- I think this is better.
- Not at all.
If you lean it on your shoulder,
it's really convenient.
- Is that so?
- I can't feel anything.
I am going to go over there.
(Haha feels uncomfortable.)
- I am very comfortable.
- I am very comfortable too.
No one is using an umbrella
except for you.
You are holding it,
but I am resting it on my shoulder.
- It's hanging from my finger.
- I mean...
It's hanging from my finger.
- I am comfortable.
- It's heavy that way.
- No, it isn't
- It's hanging from your finger.
- You shouldn't carry an umbrella...
- When I come back,
- if you find it heavy.
- Suk Jin might be on the floor.
You shouldn't carry an umbrella
if you find it heavy.
- This is more natural.
- It isn't heavy at all.
- He might be on the floor...
- It can hang from any finger.
with flyers on his body.
It can hang from my pinky finger.
- No one is using an umbrella.
- Look. You can lower it like this.
- It's uncomfortable.
- I can put it in my pocket.
- It's hanging from your finger.
- Come on.
- What? Suk Jin!
What?
(Unconscious)
I bet it feels heavy
on your shoulder.
I am carrying it comfortably.
I didn't know
vegetable hotteok was so famous.
I bet it tastes like dumplings.
Fried dumplings.
- Since when was it famous?
- I think...
- it has been famous for 20 years.
- Really?
- Yes. It has been famous for years.
- Why didn't I know that?
It has always been here.
Where are you from?
I am from Paju.
Did you come all the way here
to eat this?
- She is my daughter.
- You are here with your daughter.
- You are nicely dressed.
- He is stylish.
We are the same age.
- Really?
- What?
- He is the same age as Jae Suk.
- He is the same age as me.
- He has the same build too.
He has the same build too.
- He has a nice image.
- Really?
- The two of you look alike.
- He resembles Jae Suk.
I want to look under the mask.
He has similar eyes.
- He is wearing earrings too.
- Don't act like you didn't hear it.
- He hates that he resembles you.
- You acted like you didn't hear it.
He tilted his head upon hearing it.
That was funny.
Please look over here.
(Middle-aged women
are taking photos of So Min.)
- Your expression is the same.
- It isn't easy.
- Hurry up and look over here.
- One, two.
Did you take a photo of my mouth?
(Did you take a photo of my mouth?)
- I...
- Se Chan...
- What?
- She took a photo...
of Se Chan's mouth with a flash.
She took a photo of your mouth.
- She took a photo like this.
- With a flash too.
- One, two, three.
- I will delete it.
Will you delete it?
There is no need. You can keep it.
Since you used the flash,
his teeth shine, right?
(His teeth became popular
among middle-aged women.)
- Hotteok.
- Really?
She took a photo like that.
Why aren't you guys coming back?
- We are in a line.
- It takes a long while.
- Were you waiting all along?
- Did people line up to here?
Where did you guys go?
- Suk Jin almost got beaten up.
- Why?
- He had a fight with Jong Kook.
- With whom?
- Really?
- Yes.
Did you have a fight?
- It's our turn, right?
- Yes.
- Four honey and four vegetable.
Four vegetable. Okay.
- Four vegetable and four honey.
- Four honey.
Four honey.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Did you pay?
- Isn't the bag for us?
- How many do you want?
- Take care.
Jae Suk, how many do you want?
- Four honey and four vegetable.
- Please wait.
- Okay.
My goodness.
The weather is cool now,
- but work must be hard in summer.
- I nearly die.
- It must be hard.
- But people go, "It's tasty."
- It gives you strength.
- "Please work for many more years."
- Those words give me strength.
- Of course.
- We are the same.
- Right?
- Yes. We are similar.
- I knew it.
When people say
that they enjoy my show,
- I gain energy.
- Of course.
Of course.
It contains apples.
You see them, right?
- She brushes it on.
- It's a vegetable hotteok.
- Okay.
- She brushes it on the hotteok.
- Try it.
- Please put them in a bag.
No. You should eat it now.
It tastes different that way.
- It's like dumplings.
- Shall we carry one each?
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's carry it.
- That would be better.
- Eat it.
- Should I eat it now?
- Yes. Try it.
- It must be hot.
- You will burn your mouth.
- Should I eat it now?
- Yes.
It's hot, so take small bites.
- What's this?
- Vegetable hotteok.
(My goodness.)
- Thank you.
(They receive a hotteok in turns.)
- Vegetable hotteok.
- Thank you.
- One more vegetable, please.
- Okay.
- I will come again.
- Thank you.
- There is a paper cup.
Thank you. Take care.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Come here.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
- You need to give me two more.
- I... Thank you. Enjoy it.
- Hold on.
- Be careful.
- They suddenly left.
I need one more.
- You got overlooked.
- Yes.
- I hadn't received any hotteoks,
- We need to wait for Se Chan.
but you told me to go.
- I almost left empty-handed.
- Thank you.
Be happy and healthy. I am sorry.
Hotteok suits a rainy day.
- Hotteok.
It's really tasty.
Vegetable hotteok.
Gosh, this is...
- A tasty hotteok like this...
- It's rare.
It's no wonder this place is famous.
- I thought...
- What?
it would be dry since it's thick.
But it's very crispy.
- It's exactly what I wanted.
- It's tasty.
It's hot.
- What's wrong?
- I burned myself too.
- Oh, no.
- It's hot.
- Drink water.
- It's scorching hot.
- I almost died.
- Hurry up and drink water.
- It's okay.
- Your lips will get burned.
It touched my lips.
- It's so hot.
- You will lose your teeth.
It touched here. Haha, it's so hot.
You need to be careful.
The next one has to be a drink.
- But things won't go as we want.
- Bingsu.
- That's a good one.
Bingsu would be nice, right?
Let's talk
in front of a bingsu place.
- Do you have an address?
- It's a good idea.
Set the destination
to Myeongdong Cathedral.
- I know the way.
- Okay.
- Do you know how to get there?
- I will drive.
Suk Jin,
I know all the places in Seoul.
(Yoo Navigation System)
There are one-way streets.
Will you be okay?
- Jae Suk knows how to get there.
- I know how to get there.
Why are you making a fuss
when he said so himself?
- I know all the places in Seoul.
- That's right.
He said so himself.
He knows all the places in Seoul.
Does he have something on you?
- No.
- Does he know something important?
No. He said he knows it,
so we should believe him.
Jong Kook is quite gentle.
- I am full.
- Same here.
I can't eat more.
I want to be a woman like hotteok.
Why? A hot woman?
- Yes.
- Doesn't it sound strange?
Doesn't "A woman like hotteok"
sound strange?
I mean...
Would you be happy...
if your boyfriend says
you are like hotteok?
Suk Jin, stop it already.
Hey.
What kind of a man says
his girlfriend is like hotteok?
- Come on.
- How will she recover?
So Min didn't say that.
- So Min didn't say that.
- Her beliefs are weird.
- Why do you disparage it?
- It isn't her belief.
- What did I disparage?
- Why do you disparage hotteok?
- It's his specialty.
Don't disparage hotteok.
I didn't disparage it.
- You always say I disparage things.
- I love hotteok.
My dog's name is Hotteok.
- Really?
- Is your dog's name Longtteok?
- Why is it Longtteok?
- She said Hotteok.
- Hotteok.
What's up with you?
- So it's Hotteok, not Longtteok.
- This is a trip down memory lane.
- Back in the day...
- You went to Myeongdong a lot.
- I went to Myeongdong a lot.
- He went to university there.
- I went to university there.
- I see.
Back in the day, I felt intimidated
when I went to Apgujeong.
- I still feel that way.
- So...
So Min,
why would you feel intimidated?
Apgujeong is too much.
Why? There is
nothing wrong with you.
It's too fancy.
- It's stylish.
- Yes.
You are like hotteok.
- What?
- What are you saying?
- Excuse me?
- His tone is sarcastic.
- What was up with that tone?
- Be confident.
You are a woman like hotteok.
Why do you keep disparaging hotteok?
- Your words are lousy.
- I didn't disparage it.
- Hey.
You said you want to be
a woman like hotteok.
Why do you keep calling her
a woman like hotteok?
She said she wants to be
a woman like hotteok.
Why are your comments so lousy?
Your words are perfect.
That rhymes.
Okay. Let's wrap it up.
So Min is a woman like hotteok.
Suk Jin is lousy.
- And Jong Kook is perfect.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook is perfect.
- Perfect.
- Okay.
- That was nice.
It's like a song title.
- Hotteok-like, lousy, and perfect.
- Perfect.
Things were better
before he said that.
- I agree. It wasn't that great.
- I know.
(Suk Jin teaches them
that less is more.)
I came here
during the Christmas season.
- It's nice then, right?
- It's so pretty.
- Back in the day,
- Wasn't it here?
- they used to play carols.
- It wasn't here.
(Jae Suk becomes quiet
as they near Myeongdong.)
I know the way.
(He didn't even search the way
on the navigation system.)
That's the Myeongdong Cathedral.
It's a one-way street.
Shall we walk from here?
- Myeongdong Cathedral.
Hey, you should have used
the navigation system.
It's a one-way street.
- We can go around.
- I am sure we can do that.
- For goodness' sake.
- Wait.
Hyo Im is calling.
- Hold on. Hyo Im is calling.
- I know this area really well.
- Hyo Im is calling.
- Hyo Im.
She called
because we passed the destination.
We are going
to the Myeongdong Cathedral.
- This way, we can enjoy the view.
- Hyung In.
Okay.
- It's Hyung In.
- This way, we can enjoy the view.
- Hyung In.
- We can walk there.
We can park the car here and walk.
Jae Suk was adamant about
not using the navigation system,
- so we got lost.
- Come on.
- It's all because of Jae Suk.
- We are nearly there.
Play "Myeongdong Calling."
- Myeongdong Cathedral, right?
- I haven't been here in a while.
- Play "Myeongdong Calling."
- Okay.
It's nice.
Are you leaving?
- Seriously.
- Hey.
Please play "Myeongdong Calling."
I will play it.
- "Myeongdong Calling."
- I am sorry,
but I want to listen to it
before I get out of the vehicle.
(Driver Yoo suddenly stops driving.)
This won't do.
- His voice is insane.
- It's so nice.
- Car the garden.
- It's so nice. Unbelievable.
(These strange passengers
enjoy the song.)
Let's turn off the light.
It doesn't suit the atmosphere.
What was the singer called?
It's nice.
I like Seogyo Garden.
We will... Oh, it's you.
We will lead the way.
Okay.
(They just need to follow
the staff's vehicle.)
The streets of Myeongdong
This song brings back memories...
- even though it isn't an old song.
- Myeongdong.
I made many memories at Myeongdong.
You suddenly started.
I made many memories.
(The production crew
is unaware of the situation.)
(These middle-aged men are absorbed
in the autumn rain and music.)
It's a bit like that in autumn.
(These middle-aged men are absorbed
in the autumn rain and music.)
Is it better?
- We are sentimental today.
- Yes.
- I feel lonely.
- I love the atmosphere.
Music sets the mood.
If we were going on a trip...
It would have been really nice.
- It would have been fun, right?
- It would have been really nice.
(It's a 5-minute trip,
but they are taking 20 minutes.)
When I think about it
It was like a movie
(Producer Hyung In calls again.)
Hyung In.
We are following
the staff's vehicle.
the camera crew's vehicle.
I think Jae Suk got lost again.
No, we are here.
- My goodness.
- He is childish.
- He is sucking up to Hyung In.
- Seriously.
I told him to turn on
the navigation system,
but he didn't listen.
(He is telling the producer
that he isn't the one at fault.)
- Okay.
I knew it.
(They hum as they enjoy
the romance of the autumn rain.)
(They finally arrive
at the Myeongdong Cathedral.)
It takes five minutes
to reach here from Namdaemun.
- Jae Suk didn't...
- We got absorbed in a conversation.
He didn't use the navigation system.
He said he knew the way.
I got to look around the place
thanks to you.
- Yes. It was romantic.
- What's up with you?
- He is gentle.
- For goodness' sake.
- I didn't know the place very well.
- I think Jae Suk pays him.
- Thanks to the detour,
- He is gentle.
- I learned a lot about Myeongdong.
It was very nice.
- I think Jae Suk pays him.
- I wanted to say that.
- During the ride,
- I think...
- So Min got a new nickname.
- he pays about 12,000 dollars.
- Hotteok-like Woman.
We are now in Myeongdong.
Let's check the pedometers first.
- You took 17,004 steps.
- They were filming.
So 3,000 steps remain.
You can ask the question now.
Who hasn't gone yet? So Min, right?
So Min should ask.
- Go.
- No. She is a hotteok-like woman.
Hotteok, go.
(Hotteok-like Woman
will ask the question.)
What's famous in Myeongdong?
- "Most famous."
- What's most famous in Myeongdong?
"Most famous."
(She approaches a citizen nearby.)
- Hello.
May I ask you a question?
What's most famous in Myeongdong?
The next one has to be a drink.
(The members are full,
so they want a refreshing drink.)
Or Bingsu.
(What will be the answer?)
Myeongdong Cathedral.
(They got Myeongdong Cathedral.)
She said Myeongdong Cathedral.
Myeongdong Cathedral?
Thank you.
- It's very beautiful.
- Yes.
Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk.
- About the things
- What?
- I lost
She said Myeongdong Cathedral.
- That's good.
- Really?
I have always wanted to visit
Myeongdong Cathedral.
- She said Myeongdong Cathedral.
- Let's go there.
We need to take a photo.
My heart becomes calm when I think
of Myeongdong Cathedral.
- It's beautiful.
- I have never visited it.
- Now...
- I am sorry, but are you Catholic?
No.
Her first love became a nun
after he broke up with her.
- Really?
- Yes.
She thought,
"I would rather become a nun."
"I can't believe
an ugly man dumped me."
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Since we came this far,
we should check out the cathedral.
That's right.
Get your microphone.
(Myeongdong Cathedral
is more beautiful in the rain.)
- I got it.
- It's cool, right?
- Myeongdong Cathedral is nice.
- My goodness.
- It's pretty.
- My heart...
- Emotions fill my heart.
Seriously.
- It's my first time here.
- It's prettier inside.
- It's so cool.
- I only passed by the cathedral.
It's really old.
- It's cool.
People kiss here at 12 p.m.
Why?
It was trendy to kiss
in front of the cathedral.
Was it a signature move?
- Really?
- You can kiss at 12 p.m.
The two of you can kiss.
That's a signature move.
Regardless of the shoot,
we should take a photo here.
- Can't I call you guys "Sisters?"
- No.
- Myeongdong Cathedral.
- Okay.
(They finish taking a photo.)
You know, this place...
When I build a house later,
I should use this color scheme.
- What?
- It's atmospheric.
Will you build a house
in the Gothic style?
- A brick house.
- That's the prison color theme.
No. It's very atmospheric.
- A detention center.
- It will look luxurious with age.
It's atmospheric
and you can't read the room.
- No. Myeongdong Cathedral...
- That came out of nowhere.
You are like hotteok.
- He is lousy.
- Lousy.
- I'll say, "I modeled my house..."
- He is lousy.
- "after Myeongdong Cathedral."
- Suk Jin.
We passed by Myeongdong Cathedral
many times in our 20s.
But we never actually visited.
- It's my first time...
- Suk Jin, repent.
I am sorry.
- What?
- I am sorry.
Why didn't you come up here?
It isn't a long walk.
Did you?
- No. But you frequented the area.
- Didn't you ever visit it?
- We frequented the area.
- But we had a different purpose...
- back then.
- But it's worth visiting.
- We never visited it.
- We just knew it existed.
Then why are you so absorbed
in memories?
- It's because...
- I don't get it.
It's because his first love
became a nun.
Is it true or not?
- Seriously.
- It's funny.
- Is it a lie?
- It isn't true.
- It wasn't his first love.
- It sounds like a fact.
- It isn't true.
She was his second girlfriend.
- His second girlfriend?
- No!
- Nazareth.
What's up with Nazareth?
- It isn't true.
- Sister Nazareth.
- It must have been hard.
- It isn't true.
It's so nice.
Let's ask the question.
- Okay.
- Let's ask the question.
- Children...
- How about them?
(How about them?)
- Foreigners?
- Yes.
(There are foreigners
on the other side.)
Are there foreigners?
- Yes.
- I saw them earlier.
What's most famous in Myeongdong?
Can't we ask it like that?
I will get going.
(Suk Jin sets off confidently.)
Hi.
Excuse me.
(Laughing)
Where are you from?
Can we not answer please?
- Yes?
- Let's keep it a secret, okay?
- Is it a secret?
- Yes.
Yes.
You think... Guess.
In Myeongdong... Best. Famous. What?
(Among foreigners, Myeongdong
is known for street food.)
You want to know
what's best here in Myeongdong.
Yes.
(Will he get the answer he wants?)
People.
- People.
- Yes.
Okay.
- People.
- Yes.
- People. That's what you think.
Okay.
- Have a nice day.
- What did she say?
- I told her...
that I want to know
the most famous thing in Myeongdong.
- What did she say?
- Yes.
She said,
"People."
- People?
- People. So we failed.
It's a cool answer.
- Isn't it cool?
- It's a cool answer.
- It's very cool.
- People.
- In her eyes,
people are the most famous
in Myeongdong.
(People are the most famous
in Myeongdong.)
- It's so cool.
- Because of COVID-19, Myeongdong...
was empty for a while.
- Now, there are more people.
- That's right.
At year-end...
- Your shoulders...
- You could barely walk.
- got bruised.
- Seriously.
Shall we take a photo with people?
- Let's keep it light.
- They can be in the background.
- If they are too close...
- It's cool. People.
- It's a cool answer.
- Come here.
- People.
- It's a cool answer.
People.
- People.
- It's "Apple."
- Apple.
- No. Apple.
No. Don't raise the first syllable.
- Apple. There you go.
- Apple.
- There you go.
Your choice. Famous.
Myeongdong. Talking.
- It's hard. Listen.
- How about "Choice?"
- Listen.
- Myeongdong. Famous. Your choice.
- Say, "So many people."
- So many people.
- So many...
- Listen to me.
Listen to Big Sister.
So many people.
- Apple.
- So many people.
No.
So many people.
- No.
- People.
- So many people.
- There are staff members.
Let's take a photo with them.
People.
- The cathedral is in the shot.
- In this shot,
- we need people.
- Yes.
- One, two, three.
- This is Myeongdong.
One, two, three.
- All of them are in the shot.
- People.
Both the staff members
and passersby got included.
- Let's ask well this time.
- Let's ask the question.
Who will do it?
Jong Kook hasn't done it once.
- He should go next.
- Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook will ask the question.)
It will be nice
if we get coffee at that cafe.
- Where?
- Coffee.
- It would be so nice.
- They might answer right away,
"That place."
Where?
Coffee.
I will keep my head down,
so ask me the question.
Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
What's most famous in Myeongdong?
Coffee.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Doesn't that count?
(Rain washed away their conscience.)
(This time,
they search for a citizen.)
Hello.
- There you go.
- Hello.
What's most famous in Myeongdong?
(He asks the question to the man
who meets his eyes.)
Myeongdong Cathedral.
(Myeongdong Cathedral again)
Hey.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Did you ask the question?
- He said Myeongdong Cathedral.
- Jong Kook was supposed to ask.
- What's going on?
- I was supposed to ask.
- He said Myeongdong Cathedral.
- Who said that?
- We didn't ask the question.
- Did you do something?
- Jong Kook was supposed to ask.
- Hold on.
You should have consulted us first.
- Whom did you ask?
- Why did you do it on your own?
- When did it happen?
- Did I do that?
Yes. Go up there
and take another photo.
- Thank you.
- We didn't do anything.
- Jae Suk ruined it.
- Jong Kook was supposed to ask.
- Jae Suk.
Why do you keep pooping?
- Why did you do it on your own?
- He keeps pooping.
- What was that?
- You are such a tyrant.
We should leave the area
before we ask the question.
- That's right.
- Jae Suk.
I am exhausted.
I can't believe Jae Suk.
He is like hotteok.
(They go up the stairs again.)
For goodness' sake.
Why did you ask the question?
- I mean...
- Jae Suk.
- It was Jong Kook's turn.
- Say, "Hey" first.
- Take a photo.
- Three.
(They revisited the cathedral
in 5 minutes.)
Let's go someplace far.
- The man who is going down.
- Let's go.
Jae Suk, how about
the man on the left?
Let's go down the stairs first.
If we do that,
we will end up here again.
We should leave the area.
Let's leave the area.
(They decide to leave
the vicinity of the cathedral.)
(Will it work
to their advantage or not?)
Jong Kook should ask
the question now.
Jae Suk.
If we go that way,
there will be food.
Let's go over there.
Let's go to the place
where there is food.
- Food.
- We need to see various dishes.
- Let's leave the area.
- Let's see various dishes.
Otherwise, we will keep going back
to Myeongdong Cathedral.
There is a cafe.
- I want to go there.
- I will succeed in this mission.
- That's right.
- Wait.
- Go ahead.
- Jong Kook, good luck.
Okay. I will succeed in
this mission.
Let's say, "We have been
to Myeongdong Cathedral."
We can't say that.
"We have been
to Myeongdong Cathedral."
- Let's have a simulation.
- Okay.
- Let's say you meet someone.
- Hello.
Hello. What's the most famous
in Myeongdong?
(Glancing around)
(So Min glances around as well.)
- There you go.
- It's a good tactic, right?
You didn't think
of Myeongdong Cathedral, right?
- Right? Let's glance around.
- Let's glance around.
Let's go.
- Get ready to go up again.
- Let's go to the food.
The streets are busy again.
It's so nice
that the place is crowded again.
I hope we get street food.
This is the place. Turn to the left.
It has been a while
since I visited this place.
Turn to the left.
- It smells amazing.
- The smell of Myeongdong.
It looks delicious.
- Tornado potato.
- Tornado potato would be nice.
Let's ask the man who sells
the tornado potato.
We can do that.
- Jae Suk.
- The guy who sells the potato.
We can ask him what's famous here.
- It's crowded here.
- The smell of Myeongdong.
It smells so delicious.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Okay.
- Hello.
What do you want me to do?
- Go ahead and take a picture.
- Hello.
- It's been a really long time.
I haven't been here for a long time.
Didn't we play games here
in the early years of Running Man?
Yes. We did the high jumping here.
- That's right. We did it here.
- Right?
- You're right.
- I remember that.
- We did it on the street.
- There were a lot of people.
Was it this place?
It was here, right?
I did the guy
who goes back in time here.
Gaeko and I were a team.
(A trip down memory lane)
Do you remember this place?
There was the clothing store, Safety Zone.
Right. Safety Zone.
We're walking too much.
- First...
- It's here.
The cap he's wearing
is my favorite style.
- Now...
- We should ask the question now.
- You have to ask only one question.
- Okay.
Go ahead and ask.
What's most famous in Myeongdong?
What's the most famous thing
in Myeongdong?
What's famous?
- Who wants to ask?
- Who should we ask?
- What about the man over there?
- The man over there.
- He's smiling now.
Is it all right?
(This might be their last chance,
so they are being more careful.)
I think they will say
the cathedral again.
- Old people would say that.
- They might say the cathedral.
- Just do it as you please.
- Find someone young.
Okay. Let's do this.
- All right. Let's go.
- Who should we ask?
Who is it? It's your choice.
- Go ahead and pick one.
- Your turn.
What about
the two young people over there?
- Where?
- Here.
- The ones on the left.
(A young couple catches
Se Chan's eyes.)
Should we ask them?
- Yes. Good.
- Let's do that.
May I ask you something?
(Nodding)
Please. We just need
to eat one more dish.
- Let's do this.
- Please.
But something that's not too heavy.
(They have to go to a restaurant
within 1,000 steps!)
What's most famous in Myeongdong?
We just need to eat one more dish.
What comes to your mind?
Myeongdong is famous
for its street food.
(Myeongdong is famous
for its street food.)
Street food? Which one?
(Street food?)
- Like what?
- Which one?
- Chicken skewers?
- Chicken skewers!
(It's food!)
Chicken skewers!
- Chicken skewers!
- Street food!
- You're the best.
- Chicken skewers!
- We can go home now.
- He said chicken skewers.
- Chicken skewers.
- I'm cold.
- I like the combination.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Let's go.
I think we can find it there.
- Do you like chicken skewers?
- Oh, yes.
- Really?
- No.
- Do you like chicken skewers?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- How many chicken skewers?
How many chicken skewers
do you enjoy?
- Yes.
- I hate chicken skewers.
- You ate chicken skewers?
- You're a chicken skewer?
I hate.
- I see. You hate it.
- Why?
- I'm a vegetarian.
- Why do you hate chicken skewers?
Are you Vegeta?
(They use
all the English words they know.)
- Vegetarian?
- No, vegetarian.
Are you Sun Wukong's friend, Vegeta?
No.
Haha says he hates chicken skewers.
He's a vegetarian.
Jong Kook said this. "If you don't
want to get beaten up..."
(Jong Kook said this. "If you don't
want to get beaten up...")
"If you don't want to get beaten up,
just stay quiet."
Gosh, he's so annoying.
- Gosh. He is.
- So annoying.
Hey, do you want to go crazy today?
- Let's go crazy.
- Shall we get soaked?
- Let's do that.
- Let's just get soaked.
Haha.
- Haha.
- Yes?
(Taking it off)
- You look tough.
- Hey, do you want to go crazy?
(Hey, do you want to go crazy?)
- Don't be ridiculous.
- My gosh.
He looks really old.
- "He looks really old."
- He really does.
Where are chicken skewers?
If we turn left here,
we will find some snack carts.
- Really?
- Yes.
Let's turn left.
- It's been so long.
- Turn left?
- This feels so nice.
- There's something.
Let's find chicken skewers.
- I bet it's here.
- I think so.
- It's not here.
- There are chicken skewers.
- Where?
- Over here.
- There are chicken skewers.
- Okay.
It's really here.
- That's true.
- It's here.
- It has everything.
- I can't believe this.
- Hello.
Hang on. Are these chicken skewers?
- Don't you have chicken skewers?
- Are these chicken skewers?
They are chicken skewers.
(They are chicken skewers.)
- Okay.
- Chicken skewers.
I'll have the teriyaki one.
I will have the salted one.
All right.
Let's eat chicken skewers.
(Myeongdong's specialty,
chicken skewers)
- Is this a TV show?
- Yes. Thank you.
- Two.
- We will have one more.
- How much is this?
- How much?
The chicken skewers
are so delicious.
(A super close shot)
(Yoom)
Do you sell the shine muscat too?
Of course, I do.
(Of course, I do.)
- Well...
- Isn't that obvious?
What else would it be?
- Do you think it's decoration?
- What a silly question.
What a lame question.
When I see you on TV,
the members treat you like this
all the time, so before I knew it...
That's good.
- "That's good?"
- That's good.
Do you take a card, sir?
- No.
- We will pay in cash.
Suk Jin can wire the money.
Suk Jin?
Suk Jin, wire the money to him.
Why are you glaring at me like that?
What's wrong?
How much is it? I'll wire the money.
Here. Will you pay?
(He has some cash.)
No. If you have cash, you can pay.
No.
I was going to wire the money.
- I think that's better.
- No.
It's more meaningful.
- Meaningful?
- We don't have to do that.
I feel a lot better now.
I'd like to wire the money, but...
You are done
trying three different dishes.
Now I will check your pedometers.
(The final result)
Are we going up again?
(Course 1: Going up Mount Nam)
I can't see it.
There's no one.
(Course 2: An exciting tour
around Namdaemun)
(Course 3: The mire of
Myeongdong Catholic Cathedral)
(The final result)
(The total number of steps)
It's 19,873 steps in total.
You succeeded.
- What?
- Yes!
The shoot is over.
- Okay.
- Can we go home now?
(Go home right away.)
- Thank you.
- It's over.
Let's do this again
when it's not raining.
- Let's do that. It's fun.
- It was really nice.
We should do this more often.
- I even liked the rain.
- This was really nice.
- The tour around Seoul was fun.
- It was even better in the rain.
A tour around Seoul on a rainy day.
It was a trip
down memory lane for Jae Suk.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
Thank you all for your hard work.
(We'd like to thank the citizens and
restaurant owners for their help.)
I go like this.
(A nimble fighter
with a bald head, Haha)
(Speedy mouth, Yang Ssaebssaeb)
(Why are you doing this?)
(An uppercut with words,
Yoo Jae Suk)
(A honey punch, Ji Suk Jin)
(Weaving geniuses,
Zoned-out Crazy Sisters)
(And Gym Jong Kook)
Are you intimidated by Pacquiao?
(The legendary boxer is coming?)
(The stakes are getting bigger
with the news about the big game.)
(Fighting fiercely over seats)
(They are well prepared.)
(The ring for a decisive battle)
(A legendary boxer, Pacquiao)
(The world's first boxer
who conquered 8 weight divisions)
(Pacquiao with the punch
worth tens of millions of dollars)
- The name tag...
- He ripped it off.
(But the members struggle
because of him?)
(The best boxer's attack...)
(continues on the ring.)
(Nice to meet you, Running Man.)
(Among those who get beaten up...)
(There's one person
who can turn the tide.)
- Okay.
- Good.
(He's trained for a long time...)
(only for this day.)
(All Mighty)
(Versus Word's best boxer)
(Jong Kook is not giving way.)
(And Pacquiao is driving him
into a corner.)
- He's upset.
- He's caught.
(How will the big match turn out?)
(Show Me the Fight Money)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)