(The year-end party of the stars
began last week.)
(The first guest, BE'O)
(Zhu Bajie and the tropical fish
welcomed him.)
(The second guest, Jukjae)
(The Zoned-out Crazy Sisters
were so into his song.)
- His voice doesn't waver at all.
- I know.
(The two stars who have "stars"
in common showed up like that.)
- Jukjae.
- Let's go see the stars.
- That was incredible.
He looks fine when he's dressed up.
He really does.
Are you saying Jukjae is not fine
at other times?
I've never seen him
dressed up like that before.
Isn't this your first time
meeting Jukjae?
Jukjae...
- This is your first time.
- I think this is my first time.
- Hello.
- You're so cool.
- Jukjae.
- You're the best.
- Hey, Jukjae.
- Jukjae.
- Jukjae. Hey, you...
- He's handsome.
We have Jukjae and BE'O here today.
(BE'O, Jukjae)
Hello. I'm a singer-songwriter,
Jukjae.
- Singer-songwriter.
BE'O, introduce yourself.
Hello. I'm BE'O who does music.
Nice to meet you.
- The king of the young generation.
- Young generation?
- What are you saying?
- So I'm wondering...
how they are feeling to be
on Running Man for the first time.
I've been watching this show
since elementary school.
- Right. You're a Running Man kid.
- He's one of the Running Man kids.
I used to rip off name tags with
my friends at an amusement park.
- Right.
- That's amazing.
The thing is, BE'O's father is...
two years younger than Suk Jin.
My goodness.
He's like a father.
- Hey, is that true?
- Father!
- How old are you?
- You're his uncle.
- I'm 23.
- He's 23.
Right. He's two years
older than my son.
Exactly.
It's possible if his dad
got married young.
I have a nephew and a son here.
Like I said before,
it hasn't been long...
since BE'O's debut,
But he's so popular.
but he already has
a lot of hit songs.
I love his songs.
- He has a lot of great songs.
- I really like them.
- Counting stars
- Stars
- Pearls in the night sky
- Pearls
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Sorry.
- Sorry for what?
- Right.
- Why are you sorry?
(He keeps singing
ignoring everyone.)
(Shutting his eyes tight)
I'm sorry.
My son is an elementary school kid.
He's the king of the school kids.
- Is he?
- Of course.
When I met him before,
I took pictures with him.
- Really?
- My son loves him.
You know, Haha is...
a goner in the hip hop scene.
No, I've still got it.
- He's a goner.
- He even plays along with the joke.
Why are you doing this to me?
This is how we exchange jokes.
I'm a fan of yours.
And we have Jukjae here.
As you already know,
he captivates women's hearts
with his sweet voice.
That's true.
He makes a lot of suggestions.
- "Let's go see the stars."
- "Shall we go walk together?"
Do you usually make
many suggestions to women?
- No.
- "Will you go out with me?"
- Actually...
- To do something.
I actually like rock music.
He plays the guitar really well.
- Right.
- He was a famous guitarist.
He did
a lot of famous songs we know...
He was well known
as the guitarist of IU's band.
- He worked with IU?
- Sure.
- Really?
- He's famous.
What are the songs you played?
Where you played the guitar.
Well...
(Hesitant)
I can't think of anything.
You have to think.
You just said
there were a lot of songs.
- But he can't say anything.
- Why can't you think of anything?
- That's because he did many songs.
- Jukjae, if you can't name one,
who else would say that?
He just works with many musicians.
Still...
Just name any musician.
We wouldn't know anyway.
Right. Jukjae, I told you
not to feel nervous.
Just say the names of the artists.
- The artists?
- Yes.
Why can't I think of anyone?
- What was that?
- I get it.
- He didn't sleep well last night.
- There are more.
- You didn't sleep well, did you?
- No.
- I knew it.
- It's like, "This is Jukjae."
Suk Jin really wants Jukjae...
- to write him a song.
- Did you think about it?
- Yes.
- Are you interested?
No. Stay quiet.
Jukjae promised
to give me his song first.
- Really?
- Yes.
He has many people
to write a song for.
That's true.
That sounds great.
I met him before.
I think we met before.
Do you remember when we met?
I think this is my first time.
- What was that?
- Am I wrong?
He says it's his first time.
Isn't this your first time
meeting Jukjae?
(Only 5 minutes ago,
he said it was his first time.)
- We met. He doesn't remember that.
- Where?
- When I did my radio show.
- He says...
you met him at his radio show.
You joined my radio show once.
- That's right.
- Right?
- This never happened before.
- Suk Jin remembered.
Suk Jin is the one
who usually forgets.
It's usually the other way around.
- Right.
- Was he on your radio show?
He was a guest on my radio show.
- That's right.
- He was the only guest there.
I'm sorry I forgot.
See? You almost disappointed me.
- Suk Jin...
- I was disappointed.
- You didn't remember me.
- See? You're disappointed, right?
- I'm really sad.
- That's how other guests feel.
I even remember
what I said back then.
I said he looked like Ha Jung Woo.
- That I don't remember.
- You don't remember?
- I think I said that.
- He was nice to me though.
- I thought he looked like an actor.
- Right.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
Jukjae, I like your character.
- He doesn't remember.
- I like the forgetful character.
You two should make a song together.
- What?
- "Fake Life" by Jukjae.
- "Fake Life."
- Featuring Ji Suk Jin.
- "Oblivion."
All right.
Today, we will have a race...
with the three captains
who have something to do with stars.
BE'O with "Counting Stars," Jukjae
with "Let's Go See the Stars,"
- Right.
- and Byul's husband, Haha.
(BE'O, Jukjae, Haha)
Gosh, this is...
That's quite far-fetched.
He's back as Zhu Bajie.
He has nothing to do with stars.
- My wife is Byul.
- We have BE'O and Jukjae.
He should be a star.
- He's supposed to be a star.
- Right.
I got the star.
He's the sun. The setting sun.
He's right about that.
- But I have the star.
- He has the star.
This is ridiculous.
First, you need
to choose your teams.
The captains will play
rock-paper-scissors and choose...
- two team members they want.
- Okay.
They will choose one at a time.
I'm so glad we have
BE'O and Jukjae here today.
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Yes.
- You two play again.
Rock-paper-scissors.
BE'O wins.
I want to join BE'O's team.
- BE'O?
- You're the captain.
- What are you saying?
- I also like Jukjae.
- You're the captain, Haha.
- He's the king of kids.
- The king of kids?
- But you're the captain.
- Right.
- Can I choose first?
- Yes.
BE'O goes first.
I'll choose...
So Min, he just looked at you.
- He looked at you.
- He looked this way.
So Min, get ready.
- He looked at me.
- Stop it.
- He just gave a glance.
- BE'O, who do you want?
- I think he looked at me.
I'm not good at playing games.
- I'll...
- Okay.
- I'll pick So Min.
- So Min!
- Counting stars
- Why did you glance at Jukjae?
She wants to be on Jukjae's team.
- What?
- No.
I'm sorry.
- No, it's not like that.
- She actually wants Jukjae.
- That makes BE'O look bad.
- Pick again.
- Can I pick again?
- Let's do this again.
- No.
- Pick again.
- BE'O, pick again.
- No. I want BE'O.
- We can pick again.
- I like BE'O.
- It's all right Namiko.
- I really like BE'O.
Pick again.
- Move over.
- I do like BE'O.
So Min was waiting for Jukjae.
No. I want to be on BE'O's team.
- Move over.
- It's over.
Move over.
- Can I pick again?
- Pick again.
Pick whomever you want.
I like BE'O. Why would you say that?
You can pick again. It's okay.
I really like BE'O.
- I really do.
- It's okay. Just pick one.
- You don't have to pick me.
- I want Jae Suk.
Okay.
(Jae Suk joins BE'O's team.)
- Someday
- This is really upsetting.
- I'll have one too
- Actually, I decided to pick...
So Min in my car.
- That's too bad.
- Why did you guys ruin it?
All right, I just got a hot pack
My hands were freezing
- This is nice
- Nice
(She lost her hot pack
as well as BE'O.)
The black limousine
You forced him not to pick me.
- That's not true.
- Next up is Jukjae.
- He's up next.
- It's Jukjae.
It's Jukjae's turn now.
Jukjae's turn to pick
You can join BE'O's team next time.
- Seriously, everyone is...
- This is Jukjae's turn
- Jukjae is...
- I didn't say anything.
- Jukjae.
- Yes.
I was staying still.
Who do you want to go
see the stars with?
I'll pick Jong Kook.
(I'll pick Jong Kook.)
- Okay.
- This time...
Come on, Jukjae.
- Jukjae.
- Counting stars
- I want to be on BE'O's team.
- Pearls in the night sky
He's my Jukjae.
- You'll get another chance.
- He's so witty.
- Good.
- Okay.
Nice. Jukjae.
He wants to go see
the stars with Jong Kook.
Not with So Min.
He can see the stars
when he works out with me.
- All right. It's Haha.
- Haha.
- Then I'll...
- Who?
So Min.
(She hates it.)
Why are you doing this to So Min?
You should go now.
(Dragging)
- Take her.
- Hurry and go.
- You should go to Zhu Bajie.
- Go join Zhu Bajie.
- Go hang out with Zhu Bajie.
- Come here.
(Namiko joins Team Zhu Bajie.)
- They are wearing matching outfits.
- Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you doing this to me?
They are wearing matching outfits.
Gosh, Jeon So Bal.
- Everything is ruined.
- Good.
- This is a mess.
- Right.
It's a total mess.
- They ruined everything for me.
- This is so funny.
Play rock-paper-scissors again.
- Again.
- All right.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Who do you want?
I want to go see the stars.
(I want to go see the stars.)
(Shaky eyes)
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo wants you.
- Jukjae.
- She wants to go see the stars.
- She said that.
But there's someone else
I want to pick.
- That doesn't matter.
- Really? Go ahead.
Suk Jin.
(Jukjae's choice is Suk Jin.)
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
- This is strange.
- Why would you see the stars?
- I want to see the stars.
- I'm sorry.
- I want to go see the stars.
- That's his choice.
Jukjae is funny.
- I didn't do anything wrong.
- Jukjae.
- This young man is funny.
- Hey.
At a time like this,
- you should pick Ji Hyo.
- Really?
- Yes.
- It's all right.
Still, this is...
Forget it. I won't see the stars.
- Can I pick now?
- Yes. Who do you want?
- I want Se Chan.
- Thanks!
We should mix up
the members a little.
- All right then.
- I'm also a star.
- I'm a star too.
- He's also a star.
- Right.
- Ji Hyo, we're also a star.
- I like BE'O.
- Actually,
- you are wearing matching coats.
That's true.
You two look good together.
So we have three teams now.
- I'll explain the rules right away.
- What is it?
Today, we are having the Year-End Party
With Stars Race with stars.
You each will get one card among
3 Star Cards and 6 Poop Cards.
- Okay.
- My nickname is Poop.
- Me too.
- I look like poop.
And the team who gets
2 Star Cards and 1 Poop Card wins.
- All right.
- Two stars and one poop.
The team who has more poop cards
than star cards...
will get a penalty based
on the number of their poop cards.
- So we can't get 3 Poop Cards.
- No 3 Poop Cards.
- We need a Star Card.
- That's the worst.
You will have some missions
during the race.
After the mission,
the 2nd and 3rd places can...
exchange one card
with a team they want.
And the first place can switch
two cards at most.
And each team will be assigned
to different waiting spaces...
based on the number
of Star Cards they hold.
- Waiting spaces?
- Yes.
The first-place team will get
a warm indoor space.
The second-place team will get
an indoor space with fences.
And the third-place team will get
an outdoor tent.
- No.
- It's cold.
I don't want to catch a cold.
All right. Now you will pick
one card each.
Okay.
We might get 2 stars
and 1 poop right away.
- Right. But we might lose it.
- We can get it right away.
- We might lose it.
- We should fake it.
I'm good at things like this.
- Really?
- Should we keep this a secret?
- Jong Kook, you pick one.
- Me?
All right then.
Look at their faces.
- It's either star or poop, right?
- Yes.
We can't just...
We've been doing
a variety show for so long.
- We can fake it.
- We wouldn't show it.
- You can't read my face.
- I can keep a poker face.
(A poker face)
- Of course.
- Suk Jin can't open it.
- You can't read my face.
- It's a Poop Card.
- Suk Jin got a Poop Card.
- No.
- It's definitely a Poop Card.
When Suk Jin opened it,
it reeked of poop.
- Suk Jin got a Poop Card.
- Totally.
- Let's move on to the next team.
- It's us.
- Team BE'O goes first.
- Okay.
BE'O.
- Can't you be nice to us?
- He's a guest.
- Be nice to Zhu Bajie.
Pearls in the night sky
Okay.
- What is it?
- You startled me.
Your dad wants to see it.
- Your dad wants to see it.
- Dad, this is...
(Dad, this is...)
- We both got Star Cards.
- One...
- Really?
- One, two, three.
- What's yours?
- I got a Poop Card.
Really?
- We got it.
- I know.
- Aren't I good?
- You are really good.
- It's our turn.
- Okay. Go ahead.
(Team Haha gets
the 3 left-over cards.)
We shouldn't let them see it.
- Let's see.
- We should do the same thing.
All right. One, two, three.
- No!
- My gosh.
What's with my hands?
How is this possible?
I don't know. Did you see it?
So you all are done
choosing your cards.
You will get changed
before the first mission.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- I should go dress warmly.
- Jukjae.
I think he forgot
that we should gather around.
- Jukjae.
- I think Jukjae is...
- He's out of his mind.
He's like an old man.
It's all right, Jukjae.
- He's laid-back.
- It's all right. Good.
- He's like an old man.
- He's calm.
He's like a scholar.
It's so nice to have
BE'O and Jukjae here today.
Right.
I didn't think BE'O would be
on a variety show.
- I thought he wasn't interested.
- Me neither.
- I didn't know he'd be on TV shows.
- Some artists don't do TV shows.
He's here because it's Running Man.
- That's why.
- Right.
- It's true, right?
- Yes.
You should say that yourself.
It's true.
Why do you force him?
- What's with him?
- Gaslighting.
- That's one reason, right?
- Yes.
- That's true.
- That's gaslighting.
I can't take his side on this.
This is really nice.
Isn't So Min funny, by the way?
It's funny that she's there.
(It's funny that she's there.)
I don't belong here.
Why did you pick me?
I had to pick her
to go along with the atmosphere.
- I regret it a lot.
- Don't do that.
- Okay.
- I'm so sad.
I find it funny when things
don't go well for So Min.
All right. Here's the first mission.
It's called A Trembling Move.
- Okay.
- A representative of each team...
- will play yukmok, not omok.
- I see.
- How do we do that?
- Since this is yukmok,
- you will place 2 pieces at a time.
- Place 2 pieces?
To place your pieces,
you have to do...
10 squats within 20 seconds.
You have to place your pieces,
come back, and press the button.
If you fail to press
the button in time,
the other team can get rid
of one of your pieces.
- So we have to hurry and do squats.
- Right.
For your information,
Jong Kook will coach you
when you do squats.
- Me?
- If they don't do it properly,
you can say so.
I'm quite strict about this.
Your team member...
- Jong Kook.
- You know me.
I can't go all the way down
because of the structure of my body.
You have to watch
Suk Jin carefully.
I know.
- You know me.
- Watch his posture carefully.
I can't go all the way down.
- BE'O, can you do that?
- Yes.
Good.
Your knees are
sticking out too much.
- Don't do that.
- He's very strict.
- Nice, Mr. Kim.
- You should lean back.
Your body is just like mine.
- You can't do it, can you?
- I can't.
- It's all right.
- He's a human.
You can't use
the squat toilet, right?
- My knees hurt.
- So you can't, can you?
I can't use it either.
I knew it. You can't do this.
So I go like this.
Hey.
Can you really do that?
He's like an old man.
- Like this?
- Hey.
- Does this work?
- Because I can't squat down.
Who would use a toilet like this?
He poops like this.
Do you really do that?
- Does this work?
- I just imagined it.
My goodness.
I imagined it. It's horrible.
So there will be two rounds.
You will play Round One
to switch cards.
And you will play Round Two
to get star coins.
You can use star coins
to check other teams' cards...
or buy food and things you need
in your waiting spaces.
Do we get to hear that?
Now you should discuss with your
team and decide who will go first.
When you play yukmok,
the first player...
can place only one piece.
Only the first time.
If you're too tired to do squats,
you can be substituted once.
- We should let BE'O play first.
- Okay.
- Then we will choose Jukjae.
- I'll go first.
- We have Haha.
- Black limousine
The stars are here.
Haha.
It's all right. I will have
three pieces in my next turn.
You still have one more piece.
- We have one more piece.
- Haha. You're the star.
(Slow)
Thank you.
- Why are you so slow?
- Jukjae.
- It's all right.
- He's a scholar.
- Take your time.
- Jukjae.
- Jukjae, you're so slow.
- Take as much time as you need.
- I can be fast.
- Okay. Just hurry.
That's his character.
I thought...
- he was a sloth.
- He's a scholar.
As I say start,
you press the button...
and do the squats.
Ready.
BE'O, you should place
the red pieces.
You can do this.
Start.
All right.
He's doing it.
- One.
- Why is he so slow?
This is unexpected.
Three, four,
- five, six, seven...
- He's a little...
- He's so laid-back.
- Eight, nine,
- ten.
- Okay.
Five seconds.
- One more.
- He has to press the button.
Four, three...
- Okay.
- Two seconds left.
- It's your turn.
- One.
- Two, three.
- What are you doing? All right.
- Four, five,
- Go further down.
- six, seven,
- Further down.
eight, nine,
ten. Go.
- He can do it. He made it.
- This is hard.
It's not easy to do it
within the given time.
He has no time to think.
It's too close.
- Okay. Go.
- One.
- two, three,
- Go, Scholar!
- four.
- He's a scholar.
Why are you doing this?
- Six.
- Jukjae.
- My knees hurt.
- Eight, nine.
- It hurts, doesn't it?
- Run.
- Go.
- Gosh.
Hey, you have to hurry.
- Why is he so slow?
- Hey.
- You don't have time.
- Hurry.
- Three.
Two, one.
- My gosh.
- Why is he so slow?
- You should go right away.
- He's a scholar.
- One, two, three...
- That's good.
- Four.
- BE'O got used to doing it.
- Five more to go.
- He's so cute.
- He groaned.
- Six. Seven.
- You all should do more exercise.
- Eight.
- Nine. Ten.
- He...
- He won't ever come back here.
- He always works with a computer...
to make music. That's why.
- That's good.
- Oh, we should stop them.
Good job.
- One, two...
- Hey.
- You're going down too low.
- That's good!
- No, he's doing great.
- Go down lower.
- Hey, do it properly.
- You should go down lower.
- Yes. Do it as you did earlier.
- Lower.
Seven. Eight.
- No, he did all ten squats.
- Did he?
- You don't have time to think.
- We should block the team.
- Decide on your move in advance.
- Right. I'll do that.
- Right. You should think ahead.
- I see.
- Jukjae, you've got this. One.
- It looks exhausting.
Two, three, four, five...
- He must be tired now.
- Then it's over.
Nine. Ten.
- Good. You have enough time.
- There's no need to rush.
- No one has been as relaxed as him.
- He's so laid-back.
- You still have time to think.
- He's adorable.
- Why is he so relaxed?
- Hey, go back now!
- No, you still have time left.
- Hurry up! Three!
- Two, one.
- Two.
- One.
- It's over.
- He's so laid-back.
- Jukjae is relaxed.
He's so laid-back.
- How can he be so relaxed?
- Good. Three.
He's so laid-back.
How can he be so relaxed?
Good. Three.
- Four.
- Good.
(Groaning)
(He faced a crisis
at the beginning of the game.)
- My gosh.
- Good.
- Gosh, you're still very young.
- Keep going.
- He was born in 2000. He's young.
- Nine.
- That's good.
- Are you tired?
- BE'O, that's humane.
- Goodness. He was born in 2000.
- He'll be too exhausted next week.
- That's good.
He was born in 2000.
- What is he doing?
- What? Where should I place them?
- Where should I...
- Hurry up, BE'O!
- Time's up.
- You should take one out.
(What is wrong with him?)
Take this one out.
Can I place one piece?
- I couldn't place any.
- In that case, you can't.
- I see.
- You should go back.
- My goodness.
- Can't he place any pieces?
- He has no choice.
- Why do you have such weak knees?
- BE'O, how did that happen?
- I'm sorry.
- Well... He's so polite.
- Two, three... Ten.
- Hey, Blowfly!
- We should block the white pieces.
You did quite well, Dong Hoon.
- Right, you should.
- The white pieces. That's good.
- You've got this.
- I'm done.
- Three seconds are left.
Jukjae, move faster.
You don't have much time.
- One, two, three...
- Two, three...
- He got faster.
- Jukjae got the hang of it.
- Five... Ten.
- Hey.
- You have only a few seconds left.
- Take your time.
- Hey, Jukjae...
- You have enough time to think.
- Take your time. Good.
- You're running out of time.
- Six, five, four...
- It's okay. There's no rush.
- Three!
- No. What are you doing?
- Two! One!
- Okay!
- One!
- You should take one piece out.
- Who should do that?
- Take one piece out.
- No, the other teams should do it.
- Oh, I see.
- Haha, which one should be removed?
- They're at an advantage.
- We should take this one out.
- You shouldn't think too much.
- Okay. This one is out.
- Okay. Done.
- Oh, next up is...
- Is the black piece up next?
- Which team uses black pieces?
- Next up is red. It's our turn.
- Okay. We should block them.
- It's our turn.
- Okay.
- BE'O, what's the matter?
- I'll be okay. Don't worry.
- That line should be blocked.
Se Chan, be careful.
Leave it untied.
- If he's tired, I can replace him.
- One,
- Go down lower.
- two, three, four,
- five, six...
- Spread your knees wider.
Or it might damage your knees.
- I mean, your knees.
- BE'O has reached his limit.
- Nine, ten.
- My gosh.
- Go.
- Ten.
(His legs give out.)
Hurry up and place it in the middle.
- This is fun.
- What's wrong with you?
- Between those pieces.
- This is fun.
- Place it between those pieces.
- BE'O!
(The place where the white piece was
before being removed)
- No, between them!
- Between those pieces!
- Hey, time's up.
- No, between those pieces!
- Take one piece out.
- But...
- I'll replace you.
- I'm sorry.
- Sit down here.
- Who should decide?
- Stay seated.
- That was hilarious.
- Hey.
- I mean, it was funny, but...
- I forgot where I should place it.
- I told you...
- I know.
- We'd like to change players.
- Shall I do it?
- You can do this.
- It's our turn, right?
- Right.
- Who's next?
- It's our turn.
Place two pieces between our pieces
to complete a line.
I'll start.
One, two... That's good. Three.
- He'll grab you. Hit him as you go.
- We should block the red pieces.
- Six. Seven.
- Turn around and hit him.
- That's good.
- Eight.
- Nine. Ten.
- Run.
Good.
(He gave up on the strap
of his bag.)
- It's okay.
- It snapped.
- Good. Great job. Let's go.
- What?
- Is that how you played the pieces?
- Good.
- Oh, no. This is bad.
- Where did he place the pieces?
- What are you going to do?
- It's over.
You should block this line here.
(If Team Red place two pieces here,
the game will end.)
- You should place 1 piece here.
- You can win by putting 2 here.
(It'll also end if Team Black place
two pieces here.)
- Look.
- Why didn't you block the line?
- Suk Jin, let's block it together.
- Who's up next?
- You should block the line.
- Let's work together.
- Team Black will win if I do that.
- It's over.
- Exactly.
- No, you should place it here.
- You should place it here.
- Place one here and the other here.
- Right. You should block the line.
- You should place it here.
- I'll place one here.
- No.
- No. They'll win if you do that.
- Hey, you know, right?
- We'll win either way.
- They'll win if I put it there.
- Place it here.
- No, they'll win.
- If I put it here, they'll win.
- You should block this line.
- Listen. You should block that one.
- Hey, Jukjae! Where are our pieces?
- Place it here.
- Place our pieces here.
- You've done nothing.
- All I see is this giyeok shape!
- Just put one here.
- There's no way we can win.
- We need him to place one here.
If we block the black line,
who's next?
- Team Red.
- Team Red is up next.
- Then we shouldn't do it.
- Right.
- Why?
- Okay. I have an idea.
- We won't place ours there.
- No.
We can block
both of these two lines.
- But then...
- Then they'll block the black line.
- Right. That's a good idea.
- If we block the two lines.
(He plans to join forces with
Team Red to stop Team Black.)
- Then they'll block the black line.
- Right.
- That's a good idea.
- We won't block that line.
- They...
- We won't do that.
(We won't block that line.)
- You won't?
- Then you'll lose.
- He's being a jerk again.
- Suk Jin.
- We won't take your team's card.
- We'll do that.
- It's a good offer.
- We won't take your team's card.
- We'll do that.
- Hey, that's not the point.
- Listen, Suk Jin.
- Jukjae, there's no way we can win.
- Help us, not them.
- Jukjae, why did you do a poor job?
- Suk Jin.
You have to make your decision.
- We won't take yours. Are we good?
- That's not what I'm saying.
- Are you serious?
- Place two pieces here and here.
- Okay. Let's do as he asks.
- Then...
- Then we... Of course.
- You should keep your promise.
- It's a deal.
- Hey, we offered the same thing!
- Whatever we do...
- But Suk Jin...
- What about us?
- He may not make it in 20 seconds.
You're wrong. I can do that.
- He can't pull it off? Come on.
- He may not make it.
- I just came out.
- You should do squats properly.
He can do it
since we already made the decision.
- He can pull it off.
- Of course.
- Let's put one here.
- I'll start.
- One.
- What?
That won't do.
- Suk Jin, please.
- Please. You have to pull it off.
- You should go down lower.
- Seven.
- Eight. Nine.
- Good.
- How many seconds are left?
- Ten seconds.
- You have enough time.
- Yes, that's more than enough.
- What's with his stance?
- My gosh.
- You have enough time.
- There.
- My gosh. There.
- You have enough time.
(Suk Jin chose to give up
for the sake of Team Red.)
- What are you doing?
- There.
- That's not cool.
- It doesn't matter to us anyway.
- Five, six... Nine, ten.
- You're good at it.
It doesn't matter.
- All right.
- We had no chance anyway.
(Team Red completed
a line of six pieces.)
- Okay.
- It's over.
- We had to accept his offer.
- Team BE'O won.
- Okay!
- Gosh, seriously.
- Hey, keep your promise.
- Then we'll...
calculate the probability
based on the possible moves.
- Team Haha placed second.
- It's us.
- Team Jukjae placed third.
- That's not fair.
- How would you know?
- You placed the pieces randomly.
- Then let's keep playing.
- Let's see how it ends.
- I didn't know you'd rank us too.
- Of course, they ranked us too.
- I wouldn't have placed them here.
Suk Jin, why did you do that?
- You could've placed second.
- You should've blocked their line.
- Then you would've placed second.
- Why did you put them here?
- To move fast. We had no chance.
- Did you hear what Jae Suk said?
- We had no chance to win anyway.
- After all that happened.
- That's so funny.
- It was going to end anyway.
He asked why Suk Jin did so
after all that happened.
When I joined the same team as him,
I gave up on winning.
- As soon as the teams were decided.
- We're in second place.
In Round 2, the team in 1st place
will get 7 star coins.
The 2nd place will get 5 star coins,
and the 3rd place will get 3.
- That sounds good.
- Ji Hyo will play in this round.
- So Min.
- Yes.
From our team, So Min will play.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Suk Jin, continue to play. Yes.
- Shall I?
- Hey, your jacket...
- They'll understand you.
- I'll do it.
- Play as long as you can.
- I think I can beat these two.
- I can replace you later. Right.
- So Min, you...
- The time limit is too short.
So Min,
do not place pieces apart like this.
- That's stupid.
- Try to put them together.
- Like this.
- Hey, I know that much.
- Do you really know?
- Yes.
- So Min, we're rooting for you.
- They lower my self esteem.
- What do you mean?
- That's not true. You're pretty.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Hey, don't do that to So Min.
- She's so pretty.
- "She's pretty?"
Okay. Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors, okay.
- I won.
- Hey, what are you good at?
- Get it together!
- You should've at least won that.
Stop nagging me already. Gosh.
(Frog lost her temper in the end.)
- That was good.
- Good job!
- The order is...
- You're pretty!
- Suk Jin, So Min, and Ji Hyo.
- You're so pretty. You're hip!
- Got it.
- You look so young!
- I can do it. I work out at home.
- Good.
That's great.
- I'll check the time.
- She looks so young.
- One, two...
- That's good. Oh, my.
- Three.
- Great. You look so strong.
- Five, six...
- Suk Jin, that's too much.
- Don't push your hips forward.
- Can you blur him?
- Is that the correct stance?
- Don't push your hips forward...
Is that right, Ji Hyo?
My, he's good at it.
That's good.
- I still have five seconds left.
- He's so healthy.
- You did a great job.
- Of course.
- He's better than Jukjae and BE'O.
- You did a great job.
- Faster. Two, three...
- So Min, what are you doing?
My gosh. What are you doing?
- Hey, what is that?
- I'm relieved.
- Seven.
- What is she doing?
- Look at her.
- What is that?
- Seven. Eight.
- What is she doing?
- Hurry up!
- Hurry! Run now.
- Hurry! Run.
- Move faster. Hurry up.
- What was that?
- Go back now. Go.
- Run.
- That was cute.
- Hurry up.
- Okay. She's so bad at it.
- What was that?
- Why are you so bad at it?
- She's so slow.
- It's diagonal, right?
- Yes, it is.
- Three.
- Go down lower!
- Lower.
- Ten.
Ji Hyo.
Don't think too much.
Put two pieces anywhere you want.
- Wait. What is she doing?
- Good.
- Press the button.
- Nice.
- Nice!
- Okay.
Go ahead. Start now.
- One, two, three, four, five...
- That's good.
- He's amazing.
- He'll ache all over tomorrow.
- You're incredible.
- You're such a tough guy!
- Ten.
- Okay!
(He's full of energy.)
- You're amazing.
- Good job.
- I have some time left.
- So Min, move as fast as you can.
- You should go far away.
- Move fast. One.
- What is your problem?
- Hey!
- I'm so relieved.
- What is that?
- Two.
- I mean...
- What is wrong with her?
- Move faster! Keep it together!
- Hurry up!
- You don't have time for that. Run!
- Hurry. Place pieces here.
- What is wrong with her?
- Hurry up and go back. Run.
- Go.
- What is wrong with So Min?
- You should've gone far away.
- You're so funny.
- That's not a good move.
I thought it was strange.
- You're running out of time.
- Nice.
- Just put them there. Good.
- That was good.
- We should block the line for now.
- Move.
- Yes, block the line.
- We should block all of them.
- Gosh. We don't get to attack.
- Good. Okay.
- Just put it there. Good.
- Good job.
At the end of the white line. Good.
And place the other one
anywhere you want.
- You're running out of time.
- Good.
That's good. Let's keep attacking.
- Perfect.
- It's over.
We should block both ends.
(Team Black made a line
of five pieces!)
If you don't block it, they'll win.
- BE'O, do you want to do it?
- Yes, I'll do it.
- Okay. You do it.
- Okay. Go ahead.
Oh, my. I didn't think
this would be this fun.
My gosh. It's going on for longer
than I thought.
- They'll win if you don't block it.
- It's going on for so long.
But we have a chance to win too,
BE'O.
- Eight. Nine.
- He's run out of energy.
Hey, he looks exhausted.
- They'll win if you don't block it.
- We should block both ends.
- Block both ends of this line.
- Hey, hurry up.
Yes, that's good. Go back.
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
(Next up is Suk Jin.)
Three. Four.
- They need to stretch the line.
- Seven.
- We should block the line.
- Suk Jin, block this line.
- Add pieces to the white line.
- Which one should I block?
- You should block this line.
- Let's attack.
- That's right.
- My gosh. Are you serious?
- Okay. Go back now.
- We should block the black line.
- We have to attack this time.
- You should block the red line.
There's a line of five white pieces.
- Five white pieces in a row.
- Who's next?
Isn't it Team Red?
Let's just go our separate ways.
I don't even know anymore.
- Go our separate ways?
- Then it'll be over.
- No. You can block this red line...
- Team Red is up next.
- or that white line.
- The white line has five pieces.
- We blocked it in the end.
- It's over now.
- Team Red, you can block it.
- It's over.
- Help us place second at least.
- Team Red has no chance.
- Team Red, you can block it.
- We can add two pieces to our line.
- Come on.
- We can win with two pieces.
- Don't do that.
- Can't you block that line instead?
- I should've played.
- Okay.
- Hurry. We can win with two pieces.
(All BE'O has to do is
place pieces just as he was told.)
(Will Team Red win like this?)
- Yes... No! Hey, BE'O!
- Yes!
- Okay!
- Hurry up and play our pieces.
- Why?
- You should've put it here.
- My gosh.
- BE'O, you should've put it here.
- That was unexpected.
- My gosh. What?
- Right here.
- Eight.
- We would've won.
Go now. Suk Jin.
- We'll win if I complete it, right?
- Yes.
- Gosh. I can't believe this.
- My gosh.
- Yes!
- The second place...
(Team White completed
a line of six pieces.)
- Go and press the button.
- Yes!
(It's not over yet.)
- Then the second place...
- That was close.
- Hey, come here, BE'O.
- I'm sorry.
- Why did you do that?
- I didn't see...
- the empty space.
- Don't you want a black limousine?
- Don't you? Why would you do that?
- My gosh.
- That was unexpected.
- The second round is over.
The teams that placed 2nd and 3rd
in the 1st round...
- can exchange one card.
- I see.
The team that placed 1st can exchange
2 cards at the end.
- We go 1st?
- Shall we exchange a card 1st?
Yes, you go first.
- Hold on.
- It's pointless to do so now.
- How about we pick that team?
- Let's use the coins at the end.
- At the end?
- To check the cards. Not now.
- I agree.
Okay.
I was going to choose BE'O's.
(He exchanged his card with BE'O's.)
- I'll check it.
- Okay.
Team Jukjae also exchanged
their card with another.
- You can check it now.
- It seemed hard.
What? Oh, it's the other side.
- It must be a Poop Card.
- I can tell it's not a Star Card.
- I could just tell by his face.
- Gosh. Suk Jin...
It was written on his face.
(Seok Sam picked the only Poop Card
that Team BE'O had.)
- Now, the team in the second place.
- It was written on his face.
You can exchange cards
with any of the other teams.
We should exchange a card
no matter what.
- Nice.
- Bring it to us.
- Bring it here.
(They picked Team BE'O
that had two Star Cards.)
Haha, I'll count to three
and open it, okay?
- One.
- Come on!
(Did they finally obtain
a Star Card?)
(Grunting)
They looked genuinely upset.
I don't they faked it.
The team in the 1st place
can exchange up to 2 cards.
- Two cards?
- Yes.
Okay.
Which team? Choose the team first.
Could they exchange one
with each team?
(Staring)
Didn't you promise
you wouldn't take ours?
That's right.
- I almost forgot about it.
- Suk Jin is right.
- Yes, they did.
- Didn't you make that promise?
I think you did.
Well, I did promise that, but...
- What do you mean?
- "I did promise that, but..."
I mean, we need to improve
our chances of getting Star Cards.
- We'll pick the other team for now.
- Okay.
- That team.
- Us?
- Us? Okay. I'll shuffle them.
- Yes. Please shuffle the cards.
- BE'O picked good cards earlier.
- Right. BE'O, pick one card.
- Okay.
- If you pick one,
- I'll pick another.
- BE'O, why are you limping?
- No, I'm not.
- Are you okay?
- You're giving us that card?
- I don't know which one it is.
- That one? Are you sure? Okay.
- Okay.
Take it. Go.
One more.
Ji Hyo, let's exchange one more.
(Glancing)
You picked them after all.
It's just that you picked us first.
No way. Are you going to exchange
your card for ours?
- Are you going to pick us?
- I'm sorry.
We have no choice. I'm sorry.
- I'm just curious.
- It's understandable.
I mean, your team placed first
thanks to us.
- True. I'm sorry.
- I placed our pieces...
- right here, you know.
- Are you apologizing?
- I put two pieces here.
- He's apologizing.
- You should accept his apology.
- Right. He has no choice.
I'm not doing it to keep my promise.
Another member will do.
That doesn't mean anything.
You are all on the same team.
- I'm sorry.
- I mean...
- He apologized.
- I'm sorry.
- Bow your head.
- I apologize.
- You two apologize as well.
- I'm sorry.
- My gosh.
Since when did you allow this
just because we apologize?
- It's been a while.
- My gosh.
That was neat.
- All teams have exchanged cards.
- Let's check it.
- We counted the stars you have.
- Yes.
The team in the first place that'll
enjoy all supplies they need...
- staying warm inside is...
- Is there a winning team?
- Team BE'O.
- What?
- Really?
- Yes.
- They must have Star-Poop-Star.
- I think that's the case.
The team
that's lucky to stay inside is...
- Team Jukjae.
- Nice.
The team
that will stay in a tent outside...
- in the cold is...
- You can't mistreat us like this.
(They have to stay outside
where a cold wind is blowing.)
Team Haha.
- Now, you can enjoy yourselves...
- Right.
with your team members.
- But...
- Let's go!
- We're in the last place.
- Okay.
This is where we... How nice.
What? Where should we go?
Oh, this is it.
My, this is so nice.
Oh, my. Our place is so nice.
(Cozy)
Hey, we have ramyeon here too.
That's great.
Jae Suk,
would you like to have some ramyeon?
(The best place
with various snacks and amenities)
I'm full, but shall I have some?
- Well, we just...
- That looks like...
Are we puppies or what?
- We're not puppies. What is this?
- Oh, this is all you have.
- My goodness.
- Are we puppies or what?
Can we go in with our shoes on?
- Yes, you can.
- My gosh. Our place is so nice.
- Is this where we're staying?
- Are we puppies or what?
It's not so bad.
There's a carpet on the floor. It's nice.
- Oh, my.
- What are they doing out there?
Oh, boy.
- Then we...
- Hey, guys.
Yes!
- The guys outside.
- They have to make a fire.
Gosh. We have nothing here.
(It's just a yard.)
Hey, this is...
You guys are so mean.
(The bottled water froze
as the temperature is below zero.)
- Is a dream where you pee good?
- Of course.
How about a dream where your poop is
as big as a radish?
That's a good dream.
You should buy a lottery.
- Haha.
- Yes?
I heard that we're allowed to do it.
What's that?
Are we having lunch here?
What should we do here?
Until the next mission begins,
chop firewood, start a fire,
and cook sweet potatoes.
We can move to another team
if we pay 100 dollars in cash.
- We can move to another team?
- Yes.
You can't move to another team.
Can I pay by Kakao Pay?
They want to send me
to another team.
- That's not true, So Min. Nonsense.
- So Min.
- First...
- Let's cook some sweet potatoes.
- Se Chan, chop the firewood.
- Yes?
- Okay. I'll do that.
- I'll start a fire.
- I'm good at starting a fire.
- Gosh, I'm so cold.
- So Min, that's not how it works.
- You're doing it wrong.
- You've never done it before.
- Hold on.
I'll start a fire
and let you do the rest.
We need some paper too.
Oh, there it is.
(Se Chan is going to use the paper
as kindling.)
(So Min tries to light
the piece of wood on fire again.)
- No, So Min. What are you doing?
- So Min.
I told you, that's not how it works.
I'm trying to ignite...
- You should put it on top of this.
- I know. I'm just...
- trying to ignite it first.
- No. That's not how you do it.
- Stop. We should stack them first.
- Don't do that.
- I said it wasn't the right way.
- So Min.
We can do it this way.
- What's wrong with her?
- We have to stack them first.
- Like this.
- Stack the wood first.
- Stop it. Gosh, it's hot.
- It's on fire. Stack them now.
So Min, it's dangerous.
You should stay away.
We should let air go through them,
So Min.
Why are you guys doing this to me?
Why would you call my name only?
So Min, stay away.
Look.
It's not getting enough air, So Min.
- Give me that. I'll put it in here.
- It hurts my eyes.
I said not to do it like that.
- I'm just putting it...
- It needs enough air.
- Hey!
- I put it under there.
You can't start a fire like that.
Just put it under the wood.
Like this.
- I mean...
- Let's start over again.
- We have to do it all over again.
- No. I said it was burning.
- Be careful. We should put it out.
- Only the paper is on fire.
You're not doing it the right way.
What did I just say?
- He's right, So Min.
- They say everything is wrong.
- Sorry?
- Whatever she does is wrong to you.
Whatever I do,
they say I do it the wrong way.
That's not true. It's not like that.
Among those who go camping often,
Haha is the best.
This is crazy. You'd be the only one
to survive on "Law of the Jungle."
- Yes. I've done this on the show.
- I think so.
- Really?
- He's right.
- He's done this on the show too.
- Yes.
Actually, I had a meeting with them,
but they didn't cast me.
Why?
I don't know.
They didn't tell me the reason.
- Really?
- I didn't know that could happen.
- They rarely refuse to cast anyone.
- I know.
So Min, how about we start a fire
while you're gone?
Come back when we say,
"Princess So Min will enter." Okay?
- That sounds great.
- Right? What do you say?
She'll look like
the star of the day.
Do you want to do that or not?
I don't want to do it.
Wait. It looks good.
Okay. Good.
That piece of wood caught fire.
- Good. Wait.
- So Min, we're...
(So Min's wood)
- We're trying to make it work.
- No, put it away.
- Done.
- Okay. Stay away, So Min.
It's burning now.
(Sad)
Don't be upset.
We didn't mean to upset you.
- It's burning now.
- So Min did all the work.
(Haha teases her.)
Do you do this to Song Yi too?
(While the members of the team
in the last place are squabbling...)
I think
there's food in the fridge too.
- What? Hey.
- Oh, my.
- My goodness.
- Nice.
(There's a lot of food
in the fridge.)
- My goodness.
- Nice.
- Gosh.
- What is it?
You look so jealous right now.
I wanted to know
what was in the fridge.
Jae Suk, there's this ramyeon.
Come on, mister.
Let's not be this way.
They also have coffee.
- Don't you want some coffee?
- We should move the rack.
Hold on.
- You can't.
- We can't have you stealing.
Unbelievable.
This is nice though.
Look at them in comparison.
BE'O, are you good
at cooking ramyeon?
I'm not.
(I can't cook it well.)
Is there anything you can do?
(BE'O isn't good at anything.)
All you can do
is release great songs.
- Three packets of ramyeon?
- Sure, let's have three.
- Let's cook three, then.
- Sure.
(They start cooking the ramyeon.)
- Should I add them all in?
- Yes.
- You're making ramyeon.
- Of course.
- Are you cooking ramyeon?
- Yes, ramyeon.
That looks delicious.
How many star coins
for some ramyeon?
Will you cook some for us?
- In exchange for coins?
- How much is a ramyeon worth?
Can we get three ramyeon for a coin?
For two coins, you can have ramyeon,
Americano, and whatever you want.
- Really?
- That sounds like a decent deal.
We have seven coins right now.
You must really want some.
- He really wants some.
- I...
- Excuse me.
- One for one.
We can spare one coin.
That'll get you an Americano.
How about an Americano
and an instant cup ramyeon?
We'll get you
an instant cup ramyeon.
(They agree to pay a coin for coffee
and an instant cup ramyeon.)
- Here.
- Is this necessary though?
- Hold on a second.
- Hey.
- The hot water.
- At least give us hot water.
Come on.
Pour this coffee in it.
(Pour this coffee in it.)
(Jukjae sips
the coffee they obtained.)
They must not be able to see us
from out there.
I think that's the case.
(Are two sips all that he's having?)
This is the cup ramyeon
that Son Heung Min promotes.
(He slowly walks over to the others
looking for something.)
It's the brand that he promotes.
All I need is some water.
Son Heung Min's everywhere
these days.
Absolutely.
(Looking around)
- Heung Min...
- If I were an advertiser...
What can I get you?
- This is cold brew coffee.
- And?
He must not want it.
- You don't drink cold brew?
- Cold brew isn't his jam.
You're a fussy one, aren't you?
You're quite picky.
Can't I get
an espresso-based coffee?
Jae Suk, come on.
- Okay, fine.
- Get him something else.
How about this, then?
It's black coffee.
- Give him that instead.
- That.
- That isn't coffee though.
- We want our money back.
We want our money back.
Just forget about it.
- I'll give you hot water.
- What?
Hot water.
- I'll give you hot water.
- Sure thing.
- You asked for some.
- Is that how it goes?
- Sure, get me some water.
- Hot water.
(Oh no!)
(The cup ramyeon drops.)
- What happened?
- I'm sorry.
What do you think you're doing?
- I...
- I'm sorry.
How did this even happen?
Let's clean this up.
When things seem hard for us...
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- Look at the window.
- Of course.
- They're burning firewood.
- See?
They're burning firewood.
Jukjae, check them out.
When things get hard for us,
watch them instead.
- We should be happy.
- Look.
So Min, I only say this
because it's dangerous.
- So Min, wait.
- It caught on fire.
- It's dangerous, that's all.
- Wait behind the camera.
- Hold on.
It might explode.
I think there's treasure
hidden over there.
So Min, come on.
Let's get some twigs.
- So Min.
- Yes?
Let's get some twigs.
(Se Chan tries to lure So Min away.)
- No?
- Go ahead.
No, let's go together.
- Getting twigs sounds like fun.
- Tell me about it.
- It'll burn better with some.
- Go ahead without me.
So Min, come on.
Come on.
(The Fellowship of the Twigs)
We'll bring more twigs.
(In the meantime,
Haha tries to light the fire.)
Twigs? I don't see any.
- Here.
- Hold on.
Collect these instead.
So Min, these will do.
These will burn well.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- We're good. How much do you have?
- What's this?
What's this?
- It's poop.
- Darn it.
Shoot.
(So Min picked up nature's fuel.)
(Being sick)
Hurry on over.
(Poop Girl runs to someplace else.)
- Haha!
- She picked poop up.
- Haha.
- Yes?
Haha...
(She returns cheerfully
with a tree branch.)
Cut that up with the ax.
Enjoy the ramyeon while you can.
He's right about that.
Later on, we could be the ones
trying to light a fire.
- Would you like to sit here?
- I'm good where I am.
(My gosh!)
When someone is cooking ramyeon,
it's best not to intervene.
Ramyeon always delivers.
(No way)
Jukjae, can you play
the guitar for us?
He can't do it for free, you know.
You can't request that
after moving the snacks over there.
I don't think I can...
play the guitar for free.
- Right?
- I mean...
You should at least
offer him something.
I'll give him what he wants
if he chooses to play.
Go ahead and play something.
I wouldn't let him be
if he went back on his word.
(I wouldn't let him be
if he went back on his word.)
Jong Kook, seriously.
- Must you threaten me like that?
- Gosh.
I'm just saying. That's all.
- That could be us later on.
- Right.
Let's not be too harsh.
You must start off with "Romance."
- Sure. We'll start with "Romance."
- Start off with "Romance."
- Let me play it for you.
- Seriously?
- What the...
- "Romance."
Unbelievable.
- But he's not the real deal.
- It's all right.
That's not how it should be.
No way. Jukjae, I can't accept this.
What do you mean?
It sounds the same. You try it.
- Of course, it's different.
- I'm a musician too, you know.
I may not be qualified,
but I know the sound of good music.
It's different.
- It sure is different.
- It is.
(That's what I'm talking about!)
- It's different.
- It's totally different.
- There's a sharpness to it.
- And it's emotional.
- Isn't it different?
- It is.
- It sure is.
Like I said,
I can tell what quality music is.
No wonder he's a professional.
(Absorbed in the music)
- Again, from the top.
- Not so fast.
- What can we get?
- Give us something.
Come on. It can't be for free.
Was that a one-minute preview?
- What the...
- It was a one-minute preview.
- What is this?
- A one-minute preview.
- Was that a one-minute preview?
- It was.
Get us something for that.
- Jukjae, hold on.
- That's it.
Come on.
(Chocolate)
- That's it.
- Good.
We should only be having
Ghana Chocolate!
Here. Can you play
something else now?
- Good.
- That was a good deal.
Nice.
Is there a piece
you'd like to request?
Can you play a song by Sting?
- Sting?
- That's right.
Hold on a second.
What were the chords again?
Are you attempting
"Shape of My Heart?"
(He's touched.)
(Jukjae the jukebox
plays anything upon request.)
(Ji Hyo has become a fan.)
- Your minute is up.
- Play a bit more, will you?
- Seriously?
- Forget it.
I'll take the minute.
Play for a minute
and be done with it.
- I've had it with you.
- A one-minute preview.
- It's your one-minute preview.
- That's just wrong.
- Give us something else.
- I won't allow it.
An artist shouldn't have to starve.
- A minute is too short.
- You can't...
- That's his talent.
- Hear us out.
His talent isn't for free.
You can't hear anything
if you don't pay for it.
We already paid
for your service though.
They won't pay
for the music service.
- We'll present something.
- Sure. What will it be?
How about "Limousine?"
Fine, but how...
- When nothing is prepared for him?
- What?
- Will he just sing it?
- Hold on.
It seems to be news to BE'O.
All Jukjae needs is a guitar,
and all BE'O needs is a mic.
A mic?
- Does it work?
- Of course.
- I can't hear him though.
- Go ahead.
The black limousine
(The black limousine)
(The sound comes from his throat.)
What on earth was that?
- Are you sure about this?
- You croaked like a crow.
What's wrong with this mic?
- What's wrong?
- What's the matter with it?
Mic testing. Hold on.
(Mic testing)
That's how it should be.
And then it's night in the fall
Can't you sing when we request it?
- You're doing great.
- Don't sing whenever you want...
and sing upon request.
- My eyes sting.
- Mine too. I'm tearing up.
(The team in last place
is inhaling the smoke.)
How can it be so different for us?
Exactly.
BE'O's performing for them.
I'm so jealous.
I'm jealous too.
(Bowing)
- Request a song.
- Just this once.
(Just 1 song)
(Thumbs up)
He's slow when it comes
to picking up signals.
You find him frustrating, don't you?
Right.
Why?
- He's slow on picking up on things.
- What?
That frustrates you, doesn't it?
How do you think we feel right now?
You must be frustrated.
(She puts herself in their shoes.)
- I'm starving though.
- Me too.
It'll take a while.
The foil being black
doesn't mean it's cooked.
We should've stuck those underneath
before we started the fire.
- Which ones?
- The potatoes and sweet potatoes.
- When there was no fire?
- No way.
- No.
- Topped with burning firewood.
- She's at it again.
- She's being stubborn again.
You're at this once again.
Should we rewind the video?
Does Jukjae frustrate you or not?
- He does.
- Why?
- He can't take a hint.
- Exactly.
What about you?
Do you get what we're saying?
No.
(I don't get what you're saying.)
(She confesses.)
So Min, that's it.
(The mirroring treatment worked.)
- Give it up for BE'O!
- Yes!
Thank you.
That was great.
I'm loving this atmosphere.
Who knew we'd get
to see BE'O perform?
That's it, Jae Suk.
There's nothing more to do.
- That's enough.
- All right.
("One Man" by Kim Jong Kook,
released in 2004)
Pass him the mic.
- Here's the mic.
- Please.
(Please...)
- Please don't.
- Here's the mic.
It's worth jelly and chips.
- It
- Nice.
(Has been long)
You're doing good.
(The original singer
starts to sing.)
(A singer with a million-seller
album tries to earn jellies.)
Jong Kook should release
a song like this.
Release a song.
Do you know this song?
I've never heard of it.
- You really don't know?
- He doesn't know the song.
Jong Kook, I'm sorry,
but this is enough.
- He doesn't know the song.
- He would know the main part.
- Listen to the main part.
- If he hears the main part...
- Listen to the pain part.
- Hold on.
Listen to the main part.
- He's a little...
- He doesn't know.
- You know it, right?
- Yes.
You must've heard it
in your parents' car.
- Here it comes.
- Here.
(It's coming.)
- Listen to it carefully.
- Here it comes.
(There's a man)
Oh, "One Man."
(Who loved you so much)
- You know it.
- I know it.
(BE'O knows it.)
- He knows it.
- You know it, right?
- I know it.
- Yes, you do.
What's the matter?
This is my song.
- You didn't know? It's my song.
- It's your song.
Did you not know? He didn't know.
Hey, you're interrupting
at an important timing.
- What's the matter, So Min?
- She smells like firewood.
- You smell like firewood so much.
- What's the matter?
- Why did you come?
Can you sing 2 songs for 1 coin?
- That's possible.
You should go down. I made a fire.
- Down there?
- Sing for her down there.
- This is more than enough.
- Do it for her.
- He can do it.
- Jukjae, make money.
- I'll earn a coin.
- Yes. Make money.
- You were asked to perform.
- I'll get going.
- See you, Jukjae.
- See you.
- Jukjae.
- Just sing the first verse twice.
- Okay.
- Don't sing three songs.
- He was asked to perform.
- It's so nice.
(Just for one star coin,
he sang outside.)
How many songs did you sing?
It's cold outside.
- I know. It was cold.
- The water outside is frozen.
- It's cold, isn't it?
- It's minus 7℃ or something.
The bottled water is all frozen.
You smell like firewood.
- I think I would.
- Yes.
You smell like barbecue.
Thank you for making a fire outside.
- It must've been nice for you.
- We watched a concert.
It's tough outside.
- Yes. That's how it is.
- These guys smell like Seoul.
(The country bumpkins are surprised
by the smell of Seoul.)
They smell like perfume.
You guys smell like firewood
so much.
We smell like fire.
The mission is All Kinds of Songs.
Look at the lyrics of two songs
and pick the song...
that fits the theme better
through a discussion.
- I like it.
- A discussion? I like it.
We like discussions.
- We have So Min.
- It's what she's good at.
- It's nice, So Min. Show them.
- Let's do it.
Thirty staff members will also vote
after hearing the discussion.
Only the members who pick
the same song...
chosen by the majority
will receive one point.
The rankings will be decided
based on the total points you earn.
I got it.
Before revealing the 1st theme,
listen to the 2 songs.
Shall we?
I like listening to music so much.
Play the first song.
(The first song)
- It's their song. TEEN TOP.
- "No More Perfume On You..."
by TEEN TOP.
("Not More Perfume On You"
by TEEN TOP)
(It's a "masterpiece people secretly
enjoy" that sings...)
(about the secret of a bad guy.)
I guess he's from Seoul.
I love this song.
But those moves are old.
(The one from Seoul
whose moves are old)
Is it interesting? Does it feel
like you're watching TV?
- Yes.
- It's like watching TV.
Does it feel
like you're watching TV?
(Dancing)
(Fake TEEN TOP is very excited.)
I love this song.
- What's this song about?
- Why did you choose this song?
(Song A is "No More Perfume On You"
Jae Suk likes.)
- It's about perfume.
- I love this song.
(Song B)
Is it the second song?
Isn't it Jong Kook's song?
(It's a song Jong Kook sang
21 years ago.)
("X" by Turbo became number 1
on music shows 7 times...)
(and sold a million copies.)
Do it.
Kook Jong.
(The original singer is here.)
There you go. You're doing good.
(He can still do the steps.)
(The swirl dance)
There you go.
(It's an actual dance.)
You should do it.
(Fancy performance by a former Turbo
member and a dance music singer)
- It's "X."
- Well done, Kook Jong.
(He showed what his main job was
after a long time.)
The topic of the discussion related
to the lyrics of these songs...
is the guy you should never date.
(TEEN TOP or Turbo,
which one should you never date?)
- There are a lot.
- I'll show you the lyrics.
("No More Perfume On You"
by TEEN TOP)
(The guy who asks a woman not to
wear perfume as he's cheating.)
(Don't wear perfume,
I'll get caught by my girlfriend.)
(Don't wear sparkly eyeshadow.
It'll get on my clothes.)
(Don't say other things,
just do as I say.)
"The guy who asks a woman not to
wear perfume as he's cheating."
- Not to get caught?
- Is he cheating?
- Which one is worse?
- The guy you should never date.
(The guy who asks a woman not to
wear perfume as he's cheating.)
- He's so bad.
- "I'll get caught by my girlfriend."
- Isn't he trash?
- You can't do that.
- He's trash.
- It doesn't make sense.
- Is this what the song is about?
- It's like "Love and War."
What is the song about, Jong Kook?
- Look.
- He became the boyfriend of...
- Explain.
- It's...
("X" by Turbo)
(The guy who is dating his crush's friend
as he isn't brave enough.)
(I found my dream girl
who is like my destiny.)
(But I lost the courage to approach her
because of her overconfidence.)
(I tried to find a way to stay
beside her no matter what it takes.)
"I tried to find a way to stay
beside her no matter what it takes."
"And I chose you,
her best friend in the end."
In short,
he's dating a friend of his crush,
not his crush.
He became her boyfriend
to stay with her friend.
(The guy who is dating his crush's friend
as he isn't brave enough)
Dating her friend isn't right.
He's trash.
He loves her friend.
- But...
- You sang it.
- I didn't know when I sang it.
- So...
You shouldn't dance on it like this.
I didn't know.
- So it's like...
- Gosh.
- Is he cheating?
- Between the two,
- Who is worse?
- which one should you never date?
I think B is worse.
I think A is worse.
- The last one is the worse.
- Hey.
Turbo is also...
- Look at the last part.
- No.
Turbo is also...
(Glaring)
(The original singer is provoked
by the listener's comment.)
- Hey.
- I wasn't talking about you.
I wasn't talking about you.
- Thinking about it, he's so...
- It's the lyrics.
- If I were the girl...
- I didn't write the lyrics.
- Sit down and talk. Calm down.
- Yes.
- Basically, it's a discussion.
Even if you have different opinions,
please discuss with respect.
- Okay. I'll speak with respect.
- But it makes you angry.
- How about you, BE'O?
- What do young people think?
- I think it's B.
- You think B is worse?
- He's worse? Why?
- He's worse.
- Does it make sense?
- Because...
- he doesn't like her, but he lied.
- Right.
- It's a scam.
- Yes.
- A is a scammer too.
- But he's blatantly doing it.
- Then...
Listen to his opinion until the end.
BE'O is a good talker.
- Hold on.
- Wait.
His crush is his girlfriend's friend.
It will hurt both her...
and her friend. Both will get hurt.
He shouldn't get caught
until the end.
I think A is hurting both by lying.
Both the girl he's seeing...
and his girlfriend.
For B, as he dates her,
- he might click with her.
- Yes. He might fall in love.
Then it's not bad.
- Only the beginning is wrong.
- Yes.
Yes.
- Sharing their tastes and stuff...
- Right.
- They might be compatible.
- It might end...
- in a good way, right?
- Yes.
It didn't start
in a good way, but...
Actually, A is cheating,
but B isn't cheating.
- No, he's not.
- He's not.
But B is cheating in his mind.
- Look.
- No, he isn't.
- Yes, he is.
- No.
(No, he isn't.)
(Yes, he is.)
They're breaking up.
- Listen.
- I... Why should I listen?
He might end up liking her.
- They're arguing.
- But Jong Kook.
It's the first time
after a long while.
Isn't it good in the end?
- Look.
- No, it isn't.
- Just once.
- It is, in the end.
They know each other here.
- Right.
- They're close.
Are you giving us a lecture?
- He's between best friends.
- Yes.
A guy called Turbo
is getting between them.
- Do you know what's more annoying?
- He's coming between them,
not getting between them.
In "Love Is," his friend...
- Haha.
- took his girlfriend away from him.
- Then here, he suddenly...
- Haha.
- I'm sorry, but...
- It infuriates me.
Don't say
something unrelated to this.
- But A is...
- Don't talk about "Love Is."
- He shouldn't do that.
- She doesn't know.
He's just like a boy playing around
in a nightclub.
- No.
- He's the bad guy.
- Why?
I also think he's the bad one.
- Hey.
- TEEN TOP... Listen to me.
- He planned everything.
- Yes.
He's a really secretive guy.
- You should never date him.
- He's worse.
- Don't curse.
- He makes me curse!
- You should curse at him!
- Curse after this is over.
- How can I not curse?
- He planned everything.
- You sang this song!
- They're arguing.
- Jae Suk.
- You sang it.
- Okay.
- Why are you doing this?
- Yes.
- But B is at least...
How should I put it? He's romantic.
- Because he...
- He's romantic.
He chose her friend as he
couldn't tell her his feelings.
That's what I'm talking about.
- B is cheating on his girlfriend.
- He's cheating.
- So he's worse.
- Look.
Yes. Say it.
Dating this girl, A's relationship
with his girlfriend is over.
I mean their love is broken.
- No.
- He's keeping it as a secret.
But for B, he'll ruin both his
relationship and their friendship.
- It's a disaster.
- Right.
- No.
- His relationship won't break.
- It will.
- If he falls in love...
with his girlfriend,
his relationship will not be ruined.
- It will ruin it.
- He can save one of them.
Right. Look.
I think A is worse
because of the lyrics here.
- "Don't wear perfume,"
- Yes.
- "I'll get caught by my girlfriend."
- Exactly.
Right.
Look at the lyrics at the end.
"Just do as I say." That's gaslighting.
- That's LPG-lighting.
- What do you mean it's gaslighting?
He was LPG-lighting her.
- Look. So...
- Listen.
- Listen to me.
- It says "I found my dream girl."
Listen.
"Don't wear perfume."
This means this lady...
- also knows he has a girlfriend.
- She knows.
That's why it's more wrong.
That's why he's telling her
not to do those things.
Don't do this, don't do that.
- Sit down.
- That's right.
Sit down.
I can't sit down. I'm so annoyed.
- There's someone like that?
- Let's come to A.
- No, I...
- Actually,
there's some romantic vibe
in the old song.
- It has that feel.
- It does.
- The old-times vibe. It's cool.
- Yes.
- "Yes I love you, but..."
- I know.
- "But I love you."
- It's romantic.
But this jerk is...
(He punishes him himself.)
- Does it make sense?
- Look.
Let me say just one thing.
Jong Kook...
- explained this well.
- Yes.
- In the old times, this works.
- Yes. It's romantic.
In the 90s, this makes no sense.
- It makes no sense even now.
- It doesn't.
But now, this makes less sense.
No. This works.
He's not honest.
- Then who am I?
- That's right.
- It was all for the friend.
- My life is in ruins.
- Yes.
(Staring)
- My life is in ruins.
- Jae Suk.
- Hold on. Wait.
- They're fighting.
You keep putting yourself
in the shoes of the deceived girl.
Wait. Hey.
You keep putting yourself
in the shoes of the deceived girl.
Wait. Hey.
He said "hey."
- Hey, you.
- They're breaking up.
- Fight.
- No.
- It's romantic.
- Romance.
- Jong Kook.
- Hold on.
- What's romantic?
- So Min.
- Listen up.
You seem very angry.
Tell us what you think, So Min.
- So Min is angry.
- Tell us.
- She's angry.
- So Min is annoyed.
- She'll tell us the answer.
- I only focus on the present.
Just the present.
I don't look at the future or past.
- In this situation,
- Yes.
I'm already in the shoes
of the girl he's with now.
So like you said,
- "What am I? Am I a replacement?"
- "What am I?"
- Here you have two bad people.
- Yes.
- Here you have one innocent person.
- That's right.
- This is worse.
- Precisely.
- That's right.
- There's a victim.
- Hey.
- That's worse.
Why is there no innocent person
here?
- How nice is this girlfriend?
- That's right.
But they're cheating.
- The girlfriend is a nice person.
- How nice is this girlfriend?
(The focus shifted
to finding the nice person.)
- Here...
- Wait.
- The girlfriend is the victim.
When you look at it
from a third-person perspective...
- No.
- This is worse.
There is a victim here.
There is, but...
- There is a victim here.
- Excuse me, you have to debate...
- Wait.
- Debate.
- What?
- It's a debate.
Who are you?
Please have a discussion.
Don't fight.
- Who are you?
- This made us annoyed.
- That's right.
- Hey.
First, get to your seats.
- Change the seats.
- Think about it.
- Wait.
- Sit in the seats A or B.
I choose B. Isn't it obvious?
Go over that side, As.
- A.
- Go that side.
- A is worse.
- Yes.
- A is bad.
- Yes. A is bad.
- B.
- No, B is...
Why is B bad?
- Also...
- B is...
Wait. In the lyrics...
What we should remember is...
they are both bad. Both of them.
- They are both bad.
- But who is worse?
- That's the question.
- That's B.
- It's A.
- It's A!
A is worse.
- B!
- He's talking, you know.
Isn't he talking?
Jae Suk was talking first.
How old is he?
- First, sit down.
- You can...
What? "How old is he?"
- I'm here.
- "How old is he?"
- You're talking about age?
- Age?
Sit down.
- Look.
- What?
There is one bad person here.
But there, there are two.
- No.
- There...
There is no bad person in B.
- That's right.
- Right?
Because in B, this one man...
- He ruined everything.
- hurts the girl he doesn't like...
- and her friend...
- He didn't hurt her yet.
- That's right.
- He hurt her.
- They didn't start yet.
- He didn't hurt her.
His true heart is in here!
Not yet...
It's in here.
- Hold on.
- Come back.
- First,
- Yes.
it's not something that you see
these days.
- I know.
- This used to happen before.
- It used to be covered as sad love.
- Yes.
But like I said before,
for his current girlfriend,
this is a disaster.
Exactly. I feel bad for that girl.
Have you put yourself in her shoes?
What's more important is that
Kim Jong Kook, who sang this song,
danced to this song
without knowing what it was about.
Think about
how the girlfriend would feel.
They're fighting.
(Oh, my love, goodbye)
This...
This is more shocking for me.
It's a disaster for the girlfriend.
- I'm sorry, but...
- Isn't this too harsh?
I danced to it because...
You danced to it like this.
I danced to it
because I was in a dance group.
And that was a concept.
Dancing to a sad song.
- Is that right?
- Right.
- It's romantic.
- How is it romantic?
Why is that romantic?
- Romantic?
- It's like...
I'm holding your hand,
and at the same time
looking at Suk Jin with love.
- At Suk Jin?
- Yes. Is that all right with you?
But I'll send you to him
if you really love him.
But I wouldn't tell you.
Because I can't see Suk Jin
if it isn't with you.
But I think I'll let you go...
- if you really liked Suk Jin.
- But I'm hiding that feeling.
Look. There's you and Ji Hyo,
and I'm close to her.
Can't love her?
You can't.
That's not what's going on here.
- You like me.
- Come here, So Min and Se Chan.
I don't understand him.
He's not your boyfriend. Why...
She keeps saying she's with me
but she'll love Suk Jin.
- She keeps saying that.
- So MIn.
I kept asking her
why she couldn't meet Suk Jin.
- Why would you...
- Why are you saying that to him?
- Are you his girlfriend?
- She says we're together,
but she wants to meet Suk Jin.
So I said you can't do that.
- It drives me crazy.
- Do you know what he said?
He said he'll let me go to Suk Jin
if I really love him.
He said that.
He'll let me go.
If you like him, I'll let you go.
- Love him as you may.
- Yes. She should love him.
First...
What I think is important...
is that in this song,
they know what they're doing is wrong,
They know.
- but they still do it.
- That's right.
But here,
what he's doing isn't wrong.
- Yes. He didn't do anything wrong.
- Yes, he didn't.
There's nothing wrong here,
but here, both sides
are doing something wrong.
No way.
If Jukjae wrote the lyrics
of this song,
it would have sounded beautiful.
He would have said,
"Would you please put on perfume?"
- "My girlfriend will find out."
- "Could you use less glitter?"
- It's a light song.
"Please don't argue with me."
It's just that TEEN TOP
sang it with a strong tone.
That's not true.
Could you come with me
to put on perfume?
TEEN TOP...
is an idol group.
That's fooling you.
They also look handsome.
Imagine I'm the guy here.
"I feel like I've become a man
when I'm with you."
- What?
- Did you write this?
(He sounds suspicious.)
How old is this lady?
She should be
more than 60 years old.
Is she still alive?
Let me tell you. If she's older,
her son would be in the military.
Look.
(A lady older than Suk Jin
was summoned for the discussion.)
Look.
- The part that makes me annoyed...
- Yes.
"Don't put on perfume,
my wife will find out."
- To your wife.
- That's right.
- That's crazy.
- It's horrible.
It's different when you're dating.
- Having no courage to confess.
- Yes.
- How sad is that?
- It's sad.
He dates the friend of the person
he loves to stay next to her.
- The same goes here.
- Here, he's cheating!
He doesn't get caught
that he's cheating.
He tells the girl
to not wear perfume.
- How bad is that?
- Hey.
- He's cheating.
- That's bad.
How dare you argue with him?
Stay quiet.
- He hit me.
- What did you do?
Why are you hitting him?
- What are you doing?
- Why did you hit him?
(Chaos)
(There's no dignity or class here.)
Stop.
You want more?
You understand that?
What are you doing?
- You understand that?
- Look at that.
How bad is that?
He doesn't get caught cheating.
How sad is it for the girl
he's dating?
- What did she do wrong?
- She'll love this man.
The controversy is...
- I know. That's what I'm saying.
- Look.
Hey! Look at yourself!
You look at yourself!
You sang that song.
It's because of you.
You also sang "Love is."
- I sang it, but...
- Come back, Haha.
- Come here.
- I got so angry.
I got carried away.
Let's all sit down.
- Okay.
- Let's sit down.
This got heated.
- Cheating is...
- The staff are deciding, right?
Yes. First,
the members can hold up the panel...
of the song you think
has the worse man.
All right. One, two, three.
- A.
- We all think it's A.
Jae Suk also is holding A.
It was a mistake.
- It shouldn't be facing you.
- That's right.
Four of you chose B
and five of you chose A.
The staff can also choose...
- the song with the worse man.
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
- It's so annoying.
- More people chose B.
- B.
- A lot of people chose B.
- A.
- A lot of people chose A.
- More people chose A.
- It's A.
- As for the staff members...
- A.
- Thirteen people chose B.
- "No More Perfume on You."
- That's right.
- Justice is alive.
- The society with common sense.
- Cheating...
- It makes no sense.
- Three.
How is this even possible?
The three of you who were chosen
by the majority and...
- Ji Hyo chose A.
- I got it right.
Each one of you received
a point each.
- So 3, 1, and 1 point respectively.
- Okay.
- It makes no sense.
- Let's sit down.
- That was funny.
- The second theme will be revealed.
- This game is fun.
- Let's listen to the songs first.
Jong Kook,
sing this song with care
at the concert.
- I should do that.
- It's "Meant to Be."
("Meant to Be" by Solid)
("Meant to Be" is a dance song...)
(from Solid's 3rd album...)
(that became more popular
than the title song.)
- It's just this once
- Don't you know this song?
- I don't know it.
(The man who was born in 2000
doesn't know a song from 1996.)
- I left the house with excitement
- The weather is nice, I feel great
- In any case, things were nice
BE'O hasn't heard this song before.
- Really?
- It's understandable. He is young.
It's my first time hearing it.
(Then comes Song B.)
I like this song.
It's a song by Uhm Jung Hwa.
("Love Only Allowed by Heaven"
by Uhm Jung Hwa)
"Love Only Allowed by Heaven."
("Love Only Allowed by Heaven"
is a ballad song...)
(that represents Uhm Jung Hwa
and sold 100,000 copies.)
- It's a nice song.
- It's a song by Uhm Jung Hwa.
(The sentimental frog
gets into the mood.)
(What kind of stories
do these two songs have?)
It's a nice song.
But the lyrics...
The lyrics were a bit off.
Here comes the second question.
Which couple would last longer?
- Which couple would last longer?
- A long-lasting couple.
- It will be easy.
- Yes.
- A long-lasting couple.
Unlike the first question,
this isn't about who is worse.
Which couple would last longer?
- Which couple would last longer?
- Yes.
- Explain the lyrics.
- In this song,
he swore that it was just this once
and attended a blind date.
He turned down the offer many times,
- but his friend insisted.
- So he attended a blind date.
When he got there,
- his girlfriend was there.
- Yes.
- His girlfriend lied too.
- That's right.
- They lied to each other.
- It was a blind date.
- Yes. But his girlfriend was there.
- That's the absolute worst.
They couldn't help but laugh and say
that they were meant to be.
- This makes no sense.
- Hold on.
- My goodness.
- That's the plot.
There was a twist.
They laughed and said
that they were meant to be.
This makes no sense.
- Hold on.
- My goodness.
That's the plot.
In the end, they met.
Thus, he changed his attitude
rather quickly.
It's funny.
This couple is cool.
They just laughed...
- after seeing each other.
- Yes.
They burst out laughing.
Couple A would last long.
- That's the plot.
- That's right.
- Couple B wouldn't last long.
- Let's now study...
- this song.
- Once a cheater, always a cheater.
This woman lost a friend
after she stole her boyfriend,
but the sky allowed
this fateful love.
Why did the sky allow it?
You know,
- it's her justification.
- It's her excuse.
- It's her justification.
How did she steal
her friend's boyfriend? How?
- She stole him. For example...
- Such a thing happens often.
Let's say Suk Jin and I were
a couple.
You stole me.
- I see.
- You get it now, right?
Judging from the cases
I have witnessed so far,
a relationship with a friend's lover
doesn't last long.
- It's true, but look at Couple B.
- They break up soon.
Both of them are cheaters.
- Hold on.
- Both of them are cheaters.
Here is the thing about Couple A.
- They laughed now, right?
- Yes.
They will think about it
on their way home.
- No.
- I am serious.
- Every time they fight.
- On their way home...
- "Hold on."
- "I can't believe it."
- "She agreed to a blind date."
- "I guess she wants to cheat."
- That's right.
- The cheating spirit.
- It will come up during a fight.
- Yes.
- It will come up...
- every time they fight.
- That's right.
It will come up
even after they get married...
and have a child.
"What were you thinking back then?"
"You were there too."
They will fight like that.
I think Couple A would last long.
They would last long.
- Couple B has it hard.
- But...
- you know...
- They have it hard.
- They wouldn't last.
Couple A would last long...
- despite the fights.
- I know.
- Right? They would last long.
- They would last long.
Let's take turns...
and share our opinions
for 30 seconds each.
This is what I think.
- Which couple would last long?
- The couple that would last long...
is this one because they share
something in common.
They betrayed the same person...
- for their love.
- So they will protect their love.
Because of guilt, they will maintain
a good relationship.
They will last longer than Couple A.
To endure the criticism,
they must prove their love.
I also think it's B.
The couple in Song A
won't be able to trust each other.
- There could be another blind date.
- That's right.
It's unbelievable that they laughed.
My goodness.
- They have good personalities.
- They were taken aback.
BE'O,
you are very different from me.
- They have good personalities.
- When you get married,
having a good personality
is crucial.
You put the past behind you.
- Suk Jin.
- That's how it is.
He is too young
to think about marriage.
- He is young.
- Listen.
- Calm down.
- It's true.
It's true.
What Suk Jin said is true.
I don't think
neither couple would last long.
If the woman in Song B finds
another man,
she will think
it's love only allowed by the sky.
- Yes.
- She will fall for him.
- That's a good point.
- She is bound to cheat again.
- I have the same thought.
- She is bound...
to blame it on the sky
until the end.
This couple is annoying.
They are annoying indeed.
- It makes no sense.
- They justify their love.
Their love can't be blessed.
- Seriously.
- There is a victim too.
But I had this thought.
Had Turbo sung this song,
they would have danced.
- We...
- It's a ballad song.
- We would have danced.
- We...
- Turbo was a dance group.
- Of course.
- They would have danced.
We danced to ballad songs.
We danced to "A Jazz Bar" too.
- That's right.
- Yes.
(Turbo can dance to ballad songs.)
Here is what I think.
Let's say I want to get married...
in that situation.
In Song B's situation,
I wouldn't be able to get married.
- I won't be able to invite anyone.
- Seriously.
It would be disastrous.
- But in Song A's situation,
- It would be funny.
the wedding will be funny.
"Se Chan, I knew that would happen."
"I knew you would get caught."
- The atmosphere will be merry.
- A wedding between comedians.
- It would be like a comedy skit.
- You can even talk about it...
while hosting the wedding.
- Of course.
- That's right.
- A friend would talk about it.
- "They met on a blind date."
- That's right.
"In the end, they got married.
Please give them a big hand."
- Then people will cheer.
- As for Song B,
how will the wedding go?
"Their love was only allowed
by the sky."
- Listen.
- There will only be three guests.
- "Please..."
- "Please look at the sky."
- There will be so much food left.
- They are bound to break up.
- If you think about marriage,
- Couple A is better...
- That's right.
- because they can invite people.
- We reached a conclusion.
- Yes.
- No one will choose B.
Please raise your answer
on the count of three.
Which couple would last longer?
- One, two, three.
- A.
- I chose A.
- All As.
Since everyone chose A,
we will move on to the next one.
- Everyone won a point.
- That's good.
- It's a competition.
- Please play the next songs.
There should be two bad guys.
What?
("Let's Go See the Stars" by Jukjae)
What are you up to?
It's a song by Jukjae.
- Let's go see the stars
This is nice.
("Let's Go See the Stars" is based
on Jukjae's actual experience.)
(Discord)
So Min, why are your eyes teary?
(It's nice.)
(She is cute.)
Hold on. "Put on a light jacket?"
(Getting ready for a debate)
"Put on a light jacket?"
Here comes the next song.
(The second song gets revealed.)
It's a song by Kim Dong Ryul.
"A Drunken Confession."
- I loved you from the start
I sang this song often.
I really like this song.
("A Drunken Confession" is a song
from Exhibition's 2nd album...)
(that was recorded
when the members were drunk.)
(It's a song men love to sing
at the karaoke.)
It's a song by Kim Dong Ryul.
That man...
Here is the question.
When you hear a confession of love,
which situation is more exciting?
The answer would be...
A, right?
B, of course.
It's A. Don't be ridiculous. It's A.
(The guy who asks you
to come out at night...)
(so that you can go and see
the stars with him.)
A is a song by Jukjae.
This man asks you
to go and see the stars with him.
(The guy who confesses
to the woman he loves...)
(in a drunken state)
It has the sentimentality
of the era, right?
- It's A.
- It's definitely A.
It's better to ask someone out
like that.
I hate it when a man confesses
in a drunken state.
- Really?
- It sounds like a lie.
What if he isn't that drunk?
- You sound quite drunk.
- He is only a bit drunk.
- Your face looks drunk.
- "Your face looks drunk?"
So Min,
when you consider
the situations in the two songs,
doesn't the person matter more?
- No.
- The person who is confessing.
- Let's say Jinyoung of GOT7...
- The person matters more.
confesses to you in a drunken state.
Jinyoung of GOT7 is the man
in "A Drunken Confession..."
and Se Chan is the man
in "Let's Go See the Stars."
(Let's go see the stars.)
- That's right.
- The person matters more.
(The balance is ruined.)
This man loved you from the start.
Why didn't he tell me sooner?
Seriously.
The person matters more.
- Let's say it's the same person.
- Okay.
- The same person.
- It's the same person.
"Let's go see the stars."
He does sound like a womanizer.
It sounds playful.
- He sounds like a player.
- To be honest,
I agree with Haha.
This man seems too experienced.
He must have done this many times.
"Put on a light jacket."
- He went to this place many times.
- No.
- He chose the day...
with the perfect weather,
so a light jacket is enough.
- He planned it all out.
- He mentioned a light jacket...
- because he has a car.
- No.
- No. He wants to walk.
- Think about sincerity.
- He is a womanizer.
- The old song has sincerity.
- I agree.
The love he suppressed
poured out in a drunken state.
It's quite pure.
"Let me make a confession now.
I loved you from the start."
- Listen.
- He has loved her for a while.
He has loved her for a while.
- It's true love.
- Yes. It's true love.
- As for that situation...
- How about this man?
- He likes her too.
- As for that situation...
I am sorry,
but he is simply seducing her.
- Don't say that.
- He is simply seducing her.
He is simply seducing her.
As for him,
he has loved her for a long while.
I would recommend the man in Song B
to my younger sister.
That's right.
- That's right.
- As for me.
- I would recommend him.
- Him?
Hey, he is a player!
- What?
- He has done this countless times.
- He isn't a player.
- A player?
- The man in Song B is the same.
- Is he a player?
- Jae Suk.
- Didn't you write the lyrics?
- He is a player.
- The man in Song B is the same.
- He sounds like a delinquent.
- Listen.
- Seriously.
- It's Jukjae's story.
- Let's hear from Jukjae.
- That's right.
- Didn't you write the lyrics?
Yes, I did.
Which situation
makes your heart flutter more?
"Let's Go See the Stars," of course.
I wrote it with a pure heart.
- It doesn't seem pure.
- Is it based on your experience?
I enjoyed stargazing.
- Yes. I did it often.
How could you call that pure?
Had the lyrics been "Put on a gown,"
- it wouldn't have been pure.
- Of course not.
- "Put on a light jacket."
- That isn't very pure. Look.
- "There is a lot I want to say,"
- A light jacket.
"but I won't rush things."
- That's right.
- "But I will hold your hand tight."
He is already thinking
about making physical contact.
Isn't it too much?
- Is it so hard to hold hands?
- Of course.
You can't hold hands
with someone you aren't dating.
Nothing has happened.
You can get permission.
You can excuse yourself...
- before holding her hand.
- That works.
You can ask, "Can I hold your hand?"
- I think Song A is...
- He just made a suggestion.
- If she bites, it's good.
- It's like fishing.
- No.
- It isn't like fishing.
- Be quiet.
- Listen.
- It isn't like fishing.
I bet he cast many lines too.
He is the singer.
- I am sorry.
- He is the singer.
- Ignore what we say.
Jukjae, I bet you didn't foresee
this kind of interpretation.
(They missed
the songwriter's intention.)
- I am sorry.
- I bet you didn't foresee it.
- It's just my interpretation.
- People have different views.
BE'O, what do you think?
I think the man
in "A Drunken Confession" is...
- He is sincere, right?
- He seems like a loser.
- That's right.
- I say that...
- He is still charming.
because he lacked courage
and had to rely on alcohol.
- That's right.
- That's how much he loves her.
- He should pluck up the courage.
- No.
- The man in Song A is a player.
- He is a player.
- The man in Song B isn't a loser.
- A player?
- He is a player.
The man in Song B could be
a player too.
- No. He only confessed once.
- He got drunk and...
- The man in Song A...
- Listen.
- must have confessed many times.
Maybe he confesses love
whenever he is drunk.
If he gets rejected, he will say,
"I said it because I was drunk."
- He says it himself.
- He lacks courage.
"This might be a mistake.
I might forget all in the morning."
- He might forget what he said.
- Yes.
BE'O.
You said he will say,
"I said it because I was drunk."
The man in Song A will say,
"I never said I liked you."
"I simply asked you
to go and see the stars with me."
See? He is a player.
(Those who think the man in Song A
is a player cheer.)
Suk Jin, you are doing great.
Don't say that.
- At least that man confessed.
- Jukjae was a player.
- Jukjae.
Jukjae, were you a player?
- Were you?
- It's a lighthearted suggestion.
I bet it was
the third call of the day.
- Suk Jin, no.
- No.
I bet it was a group message.
- He sent a group message.
It was the 3rd call.
It wasn't the 1st call.
- I...
- Jukjae, explain it yourself.
- Jukjae, the songwriter.
- It's not like...
It's not like I reached an old age,
but I can say this
from my experience.
What's said in a drunken state
ends that way.
- So...
- It ends that way.
What's said in a drunken state
ends that way.
If I compare the two men to liquor,
the man in Song B is like
undiluted whiskey.
But that punk, Jukjae...
- is like...
- Jukjae.
- heavily diluted whiskey.
- On the rock.
- It's light.
- Look at the lyrics.
- He is lighthearted.
The man in Song B goes,
"This won't happen again."
- He won't confess his love again.
- No.
But you know how players are.
"Where are you? What are you up to?"
"Really? Okay."
Then he calls another woman.
"Where are you? What are you up to?"
No way.
"I am home." Then he goes,
"Let's go see the stars."
He does that.
- He is a player.
- The man in Song A is a player.
The man in Song A knows
that this woman likes him.
- That's right.
- He is too confident.
- He already knows it.
- That's right.
- That confidence is an eyesore.
Seriously.
- He knows.
- Jukjae.
- That kind of confidence...
- Can you erase Jukjae's name?
"You are bound to come out..."
- "and go see the stars with me."
- That's right.
- Hey.
- "Just put on a light jacket."
(He feels dizzy.)
"We won't go anywhere far."
If she doesn't like the situation,
she can go home.
- It shows his consideration.
- In any case,
he knows...
that she likes him.
That's why he is behaving that way.
I think A will be successful
and B will be unsuccessful.
- Not necessarily.
- That's what I think.
- That's right.
- The lyrics...
I think the situation in Song B
is too oily.
And I feel like I have to lead him.
- It's like, "So what?"
- Isn't the other one oilier?
The man in Song A
makes my heart flutter more...
- because he leads me.
- That's right.
That's right.
That's a better confession of love.
The man in Song B...
Which confession of love
do you prefer?
- One, two, three.
- The man in Song A is a player.
This goes without saying.
You chose A.
A... Now...
- It's 5 to 4.
The staff members will vote now.
- All right.
- Seriously.
Which confession of love
do you prefer?
Which one is more sincere?
- Men would agree.
- One...
- It's more sincere.
- You know Exhibition.
One, two, three.
It's tacky, but B is better.
- A.
- It's A.
- It's B.
- A.
- One, two, three, four.
- five, six, seven...
- A.
- B is sincere.
- All men chose B. It's so funny.
All men chose B.
- B has depth.
- It's A.
- More people chose B.
- B got two more votes.
- Did it get two more votes?
- More people chose B.
- B won.
- So Min.
- That's right. It's better.
- Those who chose B...
will receive a point.
- It's more serious.
- Jukjae, I am sorry.
Now comes the result of the mission.
- We won all the points.
- Team Jukjae placed first.
Team Haha placed second.
Team BE'O placed third.
- All right.
- Jae Suk didn't get one right.
- What's wrong with you?
- I didn't get one right.
This time, you will receive
five coins each.
- All right.
- The 3rd place can exchange 1st.
It's so nice.
Shall we exchange the cards?
- Sure. It doesn't matter.
- Shall we exchange the cards?
We can exchange two cards.
- This one?
- Take whatever you want.
- Okay.
- Please show it to the camera.
(It's a Poop Card!)
It's yours.
We should take a card
from Jae Suk's team.
(Team Jukjae aims
for Team BE'O's card.)
It's the second place's turn
to exchange a card.
I will use three star coins.
Hurry up and distribute the cards.
- What?
- Distribute the cards.
We will exchange cards
with Jae Suk's team.
Let's check BE'O's card.
- BE'O's card.
- Show them.
- Show us.
BE'O, come on out.
Okay.
We can exchange cards now, right?
- Jae Suk's card?
- Go ahead.
- Jae Suk's card.
Jae Suk.
- Don't you have three Poop Cards?
- They were outside earlier.
We will exchange cards
with Jae Suk.
(Will they get a Star Card?)
(Gold star)
(They got a gold star!)
Thank goodness.
(Team BE'O lost a Star Card!)
(Team Haha's current cards)
(Star-Poop-Star?)
The first place...
(After the first mission,
Team Haha got a bronze star.)
(Don't you have three Poop Cards?)
(The Poop Trio acted like
they only had the Poop Cards.)
The 1st place can exchange
up to 2 cards.
Can we exchange one card
with each team?
- Yes. It doesn't matter.
- You can.
Seeing as how
she is holding it up...
It must be a Star Card.
Since she wants us to take it,
we shouldn't take it.
(Suk Jin wants to exchange cards
with Team BE'O.)
- Take Jae Suk's card.
- Okay.
Did you get it just now?
- No?
- What are you doing?
I received it.
Did you get it just now?
I can't tell you.
- Exchange cards with Team Haha.
- Team Haha.
Let's see.
Okay.
It's time for another exchange.
Se Chan, you put it away carefully.
- Carefully?
- Yes.
I don't know which cards they are.
We don't know either.
Tell me when to stop.
- Don't drop them.
- I will pick one.
- What?
- I don't know.
Did you want another card?
Why did you exchange cards
with Team Haha?
Team BE'O would have been
a better choice.
This time, the team that will get
the most amount of food...
is Team Haha.
- We can eat for free.
- We need to go outside.
We can eat for free.
- The second place is Team Jukjae.
- We like being outside.
Ji Hyo, we grilled potatoes
and sweet potatoes.
- Eat them.
- The third place is Team BE'O.
Please move to your spot.
We need to protect the cards now.
We got lucky.
Let's eat.
We should have gone there.
We are always here.
It's nice.
- The view is nice from here.
- This place is amazing.
Let's eat something.
Se Chan, it looks nice from here.
Don't even worry about the view.
Chapagetti sounds delicious.
Can we eat Chapagetti?
Of course.
- Shall we make one?
- Please make us Chapagetti.
- We will support you.
- Give us two coins as collateral.
If you do well,
we will give them back to you.
Otherwise, we will keep them.
If you betray us,
we will keep the coins.
- Otherwise, you will get them back.
- How about one?
Two coins.
You won't betray us anyway.
- We won't betray you.
- So give us two coins.
Let them pay one coin.
- One coin.
- Okay then.
- Receive the collateral.
- The collateral.
- Really?
- Choose what you want to eat.
- It's the collateral.
It's a great deal.
- Right?
- Yes.
Here.
(They complete the deal
with one coin as collateral.)
We will eat one Chapagetti.
Shall we make it?
We will betray you.
(Say hello to betrayal!)
- That was too...
- You got fooled.
(A betrayal
with no class whatsoever)
That was so cheap.
You stole 1, not 10 coins.
(Se Chan feels embarrassed as well.)
That was so cheap.
Let's eat something. I am hungry.
(It's time to savor the victory.)
- This and...
- Let's microwave another one.
(Suk Jin smelled food.)
What's that?
Crunchy fried chicken.
- Crunchy fried chicken?
- This isn't crunchy fried chicken.
We will eat it.
(It's a conversation you would hear
at an elementary school.)
Do you want it?
You are so childish.
Suk Jin, do you want it?
Answer politely.
(He is like a villain
in a tacky animated movie.)
Yes, sir. I want it.
All right.
- I didn't expect such food.
- You are so nice.
Okay. Open your mouth.
The airplane is coming.
Can't you just give me
the whole thing?
What?
- I'm sorry.
- Open your mouth.
Here comes the airplane.
(The crunchy fried chicken airplane
finally took off as he got along.)
(Opening his mouth)
- That's childish.
- It's delicious.
Give one to me.
One coin. Yes.
Try it.
(While he was begging to
have one bite of fried chicken...)
Try it.
- What are you doing?
- Try it.
- You baked the sweet potatoes.
- My gosh.
Jae Suk. Have some potatoes.
Should I?
(Team BE'O will enjoy it.)
- The previous team did a good job.
- Thank you.
(The potatoes are cooked well
thanks to the fire they made.)
Thank you.
I wish I had one more coin.
(It's even more delicious
as they didn't put any effort.)
It's delicious.
(Eating)
- The potato is really good.
- Right?
It's good.
- During this session,
- Yes.
as I said earlier,
the wish of the one who collects...
Star-Poop-Star the most
will be granted.
Write down your wish...
beforehand.
My wish?
You can write what you want
from the members.
Or you can write something you want
from the staff,
up to 1,000 dollars.
Can I write something like this?
"Just leave me alone."
I want nothing.
Oh, I could get rid of penalties.
- No penalties.
- No penalties sounds good.
You sang "Limousine."
Did you get one?
- No.
- Why not?
- I don't have a driver's license.
- You should get one first.
(While he's dreaming of having
a black limousine without a license)
Should I ask Jae Suk
to buy me an electric car?
Write that you want Jae Suk
to appear in "Jiseokjin World."
He should come once.
I appeared in "Pinggyego" so many times.
What should I write? My wish?
They said we should go down.
Let's go.
The last mission...
is Throw the Dice,
which is our signature game.
Two people from each team
will throw the dice.
- That's neat.
- The team...
with bigger total numbers will win.
That's neat.
The production team did a great job.
The members who will throw it
are decided.
Ji Hyo or BE'O can throw it.
- Yes. Let's do it first.
- Okay.
- Say that you'll do it.
- We should get six.
- Jukjae, can you throw it?
- Yes. Here I go.
(Gently)
- Oh, my.
- That's good.
- He threw it timidly.
- One.
- Oh, my.
- It's...
(Team Jukjae, 1)
- Oh, my.
- Jukjae.
You should've thrown it higher.
- You should throw it like this.
- He threw it. It's over.
He knows what to do
in a variety show.
BE'O, throw the dice.
- Let's get in the black limousine.
- Please.
I get off from the black limousine
He's doing well.
(What number is on the dice?)
- That's cool.
- One.
- Three.
- Three. It isn't bad.
- Three isn't bad.
- Not bad.
- It's okay. They might do worse.
- Three isn't bad.
Three isn't bad.
- Blank.
- Please get one.
- Let's see.
- Please be one.
What's wrong?
(The unlucky one
doesn't disappoint.)
I told you.
What's wrong with me?
I'm not really confident with dice.
Gosh, it's so...
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- Go, Korea!
- Let's go.
- Let's go with six.
- Six.
Go, Korea.
(The soccer fan wishes
on his country before throwing it!)
- Six.
- Go, Korea.
- It's five. It's not bad.
- It's good.
- It's the best for us.
- It's not bad.
- If you get 6...
- Or 3 or more.
- Six. Three or more.
- Please get six.
- Or just get three or more. Ji Hyo.
- What did they get?
- Let's go.
- One.
(Please.)
(Please get a lower number!)
- Let's go.
- One.
It's low.
- Two.
- We're in the first place.
(Team BE'O, 5)
(Team Jukjae, 6)
Jukjae, I told you.
You never know.
- I'll throw it.
- You're the best.
- I don't think he'll make it.
- Here I go.
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
- Let's get it.
- It's six, Se Chan.
- It'd be amazing.
- It's 6.
- Get 1, 2, or 3.
As long as we aren't last.
(Will they become the new number 1
or become the new last?)
- Okay. It's not bad.
- It's not bad.
(Team Haha, 5)
We almost got one.
- It's 5 in total.
- It's 5.
- Then...
- We're tied.
Team Jukjae is in the first place.
- How?
- We're in the first place.
The two teams are tied.
- So throw the dice once.
- Just once more.
- Okay. You throw it, So Min.
- So Min.
(So Min from Team Haha will try it.)
- You do it. Yes.
- I'll do it.
(What will Referee Jeon who was
mistreated all day get?)
Where is it going?
- Yes!
- Oh, my.
(She transformed from Referee Jeon
into the ace.)
- So Min, you're indeed our ace.
- That was amazing.
She's a lucky one.
(Team BE'O is getting more nervous.)
- It's not me.
- Just get six.
If they get six,
they should do it again.
(The fate of Team BE'O
depends on the unlucky one.)
Move over.
Where is it?
- It's two. Okay.
- Okay.
- Success.
- It went too far in the back.
We'll become last.
First place, Team Jukjae.
Second place, Team Haha.
Third place, Team BE'O.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
Again, if you trade now, that's it.
- Okay. We got two.
- Okay.
Let's see the wishes...
- you wrote earlier and trade.
- Yes.
- "Penalty transfer card?"
- What did Suk Jin write?
(Wish list)
- "Penalty transfer card?"
They wrote the same thing as me.
Suk Jin wants MSG Wannabe to be
on "Running Man" with a new song?
Yes. Just in case
you release a new song.
(Haha's long boots
shipped from abroad)
"Haha's long boots
shipped from abroad."
- What does it mean?
- He wants them.
The long boots. It's my wish.
(The rumor says
Haha cherishes the long boots.)
(During the show-throwing mission
in the fall special)
(He cares about the boots
more than his own body.)
(I waited for 1 year to get it!)
They asked me to write a wish.
I wrote "No penalties."
- "Penalty transfer."
- "Transfer."
"No penalties, Haha's long boots
shipped from abroad,"
"Donate 1,000 dollars
under my name." by So Min.
That's funny. 1,000 dollars.
That's heart-warming.
(It's a heart-warming wish
at the end of the year.)
Jukjae wants them to play
his song from his second album.
- That one is good too.
- That's nice.
- That's good too.
- Next week.
BE'O wrote
"One Running Man appearance."
- That's great.
- BE'O.
- This one is nice.
- "With the member I want."
- That's good.
Who do you want to come with?
Gray.
- Gray?
- Gray.
- Gray is nice.
Gray sounds good.
- Gray is good.
- It sounds good.
- He's good-looking.
- I like Gray.
He's nice.
You're going to trade one last time.
Team BE'O can pick one...
and trade first.
You should use five coins
to check it this time.
It means the rankings
aren't decided yet.
It's unfavorable for us though.
(Team Jukjae: Silver star, 2 poop)
Do we have ten?
- How many do we have?
- We got just five.
It's a relief.
- We'll take it.
- Okay.
We'll take So Min's.
- Use all of them.
- Let's use all of them. We got ten.
First, we'll check So Min's.
(He checks So Min's card first.)
Get close to the camera.
Go back.
- Why? Do you have a poop card?
- We can see it too.
We can see it too.
- I'll see yours.
- Yes. Come here.
In front of the camera.
(He peeked at the golden card.)
We'll trade with Se Chan.
Are you going to make it so obvious?
We'll give you a star too.
- Really?
- Yes. We'll give you a star.
- Are you sure?
- We got stars only.
Did you get it
to become first place?
We should mix them.
Jae Suk.
He was right. Thank you.
Second place, Team Haha,
you can trade one.
We'll trade with Jae Suk.
- Let me see.
- Let's see. Mix them.
- Each of us should have one.
- Five?
I got it
after Suk Jin betrayed me earlier.
- So Min, who should we choose?
- I want to see BE'O's.
Let's check BE'O's card and take
Jae Suk's card if it's bad.
- Yes. Let's do that.
- BE'O.
- Let's see it together.
- Come here.
- Gosh.
- Why?
- They changed it.
- No, we didn't.
- We didn't.
- You can't do that.
We didn't change it.
Change it.
Let's just trade.
- Take it.
- Show us.
We traded.
(They traded the card with Ji Hyo,
not Jae Suk. What will happen?)
Now, Team Jukjae can trade
up to two cards...
or keep the status quo.
- Jukjae, who do you want?
- Pick the one you want.
- So Min...
- Yes. So Min.
So Min, go see the stars with him.
- Really?
- Go see the stars.
They're really going
to see the stars.
(The bystanders in the back
are more excited about it.)
(Team Jukjae decided to check
So Min's card.)
(Here comes the gold star.)
(Grinning)
I'll trade.
Thank you.
That was a good guess.
- That was amazing.
- I knew you would do it.
- We won't change any more.
- Good.
Then the race is over now.
It's a bummer.
I'm sad.
We will reveal the results
of today's race.
Team Haha will go first.
Star.
- It's not a star. It's poop.
- It's a Poop Card.
- Star, poop, and...
- Star and poop. Right.
It's poop, star, poop.
Next up is Team BE'O.
- It's all Poop Cards.
- Poop.
(Poop, poop, poop)
- That's the worst.
- Is that possible?
- Is it possible?
- This is the worst.
Now, Team Jukjae,
show us your cards.
Start. Star.
- Poop.
- Star.
(Star, poop, star)
- They were good.
- Jukjae did a good job.
It's not just a star.
It's a silver star.
So your wish will be granted.
- Okay.
- Your songs will be on Running Man.
- This is great.
- It's huge.
All right then.
Team Haha who got
2 Poop Cards and 1 Star Card...
- will get a small penalty.
- What is it?
The small penalty is...
to write New Year's cards...
to the members of Running Man.
Is this small?
- It's bothersome.
- It's really hard.
- What's the big penalty?
- It's really bothersome.
- What's the big penalty then?
- It's really tiresome.
What's the big one?
Team BE'O with three Poop Cards...
will get water slaps
to fight the winter cold.
- I want to do that.
- This is better.
Get water slaps
to fight the winter cold.
(I want to do that!)
- I'll get a water slap.
- That's better.
- Let me go home.
- This is fun.
- This is not right.
- This is a lot better.
- Hey.
Jae Suk, this is better.
I like it better.
- This is a lot better.
- This is easy.
- I like it.
- This is better.
You three can give us
water slaps before you leave.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Let's start the penalties.
- Why is this small?
- Why is this a small penalty?
I'll just shower here.
All right then.
We will get water slaps then.
One at a time.
(Aiming at his protruding mouth)
It won't be bad.
It went to the side.
- All right.
- Good one.
- You're good at this.
- Hey.
- All right.
- Good one.
(He got splashed
trying to use his strength.)
He got splashed.
Why did you get splashed?
He keeps getting splashed.
That's so funny.
The big penalties are over.
Team Haha will stay here
and finish their penalties.
- Okay.
- This isn't a small penalty.
- Thank you.
- Good work today.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
We're leaving now.
- We will get going.
- Bye.
- This is a lot better.
Bye.
"Happy and..."
What else should I say?
If I don't like the card,
can I ask them to write again?
(Trying to come up with something)
I just keep saying thank you.
(Thankful... Grateful...)
(And thankful again...)
All right. I'm done.
- Okay.
- Done.
All right. Thank you.
Thank you.
(We thank Jukjae and BE'O
for joining us with shining smiles.)
(They are gathered together
to enjoy Christmas.)
(Santa Yoo and six Rudolphs)
(The unusual VIP treatment...)
(makes them suspicious.)
(They can't go home
before giving out all the gifts?)
I thought it was strange.
(She's not swearing.)
(Shoe...)
(The members show off
their poor stamina as always.)
(And the citizens are just as bad.)
(Will they be able to go home?)
(Even the citizens
turn away from them.)
(But they give out the gifts
they chose with their whole hearts.)
(The great gifts that will
give people precious memories)
(Congratulations)
(It's Christmas,
so you shouldn't be disappointed.)
(Santa Yoo and Six Rudolphs)