- Hello.
Hello. It's Jong Kook's
birthday today.
(Running-ri News, Kim Jong Kook's
birthday party on April 25)
(The day of the shoot
is Kim Jong Kook's birthday.)
(There's a sumptuous feast that will
make Jong Kook feel uncomfortable.)
Is this for Jong Kook's birthday?
- It's a birthday meal, but...
- The table is full of food.
- My goodness.
- Hello.
(The members start coming in.)
Happy birthday to you
Here's the birthday man!
- He's the birthday man.
- My gosh.
Surprise!
Happy birthday to you
- Seriously...
- He must be shy.
- He hates things like this.
- Surprise!
(He's reluctant to come in.)
- You are a lucky man.
- He really hates it.
- He hates it.
- He doesn't like it.
- Our group chat room was crazy.
- The birthday meal.
- My gosh.
- Stand in the middle.
This is really embarrassing.
Aren't we supposed to do this
at the end of the shoot?
He is blushing right now.
- This is driving me crazy.
- It's your birthday today.
- But still...
- Our group chat room...
(Here's the birthday gift for him!)
- Here's the birthday gift for him!
- Happy birthday to you
- She's the gift.
(She seems more excited
than usual today.)
(Song Ji Hyo, Running Man's star,
livens up the party.)
- Happy birthday, dear Jong Kook
- Boombastic!
What is this sound?
- "Happy Birthday song."
- Gosh, will you stop that?
This is your song.
- It's Jong Kook's song.
- Right.
My goodness.
(The birthday party begins.)
(They start dancing
to celebrate his birthday.)
Let's form a circle
with Jong Kook in the middle.
(Sighing)
Let's form a circle
with Jong Kook in the middle.
Come and stand in the middle.
- Let's go round.
Hold my hand.
(Happy birthday!)
(He claps his hands
with a blank look.)
This is so...
- I feel dizzy.
- I hate this.
- If I were Jong Kook...
- Me too.
- I would hate it a lot.
- I mean...
- It only embarrasses him.
- Let me...
Let me tell you something first.
I hate it so much.
- Isn't this nice?
- This is horrible.
- You should be happy.
- Sure. This is a good thing.
- Right. You should be happy.
- But...
Aren't I supposed to be happy?
- You must be happy.
- That's...
That's the most important thing.
You've been smiling the whole time.
Why do you say you're not happy?
- He's smiling broadly.
- That's because of the cameras.
- That's why he's smiling.
- Look at him.
That's because of the cameras.
- He's smiling from ear to ear.
- My gosh.
- All right.
- Please eat before it gets cold.
- Okay.
- Let's eat.
Look at that.
- There's yellow corvina too.
- This is amazing.
- It has names.
- There are our names on them.
- Jong Kook...
- There are name tags.
Why do the cushions have
our names on them?
They have names.
- That's yellow corvina.
- There's raw beef.
My goodness.
Jong Kook, there's seaweed soup.
Seaweed soup.
- Thank you for the food.
- My goodness.
- Happy birthday, Jong Kook.
- All right.
- This is great.
- Happy birthday, Jong Kook.
All right. Thank you.
Ji Hyo, the seaweed soup
is really good.
You are a good cook.
- How did you know that?
- Did Ji Hyo cook all this?
It's still warm.
- My gosh.
- Can we eat this in the morning?
We don't get to eat warm food
like this during a shoot.
- This is so good.
- It's delicious.
We usually eat cold food.
That's because
it's Jong Kook's birthday.
- It's Lord Kim's birthday.
- It's so tasty.
Even the elders wouldn't
get such nice dishes like this.
- My gosh.
- This is all thanks to Jong Kook.
- The food is really good.
- I love it.
It's still warm,
- so it tastes even better.
- Seriously,
the dishes are made
with love and affection.
The galbi tastes really good.
- It's delicious.
- By the way,
- I wish we didn't have this cake.
- Why not?
If it wasn't here,
it would've been a nice meal.
But we should have Jong Kook
blow out the candles.
- Right.
- We need a lighter.
- We have one here.
- The lighter.
This is what we do on a birthday.
Sure. Blow out the candles.
- Jong Kook, shall we take a photo?
- No.
- Let's take a photo together.
- That's enough.
- Let's do that.
- Hey, stop it.
That's all we will have left.
- Make a wish.
- Okay!
Gosh, Jong Kook. No.
- That's not right.
- Thank you.
- You can't do this.
- That's enough.
- I will count to three.
- We have to at least applaud.
- We will applaud.
Anyway, I made my wish.
- You should say it out loud.
- Out loud.
- I should do it quietly.
- That's not true.
You should leave
video messages to each member.
Tell us you love us.
- Gosh, he is...
- Even I feel uncomfortable.
Should I kill him?
Thank you, guys.
I hope all of you will stay healthy.
All right.
One, two, and three.
(Even his birthday wish is health.)
- This is so good.
- I think this is tteokgalbi.
It tastes amazing.
Are you two...
visiting your parents?
I like the food, Father.
(He has a coy daughter-in-law.)
- You do?
- Yes, Father.
- But our family doesn't like you.
- Let's eat quietly.
- You don't belong here.
- Father.
Please give me the recipe.
I want to cook this for my husband.
- The recipe for this?
- Yes.
I bought it at the restaurant
in the neighborhood.
If you want the recipe,
you should go ask the chef.
She says her husband.
Ji Hyo, you were
on "Problem Child in House."
- With Jong Kook.
- Right.
I went there.
Well... That's amazing.
She is very supportive.
- Hang on.
- What...
- I mean...
- Why? It's great.
- Well...
- What's wrong?
- What is that supposed to mean?
- It's great.
Isn't that nice?
What do you mean by "amazing?"
That's amazing.
You've got a letter.
- Who is that?
- What?
(You've got a letter.)
- Who is that?
- What?
- You've got a letter.
- Hey, Myung Jae.
- Myung Jae, is this what you do?
- Myung Jae.
(The assistant director is
occupied with trivial work.)
Just throw it.
You've got a letter.
- My gosh.
- What's that?
- He looks feeble.
- What was that about?
He just needed to be outside
the view of the camera,
but he actually went out.
- He's embarrassed.
- He feels shy.
He's shy.
"Running-ri Correspondence."
"The two towns of Running-ri
are long-standing enemies,"
"so they get into a fight
whenever they face each other."
"And now they are filing suits
in conflict with each other."
"Hopefully, a prompt and amicable
settlement will be reached."
Ji Suk Jin, Haha,
and Song Ji Hyo...
- belong to Town A.
- They are a team.
Yoo Jae Suk, Yang Se Chan,
and Jeon So Min belong to Town B.
- What about me?
- The charges.
(I'm not there?)
It's Ji Suk Jin
versus Yoo Jae Suk.
The plaintiff is Suk Jin,
and the defendant is me.
- I see.
- The charge is contempt.
"Ji Suk Jin from Town A
files a suit against Yoo Jae Suk..."
"for his endless mockery
and insulting remarks."
I'd like to file a suit.
Haha is suing Se Chan
for libel and slander.
Haha is the plaintiff.
"Haha from Town A files a suit
against Yang Se Chan from Town B..."
"for his constant pranks
and spreading of false rumors,"
"which have significantly
tarnished his reputation."
- What?
- Song Ji Hyo and Jeon So Min.
"Song Ji Hyo from Town A files
a suit against Jeon So Min..."
"for her constant flirting
with men from other towns,"
"which kept her
from concentrating on her work."
"Notice. On April 25, new residents
at each other's throats..."
"will move into Town A and Town B."
(New residents will be moving
into Town A and Town B on April 25.)
What is Jong Kook doing?
As the correspondence confirms,
there are long-standing enemies
in Running-ri.
Ji Suk Jin versus Yoo Jae Suk.
Haha versus Yang Se Chan.
And Song Ji Hyo versus Jeon So Min.
The older residents
are from Town A...
while the younger ones
are from Town B.
(The older residents
are from Town A.)
So there will be two teams.
And each town has
new residents moving in.
- Really?
- Please welcome them.
- What?
- Who are they?
(Who are the new residents?)
What? My goodness.
- He's Cho Jun Ho.
- I know them.
- They are twin brothers.
- Girls' Generation.
- Gosh, Hyoyeon.
- Hello.
(The new residents in the two towns)
Yuri from Town B,
- Yuri from Town B.
- and Hyoyeon from Town A.
Please come on up.
Happy birthday.
- That's right.
- Happy birthday.
- All right.
- Is it your birthday?
- You're a year older now.
- That's enough.
- Let's sit, guys.
- Happy birthday.
- This is like a national holiday.
- I know. It's like a holiday.
This feels like a holiday.
- It's a holiday.
- This is nice.
I can't believe
you two look just the same.
- My gosh. I can't tell who's who.
- They are twins.
- Is this for me?
- They don't look the same on TV.
- Jun Hyun, are you the younger one?
- Yes.
And Jun Ho is the older one.
- How many minutes apart?
- We're eight minutes apart.
- Eight minutes.
- Eight minutes?
I've seen you guys
on many TV shows lately.
- They fight a lot.
- Right.
Seriously, they fight like crazy.
I've never seen brothers like them.
They are really funny though.
(They fight a lot at home...)
(as well as outside.)
(Don't you try to talk to me
from so close ever again.)
(They fight physically
and mentally every day.)
- Now he has a syndrome.
- What syndrome?
- People like it when we fight.
- I see.
- So when someone recognizes us,
- On purpose...
he picks up a fight.
That's what he does.
- It can't happen.
- He can't help it.
I feel like I should
show them something.
That's why they like us.
I know how it feels.
Identical twins at least
try to have different hairstyles.
But you have the same hairstyle.
We usually have
different hairstyles.
But after we did some TV shows,
he wants to signify
the identity of twin brothers.
He wants more people
to recognize you.
They don't recognize us
when we look different.
When we look the same,
they recognize us right away.
- So do you wear the same clothes?
- Yes.
- Even the clothes?
- That's unbelievable.
Yuri and Hyoyeon,
aren't you two close friends?
(She's eating seaweed soup
with some rice.)
- Yuri?
- She's eating.
- Yuri.
- Yuri is eating.
Yuri is different from...
her early days in Girls' Generation.
Of course she is.
He's straightforward.
- Let me just eat first.
- You are eating.
Yuri is... Seriously,
I always thought Yuri would
make an amazing entertainer.
- She did many variety shows.
- Before we came here...
Actually, I came here
after getting a call from Yuri.
She asked me to join this show
saying I was her best friend.
- So I was very touched.
- I see.
- But you two aren't so close?
- No.
- I didn't feel that way.
- What are you talking about?
- Hey, why would you say that?
- What?
But a few days later,
my manager told me...
that we'd be here as enemies.
(We'd be here as enemies.)
You two are enemies.
- That's what you are.
- I had no idea.
Hyoyeon is just like Suk Jin.
She often makes
a slip of the tongue.
- Really?
- Hyoyeon?
She met Ha Suk Jin
at an award ceremony.
You know that, right?
She called him Ji Suk Jin.
She called him Ji Suk Jin?
To Ha Suk Jin?
- You did?
- "Ji Suk Jin is the best!"
That's hilarious.
And she called Jun Hyun Moo
Im Chae Moo.
They are totally different names.
- Well...
- You would know this one.
She called Brian McKnight
Brian McMorning.
McMorning?
- That's impressive.
- Brian McMorning?
- There are a lot.
- That's impressive.
- But Brian McMorning is a little...
- She did it on purpose.
- I think she did it on purpose.
- I bet it was intentional.
- No.
- You wanted to show something.
No, I didn't intend anything.
- Really?
- I wish she did.
- You wish.
- McMorning.
I don't think
Brian McMorning was intentional.
But there's more.
She called Whoopi Goldberg...
Whoopi Golden Retriever.
- That must be intentional.
- I think so.
She called Whoopi Goldberg
Whoopi Golden Retriever.
- That must be intentional.
- I think so.
- It's intentional.
- You have to admit it.
- It must've been intentional.
- I swear.
Hyoyeon.
Seriously, it wasn't.
- It smells fishy.
- That can't be right.
It was right after my debut,
so I couldn't intend anything.
- You couldn't?
- I was so nervous.
- Oh, right.
- What?
I heard something
about Jun Ho and Jun Hyun.
- They prepared some dances.
- Really?
They are so determined. Good.
This is crazy.
I've never seen
judo athletes dance before.
- Dance?
- It's not a break-fall, right?
- Of course not.
- My goodness.
- That's what they prepared.
- We have to watch it.
We have to smile at the cameras
while we dance. You know, right?
- They are celebrities.
- You look like...
In those outfits,
you two look like Yookgaksu.
- The duo.
- Right.
- Heungbo is unbelievable
- I think I saw them on TV.
Heungbo is unbelievable
I saw them on
"The Return of Superman."
They've grown a lot.
Seriously, this is...
- I'm so excited.
- This is the judo dance.
I've never seen judo dance before.
My goodness.
What?
(What? Is this IVE's song?)
- What?
- Ready.
(What?)
- I see.
- That's a judo technique.
They look so serious.
- This isn't funny.
- Right.
(They dance like elementary
school kids with serious looks.)
What are they doing?
(A break-fall for the finale)
(The dance ends with a short skit.)
Hang on. The break-fall
didn't seem right.
- What...
- Hang on.
Can we do the ending again?
We didn't do it properly.
That was...
- The ground was shaking.
- The break-fall wasn't right.
- He fell on his back.
- It was so hard.
- Wait.
- It didn't seem right.
- Yuri and Hyoyeon, you should...
- Yes.
- I want to see their dances.
- Show us just a little.
- We all want to see it.
- Please show us.
- Dear me.
- Do all of your dances for us.
- Show us a little.
- You see, I...
A short version will do.
- I feel so happy...
- Like you do when you rehearse.
You know that Yuri is successful
as an actress these days, right?
- Yes.
- She still goes on variety shows.
Right. Of course.
- I'm so grateful to her.
- I know.
I told Eun Hye to appear on
variety shows too.
(I told Eun Hye to appear on
variety shows too.)
- Today is his birthday.
- But it's true.
- It's his birthday.
- Give him a break.
Eun Hye and Jin should've kept
doing variety shows.
It's Jong Kook's birthday.
Jin, right? I told Eun Hye and Jin
about it so many times.
- It's his birthday.
- Jae Suk.
- It's a happy day.
- Gosh, I need to drink today.
- Come on. It's a happy day.
- Darn it.
Don't be like this
on a happy day like this.
- I told them numerous times.
- He likes that joke so much.
- I can't believe...
- He keeps bringing her up.
I thought he would stop
bringing her up, but he won't.
- I might've forgotten a few moves.
- It's okay.
- You look amazing.
- I might've forgotten the moves.
- Your body must remember.
- You can skip some moves.
(It's been a while since they last
did Girls’ Generation's dance.)
We don't know
what song will be played.
Let's go.
"Into the New World."
("Into the New World" is their
debut song released 15 years ago.)
- This is my favorite song.
- It's a great song.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
You look so pretty!
Their bodies are reacting
to the song.
They remember all the moves.
(Their bodies remember
the dance from their debut song.)
- They're dancing so effortlessly.
- Goodbye
Let's go!
(Kicking)
(The old fans are
exceptionally excited.)
Here we go!
(The 2nd song is "Tell Me Your Wish"
released in 2012.)
It sure is your birthday, Jong Kook.
The Girls’ Generation members are
performing for you.
(He's barely keeping a smile
on his face.)
Say your wish! Come on!
(His wish is that their performance
will end shortly.)
- Tell me your wish.
- All right.
(As Yuri and Hyoyeon do
a dance move for him...)
Tell us your wish.
(One Man wishes he could hide.)
- It's "Hoot."
- "Hoot."
I love this song!
They remember every move.
- They're amazing.
- Sing along, everyone.
They're incredible.
(He's getting overexcited
and singing, "I hoot.")
I don't remember the rest.
Why did you forget it?
I can't remember the rest.
- Thank you. That was awesome.
- Thank you.
- That was amazing.
- I'm impressed.
But they didn't dance to "Gee."
- I wanted to see "Oh!."
- That's enough.
- We didn't dance to that? Let's go.
- "Oh!"
(Ms. Kwon got excited
when it was already over.)
Dance to "Oh!" for us, please.
- Hyoyeon, show us, please.
- You were amazing.
- I really wanted to see it.
- It was awesome.
- I wanted to see this move.
- Can you play the song?
- It's cheerful.
- Yuri, you do it.
- Me?
- Yuri got excited.
- Right.
- Right now?
- I want to see the "Gee" dance.
- But...
(The encore performance begins.)
What was it? Let me think.
(Jong Kook becomes pale
as the song goes on.)
Keep going.
- That's great.
- Yes, keep going.
(Please stop it.)
- That's amazing. All right!
- She's cute.
Keep going!
- That was great.
- Thank you.
(He finally smiles
since her performance ended.)
- My goodness.
- That was amazing.
- The song would suit So Min.
- I'm so proud of you.
- So Min, do the dance just once.
- Do the highlight dance move.
- It's his birthday.
- Please show us.
- This is perfect for So Min.
- Exactly.
- For Jong Kook.
- I'm so excited.
- So Min looks excited.
- I really...
Come on. Show us.
Let's go!
Oh, gosh.
- It's so cheesy.
(Her cheesy dance makes
everyone shudder.)
- It's so cheesy.
- That's enough.
- My gosh.
- I need kimchi.
- She's so funny.
That's enough. Stop the music.
Stop.
(Gobbling down kimchi)
I love kimchi.
- I love them all so much.
- My gosh.
- That was so cheesy.
- I mean it.
- That was good.
- It was intense.
- She'd make a great idol singer.
- I agree.
- Exactly.
- That was so cheesy.
- Ji Hyo, show your dance just once.
- Me?
- Don't do that.
- Ji Hyo has her own dance style.
- That'd be the real deal.
- Don't do it.
- Go on.
Ji Hyo has her own dance style.
- She has her own style.
- I'm excited.
- She looks so pretty today.
- It'll be an old-fashioned dance.
An old-fashioned dance.
There she comes.
It sure is your birthday.
Hey!
She put her foot on the table.
Stop the music now!
- Gosh.
- Stop the music.
- Stop it.
- Ji Hyo.
- Come on. What are you doing?
- This isn't an R-rated show.
- Stop it.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hey! What are you doing?
- What's wrong?
- We're eating here.
- Hey.
That was inappropriate.
- But that's my style.
- What was that?
- It's my style.
- Why would you put your foot...
Why did you put a tablecloth
on the table?
How dare you call my skirt
a tablecloth?
(Laughing hard)
- Get her out of here. Now.
- What's going on?
(Suk Jin is running out of breath.)
- He's laughing so hard.
- Hey!
- She took me by surprise.
- He loved it.
- I was taken aback.
- Suk Jin loved it.
Be careful.
That was unexpected.
- Hey.
- What's with the tablecloth?
Check Suk Jin's blood pressure.
Check his blood pressure.
(He regained his vitality.)
- Suk Jin...
- That was completely unexpected.
I couldn't even imagine that.
That was unexpected.
- Seriously...
- It was unbelievable.
- She's unbelievable.
- It was unexpected.
- She's drinking dongchimi.
- She always catches us off guard.
She's drinking dongchimi
after dancing.
- I was thirsty.
- It was cheesy even for herself.
- I'm still thirsty.
- That's why she's drinking it.
That was funny.
Today's race where the enemies
with grudges against each other...
compete against each other...
is Enemy Cha-Cha-Cha,
Town A Versus Town B.
The two towns will compete with
each other.
- Jong Kook, who belongs to no town,
- Yes.
- is Chief Kook.
He can choose the town to join
in every mission...
through negotiation with both towns.
- I see.
- Got it.
- That's good. I like that.
- Okay.
The winning team members get
different amounts of money.
The losing team members get
a random amount of money...
out of different amounts
including negative numbers.
Chief Kook also gets
one of the amounts.
- It's an individual competition.
- I see.
The top two with the largest amounts
of money win and get a prize.
The bottom two get a penalty.
Before we officially begin the race,
each of you will check
your enemy's ability through a game.
- What is it?
- My enemy's ability.
You need to move fast and accurately
to shoot your enemy.
It's I Can Shoot You.
"I can shoot you."
"I might shoot you."
So Min is good at this.
Ready, go.
"I might shoot you."
We'll place disassembled water guns
on the table.
You have to assemble your water gun
and fill it with water,
- We've played this game before.
- shoot the opponent's headband,
and shout the letter written on it
to win.
- Okay.
- That's interesting.
You may disturb your opponent
while assembling the gun.
The winner gets 2 dollars,
and the loser gets 1 dollar.
Chief Kook,
you won't play this game.
Understood.
The first round is...
- Haha versus Se Chan.
- Great.
- Mapo One-Month Punch.
- Bang! Mapo One-Month Punch.
- Let's go.
- This is good.
- I'll teach him a serious lesson.
- Bang.
No mercy.
(They became enemies
as they got cheeky with each other.)
- I see.
- It'll be fun.
- We need agility.
- The amount of water matters too.
Just a second.
(Haha and Se Chan,
the 2 enemies look determined.)
Ready.
(Which of them will win
this match of enemies?)
What's going on?
(As soon as it began, Haha threw
Se Chan's water container.)
- Se Chan is clenching his teeth.
- Come on.
- Hurry up.
- Did you see that?
(They're trying everything
to disturb each other.)
Se Chan is clenching his teeth.
What is he doing? My gosh.
- This is so funny.
- Hey.
Haha is so fast.
- Se Chan is annoyed.
- Yes, he is.
- Good.
- It's starting to show.
(The game started getting dirty.)
It's starting to show.
This is ugly.
(They started tussling in the end.)
(Se Chan bites his head
with his front teeth.)
(Biting)
- It hurts so much.
- He dropped it.
(He's like a nutria
biting a chestnut.)
- Pick it up.
- That's ugly.
Come here.
- Se Chan, pick up the headband.
- It hurts!
That's good. One more time.
(A water slap)
- Gosh, it hurts so bad.
- Hurry up.
Check if it's yours or his.
(The headbands are soaked,
lying around on the ground.)
Whose is that?
(The person
who reads the letters first wins.)
- Let me answer. Bidet!
- Eel!
- Haha wins.
- What? Really?
(Haha from Town A who shouted
the answer first won.)
Haha wins.
- Are your front teeth okay?
- Wasn't Se Chan fast?
Am I bleeding right now?
Right here.
Hey, you guys...
You put too much pressure
on the twins.
- Exactly.
- How...
How much more intense should it be?
Exactly. They raised the bar.
- Hey, let's make it intense.
- Hey.
The second round is
Jun Ho versus Jun Hyun.
- All right.
- I'm excited to watch this.
I'm so excited.
- I'm excited about this match.
- Go, Jun Hyun.
They'll throw each other down.
- Of course.
- Good luck.
They'll do a foot sweep,
- and throw each other down.
- This will be intense.
No foot sweep, okay?
- It's a perfect day to fight.
- Okay.
- Let's play fair and square.
- Your fans are watching you.
- We need this to make characters.
- A lot of fans are expecting...
- to see you two fight.
- We should make characters.
(The greedy twins want to be funny
more than to play fair and square.)
Ready.
Set.
- Oh, good. He's fast.
- Hey, stop it.
(Jun Hyun cheated from the start
unlike what they agreed on.)
- Wait. Okay. Got it.
- Look.
He'll be able to read it shortly.
That's good. Keep going.
- Okay.
- I learned some skills from them.
- I'm impressed.
- I learned from them.
The guys from Town B play so dirty.
- My gosh.
- You...
You should pour water on me too,
so we can make it fair.
- Don't play dirty.
- You should pour water on me too...
(He pours water on his face.)
- My gosh. What is he doing?
- What are you doing?
- Duck.
- What was that?
- What are you guys doing?
- What's going on?
- Hey.
- Could the letters be reversed?
He's doing a shoulder throw.
(A shoulder throw)
- It's over now.
- My gosh.
- He won't fall.
- He's trying to throw him down.
(They started with a smile,
but now they're fighting seriously.)
- He won't fall.
- That's impressive.
- He didn't fall.
- This is fun.
- The letters are visible now.
- Hey, you should give it to me.
- You can read the letters.
- The letters are visible now.
- Just read them.
- Garlic.
- No, don't read it.
(Garlic!)
Correct.
(Jun Ho got the correct answer.)
(Jun Ho from Town A wins.)
- Gosh, Jun Hyun.
- Gosh, seriously.
Gosh.
Great job!
"You should pour water on me too,
so we can make it fair."
(They manipulated the game results
to make the viewers laugh.)
- That was funny.
- "So we can make it fair."
- Good job.
- Jun Hyun, that's a shame.
I'm sorry I couldn't do better.
- You did great.
- He won.
- Good job, Jun Hyun.
- Now...
- Shoes.
- Wig.
As for the results of
the preliminary mission...
Each of the winners will receive
two dollars.
- The losers will get one dollar.
- Yes.
As Town A has more winners,
you will get an extra 50 cents.
(The members of Town A receive
an extra 50 cents each.)
- It's time for the first mission.
- Yes.
Before we begin the first mission,
Chief Kook has to choose the team
he wants to be on.
The members of Town B seemed to be
no match for their opponents.
- Jong Kook, please.
- Jong Kook.
You never know.
Jong Kook could play a critical role
to win in every mission.
- Really?
- We'll need him on our team.
- We need to recruit him.
- Okay.
Chief Kook, you can choose
any town...
after negotiating with
the delegates.
The delegates will persuade him
with words.
You can collect money from everyone,
and offer him a reward.
For example, you can offer
1 dollar or 1.2 dollars.
I'll expect a reasonable amount.
The delegate must pay
half of the agreed amount.
- What?
- The delegate must pay...
- half of the agreed amount.
- Okay.
You can collect the remaining amount
from your team members.
- You understand the rule, right?
- As you all know,
- I'm not a greedy person.
- Yes.
I'm a reasonable person.
The delegates
for the first negotiation are...
- Yuri and Hyoyeon.
- Oh, I see.
Only the two of them have
the authority to make the decision.
- I see.
- You may start persuading him.
- How much money...
- Which of them won?
- Right now?
Just give him
all the money you have.
Hyoyeon, how much money do you have?
Did you win or lose?
I have 2 dollars and 50 cents.
- You have more than she does.
- Yes.
Since she has only one dollar,
- I'll offer more money.
- offer him 1 dollar and 20 cents.
We'll pay half of the amount
you decided.
Do you always talk loud enough
for the other team to hear you?
This is us whispering.
We do this on variety shows.
- This is our first time.
- I can't hear you guys.
- Jong Kook can't hear us at all.
- I can't hear you.
Yuri will have to pay half,
but she has only one dollar.
- I have only one dollar.
- True.
Yuri, give him all you have.
It doesn't matter.
(What should I do?)
Tell me the amount you can offer me.
I'll decide based on that.
- We'll give you all we have.
- Okay.
- But we don't have...
- You all have one dollar.
- We have seven dollars in total.
- We don't have much money.
- So we...
- You can't give me all you have.
Take just two dollars.
- Jae Suk, don't say anything.
- Take just two dollars.
(Annoyed)
- My gosh.
- Jae Suk.
- Why?
- Can't you be more desperate?
- Be desperate.
- What's wrong with you?
- Well, this is...
- You don't sound like you care.
I'm sorry.
- I mean...
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, I live in Anyang.
- Yes?
You live in Anyang?
- You don't live in Anyang.
- She lives in Anyang?
I moved to Anyang recently.
- Your parents will be upset.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
- He likes people living in Anyang.
- Our team member lives in Anyang.
- Do you really live in Anyang?
- Jong Kook.
- She's lying.
Your girlfriend is on our team.
(I'm on this team.)
Hey, don't make that face.
Just don't do anything.
Stay seated.
- Come on. Stop it.
- Oh
- She'll be disappointed.
- Stay seated.
She'll be upset
if you don't join us.
He must feel uncomfortable being
on the same team as his girlfriend.
- Right. It must be uncomfortable.
- He won't join that team.
- Then let me...
- We'll offer you...
You can write your final offers down
on the board.
- Write it down on the board.
- I see.
- I have more money than she does.
- Write down your offering amount.
Yuri, she has more money...
Never mind. It's up to you.
Can you tell me
how much money each of you has?
Jae Suk and So Min have 2 dollars.
I have 1 dollar.
And Jun Hyun has one dollar.
- I'll lose too much.
- I know.
- It's a lot.
- He has two dollars.
It might be better
if I didn't join your team.
- Why?
- No. Please join our team.
She only has one dollar.
She'll suffer too much damage.
- Even so...
- We can get more money.
- I'm betting on you.
- Okay.
- That's so cool.
- I'm offering all my money.
- Right. I know.
- That was a great comment.
I'll consider all the aspects...
- I'll see how sincere you are.
- I'm sure he won't turn me down.
- I'll give it serious thought.
- Okay. I wrote it down.
Jong Kook,
just pick the team already.
- What's your problem? Don't...
- My gosh.
(What's your problem?)
- Don't make him want to join them.
- It won't work because of him.
- Jong Kook.
- Don't worry about him.
- What?
- Gosh, seriously.
- All right.
- You're not helping.
- I just told him to hurry up.
I think he'll join us
if we just offer two dollars.
- Jae Suk is getting in their way.
- Gosh, you.
- I mean, that man...
- Please reveal the amount.
- One, two, three.
- Hey!
- Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
- We agreed to pitch in.
- My gosh.
- She asked which of us lost. Why...
- I asked...
As for the first mission...
The amount of reward matters too,
- but that man was...
- Right. I knew it.
I really want to
take the money from him.
- Good.
- Then you should join our team.
- I knew he would join us.
- I've decided to join them.
- Okay!
- Oh, yes!
(Shocked)
- I don't understand.
- That man...
If you want to
go out with Jong Kook,
you should do what I did.
(You should do what I did.)
Do you understand?
You should never cater to him.
- You should play hard to get.
- Never cater to him.
- That man...
- He really provoked me.
- Right.
- I should join his team.
- Impressive.
- You saw that, right?
- A bad man.
Jong Kook will receive one dollar
from each of Yuri and Jae Suk.
- Okay.
We'll move to another place
after you get changed.
- Let's go.
- Gosh.
(At the place for the 1st mission,
judo mats are on the floor.)
It's judo.
- Are we playing judo?
- Will we really play judo?
What do I do?
It'll be fun.
- This is great.
- They placed judo mats here.
We'll definitely need Jong Kook
for this game.
- Okay.
- That's not true.
- A judo athlete is on your team.
- Gosh. What a shame.
- Look at these judo uniforms.
- Right.
- Hey, Jun Ho.
- We're doomed.
- We're in trouble.
- Judo?
I wouldn't be that important.
Each team has a judo athlete.
Jun Ho, you should
fight with Jong Kook.
- I think I'll lose to him.
- Hey...
What was your brother's name?
- My brother? Jun Hyun.
- Jun...
- Jun Hyun? Okay...
- Yes.
- If we win two points...
- Exactly.
- Then we can win.
- The sun and the moon...
- You all look so weak.
- Why?
I can beat you,
if not everyone else.
You all look so weak.
- Are we playing judo?
- You're so weak.
- I'm stronger than you.
- No one dares to go to the center.
- I can beat Jae Suk easily.
- They're talking from afar.
- You look so weak.
- Hey, long-headed locust.
- Long-headed locust?
- Right.
- Hey, long-headed locust.
I weigh 10kg more than you.
You look so weak.
- There she goes. She stepped up.
- Look at her.
- You want to fight with me?
- She stepped up.
(Suk Jin finally moved forward
as the weakest player came out.)
(Making a fuss)
(Kicking and shouting)
You kicked my anus.
- How dare you?
- He kicked the anus?
It went right in.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Please gather in the middle.
- Let's gather around.
In the middle.
- Oh, I see.
- Let's stand in the middle.
Come here.
- Okay.
- Everyone.
In this mission,
you will have a chance
to teach your enemy a lesson.
(The 1st mission is
Judo with No Mercy, No Friendship.)
It's
Judo with No Mercy, No Friendship.
- Okay.
- Judo.
- Judo?
- "No friendship?"
- Then would you say, "Okay?"
- Right?
- He's ridiculous.
I learned judo before. I learned
forward rolling and back fall.
- Se Chan knows how to do it.
- Oh, my.
You will have a match
against your enemies.
It'll be a 1-on-1 match
between the enemies.
- Within two minutes,
- Yes.
you have to get more points
than your opponent does.
- How?
- Here's how to get points.
You get one point for each sock
you take off of your opponent.
- What's that?
- Socks?
You get two points if you tear off
your opponent's name tag.
(1 point for a sock, 2 points for
a name tag, 4 points for the top)
You get four points
if you take off the judo top.
- The top?
- My gosh.
- Take off the top?
- I think...
- I mean, the judo uniform.
- the twins are at an advantage.
Give us more points
if we take off more clothes.
- Let us give it a try.
- I can...
- I don't mind showing my underwear.
- I can take off his underwear.
- Let us do that.
- How many points can we get for it?
Just the shirt will do.
Will you give me a point
if I take my own clothes off?
- I'd take my pants off by myself.
- Come on.
- That'd be so weird.
- I will...
Deduct a point if everyone is
disappointed when we take it off.
- Deduct a point?
- I'll just...
I'm not worried
if you'll be disappointed.
- You lose a point.
- I'm confident.
I guess
I'll get the highest score today.
I wouldn't be embarrassed.
- I don't want to imagine that.
- That'd be so funny.
- Don't imagine that.
- It's horrible.
- Chief Kook, you can choose...
- Yes.
- anyone you want to fight with.
- Okay.
- Great.
- That's good.
- Pick Jun Ho.
- Okay.
- Choose the weakest one.
- You can choose anyone.
- I might fight with Trainer Kook.
- Yes.
- Of course.
- Trainer Kook.
- Please put on the uniform.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook will knock you up.
- This is great.
- It's going to be intense.
- Gosh, seriously.
This brings me back the memories of
the shoulder throw.
You're talking about...
getting robbed, right?
Well, I admit that it happened.
I haven't worn these in a while.
Stop lying.
You have never worn them before.
(They're talking big
as they're wearing judo uniforms.)
It's been a while
since I last practiced.
Honestly, I missed this scent.
The scent of a judo uniform.
I remember that my uniform was
soaked in sweat on my way home.
- I miss those days.
- I really miss those days.
You?
You're such a loser.
- Hey. Yuri.
- You're such a loser.
Who would like to go first?
Maybe Chief Kook?
- That wouldn't be fair.
- Let me see...
- the weaklings go first.
- It wouldn't be fair.
Shouldn't we see
the representatives first?
I'll see how the others are first.
Those who are familiar with
the smell of sweat.
- How about it?
- Sure.
It's been a while,
so take a trip down memory lane.
Just like I used to,
let me breathe in
the scent of the dojo.
(The memory
of being robbed of money)
Back when...
the National Sports Festival
took place...
- I mean...
- He's no competition.
I threw a lot of guys like him.
- Get over here.
Look at him move as I pull.
(He says that
while being shaken as well.)
Shall we begin?
- Should we begin right away?
- Right now?
Look at you pulling him
at your will.
Go for it!
Nice!
(The keyboard warriors
carry distorted memories.)
Check him out from behind.
- Well...
- You seem like an expert.
Doesn't he look like...
the dojo's first chairman?
- The dojo's...
- The master of Brazilian jiu-jitsu.
- Okay!
- That's right.
- He founded this dojo.
- The famous martial artist.
Nice. That's what he's famous for.
- You will only get two minutes.
- Two minutes?
Two minutes
is longer than you think.
- Two minutes...
- I won't need that much.
I'll only need 30 seconds.
(He claims that he can
drop Jae Suk in 30 seconds.)
- Please don't cry afterwards.
- I bet he will.
- No crying.
- No peeing.
And no telling your mom.
Get ready.
(Round 1: Suk Jin vs Jae Suk)
- Close the distance.
- Go for it.
- Grab him. There isn't much time.
- Use the techniques.
No, just grab him.
(After sensing each other out,
they grab the collars.)
(Take that!)
(Seok Sam drops
to an outer reaping throw.)
Nicely done.
- Good.
- Suk Jin!
Go, Jae Suk.
(Forget 30 seconds,
he can't hold out for 5.)
(Giggling)
- My gosh.
- That's it.
- The sock.
- Press down.
All right.
(Jae Suk goes for the sock.)
Look at him playing defense.
(Suk Jin's close
to losing a point.)
He almost took off the sock.
(They are both after
each other's socks.)
- No!
- What are you doing?
(Seok Sam wins the first point.)
(Seok Sam managed
to take off the sock first.)
(Town A Ji Suk Jin 1,
Town B Yoo Jae Suk 0)
- What are you playing at?
- It won't come off.
(Suk Jin manages to take both off.)
Okay with the socks.
Now, go for his name tag.
- Look at how pale his feet are.
- What now?
- Go for his jacket.
- Right, I'll take his jacket off.
- Yes, his jacket.
- He's going for it.
Take his jacket off.
- Hold your ground.
- Rip his name tag off.
Suk Jin, subdue him.
(Jae Suk manages
to take one sock off too.)
Why do they both have
such pale feet?
They are as pale as they can get.
- They're very clean too.
- No, more like pale.
- Pale?
- You're tied right now.
(The facial massage begins.)
What on earth?
(Jae Suk presents Seok Sam
with a familiar smell.)
Once again, he's being victimized.
- He was off to a good start though.
- Where is his name tag?
(Chuckling)
My gosh.
Isn't the smell
a blast from the past?
Doesn't this bring back memories?
How can this be
when you're 10kg heavier?
(Groaning)
He's drawing up
every last bit of energy.
(However, he soon flames out.)
- You...
- It's over.
Oh, no. No!
- He did it.
- It's over.
- He got the name tag.
- It's off.
Okay, he has it.
- Nice!
- Yes!
(Town A Ji Suk Jin 2,
Town B Yoo Jae Suk 4)
- He won.
- What a blast from the past.
Just like old times.
- I...
- All right.
- Our feeble brother.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- Drag him out.
- Suk Jin!
It's you against me next,
so get ready.
- Get ready.
- What?
- Drink some water.
- Step out.
- Should we call an ambulance?
- Jae Suk wins with four points.
Get out there and have some water.
(Seok Sam is pulled
out of the danger zone.)
- Goodness.
- It just got hot in here.
This requires a lot of stamina.
Jae Suk looks sexy right now.
That was exhausting.
Give me another chance!
(The nostalgic battle
ended with Jae Suk winning.)
Who would like to go next?
The brothers are at war.
The twins are up.
Cho Jun Ho versus Cho Jun Hyun,
I can't wait.
Warm up to prevent any injuries.
(The battle of the masters)
Don't forget
to break your fall, okay?
Holding out
will only lead to injuries.
- He wants us to rig the game.
- Gosh, no.
- It's a warning, that's all.
- This we must watch.
They specialize in judo,
- so this is a real game.
- I need to watch this.
Let me show you
how to manage a game.
(Let us tell you about Cho Jun Ho.)
(At the World Championships...)
(and at the London Olympics,
he won the bronze medal.)
(Not only did he
take the world by storm,)
(but in a match
against his own brother...)
(He claimed victory over his brother
with a shoulder throw.)
(Age matters, doesn't it?)
(The 8-minute younger brother
is tough competition though.)
(His tenacity
and competitiveness...)
(led to many memorable games.)
- I can't wait.
- Who was better...
as judo athletes back in the day?
I was better back then,
but that changed after we retired.
He hasn't been able
to take a game off me.
- Really?
- Is that so?
For real?
Are you ready?
You don't look cool at all.
- I'm amazed.
- Get ready.
- This is for real.
- Go, Jun Hyun!
- This one is for real.
- A battle between brothers.
This sounds like fun.
Go, Jun Hyun!
He didn't even say "go."
The older brother bowed first.
- Jun Hyun didn't bow.
- This is for real.
(The brothers collide.)
- Okay.
- This is for real.
- This is a game of judo.
- I can't believe it.
- My gosh.
- A game of judo.
- Tensions run high.
- My gosh.
Go for the name tag!
(The twins aren't holding back.)
- Tensions are running high.
- This is real for them.
(Jun Ho lands a scooping throw.)
Are we watching ssireum?
(Jun Ho throws his brother
to the ground.)
- Jun Hyun!
(Jun Ho throws his brother
to the ground.)
Guys!
- Jun Hyun!
- Oh, no.
- No.
I can't believe this.
His name tag.
Oh, no.
- His name tag.
- Oh, no.
- Look.
- Seriously?
(The older brother
goes after the name tag.)
You can't let him grab behind you.
(The name tag came off!)
- Seriously?
- You can't let him grab behind you.
(The brother from the Town A
scores 3 points in a flash.)
- Seriously?
- No way!
Can you believe it?
- The name tag came off.
- Take off his jacket, then.
(Town A Cho Jun Ho 3,
Town B Cho Jun Hyun 0)
- Shouldn't you stand?
- The name tag came off.
Rip off his clothes!
- Take off his pants.
- He took your name tag off.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, no?
- If I take off his pants,
please award me four points.
Not the pants, you jerk.
You're wearing something underneath.
It's easier to take off his pants.
No, not the pants.
Jun Hyun's like, "No, don't."
- "No, don't."
- He's pleading.
- Take off his jacket.
- The twins are hilarious.
Aren't they funny?
Seriously?
This is exhausting, you know.
(He attempts a second
scooping throw.)
No way.
This sure is entertaining.
(The older brother
scores another full point.)
A full point!
- What on earth?
- Look!
(Jun Hyun is now being
dragged around.)
Are you kidding me?
(Jun Hyun is now being
dragged around.)
Stop picking on your little brother!
Go after his name tag.
- Let go of me.
- Age does matter, right?
- This isn't easy.
- Hold on a second.
- He's dragging you around.
- You're owning him.
Jun Hyun!
- He's weaker than I thought.
- It's an arm bar.
- Arm bar!
(Jun Ho tries to hold him down
with an arm bar.)
- Yes!
- Seriously?
(Jun Hyun won't lose points,
just his pride.)
You have 30 seconds left.
Jun Hyun, are you kidding me?
All that's left is his jacket.
(All that's left is his jacket.)
(It's becoming more
like a dog fight.)
- They're not kidding around.
- Look at them.
- He got the pants.
- The pants.
- The pants are coming off.
- I'm amazed.
The pants aren't worth any points!
- Reward me for the pants!
- The socks.
Get the socks.
- The pants are off.
- You have 15 seconds left.
Only 15 seconds.
- Go after the socks.
- Seriously, Jun Hyun?
Jun Hyun, are you kidding us?
- I mean...
- Look.
- I took off his pants.
- Give him points for that.
- Please!
- Give him some points.
- That wasn't the rule.
- Give him points for that.
- Did you get my name tag?
- Yes.
- That was incredible.
- Jun Hyun!
I'm sorry.
I thought that we were tied.
You should've gotten his name tag.
That was incredible.
Give him a big hug, will you?
- A big hug?
- That'd be cool.
(The two brothers battled it out
with love and respect.)
- A big hug.
- Yes, reconcile.
(Joke's on you!)
(He messes with
his younger brother.)
Gosh, Jun Hyun.
- Seriously?
- I knew it!
Shouldn't he receive
a penalty for that?
- Nice!
- Of course he fell for it.
We all thought
we'd see two brothers hug.
- Exactly.
- That's what everyone thought.
Jun Ho, you...
What? Come at him
if you have a problem.
- What?
- Take him on if you can.
- Take him on.
- Just because you lost...
Would you like to breathe in
the smell of sweat again?
Bring it on.
I'll take on the little brother.
(Whimpering)
- No way.
- Who's going next?
This time,
- So Min's playing.
- It's time for a woman to play.
Cho Jun Ho's playing one more time.
The rival.
Ji Hyo. You should go.
Right. Ji Hyo. You should go.
Ji Hyo is really strong.
Ji Hyo looks like a pro.
- Right?
- Yes.
You're so good-looking.
So Min.
Don't try to do anything.
She...
- What is she doing?
- She's immersed.
- She's too into it.
- Why is she doing that?
Stop...
- I'm sorry.
- giving her excuses.
- What's she doing?
- Just do it.
Just do it.
(Martial Arts Frog gained
confidence from her master.)
That's hilarious.
- Are you going to be okay?
- She looks perfect.
Go, Neunggok!
- Good luck.
- Go, Mapo!
- Mapo.
- Go, Mapo.
Mapo-gu.
(The game begins.)
Mapo.
- Boombastic!
(Jumping)
Catch her.
(Hitting)
(Frog got smacked
for fooling around.)
Hit her, So Min.
Fool around even more.
That's good.
(Ji Hyo grabs her by the collar
to begin the real game.)
Take it slow.
- She's down already.
- So Min. Go for her sock.
It's not about strength.
- Rip the name tag off.
- It's about the skills.
(Martial Arts Frog got her name tag
ripped as soon as the game started.)
- What was that?
- She's a monster.
It's about the skills. Gosh!
Oh, I shouldn't be impressed.
(The race goes exactly
as everyone expected.)
So Min will get dragged around.
That's right.
- She's super strong.
- You need to take her down first.
(Another point)
- So Min has no chance.
- Wait.
Judo was so easy for her.
- That's right.
- What is she doing?
- Judo was so easy.
- Hey.
We should have Se Chan...
- play against a woman.
- That's great.
- Take her top off.
- She's really good.
- She's really strong.
- That's incredible.
What on earth is she doing?
Ji Hyo is as strong as a man.
(Ragged)
- Take it off.
- She's given up.
- "Take it off."
- Take it off.
What a tough man.
Throw her.
So Min. You're doing great.
- Trip her.
- Wait.
(Wait.)
Wait. I'll take it off.
(I'll take it off.)
(So Min says she'll take off.)
- Ji Hyo. I will take it off.
- Don't!
Hey.
- Ji Hyo. I will take it off.
- Don't!
(She takes it off in a cheesy way.)
- Hey! You can't just take it off.
- So Min.
Stop it!
- Hey.
- Stop it.
- Cover her.
Stop it already.
You gave away all the points
you could.
I'm sorry.
Why would you take it off
on your own?
Good job.
She was good.
"I'll take it off."
- I couldn't throw her.
- No?
- She was too fast.
- Well done.
Next is Yuri versus Hyoyeon.
- Yuri.
- Good luck.
- I'll do my best.
- You can do it.
- Nice.
(Hyoyeon from Town A
versus Yuri from Town B)
I'm scared.
I'm not sure about this.
(Why is Yuri afraid?)
(Hyoyeon is known for her strength
among Girls' Generation members.)
(Even though they had
many matches before,)
(she could never win
against Hyoyeon.)
Hyoyeon. Show us what you got.
Show us.
Get ready.
(Determined)
- You're nothing against Hyoyeon.
- Go.
- I have a feeling Yuri will win.
- What are you doing?
- Get close to her.
- Yuri is strong too.
- Hurry up.
- They're the same size.
Hyoyeon. Get closer to her.
Get closer?
- How do you do that?
- She lost a lot of weight.
- Hyoyeon...
- What are you doing?
(Hyoyeon uses her technique first.)
- Good.
- Hey.
Go for the socks.
- Good.
- Hey.
- Go for the socks.
- She's down.
- Good job.
- Go for the socks.
- Good.
- Good job.
You're doing great.
- This is intense.
She is not a toy.
- Yuri. The name tag.
- No, Hyoyeon!
That's right. Good job.
(Yuri tries to make Hyoyeon faint
with mysterious shouting.)
- Good job.
- That was good.
Yuri is strong.
Yuri. Watch out.
Her hand is approaching.
(Hyoyeon was able to put her hand
on Yuri's back!)
No!
The sock.
The sock. Take her sock off.
(Hyoyeon is aiming for
Yuri's socks!)
Good.
Her left sock. That's right.
- Yuri. Good job.
- You still got more points.
(She tries to escape by
folding her body in half.)
You're flexible.
You got out.
Yuri is stuck.
You're doing great, Hyoyeon.
(Ripping)
Okay!
You're doing great, Hyoyeon.
(Yuri ripped her name tag off!)
The sock.
(Yuri gained 2 points first.)
- Yuri. Enjoy it.
- The sock.
Hey. Take that off.
If you take her two socks off,
we win.
You're doing good, Yuri. Okay.
- Good job.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- You did it.
- Don't leave yet.
- Okay!
Okay.
- Yuri is stronger than I thought.
- You did it.
Six points.
- Okay.
- Wasn't that tough?
I'm worn out.
Hyoyeon.
- Good job, Yuri.
- We still have Se Chan.
- Look at her eyes.
- I've been working out.
Well done.
- Good job, Yuri.
- Aren't you tired?
You did great.
- You're so strong.
- Yuri.
(He looks as if
he has some stories.)
Yuri.
- Look at their faces.
- Okay.
(Two children think they're big
when they're in uniform.)
- Okay.
I could never beat her.
(Two children think they're big
when they're in uniform.)
That bald guy.
He has some stories.
- They always have a good start.
- Se Chan.
Exhaust him.
Se Chan. End it.
- Haha. You're strong.
- Look at his eyes.
You know Haha is weak.
- Look at his eyes. They're scary.
- Look at his face.
- Haha. You look like a pro.
- Haha. You're strong!
- End it.
- You're strong.
What's wrong with them?
Since it's hard to take the top off,
we'll give three points for pants.
Get ready.
- I got it.
- Go, Se Chan.
Good.
They're serious.
I got you.
If you go under,
it's disadvantageous.
That's right.
- Go for the socks. Okay.
- Good.
Nice.
If you go under,
it's disadvantageous.
- Come on.
- Watch out for your right foot.
- Take it off.
- My goodness.
- Show your strength.
It's time for a technique.
It's the arm bar.
- The arm bar.
- Where is he going?
(Haha turned Se Chan!)
- Good.
- The arm bar.
He's biting the clothes.
(Biting)
Isn't that a zombie?
What's he doing?
- What are you biting?
- He's a zombie.
- That's a zombie.
- What's he doing?
What's wrong with him?
What are you biting?
(He's about to rip something else
other than the name tag.)
That's weird.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm sorry.
(The two are determined
to ruin each other.)
Rip his name tag off.
Se Chan.
(Slapping)
This is no time for that.
Think about the score.
You must win the points.
Se Chan.
Se Chan. Take his pants off.
(Banging with his head)
Se Chan.
Se Chan!
Se Chan. This is no time for that.
Se Chan. You shouldn't be
on your back.
Yes. Get up.
(The soft tofu fights back!)
- Good.
- No!
Okay.
The sock.
- Take his pants off.
- The sock.
- Go for the sock, Haha.
You have 30 seconds left.
Se Chan. In the back.
Just get three more points.
Haha's using his shaved head
as his weapon.
That feels weird.
Stop it.
(Unexpected sandpapering)
What's wrong with him?
Stop it.
(A strange feeling to
his soft tofu-like skin)
- Endure it.
- It's almost over.
(The game ends.)
That was so much fun.
"That was so much fun."
Come here.
That was fun.
(Haha is satisfied after filling
his stomach with tofu.)
I couldn't avoid it.
This is bad.
Okay.
They're three points ahead.
I'm not sure if I can coach him.
(For the last game, Chief Kook
chooses the oldest member.)
- Suk Jin is fast.
- Just don't lose any points.
Suk Jin.
Pull the top out of the belt.
Don't hold onto it. Take it out.
- The chest...
- Good job.
You're good at keeping balance.
- You have good core strength.
- You're very swift.
You're doing great.
I'm not so easy, you punk.
(But he quickly falls to the floor.)
Hey.
(He spoke his true feelings
out of urgency.)
- He cursed.
- He just cursed.
He just cursed at Jong Kook.
- Why would you curse?
- We're still two points ahead.
(Town A is still ahead by 2 points!)
You have 35 seconds left.
- How many seconds?
- Thirty five seconds.
Grab it here.
Suk Jin.
You just need to endure it.
Endure it!
No. Endure it.
- Three, two, one.
- Endure it!
We won!
- We won!
- He endured it.
Did he win?
- He won.
- Did he win?
Really?
Town A wins.
What?
Did he win?
I should've ripped his name tag off.
That was close.
You endured it well.
- You're good at enduring.
- You did a good job enduring.
(Falling)
You did a good job enduring.
(The old man doesn't have
the strength to pull his pants up.)
- We lost, but we fought well.
Suk Jin. Good job.
Suk Jin.
You lost, but you still fought.
I pretty much won, right?
- You lost, but you still fought.
- You did a good job.
Both teams will draw money.
The winning team will pick
from positive amounts.
The amounts vary from 3, 2,
1.50, 1, 0.50 and 0 dollars.
Really?
The losing team will pick from...
1.50, 1, 0.50, 0, minus 0.50,
and minus 1.50 dollars.
We need to pick well.
- Okay.
- We need to pick well.
Okay.
The members of the winning team...
will pick and open an envelope.
- Okay. Let's do it.
- We do it separately.
- You do it separately.
- This is incredible.
Do we choose from this side? Okay.
We can look, right?
- We choose from this side.
- Yes.
Choose among the green envelopes.
(Hyoyeon, Haha, Jun Ho: 2.50 dollars
Suk Jin, Ji Hyo: 1.50 dollars)
- Pick one, Hyoyeon.
- Me?
- I will pick...
- Number three.
- number 2.
- Number 1.
The highest amount is 3 dollars
and the lowest amount is 0 dollars.
Is there zero dollars?
The envelopes
should have been facing down.
- All right.
- Let's open the envelope.
Haha, go ahead.
- Two dollars.
- My goodness.
- Okay.
- You are lucky.
- That's a lot.
- Ji Hyo, how much did you get?
- I got 0.50 dollars.
- Ji Hyo got 0.50 dollars.
We avoided 0.50 dollars.
But 0.50 dollars
isn't the worst you can do.
- I got 1.50 dollars.
- Jun Ho.
- You got 1.50 dollars.
I have a bad feeling about this.
- Then...
- Zero dollars.
- One dollar.
(The remaining options are
3, 1, and 0 dollars.)
- Drum roll.
- Three dollars.
- Zero dollars.
(Hyoyeon: 2.50 and 0 dollars)
All right.
Why did I have to pick this one?
(The remaining options are
3 and 1 dollars.)
I got...
three dollars.
Suk Jin got three dollars.
Okay, Suk Jin.
- Yes.
- Can I open this one?
- You fought well.
- The amounts have been added.
Members of the losing team
will pick now.
It's our turn.
- That one is mine.
- We need to pick well.
I like number three.
- Okay.
- As for me...
The highest is 1.50 dollars and
the lowest is minus 1.50 dollars.
- Minus?
- If your total amount is minus,
it will be your debt.
- I should have done better.
- Open the envelope.
Did you say
the lowest is minus 1.50 dollars?
(Jae Suk: 1 dollar)
- Gosh.
- He got 1.50 dollars.
- The highest amount.
- He is lucky.
- Which number did he pick?
- What is up with him?
- What was the envelope number?
Number four.
(Jae Suk is lucky these days.)
- Minus 0.50 dollars.
- Okay. Minus 0.50 dollars.
Minus 0.50 dollars.
I thought it was 5 dollars.
- I bet I picked a bad one.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
Maybe not.
- Maybe not. Let's see.
- Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook: 2 dollars)
He got 0.50 dollars.
I got 0.50 dollars.
(Jong Kook:
2 dollars and 0.50 dollars)
- I bet Yuri picked a bad one.
- Thank goodness.
She got one dollar.
(Yuri: 0 dollars and 1 dollar)
- She picked a good one.
- One of you will get...
minus 1.50 dollars.
- Okay.
- If it's minus...
- Thank goodness.
- So Min took what Se Chan picked.
- Shall we switch envelopes?
- Yes.
- Let's switch envelopes.
- All right.
- Go ahead.
- It went to the original owner.
Okay. So Min.
- Shall we open them together?
- One, two, three.
Okay.
- Three.
- Okay.
(So Min got minus 1.50 dollars.)
I'm so lucky!
- Boombastic.
- Why did you switch them?
You shouldn't have switched them.
All right.
- I shouldn't have switched them.
- Seriously.
The amounts have been added.
Before we set off
for the second mission,
Jun Ho and Jun Hyun will negotiate
the terms with Jong Kook...
as town delegates.
- The two of them.
- Let's go.
Who has the most amount of money?
- Suk Jin.
- How much do you have?
- I have 4.50 dollars.
- He has a lot.
- He has everything.
If he pays half of the amount,
I will go to your town.
- That's a good idea.
- Okay.
Hold on.
(Seok Sam suddenly lost
1.50 dollars.)
I will go to this town.
- Chief Kook joined Town A.
- All right.
We will move to the location
of the next mission.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
This is fun.
Okay.
Here comes the birthday boy.
It's time for the second match
between Town A and Town B.
- Yes.
- We need to win.
- They don't stand a chance.
Chief Kook is a resident of Town A.
- We welcome you.
- Okay.
Okay.
- I will do well.
- Let's go.
- We are weak.
- We need to do better.
We need to do better.
I am not joking when I say this.
- So Min and Jun Hyun,
- Jun Hyun.
- you guys need to do better.
- Okay.
You were really bad at judo.
(You were really bad at judo.)
- What was that?
- He lost big time.
I think he went easy
on his older brother.
- Don't do that.
- Don't go easy on him.
You should have done
your absolute best.
Before we reveal
the current mission,
Haha will turn the board.
- Okay.
- What could it be?
- It's a quiz.
No. I bet it's a poll.
- A poll.
- Maybe it's...
something like yutnori.
We are good at guessing
the results of a poll.
- It's yutnori.
- My goodness.
It's a mix of quiz and yutnori.
Good. We can do well.
- Good.
- Quiz and yutnori.
(It's obviously a quiz.)
This is bad.
We are set.
That team has two dumb ones.
- Thank goodness.
- They have Hyoyeon and Ji Hyo.
- Hey.
- They have three dumb ones.
- Empty Head.
- Hyoyeon is smart, okay?
- Dumb ones.
- Let's do this.
I get teary-eyed...
- whenever we have a quiz.
- Why?
- I become so nervous.
I should give you guys
a private lesson.
Please make a class.
I should do that.
- Seriously.
- It's hard to be knowledgeable...
because I am focused on work.
Starring in variety shows
for years...
makes you smart.
- You end up studying during work.
- It's true.
To be honest, I learned everything
through variety shows.
What? Did you say
you learned things?
Of course.
Why do you keep acting out?
- I am not acting out.
- You know it's true.
It's true.
Before he starred in variety shows,
he couldn't write his own name.
(Before he starred in variety shows,
he couldn't write his own name.)
- Variety shows made him smarter.
- That's how dumb he was.
- I couldn't write my own name?
- That's right.
He is the original Empty Head.
You respect me.
I do, but you need to show me
what you can do...
- like Jae Suk and Suk Jin.
- Seriously. Among Empty Heads...
- Empty Heads.
- He is the best among them.
He is the best indeed.
Jun Ho and Jun Hyun,
how good are you with quizzes?
- How good are you guys?
- Are you guys knowledgeable?
Me? I think I will be fine
as long as it isn't English.
- Are you okay with other subjects?
- Of course.
Are you okay with other subjects?
- Did you study other subjects?
- Yes.
You know world history.
- World history?
- Between the two of you,
- who got better grades?
- That's right.
- Who got better grades?
- I always did better.
- What?
- I ranked 22nd in my class.
Really?
- People think I am a strong man,
- That's right.
but I am actually a smart man.
This is bad.
I think Jun Hyun talks big.
- I think he talks big.
- He always talks big.
- I mean...
- I think he talks big.
Yuri, how is Hyoyeon?
- Hyoyeon?
- Is she knowledgeable?
I stopped studying a long time ago.
You are Empty Head like us.
- That's good.
- Hyoyeon.
- Empty Head.
- Brian McMorning.
- Okay.
- I remember that.
- We have Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk.
- We have Suk Jin.
I can take on Jae Suk.
- I can take on Jae Suk.
- Listen.
- He went to Inha University.
- Hey.
- He didn't go to Inha University.
- I went to Ajou University.
- Really?
He was
a business administration major.
- A business administration major.
- Bachelor's degree.
- Did you take an exam?
Of course I took an exam.
I didn't have a lottery, okay?
That's not how
you enter a university.
- I still can't believe...
- Okay?
that you majored in
business administration...
- at Ajou University.
- I didn't play rock-paper-scissors.
- Was it easier to get in back then?
- It's unbelievable.
Getting into Ajou University
wasn't as hard as it is now.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Hyun Woo takes after his dad.
- It's a prestigious school now.
Hyun Woo takes after his mom.
He takes after his mom too.
Suk Jin is wise.
Isn't that right, Suk Jin?
The only thing Hyun Woo got
from his dad is his nose.
- Hey.
- The DNA is strong.
- Why did you bring up his nose?
- Seriously.
- Big Nose.
- He has a point.
- It might hurt his feelings.
- It might hurt...
- Why would it hurt his feelings?
I don't know
if he likes his nose or not.
- I haven't asked.
- Why would it hurt his feelings?
He might be self-conscious
about his nose.
Does Ji Ho have a protruding mouth?
Hold on. Why did you bring up Ji Ho?
- You started it.
- He can get braces, okay?
Shall we have a war about
our children? Shall we do that?
My son, Dream, hasn't grown taller
since first grade.
He hasn't grown taller.
Hasn't Dream grown taller?
- No.
- DNA does matter.
It would be strange
if his son is tall.
- That's right.
- Both his parents are short.
My dad is 180cm tall, okay?
I forgot about that.
Your older brother is a doctor,
but you are a thug!
(Your older brother is a doctor,
but you are a thug!)
(DNA isn't the only indicator.)
In this mission,
Town A and Town B residents
will compare their knowledge.
- Gosh.
- It's the Quiz Snake Ladders.
- Snake Ladders.
- It will be hard.
The die has sides that represent
numbers from 0 to 5.
The rules are simple.
Roll the die
and answer the question...
that corresponds with the subject.
If you get it right, you stay.
If you get it wrong,
you go back to the starting line.
(If you get it wrong,
you go back to the starting line.)
You need to get it right
in order to advance.
- You can catch the opponent's pawn.
- Okay.
The finish line consists
of five squares, right?
Yes.
Land on any squares
and answer the question to finish.
(The number of stars
determines the level of difficulty.)
If you land on the five-star square,
- you will get the hardest question.
- The level of difficulty.
- That's good.
- That would be better.
If you fail to answer,
do you go back to the beginning?
- Yes.
- My goodness.
If you succeed at any square
of the finish line, you are done.
It's okay. We can do it.
How difficult are the questions?
- They are easy. However,
- Are they easy?
other members can't help the player.
You only get five seconds.
- Make them difficult.
- It's better that way.
- Say that they are difficult.
- Make them very difficult.
It's better that way.
- It's less embarrassing.
- You know that, right?
That's right.
- It's fair that way.
- That's right.
Jun Hyun will be
the first player on our team.
- As for us, it will be Jun Ho.
- Okay.
- The rivalry should continue.
- That's right.
I am nervous.
(I am nervous.)
They usually give
difficult questions...
- on the show.
- I know.
- They aren't difficult.
- You can't think of the answer.
- Seriously. You can't think of it.
- Your mind goes blank.
Your mind suddenly goes blank.
You become flustered.
Don't act like
it's a momentary lapse.
- You don't know the answer.
- It's true.
I am pretty nervous.
This is nerve-racking.
This is very nerve-racking.
- Four.
- That's good.
- Entertainment and sports.
I envy him.
Entertainment and sports.
We are off to a good start.
- You must answer in five seconds.
- Okay.
- I get one question, right?
- Yes.
Let's go.
- It isn't very difficult.
- It isn't difficult.
Get ready to play the tune
for the correct answer.
In an international soccer match...
- It will be easy.
- He might not know about soccer.
Sending the ball into your own net
is described as OG.
- OG.
What does OG stand for?
- He wouldn't know.
- He would know.
- Your own net.
- Aren't there choices?
- Five, four,
- Sending it into your own net.
- three,
- Oh, my gosh.
- two...
- Oh, my gosh?
(What does OG stand for?)
- Okay.
- It wasn't...
- an easy question.
- Oh, my gosh.
- It was hard.
- Own goal.
- That's right.
- Own goal?
- Own. O-W-N.
- Own.
- Own goal.
- I should have gotten the question.
- English.
- Five.
- What's the subject?
- Korean history.
- It will be hard.
- Korean history isn't bad.
Jun Ho, you don't know much
about Korean history.
(Teasing)
- Yes, he does.
- He knows so much about it.
You fell asleep
during the Korean history class.
- You are annoyed, aren't you?
- Really?
Here comes the question.
It's about the leader
of Donghak Peasant Revolution,
- Jeon Bong Jun.
- I know this one.
He is my ancestor.
Which nickname did he have
because of his short stature?
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
General Mung Bean.
(Correct)
- Let me answer. General Mung Bean.
- Okay.
(Jun Ho quickly got
the correct answer.)
That was incredible.
- He is the older brother indeed.
- Seriously.
A younger sibling
can't surpass an older sibling.
(Town A advanced 5 squares!)
- You answered so confidently.
- Let's go.
You said you are good at quizzes.
- Seriously.
- I am sorry.
(His claim of being a smart man
was proven false in 5 minutes.)
What's wrong with you?
I got on my knees
as soon as I failed to answer.
- Yuri.
- Me?
- Okay.
If you get five
and answer correctly,
you can catch the pawn.
- You can catch the pawn.
- Come on, Yuri.
- Catch the pawn.
- Five.
- Let's catch it.
- I love you
- It's English.
- English?
- Isn't English better?
- Yuri,
- you performed abroad many times.
- You can speak English, right?
- A little bit.
- She knows enough to go shopping.
- I just know enough to go shopping.
I am in trouble.
- Imagine that you are at a shop.
- My heart is beating fast.
I am the same.
- So Min and I are anxious.
- Seriously.
Talking about English
makes my heart beat fast.
- I am like...
- You know,
So Min isn't talking anymore.
Your lack of knowledge
isn't exactly a secret, okay?
Just take it easy.
- Here comes the question.
- Let's go.
In English, a fly is "Fly."
- Fly.
- A butterfly is "Butterfly."
- What's a dragonfly in English?
- It's so easy.
Hold on. I...
- A dragonfly.
- A dragonfly?
What is it?
A dragonfly? What is it?
- Dragon...
- Dragonfly.
It's "Dragonfly," right?
- Jae Suk!
- That's right!
I got it right! Dragonfly!
There was a character
with the same name.
I got it right. Dragonfly.
- I should have gotten English.
- I am so flustered.
I got it right.
It's Town A's turn.
We can't advance.
- I got it right, So Min.
- We are pretty good at this.
I am sorry.
"Dragonfly" is basic knowledge.
I didn't know either.
You heard the answer first.
No, I didn't. I knew the answer.
- Let's go, Hyoyeon.
- Hyoyeon.
- Let's get English.
- Let's go.
I am nervous.
- Hyoyeon.
- You got this.
- Four.
It's English.
- English?
- Didn't you live abroad?
- Hyoyeon is...
- I lived in China.
totally from Incheon.
- I thought she was Korean American.
- Incheon?
- I know.
- I thought she could speak English.
Many people think that, right?
- So many people think that.
- All right.
Here comes the question.
- There are 12 months in a year.
- Yes.
Say 5 months in 5 seconds.
- Months?
- Yes.
This is easy.
July, June,
May, April,
Monday...
Where did Monday come from?
(Monday?)
- Monday.
- Where did Monday come from?
Monday.
June, July, April...
- She became flustered.
- Monday!
- Seriously.
- Hey.
Was she about to say
Monday and Sunday?
If you hadn't said that,
you would have looked cool.
She was probably confused.
- I was totally confused.
- She was probably confused.
- It's okay.
- Hyoyeon, you did well.
- I did well, right?
- You did well.
You were nearly done.
It's our turn.
It isn't even my turn,
but I am so nervous.
So Min is really nervous
even though it isn't her turn.
- So Min, go next.
- Go.
- I hope...
- you don't get two.
- You will go against Ji Hyo.
Go, So Min.
- Just don't get two.
- This is nerve-racking.
- One.
- Korean.
- It will be dictation.
- That's a good subject.
- It might be about grammar.
- Dictation.
- Korean is a good subject.
- It will be easy.
Korean is hard.
- All right.
- It's hard.
Who wrote the first Korean novel,
"The Story of Hong Gil Dong?"
- Don't you know it?
- It's easy.
The author
of "The Story of Hong Gil Dong."
(6 months ago,
Empty Heads had a study session.)
- "The Story of Hong Gil Dong."
- "Call each other brothers."
("Call each other brothers?")
"For I cannot call my father
'Father'..."
You were referring
to that line, right?
You're wrong.
"Call each other brothers"...
is the expression you use
for close friendship.
(She learned about the author
during a lesson from Suk Jin.)
- Heo Gyun.
His name is similar to Heo Jun's.
Heo Gyun.
(She definitely memorized
the name, Heo Gyun.)
(Will So Min remember the name?)
- Don't you know it?
- It's easy.
Heo...
(That's it!)
Heo Jun. Heo Cham!
(Heo Jun!)
(Heo Jun?)
(She memorized it as a name
that is similar to Heo Jun's.)
- Someone told you, right?
- No.
- Hey!
- How shocking.
- Heo Jun...
was played by Jeon Gwang Ryeol.
Her pulse is racing.
It's Heo Gyun.
It's not like that.
- We learned it a while ago.
- Where did Heo Jun come from?
- My heart is beating so fast.
- Hey.
We haven't left the starting line.
Heo Jun is a bit...
At this rate, we will have
a never ending quiz show.
- Seriously. What do we do?
- Let's go.
(It's Haha's turn.)
- Which subject do you want?
- Two.
- It's English. Okay.
- English.
Haha is good at English.
- He is pretty bad at it.
- He doesn't know the Alphabet.
In email, what does e stand for?
(In email, what does e stand for?)
- Electronic.
- Pardon?
- What?
- What did you say?
Say it again.
What's the spelling?
(The production crew asks him
to spell it out.)
Okay.
(Surprised)
(Electronic guy)
- Electronic.
- Haha is good.
- At the end...
- Since he has children,
- he is knowledgeable.
- Electronic.
I thought he would put K at the end.
- Seriously.
Electronic.
- Electronic.
- He didn't put K at the end.
- He is good.
- All right.
- He learned it.
- Electronic.
He is good.
(Thanks to Haha,
Town A advances 2 squares!)
Okay.
(Yoori got 5.)
- Korean history. Let's go.
- I need to get it right.
- Let's go, Yuri.
- Okay.
Let's begin.
What's the name of the policy
from the late Joseon Period...
that was implemented
in order to recruit people fairly...
regardless
of their political affiliations?
- The name of the policy?
- Yes.
- It's an exam, right? An exam.
- What?
In order to recruit people fairy...
Don't give her a hint.
- Hold on.
- Don't tell her anything.
What's the name of the policy...
that was implemented
in order to recruit people fairly?
- I know the answer.
- Yes, you know the answer.
- You know the answer.
- I really know it.
- It's an exam.
- A policy.
Five seconds passed.
- Hold on.
- A policy.
- Give me a hint.
- Five.
- Just this once.
- Three,
two,
- one.
- A policy.
- Tangpyeongchaek.
- Come on.
For goodness' sake.
- It's in the textbook.
- Yes.
It isn't
"Winning the state examination."
Winning the state examination.
- Tangpyeongchaek.
- It's different from tangsuyuk.
- Right.
- Hold on. Suk Jin.
- What?
Why do you keep making fun
of my teammates?
- It's not like that.
- He acts all haughty.
- Seriously.
- What's wrong with you?
Why do you keep making fun
of my teammates?
- He is so annoying.
- Suk Jin is so annoying today.
- Let's begin.
- Which subject did she get?
- World history.
I am so nervous.
What's the name
of the French hero...
who saved France from a crisis
during the Hundred Years' War?
- You should know the answer.
- I know it.
- You know it.
- She is like this.
- Be quiet.
- That's right.
(What's the name
of the French hero?)
I don't remember!
(She becomes angry
instead of giving the answer.)
Why don't you remember it?
Why did you say you know the answer?
- We know it.
- Do you know it?
- One, two, three.
- Napoleon.
What are you talking about?
- What's the answer?
- It's Joan of Arc.
- Joan of Arc?
- Those Empty Heads.
The three Empty Heads said
"Napoleon."
- One, two, three.
- Napoleon.
(Team Napoleon had
4 members, not 3.)
- Hey.
- We mouthed the word.
- It's Joan of Arc.
- We went,
"Napoleon."
Oh, no.
It's Joan of Arc.
Hundred Years' War.
- We are back to the beginning.
- I am sorry.
- I feel dizzy. Seriously.
- This won't end.
It's this town's turn.
I think Yuri is...
- I think Yuri is suffering too.
- She is having a mental breakdown.
None of them can laugh.
Hey.
How could you give a guest
a mental breakdown?
- I feel dejected.
- I hope this ends soon.
- I hate this segment.
- It's okay.
Se Chan, go ahead.
World history
or entertainment and sports.
- Entertainment and sports.
- You got this.
Show us what you can do.
Try to get four.
Don't let me get English.
- Five. Korean history.
- Good.
- Korean history.
- That's one of the better ones.
- You have a chance.
- Why are you showing confidence?
- What?
- Korean history is better.
- Korean history...
- He has a chance.
- He watches many period dramas.
- Yes.
- I learned from dramas.
- That's right.
- Let's begin.
- Please read it slowly.
I am bad at listening.
Please read it slowly.
He wants time to think.
What's the name of the general...
who became a hero in 1018
by stopping the Khitan invasion?
Gang Gam Chan.
(Correct)
(Se Chan knows
who Gang Gam Chan is.)
(They can't believe their ears.)
Gang Gam Chan is
the only one he knows.
Seriously.
As soon as I heard the question,
I went, "It's Gam Gang Chan."
Hold on. What?
- Hey.
- He doesn't know anything else.
I went, "It's Gam Gang Chan."
- Hey.
- He doesn't know anything else.
- Did you say "Gam Gam Chan?"
- What?
- What's the exact answer?
(His pronunciation
comes under fire.)
- What's the exact answer?
- He said it's correct.
- No.
- Say it.
Don't ask. Don't be like that.
- He pronounced it strangely.
- Say it.
- Write it down.
Don't be like that. I got it right.
- Hurry up and say it.
- "Gam Gam Chan?"
"Gam Chan?"
- What's the answer?
- Gam Gan Chan.
Gwang Gam Chan. Gam Gam Chan.
- Gam Gam Chan.
- Come on.
- He got it right.
- Gam Gam Chan.
- Write it down.
We were uncertain,
but your pronunciation seems off.
- Please write it down.
- Gam Gam Chan.
- Hey.
- Come on.
Why are you making him
write it down?
- It won't be an issue if he knows.
- I looked cool, okay?
Why are you doing this?
- Is his last name Gam or Gang?
- You should know it.
Don't say anything.
All right. Write it down.
(He begins
to write down the answer.)
This is the biggest crisis.
- If I get this wrong...
- Se Chan.
Just write it down.
Think of Kang Chan Hee.
- Hey!
- What's wrong with you?
Why can't I talk about
Kang Chan Hee?
- Don't give him a hint!
- What?
- Jae Suk.
- For goodness' sake.
- Kang Chan Hee isn't here today.
- Hey.
Why did you give him a hint?
I didn't do anything.
Show us the answer. One, two, three.
(What did Se Chan write down?)
Two, three.
Gam Gang Chan.
(Incorrect)
(That punk.)
(General Gang Gam Chan's last name
became Gam.)
Gam Gang Chan.
Because Jae Suk talked about
Kang Chan Hee,
he wrote down "Gam Gang Chan."
He got "Gam Gang Chan"
from Kang Chan Hee.
Gam Gang Chan.
You shouldn't have said anything.
- Hey.
- You confused me.
Why didn't you get "Gang Gam Chan"
from "Kang Chan Hee?"
- No.
- Gam Kang Chan Hee.
- Kang Chan Hee.
(Gam Kang Chan Hee)
For goodness' sake.
My answer was correct.
Your answer was correct.
- You were close.
- My stomach hurts.
- He startled me.
- You were flustered, right?
- Your answer was correct.
- My answer was correct.
I am so frustrated.
It's Ji Hyo's turn.
Here comes the Red Hare.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Okay.
Here comes Ji Hyo.
- English.
- It's okay. You can do it.
- I am not good at English.
- We can't get past that part.
Ji Hyo's face fell.
Why can't there be rivalry?
- Seriously.
- You can do it.
- All right.
- It will be easy.
What's the English title
of the movie, "Parasite?"
You know this.
Come on.
(What's the English title
of the movie, "Parasite?")
- Two...
- "Amoeba?"
"Paracide."
("Amoeba?")
- "Paracide."
- I thought it was "Amoeba" too.
"Amoeba!"
- Isn't it "Amoeba?"
- What's the answer?
- "Paracide."
- Guys.
- I know it's "Paracide."
- "Paracide?"
- "Paracide."
- What?
- It's incorrect.
- "Paracide."
What's "Paracide?"
To be honest,
I thought it was "Bacteria."
- "Bacteria?"
- I thought it was "Bacteria."
"Bacteria."
(Empty Heads' answers
are quite varied.)
- "Parasite?"
- Why do you guys keep answering?
- She keeps...
- Just sit still.
She keeps asking me
what the answer is.
- Just sit still like Yuri.
- Right.
It's this team's turn.
Jae Suk, it's your turn. Get five.
- Get five.
- It's my turn.
- Let's advance.
- Jae Suk.
- Please.
- Five, I love you
- Five
- I love you a lot
- Five.
- Zero.
- Three. It isn't half bad.
- It's good.
World history is a good subject.
Just get it right.
- Let's advance.
- Let's advance this once.
We can advance this time.
Let's advance.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
World history.
- In Europe,
- What? Europe.
this movement emerged
in the 14th to 16th centuries.
The name means
"Revival of literature and art."
What's this movement?
- Renaissance.
It was easy.
- I had no idea.
- We are advancing.
- It was easy.
- Let's advance three squares.
World history is unexpectedly easy.
Let's advance three squares.
Which Greek philosopher said,
"Laws are not made for the good?"
Socrates.
Yes.
- I knew the answer.
- I knew it was Socrates.
I knew it was Socrates.
- It's our turn.
- Let's go.
- Yuri.
- Yes.
Yuri, get it right.
My goodness.
Get a high number.
Roll the die.
- Five.
- Yuri, get it together.
Five.
- Four.
- That's good.
That's good.
I keep getting English.
You can do it.
Yuri, you can do it.
You have it in you.
Let's go.
(It's a chance to get ahead.)
- Let's begin.
- Don't be intimidated.
When the performance ends
and the audience applauds...
Encore.
- What?
Hold on.
Listen to the question.
- She got ahead of herself.
- It's encore!
It's curtain call.
- Yuri isn't strong-minded.
- Encore.
Why isn't it encore?
- Yuri isn't strong-minded.
- Hold on.
- People ask for an encore.
- Listen.
Why did you behave flippantly
without letting him finish?
- You behaved flippantly.
- Encore.
- You are in trouble.
- I feel dizzy.
- You are really in trouble.
- What are you going to do?
- I feel dizzy.
It's the curtain call.
Yuri, just accept it.
- That's the way to do it.
- Variety shows suit Yuri.
Variety shows suit Yuri.
How did she get "Encore?"
When Yuri finishes performing,
people ask for an encore.
Seriously. What's your problem?
- Good job.
- Yuri was too hasty.
- Curtain call.
- You haven't heard of it, have you?
- Why does he keep acting haughty?
- Have you heard of it?
- Suk Jin.
- I bet you haven't.
- Don't point at me.
- Of course he has heard of it.
I know what it is.
- Gam Gang Chan.
- You should have waited.
Gam Gang Chan.
Hey, Heo Jun.
Stay still.
- Gam Gang Chan. Heo Jun.
- Encore.
Jae Suk, Suk Jin is so annoying.
- The next question.
- We can win.
- She is so cute.
- I bet he hasn't heard of it.
- If we keep going like this...
- Let's go.
Has a quiz like this ended
during the shoot?
It will end.
- Why can't we advance?
- We haven't advanced a square.
- I feel so dizzy.
- There are only 12 squares.
So Min feels dizzy.
So Min doesn't want to do this.
Please throw us white cloth.
Ditch the rule about
going back to the starting line.
Let's do that.
- Shall we do that?
- We can't advance otherwise.
What's the name of the emperor
who searched for the elixir of life?
Don't give it away.
Qin Shi Huang.
(The older brother is better
than the younger brother.)
- All right.
- He is good.
What's the tomb
of the king of Egypt called?
- This is easy.
- Think about it.
Pyramid.
(Thus, the two towns advance.)
- What?
- Pyramid.
- Write it down.
- Yuri.
- It's Yuri's turn.
- Let's go.
Everyone, it's Yuri's turn.
- Yuri, encore.
- Encore.
(The audience cheers
for Ms. Encore.)
- Let's go.
- Let's go, Yuri.
Show us what you can do.
Get five.
(The squares at the end have
different levels of difficulty.)
- Yuri.
- Get five. Let's go.
(She needs a small number
to get an easy question.)
- Two.
- That's perfect.
(She gets the easiest question!)
- Level one.
- That's perfect.
- Yuri, get it right.
- It's level one.
- You can do it.
- Even though it's level one,
you never know because it's Yuri.
- You can do it.
If you get this right,
people will forget about encore.
- Encore.
- Think of your image.
- Good luck.
- Let's begin.
Think of your image.
What's the term that refers
to the moral obligation...
- those of a high social class have?
- Hold on. What?
What's the term that refers
to the moral obligation...
- those of a high social class have?
- This is really easy.
- It can be confusing.
- It's used often.
- Three...
- Don't say anything.
What? What did you say?
The term that refers
to the moral obligation.
Those of a high social class
have more moral obligations.
- Moral obligations?
- She doesn't know.
They have more moral obligations?
She doesn't know the answer.
Don't say anything.
- Don't say anything.
- She doesn't know the answer.
- Hold on. I am nervous.
- It has two words.
- I am nervous.
- Don't say anything.
- Eight letters...
- What's wrong with you?
Five, four,
- three...
- Bourgeois.
"Bourgeois?"
- Three...
- Bourgeois.
("Bourgeois" came out of nowhere.)
- Oh, no.
- It's "Noblesse oblige."
- You don't know what it is.
- I know what it is.
I know what it is.
- Do you know?
- I know what it is.
- Hey.
- It's "Noblesse oblige."
- Sit down.
- Stop it.
- Do you know...
what So Min said?
- Stop it.
- So Min said, "Great people."
- "Great people?"
Great people.
(A truly great person
when it comes to quizzes)
- Great people.
- I want to use the restroom.
- I am about to throw up.
- You know,
- Yuri.
it's natural to be confused.
Noblesse oblige.
- Can I use the restroom?
- No.
- You are up next. You can't go.
- I need to pee.
- You are up next.
- But...
- I want to use the restroom.
- Go ahead.
- Can I go?
Quiz gives them a stomachache.
Seriously.
- It's because of the quiz.
- The irritable bowel syndrome.
- This is too much.
- I might end up going home.
Three. Here I go.
- We caught the pawn.
- We caught it.
- You need to answer the question.
You need to answer the question
to catch the pawn.
- You need to answer the question.
- That's right.
- Why did you use your thighs?
- Answer the question first.
- Answer and catch.
- "Answer and catch?"
- Suk Jin's Answer and Catch.
- Catch.
Why did your cheeks turn rosy?
It's strange.
- He is sick and tired of it.
- It's hot.
- It's too hot.
- Your cheeks turned rosy.
This is driving me crazy.
Korean history is hard.
- You can do it.
- I need to catch the pawn.
He can handle Korean history
because he is ancient.
That's right. I was probably alive
when historical events happened.
- That's right.
- I used to live in Hanyang.
- He used to live in Hanyang.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
(If Suk Jin gets it right,
his team will win.)
Where was the bell
which notified an emergency...
as well as the time
the city gate closed and opened?
Shinmungo.
(Incorrect)
The answer is "Bosingak."
You must have been alive then.
Shinmungo.
We are saved.
- We are saved.
- What?
It's "Bosingak."
- Is it "Bosingak?"
- "Shinmungo?"
- I had no idea.
- He doesn't have much knowledge.
You don't have the basic knowledge.
You can't laugh
because you don't know anything.
Suk Jin.
(Mr. Shinmungo
begins to aggravate them again.)
- You don't know anything.
- He is like that until the end.
You don't know what "Shinmungo" is.
I bet you don't.
You are really aggravating.
- I bet you don't.
- Mister, what's wrong with you?
- Seriously.
- Suk Jin.
- Why do you keep doing that?
- Mister.
- What a strange man!
- We have the basic knowledge.
What's wrong with you?
- You don't know anything.
- Why do you keep teasing us?
Tell us what it is then.
- Suk Jin.
- He is really aggravating.
- Suk Jin is annoying.
- He is annoying.
If So Min and Se Chan dated,
they would have fun together.
- They would have fun together.
- We wouldn't know anything.
- Seriously.
- We would be happy.
- We don't know what "Bosingak" is.
- So Min, it's your turn.
- I need to use the restroom.
- I will let you go ahead.
- Hurry up.
- You can do it. You can answer it.
- The question...
- Get five.
- You can do it.
- Go ahead.
- You can do it!
- Why is everyone so annoying?
- Go ahead.
(The best-case scenario is
getting a level-1 question with 2.)
- Let's get five.
- Come on.
- It's five.
- Five.
(The worst-case scenario is
getting a level-4 question with 5.)
Let's get 5. It's 5.
(Finish line)
(She got a level-four question.)
- It's five.
- Five.
So Min, this is better.
It wouldn't look strange
if you get it wrong.
You will be a hero
if you get it right.
- So Min, you might get it right.
- Then you will graduate.
You will be a hero
if you get it right.
You will move up a level
You will graduate
from the Empty Head Club.
Then... Oh, right.
- Let's begin.
- What?
- Why?
- Then...
(Getting up)
Let's begin.
- What?
- Why?
(So Min suddenly runs
toward the production crew.)
Why? What are you
trying to tell them?
(Whispering)
She wants to use the thing
she earned the other day.
(She wants to use the thing
she earned the other day.)
The card.
- Is she using the card now?
- I see.
You can't do that.
No, it's not like that.
Can she use that?
(So Min suddenly recalls the wish
she earned 10 months ago.)
(Tell me the answers to English
and Chinese character quizzes.)
(So Min won the chance card
for quizzes last summer.)
It was a few months ago.
- It was a long time ago.
- The chance card for quizzes.
(She won the chance card
for quizzes a few months ago.)
(The chance card for quizzes)
It's over. We won.
- That's right.
- This is unbelievable.
Will our viewers know
about this or not?
- They don't.
- Are we supposed to say...
- you solved the quiz?
- Sure.
- That's perfect.
- It's a good idea.
- Are you using the card here?
- Right now?
That means a lot to her.
It's such a great card.
- It's over. We won.
- My gosh.
(So Min's crucial chance
to get away from the quizzes.)
We should act surprised then.
- You should.
- That's clever.
Why would we do this
when it won't go on TV?
It will. We will ask a question.
And you give us an answer.
We will say it's correct.
(And you give us an answer.
We will say it's correct.)
- Just anything?
- No matter what she says?
- You say it's correct anyway.
- She can give a random answer.
- What are you talking about?
- You don't tell her the answer.
Okay. I get it.
(Whatever she says, it's correct.)
(It's not that she gets
to hear the correct answer.)
- You can't do that to her.
- Okay.
- You should tell her the answer.
- You should tell me the answer.
- Right. She won't look cool.
- She won't look smart.
- Great.
- This is ridiculous.
- That makes sense.
- So Min.
So Min. It's like getting a shot.
It will sting for a moment.
It's an injection. It stings.
- You have to cut this out.
- It's an injection.
- It stings.
- So Min, that's it.
It's an injection. It just stings.
- It will sting for a moment.
- It's like an injection.
So Min, you won't look cool though.
- Right.
- It will just sting a little.
- It won't take long.
- We need to get this quiz right.
- It's no big deal.
- It's all right.
Once you give an answer,
they will say it's correct.
- It will sound great. So Min.
- She won the card.
- It will sound good.
- Make sure...
- to show some reactions.
- Okay.
- Pretend I got it right.
Okay. We will make you look cool.
So Min, you did it.
So Min.
Once you talk,
it will be dubbed
with a voice actress' voice.
(Once you talk, it will be dubbed
with a voice actress' voice.)
- So it's not her voice.
- So Min.
- Right.
- I see, So Min.
So you should say something.
All right. It is a procedure...
where members of the National
Assembly prolong debate...
You must know the answer.
- Hang on.
- to delay a decision legitimately.
You can hear it
on the news every day.
It's the prolonged debate of
members of the National Assembly...
to delay a decision legitimately.
- That's...
- It's on the news every day.
- Break time.
- Hang on. A debate?
- Whatever you say is correct.
- You'll get it anyway.
I want to get it right.
There's no way you can answer it.
Just say anything.
Why would you say that?
- Don't say that.
- You will never get it right.
Filibuster.
(Correct)
That's unbelievable.
- Filibuster.
- My goodness.
(She gives an answer with fluency.)
(Impressed)
(That's amazing.)
There you go, So Min.
She did it.
- My goodness.
- How did she know that?
(Her brilliant answer
makes everyone applaud.)
You are very smart.
- Right.
- My goodness.
We won. We won the race!
- Unbelievable.
- Yes!
- Gosh, So Min.
- We win.
But it seemed like So Min was
saying something shorter.
It was short.
Like a three-syllable word.
Hearing.
(Her real answer is
just between us.)
You nailed it.
Thanks to So Min,
Yes!
Town B wins the race.
- So they will pick the amounts.
- Okay.
We should do this right.
We should pick a good one.
I should pick a good one.
Not the one with negative numbers.
I need to pick a good one.
- I should do this well.
- Everyone.
Before you pick anything,
you should know that Town B
has more members to get a penalty.
- Really?
- They have lower amounts.
- We should pick good ones here.
- Right.
- I'll pick one.
(Hyoyeon: 1, Se Chan: 1,
and So Min: 1.50 dollars)
The losing team picks first.
The losing team.
I can't choose one.
Please. I need good luck.
(The losing team picks an amount
between -1.50 to 1.50 dollars.)
- My gosh.
- Seriously, this is...
Thank you for picking one for me.
This is important.
It shouldn't be a minus.
Hyoyeon, you should pick a good one.
- It's us.
- All right.
I pick number two.
(Now it's Town B's turn.)
(Se Chan has 1 dollar.)
- Number 2.
- Number 1.
- All right.
- You always get good numbers.
Number two?
- Number 1? I want number 1.
- I picked 2 dollars.
You got two dollars.
(The amount they pick now
can change their rankings completely.)
(How will it turn out?)
The result is in.
It's quite interesting.
- Interesting?
- An interesting result?
All right.
Let me announce the winner first.
(The winner of today's race!)
Kim Jong Kook with nine dollars.
(1st place Kim Jong Kook)
- I picked good numbers.
- Right.
- I lost twice.
- He got great numbers.
And the difference between 2nd
and 3rd places is only 0.50 dollars.
Who is it?
- Is it you?
- No, it can't be me.
It's Haha with five dollars.
(2nd place Haha)
- He's my business partner.
- Haha is second place.
Second place?
- That's a lot.
- I think I have about four dollars.
I will announce the rankings
of the rest later.
Let me tell you the two members
with the lowest amounts.
- Who are they?
- I guess it's me.
All right.
The member with the lowest amount.
(Hyoyeon, So Min, and Se Chan
had the lowest amounts earlier.)
To get the penalty.
Who is it?
Yang Se Chan with two dollars.
(Yang Se Chan is the last.)
Was it that bad?
What are you going to do?
My goodness.
- Gosh, Se Chan...
- So am I getting a penalty?
Gosh, I'm so upset.
And above him...
Who is it?
Who would it be?
I bet it's me.
It's Yoo Jae Suk with 2.50 dollars.
- That's right.
- My gosh.
Is it you? I knew it.
Please leave
Protruded Brothers alone.
But the penalty...
I've been getting
a penalty for weeks.
- Protruded Brothers.
- Please bring in...
the prize first.
(The prize will be revealed first.)
- It's honey.
- Honey is rare these days.
It's honey.
It looks really nice.
It's the finest honey gift set
that will make the broken hearts...
of the enemies sweet.
- I will give this to my mom.
- Good.
I'll give this to my mother-in-law.
She will love it.
And here's today's penalty.
Actually, we had different penalties
for the members and guests.
- Really?
- But only the members lost.
Here's the penalty for the members.
(Today's penalty
for Jae Suk and Se Chan is...)
You will have to come
one hour early for the next shoot.
(Coming 1 hour early
for the next shoot)
You two will come an hour early
and do something special.
- My gosh.
- Darn it.
(One week later)
(For your Running Man)
- What is this?
- What are we doing?
(Are you ready to cast a vote?)
Thank you for supporting me.
(The only throne)
(And the 100 kingmakers)
(I hope those who voted
for Jong Kook will be eliminated.)
You're good.
(To become the last one)
(To be selected by the 100 people)
(They should be able
to deal with anything.)
Please go stop him.
(The higher you go,)
(the stronger the wind becomes.)
(Please.)
(220,000 views, 1 year ago)
(They can't survive
once they get eliminated.)
(It's a race for survival.)
(Which member of Running Man
will be at the top?)
(The 1st Division Game)