It's The Running Tag of Tails.
You will hide your name tags in Sangam-dong.
Please go to Nanjicheon Pond.
SBS.
This is perfect.
- Hey. - I worked really hard for this.
- It's over. - Hyung In, can I enter your house?
Se Chan found your name tag.
- This is... - You're just one of us now.
My gosh.
- I can't believe... - Someone gave him the address.
No, it wasn't me. Jae Suk, I'm serious.
- I didn't do it. - I can't believe this.
The race will be over once one of you collects six tails.
Then we will continue the next race in the SBS building.
- Is it the first race? - Yes.
- Is this for two episodes? - The two members...
with the highest scores will be the winners and win the prizes.
Two in the last will be getting a penalty.
- Two members. - You will get the most points...
in the first race.
You will move on to the next race with the ranks from the first one.
- Really? - So it's important to get...
many points and high ranks in this race.
I'll tell you how to get more points in the first race.
- If you find someone's name tag, - I found it thanks to you.
you get 100 points.
- Yes. - I'm out?
- Suk Jin is eliminated. - And if your name tag...
is found by someone else, you lose 100 points.
- Jae Suk found your name tag. - Oh my, he found it.
If you found the name tag of a member who has tails,
you get extra points according to the number of tails.
- Congratulations. - He is so simple-minded.
- Song Ji Hyo is out. - It's over.
Se Chan, you found Jae Suk's name tag.
So the race is over.
- Only she knows where he hid it. - Amazing.
No, it wasn't me. Jae Suk, I'm serious.
- You're unbelievable. - You're really...
- Jeon So Min, you are... - Seriously, I didn't do it.
Let's go.
- You have no choice. - I know.
Seriously, Jeon So Min...
How could you do this? My gosh.
I'm sorry, but you have to hurry.
We have to go. We don't have time.
- Hurry up. - What's all this?
Hold this.
I did it. You should give me some points.
"You can open the door." She said that.
Let's hide my name tag someplace else.
Will you be able to hide it in a good location?
I will have three minutes.
I can move around in this car.
- Se Chan. - Hey, So Min.
What?
Where are you?
If I...
tell you that, will you make me number two?
I will give you the highest number. I think Ji Hyo is coming now.
It might be over soon. So I should hurry and...
Jae Suk just moved his name tag.
Where?
If I tell you that, will you make me number two?
- Yes, I will. - Wait. Let me see where I am now.
It's my first time going to a producer's house.
Thank you.
So Min, what's with you?
It's the So Min I know. I almost got disappointed.
I knew this would happen. I knew it would go like this.
- Seriously, I'm...
- Hello.
I was so disappointed.
So Min, you...
So Min is upset as well.
I knew you'd do this.
I see.
I realized it after hiding mine.
"Oh, right. So Min is watching."
So I asked the driver to stay there.
You shouldn't have trusted her.
Why did you trust her?
I didn't trust her.
I was just in a hurry.
- I mean...
- And...
So Min helped me twice.
- She made him number one.
- Right.
And that's not all.
When I was in the elevator,
So Min heard Hyung In
talk on the phone.
- And I found Haha's name tag.
- It was really hard to find.
Hyung In was...
- acting a little strange.
- I thought it was ridiculous.
What kind of producer
would let us use her house?
- That doesn't make sense.
- Hyung In, are you okay with this?
They must be really close.
I didn't know
I'd go to Hyung In's house.
Me neither.
- Seriously, Hyung In was...
- It was new.
- It was your first time, right?
- It was.
It was my first time
going to a producer's house.
Ji Hyo, why did you go to her place?
I was going to go to Pyeonghwa Park.
Then I came up with a place
where you can't find my name tag.
I was near Hyung In's house,
- so I asked for her passcode.
- That's unbelievable.
She didn't tell me,
so I sent her like 30 text messages.
"Hyung In, please help me."
- And I was there.
- And she got caught.
So I will tell you
the points you've earned.
Se Chan got 650 points.
- Yes!
- That's a lot.
Jae Suk got 450 points.
- My gosh.
- That's not bad.
And Haha and Ji Hyo got zero points.
- What?
- Why?
Suk Jin got minus 20 points.
- Oh, dear.
- Minus?
- Minus 20 points?
So Min got minus 60 points.
Why is it minus?
Jong Kook got minus 100 points.
- Why?
- Why is it minus?
You lose 100 points
when your name tag is found.
Those who didn't find anything
have low points.
- I see.
- I lost mine at the beginning.
Anyway, you will have the next
mission with your current ranks.
Those with higher ranks are
more likely to win more points.
- Okay.
- So it's continuous.
Se Chan, you are
to decide your ranks.
It's ridiculous
that Se Chan gets to decide.
- Is it my call?
- Is it Se Chan's decision?
- Where's number one's seat?
- The one on the left.
I see. Move over.
Me?
- Move over.
- Sir.
- Hey.
- Hey, I...
How did you gain so much weight?
- Why is he...
- He gained a lot of weight.
What happened to you?
I keep gaining weight these days.
You look like a toad now.
But you look pleasantly plump.
- Pleasantly plump?
- That's not true.
You're the last. Go to the back.
- He's like an anchovy.
- Anchovy?
Actually, So Min was a big help.
I gave him my everything.
- So I have to make her number two.
- Hey.
- My gosh, give it to her.
- I mean,
- So Min... All right.
- Hey.
- I also helped you.
- So Min gave me everything.
I should've taken her phone away.
- Jong Kook.
- You shouldn't trust her like that.
- Her phone... Gosh.
- Why did you trust her?
So Min is number two.
I should've taken her phone away.
- Me.
- You can never trust her.
Se Chan, you can't abandon me.
- I won't abandon you.
- If I don't get picked here...
- How could you...
- I gave you all my tails.
So I enjoyed them. I loved it.
Number three is Jong Kook.
Okay. And Ji Hyo.
You're the last. This is it.
Please take your seat.
I'd rather be number seven
than flatter him.
- This is so upsetting.
- I guess we will draw.
Gosh, this is...
Let's just solve quizzes.
It's like a minefield over there.
We can get more points here.
Is that all right?
I love it.
- Salute.
- I'll give you a mission now.
- Okay.
If you complete the mission,
you will draw three ping-pong balls
for each question.
- Really?
- In the box,
you have 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2,
and 1 balls, respectively.
The one with the highest rank
has the most balls.
- So he's more likely to get picked.
- Right.
And the one with the lowest rank...
has the least chance
of getting picked.
- Oh, dear.
- If three balls have the same name,
the member will get all the points.
- Oh, dear.
- Okay.
Then I will give you a mission.
The mission is called...
Reversed Telepathy.
You will hear a keyword we give you.
And you will write down a word
that's related to the keyword.
Five members or more
should give different answers.
- Different answers?
- I see.
- I know what it is like.
- We can do this.
- We have good teamwork.
- Not the same answers.
Five members or more should
have different answers.
- So...
- I can do this.
You should just give random answers.
If you give different answers,
we will draw three balls.
- I'll write the obvious ones.
- Okay.
- And if you...
- Because you're number one.
fail the mission, Yang Se Chan,
who is currently number one,
will lose 50 points.
If you fail.
- Number one is not good.
- He loses points?
Yes, 50 points.
That's a lot.
- Then we should fail.
- If you succeed,
you might get 90 points
per question.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
You can also change
your ranks after each question.
I can change the ranks?
You can switch
the ranks of two members.
- I will try my best.
- I'll work hard.
- Try your best.
- Here's the first question.
At least five members
should give different answers.
- Okay.
- I can do that.
A three-syllable capital city.
- A three-syllable capital city?
- Yes.
You get ten seconds.
A capital city.
- You can't cheat.
- We can give different answers.
This is difficult.
Hang on.
This is mine.
A capital city?
- Don't write it.
- This might not be a capital city.
Three syllables...
- All right. Ten.
- Hang on.
- Wait. I can't think of anything.
- What if I don't write anything?
Then you fail.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- If we give the same answers...
- Hang on. To get points...
- I'm sure we have the same answers.
Haha, what do you think we wrote?
It's obvious. What we know is...
- Hang on.
- I wrote a difficult one.
- Eight, seven,
- Just write anything.
six, five,
- What did you write?
- four,
- three, two, one. Open.
- I don't think this is a capital.
- It should be a capital city.
- Mine is a capital city.
- Gosh, Tottenham?
- Hey.
- Tottenham? That's ridiculous.
- My goodness.
- What do we do with Tottenham?
- Who wrote Tottenham?
Ji Hyo.
- Take turns and read your answers.
- Is it wrong?
- Bogota, the capital of Columbia.
- Okay.
- Lisbon.
- Manila.
- This is...
- Tottenham.
- Tottenham is wrong.
- This is...
- Washington.
- Brussels.
- Okay.
- Sidney is wrong, right?
- It's wrong.
But you gave five different answers.
- You can't do this.
- This is...
- You succeeded.
- Okay.
(The ones in the lower ranks
got it right against their wills.)
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo...
- gave wrong answers.
- Suk Jin.
- I tried my best.
- I know.
You two will go higher
in the next round.
You wrote Tottenham?
I couldn't think
of any capital cities.
A three-syllable word.
- So we...
- Did we succeed?
- Yes.
- We should get it wrong.
- But this is...
- You might get points.
If you do a good job,
I will bring you here. Don't worry.
- Really?
- You can come up higher.
- Will you do that?
- Of course.
I have a good reason.
- Isn't it cool that I wrote Bogota?
- Bogota?
- That's so cool.
- The capital of Columbia.
- No one knew it.
- Well done.
- There you go.
- I'm cool.
We will draw three balls.
Please.
(The members in higher ranks
with high probabilities...)
(and the ones in lower ranks
with low probabilities)
Kim Jong Kook, Song Ji Hyo,
and Jeon So Min.
(Kim Jong Kook, Song Ji Hyo,
and Jeon So Min.)
I'm not one of them?
(There are 7 balls
with his name on them.)
I'm not one of them?
- I'm so glad.
- We did it.
Kim Jong Kook, Song Ji Hyo,
and Jeon So Min get 30 points each.
- Thank you.
- So the probability matters.
This is nice.
- Thank you, Se Chan.
- Okay.
- I'll try my best.
- Good.
- My gosh.
- Do we stay here...
or go up?
You can switch two members.
I have no choice.
Ji Hyo should be number seven.
- I have no choice.
- You can only trade two members.
- Ji Hyo and...
- I worked hard.
You know I gave a different answer.
Hey, I'm the one
who first betrayed him.
You know I was
nothing but loyal to you.
All right.
- Hey.
- Nice.
(Punching)
(A new comedy skit is complete.)
- Comedians...
- Well done.
Hurry. "Well done?"
Well done.
- Hurry.
- First...
- Jae Suk has many points.
- Right.
So...
- I have zero points.
- The ones with lower points...
If you can't decide, just pick me.
All right then.
- Haha and Ji Hyo will switch.
- Thank you.
- But I...
- This is the right thing.
- I don't have many points.
- Suk Jin, you are up next.
If you keep going like this,
I won't cooperate.
- You won't cooperate?
- All right.
- Here's the second keyword.
- Okay. Let's go.
Chinese idioms about animals.
- Cheongomabi.
- Gungyeilhak.
That's good. I was going
to write it, but I changed.
- Pass.
- I changed it.
Tosagupaeng.
Hosiubo.
- Hosiubo?
- Yes.
Obiirak. But someone wrote it.
Hang on. Please take a look at this.
- What?
- What is it?
- Ji Hyo, what's that?
- Look.
- Hey, Tottenham.
- You should read this.
- Tottenham, what did you write?
- Let me see.
- Show us.
Just show us.
Nyangjungjichuk?
- Jichuk?
- What?
- Nyang?
- Is it a cat?
- A cat?
- Nyang, a cat?
That sounds cute.
And this should be "chu."
- And this is "nang."
- Is it about a cat?
- A cat's punch?
- It means a cat.
- Nyang.
- A cat?
All right. You have 2 same answers
and 1 wrong answer.
- So you failed.
- We failed.
Se Chan loses 50 points.
Will you go like this again?
I'll switch seats.
- I should go up.
- Send me up.
- Jae Suk will come up.
- Okay.
Who will switch with him?
- So Min will go down.
- No. I don't want to.
So Min and Jae Suk
will switch seats.
- If I go down, I'll mess it up.
- How?
I will write
the same answer as yours.
- So Min.
- Just go.
Get lost.
So Min, go down.
- Why are you there?
- You don't belong here.
So Min, this isn't fair.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- We should go against him.
- Captain Yang.
- Yes?
Why would you have someone...
- who talks nonsense sits here?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm so upset.
- All right. Let's begin.
A great man from the Joseon Dynasty.
But not a king.
- What? A great man?
- A great man of the Joseon Dynasty.
- Someone famous?
- Sure.
The Joseon Dynasty...
Exactly...
We should give different answers
for our captain, right?
I have a few options.
- No.
- The Joseon Dynasty?
- Why?
- Hey.
It's Joseon. That's...
- It's...
- You can't tell him that.
But this doesn't make sense.
He wrote Gang Gam Chan again.
No. I made a mistake.
- It's Kang Chan Hee.
- All right.
- Okay.
All right. Open.
Which one should I pick?
- Open your answers.
- What?
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin is upset.
- Suk Jin is mad.
- Why?
- What?
- What did he write?
- He's throwing a tantrum.
- A tantrum?
- He wrote Choi Bul Am.
- Excuse me.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- This is what I think.
- He's throwing a tantrum.
- He's a great man in my heart.
- It's all right.
- This is how I feel.
- Two people wrote Jeong Yak Yong.
Who wrote Jeong Yak Yong?
- Jeong Yak Yong?
- Do you know Jeong Yak Yong?
I do.
- Gosh, this is crazy.
- Of course.
- Just keep going like that.
- Hey, you know the answer.
- Now you have two questions left.
- Okay.
The keyword is...
economic terms.
(Economic terms)
- This is difficult.
- Economy.
I'll write the recent one.
- This is mine.
- What?
I know what you're talking about.
It should have something
to do with the economy.
- You are not supposed to insist.
- Okay. Good.
Captain Yang, do you want me
to do it right or not?
If you do well, you will
come up in the next round.
- Really?
- We have one more question.
- An economic term?
- All right.
You have five seconds.
You should explain what it means.
- What?
- Your answer.
Hey. Wait.
You should explain
what your answer means.
- I should change my answer.
- That's not right.
- Does it have to be correct?
- Of course.
You should give the correct answer.
(Inflation)
Then I should go
with something I know.
One, two, three. Open.
(Will 5 members or more
give different answers?)
I knew he'd write that.
Right. That's what Se Chan knows.
It's inflation.
Hang on.
Explain the word.
- Inflation, an increase in prices.
- Okay.
Inflation...
- in an economic recession
- Okay.
What about this?
- Big step.
- A rise in interest rates.
Did you write big step?
- Hey.
- By 0.5 percent.
Next. What is that?
- Big step.
- What did Haha write?
DC.
What did you say?
Discount.
- What did he say?
- Discount?
- Isn't it an economic term?
- What's that?
- DC.
- What about it?
- Why? Go ahead.
- We'll do some research first.
- Is it an economics term?
- Next, Ji Hyo.
My answer is "IMF"
as in the currency crisis.
- What does it stand for?
- Correct.
- Technically, it doesn't mean that.
- That's right.
- The IMF is...
- People collected gold, you know.
- That's right.
- But...
- the IMF...
- And US dollar bills.
- It's Ji Hyo. Let it count.
- Right.
- IMF...
- What caused the financial crisis?
- What caused it?
- Yes.
- It was a currency crisis.
- I asked what caused it.
Because there was a crisis
with the currency, I guess.
- The IMF...
- She's right.
- That's correct.
- Okay. We'll let it count.
- Good. Let's move on.
- That's correct.
- Please explain, So Min.
- It's correct. It stands for...
- "Save, share, exchange, reuse."
- SSER.
- The SSER movement.
- That's correct!
- Yes, that's right.
- It's an economics term.
- That's right.
- The SSER movement.
- We all participated in it.
- Don't you know this?
- "Discount" is a correct answer.
- "Save, share, exchange, reuse."
- Correct.
- Next.
- My answer is "barter."
- "Barter."
(The old economic system appeared.)
- Before people started using money.
- That's correct.
Before cash was used,
barter dominated economies.
- Correct.
- Okay.
Finally,
we all wrote correct answers.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- It's different since I moved up.
Se Chan, I wrote "barter"
that no one else wrote.
I know that. Good job.
- I hope my name will be picked.
- I'll pick three balls.
- Okay.
- Please show me a miracle.
- I lost 100 points.
- Great!
- My score is minus 100.
- One of them is Haha.
- Haha, Haha, and Jae Suk.
- Okay!
(Haha, Haha, and Jae Suk)
Okay!
(Se Chan failed again.)
How could you miss it every time?
What's wrong with you?
Really?
- Are my answers even in there?
- Haha gets 60 points.
- Se Chan.
- Okay.
- I need more points urgently.
- Right. I should change it.
- If you don't...
- Here goes the last question.
- Can I change the order?
- Yes, you can.
- Suk Jin, switch seats with Haha.
- Okay.
- This is fun.
- Move. Go down.
- Yes, I've moved up.
(Haha got demoted,
and So Min stays in her seat again.)
- I'll do my best.
- Thank you.
- It's different now that he's here.
- Of course.
Jae Suk is so reliable.
Why do you favor him?
- Do you know what "big step" is?
- Do you know the term?
- Yes.
All right.
You punk, the only term you knew
was "inflation."
- What did you just say?
- My gosh.
- That petty idiot.
- "Petty idiot?"
- What's his problem?
- You used to be a mere bike thief.
Leave, you punk!
For this question,
you all need to be...
- on the same wavelength.
- Okay.
- I hope to get some points.
- I guess we need more wit.
Write one of the special cities
or metropolitan cities in Korea.
(Including the special self-governing city
and province)
- I'm at the bottom.
- You're not allowed to give hints.
- You guys know, right?
- No hints.
- "You brat!"
(Everyone started giving hints.)
- I'm at the bottom.
- We should write different cities?
- "You see, you brat."
- Don't give one another a hint.
(Everyone makes loud noises
to give a hint.)
- "Honjeoobseye."
- "You punk!"
- "Mendorong ttottot."
"Honjeoobseye."
My goodness. Don't write this one.
- Hey, I'll write that one.
- Oh, gosh. No.
- You can't do that.
- Everyone.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- My goodness.
- You punks.
Hold on. A metropolitan city?
Or a special city.
It's not easy.
- Five, four,
- Write your hometown.
- three, two...
- I'll write what you wouldn't.
- My goodness.
- It's not easy.
Wait. They might not write this one.
- Somebody should go with "whale."
- I write an easy one.
- I gave up on the city.
- All right.
- The city of soccer.
- Time's up.
Okay.
- Here.
- I wrote this. Good.
- Busan.
- Seoul Special City.
- Daegu.
- Good.
- Is it a direct-controlled city?
- Incheon is a metropolitan city.
- It's been renamed.
- What's wrong with him?
- I'm relieved.
- Let me check.
- Two of you chose Seoul.
- Daejeon?
(Both Jae Suk and Ji Hyo write
Seoul.)
- Wait. Two of you wrote Incheon.
- Why?
- Gosh. Why did you write Incheon?
- Why did you guys do that?
Haha wrote "JeJu Metropolitan City."
- Hey, Jeju is...
- Jeju is not a metropolitan city.
- a special self-governing province.
- What's wrong with him?
Haha wrote "JeJu Metropolitan City."
(Everyone bursts with anger.)
(Jeju is
a special self-governing province!)
- Jeju is not a metropolitan city!
- Gosh, that...
- I can't believe him.
- That idiot!
That idiot.
Are you serious?
- My gosh. That's hilarious.
- It's a self-governing province.
- My gosh. How...
- Tell Dream not to watch this.
- Did you try to be funny?
- Why did you change your answer?
- He talked about a whale.
- Did you? Hey.
Hey, did anyone pick Gwangju?
- I mean...
- Hey, Jeju is...
a special self-governing province.
Why did you
speak in Gwangju dialect?
Suk Jin said he'd write it,
so I changed my answer.
- I thought she'd write it.
- Let's try one more time.
- It's an interesting result.
- I don't understand.
- You acted so arrogantly.
- "Jeju Metropolitan City?"
You kept shouting the Jeju dialect
"mendorong ttottot."
And you wrote
"Jeju Metropolitan City?"
- He's a weirdo.
- He also said "honjeoobseoye."
You shouldn't let Dream watch
this episode.
- I did it to drag him down.
- Haha.
- He's lying.
- There are cities and provinces.
I know. I intentionally wrote
an incorrect answer.
- Nonsense. "Mendorong ttottot!"
- What a joke.
Now, we'll move on...
- Is it over?
- Yes, the first mission is over.
- This is ridiculous.
- It was an easy question.
Se Chan, change the ranks
before we begin the next mission.
- For a game?
- Yes.
- Is the order important?
The order has been decided.
We'll prepare for the next mission.
That was hilarious.
(The new ranks have been announced.)
They brought a strange machine.
What do we do?
- It can tell if you're lying.
- You mean, it's a lie detector?
In this mission, you need luck
and a good hunch.
It's Did It Go through?
There are 30 outlets on the walls.
Can you see them?
- Yes.
- Why are there so many outlets?
But only six of them work.
- Six of them?
- I see.
Starting with the captain,
in the order of your ranks,
put on the pad of the low-frequency
therapy and call a number.
You get 30 points if you choose
an outlet that doesn't work.
(If it works, they get 30 points.
If not, they get eliminated.)
If it works, you get eliminated.
- Right away?
- Yes.
You'll repeat this starting with
the member who's first in rank.
Then the member who's first in rank
is at an advantage.
Right. But you never know
what Se Chan will choose.
- Is this a real machine?
- He might fail.
(The member who's first in rank
will go first.)
He's spraying water on it
to make it more intense.
(The muscle relaxation massage
for the members who ran all morning)
- Is it strong?
- No, it's not so strong.
- On my bare skin?
- My gosh.
- Of course.
- It'll kick in easily.
It'll kick in easily
if you put it on there.
When Se Chan calls a number,
one of you should plug it in.
- Okay.
- Numbers from 1 to 30?
Yes.
Will he pass if he endures it?
No. Even if you try to endure it,
we'll know.
- Really?
- Will it be turned off right away?
She should unplug it.
Please unplug it right away, okay?
Promise me. Based on what I heard,
it should be unplugged right away.
Look at her face.
I don't think
she'll unplug it right away.
This isn't the first time, you know.
Please call a number.
(Which number will he choose?)
- Number 12.
- Okay.
- You picked one in the middle.
- Yes.
- You should consider the location.
- I wonder if it's a fake.
- That's right.
- Could it be fake?
You'll get 30 points
if it doesn't work.
If not, you'll get eliminated.
It's advantageous to go first
considering the probability.
(Only 6 out of 30 outlets work.)
You never know.
He might get eliminated.
(There's a 20 percent chance
of getting a massage.)
(What could be the result of
the first choice?)
(Groaning)
Unplug it now. Pull it out.
(The low-frequency therapy machine
is turned on.)
Unplug it.
Does it really hurt?
(The unlucky guy got eliminated
despite the 20 percent chance.)
Are you not faking it?
- Was it intense?
- You should unplug it immediately.
(She hasn't unplugged it yet.)
Was it that strong?
(The baby octopus flails
after the low-frequency massage.)
- Jae Suk, it's true.
- No way.
- You'll see what I mean.
- Okay.
- Se Chan is out. Next.
- Gosh.
- Number 12...
- Since you gained weight,
you look funnier
when you react like that.
- Jae Suk, it's no joke.
- Hey.
- There are five real outlets left.
- Correct.
- Number 12 was a real outlet.
- All right. Here.
The members who try earlier
than the others are at an advantage.
So I won't choose a small number.
I'll go with number 21.
You know how Jae Suk always...
- He always picks a bad one.
- He could smell it.
Yes, he always picks a bad one.
He never picks a good one.
- Number 12 was real, right?
- Here we go. All right.
So Min, just plug it in now.
One, two, three.
(Will he get unlucky as usual
and get a massage?)
One, two, three.
Plug it now.
See?
- It's a fake.
- Number three.
(Number 21 is a fake.)
You survived and got 30 points.
- Thirty points?
- Yes.
- Which one should I choose?
- Next.
- Good.
- Is number 21 fake?
- Number 12 was real, right?
- Yes.
- Jong Kook, come here.
- Then shall I go with number 11?
(He figures two consecutive numbers
are unlikely real outlets.)
I thought that too.
I was going to pick number 13.
- Number 20?
- I'll go with number 11.
- Number 11.
- Number 11? Okay.
- Here we go.
- I thought the same thing.
(Could Detective Kim's guess
be right?)
There.
- It's a fake.
- Pass.
- Okay.
- You got 30 points.
- Who's next?
- Me.
(Number 11 turned out to be fake.
Jong Kook got 30 points.)
(Next up is Ji Hyo.)
What's the first number
that pops into your mind?
- Number 2.
- Number 2? Okay.
- Ji Hyo, are you ready?
- But I think that number two is...
(Ji Hyo chose a small number.)
(What could be the result?)
- Pass.
- Okay.
Really?
- Okay. Good.
- Then I...
- So Min.
- Am I doing it the right way?
- I'll help you.
- I'm so nervous. What do I do?
- Number 10.
- Okay. Number 10.
Should I go with number 1?
Or number 10?
- Number 1 or 10?
- Which number?
- I'll go with number ten.
- Okay. Turn around.
Okay.
(Real)
(Screaming)
It was the wrong outlet.
(The prank addict plugged it
into the real outlet.)
- I plugged it into the wrong one.
- It says "Real."
- It was a mistake.
- He got back at her.
- I made a mistake.
(Jae Suk avenged her betrayal.)
- I got confused.
- Hey!
I'm sorry.
We shouldn't leave it to him.
That felt so weird.
- Don't make a mistake again.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry!
- You shouldn't do that.
I won't make a mistake again.
- I see why you made a mistake.
- I'm sorry.
- Right. It's close to number ten.
- They're close to each other.
- It felt like...
- I'm sorry!
- ten frogs jumping in my arm.
- I won't make a mistake again.
I felt like I had ten frogs
jumping in my arm.
- Number 10.
- Number 10. Okay.
- It's understandable.
- Face the front.
- Face the front. Come on.
- Turn around.
- You'll do it again, right?
- No, I won't.
- No way. He won't do it again.
- Pass.
- I'm relieved.
- Ten frogs were jumping in my arm.
- I see.
- It's like buzzing.
- I mean... That's right.
Next up is Haha.
- He'll go with number 16.
- Number 16?
- No. Wait. I didn't choose it.
- Number 16.
I said, I didn't choose that number!
Thank you.
- He didn't choose the number.
- You didn't plug it?
- He didn't pick it.
- Number 16.
- Let's do it again.
- He passed since he tried it.
- Really?
- That's a relief.
- Seok Sam, you're up.
- I hope he'll pick a real one.
(Next up is Seok Sam.)
Stop smirking like that.
It's weaker when the guys do it.
(Screaming)
(The low-frequency therapy machine
is turned on.)
Why? Was he wearing it?
(The veteran MC keeps
making the same mistake.)
- Darn you.
- I didn't know you were wearing it.
Gosh. Why you little...
- This machine is unbelievable.
I really didn't know.
I'll go with number 29.
- Number 29?
- Number 29.
It looks lonely.
- Let's go.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
- It's a fake.
- Pass.
- Nice.
- We have to pick wisely.
- It's very intense.
- It's time for someone to fail.
- But no one has yet.
- Oh, you are...
- You're calculating?
- Yes.
- Back to number one. Please sit.
- I'm anxious.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Is it my turn?
- There are five real ones left.
Does anyone want to plug it in?
I'll do it.
- He needs something to do.
- Okay. I understand.
- Okay. Yes.
- This is it, right?
Wait.
You shouldn't adjust the intensity.
- You shouldn't...
- I didn't.
- Right. He didn't adjust it.
- I left it in an intense mode.
Please go and check it.
- Okay.
- I wasn't lying, right?
- Oh, no. It would hurt.
- Really?
He increased the intensity
when it was set to a weak mode.
You shouldn't have changed it.
You could've died.
All right.
(Meanwhile, Seok Sam plugs it
into the real outlet.)
Now, choose a number.
(The revenge has begun.)
- I...
- What number do you want?
(What? Is he enduring it?)
- I'll go with number 22.
- Wait. Are you enduring it?
- What's going on?
- Come on. Mister.
- Why?
- Why did you pull this out?
- Gosh.
(Jae Suk unplugged it.)
Hey, why did you unplug it?
- You shouldn't do that.
- It doesn't work when unplugged.
- Why?
- You shouldn't unplug it.
I was going to plug it in
when I was ready...
- after choosing a number.
- Come on.
- What's wrong with that?
- Right. That was a good idea.
Right?
(Once again, he makes it obvious
that he's waiting for a chance.)
(Then he plugs it.)
Then...
- I pick...
- Mister.
- number 22.
- You reduced the intensity.
- Now...
- Unplug it.
- Gosh. Hey.
- That's how it feels.
(Groaning and laughing)
Hey, unplug it. Turn it off.
Pull it out!
It hurt.
It's intense, right?
My gosh.
- You looked like you were dancing.
- Gosh.
I want Jae Suk to fail.
I want him to fail too. What number?
I pick number five.
- Number 5?
Number 5. I'm sure of it.
- Number 5.
- Here we go.
(Someone must fail by now.)
(How will it turn out this time?)
Will he fail?
(Screaming in pain)
Did it kick in?
(It kicked in!)
- Did it kick in?
- Turn it off.
(The second member to fail
got caught while acting up.)
I'm next, right? Okay.
I'll go with number three.
I pick number three.
- Number three?
- Yes. I'm ready.
Okay. Good.
I already picked number 3
when Jae Suk picked number 5.
That's incredible.
- Next.
- Ji Hyo, you're up.
She calculated the probability.
- I'm sure she'll pass.
- Really?
- She calculated the probability?
- She analyzed the numbers...
that turned out to be real.
- She did?
- Yes, she's done analyzing.
- Really?
- Yes.
- The one who wrote "Tottenham?"
- She wrote "Tottenham."
Yes, the one who wrote "Tottenham"
did it.
- She wrote "nyangjungjichuk."
- She wrote "Tottenham."
- I didn't know...
- She wrote "nyangjungjichuk" too.
- A cat's punch.
- She wrote "nyangjungjichuk."
- Yes, she did.
- I can't...
- I knew it was a wrong answer.
- She wrote "nyangjungjichuk."
- I wrote "nyang" intentionally.
- It was funny.
The ugly, the old,
and the one who wrote "Tottenham."
(The ugly, the old,
and the one who wrote "Tottenham.")
- Like a movie title.
- Right.
She explained it to me.
She's done analyzing.
- Good.
- What number did you choose?
(Real: Numbers 5, 12, Fake:
Numbers 2, 3, 10, 11, 16, 21, 29)
Hey, Tottenham, which one?
I will...
go with number four.
- Number four.
- Ms. Tottenham.
"You'll survive
if you risk your life."
("Probability is the science."
by Songttenham)
(What could be the result of
her analysis of all possible cases?)
- "You'll die if you try to live."
- Number seven hasn't been picked.
(Groaning)
(She failed to
calculate the probability.)
- She has finished calculating it.
- Unplug it.
(She picked a real outlet
after a thorough calculation.)
- She has finished calculating it.
- Unplug it.
- What's the point of calculating?
- It was pointless.
- Tottenham didn't let us down.
- Nyangjungjichuk.
- She says it hurts.
- It hurts.
- Nyangjungjichuk.
I knew that Tottenham would fail.
- It hurts.
- She's out.
- Oh, no. Tottenham.
- It hurts.
- It's my turn.
- There are three real ones left.
I'll go with number 18.
(Suk Jin picked number 18.)
(Screaming)
(Number 18 was a real outlet.)
- How many are there left?
- I'll go with number 19.
- Number 19?
- Number 19.
(Groaning)
- It hurts, right?
- She's out.
See? I told you so.
Haha and Jong Kook are
the two finalists.
I can't believe
I survived this long.
We have 3 outlets left.
Numbers from 23 to 25.
- I pick number 25. Let's go.
- You have no choice.
I'll go with number 25. Let's go.
It was no joke.
(If Jong Kook fails,
Haha wins automatically.)
Oh, it kicked in. Gosh.
(Jong Kook is out.)
- All right. Haha is the winner.
- Yes.
As a result,
Se Chan got zero points
in this mission.
Jae Suk and Ji Hyo won 30 points.
Suk Jin won 90 points.
So Min won 120 points.
- Jong Kook got 180 points.
- Oh, my.
And Haha got 210 points.
- I should've won 210 points.
- Haha, I'm impressed.
Mendorong ttottot!
Jeju dialect, yes!
Now, we'll move to the back...
- for the last mission.
- Let's go!
- What is this?
- What is it?
Oh, my. It's moving.
I guess it's to make us fall off.
Right?
(Shouting)
- What is this?
- It's a conveyor belt.
What is this for?
I'll explain the rules of
your last mission.
This is
a very interesting formation.
(This is
a very interesting formation.)
Come down. You might fall off
while acting up like last time.
- Gosh, seriously.
- What's with that face?
- Let's leave him be.
- I've hurt...
I've gotten a cut on my eyebrow
while acting up like this.
Of course.
- "I'm sorry!"
- I'm sorry.
First,
I'll announce your current scores.
- Am I still in 1st place?
- The person in 1st place is...
Jae Suk with 540 points.
- Great!
- I'm impressed.
And Se Chan placed 2nd
with 350 points.
- I lost points.
- Okay.
- Haha placed 3rd with 270 points.
- I should've done better.
- Okay.
- I'm not even in third place.
Jong Kook placed 4th
with 110 points.
- What?
- What? Am I...
- That's unexpected.
- Am I ranked that low?
So Min placed 5th with 90 points.
- Gosh. I'm in fifth place.
- It's because you lost points.
Suk Jin placed 6th with 70 points.
Ji Hyo is in last place
with 60 points.
The winner will probably be
1 of the top 3, right?
- You can say that.
- Can I turn the game around?
- That's possible.
- Of course.
"Can I?"
- "Can I?"
- Why did you drop the honorifics?
- "Can I turn the game around?"
- "Hey, young man."
- "Yes, you can."
- It came out wrong.
- I meant to use honorifics.
- It's possible.
All right.
- To give you a chance to win,
- Yes.
we'll let the bottom two
choose their team members.
- You mean, us?
- I see.
- So Min is on our team.
- Okay.
- This is a perfect combination.
- Right. It's neat.
- Indeed.
- Don't you want one more member?
- The last mission is...
- What is it?
a Running Man style game.
It requires physical strength
and wit. It's Marathon Quiz.
The conveyor belt is moving.
I think we'll have to run on it.
The representative member has to
run in this direction...
on the moving conveyor belt
and look back at the others...
to see what they describe
while running.
(The representative member has to
guess a keyword while running.)
- We'll win this.
- I see. Just like...
- Speak With Your Actions?
- We'll definitely win.
I like the game.
- The other members have to...
- While running?
describe a proverb
with your actions.
- I see.
- With actions?
The member has to look back
while running.
You have three minutes
in each round.
- Three minutes?
- Both teams can pass keywords.
You just have to run
for three minutes.
Yes, but you'll start at Level One,
and the speed will
increase gradually.
If you fall off, the round ends.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Two members of each team will
take turns.
- We'll have four rounds in total.
- Okay.
- Two of us will take turns?
- Correct.
Then the two of you should run.
No. We'll choose the member to run
randomly.
(The representative member will be
randomly chosen.)
- Really?
- Yes.
- The four names are on them.
- Okay.
They all like chatting.
- The member to run, right?
- Correct.
- We should do it with actions only.
- So Min.
- It's Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- I'm relieved.
- Gosh.
- Jae Suk, please put on the gear.
- Okay.
- And...
- We're not allowed to speak.
So Min, this is "To move to Gangnam
following a friend."
- "A friend."
- "Following."
- "To move to Gangnam."
- Okay.
- This is for the word "friend."
Now... You have three minutes.
- Three minutes.
- You've got this.
- Now...
- So Min, is that it?
I'll describe the last word.
Everyone, we'll begin now.
Turn on the conveyor belt.
(The game begins.)
- That's easy.
- What does it say?
(To swim on the ground)
Hey, this is not easy.
(It's too fast!)
It's too fast.
(The treadmill is
moving quite fast.)
- I can't see you.
- Captain!
Hey, I can't see you.
- Come here.
- Jae Suk, look at us.
It's really fast.
Jae Suk, look at us.
- Is it okay?
- Look at us.
What is it?
Hey, don't just run
and try to guess the proverb.
- What is it?
- One at a time.
To swim on the ground.
- Okay.
- Correct.
Hurry up.
(They barely managed to
get the first question right.)
You have to look at us.
I can't see you. Move to this side.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
(To hit a rock with an egg)
To hit a rock with an egg.
- Good.
- Okay.
To hit a rock with an egg.
(One minute has passed,
and the speed goes up.)
What is it?
- He moved on to the next level.
- Yes.
It's so fast.
Why is it so fast?
- Jae Suk, look at us.
- Jae Suk.
(To spit in a lying position)
To eat rice cakes
in a lying position.
- No.
You're not allowed to make a noise.
What is it?
Hey, you should look back at them
while running.
Jae Suk.
- To spit in a lying position.
- Correct.
You have one minute left.
It's getting even faster.
(As two minutes have passed,
the speed goes up to another level.)
Look at us.
- How should we describe it?
- Jae Suk.
(Old habits die hard.)
- That's good.
- What is it?
- Jae Suk, look at us.
- Look!
One, two, three. Look!
- What?
- Look!
- I don't know. Pass.
- Pass.
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk, are you exercising?
He's just running.
He won't try to get questions right.
I can't look back.
Jae Suk, look at us!
- I can't look back at you!
- Is he here to exercise or what?
- Are you here to run?
- I can't look back!
(He looks like he's at a gym.)
Jae Suk, look at us!
Let's get
just one more question right!
Let's get this one right! It's easy!
- Jae Suk!
- I can't look back!
- Time's up!
- Gosh.
- We got a lot though.
- Yes, we got a lot.
Jae Suk can't look behind him.
- It's too fast.
- You answered four correctly.
- If I don't get selected...
- I should be the one to run.
- We'll pick out the next runner.
Unless it's Jong Kook, we're doomed.
- The runner is Suk Jin.
- We're doomed.
- Don't you lie.
- It's true.
(They're doomed.)
- Don't lie.
- Be honest, will you?
- Choose again while we watch.
- They...
They'll never answer four correctly.
Suk Jin will never get four right.
We'll stay close to the edge.
- Okay.
- Only that way you'll see us.
(Team Suk Jin gets in position.)
- All right.
- You have three minutes.
- Start.
- Here we go.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin!
(A dog's life is a good life.)
- Suk Jin.
- A dog.
- That's right.
- Suk Jin, keep looking.
- A nap?
- Look at him run.
- A dog's full.
No.
- Look.
- Being a dog...
A dog and seven?
Of course not.
That isn't the number.
- A dog.
- Here.
- You can't talk.
- A dog.
He will never get this.
Seven? A dog and seven.
- Don't give him numbers.
- Pass!
Forget about the number.
- Don't do that.
- He'll never get it.
(It is darker under the lamp.)
- Suk Jin.
What?
(Huffing)
It sped up.
- This is an easy one.
- This one's easy.
Someone must be after Suk Jin.
- Someone's after him.
- This is an easy one.
- This one's easy.
- This is a bad moment for him.
- Keep running!
- You're being followed.
- Suk Jin, it's an easy one.
- He's being followed.
You're being followed.
- This is an easy one.
- Suk Jin.
- Look.
(He runs as if he is being chased
by the Grim Reaper.)
(But then...)
- Oh, no.
- Don't give up.
(But his legs start to give in.)
(He is at the front gate
of the afterlife.)
- Don't give up.
- It's an easy one.
(His eyes are already giving in.)
This is too easy.
- Suk Jin.
- Don't give up.
- All right.
- It's over for our dad.
Somebody get him an oxygen tank!
(His colleagues encourage him,
but he's close to passing out.)
- He's being chased.
- Don't give up.
Suk Jin, this is an easy one.
- Suk Jin.
- Don't give up.
- Do it.
- It's over.
- Suk Jin!
- Keep going!
- I...
- Stop.
(Grunt)
Suk Jin.
(He gives up in the end.)
Game over!
(They end the race
with zero points.)
"A dog's life is a good life."
- Suk Jin was being chased.
- He was being chased.
It was as if someone was after him.
Suk Jin. Get him oxygen.
Get him an oxygen tank!
- Get him some oxygen.
- Are you all right?
- Get yourself an oxygen tank.
- Are you okay?
- I...
- Are you all right?
Jae Suk's insane.
I have to give it to Suk Jin.
That was impressive.
- His will to live...
- He was being chased by something.
Suk Jin wanted to live.
- Compare the height of acorns!
- Yes!
Enemies...
- find us during the worst times.
- Okay!
(Team Ji Hyo stacks points
by following a stable plan.)
- Small chilies are spicier.
- Okay!
Haha.
We need 6 to tie and 7 to win.
- Let's aim for seven.
- Sure.
- That's cool.
- Nicely put, Haha.
All right.
- I'm impressed Haha.
- Go!
- Let's do this.
- Nicely said, Haha!
"While it's warm."
(You...)
- "Welcome."
- Looking good, Haha.
- Nicely put.
- I'm sorry.
He apologized.
(He apologizes for being dumb.)
- He'll be teased for three weeks.
- I know.
I'm really sorry.
- I found it charming.
- You can't give them a reason.
Okay.
The result of this game...
could shake up the ranking
in every possible way.
We'll win for sure.
- Let's do this.
- He won't get any of them right.
Check out Haha's pants.
- And go.
- Look at Jong Kook first.
- This one's easy.
- It's an easy one.
Look at him run.
He's really bad at it.
(An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth)
- Be witty.
- No, look at me.
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth.
(Eating mustard in tears)
- Go ahead.
- Here.
(Eating mustard in tears)
Eating mustard in tears.
- Yes.
- Next.
- Over here.
- Haha.
(A frog in a well)
- A frog in a well.
- Yes!
- That is correct.
- Here we go!
- A frog in a well.
- Yes!
- That's...
- Here we go!
Over here!
(Lobsters side with crabs.)
(They're getting nervous.)
- It's an easy one.
- I know what it is.
Here.
Crabs...
(That's it!)
Haha's legs are giving in.
Crabs...
- Haha's legs are giving in.
- Over here.
- Haha!
- Haha's legs are giving in.
- Over here. Haha!
He can't look behind him anymore.
- Just this once.
- Haha.
Look behind you.
- Look behind you.
- Come this way.
(Running at full speed)
This is an easy one.
(It's been a while since
Running Man lived up to its name.)
- This is easy.
- It's an easy one.
- Look at him run.
- Haha!
- He doesn't want to fall.
- Look behind you.
- It's an easy one.
- It's over.
- Think!
- He can't look behind him.
- What would this be?
- Think!
- He can't look behind him.
- A crab.
Right. And this?
"While it's warm."
- What can this be?
- Keep running!
He can't turn his head.
"Welcome."
Looking good, Haha.
- Go!
- Keep running for now.
- Hold on.
- He can't look behind him.
He can't turn his head.
- But this is an easy one.
- He's almost done for.
- Haha.
- Look at this.
- He's almost done for.
- Five...
- Haha.
- Haha!
- Look at us.
- Three, two, one.
This is an easy one.
- Haha.
- Over here.
- Look at us.
- Hey.
Think.
This isn't about who can run better.
He's out of energy.
(He gives up on the marathon.)
- Haha did so well though.
- I know how tough it is.
- You ran really well.
- I know.
That was hilarious.
It was "lobsters side with crabs."
You answered four correctly,
but Team Ji Hyo
is the ultimate winner.
- Okay!
- Yes!
- What was the answer?
- Haha.
It was "lobsters side with crabs."
And "frog in a well."
Okay. Let's party.
- I didn't come in last.
- Okay.
Thanks to So Min...
- So Min.
- You're an angel.
(Every member on Team Ji Hyo
received 200 points.)
You brought us fortune!
You should've been the one to run.
All right.
Here's the final result.
Those in 1st and 2nd place
will win the prize...
while those in 6th and 7th
will receive the penalty.
In first place is...
(The race took part
in Sangam-dong itself.)
(Who will win the cut-throat
Running Tag of Tails Race?)
In first place...
with 740 points is Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk finished in 1st place.)
(He's the first winner
of the Running Tag of Tails Race.)
- What's the prize?
- Jae Suk...
has won your favorite prize.
The Korean beef gift pack.
- Yes!
- I knew it.
- No way.
- And in second place...
- with 550 points is Se Chan.
- Yes!
Your prize is watermelons...
that is not only sweet
but expensive.
They will be delicious.
(He wins sweet watermelons.)
- All right!
- Why are they so lucky?
And those who will receive
the penalty are...
(Who will receive the penalty?)
You are to link...
seven people on the street
and create a long train.
Unbelievable.
(Receiving the penalty
are Suk Jin and...)
If only we had won the final game.
All right.
Suk Jin.
(He locates his target.)
Ma'am, excuse me.
Could I maybe lend a hand?
You can stand behind me and...
(She walks right past him.)
Maybe we can...
(His lack of confidence
led to a failed attempt.)
I should search for people outside.
Excuse me.
Are you perhaps free?
(Chuckling)
If you're free...
Darn, this is embarrassing.
(His 2nd attempt
was also a failure.)
Hello, sir.
Do you...
- have some time to spare?
- Sure.
Can you walk around the block
grabbing onto my back?
- Is it possible?
- Sure.
(He manages to find his first tail.)
I got someone to help me.
- All right.
- Where are we going though?
I'm not so sure myself.
If you are not too busy,
can you join the train?
- Me?
- Yes, get behind him.
Luck will find those
who chose to help out today.
Sir, could you join the train?
I apologize for the inconvenience,
but we'll all have
a bright future ahead of us.
- Good luck.
- Let me see.
Two, four...
I'm sorry about this.
I know it's embarrassing,
but consider this as gaining karma.
Excuse me!
(It's as if the citizens
are being punished.)
I need two more people.
I'm sorry it's taking me so long.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. Just please stay with me
a while longer.
I'm sorry, but can you join us?
I need two people.
Please.
(He successfully recruited people
to be the last tail.)
Are you done?
I love you.
Why is he saying "I love you?"
I love you all.
Suk Jin made it.
(Suk Jin made it.)
Thank you. You'll be blessed.
Thank you.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
I need about six people
to become my tail.
If you're not busy...
Be my tail, guys.
- Do I need to walk a lap?
- Say choo-choo, puff-puff too.
Choo-choo, puff-puff?
- Choo-choo.
- Puff-puff.
(They have to say
a humiliating chant as well.)
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Let's take a photo to commemorate.
Okay.
(Yeoui Island in midsummer
where the hot sunlight is pouring)
Hello.
Well...
Why am I here?
This is Yeoui Island.
I'm at Yeouido Park.
What are we doing today?
Why am I here alone?
We're all starting
at different locations, right?
The weather is amazing.
(Staggering)
Did you film it?
- Hi.
- Hello.
- What are we doing separately?
What's going on?
Today, the winner is decided
based on individual mission funds.
(Today, the winner is decided
based on individual mission funds.)
Before we start, we'll give you
a mission fund as you want.
(There's no limit.
They'll be given cash as they want.)
What's the maximum amount?
There's no limit.
Give me 1,000 dollars.
You won't give it to me.
You don't have 1,000 dollars.
We'll give you cash.
How much is that?
We have enough.
There's no limit to what I can say?
Will you give me as much as I want?
- We'll give you what you wrote.
- Okay.
But if you wrote the most or
the least amount, you won't get it.
Gosh, this is...
If the person who wrote the most
or the least amount can't get it...
(The person who wrote the most
or the least amount gets nothing.)
You should think
about what others would've written.
How much is the maximum amount?
- There's no limit?
- Right. There's no limit.
Gosh, so I can't be too stingy
nor too extravagant, right?
- You should be moderate.
- Moderate.
Our members are not moderate.
There are about 3 or 4 people
who go all in.
So I should just avoid the most
and the least amount?
How about 1,000 dollars?
Is it too much?
I was going to say 10,000 dollars.
But it won't do.
The cicadas are crying so loudly
all of a sudden.
Ji Hyo, someone might write
10,000 dollars.
(Se Chan starts raising the bet.)
Ji Hyo,
it's the gangster special today.
I'll buy a yacht
with the money today.
Okay. Then I'll go all in too.
How much did you write?
I saw a lot of green
in the envelope.
Yes, there's a lot.
(He's testing the water first.)
You know those uneducated guys
including Se Chan.
Yes. There are uneducated guys.
They will lose their mind
if they see it.
(Haha avoids answering
by changing the topic.)
I wrote just the right amount
by my standard.
How much did you write?
I should write
at least 1,000 dollars.
- You say that, but you won't do it.
- Hey.
Suk Jin, we should write
between 50 dollars and 100 dollars.
- Really?
- To avoid the most and the least.
Think mathematically.
Base multiplied by height divided by two.
Do you not know it?
What's that? It's so random.
It's Pythagorean theorem.
(Pythagorean proved
all sorts of theorems.)
You ignorant punk.
(Laughing)
You're the master of mind games.
You should be bold
when it comes to this.
(Did he write a bold number
as he said with confidence?)
This is just enough. Some guys
could write a few dollars.
Dollars.
Okay.
It's enough.
Which one should I choose?
Make a guess, ding-dong-dang
I wrote 375 dollars.
(Ji Hyo wants 375 dollars.)
Someone must've written
a number bigger than 100.
Those reckless guys
won't stay still.
I'll go with 100 dollars.
(They all submitted
the amount they want.)
- All members wrote the amount. Yes.
- They did?
Ji Hyo,
you didn't write the most
nor the least amount.
We'll give you cash as you wrote
as the basic mission fund.
This is awesome.
I got it right.
Yes.
You didn't write the most
nor the least amount.
- Thank you.
- As your mission fund...
Who wrote the least amount then?
Did someone write a number
smaller than 100?
(It means someone wrote more than
375 or less than 100.)
This is incredible.
(Everyone was given
their mission fund.)
(Two of them are penniless.)
All right. Three special guests
will call you as your captains.
- And? Okay.
- You can call them if you know.
Who is our captain today?
You should tell me.
- I think we're the main.
- Hello.
- Why is there no one?
The captains don't have
mission funds.
The captains will negotiate to
receive the fund and pick members.
(The captains will negotiate to
receive the fund and pick members.)
With this money?
No way. That's nonsense.
It was so hard to get it.
Each team will have three people
including the captain.
The one who wasn't chosen
will make their own one-member team.
A one-member team is nice.
- But to carry out the mission...
- Is it a disadvantage? It's bad.
When they call me, I should make
a deal by offering what I can give.
Will Sae Ho appear? No, right?
He isn't coming, is he? Be honest.
It's not Sae Ho, right?
Don't do that.
- Hello.
(Near Yeoui Island at that time)
- Why is there no one?
- Hello.
(Super special guests appeared
walking slowly.)
(Lee Yi Kyung, Ha Do Kwon,
Joo Woo Jae)
(Familiar guys showed up awkwardly.)
- What? Why is there no one?
- What's going on?
- You don't see any members, do you?
- No.
You'll become the captain
of each team today.
(The 3 guests will become
the captain of each team.)
You need members in your team
for the race.
Recruit two Running Man members
you want...
to form a three-member team.
- The remaining member plays alone.
- Okay.
Today, the more mission fund you have,
the more advantageous it is.
The members received
the basic mission fund.
Out of seven members, the ones
who wrote the most amount...
- and the least amount got none.
- All right.
But they will lie, saying
"I have this amount of money."
"And I will give you this much."
And those who received money
will negotiate with you.
"I received this much and I'll give
you this much. Let's work together."
So you must pick up
two trustworthy members...
to come to the opening place.
- We should pick them up?
- Yes.
- You'll compete with one another.
- Okay.
Let's go then.
How can we get there?
(He immediately
sets off by himself.)
It's meaningless.
- Why would you run when it's hot?
- I know.
It's meaningless.
Have you heard something
about today's guests?
Isn't Woo Jae coming today?
There will be Long Legs.
(Jong Kook also knows
that Long Legs is coming.)
The one from Anyang will come.
(On the other hand, Se Chan
knows nothing about the guests.)
- Se Chan.
- So Min, who are today's guests?
I don't know either.
So Min, you should text
your boyfriend quickly.
- And ask who the guests are.
- My boyfriend?
- It's one of the staff members, no?
- I don't have a boyfriend.
All the staff members are married.
I don't have a boyfriend.
I don't have one.
I heard they're special guests.
It could be Sae Ho or Chang Hee.
I actually said it.
"If it's Sae Ho, I'll just go home."
Do you see a drone?
Just tell me about it.
Is there a drone over there?
No, there isn't.
I see one.
- Really?
- Yes.
(She bragged about a drone
and quickly hung up.)
It's coming.
(She's enjoying a drone solo shot
by herself.)
(Come here.)
It's fascinating.
I feel like it's looking at me.
Follow me.
(So Min is excited
to have a pet drone.)
It's fascinating.
I think it's looking at me.
It's looking at me.
Go.
(Moving)
It's coming.
(Frog loves everything
that pays attention to her.)
It's fascinating.
It looks like a big mosquito.
It sounds like a big mosquito.
(Captain Do Kwon looks serious.)
(Analyzing painstakingly)
(Do Kwon thought about it
for a long time.)
Hello.
We should actually cooperate later.
- I don't want anything.
- Okay.
I just want to see Jong Kook's fall.
- Jong Kook's fall? Okay.
- Yes.
I'll help you win.
Can you make my dream come true?
So do you want me not to accept
Jong Kook's offer?
Pick him up, act like you'll accept him,
then ditch him at the end.
- Just like that?
- Just ditch him with no mercy.
- Hello, Yi Kyung.
- Yes, this is Yi Kyung.
Let's pretend to recruit him
then ditch him.
That's right.
He needs to get hurt too.
(Codename: Jong Kook's Fall,
which is Do Kwon's dream)
Sure. Let's all ditch him
and make him play alone.
- Yes, let's do that.
- Yes.
(Jong Kook is waiting for a call,
not knowing anything about it.)
I don't think Do Kwon would pick me.
I bet he'll try to sabotage me.
(Will Jong Kook be on his own
just as Do Kwon planned?)
How come no one is calling me?
(Meanwhile, So Min is waiting
for the team leaders to call her.)
- Hey, So Min.
- Jong Kook.
Do you know who today's guests are?
The sly one.
And we have a uselessly tall one.
You mean Woo Jae?
(Woo Jae?)
- Woo Jae is joining us today?
- Yes.
- Gosh, what about the other one?
- Why?
I know just the two of them.
I don't know who the last one is.
I think it's Yi Kyung.
He's calling me.
It must be Yi Kyung.
He rarely calls me.
Yi Kyung is calling you?
- It must be Yi Kyung.
- Yi Kyung is our guest for today?
Yes, he keeps calling me.
I'll call you back
after talking to him.
All right.
So the last one was Yi Kyung.
Wait a minute.
And he's not calling me?
Why these little punks...
(Team Leader Lee is contemplating
after excluding Jong Kook...)
(just as they planned.)
I'll try calling Suk Jin.
He's not on my list anyway.
- Hey, Yi Kyung!
- Sorry! I pressed the wrong number!
Yi Kyung...
(Hanging up)
Hey, Yi Kyung!
So Yi Kyung is joining us today.
(The first call from a team leader
ended as soon as it started.)
(Persevering Suk Jin
is calling him again.)
He's calling me back.
- Suk Jin! What's up?
- Yi Kyung.
Yi Kyung, you should join me.
I prepared lots of money for you.
You need money right now, don't you?
I can give you 60 dollars.
- You can give me 60 dollars?
- I can give you 60 dollars.
How much do you have that you're
willing to give me 60 dollars?
I have 80 dollars,
but I'm giving you 60 dollars.
If you won't come to me,
I'll join someone else.
Everyone wants me on their team
right now.
Is that so?
Then you should join them.
What?
- Hey.
- Yes?
I'll give you 80 dollars.
(I'll give you 80 dollars.)
(Seok Sam is suddenly
offering every penny he has.)
How much do you have that you're
willing to give me 80 dollars?
I'm giving all the money I have.
I don't need any.
But you said everyone wanted you.
- They do.
- Yes?
But they're asking for more.
All right, then. Stay right there.
- Okay.
- All right, Suk Jin.
Does he take me as a fool?
(The call ended without any gains.)
Jae Suk is calling. Hey, Jae Suk.
Suk Jin.
I heard you hit the jackpot.
I heard that you did.
I didn't hit the jackpot.
Hold on. Someone's calling me.
Hang up for now.
Hey!
(The shortest phone call)
- Hey, Yi Kyung.
- Hey, Jae Suk!
Where are you, Yi Kyung?
So how much should I pay you
for you to come to me?
I'll tell you honestly.
- Please be honest.
- I'll be completely honest.
I have exactly 300 dollars.
- You have 300 dollars?
- Yes.
How much are you willing to give me?
I'll give you 100 dollars.
(Laughing)
(Yi Kyung only laughs
without giving him an answer.)
- Okay?
- Just one-third?
Fine. I'll give you 150 dollars.
Let's settle with 150 dollars.
Okay. I won't ask for more.
I'll take 180 dollars.
- All right. Make that 150.
- No. Make that 180.
Hey, you just cursed at me,
didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Why don't you hand me 180 dollars?
You must know this.
There are members
with no money at all.
You'll be in trouble
if you join hands with them.
All right.
Are you under Wonhyo Bridge?
- Yes.
- I'll be there.
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
I must have Jae Suk on my team.
(Meanwhile, Woo Jae
is calling Se Chan.)
- Hey, Se Chan.
- My gosh, Mr. Joo.
Why is it so hard to reach everyone?
Because of the money
we got from the mission...
Why is it so hard to reach you?
- I heard about today's mission.
- Yes, sir.
And this is the only time
I can act arrogant.
(It looks like he decided
to enjoy this moment.)
That's true.
I have the right
to have the members...
- get in the car.
- That's right.
You're right. You can make
a few people suffer.
- Mr. Joo.
- So...
Don't use honorifics.
Okay, fine.
- Be real with me.
- Sure.
I don't want to abuse my power
just because I'm a team leader.
Sure. A vertical relationship
sounds great.
It's a horizontal relationship,
not the vertical one.
Isn't it called
vertical relationship?
(Chuckling)
(Getting a headache)
How much did you ask for? Be honest.
What do you mean?
I only have four dollars.
Everyone else asked
for about a few dollars.
They did that so they wouldn't
be in the last place.
Woo Jae, hurry over.
You just called, right?
- Just come already. I'm hot.
- Where are you?
Under Seogang Bridge.
Can you take a photo of the bridge
and send it to me?
My gosh. You're driving me crazy.
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't like the way you talk.
(I don't like the way you talk.)
That's because...
You must understand me.
How much did you ask for?
Gosh, I asked for 300 dollars.
Then I'll just take 200 dollars.
How can you take 200 dollars
when I have 300 dollars only?
You must consider the fact...
that you might end up with no one.
Woo Jae.
If you want to be on a team...
(If you want to be on a team...)
- Woo Jae.
- You should at least take me.
You...
Who taught you the basics
of variety shows?
The members of Running Man.
Can you send me a photo
of Wonhyo Bridge?
My gosh, this is...
Oh, my. Big Baby.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
Do Kwon, where are you?
I'm on my way to meet you.
Where are you?
Do Kwon, who are you considering...
as your teammates?
I'm thinking
of having you and Haha...
on my team.
- Haha?
- Yes.
How about me and Jong Kook?
(How about me and Jong Kook?)
What do you think
of including Jong Kook?
(Ji Hyo suggests including Jong Kook
whom Do Kwon was going to exclude.)
You and Jong Kook?
- What do you think of Jong Kook?
- I'd love to have him.
Then you should...
have Jong Kook on board first.
I'll be joining you for sure.
You know me.
- Of course.
- You know I'm the loyal type.
- But I...
- I'll choose you for sure.
I'll choose you too.
How much will you give me?
I have plenty of money.
- You do?
- Yes, I do.
Gosh. Then how much do you have
and how much are you giving me?
Come on, Do Kwon.
I'll give you half of it.
Half of it?
(Ji Hyo with 375 dollars
joins Do Kwon on her own.)
- Thank you so much.
- It's no problem at all.
Hurry up and come to me
with Jong Kook.
All right.
(He promised Ji Hyo to meet her
with Jong Kook.)
Let's get going.
I'm going to pick Jong Kook up.
Please go to the back gate
of the KBS building.
(He sets off to pick up Jong Kook,
his target.)
(His plan of isolating Jong Kook
is going smoothly.)
Hey, Frog.
- Jae Suk!
- What?
Do you know today's guests?
Of course I do.
Can you tell me?
I know only two of them.
- Must I share this with you?
- Yes.
- It's Lee Yi Kyung.
- Okay.
Joo Woo Jae and Cho Sae Ho.
(Lee Yi Kyung, Joo Woo Jae,
and Cho Sae Ho?)
(Lying about the guest lineup)
It's Sae Ho?
(Giggling)
I'm going home.
Why?
Sae Ho doesn't have feelings
for you either.
Tell him to stop coming
to our show, seriously.
Why does he keep joining our show?
Why not?
Does he lobby
our producers or something?
What are you talking about?
Sae Ho is also very busy,
but he fixes his schedule...
to join us when we ask him.
Do you know Woo Jae's number?
I do.
Can you tell me?
Why?
Just because...
(Just because...)
Okay. Hold on. I'll tell you.
- Okay.
- All right.
I sent it to you.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
She thinks...
(Chuckling)
I gave her Sae Ho's number
instead of Woo Jae's.
(I gave her Sae Ho's number
instead of Woo Jae's.)
(Lying about Woo Jae's number)
I changed the name to Joo Woo Jae.
(He finds it hilarious.)
(A perfect crime where
he even changed the saved name)
My gosh.
What? This is Sae Ho's number!
(Sae Ho's number was passed
to her in disguise.)
Jae Suk is so mean.
I don't want to talk with him.
He doesn't even want me.
Why must I call him first?
It's...
(Calling Team Leader Cho
who doesn't even want her)
Jae Suk gave me Sae Ho's number
when I asked for Woo Jae's.
- So...
- Sae Ho, I'll give you 30 dollars.
- What?
- I'll give you 30 dollars.
- Thirty dollars?
- Yes.
Why would you give me 30 dollars?
I'll give you 30 dollars.
- You're giving me 30 dollars?
- Yes.
Why?
(Why are you giving me 30 dollars?)
Well, that's how we team up
for today.
- Today?
- Yes.
- Why are you...
- What team?
Why are you acting
like you're not today's guest?
- What are you talking about?
- You're our guest for today.
A guest for which show? Running Man?
Yes. You're not our guest?
- Out of nowhere?
- You're not our guest?
No, I'm not.
No, you are today's guest.
Don't you lie to me.
Then let's do a video call.
(She even video calls him.)
You are our guest for the day.
No, I'm not!
Yes, you are!
No, I'm not. I'm at home.
Let me see. Turn the camera.
What? You're really home.
What? You're not our guest
for today?
- No, I'm not.
- But...
But he said you're our guest.
- Jae Suk did?
- Yes.
But I'm not the guest.
I'm sorry. Oh, gosh.
I'm sorry for this.
It's all right. So Min.
Isn't the Han River beautiful?
Yes, it is,
but you're even more beautiful.
(Yi Kyung has arrived somewhere.)
Goodness.
- Hey, Yi Kyung!
- Jae Suk.
- Gosh, Yi Kyung.
Look at this.
- Gosh.
- Would you like to listen?
(It was Se Chan
who was calling Yi Kyung.)
His caller ringtone is so old.
He's supposed to be a VIP guest.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Goodness. Yi Kyung.
What brings you to call me?
Your caller ringtone is so nice.
It's so refreshing.
Se Chan, let me ask you directly.
How much will you give him?
I'll give you half of what I have.
- All right.
- How much is that?
I have 10 dollars. I'll give you 5.
Jae Suk! Where did he go?
(Se Chan was rejected right away
for offering a small sum.)
- Jae Suk.
- Gosh. Hey, So Min.
- What is it?
It wasn't him!
What did you say?
Sae Ho isn't today's guest!
I even video called him!
(Sae Ho isn't today's guest!
I even video called him!)
(The victim of Jae Suk's lie)
Seriously. You're so naughty.
(The victim of the fake guest case)
Jae Suk.
I called him and went, "30 dollars."
He was like,
"What are you talking about?"
Give me Woo Jae's number.
- Woo Jae?
- Yes.
Why do you keep singling out
Woo Jae?
- That's because he is...
- All right. I will send it to you.
someone I can recruit
with the smallest amount of money.
All right.
(He finally sends her
Woo Jae's number.)
Okay.
I will offer 100 dollars to Woo Jae.
Please take a photo of me.
(Suddenly apologetic)
(After sending the photo,
she tries calling Woo Jae.)
The number you have dialed
is not available.
Come on, Woo Jae!
(Captain Joo stays on the phone
for a long time.)
Woo Jae!
- Hey.
- Hello.
Do you know...
how long it took you to call me?
I am disappointed
that you called me so late.
The number you have dialed...
I guess Woo Jae
is calling everyone...
and figuring out
who he wants on his team.
I should offer a lot of money.
I should be honest.
I will call Yi Kyung.
- Captain Lee.
- Hello.
- Yes?
- I raised the price a bit.
- Okay.
I can give you 120 dollars.
I see that you lied to me.
Yes. That's how things are
on Running Man.
Be honest with me.
How much can you give me?
I have 120 dollars.
I will give you all 120 dollars.
We don't have much time left.
- You will give me 120 dollars?
- Yes.
Raise the price a bit more.
Call me after you are done thinking.
(Captain Lee isn't easy.)
This is my final offer!
Raise the price a bit more.
Call me after you are done thinking.
I have a lot of people lined up.
Isn't 120 dollars enough?
- Did you say 120 dollars?
- Yes.
Give me a bit more.
I will give you 150 dollars.
- I will give you 150 dollars.
- You know,
- money keeps coming out.
- Yes.
I wonder how it keeps coming out.
I need some money for myself.
Then be honest and tell me
how much you have.
Do Kwon is on his way here.
- Really?
- He is on his way here.
I bet 300 dollars on Do Kwon.
You should go to him then.
(Levelheaded)
Why did you call me then?
I was wondering
if you would like to come.
- Suk Jin, join my team...
- He is too far.
for 290 dollars.
Did you say 290 dollars? Okay.
- Join my team for 290 dollars.
- Okay.
We have a deal. Okay.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay. 290 dollars. We are coming.
- Okay. Hurry up.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Someone came.
Who is inside?
(Suk Jin is meeting someone
for the first time today.)
- Suk Jin.
- What?
- Hey.
- Suk Jin.
What?
- Let's go.
Give me 290 dollars.
- I am supposed to do it later.
- Really?
I am supposed to do it later.
Isn't that right?
- Is it true?
- It's true.
- I see.
- I have the money right here.
Hey.
- Okay.
- It looks like...
you are calling so many people.
You shouldn't be that way.
Woo Jae, you punk.
You didn't give me a single call.
I met up with Suk Jin.
He is extremely angry...
because you didn't give him
a single call.
Yi Kyung, it's good to see you.
Your shoulders became even broader.
Look at your arms.
- I am always the same.
- You live diligently.
- Get in the van.
- Gosh, I teamed up with Yi Kyung.
- Suk Jin.
- How much did you agree to give?
Forty dollars.
- What did you say?
- Forty dollars.
For goodness' sake.
You agreed to give him 40 dollars.
Will they be the members?
- Have you decided?
- No.
- Not yet.
- What?
No.
- No?
- Don't be like that.
- I will get off.
- Not yet.
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
- Let's get off.
- This won't do. Let's get off.
- Stay in the van.
- Hey.
I will get off.
Hold on. I will call Woo Jae.
I can't believe you.
- Stay in the van.
- Decide if you want us as members.
- Otherwise, we will leave.
- That's right.
We aren't so easy.
- We aren't so easy.
Do Kwon offered a spot
for 190 dollars.
You should make a decision.
- He keeps texting Do Kwon.
- What are you doing?
- He keeps texting him.
- Suk Jin.
Hurry up and tell us.
Should we get off or not?
- He offered a spot for 190 dollars.
- That's right.
That's 100 dollars less
than what we agreed on.
If you make a decision,
I will stay in the car.
- Woo Jae.
- Take the 2 of us for 330 dollars.
- Make up your mind.
- They will be my teammates.
- Okay.
There you go.
(After some deliberation,
he makes up his mind.)
Sir, please pull over for a second.
We agreed on 40 dollars, right?
- The total is 340 dollars.
- Give me 50 dollars.
- I will give you 50 dollars.
- Okay.
So the prices are
50 dollars and 290 dollars.
Why is it so different for me? Hey.
- I am satisfied with this team.
- Of course.
- You got the ace members.
- You know...
How could you say that?
You got the ace members.
- How...
- I got fathers.
(Not ace members, but fathers)
- Yi Kyung.
- Yes?
I really am an ace member.
You know that, right?
I am incredible
at races and other things.
- I am good at everything.
- Really?
- That's right. But...
- That's right. Hey.
I am plus and Suk Jin is minus.
So together, we are zero.
- It's zero-sum.
- Yes.
That's not true.
Quizzes are my specialty.
As for Suk Jin,
I can see him grow weaker each year.
(I can see him grow weaker
each year.)
- Each year.
- You feel it too.
- Of course I do.
It's not like we need to wear
a team uniform.
Why are the two of you wearing
a vest?
Did you wear a vest to be the best?
(Laughing)
- Is that it?
- We have a connection.
I really missed you, Suk Jin.
I missed you too.
Jong Kook and I had a fight
in the morning.
- We had a fight.
- I see.
I called him "Muscle Man."
- Muscle Man.
He doesn't suit your style.
Jong Kook doesn't suit your style.
- That's the thing with Jong Kook.
- You should give him a hard time.
Jong Kook terrorizes
the members of the soccer club.
- You play soccer with him.
- You are a member.
- I quit because of Jong Kook.
- I see.
I became mentally drained
whenever I play soccer with him.
(He hated it.)
- "Yi Kyung, don't play like that."
- Seriously.
- He is bad at it too.
- His soccer skills are the worst.
- Why is he so critical?
- He thinks...
- he is a world-class soccer player.
- That's insane.
He is a bit better than me.
Is he here?
(Jong Kook meets up with someone.)
Hold on. Let me make a call.
Come on. I am going to leave.
- Hello.
- I am hanging up.
See? I hung up right away.
I said, "I am hanging up."
- Let me check one last time.
- Okay.
- How much do you have?
- Hey.
- Is money that important?
- No, it isn't.
- But I need to know the amount.
- I will give you 40 percent.
- And how much is that?
- It's 20 dollars.
(It's 20 dollars.)
Why are you laughing?
Is that amount laughable?
- Get in the van then.
- Really?
Would you be okay with 20 dollars?
- You will get Ji Hyo, right?
- Yes.
That's a bit burdensome.
- Okay. I will get in the van.
- Get in the van.
I am touched that you accepted me
for 20 dollars.
(Do Kwon's dream
from the beginning of the shoot)
(Jong Kook's fall)
(Act like you'll accept him,
then ditch him at the end.)
(It's Do Kwon's plan
to make him the remaining member.)
- As far as I know, Ji Hyo is rich.
- Are you certain?
- I don't know the exact amount.
- I don't know about her.
- She is strange these days.
- She didn't give me the amount.
You should ask her
to give you the exact amount.
Whose van is that?
Isn't that Jong Kook's van?
(She spots Jong Kook's van
and runs over.)
Jong Kook.
- Ji Hyo.
- There she is. What is she doing?
- She doesn't know that we are here.
- For now...
(Ji Hyo's appearance
makes them flustered.)
Hey, why is she coming?
- She is coming.
- Lock the door.
Did you lock the door?
(The door opens.)
(Averting his eyes)
What are you doing?
- Why didn't you come to me?
- Ji Hyo.
- Do Kwon, you...
- I was just about to call you.
- Now...
- I was about to press the button.
You weren't going
to let me into the van, right?
You can't hop in yet.
You have to make a deal first.
- I will make a deal.
- Let's talk here.
How much do you have?
Should I say it
in front of Jong Kook?
It's okay. We are a team.
We aren't a team...
- just yet.
- I will talk to her outside.
- You shouldn't get off.
- I will be back.
- Fine. Go ahead.
- I can't talk in front of you.
- Ji Hyo.
- I will give you 100 dollars.
You told me
to let Jong Kook in the van,
although I didn't want to.
I will give you 100 dollars.
I promise.
I made a promise.
I will give you that money.
- Get in the van.
- All right.
(Ji Hyo becomes a member
for 100 dollars.)
- Get in the van.
- All right.
- Did you strike a deal?
- Jong Kook.
Why didn't you answer the phone?
What are you saying?
I will move to the back.
No. I will move to the back.
It's okay.
- I...
- Did you strike a deal?
- Yes.
- Really?
Why did the two of you try
to keep me out of the van?
When did I do that?
- I am disappointed.
- I did no such thing.
- Why did you try to keep me out?
When does it end?
It's okay to make a selection now.
Hold on.
Why is Se Chan calling me?
- Se Chan called me too.
- Really?
- I think...
- He must be anxious.
he became the remaining member.
Yi Kyung called me too.
(He begins to have a meal
in a carefree manner.)
Do Kwon is loyal.
You know that I am loyal too, right?
Of course I do.
There is another one.
There it is.
This one is tasty.
Cranberry and chicken.
- It's great.
- The team members are relaxed.
As a captain, I have many worries
and internal struggles.
I have so many internal struggles.
Do Kwon, relax.
I was so busy worrying
that I didn't eat anything.
(Eating)
(Staring)
I am eating this much
even though I had breakfast.
Now that I am seeing your face...
- and seeing you eat well...
- Right?
- Yes. It's nice.
- You know,
I got everything I wanted
from this van.
I got sandwiches. I got to eat.
Do Kwon, will you finalize
the team members now?
(Eating)
- Me?
- No. Do Kwon.
- Why...
- Do Kwon.
(What will be his decision?)
Yes.
(Team Do Kwon has been decided.)
Do Kwon is great.
- Why did you scare us like that?
- He had to finalize his decision.
- That's right.
- Do Kwon.
You can relax.
You are on Running Man.
- It's okay.
- The weather is hot,
so you should eat at a cool place.
You shouldn't eat sloppily outside
since you are a celebrity.
What is he going to do?
He doesn't know...
that he will get backstabbed.
(He worries about another
without knowing his own fate.)
(He is the only captain
with 0 team members.)
Whose number is this?
Hello?
Is it you, So Min?
Woo Jae!
I will give you 50 dollars.
"I will give you 50 dollars?"
I don't have much money,
so 50 dollars is a lot.
Please know my sincerity.
I have 200 dollars.
I will give you 50...
No, I will give you 100 dollars.
- You will give me 100 dollars?
- I will do anything.
Shall people who were born in 1986
team up today?
Of course!
Hey. Roar!
I promised you the highest amount.
- So Min.
- I might give you more.
I will call you
right after I do something.
Make sure you call me.
I am under Wonhyo Bridge.
Okay.
(Someone comes to Haha.)
(The person inside the van is...)
All right.
(Woo Jae?)
Who were you talking to
on the phone?
If you tell me honestly
how much money you have,
I will go to you
with pure intentions.
- I will be honest since it's you.
- Okay.
It's under 700 dollars.
- Under 700 dollars?
- Yes.
(Intrigued)
- Woo Jae.
- Really?
Just come here.
- I am hot.
- Where are you?
I am under Seogang Bridge.
Haha.
Come over here.
What?
Get off the van for a second.
- What?
- I prepared a party for you.
- Who is it?
- Let's go to the shade.
Hey.
- My goodness.
- Come here.
It's good to see you.
- See?
- I was on my way.
Come on. We should be a team.
I was on my way to you.
But I had to meet Haha first.
- Haha. Okay.
- Okay.
I can't see you much
even though you are on the show.
You haven't gotten a sense
of the situation, have you?
We should be a team.
This is the best combination.
Don't pick So Min. She has no money.
So Min isn't the only one.
Jae Suk has no money either.
Jae Suk has no money.
- If you recruit us, you will win.
- You will win.
- We will help you win.
- Do you know why?
I have the most amount of money.
How much will you give him?
Yi Kyung offered me a spot
for ten dollars.
He is on his way here.
Since it's you,
I will give you 20 dollars.
- Do you know what he said to me?
- What did he say?
I asked him to tell me honestly
how much money he has...
and he said, "Under 700 dollars."
Nonsense. That's nonsense.
- Seriously.
- I have under 600 dollars.
I have under 500 dollars.
Is that how it's going to be?
- Do you know what he said?
- I have no money.
He told me that he has four dollars.
One said 700 dollars
and the other said 4 dollars.
Who am I supposed to listen to?
I have no money.
- But...
- Four dollars is a lie.
Who am I supposed to listen to?
What's the standard?
He is a liar.
That was just wrong.
You need to apologize.
- I will apologize.
- Apologize.
I will apologize. I will pay you
the same amount as Haha.
Let's hurry up and go.
You could get messed up.
You could get two members
with zero dollars.
Let's go to the van.
Make a decision.
We have people coming here.
We are busy.
- I am confused about the amount.
- You will have 40 dollars.
- He mentioned the highest amount...
- This is driving me crazy.
How much do you have?
Don't you think
"under 700 dollars" was too much?
It was too much. Don't you think
"four dollars" was too much?
I can't believe
you offered him a dollar.
It's no wonder
he doesn't believe me.
- I don't have much money.
- Let's get in his van.
Haha, I don't have much money.
Woo Jae, what are you going to do?
Woo Jae, are you leaving?
- So Min.
- I will give you 200 dollars.
- Woo Jae.
- So Min.
(I will give you 200 dollars.)
I will give you 200 dollars.
Did you see the photo I sent you?
You will give me 200 dollars?
(So Min offers 200 dollars.)
It makes no sense.
My feelings are so hurt.
I will give you 200 dollars.
I will give you a bit more
on top of it.
Do you have 200 dollars?
Yes. I will give you 200 dollars.
Okay.
- Really? Please let me join.
- Give me 200 dollars.
Which member did you recruit?
I don't have anyone yet.
The spots are empty.
Stay there, So Min.
Branch One, Yeoui Island, Han River.
- That's nonsense.
- Hey.
- She doesn't have that money.
- I swear she doesn't have it.
- Seriously.
- So...
how much will you give me?
- You know...
- I am in a bad mood now.
I supported you
from the very beginning, right?
You should be compensated then.
What should he do?
Woo Jae.
(Woo Jae grimaces.)
Your facial expression was so funny.
- The two of us have money.
- We have money.
Please go to
Branch One, Yeoui Island, Han River.
(He moves to So Min's location.)
Woo Jae!
(Running at full speed)
Joo Woo Jae!
Hello.
- Come here.
- I will work hard.
- Why is your face so puffy today?
- It's good to see you.
- I will give you 200 dollars.
- How much do you have?
- For real...
- You know,
it's hard to believe your words.
I have to give you money
for real, so I can't lie.
I will give you 200 dollars
for real.
If you have zero dollars,
you can lie.
I have money.
- Listen.
- No one else will give you so much.
- Of course not.
- And Haha...
You are offering much money
than the others.
I must have a lot of money then.
I will give you 200 dollars.
I have to team up with you.
Otherwise, I will be alone.
So Min has no choice but to beg.
That's right.
She needs to get in the van.
- What's going on?
- Hello.
Did you pick the members?
No, not yet.
So Min, get in the van.
All right.
How much will you give me?
Say it openly.
I will give you 200 dollars.
Nonsense.
Trust me this once.
How much will you give me?
- What I offered earlier.
- Same here.
- Seriously, I...
- Her offer makes no sense.
So Min, your offer makes no sense.
- You chose the wrong amount.
- It makes no sense.
- It's too much.
- I am not joking. It's true.
(During the money distribution)
Your amount wasn't
the highest or the lowest,
so you will receive 470 dollars.
(So Min acquired 470 dollars.)
Whose amount was the highest?
- Is it a secret?
- It's a secret.
(She meant it
when she offered 200 dollars!)
What will I do
if everyone has more money than me?
Trust me this once.
I will give you 200 dollars.
Had you offered 50 or 60 dollars,
I would have believed you.
- It's true. Trust me this once.
- I think 200 dollars is too much.
But it's true.
Hurry up, Woo Jae.
Will you choose me
as your teammate or not?
- Answer that.
- I am not joking. It's true.
I will make a realistic decision.
It's true, Woo Jae.
Then...
- Just say it.
- Relax and say it.
- We are professionals.
- I am leaving then.
Know that I offered 200 dollars.
I am leaving.
- Hey.
- Hold on, So Min.
- I wasn't joking about the amount.
- She is sullen.
- I offered 200 dollars.
- Don't be sullen.
- I am confident.
- His decision isn't final.
I am confident.
Make up your mind however you want.
(Slamming)
- She is sullen.
- Why is she sullen?
- Why is she sullen? My goodness.
- Let's go.
- I will go with them.
- Okay.
Should we give him the money now
or at the location?
- At the location.
- Okay.
It's so stupid
that he doesn't believe me.
He doesn't believe me.
I have so much money.
Seriously. I will be alone today.
Let's go.
Did no one else come?
Are we the only ones?
(It's time for the four teams
to gather around.)
It's cool in here.
The waiting room was hot.
- Hello.
- There you are, So Min.
You came alone.
I am alone today.
- Hello.
- Have you been well?
- You are alone.
- So Min, you...
I am alone today.
So Min is sullen. That's scary.
Watch how I behave today.
Did people arrive already?
- Okay.
- Do Kwon.
All right.
- So Min, you are alone.
- Are you guys a team?
This happened because someone
who looks like a lizard rolled in.
Hello.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Hey, Woo Jae.
- Hey.
- Hey, Woo Jae. Come here.
- I have a lot of money.
You never give me a call.
- I don't have your number.
- I gave you his number.
- Seriously, you...
- He gave me the number,
so I called it, and it was his dad.
Why did you do such a thing?
You're unbelievable. Hey, you...
It was just ridiculous.
Why did you do that?
- He's funny.
- That doesn't make sense.
My dad is retired,
so he's bored now.
- My goodness.
- You should call him.
- He's such a lunatic.
- He's crazy.
Why did you send him
your dad's number?
Hey, Yi Kyung. You... Listen.
He's a member of my soccer team,
- but he rarely comes.
- Right.
- Because I'm busy.
- He doesn't come.
- I'm busy.
- How dare you... Hang on.
- That's because of you.
- Listen to me.
He rarely comes. And our team
recently got a new uniform.
He wants the uniform number seven.
- Is he out of his mind?
- Even I couldn't ask for that.
- I just want the number.
- I mean...
- What's wrong with that?
- Number seven...
- I understand why you're upset.
- I know.
- That sounds upsetting.
- By the way,
aren't you Jong Kook's enemy?
Actually, I had plans.
- Do Kwon.
- He said he'd betray you.
Actually, I was
going to kick him out.
But as soon as he got in,
like a giant baby, he kept eating.
He ate sandwiches
and kept spilling things.
- I kept sighing, so...
- That's because...
he said, "You can kick me out
if you want." But he kept on eating.
I got my money's worth in the car.
By eating.
- I had enough.
- He kept eating.
All right.
I will announce the amounts.
You should tell us.
First, I will announce the amounts
offered to the captains.
- The money for the captains.
- Yes.
This team...
- Is he going to be rich?
- He got a lot.
- Haha offered 25 dollars.
- It's 25 dollars.
And Se Chan also offered 25 dollars.
- We offered 25 dollars each.
- It's 50 dollars.
- Hey, you said three dollars.
- Hey.
- You offered me three dollars.
- You should've called me.
I deceived you.
Team Ha Do Kwon.
Jong Kook offered 20 dollars,
and Ji Hyo offered 100 dollars.
- She offered 100 dollars?
- So it's 120 dollars in total.
(Do Kwon is offered 120 dollars.)
How much is he getting?
How much did you guys offer?
Jae Suk offered 50 dollars.
- It's 50 dollars.
- He offered 50 dollars.
And Suk Jin offered 290 dollars.
- He offered 290 dollars.
- What?
(50 dollars from Yoo Jae Suk,
290 dollars from Ji Suk Jin)
So he's offered
340 dollars in total.
And So Min is a one-member team.
I'll announce
the amount So Min owns.
- How much is it?
- Zero dollars?
The money So Min got is...
The money she owns now.
(So Min's mission fund is...)
It's 470 dollars.
(470 dollars)
(Shaky eyes)
You should've
offered more money then.
She has a lot of money.
- She's rich.
- She has 470 dollars?
- I offered 200 dollars.
- So she lost the money.
- No.
- No, she got the money.
She received the money.
She didn't lose the money.
I said I'd give you 200 dollars.
(I'm doomed.)
So Min, you have the guts.
And I will announce the amount
Ha Do Kwon will receive.
He will receive 120 dollars.
(He will receive the amount
he was offered.)
(Ha Do Kwon gets 120 dollars.)
That's perfect.
- I see.
- Look at him.
And Lee Yi Kyung was
offered 340 dollars.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- And he will receive...
- How much is it?
(And he will receive...)
zero dollars.
- What?
- Zero dollars.
(Suk Jin and Jae Suk
got 0 dollars.)
(Yi Kyung's team members,
Suk Jin and Jae Suk are broke.)
This is great.
My goodness.
I want 732 dollars.
(Suk Jin wrote 732 dollars.)
(He bid the highest amount.)
What? Yes.
You wrote the highest amount.
So you get zero dollars
for your mission fund.
I thought I'd get the money.
This is a moderate amount.
Okay.
All right. Jae Suk.
You wrote the lowest amount.
So you get zero dollars.
(You too?)
(Me too!)
This is great.
- That was so close.
- This is amazing.
Hey, you should be happy.
- This is how things go here.
- It's all right.
- This is Running Man.
- Right. Don't cry.
Gosh, they got me.
I got fooled.
You took him in.
She has the most money.
I offered you 150 dollars.
I picked the members
with the highest and lowest amounts.
(How much can they
give up for money?)
(Ma'am.)
(Step 1, power)
(Step 2)
(Pride)
- My gosh.
- Okay.
(Step 3)
(Dignity)
(Or...)
Hey.
(Something more...)
(If you want money,)
(don't miss out on a chance.)
(Growl)
- No mercy.
- Do Kwon.
(The three captains who are here
to upset the established order.)
(You should pick Jae Suk.)
(And the hunters never go easy
even on their team members.)
(In individual games...)
(And group games...)
What are you doing?
(Who will be the winner
in this madhouse?)
(Race of Groups Part 2)