(May 16, Gyeonggi-do Paju-si)
- What is this place?
- It's so quiet.
It's pretty here.
Is this English Village?
- Hello.
Why are we here?
(Three guests appear with So Min.)
(Kim Ji Young, Hong Ye Ji,
Hwang Seog Jeong, Jeon So Min)
(The four heroines of the movie
"2037" premiering on June 8.)
(Hong Ye Ji)
(Hwang Seog Jeong, Kim Ji Young)
(First time "Running Man" promotes
So Min's work)
- It's so quiet.
- I think it's okay to...
Is this English Village?
Yes, I think so.
English?
It's quiet because
they want us to speak English.
(English Village becomes quiet
as only Korean speakers are here.)
Because we must speak English.
That's why it's quiet.
I was here when
"Produce 48" was taken here.
It's a music program.
You're so bright Ye Ji.
Ye Ji you look so fragile.
Everyone is in a pastel tone
except me.
- I've been here...
- Everyone is pastel.
Because it's spring.
- I look dark.
- They did a good job here.
A good job.
- Only me.
- English...
English Village...
They have waiting rooms here.
- Do we have to go in?
- The waiting rooms.
Do we wait?
Do we go in?
- Ye Ji.
- One in each room?
Oh my, we have to go in.
- Really? Now?
- Everyone is inside.
See you soon. Hello.
Hello.
- Hello.
- What is this?
What is this?
We all came up together but
putting us in each room is scary.
Is someone coming in?
(The guests spend the waiting time
in their own way.)
(After about 20 minutes...)
Please gather outside.
(The staff asks them to gather.)
Do I go out?
(She takes some candy.)
What is this?
(What?)
(The youngest producer is out.)
What is this?
(Seog Jeong looks confused.)
Why is he here?
Excuse me...
(An unexpected acting battle against
the professional Seog Jeong)
- They told me to do nothing.
- Now they want us out.
They told me to stay put,
so I ate some snacks.
I also drank some soda.
Could it be poisoned?
It's not, right?
- I hear something weird.
- What is this?
Why is he smiling?
- Oh, my.
- What's this?
Seog Jeong is... Gosh.
(Surprised)
- What's this?
- What a surprise.
- I don't know...
- Seog Jeong...
You didn't beat him down, right?
Of course not. Why would I?
Police! Do not touch him.
(The police are here.)
- Gosh, what is this?
- What...
Is this the crime scene?
- It seems so.
- Excuse me?
But who are these people?
What were you doing
at the crime scene?
- We just came.
- We were just chilling.
But I...
Seog Jeong was here.
No, what are you doing?
The four of you are under arrest
as suspects.
- Take them!
- Yes, sir.
What are they doing?
But I clearly saw Seog Jeong...
But he was smiling at me.
I saw Seog Jeong here...
Was he lying there from the start?
Yes, he was just there.
What kind of situation is this?
Take them.
Hey, I know you're alive!
- Jong Seo!
- Take her!
Jong Seo!
(Thirty minutes after
the producer's death)
They told us to wear
our own clothes.
Today? I didn't hear that.
You wore what your stylist gave you.
- Did you really say that?
- There must have been a mistake.
Really? But I...
They told us to wear
our own clothes.
I just...
I see.
It might be a bit cold.
- No worries, I'm healthy.
- You sure?
Your arm has goosebumps.
Short sleeves are a bit cold but...
It's summer.
Why is the weather like this?
- It's not summer.
- You should wear...
like this normally. You look good.
I normally do dress like this.
You look good.
I like this kind of fashion.
Your glasses don't have lens though.
(No lens attack against
his fashion comment)
Hey...
- Don't do that.
- Why?
Why bother wear them with no lens?
Doesn't your wife say anything
about your glasses?
She says I look better without them.
- I see.
- Because she...
likes me so much.
- Who? Your wife?
- Yes.
You know nothing of her.
"Because she likes me so much."
My foot.
She's my number one supporter.
What do you feel about your wife?
I'm her number one supporter.
- Why do you suddenly go on...
- No.
- about your love for her on TV?
- I never lie on a TV show.
- I never lie...
- Suk Jin.
Watch some of the old episodes of
"Radio Star" and "Happy Together",
and see what you said
about your wife back then.
I didn't feel this way back then.
- It was different back then.
- But why...
- Relationships can change...
- Why is that?
as time goes by, right?
Lately, we're very happy
with each other.
- Do you know why?
- Why?
Since you've aged,
- Yes?
- you don't have enough energy now.
- You punk.
- You don't...
- You're wrong. I'm full of energy.
- I'm serious.
- You've reached the age.
- Got it?
- You punk.
- You know what I mean, right?
Men suddenly become obedient...
- to their wives...
- That's not true.
and say,
"You're the only one for me..."
between their mid-50s
and their early 60s.
- It's not that I'm obedient to her.
- He's reached that age.
- It applies to him.
- I realized that she'd been right.
- Exactly. You should've been...
- I didn't know before...
- nice to her before.
- that she was right.
- Now,
- That's how I feel now.
arrest Ji Suk Jin.
- What? Why?
- Arrest Ji Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin,
- I knew it.
you just lied to the viewers,
- pretending to be a romanticist.
- That's right.
- Yes, he's a fraud.
- I didn't lie.
- That's why you asked him about it.
- You're arrested for fraud.
- Great. But is this real?
- Why should I be arrested?
- Why can't you see my sincerity?
- You deserve this.
- This is not right!
- He deserves to be arrested.
- Seriously. Hey, how could you...
- He's been acting...
- like he's a romanticist on TV.
- Arrest him too.
Now, arrest Yoo Jae Suk.
- Why?
- Of course, you should be arrested.
Jae Suk,
you hurt your fellow entertainer's
feelings with brutal honesty.
(He's being arrested for hurting
his fellow entertainer's feelings.)
- You've been caught red-handed.
- That's ridiculous.
- You're arrested for assault.
- Wait. I was...
- He got seriously injured.
- Who?
Suk Jin.
Is stating the facts a crime?
- Brutal honesty is a crime.
- I mean...
Gosh, I'm speechless.
This is just ridiculous.
Hello. It's good to see you again.
You're dressed fashionably
as always.
Thank you for saying that.
I picked these clothes randomly.
I didn't pay so much attention to
my clothes today.
Aren't you wearing the same clothes
as Young Jin?
(Aren't you wearing the same clothes
as Young Jin?)
No, I'm not.
I'm wearing different shoes,
and everything else is different.
Why?
Hey, what's going on? Ouch. Hold on.
It hurts. Wait.
- You copied your stylist's style.
- No!
You're arrested for...
- infringement of fashion style.
- These are my clothes!
These are all mine!
- Can you make a menacing face...
- Yes.
- and show off your leg muscles?
- Come on.
Why are you making me do that?
I don't want to...
This is my angry face.
(Menacing)
- Jong Kook, your menacing look...
- Yes?
intimidates people around you,
and you have
an unnecessarily muscular body.
- Yes?
- You're arrested for disquieting.
What's going on?
What are you talking about?
Why are you arresting me?
We need you to write down
your personal information.
Be honest.
(She's writing down her information
as she was told.)
- All right. Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
You wrote "Song Ji Hyo" instead of
your real name, Cheon Soo Yeon.
You're arrested for
false entry of your name.
Have you lost your mind? Why... Hey.
Hey, I asked you about it, didn't I?
You didn't even answer me.
Then why are you...
(Screaming)
- What do you want?
- You're arrested.
Se Chan, you showed too much
of your light skin on your belly,
which disgusted other people. You're
arrested for disorderly conduct.
I was changing my clothes.
That's all.
Mister, what are you doing? Mister.
Take him away.
You should at least let me
put on my shirt.
Mister.
- Gosh, seriously.
- What's going on?
- Why can't you see my sincerity?
- No!
Let me just
put on my shirt properly.
You punk.
- Hey, why is this my number?
- You idiot.
- What does this mean?
- Hey.
Inmate 5623.
- Inmate 6666.
- It's 6666.
- It's an evil number.
- That's right.
- This number is upsetting.
- That reminds me of "The Omen."
- The movie "The Omen."
- Mine is 9487.
- "The Omen."
- Yours is 1234.
- He was born in 1966.
- "The Omen."
- Oh, right. What does this mean?
- What's yours?
- It's 0957.
- Mine is 0957.
- Were you born in 1934?
- What does 09 mean?
By the way, why isn't So Min here?
- Someone's coming. She's not here.
- What is So Min doing?
- She's here.
- What is going on?
- Please be quiet.
- Kim Ji Young is coming too.
- Why is So Min with them?
- Hwang Seog Jeong is here too.
- Seog Jeong.
- It's been a while.
- Welcome.
- He must be a detective.
- Hello.
- It's been a long time.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- What is that?
- Please come here.
- Hey!
- Greet us politely.
- Button up, you brat.
- Button up your shirt, you punk.
- Greet us.
Wait. So Min.
Hey, what are you doing?
- So Min.
- What's wrong with you?
(The problematic inmate is
walking toward Jong Kook angrily.)
- What's wrong with you?
- What are you doing? Why?
- Stop it.
- What's her problem?
- Why would you do that?
- So Min.
- How was the Grand Mint Festival?
- Great.
I really enjoyed it.
You got arrested
the day after the festival.
I was wrongfully arrested.
- I've done nothing wrong either.
- I know.
Suk Jin,
your inmate number is 6666.
- It's an evil number, you know.
- It reminds me of "The Omen."
He was born in 1966.
- My gosh. Why...
- He was born in 1966.
- It's the year of his birth.
- Is that true?
- He was born in 1966.
- Yes.
- Goodness gracious.
- Please be nice to him.
- He's the oldest entertainer.
- Why are you so surprised?
- Were you really born in 1966?
- Yes, he was.
- Please be nice to him.
- He'll turn 60 soon.
- Seog Jeong, how old are you?
- He's quite old.
- By the way, Jae Suk.
- Yes?
You look younger than you did...
- Me?
- the last time I saw you.
- What's with the romantic tension?
- What's going on?
(What's with
the romantic atmosphere?)
- Why is it romantic suddenly?
- Hold on a second.
- We don't want that.
- Why are you acting like this?
- I was just...
- We don't want romance.
- I was...
- He's married.
- We don't want any romance here.
- He's a married man.
- I was just surprised. That's all!
But he's a married man.
- You shouldn't flirt with him.
- Well...
- She's just like us.
- I won't see that.
- I like you, Seog Jeong.
- Why romance?
- I'm against it.
- He's a married man.
- I was taken aback too.
- Of course.
- That was unexpected.
- Why did you step forward?
- She acted coy.
- With a romantic gaze.
To make sure he could hear me.
To make sure he could hear her?
Seog Jeong,
your hairstyle reminds me of...
- an old professional wrestler.
- She looks like a warrior.
- The Undertaker.
- The Undertaker?
(The Undertaker style)
- Exactly.
- I agree.
Seog Jeong, your hair reminds me of
The Undertaker.
I'm serious, Seog Jeong.
Ye Ji, didn't you...
- appear on "Produce 48?"
- Yes, I did.
- Oh, my. I'm glad to see you here.
- "Produce 48."
- I appeared on "Produce 48."
- She appeared on "Produce 48."
- Really?
- "Produce 101?"
- No, it's "Produce 48."
- "Produce 84."
- I mean, "Produce 48." I'm sorry.
- It's "Produce 48."
- She said "Produce 84."
- "Produce 84?"
- What was your final ranking?
- I didn't know that.
I was eliminated in the first round.
- Why would you ask that?
- What's wrong with you?
- Why did you ask such a question?
- It's okay.
- You see...
- Only the winners are remembered.
You've crossed the line.
- Did I say anything about it?
- Only the winners are remembered.
- By Suk Jin.
- Many of those who failed...
- in an audition stood out later.
- Absolutely.
- Many of them became successful.
- That's right.
- He was a race starter too.
- As far as I know,
the four of you
filmed a movie together.
Can you tell us about the movie,
Seog Jeong?
You'll know when you watch it.
- What is the movie about?
- Is it about prison?
- Sorry?
- What's it about?
What do you want to know?
(She chuckles after asking,
"What do you want to know?")
- Why do you keep doing that?
- What is...
- with you two?
- Don't make it look romantic.
- What are you doing?
- I told you not to do that.
- We don't want that.
- What's with you two?
- He's a married man.
- She's making physical touch.
- Why did you come forward?
- Stop it!
- Why did you come here?
- He's a married man.
- What's wrong with you?
- Don't touch him.
Silence!
- Stop doing that.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Stop it. He's married.
- What's her problem?
- What's wrong with you?
- Seog Jeong.
- Hey.
- Listen. I...
If you want to stand next to him...
- I have my own reason.
- Why...
- I do have my own reason.
- What is it?
- I feel like crying.
- Why?
I haven't met a man who looked at me
so warmly in a long time.
- She drives me nuts.
- What are you talking about?
- What is her problem, really?
- I'm not joking. I mean it.
- You look at me so warmly.
- Do I?
- It touched my heart.
- I didn't know that.
- He looks at us like that too.
- He always does it.
- No other men look at me that way.
- We don't?
- I must say, she's so charming.
- How do we...
- That's why...
- My gosh.
Don't try to create a romance
between you and her.
- Don't be jealous, Suk Jin.
- She's so charming.
- Why would you be jealous?
- He wants to make a love triangle.
Why would you create a romance
between you and her?
- Why would you play along with it?
- Why are you jealous?
- Both of you are married.
- Spit it out.
- What's wrong with you?
- I just said she was charming.
- Gosh. We were trying to end it.
- I meant, as an actress.
- Why would he do that?
Seog Jeong brought us gifts.
- What gifts?
- That's right.
- I own a farm now.
- I see.
- For the 1st time in my life,
- The 1st plant you grew?
I'm growing this tree
called White Spire.
- Is it something to eat?
- So...
- I...
- Does she want us to grow it?
I grew these...
in my plastic greenhouse.
- Is it to eat or to grow?
- Jae Suk.
- You might find her phone number.
- This is...
- Or a wiretap.
- Check if there's her number.
Thank you for this, Seog Jeong.
- It's a valuable gift.
- Thank you, Seog Jeong.
Now, please tell us what we'll do
with our guests.
You are imprisoned
for different crimes.
The six of you are here
for minor offenses.
- We committed serious crimes.
- The four of them...
They committed serious crimes.
are the ones...
who were involved in the elimination
of the assistant director...
- that happened earlier.
- What?
- We found him dead.
- He was eliminated?
- The four of them are suspects.
- I see.
We got the camera footage.
We'll let you watch it.
It sounds like a brutal crime.
- Did one of them eliminate him?
- Is the assistant director dead?
- Yes.
- The assistant director.
- That's it.
- Let's watch.
Let's see
how the culprit eliminated him.
(The 4 of them came up together.)
What?
That's us walking up the stairs.
- The four of them are together.
- Yes.
So Min is behind everyone else.
- Is this man the victim?
- He's the assistant director.
- He's Jong Seo.
- Right. He's Jong Seo.
- He was on the floor.
- It's Jong Seo.
- When did he follow us?
- I didn't know he followed us.
Some time passed.
- Did he fall down the stairs?
- His name tag is gone.
- Someone ripped off his name tag.
- My gosh. What does it mean?
(He flopped down in the perfect spot
while acting realistically.)
My gosh.
(He flopped down in the perfect spot
while acting realistically.)
- My gosh.
- He's good at acting.
He's good at it.
- Did 1 of the 4 of them do that?
- But there's no clue...
- Who is that?
- Seog Jeong found him first.
When I saw her,
she was already there,
checking on him alone.
- Of course. He was unconscious.
- I think...
- I couldn't leave him like that.
- An alibi?
- Okay. For now, So Min...
- Yes.
- Seog Jeong came down first.
- So Min...
Is So Min coming down next?
(And a while later...)
- They all came down together.
- They ran into her.
- There could be two culprits.
- True.
- Maybe three of them did it.
- Now...
- Okay. It's So Min.
- I think it's So Min for now.
- We checked the camera footage...
and saw where the four of them went.
- He was eliminated after that.
- That's right.
- Therefore, they got arrested.
- The others...
You have to find the culprit
among the suspects.
If you find the culprit...
through 2 sessions of trial
until 4 p.m.,
you will receive a reward.
You can use it to pay your bail
to be freed and receive a prize.
And the culprit will get a penalty.
If you fail to catch the culprit,
the culprit will win the race,
and receive all the prizes.
There will be two missions
before the trial in the afternoon.
If you complete them successfully,
you'll have more people...
to search everywhere in the prison
before the race.
If you do well,
there will be more people to search,
which will increase the probability
of catching the culprit.
But if you don't,
you'll have fewer people
and a lower probability.
(Could the inmates be able to
catch the culprit?)
My, the weather is so beautiful.
- This is so nice.
- Indeed.
This correctional center has
good facilities, right?
- Yes, it's so nice.
- Indeed.
Since the weather is nice,
we'll do outdoor activities.
Outdoor prison is...
And you will have
a special meal today.
- That's great.
- Really?
- That's so funny.
Is it product placement?
- The advertiser sent you some food.
- All right.
- I'm excited.
- That's great.
- Let's see what it is.
- I'm excited.
(The advertiser's kindness
even spread into the prison.)
- I'm excited.
- Look at this!
- What's that?
- Did they grill it?
- How did they grill it?
How did they do it?
- They grilled potatoes?
- I often eat this. I like it.
This is my favorite.
- It doesn't make you so fat either.
- Look at this.
It's really tasty.
This is a new flavor.
- I think it's a new flavor.
- Right.
- It's grilled, not deep-fried.
- Oh, my.
So it's lower in calories.
- Smell the scent of sweet potato.
- Try this one.
- It's so good.
- All family members can enjoy it.
- My, it's so tasty.
- And its price is reasonable.
- "Texas hot barbecue."
- Try this.
It tastes exceptionally good
as they used steamed sweet potatoes.
- It's even sweeter.
- Really?
I can smell steamed sweet potatoes.
- Yes, steamed sweet potatoes.
- I see.
- The scent spread in my mouth.
- Did it?
- It spread right away.
- Se Chan.
- The scent of sweet potato...
- Should we play the snack game?
- It's amazing.
Hey.
- She wants to play a game with me.
- Yes?
- Should we play the snack game?
- It's amazing.
Hey.
(She makes a move like a bulldozer.)
- Yes?
- Stop it, will you?
- Stop it.
- Gosh.
(She aimed at him
without a warning.)
- We don't want romance here.
- Put out the cigarette.
- My gosh. Seog Jeong...
- Seog Jeong, stop it.
- Put out the cigarette, Seog Jeong.
- It's just a game!
- Even so...
- Suk Jin...
Suk Jin wants to play the game.
Gosh, don't do that.
- Even so...
- Suk Jin...
(Love spreads in the prison
like wildfire.)
Everyone, I'll explain the rules
of the first reformation activity.
You'll play a word game...
- and a physical game.
- I see.
The results will determine...
the number of search team members.
- The search is important.
- Indeed.
- Or you won't get any hints.
- Exactly.
All ten of you will play the games
together as a group.
The culprit may play
the games poorly intentionally.
- Right.
- Of course.
In the 1st mission,
you'll play 1 of 2 games.
I'll give you a word,
- and you'll spell it backwards.
- Okay.
For example,
I give you the word "kindergarten."
- Net...
- Net,
- rag, rednik. Like this.
- Okay.
The other game is
Make a Three-syllable Word.
- If I say "de..."
- Desert lime.
The 1st person should say "nim",
and the 2nd one should say "pants."
- "Desert lime" works too, right?
- Yes.
I'll pick 1 of these 2 games
just as I want.
You have ten chances.
If all ten of you pull it off
in a row at least once,
five of you can search for hints.
But if you fail in all ten attempts,
- only two of you will search.
- Okay.
To get more hints,
you need to pull this off.
- I see.
- It'll be so difficult.
The person who doesn't seem to worry
about it...
- We can do it.
- is likely the culprit.
- I'm not good at playing games.
- Why are you looking at me?
- No reason.
Jong Kook never finds a culprit
using clues.
- He just suspects everyone.
- Yes.
He focuses on the suspects'
facial expressions and behaviors.
And his hunches are right
in most cases.
Suspects, can you sit
among the inmates?
- Okay.
- That's not true.
- Everyone, listen to me.
- Yes.
Since Ye Ji is much younger than us,
it must be hard for her
to blend in with us.
Since she's only 21,
she's 50 years younger
than the oldest member.
(56 minus 21 equals 50.
What a weird calculation.)
- Hey, are you saying...
- Right. You were born in 1966.
- that I'm over 70?
- You're not 66 years old.
(You were born in 1966.
You're not 66 years old.)
Seog Jeong just declared...
that she's bad at playing games.
- Did she?
- She made sure she had a way out.
- That's right, she did.
- She could be the culprit?
- That's what she did. Listen to me.
- We look close, right?
She could be the culprit, okay?
(The petty criminals are showing off
their friendship while talking.)
- Ji Hyo, what are you doing?
- We look like close friends, right?
You're so cute.
That was good.
Ji Hyo is so funny lately.
- Keep it up.
- She's cute.
- Shall we start with Suk Jin?
- Yes.
- Please pronounce words clearly.
- I'll do that.
- Pronounce words clearly.
- I have bad hearing.
- Do you understand the rules?
- Yes, I do.
Ye Ji,
are you good at playing games?
- I'm sure she's good at it.
- Yes. I like playing games.
- Young people are quick-witted.
- True.
I'll say "Say It Backwards"
and a word.
- Take turns spelling it backwards.
- Of course, we know that.
It'll be harder for you guys.
I just have to say the last letter.
It'll be easy.
Here we go.
Make a Three-syllable Word. Ba.
(Make a Three-syllable Word,
the 1st syllable, ba)
- Gu...
- Banana!
(The director caught him off guard.)
(Time's up.)
- There are a lot of words.
- What was that?
- Why is he so bad at this?
- The director is a fraud.
- What do you mean?
- You said it'd be Say It Backwards.
Why can't you do it?
- He explained the rules before.
- An, an, ab.
- It was Make a Three-syllable Word.
- But he said...
- that we were going to play...
- Banana, Bahamas, and many more.
- But he said...
- Ba?
- I thought he said "ga."
- It was "ba."
I thought of saying "ganging up."
- That wouldn't work.
- No.
- I have bad hearing.
- It's not appropriate.
- You said we'd play the other one.
He said we'd play Say It Backwards.
- Let's start with someone else.
- It's okay.
- I understand the rules now.
- Let us play.
- Okay.
- Let's go. Who goes first?
Jae Suk will go first,
and Ye Ji will go next.
- In this direction?
- It's easy for Jae Suk.
- In that direction?
- I'll show you how it's done.
- Here we go.
- Ye Ji, keep it together.
- He's focused.
- He's nervous.
Make a Three-syllable Word. Co.
Co.
(Make a Three-syllable Word,
the 1st syllable, el)
- Co.
- Kki.
- Ri.
- It should have three syllables.
- You should've said the 2nd one.
- You said the 1st syllable.
(The 1st syllable was repeated.)
- It should have 3 syllables.
- You should've said the 2nd one.
- You said the 1st syllable.
- Why did you say the 1st syllable?
You should've said the 2nd syllable.
Why did you say the 1st one?
- Jae Suk, do you understand?
- Don't be nervous. Relax.
- Right. "Cocoa" would've worked.
- That's right.
- Co, co, a.
- Right.
- But she said "kki."
- That's right.
You wanted to make the word
"coconut", right?
- I wanted to make "coconut." Why?
- I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, but Ye Ji is at fault.
- Oh, right. I'm to blame.
- Yes.
- Ye Ji, come on.
- I'm sorry.
- She made a mistake.
- You should get it together.
- Co, co, a.
- I see.
But you were confused
about the rules, weren't you?
No. I wanted to make
"coconut" or "cocoa."
Why are you all so bad at this game?
- I'm not bad at it.
- Why...
- Let's begin.
- I'll go first.
Go ahead. You go first.
- It's too nerve-racking.
- You can do this.
It's too nerve-racking
to wait for my turn.
Here we go.
Say It Backwards. Toothpick.
- K.
- Ph.
- Ci.
- Gosh.
Who was it?
- It was reversed.
- He got it wrong.
- It was me.
- She got it wrong first.
- See, Ji Young?
- You got it wrong too.
I got it wrong too?
- K.
- K, ph, ci.
- Hang on.
- Ji Young, you're suspicious.
- K, ci, ph, toot.
- What did I do?
- Catch it.
- It's mine!
- No, it's mine.
Ji Young, you're suspicious.
(A snack packaging box)
(The advertiser's kindness was blown
by the spring breeze.)
- It's mine!
- Advertiser, I caught it!
- I'll be in their advertisement...
- Hey!
- It's mine!
- Give me that, you punk!
Give me that, you punk!
(The petty thief snatched it.)
- It's mine. I caught it.
- Darn it.
(The fierce competition
among the petty criminals)
I could've been their model.
Wasn't it a bonus game?
Anyway, that was suspicious.
I don't think it was a mistake.
- Let our aces play the game.
- No, I'm just bad at this game.
- Our aces?
- I'm not the culprit.
Se Chan will go first this time.
- In what direction?
- To your left.
- To our left?
- I'll go first.
- It'll be hard for me.
- Make a Three-syllable Word...
- I'll prove that I'm innocent.
- Now,
- here we go.
- Make a Three-syllable Word.
Say It Backwards. Chicken breast.
Tsa.
- Nek.
- What?
- It's "erb."
- Erb.
- She's suspicious.
- No.
- Chicken breast.
- Tsa, erb, nek, cihc.
- Is it that difficult?
Is it really that difficult?
Do you think you can do it...
- the moment you hear the word?
- Hey, tsa, erb, nek, cihc.
I know it's hard to say it backwards
all at once,
but you should've gotten
one syllable right!
You just had to say one syllable.
(Tapping)
- Tsa, erb, nek, cihc. It's easy.
- But...
I couldn't think of it right away.
- You should've...
- Why not?
- I bet you can't do it either.
- Chicken...
- We'll pull it off.
- Of course.
- Chicken breast.
- What?
Chicken breast.
- Er, nek, erb, cihc.
- See? It's hard.
My breast.
- "My breast?"
- What was that?
(She twisted the question.)
- "My breast?"
- What was that?
- What...
- Seriously, what's wrong with her?
- Why would you say "my breast?"
- What was that?
Little kids watch this show too.
- What's your problem?
- This isn't an R-rated show.
Haha's son Dream
must be watching this.
- Apologize to Dream!
- Gosh, seriously.
- I wanted to make it tricky.
- Gosh.
- Why is it tricky?
- "My breast."
But I think
we should feel comfortable...
talking about things like that.
- There's nothing wrong with it.
- Exactly.
- We can say "your breast" too.
- It's not like that.
You ate a lot of chicken breasts.
- You work out shirtless every time.
- Right. He shows his nipples too.
I've never heard anyone
say that before.
Hey, Seog Jeong graduated
from Seoul National University.
- Yes, she did.
- No, that can't be true.
She graduated from SNU.
- No, she didn't.
- Yes, I did.
How did you graduate from SNU?
(How did you graduate from SNU?)
- What do you mean by that?
- I can't believe you.
- I mean, I have a feeling...
- How could you say that?
- that she didn't. How did she?
- She majored in traditional music.
- How did you get into SNU?
- She graduated from SNU.
It's all in the past now! Drop it!
- How did you get into that school?
- I...
- How did you get into SNU?
- It's all in the past now.
I don't want to think about it.
Tell me how you got into the school.
- Let's try again.
- Okay. Who goes first?
- We'll start with Jong Kook.
- Okay.
Okay.
Say It Backwards. Africa.
A.
R.
- You should've said "ci."
- See?
R.
(Ye Ji, who said she was good
at games, made a mistake again.)
It should be a, ci, r, fa.
- A, ci, r, fa.
- Ye Ji.
- You said you were good at games.
- Hold on.
How can a 21-year-old
be bad at this?
When she was born in 2002?
- Gosh.
- But...
- It's easy, you know.
- We can at least do it once.
Are there multiple villains?
It was Africa, right?
"A, ci, r, fa" is the answer.
- Jae Suk...
- Let's be honest here.
Can You believe him?
- He was just as confused.
- He said it after taking his time.
What a snob.
- That's not it.
- Let him try it on his own.
Ye Ji, watch and learn.
- Ye Ji, watch.
- Have him do it by himself.
- Just you.
- If you manage to do it,
I'll consider it as a win.
What? No, we should all do it.
No, do it on your own
since you were arrogant just now.
It'll be an extra round.
- Sure.
- What do you have to lose?
- Good luck.
- All right.
- Here we go.
- Bring it on.
Give him a long word.
Say It Backwards.
Mona Lisa.
As, il, an, am.
(As, il, an, am)
(Incorrect)
Are there vacant seats somewhere?
(He suddenly announced
that we had vacant seats.)
Are there vacant seats somewhere?
Where do we have vacant seats?
- Seriously?
- And yet you were arrogant.
- It's as, il, an, om.
- Stop being so arrogant!
I only got a vowel wrong.
- As, il, an, om?
- Aren't I good at this game?
- I'm not bad at the game.
- As if.
Mona Lisa with vacant seats.
Wasn't that good enough?
- I only got a syllable wrong.
- Right.
- We have one vacant seat.
One seat is unoccupied.
- I'm amazed.
- See?
- A vacant seat?
- You did a good job.
- Let's keep going.
- Who would like to go first?
Let me start it off
since that'll be easier to track.
You need to get it right this time.
If not, it'll mean
you're the culprit.
- Exactly.
- But it isn't me.
Here we go.
Say It Backwards. Wi-Fi.
I.
- F.
- I.
W.
(They succeeded.)
- Nicely done.
- Good job.
- Good.
- Nicely done.
That one was doable. Nice, So Min.
- Here we go.
- Do I go first?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- There's no need to be nervous.
- Good luck.
- Please get it right.
- Don't tense up.
- Okay.
- It'll be a three-syllable word.
- Don't worry.
- There are only six left.
- It can't be a four-syllable word.
- Bring it on.
- Come on.
- Let us have it.
Say It Backwards. Spaghetti.
It.
- Teh.
- Ps.
- What on earth?
- Seriously?
There is no need to be nervous!
- It should be Ga and then ps.
- How can you get it wrong?
- It wasn't hard at all.
- But...
Ye Ji, what do you think?
- It was an easy one.
- Right?
Ye Ji, are you kidding me?
- How can he get it wrong?
- You didn't say anything,
but as soon as Jong Kook
suspected me of foul play...
It doesn't have to be done
at a fast pace.
Yes, just keep it
at a moderate pace.
You can slow it down if you want.
- Here we go.
- Let's get it done this time.
Make a Three-syllable Word.
A.
- Auto.
- Shop.
- Say It Backwards.
- Backwards.
(Next up is a game
of Say It Backwards.)
It's simple.
- You know when your turn is.
- There were many options.
- Say It Backwards.
- Next is Say It Backwards.
(Say It Backwards)
Triangular gimbap.
Pab.
- Nairt.
- Mig.
Triangular gimbap.
(Pab)
(Nairt?)
- Are you kidding me?
- Unbelievable.
- Get over him.
- It's him.
- Get him.
- You've been busted.
- We got you.
- Come on.
We know it's you.
- It's been a while.
- Exactly.
It makes no sense.
- What do you mean?
- What are you playing at?
- Seriously?
- How is that difficult?
It makes no sense.
Just say the syllable
that is second to last.
You need to explain yourself
with this one.
Explain yourself if you can.
- It makes no sense.
- Tell us why.
- You said Ye Ji's syllable.
What he said was the first syllable.
- Pab.
- Oh, right.
Mig.
- Nairt.
- What?
- No, that's not it.
- Hey!
(They're all confused.)
- That isn't right.
- Ralug.
He told you that the game
was Say It Backwards,
so all you had to do
was say the second to last syllable.
- After hearing the word...
- I'll do better in the next game!
There's a good chance
you'll botch that too.
What can I do
when I already got it wrong?
And just like that, this game...
- We failed.
- Only the minimum will be in play.
Does this mean
we won't find any clues?
I'm sure that the spy
deliberately got it wrong.
Won't we be able to find any clues?
But on a day like this,
we should lie down
rather than do any work.
(He lies down.)
Exactly.
- Let's party instead.
- Just like this.
Nice.
There are days like this,
don't you agree?
It's like we're in Manhattan.
Let's take a short break.
Yes, let's.
Bite me!
- Nat, tah, nam.
- What?
- She's saying it backwards.
How did you ever
get into Seoul National University?
It's all in the past,
so stop talking about it!
"It's all in the past."
(Ms. Hwang has forgotten about
her early success in life.)
"It's all in the past."
You failed all ten rounds,
which is why only two of you
will get to conduct the search.
- Does that mean no clues?
- Win this next game,
and more people
will get to join the search.
In this second game,
you will get physical.
- Physical?
- As you know, you're a team.
- Right.
The next game...
is a 6-on-6 futsal game
against the prison guards.
Finally.
- Okay, it's settled.
- Good.
- We'll see how good Jong Kook is.
- I will get to defend...
my honor today.
(For a long time, he was known
to be terrible at soccer.)
(He hates it more than
being told he's a bad singer.)
(He makes crucial assists
throughout the game.)
(He'll get to show the viewers.)
You will play in a team of six...
and the game will be split
into two halves.
There must be 3 men
and 3 women at all times.
Win the game and five more people
will be able to join the search.
If you lose or
the game ends in a draw...
- Women must be on the team.
- Are the numbers fixed?
- Okay, I got it.
- It's the same for the staff too.
- Of course.
- Will Myung Jae be playing?
- Absolutely.
- Yes, Myung Jae.
I hear he's good.
- Wait. Isn't there a second half?
- There is.
- So Min, wait.
- Get ready.
Warm up.
Yes, warm up.
Let's crush them.
They should get
a taste of Jong Kook's fury.
- They should.
- Yes, they should.
They'll see what it's like
to be hit by a dump truck.
You'll go flying at least 2m.
- Get ready to be run over.
- That's right.
You will be
in a traffic accident today.
Ye Ji, do you know
how to play soccer?
I was known as Hong Messi.
- Really?
- I'm good.
Hong Messi?
That's right.
- Were you known as Hong Messi?
- Yes.
- That's perfect.
- Hong Messi?
You need two more players.
- Jong Kook and...
- Yes, I'm here.
- Seog Jeong.
- Seog Jeong?
- Yes?
- Seog Jeong, hurry on over.
I was at the restroom.
- Good for you.
- Nicely done.
One must be lighter to run faster.
- Nicely said.
- Of course.
Who is your goalkeeper?
We'll change up the members
as we go.
- Sure.
- Got it.
- Now...
- They don't seem...
intimidating to me.
They aren't any better.
- Exactly.
- All right.
- Hold on a second.
- Please take your places.
Okay.
Go, Team Running Man.
Go, Team "2037."
- Let's do this.
- This is as far as we can go.
- Right.
- Exactly.
- When the game begins.
- I can see that far out though.
(First half start)
And go.
That's it!
Cover him.
- Here.
- Pass the ball.
Over here.
- Seog Jeong, nice.
- My gosh!
- It's good.
- That ball crossed the line.
It crossed the line. It's ours.
- It's ours.
- It didn't cross the line.
Let's spread out.
Ji Young, head over there.
- Where?
- Jae Suk, run forward.
Jae Suk! What the...
Is the ball that light?
(He hit it out of the field.)
I knew you'd do this.
I kicked it too strongly.
Is this "Shooting Running Man?"
- It's all right.
- We get to play soccer though.
Welcome to "Shooting Running Man!"
Kick it forward.
- Good.
- Oh, no.
- It's okay.
- He blocked it.
Why are they so good?
- Go.
- Run for it.
- Run!
- Keep going.
Run.
(He dribbles past his opponents.)
My gosh!
Run.
(He suddenly hugs Ye Ji.)
What on earth?
- Sorry about that.
- Seriously?
Seriously? What was that?
I didn't want her to get injured.
What on earth was that?
Are you kidding me?
- I didn't want her to get hurt.
- Kiss her, why don't you?
I didn't want her to get hurt.
He hugged her out of nowhere.
- Hold on.
- Ji Hyo is fuming!
It's not...
Hey, you.
Hong Ye Ji, get off the field!
That's not it.
- It's okay.
- He's good at all kinds of sports.
(The guards are in control
of the ball more often.)
Seog Jeong!
- Move!
- She...
Seog Jeong, over here.
- Nice!
- Seog Jeong, over here.
(She bulldozes her way
to obtaining the ball.)
Go for it.
(Se Chan is in a position to score.)
That's it. Score!
Go for it.
Score!
(A big save)
- You did well.
- It's all right.
That was close.
Guys, faster!
Here.
Not there.
(The warrior is back.)
Good.
(Groaning)
(The warrior's legs gave in.)
- Get back in there.
- It's our ball.
Stay on the other side.
(The prisoners
will kick the ball in.)
(The guards make a counterattack.)
Get him. Just cling on to him.
- Okay.
- Nice!
- Jae Suk's there.
- I'm right here.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk's there.
- I'm right here.
(He keeps dribbling
even though Jae Suk's is close by.)
Darn it.
- Jae Suk's there.
- I'm right here.
(After failing to score,
he lets out a sigh.)
Why is everyone playing it
so seriously?
- It's our ball.
- Go forward!
Give it to me.
(It's Team Inmate's kick-in.)
Go forward!
Jae Suk, go over there!
- If you stand there...
- Cut it in!
Cut it in! Heading!
- Nice!
- It went in!
Cut it in! Heading!
Nice!
(Slapstick)
Cut it in! Heading! Nice!
(Scoring an own goal,
flapping all by himself)
(Team Inmate scores a goal with
Director Lee Ju Yong's slapstick)
- Nice!
- Great one!
- It just went in.
- Good job!
- Well done.
- That was great.
- That was incredible.
It went in.
- It just went in.
- Good job!
It's become like "Shooting Stars."
- Shooting Running Man.
- Shooting...
- Running Man!
Seog Jeong.
Go up to the goalpost.
- Go up to the goalpost.
- You're doing great.
- Get his ball.
- Give it to me.
- Go forward. Pass it to the back.
Take your time.
(He doesn't pass it to Jae Suk.)
Go forward.
- Pass it to me!
- You must pass it.
It's okay.
Why are only three players playing?
Oh, gosh.
(Team Officer
quickly counterattacks.)
(But Jong Kook
cuts off their attack.)
They are...
- What was that?
- Foul!
(A sudden tackle)
Foul!
It's a foul!
(Making a complaint
while showing off his trapezius)
- It's a foul!
- They're making so many fouls!
It's a foul.
She's no joke.
- She's really fierce.
- Hey.
(They barely calm down
before the game resumes.)
- Messi!
- Go!
Pass it to Jae Suk.
- Over here.
- That's it.
(He plays all by himself again
in the corner.)
It's not out.
What are you doing all by yourself?
(The goalie defends his attack.)
That startled me.
(Giving the thumbs up
when he hasn't scored)
- We're way better.
- We're really good.
It's becoming neck and neck though.
We're way better.
- Let's go!
- It's a one-on-one chance.
(A dump truck
who succeeds in every tackle)
(Jae Suk quickly moves up
to help Jong Kook.)
- Let's go!
- It's a one-on-one chance.
Shoot!
- Hey!
- Why did he...
- It's a one-on-one chance.
- Shoot!
(He blows his chance again.)
Why did he...
- That was so...
- Shoot!
His legs are pretty long.
(The first half is over.)
His legs are really long.
The first half is over.
- Jong Kook, that punk!
- His legs are really long.
I should've scored one.
(He had 8 tackles and 1 hug
during the first half.)
- Why did you dribble for so long?
- I mean...
Why does he play the game
all by himself?
It's not that!
There were five of us
on the other side.
- I passed it to the others too.
- It's okay. He's cool.
- My gosh.
- I passed it to you too.
- He kept showing off his skills.
- It's okay.
(Jong Kook blew his chances
during the first half.)
Ye Ji, it looks like
you have to play again.
- Me?
- She doesn't have the energy to.
How come you're called Hong Messi?
Is it because you like mesh shirts?
How come she's known as Messi?
I used to be good at soccer.
- You?
- Yes.
Then how come you were so bad?
Because it's been long.
It looks like the referee
is generous with fouls.
You know it, right, So Min?
- I think you should do some fouls.
- So Min.
You should just hang on
to one of them.
You should be in charge
of using fouls.
- We'll now begin the second half.
- All right!
It's confusing
because there are no boxes.
You can't stand right behind.
Send it to the back.
- Go up there.
- Pass it to Jong Kook.
We'll be in danger
if it gets cut off.
You punk!
- You should've caught it.
- It was his ball. It's out.
Why didn't you catch it?
- You should block them!
- It was his ball. It's out.
Hurry up and run!
(Right then,
Team Officer counterattacks.)
- Gosh, we're in trouble.
- Hurry up and run!
- Hurry up!
- What? Why is he so good?
(After defending easily...)
Go.
Go up there.
So Min! It's your chance!
He's playing by himself again.
- He's playing by himself again.
- So Min!
(So Min is all by herself
on the front line.)
- So Min! It's your chance!
- He's playing by himself again.
- So Min!
- So Min.
(So Min just let
the ball roll away.)
- So Min!
What are you doing? Am I the target?
- Why did he dodge?
- My gosh.
He's playing by himself again.
- No!
- Hey!
You should cut it off.
(Jong Kook's dribble can only
be cut off by hanging on to him.)
What was that, So Min?
Why is he playing futsal
against six players?
Even Kim Byung Ji didn't go up
like that during his prime.
Suk Jin! You should cut them off
in the middle.
So Min, go up there.
Go up some more.
Heading!
You kicked it too far.
(It went out.)
Suk Jin.
Can't you see the other players?
- He hasn't scored at all.
- What's wrong with him?
(But Jong Kook is in high spirits.)
That's great.
Hey! Come down to defend!
All right. He blocked it.
- Hey!
(Right then, the ball rolls
toward the opponent team.)
All right. He blocked it.
- Hey!
(The ball misses the goal
by a narrow margin.)
That was sensible of you.
(Jong Kook almost let them turn
the game around with his dribble.)
- That was sensible of you.
- Thank goodness it didn't go in.
- I thought it'd go in. My gosh.
- It didn't go in.
So Min! Get the ball!
- Aren't I doing so well?
- All right. It's here.
My gosh.
(Receiving it with his belly)
Why would you go that way?
- Come this way.
- Why did he pass it to them?
- So Min!
- Hurry up and go!
- Hey, run!
- Watch out!
- What is he doing?
- Block it!
(A 1-on-1 chance
given by Haha's mistake)
- Hey, run!
- Watch out!
My gosh, Haha.
- Come this way!
- Oh, gosh.
(It hit the mark.)
- Are you okay?
- Switch!
- Timeout!
Timeout.
- Are you okay?
- Timeout!
You know, it was...
- somewhat refreshing.
- It really was.
- He's the only single man here.
- Give him a pain relief patch.
It's okay because you have muscles.
That was the best play
you've shown so far.
(First time taking an active role
by sacrificing his vital part)
(The game resumes.)
- Hit it! Shoot!
- Shoot!
So Min!
Distract them!
- There you go.
- Great!
Here he goes.
- Ye Ji!
- Hong Messi!
- Kick it out!
(The opponents
start counterattacking right away.)
Kick it out!
No!
(They're about to lose a point!)
(Team Officer: 1, Team Inmate: 1)
(Shaking his head)
He can't block it well
because he's injured.
He hasn't even gotten married!
Jong Kook is injured.
It can't be helped.
- Since last week...
- Give him a pain relief patch.
Will you please run?
Why isn't he running?
- Haha, run up there!
- Okay.
Why is he so slow?
- Something's up with Haha.
- What are you doing?
Pass it to me. Oh, gosh.
She got it.
Go forward. Go.
Go forward, So Min.
- Great!
- Pass it, So Min!
- Go forward!
Go forward, So Min.
- Go!
- Pass it, So Min!
- Great!
- Hey.
This is great.
Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook!
- Pass it to So Min!
(But Jong Kook is short-sighted.)
- Jong Kook! Behind you.
- Pass it.
- Kick it. You should've kicked it.
- Kick it high.
- What are they doing?
- Keep it going.
All right. She got it.
Over here!
They are not going to get up
anytime soon.
(He's showing off his skills again.)
What is he doing
all by himself again?
- What is he doing?
- Kick it!
- Hey.
- Over here.
- Kick it!
- Kick it, Hong Messi!
- Over here.
- Kick it!
Kick it!
(His shot was weak.)
- Gosh, how frustrating.
- My gosh.
Why did he have to wear sunglasses?
Take them off!
You can't see properly.
(Team Officer's counterattack)
- Heading!
- No!
- That was great.
- In the middle!
- Block it. There you go.
- He got it.
- Ji Hyo!
- They're gathered in the middle.
Pass it to So Min!
That must've hurt his back.
No!
(The ball rolls to the corner.)
Pass it to So Min. Behind you.
Pass it to the player behind you.
- Behind you.
- I should've kicked it hard.
Jong Kook! Behind you.
(In the end, he loses the ball.)
No!
(No!)
(She shoots amidst chaos.)
No!
No...
(Team Officer turns the game around
by scoring another goal.)
- What are they doing?
- I can't believe it.
- Gosh, he's driving me crazy.
- What's wrong with him?
Player number 66!
Aren't you going to run?
I was running.
Can't we switch players?
We'll just switch one.
You can switch players
if they're severely injured.
(Grunting)
He's...
- Suk Jin is mentally hurt!
- He's mentally shaken!
He can't walk!
(They all claim to be injured.)
- I'm sorry. You should play.
- Should I play?
You have three minutes left.
- Let's make a goal!
- We can do it!
Let's score another goal!
Let's make a goal! Slowly.
Pass the ball.
Suk Jin is roaming around there
all by himself.
- What?
- Why wouldn't you pass the ball?
They wouldn't pass the ball to him.
They know
where to position themselves.
(Team Officer gets a corner kick
chance a minute before it ends.)
- What's wrong with them?
- Go!
(Jong Kook cuts it off.)
- All right!
- Here he comes.
(A racehorse who only runs forward)
- He's playing by himself again.
- Ji Hyo is up there.
- You're so cool!
- Here he comes.
- Ji Hyo is up there.
He's playing by himself again.
- You're so cool!
- It's a no-mark chance!
(Jong Kook finally gets a chance
to score.)
- You're so cool!
- It's a no-mark chance!
(He fails to score.)
It's a no-mark chance!
It didn't go in.
(The game ends.)
Team Officer wins!
(Team Officer wins.)
How many were blocked?
How many goals did you have to miss?
Ji Hyo was right there!
(He's frustrated.)
Your girlfriend was right there!
I was going to pass it to you,
but they caught up.
Of course. I understand.
- It was supposed to be 5 to 1.
- Jong Kook didn't score at all.
- Gosh, I ran so much.
- Good work, Jong Kook.
I ran so much. Why didn't you run?
Everyone, please gather over here.
- This is so frustrating.
- That's disappointing.
- We can't do it with one player.
- How many chances did he blow?
- I mean...
- He didn't score at all.
What were you trying to show us?
I ran up there many times.
- My gosh.
- Only if he doesn't put together...
the funny parts only...
(He's worried about
how the director will edit it.)
My gosh, Jong Kook.
Don't you mess with it.
(The production crew only included
the parts where he played bad.)
He keeps badmouthing me.
My gosh.
You acquired two players
from the previous mission...
and two players
from the current mission,
so only four players can go
and search the area.
All right.
We should send out the players
who aren't likely to be culprits.
(They picked four players
they'd send out for a search.)
If only four players can go,
players from our side should go.
- These four will go.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Ye Ji, come with us. Let's go.
(A mysterious murder case
that occurred on the set)
Where could the hints be?
(Make the real culprit
take the stand in court.)
Did you notice
anything strange today?
Or did anyone act differently?
Maybe she behaved
a little strangely?
(Someone who acted strangely?)
Ji Young is actually...
not very athletic.
But she seemed...
Doesn't she seem
especially spiritless?
- Yes, she seems to lack energy.
- She seems that way.
- She's usually not like that.
- She's usually very active.
- Right. She's very active.
- Really?
I think Seog Jeong is here
just to be entertaining.
She's determined to entertain us.
She's trying
to make it entertaining.
So Min always ruins everything.
- It's So Min. I think it's her.
- Maybe she's given the role.
Right?
But to think that So Min
is the real culprit...
But it'd be too obvious
if it was So Min.
- Where?
- We're starting now?
- Over here?
- From here?
- What? It's too vast.
- The area is too big.
There's a second floor too.
It looks like there's nothing.
There's nothing.
What kind of hint
are we supposed to find?
(The time passes helplessly
without finding any hints.)
I don't think there's anything
in here.
This can't be it, can it?
There's paper in here,
but it can't be it.
It's not.
There seem to be no objects
that look like hints.
(Everyone is looking for a hint.)
(Surprised)
(Ye Ji found something.)
- You found it?
- Yes, I found something.
- What is it?
- It's a letter to Kwang Soo.
Hey!
What? What is it?
- Kwang Soo...
- I found it in here.
Kwang Soo?
"To Kwang Soo who only has
121 days in prison."
"From Young Seok,
inmate number 664."
"Kwang Soo,
I got only a week left in prison."
"I could hang in here
thanks to your help. Thank you."
("Kwang Soo,
I got only a week left in prison.")
"From Young Seok,
inmate number 664."
The part before the number
is torn off.
It means his inmate number
ends with 664.
(Is the number 664
a hint about the culprit?)
"Your performance in prison
is the most important part."
"When your turn
to clean the bathroom comes,"
"don't skip it
and do your job well."
"You tend to fly into rage,
so control your temper."
"Try to disregard Ggan Dol
who always gets on your nerve."
"You're a good singer, so continue
to perform in choir with passion."
"Attending every event is a way
to leave a strong impression..."
"on the officers."
"Hoping you'll sing with your soul
and continue to have a dream."
I think the number 664
is a big hint.
- Keep it for now.
- Okay.
- Make sure not to lose it.
It feels like
there'll be a hint here.
(And Se Chan who was
looking around by himself...)
Wait. What is this?
What's with the minutes?
What is this?
(Running Prison 1st Meeting Minutes)
(It's meeting minutes
of Running Prison?)
Is this a hint too?
(Participants: Warden Choi Bo Min,
Assistant Warden Kim Beom Jin)
I should take a photo of this.
(Collecting evidence)
(What kind of hint
will they find in the minutes?)
I got it. I can share this
with them, right?
It's minutes.
(He shares the hint with Haha
right away.)
"Participants, Warden Choi Bo Min,
Assistant Warden Kim Beom Jin,"
"Officer Lee In Seok."
"Hold a reformation ballad concert
with ChoNam Zone."
(Running Prison 1st Meeting Minutes)
- My gosh. What is this?
- Did you find something?
I thought Seog Jeong
was the real culprit.
But you tell me.
The hint mentioned that the culprit
was a good singer.
Right. The letter mentioned
that they were a good singer.
- And here, it says,
- A ballad concert.
"Hold a reformation ballad concert
with ChoNam Zone."
(Both hints say that the culprit
is a good singer.)
Aren't you the culprit?
- No, I'm not the culprit.
- Then sing for us.
- I'm a bad singer.
- Show us.
- I can't sing.
Don't you think she's being strange?
- No, I'm not!
- She was even on "Produce 48."
- You were good.
- You...
- You!
- I'm really not the culprit.
I'm serious. I'm not the culprit.
I mean it.
- You!
- Come on.
If I were the culprit,
- I wouldn't have shared the hint.
- Right. She wouldn't have.
No.
She would've shown it to us
so we wouldn't doubt her.
- Oh, she faked it?
- Because she's...
I'm not the culprit.
- Let's get going now.
- All right.
Why would you make us move
all of a sudden?
- Here.
- Why?
- Let's get going.
- Okay, fine.
(He's even suspicious
of the production crew.)
It was Ye Ji.
- Ye Ji.
- They're suddenly cornering me.
So you were a good balladeer.
You lied about your age, right?
Don't I look so relaxed?
- Is that from yesterday?
- Yes.
The sky is beautiful.
(So Min is showing off the photos
from the festival she went to.)
You must've enjoyed it.
There are so many people.
Are you looking for a hint?
I'm just wondering
why they set this up here.
- Right. It could be in there.
- You're right.
- Try opening the cabinet.
- He's right.
I didn't think of that.
(The old detective thinks
there could be a hint in the room.)
Why did they put these here?
Wait.
What is it?
- You found something?
- There's nothing.
- I wish there were some papers.
- It looks like there's nothing.
I also checked it earlier.
Look around the place.
There could be a hint here.
It's confusing.
Hey, I found a laptop.
What? Turn it on.
- Turn it on.
- No way.
Isn't it strange
there's a laptop in here?
It is. There could be a hint
on the laptop.
You're right. There must be a reason
they left it in there.
It's strange how there's
a laptop in here.
Isn't it strange
that a fully charged laptop...
was deep inside the cabinet?
You should click the videos folder
to check CCTV footage.
Because earlier...
There it is. CCTV one.
(There's a folder that says CCTV 1?)
There really is a hint.
- Wait.
- It's the clip from earlier.
No, it's a different one.
Isn't it the same footage?
- It's the same footage.
- Is it?
- But it's...
- It's the clip they showed us.
Is there anything else?
There's nothing else.
That's the only one.
You see?
- It was nothing.
- I know.
- Guys!
- We caught the culprit.
- You caught them?
- Who is it?
- First of all...
- It's over.
- Who is it?
- Haha is not the culprit.
- Why not?
- The culprit...
- That's not true!
- The culprit is...
- I could be...
The hints said that the culprit
was a good singer.
- Wait.
- So he can't be the culprit.
- I am one of the suspects.
- He wasn't the culprit.
It's not him, then.
If you start doubting me from now,
- He's not the culprit.
- I'll treat you to a meal.
- He's not the culprit!
- Hey!
Ye Ji, what did you find?
We found a letter.
- "To Kwang Soo?"
- It was meant for Kwang Soo.
It was already torn off.
"To Kwang Soo who only has
121 days in prison."
With Sleepy...
"From Young Seok,
inmate number 664?"
It's an inmate number
that ends with 664.
Also, they should be a good singer.
- Wait. Ji Young.
- Ji Young.
- Also...
- Wait. Ji Young.
- Yours ends with 664.
- That's right.
- Wait. What?
- A part of it is torn.
(Ji Young's inmate number
ends with 664 as well.)
("From Young Seok,
inmate number 664")
I told you.
The number ends with 664.
I didn't see her as a criminal.
- Wait. It's you.
- Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
- You've worked with...
- I miss him.
- You've worked with him before.
- "Kwang Soo, I got..."
"only a week left in prison.
I wanted to share some tips."
"Your performance in prison
is the most important part."
"When your turn
to clean the bathroom comes,"
- Hey.
- "don't skip it..."
- What's wrong with you?
- "Make sure..."
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- How can you hit me with your knee?
- I was so immersed.
- He was too focused on it.
He was too focused on it.
- Please focus on the letter then.
- "You tend to fly into rage..."
- "During lunch time..."
- Hey!
Let's see it together.
"Until we
see each other again outside."
"Hoping you'll sing with your soul
and continue to have a dream."
- Sing with your soul?
- If you look here...
This is the first meeting minutes
of Running Prison.
(They check the minutes
together as well.)
It says, "Hold a reformation
ballad concert with ChoNam Zone."
- "Within the gardening area,"
- They're a good singer?
"make a water garden."
- Yes?
- Gardening is about me, then.
Seog Jeong is good with gardening.
Gardening is about me, then.
(Then could it be Seog Jeong
who owns a farm?)
- You see? I mentioned this.
- She's a good singer too.
- You see?
- Seog Jeong.
I know.
- Who is it?
- Gardening is about me.
She's a good singer too.
- I found a hint too.
- What is it?
These pages were folded
in the book I found.
(Jong Kook found another hint
at the end of the search.)
A tablet... Wait. What's this?
("Keys to Passing the Exam")
(An exam preparation book?)
These pages were folded.
From page 165 to page 180.
- Or it could be...
- Isn't that someone's height?
There could be something
between the pages.
I think it is someone's height.
- Right?
- You're right.
- From 165cm to 180cm.
There are so many people
who fall into that range.
- Everyone falls into that range.
- Except for Haha.
- You're 163cm tall, right?
- Haha is an exception.
Haha is not the culprit.
You're 163cm tall and a bad singer,
so you're not one of the suspects.
- Seriously...
- Anyone shorter than 165cm?
(Luckily, Haha doesn't fit into any
categories that the hints provided.)
- Hey.
- Okay.
You should start doubting me.
- Got it?
Is there anyone shorter than 165cm?
I'm taller than that.
- Someone shorter.
- Ji Young.
- How tall are you?
- I'm 164cm.
- Then Ji Young isn't the culprit.
- It's not Ji Young.
- It's not her.
- It must not be her.
Ji Young
doesn't fall into the range.
- But...
- How tall are you?
- I'm 165cm.
- Someone purposely...
- She falls into the range too.
- wanted to slander others.
She should be included too.
They must be good at
gardening and singing.
It's you.
- It points at you.
- It's you.
It doesn't make any sense. Come on.
It's either Seog Jeong or So Min.
(Jae Suk has a hunch
it's either Seog Jeong or So Min.)
But I am not a good singer.
I am just mediocre.
- She is a good singer.
- Can you sing a bit?
- Let's hear it.
- Don't sing badly on purpose.
Please sing a bit.
(Foggy)
See? She is a good singer.
(Jangchungdan Park)
- She is good.
- She is really good.
- Ye Ji, sing.
- Sing.
- Ye Ji said that she is tone-deaf.
- She said that.
- I can't sing.
- She is the culprit.
- Ye Ji, sing.
- Sing.
- She was on "Produce 48."
- Seriously.
(You must know
that I am drawn to you)
- She is good.
- It can't be Haha.
- Say
- You punk!
(You punk!)
It can't be Haha.
- Haha, you aren't the culprit.
- It isn't Haha.
- Come over here.
Haha should deduce diligently today.
But Ji Young can sing
really well too.
- That's right. She has good cheer.
- Ji Young, please sing.
Sing.
(Run with me)
- She is good.
- We don't have to go far
- She sang "Run with Me."
- So Min remains.
- It's suspicious.
- So Min is a good singer.
- So Min, go ahead and sing.
Seriously.
Come on
(Love is the same)
- It isn't So Min.
- She tries too hard.
(She avoids suspicion right away.)
- It isn't So Min.
- You can be at ease.
- You aren't the culprit.
She avoided suspicion.
(You can't forget sadness)
- It isn't her.
- It isn't So Min.
It isn't her.
- It isn't her.
- It isn't So Min.
She totally avoided suspicion.
- So Min is okay.
- So Min isn't the culprit.
- You can be at ease.
- Seriously.
You can be at ease.
- "You can be at ease."
- All right.
This is your last chance to find
the culprit...
who eliminated the youngest producer
in the morning.
This is the final race,
the Silent Culprit.
(The final race, the Silent Culprit)
At 4 p.m.,
the last trial will take place.
At 3:30 p.m.,
the first trial will take place.
- There will be trials.
- Yes.
Let me tell you about the trials.
There is a court.
When you go there,
you will find a cage.
If the culprit is
inside the cage at 3:30 p.m.,
the race will end right away.
If someone else is inside the cage,
the race will go on
for another 30 minutes.
Put the culprit inside the prison...
- by 4 p.m..
- How will we do that?
- Do we arrest the culprit?
- That's right.
- We arrest the culprit.
- Yes.
Five minutes before the trial,
- we will make an announcement.
- Okay.
When it's time for a trial,
the bell will ring five times.
Put the culprit inside the cage
during that time.
- The bell needs to ring.
- So Min.
The innocent ones
should stick together.
- In that case...
- I am not the culprit.
- Me neither.
I know you aren't the culprit.
(Who will go inside the cage
for the first trial?)
(Ji Hyo visits the crime scene.)
(She follows the route
the youngest producer took.)
CCTV three.
CCTV two.
Then CCTV one...
(The title of the video she watched
was "CCTV 1.")
I just watched a video
from CCTV one.
I need to watch the videos
from CCTVs 2 and 3.
(She learned about other CCTVs.)
I need to watch the videos
from CCTVs 2 and 3.
(There could be video files
from other CCTVs.)
Did you find something?
- Suk Jin, come over here.
- What is it?
Hurry up, Suk Jin.
Hurry up. Suk Jin.
Do you see these red insects?
(Do you see these red insects?)
- Yes.
- Aren't they fascinating?
(For goodness' sake!)
Look at them.
Aren't they fascinating?
Why would they be fascinating?
I thought you found a hint.
Hurry up and look.
Look at these red insects.
Why would they be fascinating?
I see them, okay?
There are so many of them.
What's up with them?
- Suk Jin.
- It's protective coloration.
- Yes?
Gosh.
What is it?
Look at this three-leaf clover.
(Look at this three-leaf clover.)
For goodness' sake.
(He got fooled for the second time.)
What's up with the members...
- who were born in 1986?
- Did So Min tease you too?
Isn't that three-leaf clover
fascinating?
- All right.
- Suk Jin, it's nice.
- I am going.
- So Min.
Those rookies
passed by a place like this.
(Being pretentious)
(Jae Suk walks around loudly.)
"The Dads'..."
"List."
(What?)
(He finds a suspicious envelope
between the books.)
I knew there would be
something like this.
"A crime scene report.
Victim, Yoon Jong Seo,"
"a police officer
at the Running Police Station."
"May 29th. Key findings."
"The victim was
in good physical condition."
"There is evidence
he got kicked in the butt."
"The exact shoe size
can't be determined,"
"but it's estimated
to be over 240mm."
Okay. I got this.
(The shoe size is estimated
to be over 240mm.)
Over 240mm.
They say the culprit always returns
to the crime scene.
(So Min visits the crime scene.)
He was on the floor like this.
If I remember correctly...
Jae Suk.
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
- I am looking around.
- I am checking out...
the crime scene.
- Hold on.
- Same here.
What are you doing here?
- I am checking out the crime scene.
- It's perfectly natural.
- Did you find something?
- Yes, I did.
- Please say it with us.
The culprit's shoe size
is 240mm or bigger.
- It's 240mm or bigger.
- My shoe size is 240mm.
- Her shoe size is 245mm.
- It's exactly 240mm.
Ji Hyo said your shoe size is 250mm.
- Why are your feet so big?
- It isn't 250mm.
- My feet aren't that big.
- It's 250mm.
- I heard that it's 260mm.
- It's 240mm.
Come on. It's 240mm.
What else did you find?
What's Seog Jeong's shoe size?
And Ye Ji...
I have a question.
Can't the culprit be...
- in Team Blue?
- Of course not.
It's so strange.
- So Min.
- Yes? It's strange.
You know
that you are being suspected, right?
- But I...
- What's your shoe size, So Min?
(Why did So Min change the subject?)
- Seog Jeong, I found a hint.
- Really?
The culprit's shoe size is
240mm or bigger.
What's your shoe size?
It's 245mm.
(Is it me again?)
I am so shocked.
All the hints point to me.
You are under a lot of suspicions.
But I am not the culprit.
But all the hints point
to you, Seog Jeong.
- That's ridiculous.
- All of them point to you.
It would be absurd
if we don't put you in the cage.
All the hints point to you,
Ms. Hwang. Listen.
- You like horticulture. Listen.
- But I...
- You like horticulture.
- "Ms. Hwang" sounds strange.
- Ms. Hwang, you like horticulture.
- Go ahead.
You like to sing. You can sing well.
Your height is
between 165cm and 180cm.
Not over that,
your shoe size is 240mm or bigger.
All the hints point to you.
Did you find any one of those hints?
No. I didn't find a single one.
Then why are you acting like...
you found all the hints?
- We only have two chances.
- If I get wrongfully imprisoned,
can I hit you once I get released?
Have you been taking a nap?
Can I do something then?
- Come here.
- What do I get in return?
Come here. You need to eat
some rice with beans.
- What?
- It's what prisoners eat.
I always eat rice with beans.
My mom is diabetic.
You didn't need to reveal that.
- Seriously.
- It's true.
- I am the honest type.
- It's unrelated to the situation.
- All right.
- You always eat rice with beans.
I eat brown rice.
I even boil beans ahead of time.
- Really?
- Yes.
Do the hints have the R sticker?
(Ji Hyo looks for hints
while the others talk about rice.)
(She found something.)
This is...
the security camera two.
It's a crucial hint.
I took photos
of the security cameras earlier.
(At the crime scene, she spotted
other CCTVs.)
(A video from CCTV 2
can be a crucial hint!)
It's a crucial hint.
Okay. I will watch it
before I show it to the members.
(She decides to check it secretly.)
- Ji Young, is that you?
- Yes.
- Did you find something?
- What is it?
- It's a crucial hint.
What did you find?
A book.
(Ji Young joins him with a hint.)
- Some pages were dog-eared.
- Okay.
Did you find something?
(Ji Hyo joins them.)
I read the dog-eared pages.
The book is about
exercises for the spine.
Although it seems unrelated...
The dog-eared pages are 165 and 180.
My goodness.
It means the culprit's height is
between 165cm and 180cm.
Why were you reading the book?
Really?
The height is
between 165cm and 180cm.
The shoe size is 240mm or bigger.
Is it 240mm or bigger? That means...
it's Seog Jeong.
(Ji Hyo holds a crucial hint,
a video.)
I read the book for no reason.
The shoe size is 240mm or bigger.
Then it's her.
Ye Ji has small feet.
My shoe size is 230mm too.
- Is your shoe size 230mm?
- Yes.
My shoe size is 235mm.
Seog Jeong's shoe size is
240mm or bigger.
- My shoe size is 235mm.
- Is it 235mm?
It's either So Min or Seog Jeong.
It's Seog Jeong.
I think the culprit is
either So Min or Seog Jeong.
Inmates of Running Prison,
the first trial will open
in five minutes.
Please gather around.
The bell needs to ring first.
Put her in the cage.
(It's the first opportunity
to arrest the culprit.)
Put her in the cage.
It's either Seog Jeong or...
I am not the culprit.
What are these sunglasses for?
- What?
- These sunglasses are a hint.
- Did you find them?
- Yes.
- Sunglasses?
I don't know what they are for.
What are they for?
- Sunglasses?
- Will they let us see something?
- Let me see them.
- A film is attached.
I bet they can help us see something
that is invisible to the naked eyes.
- Something like words.
- That's right.
I don't know what they are for.
- Suk Jin!
- What? You startled me.
What?
- What is it?
- Earlier,
- Go on.
I told you about...
- CCTVs.
- Yes.
There was a monitor in the room.
- Did you see anything?
- I didn't see anything.
- The screen was white.
- These sunglasses must be related.
- Let's use these sunglasses.
- I get it now.
Let's use these sunglasses.
- Really?
- Yes.
We don't have time though.
- Let's put one of us in first.
- Yes.
- Let's check on the second try.
- Okay.
Okay. For your information,
- Ye Ji is eliminated.
- What?
(Ye Ji was eliminated
while searching for hints?)
- Ye Ji is eliminated.
- Who did it?
- Why?
- Someone eliminated her.
What? How?
- What happened?
- She is eliminated?
(One of them eliminated Ye Ji!)
She's eliminated? What does it mean?
We should see the overall picture.
(Ye Ji is the second victim
after the youngest producer?)
- This is not a simple matter.
- She's eliminated?
How about Se Chan?
- Where is he?
- How about Se Chan?
Gosh.
- Hey, why are you back only now?
- Where have you been?
- Did you put it up?
- No.
Ye Ji died.
- Ye Ji is eliminated.
- She's out.
- Do you know anything about it?
- What's that?
Really?
- You came too late.
- Why did you...
- I mean...
- Why?
What happened to Ye Ji is one thing.
- Isn't it Ye Ji's bag?
- No.
- It's not Seog Jeong.
- Why not?
- It's the youngest producer's.
- Did you find her bag?
The text was amazing.
- What is it?
- What does it say?
What's this? There's a phone.
(Se Chan found a phone
in the youngest producer's phone.)
Gosh, it must be So Min.
(Gosh, it must be So Min!)
Jeonsobari.
(He's sure So Min is the culprit
after reading the text messages!)
This is a plot twist.
- It got me surprised.
- Why?
- Hurry up and tell us.
- We don't have time. Hurry up.
- This is a message from Ji Yeon.
- Okay.
"You have a shoot this week, right?
Are you okay?"
This is Jong Seo's reply.
"They keep asking me what we will
do. It's driving me crazy."
- "I didn't tell them..." Listen.
- It's not me.
"They're even threatening me now."
- "I must see them every week."
"It's suffocating."
(They have to meet for a shoot
every week?)
- It's So Min.
It's So Min.
It says "every week."
- It's really not right.
- It's not Seog Jeong.
- I'm really not.
- So Min.
He's right. It's So Min.
(They're suspecting So Min instead
of Seog Jeong before the verdict.)
- You go in, So Min.
- Let's check.
- So Min, you go in for now.
- No.
I don't think it's right. Because...
- It's not me.
- It can't be her motive...
- to eliminate someone.
- But I said earlier.
- Look, Suk Jin.
- Are you helping her?
- They meet for a shoot every week.
- Suk Jin.
I think this can't be evidence.
It's the motive.
Why are you defending her?
I'm not defending her.
Are you helping her?
- I told you.
- We should put Seog Jeong in.
- Why would you put me in?
- It's not Seog Jeong.
It's frustrating. Think about it.
There's 1 hint about So Min.
There are 4 hints about Seog Jeong.
And you want to put in who?
But Seog Jeong won't see him
every week.
- Right. That's too...
- It's not every week, but...
- I'm really not it. This is crazy.
- She's not.
- I'm really not.
- Are you really not?
I swear I'm not.
(They send So Min to the cage
because of the text Se Chan found!)
No. For round one,
- we should put Seog Jeong in.
- Or let's put So Min in and...
- So Min, come here.
- I...
- Why did you eliminate the suspect?
- I'm not.
- We don't have time.
- Why would I...
- Why would I eliminate Ye Ji?
- Jae Suk.
We have two chances.
You can't put her in.
- Hey.
- I'm really...
Why are you trying to stop me?
You're being ridiculous.
I mean... Think about it.
Why are you trying to stop me?
There's one hint about her.
So Min, you should go in for now.
- I mean...
- But she...
- So Min.
- It's unfair to put me in...
because of those text messages.
This isn't rational.
So Min, go in.
Why would you put her in?
- Hold on.
- Wait.
- We'll lose our chance.
- Mister.
We should vote.
Why are you trying to put her in?
This guy is suspicious.
- Let's vote.
- Right.
- He wants to put her in quickly.
- What's suspicious about this?
- Isn't he a little suspicious?
- Let's take a show of hands.
- Should I go in then?
- No.
- We should put Seog Jeong in.
- It can't be you.
- Right.
- It's not me.
- Me?
(The bell starts ringing.)
- Why...
- No.
- You have no rules or basis.
- I don't think it's Seog Jeong.
- The culprit might have a grudge.
- Let's vote.
- It's four.
- Seog Jeong was kind of...
- acting strange.
- We don't have time. Hurry up.
Seog Jeong, you go in then.
- Me?
- No.
- Why would you...
- You have no rules or basis.
There are too many hints.
If it's not Seog Jeong nor So Min,
who is it?
I think it's hard
to find the culprit...
- with these hints anyway.
- There's no reasoning.
You go in.
This is ridiculous.
- He said "every week."
But as Suk Jin said,
just because we found
the text messages,
you can't assume she's the culprit.
But Jae Suk,
if "every week" is the key
in the text we found at the end...
We should get things straight
about Seog Jeong before moving on.
Seog Jeong, sit down.
(Seog Jeong was brought to justice.)
What did you say?
So many hints are pointing
to Seog Jeong.
- There are so many hints.
- Okay.
Seog Jeong is the first one
brought to trial.
- I'm really not.
- It's So Min.
- I'll tell you.
- I'm really not.
- Green siren and confetti...
- Will she be eliminated?
mean you caught the culprit.
She'll be eliminated.
Red siren...
- means your first trial failed.
- Okay.
- But she won't be eliminated.
- She will be eliminated.
Gosh, you guys are...
All right.
The result of the first trial.
(The result of the first trial is?)
- I'm not.
- Is it green?
- Who put me in here?
- The result of the first trial.
(She found the youngest producer
who had been eliminated first.)
(From gardening to singing,)
(height, and shoe size, most
of the hints were pointing to her.)
The result of the first trial.
Even if it's not her,
we should put her in first.
One.
Two.
Three.
- I told you.
(Seog Jeong isn't the culprit.)
He sees her every week.
- It's So Min.
- He sees her every week.
- I said it wasn't me.
- I told you it was Jeonsobari.
There will be the last trial
exactly 30 minutes later.
They will suspect me again.
- The key is he sees her every week.
- But I'm really not.
I told you I was not.
I said it 300 times.
- I said it was not me.
- I'm sorry.
- I clearly said it wasn't me.
- You have 30 minutes...
before you put someone in the cage.
I'm not.
I swear I'm not.
Just go for now.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's not me.
It's none of us here.
(Ji Hyo goes straight to get
a laptop with a USB memory stick.)
I should find Suk Jin
to get a laptop.
(Ji Hyo goes straight to get
a laptop with a USB memory stick.)
I'm really...
It's so unfair.
They will say it's me again. Gosh.
- So Min.
- It's so unfair to me.
So Min. Tell me.
- So Min, you kept saying that.
- Haha.
Did you say that just now
because I'm here?
- No.
- Did you...
No way.
"Gosh, they will say it's me again."
It seems you said it
so that I can hear you.
- Haha.
- To win me over to your side.
That's a laptop.
Gosh, I have to see.
(Ji Hyo arrived at the gym
where the laptop is.)
(The USB memory stick with
"CCTV number 2" she found earlier.)
Okay.
"CCTV number two."
(She found
the "CCTV number 2" file.)
("CCTV number 2" captured
what happened in the morning.)
(It's a completely different angle
from the CCTV number 1 earlier.)
I just looked over this earlier.
(Se Chan is in front
of the whiteboard he found earlier.)
This is a little strange.
(Wet wipes
in front of the whiteboard?)
What's this?
Should I...
Will it show something
if I remove it?
I took a picture, so it'll be okay.
No way.
I think I'll get chills.
(There are letters
that won't be erased?)
I was right.
(Ja, Da)
Gosh.
What? Some letters aren't erased.
(After four suspects,)
(the youngest producer
finally appeared.)
Kim, Beom.
(The whiteboard and the CCTV
are slowly revealing the hints.)
(What?)
(The other room?)
(The youngest producer was killed
in the opposite room.)
(And on the whiteboard...)
"The culprit is a man."
(Minutes of the 1st
Running Prison Meeting)
(The culprit is a man.)
This is amazing.
It's one of our members.
(The culprit is one of our members!)
(The culprit is one of the guys.)
Among the members...
(Real suspect number 1: Haha)
- It's you, isn't it?
- Why me?
Why are you suspecting me
out of nowhere?
Why?
(Real suspect number 1: Haha)
(There's Jong Kook over there.)
(Real suspect number 2:
Kim Jong Kook)
Where should I go?
(Real suspect number 2:
Kim Jong Kook)
People were going in and out
of the cage earlier,
but it didn't affect me at all.
(Suspicious)
Okay. I should have a rest now.
(Real suspect number 3:
Yang Se Chan)
Did you not take it off?
Why would I do that?
Did you not take off
Ye Ji's name tag?
- You know what?
- Go on.
I take off the name tag
of important people.
I don't take off the name tags
of younger ones.
So weak.
(One of these clumsy-looking guys
is today's culprit.)
I hope the sunglasses work.
The culprit...
- Suk Jin, I found it here.
- Where?
No wonder why it was on.
- Look at this.
- Why? Let me see.
(It's still a blank white screen.)
Why? Let me see.
Right.
- Can you see it?
- "Futsal strategies."
(He can see something
on the screen...)
(with the glasses on?)
- Can you see it?
- Yes.
(It's definitely
a blank white screen.)
- Give them to me.
- Look at this.
- Let me see it for a moment.
- Wait. 1, 2, 3, 4. Team Blue.
One, two, three, four. Team Blue.
(It seemed there was no hint
on the monitor!)
Look at this.
This is...
- Do you see anyone?
- What's this?
- What colors?
- Futsal strategy board.
Pink.
(The sunglasses reveal
a mysterious clue.)
This is incredible.
It's so fascinating
that I can see a different image.
I can't see it
without the sunglasses.
It's so fascinating.
(He decides to take a photo.)
I should take a photo like this.
Hold the glasses for a second.
Not those glasses.
Those are my glasses.
(Those are my glasses.)
(Jae Suk loves playing
with Suk Jin's glasses.)
I got it.
There is another pink one.
(The futsal strategy board
is a mystery.)
What is this?
There are 2 goalkeepers
from 2 teams.
One member is having a corner kick.
What is this?
I don't know what this is.
Why is the goalkeeper here?
Jae Suk and I can't figure out
what this is.
We are out of ideas.
What is this?
(Futsal?)
Those ones aren't pink.
They can't be initials, right?
J.K...
Oh, it would be J then.
- What?
- Then...
I thought the initials
might point to Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- I didn't see the letters right.
You are saying anything
that comes to mind.
Do you have another chocolate?
Suk Jin, we are deducing.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Jong Kook's initials are J.K.
We played futsal earlier.
(They had a futsal mission earlier.)
Jong Kook made the last attack.
(Jong Kook charged to the goalpost
despite being a goalkeeper.)
(Is he the culprit?)
That's the only situation
that comes to mind.
(The goalkeepers' positions
were similar in the actual match.)
(Suk Jin's deduction makes sense.)
Jong Kook worked the hardest.
He ran around by himself.
Suk Jin, your birthday is
in March, right?
(They go to meet Jong Kook,
a strong candidate.)
- What?
- I wanted to rip it off once.
Then he is out.
- Really?
- He is out.
- I wanted to rip it off once.
That's ridiculous.
Whose name tag got ripped off?
- But...
- Jae Suk's.
Jae Suk, you are out.
- But...
- Ji Young.
(Jae Suk suddenly got eliminated.)
Oh, no.
You can't rip off a name tag
just because you want to.
- You are out if it's removed.
- It's my first time on the show.
His son must be watching
expectantly.
I am sorry.
- His son...
- You are out.
(Jae Suk died in vain.)
You told me that we aren't having
that kind of a race today.
It was the most absurd elimination
in the past 12 years.
Seriously.
- I mean...
- Ji Young, I was eating candy.
It wasn't like that.
Can't I remove a name tag?
Removing it leads to elimination.
- Not today.
- It leads to elimination.
No. Removing it leads
to elimination.
Jae Suk.
Ji Young, why did you do that?
(Jae Suk got eliminated
because of Ji Young.)
Who eliminated
the youngest producer?
(Jong Kook is searching the place
by himself.)
Hold on.
What?
What is this?
Hold on.
It's a broken clock.
What is a broken clock doing here?
(A broken electronic clock
from Age Tech)
This must represent a number.
I don't know what to do with it.
Perhaps I need to use
the sunglasses.
Hold on.
(Did he figure something out?)
The empty spots make...
numbers.
Four.
My goodness.
Hold on.
What do these numbers mean?
The numbers are 44, 42...
The numbers are 44, 42, and 37.
Age?
Hold on.
My goodness.
(A hint that points to the culprit:
44, 42, and 37)
You know,
Se Chan is 37 years old.
Haha is 44 years old.
(Out of the four culprits,
those who fit the hint...)
(are Haha and Se Chan!)
Hold on.
(One of them is the culprit.)
Those punks. Hold on.
I knew something was strange.
Did you find something?
It's either Se Chan or Haha.
- You are right.
- There are two candidates.
Seriously.
(The inmates got fooled
all day long.)
We suspected So Min
and the guests for no reason.
(Meanwhile, Haha approaches...)
(the monitor that shows
the futsal strategy.)
These are the sunglasses.
(Haha looks at the monitor
with the sunglasses Suk Jin left.)
This is what we did earlier.
There they are.
Everyone is here. Jong Kook.
The culprit isn't Ji Hyo or So Min.
(The prime suspect came
on his own volition.)
- It's one of the members.
- That's right.
We figured it out from a CCTV video.
- Really?
- It isn't one of them.
It isn't one of the guests.
Is it Jae Suk? Is it Suk Jin?
- Jae Suk got eliminated.
- He is out.
Jae Suk is out.
He came to frame Jae Suk,
so he became flustered
upon learning the news.
That's not true.
Think about what I did today.
I played the games diligently.
I found so many hints.
It's either you or Haha.
(Se Chan says he isn't the culprit.
Haha deduces for a while.)
(Haha noticed something.)
- Suk Jin, I am not that smart.
- It's a man.
You know that. I am not that smart.
I found so many hints.
(Everyone got fooled...)
(by the culprit who is hiding
among the members.)
(Who is the real culprit?)
Haha!
(He blurted out the name, Haha.)
That's what you get if you type
the characters in Korean.
(There is a keyboard
under the monitor.)
(Ha)
(Haha)
(A few hours ago)
(Suk Jin found a laptop.)
(From the start,)
(the laptop had files in the bin.)
(But everyone focused on
the files on the wallpaper.)
(In the bin was...)
(a video named "CCTV 3.")
(The culprit was Haha.)
(9:33am,
10 minutes before the crime)
(In the room the youngest producer
got called to...)
There you are.
(was Haha.)
(The youngest producer
put on an emotional performance.)
Hey.
What's up with you?
Give me some information.
I can't do that.
Hey.
It's nothing hard.
I will buy you meat, okay?
(Haha threatened him to provide
information on the missions.)
Give me some information.
You punk!
(But when he refused,
Haha began to beat him up.)
You punk!
(The man who is 168cm tall
became violent.)
(He took out
the assistant producer in anger.)
(Haha committed a crime by mistake.)
Hey, Jong Seo.
Jong Seo.
(The youngest producer ran out
in order to survive.)
(In the end, he got eliminated.)
(His dying messages were
"A higher-up" and "Producer...")
(because Haha's YouTube Channel
is "Producer Haha.")
It's all over me.
(Blue blood splattered
on Haha's clothing.)
It's all over me.
I should change
into Young Jin's clothes.
(Thus, he left the crime scene.)
Aren't you wearing the same clothes
as Young Jin?
He bought 2,
so I asked him to give me 1.
(There was something he did
as soon as he got imprisoned.)
All right.
What is this?
(CCTV videos
are stored in this laptop.)
Look at this.
There is a CCTV video.
Let's erase it.
(Haha found a video of himself.)
There we go. Okay.
(He hurriedly erased the file.)
They won't suspect me now.
Shall I break the laptop?
Soul. Song. Dream.
They refer to my family.
(Haha realized that
the last part refers to his family.)
(He quickly got rid of the letter.)
(He discarded other hints
as soon as he found them.)
I need to watch out for Ye Ji.
She is really good
at finding the hints.
- It's suspicious.
- What is it?
(Ye Ji found a crucial hint
before she got eliminated.)
Germany.
(Haha was born in Germany.)
(She got eliminated in the end.)
(Haha took Ye Ji out
and hid his identity.)
Germany.
(Haha took Ye Ji out
and hid his identity.)
(He quickly discards
the sunglasses.)
If this gets out,
I will get caught for sure.
Think about what I did today.
I played the games diligently.
I found so many hints.
According to my deductions,
it's Haha.
Haha isn't here.
- Haha.
- Have you seen Haha?
- I think it's Haha.
(I think it's Haha.)
This is really bad.
Hold on. In that case...
(Haha is under too much suspicion
to get through the last trial.)
Where should I go?
Where should I go? Hey, then...
The last trial will take place at 4 p.m.
I just need to hold out until then.
It will be over
if I don't show up, right?
(He decides to hold out
by not showing up.)
(He refuses to go to trial.)
I will hide well.
I just need to hold out until 4 p.m.
- Let's go over there.
- Yes.
- Let's go find him.
- Where is Haha?
Inmates of Running Prison,
the second trial will begin
in five minutes.
Please gather around.
Let's hurry up and catch Haha.
Let's catch him.
Won't there be the last trial?
There will be, right?
- It works the same way as before.
- We'll gather again?
- But not everyone is there, right?
- Maybe not everyone will gather.
- The culprit may avoid the trial.
- Exactly.
- He might not come.
- Yes.
Haha will definitely run away.
(The other inmates also realized
that Haha might flee.)
Hey, catch Haha.
It's Haha!
Haha is the culprit!
Dong Hoon!
(The chase began.)
Isn't Haha there?
He was with me earlier.
He stabbed me in the back.
(He feels betrayed.)
- I can't believe this.
- What do I do now?
Where should I hide?
(He's not allowed to hide
in the building for fairness' sake.)
I just have to hold out until 4 p.m.
We're running out of time.
This is bad.
Where is the map?
Gosh, that sly punk.
My feet hurt. Darn it.
- Find him!
- This is driving me nuts.
I think they're looking for me.
Gosh, this feels never-ending.
Haha!
- Where are you?
- They're here.
(Haha is getting cornered.)
There. He's over there.
I found him. He's over there.
- We're running out of time.
- Suk Jin.
- Where?
- Go straight!
- He must be there.
- Straight!
They found him. I heard it.
- Haha!
- Where?
- This way.
- Hurry up!
Where is he?
(But at that moment...)
- It's over. Darn.
- Where is he?
(The last bell rang.)
All inmates of Running Prison,
please come to the court.
(The race ended.)
Coward, come out.
- We failed.
- Didn't you find him?
- What?
- Didn't you catch him?
- We couldn't catch him.
- He hid.
This is ridiculous.
Dong Hoon hid.
We failed to catch the culprit.
(Haha is
the winner of today's race.)
It was so hard to make someone else
look like a culprit.
I almost got caught in the gym.
Had he read the letter once more,
it would've been over.
(Had Jong Kook read the letter
once more, it would've been over.)
(Haha survived to the end
after the unprecedented escape.)
Good job.
(Haha survived to the end
after the unprecedented escape.)
Dong Hoon, come out. You coward.
This is a huge place,
and he's so small.
How could we have found him?
(The heart of the global economy)
(Wall Street)
- I'll be at the top of Wall Street.
- Oh, my gosh.
(Running Man goes to New York!)
(They're all jerks!)
(A week earlier)
(There's a quote
about stock investment.)
(Jump in when you hear wailing.)
(The American
stock investment dream)
(Prepare yourselves
with the new members!)
Mom, I'm sorry
that I didn't study hard.
(You must not stop studying
if you want to make investments.)
One, two, three.
(You must be mentally strong enough
to endure continuous declines!)
It could fall
just as that banner did.
(Hope helps to turn a crisis
into an opportunity!)
(Only the one
who prepared everything...)
(will get to go to New York!)
(The Genius Investors:
Go to New York)