The weather is nice today.
We shouldn't be working here.
We have to go to Gangnam.
This isn't just right.
- Hello.
The weather is so nice today. Hello.
- It's spring.
- The weather is lovely these days.
It looks like you two are
in different seasons.
- What?
- Totally different seasons.
This is perfect for this season.
- It's just too soon.
- You must be cold.
- Is it cold? No, it's...
- Yes.
Hello.
- My goodness. I'm...
- Nice to meet you.
(Mr. Baby Octopus enters.)
- Gosh, this is...
- Oh, dear.
- Good, Se Chan.
- We should go to Gangnam.
You look good, Se Chan.
I'm going to Gangnam today.
Suk Jin.
I'm really scared of Dong Hoon.
- Hello.
- Is this "The Outlaws" or what?
- Hey.
- My goodness.
- You look nice.
- Are you from "Harry Potter?"
You tucked your shirt
into the pants.
- Sure.
- Hey.
- You are quite dressed up.
- It looks perfect.
Se Chan, you look nice.
- Next week is our 600th episode.
- Really?
- So I'd like to ask you a favor.
- What?
Ji Hyo and Se Chan came up
with this idea the other day.
We'd like you to put on your best outfits
without your stylists' help.
Something you want to show off.
- Ji Hyo. Seriously this is...
- It's like the medicine commercial.
- Is this what you wear?
- Hey.
- Are you sure?
- This is mine.
By the way,
I know the shoes aren't yours.
So Min, this isn't
how you usually look.
- They are not your shoes.
- Why are you lying?
Except for the shoes,
they all are mine.
- Seriously, I'm wearing my clothes.
- These are...
- I'm...
- You are just obvious.
This is totally me. This is...
And I can tell these are yours.
Right. This is me.
- You bought it in LA, right?
- Yes, this is me.
- I bought it in LA.
- Biggie.
- I got it in LA.
- Your shoes look new.
They are new.
I took them out for today.
- Really?
- To match the colors.
- To show my sincerity.
- So you did smarten yourself up.
- Of course.
- He did.
- This shirt is...
- He smartened himself up.
- Look at his watch.
- I'm wearing a watch.
- I saw that.
- I'm even wearing a watch.
- This is real.
- For a special occasion.
- He's serious about this.
- He's dressed up.
Take a look at Suk Jin.
- What?
- He's wearing something expensive.
Don't do that.
- What is it? Let me see.
- Look.
You're not supposed to look closely.
- Don't do that.
- That's a designer brand.
He says we should glimpse at it.
Right. You shouldn't
look closely at it.
Comedians like things
with big logos like that.
- Right.
- That's what comedians do.
- Brand-name goods...
- Obviously...
- They like brand-name goods.
- Hey, that's so tacky.
This is Gucci, this is Burberry,
and these are Louis Vuitton.
- That's so cool.
- This is crazy.
- Hello.
You're not dressed up.
No, this is fashion.
That has nothing to do with fashion.
You're supposed to be dressed up.
I bought these myself.
- Did you buy them?
- I bought them.
You must have something else.
Why are you dressed like this?
I think that's neat.
- This is perfect.
- It's not bad.
- You two look good together.
- Suk Jin.
- What is this?
- Let go of it.
Hey! Stop it!
- He does it with expensive clothes.
- This is expensive!
(It's an expensive shirt.)
(The collar is stretched out.)
- What is this yellowish thing?
- Hey, this is Gucci.
Hey, this is Gucci.
- What is this...
- It's all stretched out.
This is so upsetting.
This is an expensive shirt.
- What is this yellowish thing?
- Let go of it.
- Hey!
- Why are you wearing...
- It doesn't have to be expensive.
Why are you doing this?
- He's got a lot of business cards.
- This is Louis Vuitton.
- Let go of it.
- Suk Jin.
Just put them back in.
- In Suk Jin bag...
Real estate agents, bankers...
They all are business cards.
- Give me that.
- Suk Jin.
- I mean...
- Why are you doing this?
By the way,
you don't wear things like these.
- He's right.
- Right. You look scary.
What is this watch?
- My goodness.
- This is so...
- You don't usually look like this.
- What's with this watch?
- And, seriously...
- Why would you...
- He doesn't wear things like that.
- You know these are mine.
I think he is...
He is always harassed
by fashion trends.
- Exactly.
- Harassed?
- Am I a fugitive or what?
- Why are you so obsessed?
I'm harassed.
He's harassed by being hip.
On a stand-up comedy show,
lame thugs are always
dressed like this.
- Thugs who are bad at fighting.
- Exactly.
- I know.
- They look exactly like him.
- They just don't get it.
- And there's Ji Hyo.
She looks really hip these days.
- A fashion leader.
- Right.
When I went abroad
in this dress before,
- Jong Kook told me this.
- What did he say?
- Are you trying to pick up a man?
- My gosh.
- Jong Kook.
- Did I see this dress before?
Did I see it before?
- Yes, you did.
- This is why...
you need to set your mind on this.
- Why do you...
- He shakes her up.
- Why do you keep shaking her up?
- Gosh.
The pepper meme is going viral now.
- I know.
- Right.
The black pepper thing.
- Since the episode...
You didn't listen to me.
When she added pepper,
- I was just curious...
- That's enough.
- Aren't I right?
- You are right.
- I was just curious.
- Look at them.
- They even have similar looks.
- No.
- Don't let them stick together.
- I was just asking a question.
- Separate them.
- That's just awkward.
- By the way,
- What?
I don't want you to do anything...
that makes people
wonder about your relationship.
We don't make people wonder.
You're the one
who makes people wonder.
It's you who always starts it.
She added pepper, and I got curious.
So I just asked a question.
- You wondered why.
- The thing is,
it seemed like something was
going on between you two.
- And people noticed it.
- Nothing's going on.
- We need to add vinegar.
- That's why we had a fight.
- Let's say it was someone else.
- I sent him a text...
even after the shoot.
"Why do you not trust me?"
- Seriously?
- Let's say it was So Min.
She added pepper.
I'd ask, "Do you add pepper in here?"
What's wrong with that?
It's good for your health.
(It's good for your health.)
What was that?
- What's that?
- Why are you weighing in?
That doesn't seem weird.
It wouldn't have been strange
if it was So Min.
- She's really funny.
- Why do you keep doing this?
- Why is it okay with her?
- But...
So Min can play along
with all kinds of love jokes.
- That's true.
- I can do it even when you yell.
- She can.
- Even if you swear at me.
You should have some ground rules.
- So Min is enthusiastic.
- That's nice.
You all are dressed up nicely
to celebrate our 600th episode.
That's a lie.
Honestly, I think you all look nice.
Should we go somewhere nice today?
- I don't want to hang out with you.
- Let's just go.
- Where are we going?
- I'll give it to you.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- When? Today?
- He loves it.
- Today?
- No.
- In two years.
- My gosh.
- That's...
- Suk Jin.
When the logo wears off,
- then he will give you this.
- You are so mean.
Just wait two years.
- And it will be yours.
- Okay. I will wait.
Look at Se Chan.
It looks like he's putting up
a singing beggar show...
to celebrate the 20th anniversary
of his debut.
Look at him.
He plays along with the joke.
- He's good.
- Today, Se Chan is...
- giving a solo performance.
- Look at him.
It's his solo performance.
- You look terrible today.
- And he's Se Chan's manager.
No. I really like my outfit.
- Stop it.
- The singing beggar show.
- Seriously...
- Hey, you are...
- It's hot, but I should be patient.
- There's a butterfly.
- Butterfly.
- Follow it. There it goes.
- Go.
- Follow the butterfly.
Keep following it.
- So Min, go.
- She's gone.
So Min, you should go.
- You should go.
- That's nice.
So this is our 600th episode.
It's been a really long time.
- Sure.
- That's a lot.
It's been so long.
And this is unprecedented in Korea.
So we prepared a cake
to thank you guys.
- A cake?
- My gosh.
- All right.
- It's pretty.
- Thank you.
- It says it's the 600th episode.
- So it's been about ten years.
- Take a photo of it.
- Jong Kook.
- Do we need to sing?
- Is this Ji Hyo?
- They look like us.
It even has my double chin.
(The cookies have the detailed
features of the members.)
- Actually, this is...
- You know what?
A total of 600 episodes
means 12 years.
- Exactly.
- Did you say 12 years?
- It's been a long time.
- It's unbelievable.
I'm so touched.
This is amazing.
Of course.
- Thank you.
- We owe it all to our viewers...
- who always support us...
- Exactly.
and the production crew
who always helps us.
There are many staff members
like Chan Hee who've been...
- with us the whole time.
- Exactly.
And I'd like to thank our members.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Thank you all for your hard work.
- This is really nice.
Our show will continue.
All right. Let's blow out
the candles together.
- Thank you so much.
- One, two, three.
(Congratulations
on the 600th episode.)
- There have been 600 episodes.
- It's been a really long time.
- This is amazing.
- The 600th episode.
- This is pretty.
- It's been so long.
Today, to celebrate
our 600th episode, we will have...
With Viewers Race where we will
do things with our viewers.
- What is it?
- With our viewers?
The race will have
Part 1 and Part 2.
In each part, we will have one
candidate for a winner and a loser.
So there will be 2 candidates for
a winner and another 2 for a loser.
And 1 of these 2 will each be
a winner and a loser.
Let me tell you about
the privilege of the winner.
You can send a coffee truck...
to any place you want
in Running Man's name.
- Okay.
- That sounds nice.
And today, we'd like to donate money
to charities for good causes...
- after a long time.
- I see.
And we will do it
in the winner's name.
The amount of the donation
depends on what you do today.
You can save up to 10,000 dollars,
so I'd like you to try your best.
We should give it our best shot.
All right. Let's move to...
- the venue for Part One then.
- Shall we?
- Let's go.
- All right.
Let's go.
The weather is getting hotter.
This is really nice.
I want to try this fishcake.
It tastes really good.
I like the fishcake.
(They have all kinds of snacks
set out on the table.)
- This is good.
- It's tasty.
(It's coffee and snacks
from the fans of Running Man.)
It's delicious.
- This is a race with our viewers.
- Okay.
While you enjoy the snacks
from our viewers and fans,
I will explain
the rules for Part One.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the snacks.
Those who already checked
our social media might know this.
Via our Instagram and YouTube channels,
we've been getting...
questions about Running Man
and the members since March.
Actually, we've never had...
such a Q and A session
in the last 600 episodes.
- Seriously?
- That sounds nice.
Questions about us.
Will it be fun?
- That's the problem.
- I'm not sure.
We have to make this fun.
- It doesn't have to be funny.
- Seriously?
We just want your honest answers.
So is this like an interview?
On our Instagram,
we got 12,568 comments.
On our YouTube channel,
we got 4,682 comments.
So there are about 17,250 questions.
(About 17,000 questions)
I heard Suk Jin used
the macroinstruction.
- Did you do that?
- Is that true?
- I heard that's what you did.
- That's not true.
Among them, we picked out
the most frequently asked questions.
It must've been hard.
So we have 30 questions now.
How did you pick them out?
- It must've been tough.
- And the 30 questions are...
in the balloons behind you.
- That's brilliant.
- Hey.
- This is like a fan meeting.
- I know.
You will pop a balloon you want...
and read the question
in the balloon.
And the person who is questioned
will give an honest answer.
If you do that, you will save
6,000 dollars for the donation.
- My gosh.
- Oh, dear.
Isn't that too easy?
Are we getting 6,000 dollars
just by doing that?
That's suspicious.
This is a good thing.
Once the Q and A session is over,
the members will take a vote
on the person...
- who gave the most honest answer.
- There must be something.
And the person will be
a candidate for a winner.
And a candidate for a loser...
will be decided by the crew members.
(The candidate for a loser will be
decided by the crew members.)
- Honestly, Suk Jin is...
- Honest answers?
- I can give honest answers.
- Seriously,
- he's leading a fake life.
- That's not true.
- Fake.
- I'm honest.
- He can be on "Incredible Moment."
- Or on "Surprise Mystery TV."
- The fake life.
- I'm ready to tell the truth.
Now you can pop the balloons.
This part will make up about
30 to 40 minutes of the airtime.
So we need about eight questions.
- I see.
- Hang on.
You just told us to do it at ease,
but why would you bring that up?
- That means...
- That's a lot of pressure.
I feel suffocated.
That means we need to make this fun.
It means the same.
Why do you give us such guidelines
all of a sudden?
Just tell us to make it fun.
That's a lot of pressure.
Don't worry about the airtime.
- So Min.
- It's like...
You already said 30 to 40 minutes.
Actually, the youngest members...
don't care much about airtime.
- It's not so...
- They don't care a lot about it.
They don't bear
much of the responsibility.
- But the older members...
- It's good to be the youngest.
- I feel a lot of pressure.
- You do?
They treat me differently
after the shoot.
- Why?
- What do you mean?
After the shoot, I usually say,
"Thank you for today. Goodbye."
When I do something fun,
the head writer comes to me
and says,
- "So Min, great job today."
- Does she say things like that?
"So Min, you are
the treasure of Running Man."
But when I'm not so funny...
I say thank you,
she just walks past me.
"Hey, Jae Suk."
She talks to someone else.
She doesn't even look at me.
- Hyo Im.
- You shouldn't be like that.
Hyo Im, that's what you do
before you know it.
Ji Hyo, did Hyo Im
ever come to you...
and say that you did a great job?
She doesn't even know
whom you are talking about now.
There she is.
- That's Hyo Im.
- I know who she is.
That's Hyo Im. There she is.
- "That's Hyo Im."
- "That's her."
Ji Hyo, I forgot to ask you
our official question.
What did you do yesterday?
I stayed at home.
(I stayed at home.)
We need a screenshot of this.
"I stayed at home."
I'm collecting them.
Is the door to your place
locked up from the outside?
- Someone else locks it up?
- No.
"Ji Hyo, what did you do today?"
"I stayed at home."
We can make it into a group song.
I'm sorry. This is yours,
but I just drank it.
It's okay. It's no big deal.
- What was that?
- What are they doing?
- Why are you two so close?
- Go ahead and drink it.
You're being nice to him
because he's a good fighter.
- What?
- Because he's strong...
- Hey.
- I just like him.
- That means I'm a good friend.
- He's a good friend.
And he and I have been working
together for the longest time.
- What do you mean?
- Since "X-Man".
Don't be ridiculous.
What about
"Live and Enjoy Together"?
Right. There was
"Live and Enjoy Together".
Look at him.
(2001, "Star Survival:
Live and Enjoy Together")
(I won't get hurt
even if something hits my head.)
(I need to protect my head.)
(Do you still fight?)
- Sure.
- Okay.
(I've missed you.)
(Jae Suk.)
Look at him.
- The fan meeting.
- "Live and Enjoy Together".
- You hosted my fan meeting.
- Hey.
I'm glad you brought that up.
You stared at me
with those snake eyes.
- Snake eyes.
- At my fan meeting...
You got 500 to 1,000 dollars
like this.
"Oh, dear."
Was it 1,000 dollars?
You got paid a lot.
- "Thank you so much."
- That's very generous.
I looked at it in the mirror.
- He was like this.
- Back then, his pay was...
only 300 to 500 dollars.
Why would you talk
about my pay from back then?
- I know.
- That was his pay.
He got the money like this.
- Hey. I made the best...
- I want questions like this today.
- I made the best use of the money.
- I know.
- This is the real friendship.
(That's how
their friendship started.)
- Do you want me to pop it first?
- Okay.
- The beggar goes first.
- Se Chan.
So Min, your outfit is really...
What about the black one?
I bet it's for Jong Kook.
That doesn't include...
- Gosh, I'm startled.
- That's loud.
- Let's read it.
- I'm startled.
Here.
We have a question.
- Okay.
- I will read it.
Black.
(They have to give honest
answers to any questions.)
"Jae Suk knows all there is to know
about his colleagues' social media."
- Does he have a secret account?
- "Does he..."
"have a secret account
that he uses to spy on others?"
- That's what I thought.
- That's right.
- I want to know.
- I never thought about this.
- I bet he has one.
- The question is...
- very sharp.
- To check others' accounts.
- To spy on others.
- The thing is,
I don't need an account.
- You can see it everywhere.
- That's true.
But sometimes you know things
that weren't reported in the media.
A lot of fans post...
- such information online.
- Fans do that?
- Where do you get the information?
- On YouTube?
A forum and some other websites.
- You mean, an internet forum?
- Which forum do you often visit?
- It's...
- He meets people at a nearby cafe.
The owner of the cafe
I go to as a regular...
- That person tells you?
- tells me recent celebrity news.
But sometimes he knows
too much details...
- that's hard to find out that way.
- That's right.
I get tipped off.
- I'm not going to tell you who.
- Who tips you off?
- A celebrity or a staff member?
- It could be a staff member...
- Exactly.
or one of the people around you.
- You mean, our fellow entertainer?
- I get it. It's Sae Ho, right?
- One of our fellow entertainers.
- Cho Sae Ho, right?
- It could be Sae Ho.
- It must be Sae Ho.
I also deliver the information I got
to some other people.
- I see.
- Some tell me funny stories.
- Right.
- I mean, he knows everything.
- True.
- There's nothing he doesn't know.
You can get information easily
on YouTube these days.
That's true.
- They share information on YouTube.
- That's true.
- They share everything.
- That's right.
The fans upload videos
about the information they gathered.
- Why are you not on social media?
- Social media...
I can't think of any reasons
to be on social media.
- Jae Suk, I have a question.
- Go ahead.
When we take a photo together,
I want to upload the photo.
Do you want me to ask you first?
Or can I just upload it?
- You can just upload it.
- Come on.
- Wouldn't you mind?
- I wouldn't mind.
- That's a promise.
- Sure.
- Then I'll upload whatever I want.
- Okay. Like what?
- Something embarrassing?
- No.
- It's not like that.
- I know what it is.
- Oh, I think I know too.
- The extreme close-up shots?
- Where he looks like a monkfish.
- No, that's not it.
- So Min, you meant that one, right?
- No. His photos in general.
- When I have a photo of you...
- Then ask me before you upload it.
- Show me first.
- Every time?
I'd like you
to ask for my permission.
I have some photos of So Min too.
- No. You can't upload those.
- She didn't let me.
- She said no.
- Those are too embarrassing.
Why didn't you let him?
- I dressed as Yondu.
- Let me reveal the photos.
They were taken before my face was
painted blue. It's embarrassing.
I have a few photos of Suk Jin.
- You can upload them.
- I have his photos too.
- I don't mind.
- The ones where you're sleeping.
- I...
- Except for those.
- I have photos of him sleeping too.
- Really?
- Where I look spaced out, right?
- I have a few as well.
- I have photos of him sleeping.
- That's embarrassing.
Can I upload a photo of you smoking
an electronic cigarette?
- No, you can't.
- The one...
- I have photos of him smoking too.
- On my social media.
Please don't upload such photos.
What about the one
where Jong Kook's nipples show?
That's okay. Such photos of me are
already all over the internet.
- You don't mind?
- No, I don't mind.
- I can share your photos, right?
- Right.
My photos?
Where will you upload them?
I'll put them on the bulletin board
in my apartment building.
- Why would you...
- Because I'm not on social media.
- Will you print them out?
- Why would you do that?
- Yes. "My fellow residents."
- I like that idea.
- "Look at these funny photos."
- That's a great idea.
- "Have a nice day."
- People would love it.
- On the one in the elevator.
- Exactly.
- I love the idea.
- Just open a social media account.
I mean, you're a top show host.
- Share your daily life...
- But that's...
- up to Jae Suk.
- Why would I do that for him?
I'd have to keep posting my photos.
But I don't like taking selfies.
Then why do you not use
a messenger app?
- That's a hassle.
- Many don't use it including her.
- When you sign up for it,
- That's right.
the contact numbers on my phone
would be on the list.
- I'd get a lot of welcome messages.
- But that's...
- Not necessarily.
- That's not true.
- You can turn off notifications.
- I don't like meaningless chats.
- Exactly.
- What do you mean?
- Also, in a group chat room,
- you get hundreds of messages.
- What I'm saying is... Yes.
It's fun to talk in a group chat
from time to time.
- It's fun.
- I wouldn't give up the rest...
- for that brief moment.
- Absolutely.
- I like your comment. It's logical.
- Jae Suk, I mean...
- Everyone else uses the messenger.
- They're excited.
Exactly.
- Honestly, one of the reasons...
- I understand.
I don't want to
join your group chat is...
- Haha.
- Why?
(Haha is 1 of the reasons I don't
want to join your group chat.)
- Why?
- He sends photos of him eating.
- You mean, he acts up?
- He does that.
- He acts up.
- Yes, he does.
(This is the members' group chat.)
- And he films himself drinking too.
- Jae Suk.
"I had a drink."
(He makes a vlog video
and sends it in the group chat.)
- "I had a drink."
- That's true.
- I hate it when he does that.
- Jae Suk.
Do you know
how lonely I feel at home?
Do you know how comforting it is?
- I agree.
- It helped us while quarantining.
- True.
- I don't want to know what he eats.
- But Jae Suk.
- It got you through a hard time.
- Yes, you're right.
- How did you know that?
I heard. So Min and many others
told me about it.
- I didn't tell him that.
- Oh, I see.
- You told me.
- No, I didn't.
Based on what he said,
she badmouthed me.
- No, I didn't.
- You told me.
- How could you?
- Oh, no. So Min, I'm sorry.
- She's his spy.
- No, that's not true.
- Gosh, you spy.
- It's our private group chat.
- You asked me to send that photo.
- I'm done with it.
- I'll leave that chat room.
- So Min, I'm sorry.
- Let's open a new one without her.
- Leave our chat room.
- Without her.
- Let's open a new one.
- We let you join us. How could you?
- Let's open one without her.
- Listen. Having a group chat...
- You shouldn't do that.
- isn't all good.
- How could you?
- You guys ignore my messages.
- We're not like you.
- This is why I don't use it.
- You guys ignore my messages.
- That's not true.
- He...
- Jong Kook often leaves me on read.
- This is why.
- When did I ignore your message?
- He leaves me on read.
Haha has more than ten group chats.
- He opens a new one too often.
- That's my specialty.
- Don't act up.
- Right.
That's not what it's about.
That's me being friendly.
- No, you act up all the time.
- That's right.
- Why do you call it acting up?
- Gosh.
When Haha invites me
to parties like his birthday party,
there's something he always does.
Jung Jun Ha does it too.
- He invites friends individually.
- Really?
- "Hey, come join my party."
- I see.
- You'd meet people you don't know.
- "You don't mind, do you?"
Exactly. "You don't mind, do you?"
I meet people I don't know.
- It's uncomfortable.
- It's really uncomfortable.
And he leaves before I leave.
That's because I'm drunk.
- Why would he leave early?
- Because I'm drunk.
He gathered all those people
who didn't know one another.
- And he claims...
- You can make friends with them.
I wouldn't introduce bad people
to you, would I?
- That's not all.
- It's nice to meet good people.
He claims
that they're all good people.
- It's not like I get jealous.
- It's really uncomfortable.
- I don't get jealous.
- Here's what's ridiculous.
- So we became friends through Haha.
- Okay.
We developed friendships
and kept in touch with each other.
One day, I asked Haha,
"Why don't you see him anymore?"
He said, "He's a jerk."
- That's true.
- I mean, seriously.
- He does that.
- It's ridiculous.
- He introduced us to each other.
- That's true.
- And we became close friends.
- Right?
- But he cut ties with that friend.
- That's right.
- He ended the friendship alone.
- Haha, come on.
- My gosh.
- I didn't know he was a jerk.
I was fooled by him too.
- You should be comforting me.
- Calm down.
- I didn't know. I'm a victim too.
- How can you call yourself human?
- I'm a victim too.
You're supposed to be comforting me.
- I was just speechless.
- Haha does that.
- I was dumbfounded.
- Jae Suk.
- That's a good point.
- It's true.
- I know.
- That's a good point.
- It's fun to have a video chat.
- Yes, it's really fun.
But you always leave So Min out
during a video chat.
- We should open a new group chat.
- Why would you do that?
- Let her join the chat.
- But that's...
She always calls me
after a video chat with you guys.
"I just had a video chat with them.
I was left out again."
- That's not true.
- She sounded quite upset.
So Min is always the last person
left on the screen.
- Stop...
- Everyone else leaves,
and So Min's face is left alone
on the screen.
Then she leaves with a long face.
- She's always the last person left.
- True.
- Hey, So Min.
- She's left alone in the end.
That's why I told you,
"Why don't you leave the chat room
if no one talks to you?"
But it's so fun. I love it.
- You open a chat room next time.
- Right.
You can invite us all this evening.
We'll join the chat.
- I'm not available this evening.
- Why?
- I have to look after my kids.
- Okay.
- I'm busy.
- I should go to the gym.
- Okay. Let's do it next week.
- Next week, it is.
- Let's do it next week.
It's been decided.
We'll do it next week.
- Not today.
- Why?
- They can't make it today.
- Right.
We'll do it next week.
- There is another question.
- What is it?
- Well...
- You answered only one question?
- My answer is...
- What's your answer?
- On social media...
- You're not on social media.
- I don't have a secret account.
- No secret social media account.
It'd be okay if you started
just one account.
- Well, it's not...
- Just to visit others' accounts.
- Shall I? All right.
- You can see how others are doing.
- I understand.
- So we can talk about it next week.
I don't have a secret account
or use a messenger app.
- Okay.
- Will you keep it that way?
- I'm not planning to do it for now.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Here goes the next question.
- It's a question for Ji-rasoni.
- Me?
"You're everyone's target
in almost every episode."
"Tell me how you keep your mind
stronger than titanium."
(ID: Yoo Jin Ho, Mr. Ji-rasoni,
how do you keep your mind strong?)
- I'm curious about that too.
- He's a superhero.
- "Stronger than titanium."
- He's stronger than titanium.
He keeps his mind strong.
- "Stronger than titanium."
- To be honest, I don't know...
- what makes people think that way.
- He has healing power.
- Many people ask me that question.
- I see.
It's not just my fans.
Even my friends said,
"Don't you feel offended?
Teach them a lesson."
- Some said things like that.
- Your friends said that?
- Yes, my friends said that.
- It must be Kim Yong Man.
- Yong Man...
- "That made me upset."
- and Soo Yong.
- Oh, I see.
- No, they're not TV celebrities.
- Are they non-celebrities?
- "Hey, when they're rude to you..."
- Suk Jin.
Invite them to the set sometime.
- Invite your friends here.
- Right. Invite them here.
His non-celebrity friends.
They would be sweating buckets
while watching us.
They'd say,
"They're disrespectful to you."
- "How could they be so rude?"
- Really?
Then I tell them it's not like that.
- Some people don't understand.
- That's right.
And I understand
what they're worried about.
- But we just joke around.
- That's right.
- I have my role to play.
- Absolutely.
- When you joke around with me,
- Of course.
- my role on the show stands out.
- Exactly.
That's what I believe.
I often tell you in the restroom.
- Tell me what?
- "You can go further."
- Right. Yes, you do.
- I often tell him that.
- Yes. We're different in real life.
- Yes. That's why...
it's not so hard for me
to stay mentally strong.
- We shouldn't do that off-camera.
- Of course.
- Exactly.
- We would never do that.
- We'd never be rude to him.
- I would gather you all up.
- Right.
- Absolutely.
- I would. But I wonder...
- Yes?
if you guys would come to see me
as I say?
- Of course, we would.
- I don't think you would.
- Let's say I'm upset at you guys.
- Of course, we would.
- Se Chan.
- Yes, Suk Jin.
- I'm really upset.
- I see.
- You guys crossed the line today.
- I understand.
- Tell everyone to gather tonight.
- Right.
Tonight doesn't work for me.
I have plans. I'm sorry.
Really? Then would next week
work for you?
I have a shoot next week.
I'll let you know.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- I'll see you then.
- Of course.
I don't think you'd gather.
But still, there must be times
when you lose your temper...
- during a shoot.
- Right.
- I'm sure it happens.
- It happens once in a while.
- Just once in a while.
- Like when?
- I don't remember.
- Okay.
- When I hit you with a foam bat...
- He wouldn't have been upset.
- When So Min hit me,
- Yes.
If I expressed how upset it made me
as a percentage,
- it was zero percent.
- It didn't make you upset at all?
- Really?
- I wasn't upset at all.
It's because you didn't hit me
because you wanted to hurt me.
Right?
You didn't hit me
because you wanted to hurt me.
(Feeling guilty)
- Did she want to hit me? A little?
- Just a little bit.
- I get it. This must be his secret.
- Just a little bit?
This is how he stays
mentally strong.
- I see that now.
- She wanted to hit me?
- A little. She's a human after all.
- You could see that?
- A little bit?
- Of course.
- He keeps fooling himself...
- I didn't know that.
- like that.
- It's because you're cheeky.
I see. Because I'm cheeky?
- I see.
- He keeps calm.
- He maintains his cool.
- Exactly.
- I wasn't upset at all.
- But you were upset...
About what?
- when we selected the president.
- Oh, right.
- He got a little upset then.
- You mean, the captain?
- Yes, the captain.
- He sulked.
(While voting to choose the captain
that no one wanted to become...)
(Everyone voted for Suk Jin.)
(I'm too busy for this.)
(I have shoots all week.)
(Suk Jin was genuinely upset
as he was going to get all votes.)
"I have a shoot in the morning."
(And then they began the voting.)
(Although it was edited out,
Suk Jin got almost all the votes.)
(Why am I always the one
who is chosen for things like this?)
(Suk Jin thought it was unfair
that they always chose Suk Jin.)
(Then let's vote again.
We won't discuss it this time.)
(They decided to vote again,
so the 1st voting was edited out.)
(As a result of the re-vote...)
(Suk Jin won again.)
We should toss him.
(Sae Ho used all the ballots he had
to vote for Suk Jin again.)
(Glaring)
(This is why Sae Ho was
on pins and needles after the vote.)
(But Captain Ji accepted it shortly
and served out his term happily.)
- I got upset, which was edited out.
- He was upset.
I was genuinely upset.
- I know.
- Exactly.
- I was upset then.
- You said nothing made you upset.
- That part was edited out.
- Was he really upset?
- What made me upset was...
that it seemed that you guys chose
me for things like that every time.
- That's why I got upset.
- You're still upset.
- I was upset then.
- Of course.
But you said nothing made you upset.
- Exactly.
- Come on.
Everyone gets upset
from time to time.
- You're upset right now.
- I'm a human.
(Everyone gets upset
from time to time. I'm a human.)
(He ended up losing his temper.)
- I'm a living thing that can think.
- I mean...
Then you shouldn't have said
you'd never get upset.
- Calm down.
- It's not like that.
- You were like this. "It was..."
- You shouldn't have said...
"zero percent."
- It wasn't upset at her.
- You said you wouldn't get upset.
- But I lost my temper then.
- I see.
- It hurt your feelings.
- That's right.
"Whenever we do things like this,
it's always me, Kwang Soo,"
- "him, or her."
- You should never have said it.
- That's right.
- You shouldn't have promised it.
- Gosh. Why you little...
- I never say anything like that.
(Making a fist)
- He's upset again.
- He's upset.
What are you going to do next?
- What do you mean?
- What's your next move?
- To him? What do you mean?
- Yes.
- Was that it?
- You made a fist.
- What's next?
- Right. And then what will you do?
- What will you do next?
- I'll get along well with him.
(I'll get along well with him.)
I'll get along well with him.
- Because we're just joking around.
- That's right.
- Absolutely.
- We're just joking around.
- Each of us is...
- That was good.
- As Suk Jin said, we're humans.
- That's right.
- Yes. I lose my temper sometimes.
- It happens.
When the viewers watch the show,
some of them might think
it's too mean.
- That's understandable.
- But...
- We all love one another.
- Of course.
- We respect one another. Yes.
- We trust one another.
Also, each of us has
a different role to play...
- in a certain situation.
- That's right.
- Yes. I'm fine with it.
- We hope you understand us.
- So Min, you pick one this time.
- How about the yellow one?
- Pick the blue one.
- The green one.
- I pick the light green one.
Pop the light green one
since you dressed as Yondu.
So Min, don't throw it.
Just poke it.
I can't believe she struck
a cute pose for doing that.
(I can't believe she struck
a cute pose for doing that.)
You saw that too.
- I must say, So Min is...
- She's amazing.
- She's incredible.
- Indeed.
- So Min is...
- a talented entertainer.
- I agree.
- She's perfect for variety shows.
- She's a jewel.
- She's a jewel in the showbiz.
- She's cut out for this.
"Se Chan, when you won
the Top Excellence Award last year,"
"you cried,
and that broke my heart."
"I'm curious about the mindset
you have on set these days."
(ID: Lc42, I'm curious about
the mindset you have on set.)
- Every week... It's funny...
- That's a hard question.
(The mindset he has on set
every week...)
- It's funny...
- It's a difficult question.
- It's difficult.
- You can just...
- tell him how you honestly feel.
- Give him an honest answer.
- Be honest.
- Right. Be honest.
From my first day on the show
until now,
I haven't been at ease
on the day before the shoot.
- I see.
- It's still the same now.
- Even now?
- And...
Last night, I couldn't fall asleep,
thinking, "Is the role I play
on the show the best I can do?"
- Of course, it is.
- I always...
- think hard...
- We were told to dress nicely.
But you dressed like that
to look funny, right?
- No, that's not it.
- With that logic,
- you look funnier than him.
- That's not what I'm saying, Haha.
- I tried to...
- You look really funny.
I tried my best to dress in a way
that would suit the concept.
- I tried several outfits yesterday.
- Right.
I didn't just pick
a nice outfit I had.
I tried to choose fashion items
that could make you guys...
- Of course.
- want to comment on them.
- Really?
- I always think hard before I come.
- I understand.
- Actually, So Min and Se Chan...
- joined Running Man 5 years ago.
- It's been 5 years.
Oh, my. It's been five years.
When Se Chan and So Min
joined the team,
- it wasn't easy for them.
- Of course.
Especially because the other members
had been doing this for many years.
- That's right.
- It must've been hard.
- It's really hard to get settled.
- Indeed.
- Of course.
- It's hard.
- It's really hard.
- You see...
If I had to tell you
about the hardest time...
I felt as if I had done nothing...
on a weekend variety show.
I didn't look funny
even when I watched it on TV.
But when we finished the shoot,
you guys told me, "Good job."
On my way back home, I felt...
- so stressed out.
- He must've been under pressure.
- Of course, you felt burdened.
- I wasn't sure if I'd done well.
I went through a really hard time
emotionally.
- Really?
- Yes.
We said you had done well
because you had done well.
- And above all...
- That's right.
- It means, "You should do better."
- For you to settle in...
(It means, "You should do better.")
- Suk Jin just said quietly...
- Yes.
- We meant that he had done well.
- He said, "You should do better."
- But he wanted him to do better.
- My gosh.
- It was to motivate him...
- to do better as well.
- I'll do better.
- I didn't mean it that way.
- Not me.
- I meant it as a compliment.
- Me too.
You wanted him to do better too.
Be honest with me.
- No, I didn't.
- Be honest with me.
- I'm being honest.
- Hey.
- Be honest.
- I didn't mean it that way.
- I never meant it that way.
- Suk Jin.
- You know what I mean.
- This is the 600th episode.
- It's not like that. Se Chan.
- Did you really mean it like that?
- I didn't.
- I'm serious.
- I never thought that way.
- When he was struggling...
Hey, why are you all over the couch,
you punk?
(Hey, why are you
all over the couch, you punk?)
(Why are you all over the couch?)
"Why are you all over the couch?"
Come on, Suk Jin. What was that?
- Sit up straight.
- I mean, this is our 600th episode.
- Choose your words carefully.
- Why do you always yell at me?
- Gosh, seriously.
- You meant to quit because of me.
I'm shocked that he meant,
"You should do better than this."
I thought he might be discouraged.
It was like, "You can do better."
- "You did well."
- No.
- That's not what you meant.
- "You should do better than this."
You meant it that way too.
- No, I didn't.
- Just admit it so we can move on.
- You put pressure on him.
- You see, I...
- You know I always say...
- "You should do better than this."
- Yes.
- I realized something...
- since I've done many shows...
- That's what showbiz is like.
- with a group of people as a team.
- Right.
- Some people need more time.
- Of course.
And I'm that type of person.
It took me nine years to establish
myself as an entertainer.
- You'd been unknown for so long.
- So...
- That's right.
- When you're unsure about yourself,
your colleagues' cheerful words
keep you going,
- and help you get used to it.
- True.
You become relaxed over time,
and the time comes...
- for you to perform at your best.
- Absolutely.
And you don't know
how long it could take.
- That's true.
- You see,
people had high expectations of him
since he was a comedian,
he was afraid he might not live up
to the expectations just as he said,
- and he needed time to overcome it.
- That's right.
In the beginning,
Se Chan got a lot of criticism.
"Who is he? How can he be paid
for doing that?"
- The viewers left harsh comments.
- Hey.
(Who is he?)
(How can he be paid for doing that?)
(What?)
- Hold on a second.
- Jae Suk.
(Rolling)
- Jae Suk, I'm leaving.
- I can't believe him.
- What was that?
- Jae Suk.
- Calm down.
- How much do I owe you?
I'll give you back the money.
How much?
- Okay.
- I'll pay it and leave.
Jae Suk, I'll pay it and leave.
- How could you hurt his feelings?
- I'll give them back the money.
- Hang on.
- What did you just say?
- That was so mean.
- Hey, what was that?
- You've crossed the line.
- I...
- I'm sorry.
- How could he say such a thing?
- Gosh, seriously.
- I'll give them back the money.
- It's okay.
- Let it go.
- Jae Suk, I'll give it back.
- I'm sorry.
- That was so mean.
- I'll give them back the money.
- You've crossed the line.
- Let's all sit down.
- This is our 600th episode.
- Sit down.
- Hey.
- Anyway...
- "How can he be paid?"
(My head hurts.)
- All right.
- Let me wrap it up.
- Go ahead.
- There was nothing behind me.
- Ji Hyo, why didn't you tell me?
- Jae Suk, I grabbed you,
- but you fell anyway.
- There was nothing behind me.
Anyway, I think you should give back
the amount for two years, right?
No, I think it should be the amount
for three and a half years.
If so, I would have to give back
the amount for seven years.
What I was trying to say was...
There's more? Aren't you done?
- In the end, as we all expected,
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Se Chan did an excellent job.
- He's doing great even now.
- It just took him some time.
You know, Se Chan...
blended into the team so well,
and he's doing great now.
The same goes for So Min.
What are you doing?
I'm going to pop another balloon.
(I'm going to pop another balloon.)
He's not finished yet.
- Goodness.
- We should let Se Chan finish it.
I'd like to applaud
the cast members...
for helping the two of them
blend into the team.
- It's because... To be honest,
- That's random.
- in the showbiz,
- Yes.
a lot of people act mean
toward a new member.
- You were the worst.
You were the meanest of all.
You're the worst, Suk Jin.
- When I said hello to him,
- He was the worst, right?
he said hi halfheartedly
without even looking at me.
- "Okay."
- I mean, seriously...
- People might think that's true.
- At least we had each other.
- We could rely on each other.
- I relied on So Min greatly.
- If it hadn't been for him...
- It would've been harder.
- Indeed.
- That's why...
I want to say something.
It's the same for you, Suk Jin.
- Right. I had a hard time too.
- When he just joined the show,
people said, "Fire him
from the show. What's his problem?"
(When he first joined the show,
people said he should be fired.)
- He went extreme again.
- Calm down.
- Please sit down.
- What's wrong with him?
- I don't know. Please sit.
- I have no idea.
- "How can he get paid for that?"
- There must be more.
- You're the first one to hear that.
- Let go.
- I'm the first member to hear that.
- "He should leave the show."
- And...
- "Give your juniors a chance."
- Exactly.
But Suk Jin overcame it
and pulled it off in the end.
That's right. It doesn't work
without Suk Jin now.
- Right. We can't do it without him.
- Exactly.
- We can't even talk to one another.
- The same goes for everyone.
Right. It's so nice
to have an honest conversation.
- We should do this once in a while.
- Of course.
That's why we were all happy...
- when he won the award.
- It made me want to cry.
- We applauded so excitedly.
- We were so excited for him.
We're celebrating our 600th episode.
- It's been 12 years.
- This is crazy.
- But it's not that our show...
has always been getting
so much attention...
- for the past 12 years.
- It's hard to believe.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- They joined us during a hard time.
- Indeed.
- They went through a lot.
- Let's thank our youngest members.
- Right.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. I love you.
- I love you.
- I love you all.
- We're grateful to you two.
Start crying now.
I might start crying.
- I teared up a little.
- Right?
- I feel like crying.
- We owe it all to you two.
- Ji Hyo will pop another balloon.
- Me?
- Good.
- Okay.
We needed to have
a conversation like this.
- I wish we were having a drink.
- We're all being so honest.
- You see...
- You want a drink?
- Let's do that tonight.
- So Min.
- We're shooting a show.
- Right.
- We can have a deeper conversation.
"Have you ever gone easy on someone
during a game?"
- Go easy on someone?
- What?
- Well...
- Of course.
- To be honest, yes.
- I have.
- In a game.
I'm sure people have cut me
a lot of slack.
I doubt I was ever the one giving.
- The same goes for me as well.
- Me too.
We all went easy on others
at some point.
I'm sure it's the same for everyone.
Going easy on someone
might not sound fair.
It's more like giving them time.
- It's more like this.
- We give them time.
We know someone's a spy,
but revealing it too early
would only kill the show.
- That has been the case for me.
- Of course.
But no one orders us to do so.
- It's an unspoken rule.
- That's right.
- To make a better show.
- But...
Jong Kook never cuts anyone slack.
(Glaring)
This is him going easy on us.
"I know who it is. It's Jae Suk."
- He...
- Hold on a second.
Couldn't you tell
that I was being generous?
During lunch.
(Episode 597: During lunch,
the Mafia had to be arrested.)
(Mafia)
(Okay, I got it.)
(Rather than cutting Jae Suk slack,
he kept cornering him.)
(After saying that...)
Enjoy your meal.
- The Mafia is in this team.
- Which team?
- This one. The red team.
- Why?
- Just enjoy your lunch.
- Why us?
(After suffocating the Mafia,)
(he claims that he cut
Jae Suk some slack.)
- But...
- He let it slide for a few rounds.
Couldn't you tell
that I was being generous?
- You told us to enjoy our meal.
- Exactly.
I told you two to enjoy your meal.
- This is cutting us slack?
- "Don't say anything to them."
- "Don't pressure them."
- This is him cutting us slack?
- "Enjoy your meal."
- "Don't bother guessing."
- I mean...
- But...
- It's stressing me out.
- "Dig in, guys."
- That's cutting us slack?
- Of course.
- The stress.
- You have no idea.
- Did I keep on deducting?
- Unbelievable.
There's something you can do
when you're chosen to play the spy.
- What is it?
- Team up with Jong Kook.
- Once he believes someone...
- Yes, that's true.
He never doubts someone he trusts.
- You're spot on.
- That's a weakness of his.
He protects that person.
- Right.
- That's right.
That's something I easily fall for.
I tried playing him like that
a few times...
and ended up in the doghouse
for about a month.
(Things were awkward between us
for a month.)
"You...
How could you of all people..."
- I remember.
- Our business wasn't doing well.
You know how it was like
during the early days.
- I...
- Ji Hyo, go ahead.
- Right, I remember.
- At first,
I was in his inner circle,
but we fought because of it.
- For real?
- No.
- No, but it upset him.
- Do you remember...
the one with Hades?
Yes, the chairs.
(Episode 463.
They received the same mission.)
(They played games thinking
they were on the same side.)
(Jong Kook betrayed her.)
(Jong Kook turned out to be
a double agent.)
(Ji Hyo was deceived
by Jong Kook...)
(and the betrayal hit Ji Hyo hard.)
I didn't think of it
as a huge betrayal.
Besides, we do
what we're told to do.
That's not all.
During the next game,
I told him a lie
saying I couldn't trust him...
and that set him off.
It's because you kept saying it.
You kept saying
that you couldn't trust me.
I only said that
because I couldn't trust you.
Is this another pepper incident?
- I mean...
- Hold on.
- That's not it.
- The pepper couple.
They're so spicy! The pepper couple!
- Pepper!
- Whatever.
- They're so spicy as always!
- Fine. I'm the one to blame.
I'll apologize, okay?
It's why I said I'd buy you
a big TV if you get married.
- Suk Jin, just stay put.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Get one yourself if you can.
Are you done talking?
- What?
- Why are you asking?
There's something I still remember.
Do you remember
the Sherlock Holmes episode?
Yes, of course.
During the Sherlock Holmes episode,
I remember...
- Is this any good?
- It is.
Yes, of course.
(Quietly)
- Is this any good?
- It is.
I'd like one, then.
Thanks.
Try one.
- Suk Jin, I'm all ears.
- This one's better.
I'm all ears, so go ahead.
- I'm laughing, aren't I?
- Suk Jin...
Just know that I'm slightly annoyed.
(Just know that
I'm slightly annoyed.)
Sometimes, I laugh excessively.
That's when I'm annoyed.
- Suk Jin, I'm all ears.
- Have you had a bite?
Forget it.
I'm not in the mood anymore.
- Go ahead.
- No, it's not funny anymore.
Dig in.
- Just tell us.
- Go on.
- The Sherlock Holmes episode.
Tell us about
the Sherlock Holmes episode.
- Go ahead.
- No, eat in peace.
Can you speak up
when you're told to do so?
You're not the only one
who wants to talk.
I'm at about 20 percent.
- Are you slightly annoyed?
- Yes.
Anyway,
during the Sherlock Holmes episode,
I badly wanted the mission
to be a success.
- You know the feeling, right?
- We were on a ferry.
- You know how it is.
- Of course we do.
I was this close
to completing my mission...
- when Jong Kook came running.
- That's right.
He found my name
written in one of the books.
When he was about
to eliminate me, I said this.
It was probably edited out,
but I said...
"Jong Kook, can't you let me
complete my mission today?"
(Jong Kook, can't you let me
complete my mission today?)
- That's what I said.
- Did you?
- In the most desperate tone.
- I see.
Do you remember that?
I bet you don't.
Were you trying to be funny?
No, I wasn't joking at all.
I desperately wanted to succeed.
You get that feeling sometimes.
Jong Kook was like, "Really?"
I thought he was going
to let me win,
but he removed my name tag.
(He immediately removed
Suk Jin's name tag.)
- After saying, "Really?"...
- How professional of him.
(Episode 79)
(Jong Kook confronted Suk Jin
when he was close to succeeding.)
(He must've asked Jong Kook
to let him win right about now.)
(Removed)
(Jong Kook showed no mercy though.)
(Seok Sam was eliminated
after begging for mercy.)
It's hard for the camera
to capture such nuances.
- That's right.
- Anyway, that's what happened.
I was serious
when I asked him to let me win.
There's actually something
I'd like to say.
It's about the Name Tag Elimination.
- Because it gets physical...
- Exactly.
- You can't help but get emotional.
- I know.
- Don't you agree?
- Of course.
Yes, it gets emotional.
It's a physically challenging game.
It doesn't show on camera, but...
I don't mean that
there were any altercations,
but it can get upsetting at times.
- It's like this.
- It's like ssireum in a way.
You'd be surprised
by how physical it gets.
It's why we had to stay fit...
during the early episodes.
We've mentioned this often,
but the show's in its 12th year.
The reason...
we don't play Name Tag Elimination
isn't because we've aged.
The game entailed
a lot of injuries too.
- Right.
- Yes, many got injured.
For over a decade, we have played...
- so many variations of the game.
- Exactly.
The staff is trying...
to come up with something new,
but it's easier said than done.
It's hard to come up
with a new variation of it.
So...
I don't know
if the viewers will see this,
but the staff came up
with a variation once...
because many viewers commented
that they wanted to see it.
- It resulted in a drop in ratings.
- Right.
Although you asked for it,
- you didn't watch it.
- They didn't.
- Exactly.
- You asked, but that was it.
It's like my YouTube channel.
My subscribers
don't want to watch my videos.
It's the same.
Weird, isn't it?
I'm not saying
we're done with Name Tag Elimination,
but I'd like to point out...
that not playing the game
has nothing to do with our age.
- And...
- That's not the case.
- No, it's not.
- It's not an age thing.
- Of course not.
- To be honest,
we can still compete
with young K-pop idol singers.
- Of course.
- Right?
In our spin-off series,
I don't get eliminated...
even when two of them
come at me. Why?
Because I'm the boss.
They can't remove my name tag.
(Bald kid with superpowers)
- I'm not kidding.
- Haha's strong, you know.
- I've grabbed him before and...
- I'm like a beast.
- Yes, you're strong.
- We know how to play the game.
I'll give you that.
Could Haha have gone easy
on Jong Kook for 12 years?
- I have a bone to pick with you.
- What is it?
Whenever she plays a spy,
she stays in character...
- off-camera.
- That's right.
She does.
- And that...
- Didn't you...
The betrayal hit me hard.
What other choice do I have...
when I need to fool someone
who has been at this for ten years?
That's the only way.
I was upset over
what she did as well.
- It was part of her strategy.
- She hit her chest saying...
- "It really isn't me!"
- Yes, that!
- With tears brimming.
- Right.
I tell her I get it...
and write someone else's name down
only to see her do this.
(Smirking)
And she does this
to the crane camera.
And from behind, we're like...
(The betrayal!)
And then she tells me...
to be a professional about it.
- Just you wait and see.
- Exactly.
You have no idea how...
Guess who I learned it from?
It's horrible to play the spy.
The spy...
- The spy...
- It's my least favorite role.
- Exactly.
- Me too.
- You're playing the main role.
- It's bothersome.
- But the pressure...
- This is what troubles us...
when we have to play spies.
- The other members...
- We can tell.
They easily catch
the subtle behavioral differences.
- So playing the spy...
- We can easily tell.
That makes it hard for us
to play a spy.
- Se Chan, choose a balloon.
- I've already done it.
- Then Suk Jin.
- I'll...
(It's the oldest brother's turn.)
- What about a yellow one?
- A yellow one?
- Get closer to it.
- It can be any one of them.
Why else were we given a dart?
- You need to pick the paper up.
- Get over there.
(He hits 2 with 1 dart.)
(He kills the mood by
popping two balloons.)
What's the matter with you?
I called dibs on the one behind it.
It's all because
you were bothersome.
Unbelievable.
I get to choose, don't I?
- I mean...
- The viewers...
shouldn't chide us
for being too harsh on Suk Jin.
Try playing a game
with him sometime.
Learn it firsthand.
You need to experience it.
- It's a breath of fresh air.
- Get a taste of Suk Jin.
- You don't get to see...
what he does to kill the mood.
- Aren't I awesome?
- It's why parents...
- caned their children.
- See it for yourself.
He kills the mood?
Yes, he kills the mood.
"What names are the other's
numbers saved under?"
- Gosh.
- In my case,
Se Chan's number
is under Yangsebari.
Me too. Yangsebari.
- In my case...
- Ssaebssaeb for me.
- What about you?
- Yang Sechani.
For me, it's Yang Se Chan.
- Yang Se Chan?
- That's cold.
(Just Yang Se Chan)
- Yang Se Chan?
- That's cold.
- It's Yang Sechani for me.
- Me too.
- Yang Se Chan.
- Jeon So Min.
- That's cold.
- Kook Jong for Jong Kook.
- Kim Jong Kook...
- Trainer Kook.
- The younger.
- The younger?
- For me, it's...
Is there a Kim Jong Kook
who's older than you?
Yes, and I get confused at times.
Yoo Jae Suk for Jae Suk.
Song Ji Hyo and Haha.
Unbelievable.
How is this not business for him?
There are no words of affection.
That is what's written
on our name tags.
You're right!
But...
In Jong Kook's case...
You're the worst.
Apart from
"The younger Kim Jong Kook,"
- it's just your names.
- For those who I'm close to,
I always stick to nicknames.
- It's Ho Sae Carlos for Sae Ho.
- Carlos?
Jeonsobari,
Kook Jong,
Zoned-out Ji Hyo, and Heehee.
Heehee...
He keeps calling me Heehee.
What about me?
Yangsebari for Se Chan.
The feeble Ji Seok Sam.
That's too long.
(The feeble Ji Seok Sam)
- No wonder you called me that.
- Right.
- The feeble Ji Seok Sam.
"Bixby, call
the feeble Ji Seok Sam."
"All right. I'll connect you to
I saved you with that name for that.
- How did you save us on your phone?
- I saved them a long time ago.
I saved Haha as Haha.
I saved Ji Hyo, Jae Suk,
and Suk Jin with their names.
As for Jong Kook,
I saved him as Romantic Punch.
- I must save him with that.
- I understand.
Why did you name him that?
I bet you remember.
- We made nicknames for each other.
- Right, I do.
I thought Romantic Punch...
- made Jong Kook sound really cool.
- It does sound cool.
- So I...
- They neutralize each other.
- So I saved him as Romantic Punch.
- I see. Romantic Punch.
- I like that.
- Right? Romantic Punch.
- How did you save us, Ji Hyo?
- Right. I'm curious.
- I'm curious to know.
- I'm curious too.
I saved Se Chan by Yang Sechani.
Big Brother Suk Jin,
Ms. Jeon So Min,
- Miss?
- Ms. Jeon So Min?
- That's understandable.
- That sounds distant.
- Ms. Jeon So Min.
- What else?
Brother Kim Jong Kook.
Big Brother Jae Suk
and Big Brother Haha.
Why did you save everyone else
as Big Brother except Jong Kook?
- You're right.
- You saved me as Brother Jong Kook.
- That's funny.
- You even included his surname.
Did I save you
as Big Brother as well?
- I bet you did.
- No, I bet it's just Brother.
They mean the same thing.
I'll save him as Brother Pepper.
(Brother Pepper)
- That sounds good.
- Brother Pepper.
They're so spicy!
- The pepper couple!
- Pepper!
Just save me as Brother Pepper.
Brother Pepper sounds good.
- What about you, So Bal?
- I save Haha as Prince Haha.
- My goodness. Why is that?
- Why did you save him as Prince?
- I saved Ji Hyo as Jeoktoma.
- Jeoktoma?
- Jeoktoma? That sounds about right.
- I recently changed yours.
- To what?
- It was Big Brother Yoo Jae Suk,
but I changed it
to Big Brother Yoo Frivolous.
Big Brother Yoo Frivolous?
- I like it.
- It sounds off.
- And I save him as Brother X.
- What about me?
- Brother X?
- Why Brother X though?
- It suits him.
- Because he has that image.
- He's a mysterious friend.
- I do have that vibe.
- He's reliable, that's why.
- I had that vibe in school.
As for Suk Jin, I saved him
as Whatever Seok Sam.
- Whatever Seok Sam?
- I saved him as Whatever Seok Sam.
(Whatever Seok Sam)
- It suits him.
- Whatever Seok Sam.
- He's Ssaebssaeb.
- Whatever Seok Sam is hilarious.
- Whatever Seok Sam.
- Whatever Seok Sam is...
- Whatever Seok Sam!
- You recently changed the name.
- I did.
It sounds like a menu.
Three Whatever Seok Sam, please.
Here are three Whatever Seok Sam.
Three Whatever Seok Sam Combo,
please.
What did you save us as, Jong Kook?
For Haha, it's Ha Donghooni.
Yang Sechani,
- Jeon Somini.
- Jeon Somini?
- Ji Seokjini?
(You saved me as Ji Seokjini?)
- Jeon Somini.
- Jeon Somini?
(He just saved Suk Jin by his name
when he's older?)
Ji Seokjini.
- Tell me.
- He saved Jae Suk as Yoo Jaeseoki.
- No.
- "Genie."
- I saved him as Brother Suk Jin.
- Brother Suk Jin.
As for Jae Suk...
- It's not "Younger Bro", is it?
- No, it's not.
- I saved him as Jae Seuk.
- Oh, Jae Seuk?
- What about her?
- What about Ji Hyo?
- She's saved as Zoned-out.
- Zoned-out?
- That's it?
- Just Zoned-out?
- It's just 1 word?
- Isn't there more?
- Like what?
Lovely...
Isn't there more?
(The romance fan teases Jong Kook
with his life at stake.)
- A heart after Zoned-out?
- Like what?
- Yes, a heart after Zoned-out.
- Gosh, I'm dying to say it.
My Heart Will Be Bruised
If I Don't See You.
(My Heart Will Be Bruised
If I Don't See You)
My Heart Will Be Bruised
If I Don't See You.
(It looks like he's willing
to risk his life today as well.)
That's...
(It's the last question.)
This is so fun.
"Now that Running Man
is at its 600th episode,"
"how would you like
the show to go on?"
It's a difficult question.
I couldn't even imagine that we'd
make it to the 600th episode.
- We couldn't.
- I never thought it'd be possible.
- I couldn't imagine it either.
- I actually saw the end of it too.
Many talked about the show
getting canceled in our first year.
We must mention this.
The YouTube clips of our show
started garnering popularity.
- A collection of funny moments.
- The memes.
- That's when it became popular?
I don't know who edited
all our clips,
but we should meet them
and show our gratitude.
- They were really witty.
- They only collected funny scenes.
- Right.
- The viewers went,
"Seeing a collection of it,
Running Man seems pretty fun."
They said it was hilarious.
And we got to see their reactions too.
We learned
what the viewers found most fun.
- We applied those in our shows.
- It gave us directions.
It did give us directions.
I like that we try new approaches.
But I wish we could show
the mature chemistry...
that a show with 600 episodes
and 10 years of experience can.
I wish our show looks less set up.
It could be even rougher.
And the viewers could think,
"They can say such things
because it's Running Man."
"It's only possible
I mentioned this
during the meetings,
but I think all the content we make
is original.
I don't think we must do missions...
- or have twists.
- Whatever we do?
And that there should be spies.
We could open a business if we want.
Then it'd be the same
as the other show.
Are you talking about
"Unexpected Business?"
- No, it's not that.
- Then you should meet up...
with Producer Na Yeong Seok.
You want to be
on "Grandpas over Flowers?"
I told you that whatever we do
will be original.
You want to be
on "Grandpas over Flowers?"
Actually, I want to make a complaint
to the "Infinite Challenge" team.
- So suddenly?
- I suddenly had that thought.
- It's canceled.
- The old "Infinite Challenge?"
I'm sorry if this might offend
the fans of "Infinite Challenge."
The show
lasted over a decade, right?
- It did.
- They tried different challenges...
- every week.
- We did all sorts of things.
They did all they could on a show.
In a way, Running Man...
- is suffering because of them.
- I'm sorry,
but you said everything we do
will be original.
This is why I brought it up.
So instead of coming up
with new content... I mean we could,
but with "Infinite Challenge"...
You want to copy their ideas?
You want to steal their ideas?
You're saying we only need
to change the names, right?
So in conclusion...
You want to copy them?
In other words,
he wants to plagiarize them.
Please take back your words.
- He wants to copy them!
- Please take back your words.
You mean you want to
plagiarize them.
I'll take back my words
and put them back in here.
How did he get dragged into this?
He said he wanted to copy them.
But "Infinite Challenge"...
To be honest,
you guys did everything
so there's nothing new to try.
- I'm sure there's more.
- That's not true.
We could change it up a little
and use their ideas.
What do you think, Ji Hyo?
Our show's been going on
for 12 years, right?
If you think about it,
we've done everything we could.
Are you saying
we should quit the show?
I thought
that's what she was saying.
She suddenly went,
- "We've been working for 12 years."
- "We've done everything we could."
"Maybe it's for the best
if we stop here."
If you think about it,
we've done everything.
So the production crew...
- must suffer a lot...
- I agree.
in their meetings every week.
- Of course.
- They're really amazing.
- Our production crew.
- That's what I often think.
If we were to come up
with new items,
I can't think of any.
So the production crew...
- She's saying...
- Just say you're out of ideas.
- She just beat around the bush...
- She beat around the bush.
to say that she can't
think of any new ideas.
- But I have pride in our show.
- Seriously...
- It's a game variety show...
- That's right.
It's the only one in Korea.
I agree with what Haha said.
We must continue
the game variety show...
- That's our pride.
- and make opportunities for others.
It's not that we're only
maintaining our places.
I'm sure our show
can expand the horizon...
and more variety show stars
should be born...
so that the world of variety shows
can grow.
That must be why a game variety show
must continue.
We'll work hard
to make every episode...
with our production crew
with that mindset.
Part One ended with sincere
answers from the members.
- It's already over?
- Yes.
- So you've secured 6,000 dollars.
(They secured 6,000 dollars
for donation.)
Of course we should.
It's time to pick the winner
of Part One.
Actually, it must be hard to pick
the winner...
since everyone was sincere.
But you must pick
the best member among yourselves.
- Who should I pick?
- It's so hard to pick one.
We did prepare ballots.
Let's just spin a roulette.
This is meaningless.
Why don't you just
spin a roulette for us?
- Everyone answered sincerely.
- That's right.
Then play rock-paper-scissors
and decide.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- But Suk Jin wasn't sincere.
That's true.
Suk Jin wasn't sincere.
I was sincere!
What's wrong with you?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Suk Jin, you should join too.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Come on.
- The three of them won.
Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
- All right!
(Seok Sam wins.)
What was that?
He was the most...
Right.
The favorite of Part One
is Suk Jin.
(The favorite to win Part 1
is Suk Jin.)
It's time to pick
the candidate to receive a penalty.
It could be a hard decision,
but the staff members...
will stick the face of the member
on a panel and show it.
- What if the favorite to win...
- They could get the penalty.
It doesn't matter. They can overlap.
- That could happen.
That could happen.
Everyone, please stick their faces.
(The vote begins.)
- Everyone is like...
- Let's see.
They're all looking for Suk Jin's face.
They're all working hard to find it.
They're all like,
"Which one is Suk Jin's?"
"Where is Suk Jin's face?"
You're all looking
for Suk Jin's face.
You're all looking for him.
- They're all looking for him.
- Don't say such things.
They're like,
"Where is Suk Jin's face?"
- They're all looking for him.
- Why would you say such things?
- "Where is Suk Jin's face?"
- They all love Suk Jin so much.
- Why would you say that?
- They were all like...
- "Where is Suk Jin's face?"
- We're just saying things...
that we heard.
- It's hilarious.
- It'd be funny.
They all agreed to pick honestly.
Of course.
- Please be honest.
- Show us who you picked.
In 1, 2, 3.
It's Suk Jin.
(They all picked Suk Jin.)
(Suk Jin's face is everywhere.)
It's Suk Jin!
- It's an overwhelming result.
- So many of you picked me.
They all picked Suk Jin.
Are you all here
to create his fan club?
- I know.
- I guess I'm...
- So many picked Suk Jin.
- It looks like many of them...
picked me.
Suk Jin is the winner
and loser of Part One.
Thank you!
- You can take it all!
- I'm truly grateful.
It's like having his wish come true.
He's taking all the airtime
for the 600th episode.
- He's the hottest one here.
- He's a greedy one.
- He's so popular.
- I'm jealous though.
- He's greedy.
- It's time for Part Two.
Let's gather again
after getting changed.
- Okay!
(Now it's time to enjoy Part 2,
which will be more exciting.)
(Running Man)
Gosh, this is nice.
There's a panel.
- What is it?
- You're right.
- What could it be?
- Why...
- Why are you wearing hanbok?
- Why am I the only one in hanbok?
Why is she wearing hanbok alone?
I have no idea!
- They suddenly told me to wear it!
- Is it a mission or what?
- It's not New Year's.
- You're a spy, aren't you?
- You're a spy.
- No, I'm not!
Why is So Min wearing hanbok?
I went inside to change,
but they told me to wear this.
There's a reason
why she's wearing hanbok.
I told you earlier that this episode
would be joined by the viewers.
They not only left comments...
but also gave us outstanding ideas.
Ideas?
We picked the one that was
most recommended.
We thought it'd be nice
to give it a try.
- Is that so?
- We screen-captured the comment.
- What is it?
- Is that so?
Let's see.
What could it be?
(The idea from a viewer
that was most recommended)
"I want to see the members..."
"acting differently
from the usual image they have."
"Jae Suk
who brags about his wealth,"
- "Se Chan who goes to SNU,"
- Gosh.
- "super popular Ji Hyo,"
- "Super popular Ji Hyo."
"a paper-doll-like Jong Kook,"
"So Min with courtesy in hanbok,"
"Suk Jin who is interested
in the members,"
"and Haha who loves
Running Man the most."
- I do love Running Man the most!
- "And Haha..."
(Haha who loves Running Man
the most is brought back.)
They want us to act differently
from the usual image we have!
Username yuws!
How could you say that?
- You're quite witty.
- This is...
- I love this show the most!
- This is really difficult.
Jae Suk who brags about his wealth?
Jae Suk who brags about his wealth.
- The number of likes...
- I like it.
It received 8,800 likes
when we screen-captured that.
"Se Chan who goes to SNU?"
- SNU? That's impossible.
- This is incredible.
Let me give you
an additional explanation.
You'll be carrying out
the missions in Part Two...
with the theme that was
assigned to each one of you.
As for Jae Suk,
you can just show off your wealth.
- Okay.
- It doesn't sound easy.
As for Ji Hyo,
you're the most popular member
and the leader of this group.
- You're the most popular one here.
- The brightest one.
- You have to lead everything.
- You need to talk a lot too.
- You need to act silly too.
- Something like, "Quiet, everyone."
- A super popular one.
- She'll be hosting the meeting.
- That's right.
- Use trending expressions also.
- You must appeal your hip side.
- "Let's get started."
Let's get started. Bombastic!
(Acting like a popular kid)
- That's it.
- You need to say it faster.
You must listen to what Ji Hyo says.
- Skrr
- Respect!
All right, now. Bombastic!
- Hey.
- This isn't how it goes?
It sounds like you're pressing us.
- Don't say that.
- As for Se Chan,
he's always scholarly,
- and...
- You're telling him to keep quiet.
he uses many big vocabs.
You want me to use
four-letter idioms, right?
This is the most difficult mission
for Se Chan.
I have a question.
They're telling me
that I have no courtesy, right?
I'm not sure what they intended
to tell you.
You can't speak in that tone.
- Oh, okay.
- You can't speak in that tone.
Bombastic.
- She's a girl with courtesy.
- Bombastic.
(Modest)
Let's all work hard for this mission
as per the idiom, hyeongseoljigong.
So in Part Two,
you can increase the donation
to 10,000 dollars through missions.
Is that so?
You must remain in character
that you were given...
while carrying out the missions,
and you'll pick the best
and worst members afterward.
That will decide the winner
and a member who'll get a penalty.
Goodness,
you planned this really well.
I bet "How Do You Play?"
couldn't even come up with such a theme.
"How Do You Play?", you're just...
Running Man is indeed the best.
Running Man is way better
than "How Do You Play?"
- Bombastic!
- What does that even mean?
- What does it mean?
- It's just an expression.
- The first mission...
- Yes?
- is Captain Ji's cooking class...
that the viewers wanted to see
the most.
- Yes!
- Gosh.
(Captain Ji's cooking class)
(The reason they're holding
his cooking class for episode 600)
(Captain Ji proposed to hold
a class and make cookies.)
(But he was met with strong resistance,
so it was canceled.)
(But he continued
to show his love for cookies.)
(Why won't they hold the cooking class?
I want to see it.)
(It's a shame that you didn't
show Captain Ji's cooking class.)
(The viewers strongly supported
Suk Jin's cooking class.)
(So the cooking class
was miraculously brought back.)
- Hey.
- I love it.
No! We shouldn't do it
for the sake of Running Man.
Suk Jin's talent will show itself,
as per the idiom, nangjungjichu.
- Just do it if they tell you to.
- I love it.
- Don't push me.
- Don't you want to see it? Hey!
Don't push me, Suk Jin.
- Why you little punk...
- Don't push me.
- Seriously...
- Why is he so violent?
- Hey!
- Come on, Suk Jin.
Stay out of this, will you?
You might dislocate my shoulder
at this rate!
(So Min gives a big bow
out of nowhere.)
(She expresses her regret
with a big bow.)
There you go. She's so polite.
Your remark has a hidden meaning,
as per the idiom, unjungyugol.
Is that how you use it?
All right. You'll make 1,000 dollars
from making cookies.
That means we'll just give you
1,000 dollars if you make cookies.
- Mr. Producer?
- Yes?
The 1,000 dollars...
(Scoffing)
- I don't know.
- Will you pay for it?
- What about 1,000 dollars?
- I mean...
Do we have to do this
just for 1,000 dollars?
Must we watch
Suk Jin's cooking class?
Can't you just pay them
to edit this out?
- Gosh.
- Let's just have fun.
- I do not want to attend it.
- Please spend your money.
I think 20,000 dollars will do.
Must we watch
Suk Jin's cooking class?
- Do we have to?
- Everyone, gather up!
Hey! Hold on!
Se Chan is going to...
spell the word, "cookie."
All right!
Cookie?
- It's simple!
- Go ahead.
Tell us the spelling
of "cookie" first.
- It must begin with a C.
- That's right.
- So it's C...
- C!
- O!
Oh, yes.
- K!
- It's a K already?
- That's not right!
- Okay, let's sit!
Okay! He's so funny.
- My gosh.
- You should be knowledgeable...
- to make jokes.
- Guys, bombastic.
I hate learning things the most.
The viewers really wanted
to see the cooking class.
Really? You wanted to see
my cooking class?
Everyone, please wear your mask.
Wear your mask
as you'll make cookies too.
There's a bib too.
Here's the thing about cookies.
The reason I began making them...
- Guys, bombastic!
- Don't tell us such things.
Just shut your mouth
and teach us how to make it.
- You want me to shut my mouth?
- It's like nakhwayusu!
- Why would he mention his wife?
- I don't even know what it means.
- How do I put this on?
- All right.
How do I...
He can't even put on an apron.
How will he teach us?
- Jong Kook!
- Yes!
Come here and put this on for me.
- I'm supposed to be the weak one.
- How do I put this on?
- That's right.
- Just put it on for me.
- You want me to beat you?
- But I'm not a pushover.
- How do I put this on?
- This?
Put it on me. How do I do it?
Isn't it weird?
- You should just...
- How do I put this on?
- Is this how it's done?
- Give it to me.
How do I...
- That's it. That's how you do it.
- Like this?
- Hey.
- Is this how you do it?
- It's too much.
- I'm not sure.
- Why you little...
- All right. How do I do it?
- It's strange.
- How did you put yours on, Ji Hyo?
You must square C
and subtract from it.
- Square C and subtract from it.
- Square C and subtract from it?
Then subtract its square root.
- Subtract the square root of C.
- How do I put this on?
Then you'll get the value of X.
- Oh, the value of X?
- You need to subtract it.
Since it's the square root
of B plus...
So that's how it works.
(The math genius' formula
was of great help.)
Everyone, follow after me.
There's a scale in front of you, right?
- Yes.
- Turn that on.
- How do I turn it on?
- Put that on before turning it on.
Make the weight into 0g
by putting the beaker on.
Get the oatmeal powder. Guys!
- Hey!
- Yes?
- Add the oatmeal powder.
- When? Now?
Yes, just add it now.
Just follow along.
Press the on button.
- Do I press it?
- Press it.
- Also...
- Make it into 0g.
What does he want us
to do with the oatmeal powder?
Wait a minute. This isn't right.
- This is hard.
- This is only 140g?
That's 140g?
- How big is this? It's 5kg.
- It is 140g.
It is 140g.
It's filled up to the line.
- How much do you want us to add?
- Add 140g of oatmeal powder.
How come it's only this much?
It's strange.
- Gosh, Suk Jin...
- Suk Jin, look what happened.
This is my 140g.
- What's going on?
- What?
Only the beaker alone is over 100g.
- No, it can't be.
- How do I do it?
He doesn't know anything.
What are we supposed to add to this?
- The thing is...
- To this?
- What do you want us to add?
- How troublesome.
Are you all following?
- No, not yet.
- No, I'm not following.
(A dogmatic class that
no one can follow)
Why are we shooting
a video for YouTube...
when we haven't secured
enough airtime?
Hey, this isn't for YouTube.
What do we do now?
- Mix it like this.
- Is this supposed to be granola?
- Like this?
- Do it like this.
You'll be surprised by what you see.
(The students of a class making cookies
they'll be surprised to see)
- You'll be surprised?
- Are you done?
You'll be surprised by it.
- You'll be surprised by its taste.
- We'll be surprised?
Hey, it'll be incredible.
I forgot to add sugar!
- Sorry?
- Bo Pil.
I'm telling you this
out of my love for Running Man.
Let's just come up
with something new.
(Let's just come up
with something new.)
I can't stand it anymore!
I can't let
Running Man go down like this!
Quit this already.
If you love Running Man,
quit the cooking class.
All right. You should mix it.
(They're done making cookies.)
(We quickly edited out
the cooking class...)
(out of love for Running Man.)
We're playing a game.
Is it human bowling?
- I know.
- Do we have to jump...
- and hit the pins?
- This is new.
- Is it soft?
- It is.
I'm not good at games like this.
Everyone.
This is the 2nd mission of Part 2.
Every member has to complete
the same mission.
It's called
Comfort from Being Motionless.
(Second mission,
Comfort from Being Motionless)
You'll each give it a go.
You'll land after you jump.
You need to have more than
seven pins intact in total.
- Seven pins?
- You'll get an extra 1,000 dollars...
if you leave seven pins intact.
If you fail,
you'll lose 1,000 dollars.
- But it's hard.
- Do we get only one chance?
Yes, you can go only one time.
So each one of us
can knock down only one.
- That's right.
- Is this even possible?
Won't all of them be knocked down?
- Would you like to practice?
- They'll all be knocked down.
- We should land far.
- Let's practice.
Comfort from Being Motionless.
- So this is how it goes?
- This is how it goes.
- But they all get knocked down.
- With both your feet and hands.
- This isn't easy.
- You shouldn't make them fall.
- Let's all practice.
- Let's give it a go.
(It's time for Suk Jin's practice.)
We should jump from there.
No!
(Falling)
(They're all knocked down.)
- That's just...
- Suk Jin.
- You were meant to make them fall.
- That was...
Give it a go.
(Jong Kook goes next.)
- My gosh.
- He made all of them fall.
This isn't easy at all.
(It's a difficult mission
for Jong Kook as well.)
Here we go.
Wouldn't it be better
to do it barefoot?
- No.
- Hey, you punk!
No, you can't do that.
Hey, do you do this
on "How Do You Play?" as well?
Do you have a death wish?
- What did you say?
- Do you have a death wish?
(Do you have a death wish?)
Oh, right. I forgot.
(He can't get used
to being a weakling.)
So Min.
- She is so polite.
- How is she so polite?
- My goodness.
- She is incredible.
She is so ladylike.
Which family is that lady from?
I feel like I am jumping
into the Insangsu Sea.
Will you be able
to jump in that skirt?
(Shim Chong who is jumping
into the Indangsu Sea)
I guess it doesn't matter.
- She is so polite.
- I guess it doesn't matter.
My goodness.
- All right.
I landed very lightly.
- Se Chan, give it a go.
- I landed very lightly.
He is strong
when his feet are on the ground.
- Okay.
- You should have succeeded.
- I got the hang of it.
- Don't land on one foot.
- Land on two feet.
- That would be better.
You need to land at the end.
- Gently.
- You need to land gently.
Put your hands on the mattress
after you land.
Gently.
(They finally succeed
in saving 3 bowling pins.)
- He is good.
- That's how you do it.
People who are good at this
should go first.
- Let's do our best.
- Let's practice one time each.
Let's give it a go.
(Suk Jin practices
to keep the momentum going.)
Gently.
Not bad.
- I saved one.
- All right.
- I think we will succeed.
- We will be able to save seven.
Boombastic, give it a go.
Boombastic.
She will do better.
You...
- Can't you jump?
- What was that?
She is a popular member indeed.
- It seems like...
- That was an original method.
she can't move her body
as she wants.
It's better to land on two feet.
I got the hang of it.
So seven bowling pins in total
need to remain standing.
There you go.
(A clean success)
- Grasshopper.
- There you go.
That's how you do it.
(Grasshopper got the hang of it.)
- He is really good.
- He is good.
- You do this at home, right?
- Just keep 1 standing.
- It's my 1st time.
Just keep one standing?
Let's do five.
They asked us to do seven
since they underestimated us.
- It's easier to do 5.
- Is it easier to do 5?
- That's right.
- So it's harder to do more.
- We need to keep them standing.
- This is confusing.
- Say that you will do 10.
- Let's do 10.
All right. Jae Suk should go first.
Jae Suk is really good.
- We need to save seven or more.
- Yes. Jae Suk, go ahead.
- Let's do a cheer.
- Let's go.
- Ji Hyo, go first.
- Give it a go.
- Here comes the popular member.
- Boombastic.
Skrr
Gosh, I am scared. I am nervous.
- Don't be scared.
- Land on two feet.
Go.
(Ji Hyo didn't succeed once
during practice.)
You can jump over it.
She failed.
- What?
- That's it.
She failed.
- What?
- That's it.
- All right. There you go, Ji Hyo.
- Three.
(She succeeded in saving 3!)
(Ji Hyo saved 3 from the start!)
- Three.
- There you go, Ji Hyo.
- She did well.
- Three.
- Three. She saved many pins.
- You did well, Ji Hyo.
- You succeeded.
- It will end soon.
- Jae Suk, let's end it.
- Do it.
There is no need to prolong it.
So Min.
- So Min.
- Will I be able to do it?
- You can even bow, So Min.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Don't be pressured.
- We are good at this.
(The current number of pins)
Land gently.
There you go. That's it.
(She isn't very athletic.
Will she succeed this time?)
Land gently.
There you go. That's it.
Well done.
- It wasn't easy to jump.
- Good.
- Good job.
It won't work
if you land on one foot.
You saved three so far.
Should I go next?
Okay. Should I go next?
He got this.
All right.
(He totally failed.)
(Jong Kook failed in the end.)
- He failed.
- I couldn't land gently.
Jong Kook is definitely strong.
- Suk Jin, let's finish it.
- Seok Sam.
- Suk Jin, finish it.
- Okay. This is nothing.
Will it end if Suk Jin saves five?
It will end.
Should I save five?
I think he will succeed.
(Suk Jin did pretty well
during practice.)
(How will he do this time?)
He landed too strongly.
He succeeded.
It's okay.
- He succeeded.
- Two.
- Did he succeed?
- He saved two pins.
- Is it over?
- We need to save two more.
- How many?
- Two more.
We are in trouble.
- We have Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes. Jae Suk will succeed.
- All right.
- Gosh.
- Two pins remain.
- You should finish it.
I will have to try it
and see what happens.
- You will succeed.
- It won't be easy.
- I think you will succeed.
- You will succeed.
- Do it with seriousness.
(It has been a while
since he became an ace member.)
Do it with seriousness.
(Will he succeed and live up
to people's expectations?)
Why did you do that?
(Falling)
- No way.
- For goodness' sake.
You always tremble
when you receive the spotlight.
- Why were you so nervous?
- Why did you do that?
- What was that?
- You did well before.
- You succeeded earlier.
- You did so well before.
You always act like this
when you receive the spotlight.
- You failed.
- Why were you so nervous?
- Hey.
- I didn't say, "Here I go."
Two remaining members
need to save three pins.
Se Chan and Haha,
you need to succeed.
- I will go.
- They can do it.
Save one each.
- Yes.
- This puts pressure on them.
This puts pressure on them indeed.
- Jump gently.
- Gently.
Jump like a frog.
I think he will succeed.
- Jump like a frog.
- I think he will succeed.
Two pins?
(Did he save 2 pins?)
- Gosh.
- One.
(He saved 1 pin.)
- Haha.
- What now?
Haha needs to save two or more.
- You need to save 2.
- Haha needs to save 2.
- Do it out of love for the show.
- Love for Running Man.
- Dream is watching.
- Hey.
- Haha, save 2.
- Save 2.
- Do it out of love for the show.
- Now is your moment.
- Dream is watching.
- Two or more.
You just need to save one or more.
Okay. One or more.
- One?
- Save one.
- One or more.
- Let's go.
- Show us your true love.
- That's right, Haha.
Let's go.
- True love for Running Man.
- Show us how much you love it.
- That's right.
- Please.
I love it the most.
It's the most precious.
Look at him. He is so serious.
What are you saying?
- He loves it the most.
- I love Running Man.
(I love Running Man!)
Give me a break.
(Will he be able to prove
his love for Running Man?)
Gently.
(He just needs to save one!)
(It's a strike.)
- That was so funny.
- Your love for the show...
- crumbled.
- Hey.
I thought you had succeeded,
but the last one swayed and fell.
- They fell like dominoes.
- It was so funny.
It was so funny.
- We were so close.
- All right.
- You don't love the show.
- We were so close.
- I love it.
- It was so funny.
- It was like a cartoon.
In any case, you failed.
It's time for the last mission.
- It's too bad.
- Before we do that,
please pick a member
who represents Running Man.
- A representative?
- Yes.
- Jae Suk.
- Why me?
- Just do it.
- It's you.
- It's easier that way.
Let's begin the next mission.
- Okay.
- The representative.
- What does the position involve?
- It probably isn't a good thing.
- I agree.
- That's why I picked Jae Suk.
- I know.
What does the position involve?
Do we need to play table tennis?
- I love table tennis.
- Table tennis?
I love table tennis.
- Suk Jin, you are good.
- Of course.
- The cookies are ready.
- Really?
- Let's eat cookies.
- Will they be tasty?
- You made them.
Taste them.
Let's try them.
Be honest and tell us
how the cookies taste.
- This is mine. A person.
- They smell like...
- fried chicken.
- Mine disappeared.
- They smell like fried chicken.
They are supposed to cool down.
- Mine is crooked.
- Is this mine?
Let's eat.
- Here.
- They are supposed to cool down.
Why is it so bitter?
It's hot.
- What is this?
(Everyone expresses the taste
with a grimace.)
- The taste...
- Why is it bitter?
Everyone, I understand how you feel.
- I think it tastes a bit bad too.
- It tastes like...
- burnt puffed rice.
- I think it's burnt.
You said your mother-in-law
asked you where you bought it.
She loves it.
But it needs to cool down first.
- It's bad because it's hot.
- It tastes horrible.
It tastes bad.
- Who would eat this?
- It didn't come out well, but...
- It's the smell.
- It's too bitter.
I won't eat it.
I am sorry. I will put them aside.
- I am sorry.
- I want to eat more.
I think these cookies are delicious.
- You won't eat more, right?
- Seriously.
- They taste incredible.
- You won't eat more, right?
- They are healthy cookies.
- They taste bad.
All right.
Is it going to end like this?
- It's okay.
- I can't believe it.
I know you secretly think
that they are tasty.
All right. With this mission,
you can win 2,000 dollars
for donation.
- Okay.
- That's great.
- It's the last mission.
- Okay.
The representative,
Jae Suk is the key to this mission.
It's Fly Like a Butterfly
and Sting Like a Bee.
(Fly Like a Butterfly
and Sting Like a Bee)
Hit a ping pong ball...
and blow out the candle
that is at the end of the table.
- It will be hard.
- How am I supposed to do that?
- He gets multiple tries, right?
- It will be hard.
You will have enough time
to practice.
Say "Here I go" before you begin.
The number of ping pong balls
Jae Suk will receive...
- depends on other members.
- Why?
Other members
will stand on the stage...
and hit the ball once each
in a relay.
The number of times they succeed
will be the number of balls.
You need to hit the ball
in succession.
Where?
The stage.
This isn't the stage.
- That's the stage.
- We will each hold a racket...
- and go, "1, 2, 3."
- Jae Suk.
- Yes.
- I got it.
- Not like that.
- Jae Suk, hit this.
- This is the last mission.
- Hit this.
- Here is the thing.
- Hit the hand.
- Hit this.
- This is the last mission.
- Here is the thing.
- Hit the hand.
You did it.
- Here is the thing.
- Hit the hand.
(Bullseye)
You did it. That's how you do it.
Do it again.
It will be amazing
if you succeed right away.
No. It was too strong.
(The candle appears.)
- That's the height.
- It will be too hard.
Send the ball here.
You did it. You will succeed.
(He hits the target at once.)
It counts if you hit the candle
and have it go out.
Shake it.
(He begins to practice
with the lit-up candle.)
Gosh.
This is too hard.
Six.
(It's the master level
of difficulty.)
Gosh.
This is too hard.
(He keeps missing.)
Send the ball here.
(Suk Jin comes to help.)
All right.
(Faltering)
The flame will go out
if the ball brushes past it.
- I think Jae Suk is nervous.
- Hit it lightly.
Broaden the range.
There you go. Hit it like that.
- I don't think it will work.
- It will be hard.
- The candle is too small.
- Keep trying.
(The ping pong ball keeps going
to different places.)
- Jae Suk.
- It isn't working.
It's okay. You will find the aim.
There you go. Find the aim that way.
(Despite dozens of practice rounds,
he hasn't put out the candle once.)
Wait.
I feel like I am training
with my coach before the Olympics.
Come on. You can do it.
You can do it, Jae Suk.
Send the ball here.
(It's like a training center.)
Here.
That was too hard.
- Hold on.
- That was too high.
Imagine hitting my face.
(Coach Ji has
a unique training method.)
(Ouch!)
Suk Jin, it's working.
Imagine hitting my nose.
(The ball brushed
against the flame.)
There you go.
There you go. You are getting there.
(Coach Ji's training method
is effective.)
(The ball hits the candle.)
It came at my nose.
(Thanks to Coach Ji,
he starts to get the hang of it.)
You are almost there.
I am getting there.
You got this.
Let's do it here.
Pick up the balls.
Okay. Let's pick up the balls.
- Pick up the balls.
- Pick them up.
(The members come and support him.)
It's a ruckus.
You got this.
Let's try again.
(Charging complete)
Why don't you hold it with one hand?
- Okay.
- This is hard.
- It isn't easy.
- Think about the beginning.
I am trying.
- If he succeeds by chance...
- It hit the candle.
The flame should have gone out.
- It might not work.
- You are right.
Seriously.
(It touches the flame slightly.)
It touched the flame two times.
It doesn't go out
even when it's hit by the ball.
- Seriously.
- It needs to hit the wicker.
It needs to hit the wicker.
It hit the candle.
- It still didn't go out.
- Seriously.
It needs to hit the wicker.
(The ball hit the tip of the candle.)
It hit the candle.
- It still didn't go out.
- Seriously.
I guess it needs to press the flame.
- You did it.
- It went out.
(The candle went out
for the first time.)
That doesn't count.
- Doesn't it count?
- It counts.
I guess you need to hit the body.
- Hit the body.
- Yes.
Hit the end of the body.
You need to tip it over.
Hit the end.
Hit the body.
(Blowing)
It went out.
(The two kids joke around,
but Jae Suk stays serious.)
- It went out.
- There you go.
(He succeeds again!)
There you go. That's how you do it.
- All right.
- Give it a go. I bet you can do it.
- You can do it.
- That's right.
I think you can do it.
- It hit the candle.
- There you go.
Aim for the end. There you go.
It hit the wicker just now.
You got this.
That's good. You got this.
- Jae Suk, let's give it a go.
- You are nearly there.
Shall we decide on
the number of balls now?
- Let's do that.
- We can keep going, right?
That's right.
Give me as many balls as you can.
Say, "Here we go."
- Let's go.
- One, two, three.
- Here we go.
- Go.
- All right.
- Go 1st?
- Why don't you go 1st?
- Haha.
- Keep your racket flat.
- Keep it flat.
- Do you want to go first?
- Go first.
- Keep your racket flat.
- So Min.
- There you go.
- That's it.
- Okay.
- How do I do it?
- Send it up.
- Just send it up.
Send it up.
- Don't try to pass it.
- Send it up.
There you go.
- Don't try to pass it.
- Send it up.
(Ji Hyo, So Min,)
(Jong Kook, Suk Jin)
- Okay.
- Six. Take it.
- Take it.
- Seven.
- Anyone.
- Eight.
(They hit it 8 times.)
That's good.
(Ji Hyo,)
(So Min,)
(Jong Kook, Suk Jin, Haha)
(It's Suk Jin's turn.)
It's my turn.
Stop.
It was my turn.
(The relay ends
because of Se Chan's mistake.)
- It was my turn. You hit it twice.
- It was Suk Jin's turn.
- I saved it.
- You have 11 attempts.
You have 11 attempts.
- All right.
- Eleven attempts.
You have 11 attempts.
- Eleven?
- Yes.
Eleven isn't half bad.
- We did well.
- That's right. We did well.
We should have hit it
at least 40 times.
Once you yell out, "Here I go,"
you can't practice.
Jae Suk is serious.
(The representative of Running Man,
Jae Suk is serious.)
Good luck, Jae Suk.
Eleven attempts.
Good luck.
Jae Suk, let's go.
- Let's go!
- The viewers are watching.
Jae Suk, let's go.
- Go slow.
- Send the ball here.
We will move everything.
It will be hard.
Jae Suk, go slow.
There is no reason to go fast.
- There is the rhythm.
- I think he will succeed.
Good.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
- The candle is shorter now.
That's right.
Maybe it was better
when it was longer.
All right.
Just aim for the body.
Put out the flame.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- He might succeed right away.
- Let's go.
You never know.
He might succeed right away.
(Jae Suk has 11 attempts.)
(It's time for this first attempt.)
Just hit it roughly.
- It was close.
- You got this.
- The first attempt.
- See?
He can do it.
You are nearly there.
(He moves on to the second attempt.)
There you go. It's okay.
- You have many attempts left.
- You only tried twice.
It needs to come here.
Stop it. Don't pressure him.
It's okay.
It isn't okay.
Good.
There you go.
(The ball brushed
against the top of the candle.)
- It was so close.
- That's how you do it.
You are nearly there.
You didn't succeed
because the candle is shorter now.
It's shorter now.
I am becoming nervous now.
You got this.
With you here,
it feels like the Olympics.
- The Olympics.
- The medal ceremony.
(Jae Suk looks like
he is playing in the Olympics.)
Give it a go.
- It's okay. You are nearly there.
- Not there.
Take your aim.
- Keep going.
- Go.
- You have six attempts left.
- Don't send it to the same spot.
- What's up with you?
(He used up half
of the given attempts.)
- It keeps going to the same spot.
- What is she doing?
Is she praying?
What is she doing?
(I pray for his success.)
I didn't die, okay?
- Please help Jae Suk succeed.
- I think...
- that kept you from succeeding.
- I pray...
that Jae Suk will hit the candle.
(Please help Jae Suk succeed.)
Why don't we do the same training?
Aim for my face.
(He uses his face as the target.)
Six attempts left.
(He has 6 attempts left.)
I wouldn't be disappointed
if he hadn't succeeded before.
But he succeeded twice before.
That was close.
(He hits the 6th ball.)
- Okay.
- It hit the candle.
- It did, right?
- Yes. It hit the candle.
(It's the 7th attempt.)
Okay.
It hit the candle.
(It was close.)
- Keep going.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
The eighth attempt.
- The eighth attempt.
- It's off now.
He got the hang of it.
All right.
(It hit the candle!)
(Will the candle go off?)
- All right.
- He did it!
(It went off!)
(It's a success.)
(We did it.)
(The confetti falls in celebration.)
Jae Suk.
What was that?
This is Running Man.
We are Running Man.
Wax dripped on me. It was so hot.
Running Man!
(They shine the most
when they are together.)
Running Man doesn't disappoint!
He did it!
It went off.
It was a very difficult mission.
- Seriously.
- You did it.
(Mr. Game Man achieved a feat
for the 600th episode.)
Since Jae Suk succeeded
to complete the mission,
a total of 8,000 dollars
will be donated.
(The total will be 8,000 dollars.)
(They did it together.)
That's a lot.
Vote for the best members
of Part Two.
I pick Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- In terms of achievements.
- She kept saying, "Boombastic".
- Me too.
- That's right.
(Ms. Boombastic
lifted up everyone's spirits.)
The winning candidate
for Part Two is Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
- You did it.
- And...
- Boombastic.
the worst member of Part Two...
who didn't do much
will be picked by the staff members.
- Okay.
- Haha.
- Suk Jin.
It's Haha.
Haha got over 11 votes.
- The worst member is Haha.
- Haha.
Haha.
- Hehe. Hoho.
- I tried so hard.
The two candidates for victory are
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
The two candidates for a penalty are
Suk Jin and Haha.
- Suk Jin is everywhere.
- I am in both things.
The names are written at the bottom.
The member who gets picked
will be the winner.
Okay.
The winner will have
the honor of being the main donor...
and the privilege of sending
a coffee truck anywhere.
That's incredible.
- That's a nice privilege.
- I am jealous.
(The winner will be picked first.)
- Let's go.
- Here we go.
- Get ready.
- Okay.
This is fun.
(The draw begins.)
- Go.
- It's going down.
Let's go.
- It's Suk Jin.
- It's going down.
- Go.
Let's go.
- It's Suk Jin.
- It's going down.
(Is Seok Sam getting lucky
after a long time?)
(Or Ji Hyo?)
- It's me.
- Suk Jin? Ji Hyo?
(Ji Hyo, Suk Jin)
(Making a sharp turn)
- It's Ji Hyo.
- My gosh.
(Ji Hyo wins.)
How is this possible?
- It's no surprise.
- I can't believe this.
- Ji Hyo is the winner.
- Boombastic!
Skrr
I expected to win.
Gosh, Ji Hyo.
I can never beat you.
Now we will decide the loser.
- Put Haha's name on Ji Hyo's spot.
- Okay.
Suk Jin wouldn't...
- get the penalty, would he?
- What if it's me?
No way. It can't be Suk Jin.
All right.
- That's so cruel.
- The loser will get a penalty.
Let me tell you what the penalty is.
- Okay.
- What is it?
I said there would be a penalty,
but it's something honorable.
- What?
- What is it?
To our viewers who have supported us
for the past 600 episodes,
you will write a thank you letter
on behalf of our members.
(Writing a thank you letter)
- Oh, dear.
- Gosh.
How long? A sheet of paper?
We'd like you to write
a thank you letter with gratitude.
- Suk Jin hates it.
- That's his least favorite thing.
- It is a real penalty.
- You should be grateful.
- Actually...
- We are always grateful.
- I'd love to write a letter.
- He has bad luck.
But I have no luck with this.
- I'd love to write a letter.
- Me too.
- Left and right.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
- I bet Suk Jin will lose.
- It's Haha.
It's Haha.
No, it shouldn't go that way.
Hey.
(Haha, Suk Jin)
(The loser is Ji Suk Jin.)
It's Haha.
No, it shouldn't go that way.
(One-way street)
This is unbelievable.
- It never went this way.
- It's unbelievable.
- I know.
- Why did it go that way?
Isn't it supposed...
- to go back and forth?
- This is unbelievable.
It wouldn't go the other way.
- It refused to move.
- I can't believe this.
- This is for you.
- Did you set this up?
- Do you have a button or something?
- The ball did a great job.
Does the ball have a magnet on it?
This is impossible.
We could do 600 episodes
thanks to Suk Jin.
Tell them how grateful we are.
- And my feelings.
- Your feelings...
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(Everyone left for the day.)
- Please.
- This isn't enough.
I'd need more sheets.
I'll just write down how I feel.
Gosh, I'm getting
a little emotional.
It feels strange. The 600th episode.
(It feels strange.
The 600th episode.)
(He writes a letter to the viewers
on behalf of the members.)
(First of all, I'm grateful
that I can write this letter...)
(to our viewers
on behalf of the members.)
(We wouldn't have been
able to come this far...)
(without the help, love, and
affection of our viewers.)
(I can't thank you enough for
having loved and supported us...)
(when we don't deserve any of that.)
(I'm not sure
how much further we can go,)
(but this might be in the 8th inning
of a baseball game...)
(or 30 minutes into
the second half of a soccer game.)
(The members and production crew
will try their best...)
(to make a show that gives you
the best laughter. Thank you.)
(The oldest member
of Running Man, Ji Suk Jin)
We are so cool.
(With Suk Jin's warm heart,)
(the money that
the members saved today...)
(have been donated
to children from low-income.)
The real deal
shows up at the last moment.
(The powerful punch
with the burning taste)
(Fighters are here
to challenge him.)
(Byeon Woo Seok, Joo Woo Jae,
Park Gyeong Hye)
(In the fierce fight,)
(the first thing
you need to win over...)
(is yourself!)
(In any circumstance,)
(you should never be
consumed with anger.)
(It's possible for Woo Jae.)
(Your female friend?
That female friend!)
(It's time to keep a lid on your anger.)
(The objectives are clear.)
(To become the Running Monster Master
in this section,)
(they have to come up
with a decisive move.)
(Who will be the winner
of this awful fistfight?)
(The Decisive Punch)