- Hello.
- Hey.
- Are you wearing golf clothes?
- Yes, I am.
- That's so cool.
- You look nice.
We should go golfing sometime.
You're here.
I heard Se Chan was good.
- People say that.
- Hello.
This is a fairway snack bar.
I see. This is a snack bar.
But it's so sunny in here.
There is no shade.
Hello.
You guys should carry
a golf bag around like this.
What are you doing with the toilet bag?
This isn't a toilet bag.
Are you going to a bathhouse?
Have you not played golf before?
This is a clutch bag.
If your shirt is torn,
you should buy a new one.
It has patches.
Aren't these climbing clothes?
- What is he wearing?
- Am I wearing the right one?
- What are the gloves for?
- What's with your gloves?
- I was just told to wear these.
- This isn't UFC.
- The gloves...
- Suk Jin.
- What?
- You look cool.
People wear things like this these days.
- That's not true.
- Are you a kangaroo or what?
- Kangaroo?
- Are you a kangaroo? What's this?
Hey, you could use some pockets
while playing golf.
- That's too weak.
- What's weak?
Are you a golf instructor?
- He looks like an instructor.
- All right, guys.
- I think I've seen him before.
- He's a golf instructor.
- I saw him before.
- You're a pro, right?
Good shot.
In that outfit, you look...
(You look like Gook Jin.)
You look like Gook Jin.
I'm telling you.
Right?
He looks just like Gook Jin, doesn't he?
"Hello? Excuse me?"
- "What?"
- "Don't stay up all night."
- They look alike.
- They are similar in size.
- I know.
- Well... I'm a little...
My goodness.
- Seriously, Jae Suk...
- "Hello?"
You shouldn't play golf.
Good shot.
(His weak points stand out
when he's dressed in golf clothes.)
- "Hello?"
- My goodness.
- You look horrible.
- Okay.
- What?
- Are you a kangaroo?
- They already said that.
- Are you a kangaroo or what?
- Why are you doing this?
- He's tearing it off.
Hey, this is the point.
Is this a cushion?
- Hey.
- What is this?
- What are you doing?
- It's a diaper.
- A diaper.
He should use it in an emergency.
My jacket is too simple without it.
Give me back.
(Innocent)
The girls won't be here today.
We shouldn't be so excited.
- This is so fun.
- We're being too...
(The snack bar is
like an indoor playground.)
I'm happy as long as you guys have fun.
This is what Suk Jin likes.
He loves it.
Who else would play with him like this?
You should shift weight.
- How?
- You stand like this. Look.
Those who are not good
swing the club like this.
That's what you do.
You shouldn't do this.
You should move your body.
Suk Jin, who are you looking at?
Do you see someone?
Move your hips like this. Gosh.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- Are you all right?
- Suk Jin, it just made...
- Suk Jin.
- a cracking sound.
- You should be careful.
- You should warm up first.
- Gosh.
- Be careful in the morning.
- I'm fine.
I've never played golf before.
You've never played golf?
I've never gotten on the field.
- Have you ever swung a club?
- I have.
- You have?
- So you played it before.
- Indoor...
- You two...
You two look like typical...
You two look like typical bullies.
- No, we're not.
- You look like bullies.
We look like local gangsters, right?
- And I'm his minion.
- Exactly.
- "You're right, boss."
- "All right. Have a seat."
"Yes, boss."
"I'm sorry I'm late, boss."
"Hey, have a seat."
- "Hey, guys."
- It's so typical.
The weather is nice today.
- By the way, today...
- What's going on?
- Some members are absent.
- Unfortunately,
- So Min got...
- I was waiting.
- Her leg.
- She had surgery.
- She's leaving the hospital today.
- I see.
- Right.
- And...
Ji Hyo didn't...
- She didn't get the vaccine.
- Right. She couldn't.
- She's allergic to western drugs.
- That's right.
- We all know that.
- So she rarely takes...
- western medicine.
- She just fights sickness.
- Totally.
- She can't even take antibiotics.
She will have a PCR test on Wednesday.
- Then the self-isolation ends.
- It will end.
I talked to her on the phone.
Ji Hyo says she loves being isolated.
I've talked to her too.
I called her
and asked if she was doing okay,
- and she was just happy.
- She's really happy.
That's how she lives.
- I know.
- Seriously, she's just happy.
Ji Hyo calls me once a day.
- Really?
- Yes.
- She does?
She's changed a lot.
- Ji Hyo has changed a lot.
- Gosh.
And So Min calls me morning and night.
So Min does? I see.
I asked Ji Hyo, "What are you doing now?"
"I'm making hot pot bulgogi."
Seriously, she said this.
Who did? You mean Ji Hyo?
- I'm serious.
- She sounds so sweet.
- She was so excited.
- What's with her?
Did she really talk with a melody?
- Yes, she did. I was shocked.
- She did?
- "I'm making hot pot bulgogi."
I can imagine that though.
It feels awkward to shoot
this show without them.
- It's strange.
- It's awkward.
I know. It feels weird.
This is when...
- So Min weighs in.
- Right. That's what she does.
- She'd walk around here.
- And she'd talk about our clothes.
Ji Hyo is quiet during the opening,
but I can feel her absence.
- I know.
- Exactly.
So Min would've already tried
swinging the club several times.
I know. She would do that.
Today, we have a special guest
who's perfect for this place.
Someone's coming.
Please bring in the guest.
- Who is it?
- "Hello?"
- It'd be funny if it was Gook Jin.
- Gook Jin?
- "Hello?"
- I wish we'd have Gook Jin here.
(Who's today's special guest
at Running Man Country Club?)
My goodness.
- I wish we'd have Gook Jin here.
- Who is it?
(The golf master, Pak Se Ri)
Coach Pak.
(A golf hero)
(A golf empress)
(A golf master)
(She made Korea stand back up.)
Pak Se Ri's superb winning mentality.
(The living legend of Korean golf)
(She's the legend
with all kinds of records.)
(She will guide the novice golfers
of Running Man today.)
(Today's guest is Pak Se Ri.)
(This is her first time here,
but she looks somewhat familiar.)
- Jong Kook.
- She's Pak Se Ri.
(Jong Kook!)
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
- Please play "One Man" for her.
- They look alike.
- Play "One Man" for her.
- Please come here.
Why would I sit next to him?
Just sit.
It's like a decalcomania.
- Did you two go to the same salon?
- She looks like Jong Kook.
You two really look alike.
You should've told me.
I would've worn a matching shirt.
I would've worn a vest.
You two are wearing matching tops.
Hello.
- We talked on the phone before.
- Right.
When?
- When?
- We talked the other day.
- We talked on the phone.
- Why are you acting friendly?
- We did talk on the phone.
- Someone called me.
- Who was it?
- Suk Jin did?
You called her on "Se Ri Money Club."
- That's right. He did.
- Oh, right.
- During the shoot.
- That's when.
- Suk Jin.
- What?
The shoot should go smoothly,
but why did you bring that up?
We just talked on the phone.
You broke the flow.
- It was nice talking to you.
- You too.
- Please have a seat.
- Let's sit.
He's acting as if we're at a restaurant.
Suk Jin seems upset.
This isn't a restaurant.
- No.
- She didn't seem so excited.
- Why are you sulky?
- That's not true.
- I'm not sulky.
- Don't be sulky.
- They are just saying that.
- Anyway,
Coach Pak Se Ri is...
- She's really...
- She's a legend.
She's a hero.
I met her on "Happy Together."
- Did she join the show?
- She did.
- It was a long time ago.
- I see.
- Right.
- It was "Metal Tray Karaoke Room."
- Yes.
- Seriously?
- That's true.
- It was a really long time ago.
That's when she looked just like me.
Is he talking about that time?
(Upset)
You two really look alike
when you sit next to each other.
- Totally.
- That's true.
You must get that a lot.
I bet you're tired of hearing it.
I was once invited...
- to Running Man before.
- You were?
Back then, the theme was...
- the doppelganger special.
- Right.
- I know.
- I see.
Why did you not join us?
- She should've been here.
- I asked what it was about,
and I heard I'd be here
as Jong Kook's doppelganger.
So I was like, "Forget about it."
- I gave a flat refusal.
- Back then,
K.Will joined us instead.
- Right.
- That's when.
And I kept my distance from Running Man.
I just felt distant from this show.
But my niece loves Running Man.
- She does?
- Seriously?
Whenever I go to see her,
she's watching Running Man.
So I knew she loved this show.
She likes our show because it has
someone who looks like her aunt.
- Exactly.
- That's why.
- It features her family.
- I know.
Let me tell you something.
She hates it when someone
she just met talks down to her.
Make sure not to talk in a casual way.
Would it be strange
if we talked in a casual way today?
(The man who's 11 years older than her
asks her carefully.)
I want to talk in a casual way.
- You should never let him do that.
- What?
Don't let him talk casually.
You should never do that.
Do you want to see how it feels?
- I will show you.
- Don't do that.
Stop it.
- Se Ri, did you eat?
- Suk Jin, did you eat?
- She likes it.
- My gosh.
Don't treat our national hero like that.
I just want her to see how it feels.
Feel comfortable.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- What was that?
My gosh. What's with you?
Don't talk casually.
She likes it when I talk casually.
- This is awkward.
- No.
Are your bodyguards here?
I'm sorry. I'll stop.
- Are your bodyguards here?
- She likes it.
- I don't think so.
- He should learn his lesson.
Your bodyguards should teach him a lesson.
- This is funny.
- Today,
we have Pak Se Ri who's a rich friend
and the national team coach.
And we will have a race called
Se Ri and Birdie Buddy.
- Se Ri and Birdie Buddy?
- Birdie Buddy.
Today, Se Ri will be a variety show coach.
She will lead the five reckless members
of Running Man...
- doing the 18 mission holes.
- My gosh. The 18 mission holes.
It will be too difficult.
All the five members of Running Man are...
subject to a penalty now.
(The 5 members are subject to a penalty.)
Only those who buy an exemption card...
will be exempted from a penalty.
And you will get the money
to buy an exemption card...
after each mission.
The six of you will be a team.
And we will give you prize money.
You can buy penalty exemption cards...
- and even the prize with the money.
- Okay.
All the prize money will be
paid to Coach Pak.
Everything will be
at Coach Pak's discretion...
including planning strategies
and distributing money.
Is it okay not to give them
any money at all?
If you don't do well,
you're not going to get any money.
- Se Ri wouldn't give us any money.
- I'm not sure if I can say this.
You did a TV show
with the disobedient guys before.
But we're not like them. You'll see.
- Look at you.
- He's so sly.
- You are flattering her.
- Look at him.
He's so annoying.
He will make her upset today.
- She will get upset because of him.
- I know.
- He will upset her all day.
- She'll get furious.
Coach Pak, I'm very obedient.
- He should play well.
- You'll see.
Coach Pak, you will start
the race with 100 dollars.
- Hundred dollars.
- And you'll get the menu.
You can do whatever you want with it.
- Okay.
- What's that?
Please take a look at the menu.
(Running Man Country Club Menu)
The blanks will be revealed
at the end of the race.
- Exemption card.
- It will be revealed at the end.
There's a Korean rib eye set.
The hidden option will be revealed...
- if some of you pay 200 dollars.
- Hidden option?
The hidden option is revealed
when 200 dollars is paid.
(They should pay 200 dollars
to open the hidden option.)
- It's not open yet.
- The bills have my face on them.
Coach Pak,
you can give this to your niece.
- She will love it.
- Right.
- This is actually nice.
Your niece will be excited.
- I know.
- She'd love it.
Tell her not to use it though.
I guess Coach Pak likes stuff like this.
She likes small and cute things.
She loves it.
- Give her some of our scratchcards.
- And R coins.
(We did give her some souvenirs
after the shoot.)
Before we start the race,
we will give you a mission...
where you can check
the members' basic golf skills.
It's called Putting Genius.
- Putting Genius.
- Putting.
- Jong Kook.
- I haven't done it for a while.
You will try...
putting in turn
on the miniature golf course.
If you pass level 1, you get 100 dollars.
And 120 dollars for level 2,
and 140 dollars for level 3.
- You will each be given one chance.
- Okay.
If you want to try again,
Coach Pak should try ten dollars.
- Then we will let you try again.
- Pay ten dollars?
Yes. You can pay the money
if you see anyone talented.
I don't think Coach Pak is so generous.
- She's not.
- You know me.
(The rich woman,
Pak Se Ri, is quite strict.)
I'm not generous.
Give us the balls.
(There were a lot of rumors
about the members' golf skills.)
- This is...
- You know what?
- Coach Pak...
- This will be fun.
I only use...
Cameron.
(He's quite picky when he's not so good.)
Those who are bad care about brands.
I want the thing that Tiger Woods uses.
I use the half-moon putter.
I use Cameron.
You each get to try it once.
- Can we practice?
- Let's practice.
- You get to practice only once.
- We get to practice once.
Only once?
I'm not good at this.
- Let me practice.
- It's all right.
Coach Pak, I'm not doing this on purpose,
but I hit the ball
without looking at it. Is it okay?
- What do you mean?
- Without looking at what?
- I hit the ball without looking.
- Where do you look then?
- Where do you look?
- This is what I do.
- I look at the hole.
- How...
- You can do that.
- This is what I do.
- You get to practice only once.
- Just give it a try.
- Okay.
- Here...
- That's strange.
He's standing here, but...
Good. Go ahead.
What? My goodness.
(He almost made it.)
(It's true that
Suk Jin doesn't look at the ball.)
Why do you hit the ball
looking at the hole?
- That's what I do.
- Seriously?
- I look at the hole.
- It works anyway.
It goes in the right direction anyway.
- It went well.
- It's the power that matters.
- It should've been stronger.
- Exactly.
It was a good stroke.
Why don't you go for 100 dollars?
I need 140 dollars.
It's too far. Try the closer one.
I want 140 dollars.
- I can win 140 dollars here.
- It offers more money.
The money is different.
I can get 140 dollars.
I've never seen Jae Suk play golf before.
I've seen it a lot.
He shakes a lot when he plays golf.
- He does?
- Look at him.
(His buck teeth stick out
as he's nervous.)
- My gosh.
- Jae Suk is playing.
Oh, no.
(He got too enthusiastic and hit a homer.)
That wasn't even close.
It was so close.
- It was a homer.
- You should hit it like this.
- Who'd putt like that?
- It was like...
He's like Gook Jin.
- "What?"
- I'll go with 140 dollars.
Gook Jin.
I want to see Jong Kook play.
He does look good.
I think I saw a man like him
at the Giheung Country Club.
(He's a bully golfer who cares
only about his driving distance.)
The Giheung Country Club.
- Right.
- At the Giheung Country Club.
- Jong Kook,
you've still got the putting posture.
That's because...
- Coach Pak scolded him a lot.
- I had a good scolding back then.
- She criticized my posture.
- It was his weak point.
He wouldn't let someone else
scold him like that.
But you need to get a good scolding.
(Staring sharply)
- He learned it the hard way.
- He's right. You should be scolded.
He should.
You should be scolded
if you don't do it right.
That's how I've improved.
You hit it well. It's nice.
- Oh, dear.
- You pulled it a little.
I did? I do that every time.
He's got a good sense of distance.
- I do it every time.
- Don't pull it.
- But...
- I pulled it.
- he's got a good sense of distance.
- My gosh.
Haha, you should take a lesson.
You should get some advice
from the national hero.
- He's never done this before.
- You can't hold it like that.
Get some advice from the national hero?
Move over. What do you know?
He's holding it like this.
- Hey, back off.
- Ask her.
You've never tried this before?
You won't have a chance
to get a lesson like this.
- Hey.
- Se Ri is teaching you.
It's not something you can buy with money.
When you play golf...
No, hold it like this.
You should take a day off.
(The novice golfer is
encouraged to take a day off.)
- Why is he wearing gloves?
- This is a lot of work.
- Okay.
- Why are you wearing gloves?
You can imagine
that the triangle moves together.
It's like playing pool.
(What's the result of her lesson?)
My goodness.
(The ball bounces out of the hole cup.)
- You're good.
- That's right.
- It's like playing pool.
- You're a genius.
- How could you be so good?
- This is...
You can do this.
Of course he can.
- This is no big deal.
- But...
- you don't do as you're told.
- Is the practice over?
- Shall we try now?
- Let's try.
Golf is really fun.
Is it fun?
I should try level one.
- I should...
- Try the middle one.
- You get to try only once.
- It was too strong.
I should do this right.
(The members are proud
of their golf skills.)
Suk Jin, that's...
Look to the right.
(The gallery is quite loud.)
Suk Jin, look to the right.
Who would do that at a golf course?
- This is Running Man.
(The gallery has no manners
on Running Man.)
- Can we distract him?
- Stay quiet.
- Don't do that.
- We can interrupt him.
You should look at Kang Chan Hee's feet.
- Kang Chan Hee's feet.
- Look to the right.
- You can do this.
- Kang Chan Hee's feet.
You can do this if you control the power.
You can do this...
- if you control the power.
- See?
- I pulled it.
- You did.
- See?
- I pulled it.
- You did.
- It wasn't even close.
I heard Se Chan was really good.
- Is he really that good?
- He says he's good.
- He's good.
- Is he?
- Se Chan is really good.
- That's what I heard.
- He's very good.
- He can't be that good.
Guys like him...
- are good at many little things.
- Right.
- You should move over.
- What?
Are you standing there on purpose?
They are just like bullies.
They are not supposed to be here.
It feels like I'm surrounded by a wall.
You should keep your distance.
This is where I was standing.
I should look at it from a distance.
- This is where I was standing.
- We don't have to back off.
You don't have to back off?
- This is an individual match.
- I was standing here before.
- You're unbelievable.
- All right.
- Look at him.
- Se Chan is serious.
You can hit it like that.
There are guys...
- who are serious about golf.
- I know.
You're being too serious.
Your girlfriend isn't here today.
- He doesn't care about her.
- He doesn't.
Are you trying to distract him now?
She's leaving the hospital today.
What are you doing here?
You look so happy.
You're the worst boyfriend.
Do you call yourself a human being?
It's not going in.
- You pulled it.
- It's not going in.
Look at that.
- It's not even.
- Right.
It's not even.
And you pulled it.
- It's not even, is it?
- It's not even.
Who's next?
- Can I try?
- I'll go next.
- Jong Kook.
- It's not easy.
- You can still try level one.
We don't do that.
- My gosh.
- This is about our pride.
- We don't want 100 dollars.
- We have a bigger goal.
We're not petty.
- This is...
- Jong Kook should make it.
You should make it.
That was nice.
- Good.
- That was a nice one.
- Like this.
- Okay.
- Did I pull it?
- No. Just do it.
Like this.
Your girlfriend is now
under home quarantine.
Gosh, this is crazy.
"Ji Hyo, what are you doing?"
"I'm making hot pot bulgogi."
- He should do this for her.
- Exactly.
- Your girlfriend is in quarantine.
- He should make money.
He pulled it.
- Your girlfriend is in quarantine.
- "I'm making hot pot bulgogi."
(He fails.)
- Oh, no.
- He pulled it a lot.
- It's not even.
- Hey.
Why did you hit it like that?
Why would you do this
after hitting the ball?
- You should do it right.
- Gook Jin.
- All right.
- This is a lot.
(Revenge)
(He gave as good as he got.)
You can't use your knee like that.
I was trying to help you.
Did he give you a knee kick?
- You can't give a knee kick.
- Coach Pak.
I can overcome things like this.
Don't worry.
(2nd knee kick)
Go ahead and do it.
I was standing like this.
- Did you just kick me?
- No, I didn't.
- Go ahead and do it.
- Didn't you kick me?
I was standing like this.
This is how I was standing.
- That's a nice chair.
- Good.
- Check the ground.
- There's a chair.
- It's a nice chair.
- Did you check the ground?
It is nice.
- Around here. Good. I'm ready.
- Good.
He usually gets lucky
when it comes to things like this.
You're too close to the ball.
I think you should straighten
your back a little bit.
- Should I?
- Yes.
I'll do as you tell me, Coach Pak.
You can think of me as your avatar.
- He does look like Gook Jin.
- Don't worry, Coach Pak.
- "Hello?"
- I think he's pulling it.
- I won't let you down.
- Swing it gently as you do now.
- Gently. Got it.
Also, this half-moon shape...
All right. Come on. Seriously.
I'm the half-moon!
- Really? Aren't you a thug?
- I'm the half-moon.
- He's a half thug.
- I see.
Just do it already.
- He's a half thug.
- Good. It was perfect just now.
(He finally hits the ball
after chattering for a while.)
- Oh, no.
- He pulled it.
(How well did
the talkative Yoo Gook Jin putt?)
- Oh, no.
- He pulled it.
- Darn it.
- He failed.
- Oh, no.
- He pulled it.
(The ball went past the hole.)
(Darn it.)
Maybe you should've hit it
a little more to the right.
- Why would all of you...
- It wasn't even close.
- Why are you so disappointed?
- I knew I was pulling it a little.
- As I said, it wasn't even close.
- What a shame.
- I could've gotten 100 dollars.
- Putting is difficult.
- You all pulled it.
- Why did I do that? Gosh.
I'll place it here.
- Go ahead.
- Haha is...
- He might pull it off unexpectedly.
- He has a good chance.
Beginners who know nothing can be bold.
- That's true.
- That's why they can do better.
- He may surprise us.
- Right?
- Yes, it's true.
- Those who know a little act up...
- Is it really a golf outfit?
- Acting up?
You're too close to the ball.
Are you holding it
as I taught you earlier?
- You should adjust it right.
- You don't have a good memory.
Hit the right spot.
I have a really bad memory.
- Listen to Big Sister Se Ri.
- Right, you should listen to her.
You can straighten your knees more.
Can I call you "Big Sister?"
- Of course. She's older than you.
- Relax this arm.
- She wouldn't mind that.
- Lower your upper body.
The direction seems...
- Just go ahead.
- Trust yourself and go for it.
- Hit it as you are.
- Just hit it.
- Look at the ball.
- Hit it lightly.
- That's good.
- What?
(Has Se Ri's lesson helped him improve?)
It's going in.
(It almost fell into the hole.)
(Every cast member including Haha failed.)
- What a shame.
- It almost went into the hole.
- Exactly.
- Can't you give us another chance?
You can get another chance
only if Coach Pak pays ten dollars.
- Really?
- Just give us another chance.
- Ten dollars for one person?
- Only one person? Come on.
Make it two at least.
Then I should pay 50 dollars
to give everyone another chance.
- Right. You wouldn't pick just one.
- Exactly.
(She will try in front of her pupils
who are whining.)
- That's great.
- It's going in.
(How well could their teacher putt?)
- That's great.
- It's going in.
(A clean shot)
- That's great.
- It's going in.
(1 shot, 1 kill.)
- She's amazing.
- She's incredible.
- She's absolutely amazing.
- Indeed.
- She's on another level.
- That was amazing.
- Coach Pak...
- Here's 140 dollars.
- Give this to her, please.
- Help us out. You won 140 dollars.
- So we can try again.
- I really want another chance.
- Oh, I won it for putting.
- Correct.
- Please pay ten dollars for us.
- Except for Suk Jin.
- All of us except for Suk Jin.
- But I barely know you guys.
Well, you know...
- She has a point.
- I met you for the first time.
- She's good.
- We speak casually to each other.
- What's wrong with him?
- Coach Pak.
- Don't drop the honorifics.
- Except for Suk Jin.
- You don't have to help him out.
- I really like playing golf now.
- Give us ten dollars each, please.
- Please help us out.
How about we play rock-paper-scissors?
- I like the idea.
- What do you say?
That's a good idea. I'll help
the three of you this time.
- Three of us?
- Yes, only three of you.
- Three of us? Then...
- Then...
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do that.
- Yes. That'd be fair.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's play palm face down or up.
- Okay.
- The majority wins.
- Right. Got it.
- You mean the three of us?
- Rock-paper-scissors is better.
(Se Chan sends a hand signal.)
The three whose palms are facing
the same side.
- Three of us.
- Okay.
- What if... Okay. Three winners.
- Let's begin.
- Palm face down or up
(Seok Sam is out.)
Okay.
- Palm face down or up
(What?)
- He's out. It's over.
- Right.
- You're 4, not 3.
- You're out.
- We agreed on three of us.
- You're out, Suk Jin.
- It's over for now.
- The four of us should play again.
We should play the game
until we have three winners.
One got eliminated for now.
- No.
- One more will be eliminated.
- The three of you get a chance.
- Right.
- Let's...
- Did you see that, Coach Pak?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors...
- They're ruthless.
Suk Jin, move aside.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors...
- They're ruthless.
(The habitual swindler got caught
trying to scam him.)
- Hey.
- What happened?
- He just raised his arm...
- How dare you give them a signal?
- No, he didn't.
He didn't give us a signal.
He was just doing a stretch.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Hey, did you give them a signal?
- Did you do that earlier too?
- No, I didn't.
All right. Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay.
- Two won, and two lost.
- We won.
- We should play it again.
- The two of us won.
- Let's play...
Ready.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay.
- Done.
(Haha won.)
- Okay.
- Done.
- You got what you deserved.
- The two oldest members are out.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- The oldest two are out.
- Coach Pak.
- Let's do this.
- Here's 30 dollars.
- Okay. Good.
- For the three of them.
- Coach Pak, spend ten more dollars.
- I'll pull it off this time.
- No matter what. That won't happen.
- Just ten more dollars, please.
- Mister, step out of the mat.
- No way.
- I'll try to win 100 dollars.
- Jong Kook.
- That'd be good enough.
- Winning the money will be helpful.
I'll place the ball
closer to the hole too.
But it's not easy to hit it
from here either.
Come on. It's cowardly of you.
- Gosh.
- He should win some money.
Fine. I'll place it here.
Let's do this.
- You should put it in the hole.
- Choose an easier spot.
- I'll do the same.
- But...
- It's okay. He can do this.
- I'll give it a try.
It's not that hard.
Gosh. Just hit it already. Seriously.
(Gosh. Just hit it already. Seriously.)
- This is not being broadcast live.
- You see,
Jong Kook loses his confidence
when playing golf.
- That's so true.
- I see.
- I mean...
- He gets so timid.
- Right? He gets timid...
- I have little knowledge of this.
and always hits balls too lightly.
- Your stance is good.
- Indeed.
- Try to be a little bold, will you?
- You know...
It's not easy to control it.
It's normal to get timid.
- His stance is not bad.
- Try to be a little bold, will you?
I really don't want to play golf with him.
- Nice. He did it.
- I really don't want to...
Nice. He did it.
- No. He hit it too hard.
- He did it.
- It curved a little at the end.
- Why did you make the same mistake?
- You hit it the wrong way.
- Didn't it curve a little?
- I'll try the 100 dollar distance.
I'll try the 100 dollar distance.
You won't pull it off anyway.
Go ahead. Putting it in the hole is
what matters.
He'll be so embarrassed
if he fails to put it in the hole.
It's not easy to do it from this distance.
- Stop it. We agreed on the rule.
- Just one, please.
- Put it back in.
- You don't have to give it to me.
- It's my money.
- I know, but...
- I can spend it as I want.
- It's going in.
(Yoo Gook Jin convinced her
to give him 10 dollars.)
(Meanwhile, Se Chan hit the ball.)
- It's going in.
- But...
It's going in.
- Yes! I won 100 dollars!
- He pulled it off.
It's going in.
(He pulled it off perfectly.)
(Yes! I won 100 dollars!)
Se Chan, we'll give you 100 dollars.
Yes!
- I'll pay ten dollars. Thank you.
- Okay.
Can I give my money to another member too?
Yes, you can.
Hey, I can give away my money too.
- Really?
- I can give you...
- When you hit it...
- Hey, repay me 100 dollars.
Pardon me?
- Repay her the money now.
- Coach Pak, please.
Why should I give you the money back?
- You owe me.
- Of course you should repay her.
That's ridiculous.
Repay her the money now.
- I lent you the money.
- Exactly.
- Se Chan, don't repay her.
- Just give her the money now.
- Pardon?
- Invest the money in me.
- Give me back the money.
- Repay her now.
- Hold on a second.
- I'll give you back if I succeed.
Pay me the money back
and invest the rest in him...
- or anyone else.
- I can't believe...
the national heroine is demanding
to repay only ten dollars.
- Come on. It's hard to earn money.
- Okay. Here you go.
- Give her the money.
- You don't have to give it to him.
- Okay. I'll invest in you.
- Thank you.
Everyone has another chance now.
- It's fair now, right?
- Okay.
- Here. Try again.
- Sorry?
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
(Jong Kook succeeded in getting
an investment.)
- It's fair now, right?
- Okay.
(Haha challenges to win 100 dollars.)
- Oh, no.
- You hit it too hard.
- He's done.
- All right.
- I didn't know it was this hard.
- I should've coached him.
- It's too difficult.
- I gave Jong Kook ten dollars.
- Okay.
- Se Chan.
- It's Yoo Gook Jin's turn.
- It's so difficult.
It's okay. If he pulls it off...
It'd be more rewarding
if we could win 200 dollars.
- Hit it lightly. Gosh.
- He hit it too hard.
- Come on.
(Jae Suk failed again.)
- He hit it too hard.
(Yoo Gook Jin messed up the chance
he got by begging.)
- I told you to hit it lightly.
- That's too bad.
I'll give you 50 dollars.
- It almost went into the hole.
- I know.
You hit it too hard.
I didn't know golf was so fun.
My gosh. They must be out of their minds.
- This is not an official game.
- Come on.
I'll give you 30 dollars.
- Give me 40 dollars.
- Deal.
- I have no money left now.
- Okay.
Aim to win 100 dollars.
They're all going crazy
for a game for the opening.
Further to the back.
(Another golf addict tries again.)
Look to your left, Suk Jin.
That's good.
- Okay! Yes!
- He pulled it off.
- Okay.
- Good job.
- Move.
- Nice.
- Take your ball out of the hole.
- Place it closer to the hole.
- I'll place it here no matter what.
- Come on.
- Where did he get the money?
- So I can give you 40 dollars.
- Place it closer to the hole.
- I borrowed ten dollars from him.
Place it closer to the hole.
- So I can give you 40 dollars.
- He's acting like a thug.
- I want to have 100 dollars left.
- I want to borrow money too.
Don't forget you promised me
that you'd pay me.
- Hit it less hard than earlier.
- The direction was perfect.
- He got two more chances... Oh, no.
- Gosh.
- Why would you keep pulling it?
- That wasn't even close.
- He hit it too hard.
- Gosh.
- Why would you keep pulling it?
- That wasn't even close.
- He pulled it.
Coach Pak is starting to get annoyed.
- How many times did you hit?
- Of course she gets annoyed.
- A hundred dollars?
- She got upset.
I'll aim to win 120 dollars this time.
I think I can do this.
I just have to hit it slightly to...
Just hit it already.
You took more time, Jae Suk.
I'll just hit it.
- Look to your right.
- I'll hit it now.
Slightly to the right.
(Jae Suk got scolded by the teacher
and took it out on Jong Kook.)
- To the right?
- This is your last chance.
Who are you to make that decision?
We can't play this game all day long.
- That's true.
- We haven't even begun the race.
- This won't improve our ratings...
- Gosh, seriously.
(Angry)
Does he always sabotage others
when playing golf?
- He's driving me crazy.
- But...
- It's actually not allowed.
- People would start fighting.
But people do that
when playing golf with friends.
Slightly to the right?
I should look that way.
Okay. I'll do that.
- Lightly.
- That's good.
- Did I hit it too hard?
- You did it!
- Great job.
- Jong Kook!
- That's good.
- Did I hit it too hard?
- You did it, Jong Kook!
- Great job.
(Jong Kook pulled it off too.)
Okay.
- As a result of the game,
- He must've spent all his money.
- some of you won money.
- Yes.
The money you won will be useful.
- Coach Pak can give you her money.
- Got it.
Let's go to the first location now.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
What are we going to do here?
What will we do? Those computers
make me anxious.
- I'm not good with computers.
- It's okay.
I'm really bad with computers.
- I'm not good with computers.
- I can't even turn it on.
Me too. What am I supposed to do?
- I guess we'll be doing a search.
- I guess so.
I just...
(Suk Jin sits next to Se Ri.)
Are your visions cloudy? Is that the case?
- I've aged. That's all.
- I saw you...
- Oh, I see.
- I've aged.
Why?
I don't think he's good with computers.
I'll sit here, so I can ask you
some questions.
- He kept looking at it.
- I'll ask you what I don't know.
(She sat next to the younger member.)
- I'm younger than him, right?
- Sorry?
Yes. And it'd be more comfortable
to ask you questions.
- I don't think he knows much.
- I'm younger than Suk Jin.
I know what I need to know.
We'll probably search for golf courses.
- As I said, you will play 18 holes.
- Yes.
The 1st mission you'll complete
before the 1st to 3rd holes is...
Search Engine King of the Field.
- Oh, I get it.
- I knew it.
- Right.
- Okay. Let's do this.
We'll show you a photo,
- and you'll have 20 minutes...
- Yes.
to figure out...
the name of the person in the photo
based on the characteristics...
or anything you can see in the photo.
- What?
- I see.
- Someone we don't know?
- Correct.
- Then how do we get information?
- You can find him or her easily.
- Let's give it a try.
- We can find the person easily?
- It could be a golfer.
- All right.
- I don't know many golfers.
- If you can't figure it out...
based on the first photo,
you can move on to the next level,
which is up to Coach Pak.
It'll be easier to find the person.
- I guess we'll have to pay money.
- I see.
However, you'll get less money...
- whenever you see another photo.
- Okay.
Therefore, you'd better get it done
with the least number of photos.
We'll have to be quick, but we can
do it within the given time.
Correct. And you can say
the six of you are on the same team.
- Really?
- Are we going to do it as a team?
- Okay.
- We should work together.
- Of course.
- Let's work together.
- Let's share information.
- Let's do that.
- That'll make it much easier.
- We can share information.
There are four levels for each question.
If you think that the first photo is
too difficult for you,
ask us to show you the next one.
- That's how it's done.
- Show us. It won't be difficult.
Here's the first-level photo.
- Show us.
- We'll work together.
(The 1st level photo)
- Show us.
- We'll work together.
- Hey, I know who that is.
- I know who he is.
I know who he is.
Is he French?
- Isn't he an actor?
- No.
No, he's not. He's...
- He's not an actor.
- I've seen him somewhere.
- Wait. He may be an actor...
- I think he's an actor.
- Is he a politician?
- No.
- He's not an actor.
- Isn't he the governor of a state?
- Right. I think so too.
- He's a politician.
- It's a scene from a movie.
- He's the governor of a state...
- No, I don't think so.
- You may begin.
- This is all we have?
- Yes.
- This photo is all we have?
- Hang on. I think...
- Hold on.
- I think I saw him...
- He's not the governor of France.
- What do you think?
Maybe New York...
"The governor of France?"
(Se Chan thinks the US national flag
is the French national flag.)
What makes you think he's French?
- The governor of New York...
- Hold on.
(Meanwhile, Coach Pak...)
(was typing English
only with her index fingers.)
What makes you think he's French?
(What? Why do I see
English letters on the screen?)
Why can't I delete this?
- New York...
- Why?
- Pardon?
- Why can't I delete this?
You can delete it with this key.
- Oh, I was mistaken.
- Convert the language like this.
This one?
- Wait.
- I think...
(Se Ri's doppelganger types
with only 2 fingers as well.)
Why am I typing English letters?
(He also typed English letters
just as Se Ri did.)
(He deletes everything
and types English letters again.)
Gosh. How should I change it
to Korean? Wait.
- He can't...
- Oh, okay.
(While the 2 doppelgangers are
struggling with typing...)
Wait. The badge on his jacket...
That's the US national flag, right?
- If you search...
- Things like that badge...
must be hints.
(Actor from "Don't Look Up")
(The American series lover searches
for an American actor for now.)
- You know... Something...
- Hold on. Can you see...
(The cast of "Don't Look Up")
I've seen him many times before.
- Suk Jin.
- I'm sure he's a politician.
- He must be a politician...
- That badge looks like...
(What?)
Isn't it a badge of a political party?
(Can I say the answer now?)
- Can I say the answer now?
- Yes, you can.
Isn't he Mark Rylance?
(Mark Rylance)
Mark Rylance.
- Incorrect.
- What a shame.
I'm pretty sure he's a politician.
Isn't that the American flag?
- Chuck Schumer?
- Incorrect.
Who is Chuck Schumer?
I'll type in "US senators."
Se Ri, you can tell us to show you
the next photo anytime.
- We've got this.
- We don't need that.
Don't show us that yet. Wait.
How... I can't see the details
of the badge.
- In what year was this taken?
- Can you bring it to us?
- It's the American flag, right?
- Yes.
- The badge?
- Didn't I already tell you before?
- Take a look at it.
- We already talked about it.
- Show me. Let me have a close look.
- He's definitely a politician.
- I've seen him somewhere.
- Show me.
I'll take a look first.
Let's take turns, okay?
Oh, looking at it closely,
I see that he's not the actor.
- Hey.
- I've never seen him before.
- Hey, you guys...
- There's a badge on his jacket.
- Bring it to me.
- It's the American flag.
- Let us have a look.
- It's not fair.
- Let me take a look first.
- Just give us a minute.
- Don't you think it's unfair?
- What is this?
I was the one who brought it here.
And he said, "Let me take a look first."
- Okay.
- He's a married man.
- I see a wedding ring.
- First of all,
- you see the flag, right?
- I've never seen him before.
- You mean the badge?
- Let's search for the badge first.
- Right. Let's do that.
- The badge with the flag on it.
- It's called a badge, right?
- Wait. Hey.
You can get a badge with the flag
on it for 58 dollars online.
Can you order one for me?
Will you buy one?
- No, that's not what I meant.
- Hey, how do you spell "badge?"
- Is it V or B?
- It's B.
It's B.
I see a lot of people wearing badges.
- Right? Check out each of them.
- There are so many of them.
- I just have to find his face.
- I see a lot of photos.
Great. Let's take a look.
I must say, you guys are
unbelievably stupid.
- Let's see who finds him first.
- You have no idea...
They don't even know what to search for.
Can't we ask for a hint?
- They all look the same now.
- I know, right?
Let's see the second-level photo.
We can't find him with this photo.
We're running out of time.
We must find him in 20 minutes.
- Is that so?
- I agree.
If Se Ri approves, we'll show you.
- We need more hints, Se Ri.
- Let's go for it, Se Ri.
- Se Ri.
- Time is of the essence.
- Yes?
How much money will be deducted?
Hundred dollars.
- From 300 dollars?
- Yes.
- That's too much.
- A presidential candidate.
- Okay. We'll spend 100 dollars.
- All right.
Here's the second photo.
(The 2nd level photo)
- What?
- He's standing next to Joe Biden.
I know! He's the vice president of the US.
- Is he?
- The vice president of the US.
(The empty heads still have no clue.)
- Oh, right. It's Kamala Harris.
- Jae Suk.
- I was wrong.
- He gets confused all the time.
He's right next to Joe Biden.
Then I should type in his name.
I already typed in his name.
(He typed in "Joe Biden's photo.")
I typed in his name a while ago.
What should I type in?
"Joe Biden's best friend?"
- Come on. Tell me.
- I'll type that in.
No, that's not what you should type in.
We just have to look for that photo.
They're clearly at an event.
If you look at the photo...
- That's an election campaign.
- Biden's presidential campaign.
- Exactly.
- I don't think so.
We should find the man next to Joe Biden.
The vice president of the US is
Kamala Harris.
- Let's see...
- Why is he...
alone in most of his photos?
(That's because you typed in
"Joe Biden's photo.")
There might be a hint
on the area where it was taken.
My gosh. This is difficult.
Show me.
(Show me.)
Show me. Let me take a look first.
Give me that.
Show me. I'll have a look first.
- Why should you be the first one?
- Come on. Show me.
- Why...
- Bring it to me.
They were at a high school.
- A high school?
- It says...
- Did they go to the same school?
- "High school."
If they were at a high school...
(Joe Biden's college alumni)
(Images)
I think it says, "Charter High School."
- It's "charter."
- Yes.
I see the word "college"
written here too.
I guess... I'll explain to you.
Look at this photo.
Look. What do you think it is?
He's running for president.
- This man went there to help him.
- To support Biden?
- Yes, I think that's the case.
- Right. This tie...
(Joe Biden's suit)
(Joe Biden's sunglasses,
Joe Biden's inauguration ceremony)
(Joe Biden's presidential campaign)
(Haha typed in just as he heard.)
- "Biden's presidential campaign"...
- Let's type that in.
"Support for Biden's
presidential campaign."
(Support for Biden's
presidential campaign)
I typed in "Joe Biden's
inauguration ceremony."
I'll find this man.
I found him shortly.
Gosh, this is so frustrating.
I really want to find out who he is.
He said, "I found him shortly."
- "Biden's man."
- Yes. Good.
- No. "Biden's..."
- Gosh.
- "Biden's..."
Who on earth is this man?
Who on earth is he?
- No, he looks younger than that.
- Since we...
Let's see the third photo.
How much time do we have left?
- You have 4 minutes left.
- Let's win 200 dollars at least.
- He's right. Let's do that.
- Okay.
- Show us.
- Here's the third-level photo.
I don't see it yet.
(The 3rd level photo)
It says...
Can you read
the letters above his name?
- All right.
- Let me have a closer look.
I can see "30330."
I'll type in that number.
(It's written "Text CA to 30330."
It seems to be a big hint.)
- Type this phrase.
- "Text CA to..."
- What did you say?
- "Text to CA to..."
- Does it stand for Texas?
- Yes.
He must be the governor of Texas.
- Wait.
- I found him.
- The governor of Texas?
- It's him.
(I found him. It's him.)
("The governor of Texas Lifts
the Mask Mandate")
(They look completely different
from each other.)
- The governor of Texas?
- It's him.
- That's not him.
- Really?
- You didn't have to yell at me.
- I'm sorry about that.
You're the only one
I can yell at now.
- "Texas..."
- Do you want to...
- What did you find?
- Is he Beto O'Rourke?
- Incorrect.
- No, he's not Beto O'Rourke.
- I can't believe Jae Suk.
- Don't just say any random names.
What are you searching for?
Why don't you look at the photo?
- Me?
- Regarding the election.
- I found him!
- Okay.
(I found him!)
I... This is... I found his photo.
- You found him.
- This is him.
- I found his photo. This is him.
- You found him.
(Haha found
the same person's photo.)
- I found his photo. This is him.
- You found him.
- Nevada Caucus.
(Before the Nevada Caucus)
(Nevada Caucus!)
- Incorrect.
- No, wait.
(They started reading
all the words they could see.)
- No, wait. Bloomberg.
- Bloomberg.
(Biden, Bloomberg)
Incorrect.
- Hey, what did you find?
- What did you...
- Haha found his photo.
- Sanders.
- Incorrect.
- Chasing Fiercely.
I'm looking at him.
He's in this photo.
- Newspim?
- Incorrect.
"Chasing Fiercely?"
- What's that? Hey.
- We're almost there. This is it.
As I said, I found his photo.
- Come and have a look.
- Show me.
- Haha found this photo.
- That's him.
- But we can't figure out his name.
- Is it?
- Haha found his photo.
- Is it really him?
- Let me take a look.
- But...
- Isn't his name written there?
- There are six foreigners in it.
- What is his name?
- Gosh, this is frustrating.
Isn't it so funny?
Haha found the photo,
but he can't figure out his name.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
You have 30 seconds left.
You said you'd found a photo.
What are they doing in the photo?
They're smiling.
- That's not what I meant.
- They're smiling happily.
- A good thing must have happened.
- Why did they gather?
The article must explain
about the occasion.
Time's up.
- What? Hey.
- Time's up.
Who is he?
- I'll show you the fourth photo.
- We didn't see the last one.
- And I'll tell you his name.
- Okay.
This is the last photo.
- "Safer L.A.?"
- L.A.?
Is he the governor of Los Angeles?
- "Safer L.A.?"
- L.A.?
(Is he the governor of Los Angeles?)
He's Eric Garcetti,
the current mayor of Los Angeles.
- Gosh.
- The mayor of Los Angeles?
I searched for the mayors of Manhattan...
and New York City.
Why didn't I think of Los Angeles?
- He's the mayor of Los Angeles?
- Is there a mayor in Los Angeles?
He's the mayor of Los Angeles.
- Oh, I found an article about him.
- Gosh, seriously.
He's the mayor of Los Angeles.
- Wasn't he in the group photo?
- I'll pull it off this time.
- Let's move on.
- Gosh.
- This person is also very famous.
- I see.
- Here's your next question.
- Let's take a look.
(The 1st level photo)
I know who he is. He's an actor.
(I know who he is. He's an actor.)
- He must be... Hold on.
- He's an actor.
- Hold on.
- Could he be someone...
with extraordinary powers?
- He's quite fit.
- Wasn't he in "Iron Man?"
- The glass is shattered.
- The wine glass is shattered.
Someone who shattered a wine glass.
Shattered wine glass.
A photo like that isn't enough to...
(Someone who shattered a wine glass.)
This is annoying.
How can I search for this man?
- I hate things like this.
- What should be the keyword?
I looked up a shattered wine glass...
and got "Is wine glass recyclable?"
- That's what I got as well.
- Right?
Isn't he Michael Rooker?
(Answer: Michael Rooker)
- I'd be amazed if that's right.
- Is he right?
You are correct.
How did you find him?
(He got it from the level 1 photo.)
He was in "The Walking Dead."
- He also played Yondu.
- Okay!
What did you type in?
- Yondu?
- What did you type in?
- Actor from "The Walking Dead."
- You knew he was an actor.
We'll move on to the third round.
Who on earth is he?
- Hold on.
- Does he have hives?
He has only half a beard.
- A beard.
- Do you know who he is?
A man with half a beard.
- Does he play soccer?
- That's not him.
- That's a beard.
- Found him!
- He's a high jumper.
- You're right.
- You got him.
- Really?
Then say his name!
Italian high jumper Tamberi.
Super handsome... Sorry about that.
- Gianmarco Tamberi.
- That is correct.
- Nice.
- What a relief.
- Unbelievable.
- And like that,
you earned 600 dollars
over the course of three holes.
- Really?
- Is that it?
- That was fun.
- We earned 600 dollars?
- Yes, 600 dollars.
- Another round would've been nice.
Head Coach Pak will distribute the money.
I'd appreciate it
if you considered our contribution.
- Coach Pak.
- Coach Pak, here you go.
- A total of 600 dollars?
- Thank you.
Coach Pak?
There are exactly six of us.
What a coincidence.
A few complained during the entire game.
- This is for your hard work.
- Absolutely.
Is that 50 dollars? Thank you.
And...
Thank you.
Jong Kook, you also get 50 dollars.
- You found one of the people.
- Thank you.
I also looked someone up.
- Coach Pak?
- I almost found the right person.
(They keep eyeing the coach's move.)
I did nothing to deserve the money, but...
(She pockets the money.)
- Coach Pak, what are you doing?
- What?
- Only those on "Se Ri Money Club."
- I found L.A., you know.
- It just happened that way.
- We should be grateful.
You only gave money
to those on "Se Ri Money Club."
- Coach Pak.
- But I looked up the last person.
- We contributed the most.
- But Se Chan was faster.
- But Coach Pak...
- Okay, fine.
- Me too.
- I should receive some of it.
- Gosh.
- But Suk Jin...
- Right?
- I tried my best.
- About ten dollars should do.
- Yes, that should do.
- That sounds like enough.
- How about 30 dollars?
- Is this 20 dollars?
- How generous of her.
I shouldn't be giving out
free money like this.
- Can't I get 30 dollars?
- You should pocket the rest.
- Please pocket the rest.
- It's not like I can cut the note.
Don't you have 5,000 won bills?
(Don't you have 5,000 won bills?)
That's too generous of her.
Do you promise to try harder?
- Se Ri, wait.
- You didn't have to.
- Coach Pak, this isn't necessary.
- Cut the note in half.
He didn't do anything
to deserve the money.
There won't be a next time.
Why not?
The money's supposed to be distributed.
- That's nonsense.
- That's enough, Suk Jin.
- But...
- I'm not a bank, you know.
- That's enough.
- But...
- Give it back then.
- You're going to make him cry.
- I'll take it back.
- No way.
Thank you.
The money is supposed
to be distributed, you know.
- Don't complain.
- So why...
Who are you to keep it all?
What on earth is happening?
(Seok Sam's speaking in a peculiar way.)
- It's upsetting, you know.
- What are you saying?
What's with that tone?
We have up to 18 holes to play.
From hole number 4 to hole number 6,
your teamwork will be tested.
The game is Team Play Good Shot.
What's that?
You will go around...
naming the right word
that fits into the category.
We will decide upon
the number of answers required.
- Okay.
- From one corner to the next,
let's say you're supposed
to name ten words.
You can answer more than once
if you know more answers.
You must all name at least one though.
You will win 100 dollars
every time you succeed.
But Coach Pak must pay ten dollars...
- each time you answer incorrectly.
- Okay.
- Name three if you know more.
So she loses ten dollars...
- every time we answer incorrectly?
- Yes.
That doesn't sound easy.
- All right.
- We'll start with Jong Kook.
- Sure.
- Go ahead.
You must name ten...
and Haha must name at least one.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Haha needs to answer.
- We must hand it over to you.
I must at least say the ninth word.
- The ninth.
- No pressure, guys.
- Say as much as you can.
- Here's the first round.
What is it?
We're not feeling the pressure.
- What is it?
- What's the category?
- Bring it on.
- What is it?
- Come on!
- We can do this.
- We can answer ten for sure.
- You underestimate us.
- Bring it on.
- Capital cities in Europe.
- What?
Rome.
Say a few more.
Zurich.
- Why not?
- European cities?
Zurich isn't the capital city.
It's Bern.
Are you kidding me?
Bern is the capital city of Switzerland.
You must pay a ten-dollar fine.
- I was clueless.
- Please pay up.
Are you kidding me?
- Hear me out.
- Coach Pak,
make him pay the ten dollars he has.
It's okay.
We're all allowed to make mistakes.
I'll...
- Seriously?
- Coach Pak!
Just make him pay out of his own pocket!
He named the wrong city.
- Why must you pay the fine?
- But...
Coach Pak, I'll hand it in for you.
- Allow me.
- Coach Pak!
- Suk Jin should've paid.
- All right.
You have a limited number of chances.
Here's round two.
That was a difficult one.
Tell me about it. I was just as clueless.
Should we start with Haha this time?
- Sure.
- No way.
- We'll start with Haha.
- Go ahead.
Capital cities in Europe.
Lisbon.
Luxembourg.
(Capital cities in Europe)
(Her time is up.)
(Se Ri's mind stopped thinking.)
- There's Rome.
- There's also Bern.
- Remember?
- An answer was already said.
You could've said the same city.
- You could've said the same city.
- You heard us in the last round.
She already has ten dollars ready.
How can you not know the capital cities?
Coach Pak!
Yes, I don't know them. So what?
(She pays the fine
with an absence of guilt.)
There's also Geneva.
- Geneva isn't the capital city.
- And Bern.
Geneva is just a city in Switzerland.
- What else is there?
- Switzerland's capital is Bern.
- There's France, Paris.
- Paris, of course.
Brussels, Belgium.
- England, London.
- London and Paris.
- There are many.
- Paris, Rome...
- What's the capital of Germany?
- Just so you know...
- Germany?
- Coach Pak glared at me just now.
- Why?
- As I named the cities...
- You are the annoying type.
- I kept on naming them.
- For a second,
- I flared up.
- What's the capital of Germany?
Is it Munich? What is it?
- Munich.
- What's the capital of Germany?
- Germany.
- That would be Berlin.
- Berlin, okay.
- What's Munich then?
- Just a city.
- A city in Germany.
Is it a city?
That was close.
- What was close?
- All right.
This is your third attempt.
- Start from there.
- We'll start with Jong Kook.
- Austria, Vienna.
- Right, Vienna.
- Vienna, noted.
- Let's do this.
- It'll be an easy one.
- Bern.
- Bern, Vienna...
- I can name ten by myself.
Bern, Vienna, and Rome.
- Here we go.
- This will be easy.
It's only ten.
Name Asian cities...
- that aren't in Korea.
- What...
- Three, two...
- Cities?
Tokyo.
Shanghai.
Hanoi.
Malaysia?
- What's the category?
- Asian cities.
- Just cities.
- Like Kuala Lumpur.
- She already has her money out.
- Hold on.
- Are you kidding me?
- She played with it in her hands.
That's how generous she is.
She is like Ji Hyo.
- Are you kidding me?
- What's all this?
I can afford it. So what?
It's mine, isn't it?
What can we say to that?
- Please pay the fine.
- It's here.
(Generous Madam Pak
is an earnest taxpayer.)
How adorable.
- You'll try again.
- Sure thing.
This is your fourth attempt.
Asian cities outside of Korea.
(Asian cities outside of Korea)
Shinjuku, Tokyo, and Shanghai.
Shinjuku isn't a city.
(Shinjuku?)
- What on earth?
- That's...
- Haha!
- It's a neighborhood.
- Seriously?
- Have you lost your mind?
- Just name one, darn it!
- You know what he told me?
- Why get ahead of yourself?
- What did I say wrong?
- Unbelievable.
- What was that?
- Shinjuku is a neighborhood.
- Shinjuku...
- Like Apgujeong.
- Guys, hear this.
He said I only had to say Shinjuku.
It's as if he was going
to name all ten cities.
- Because you said that...
- What you said is this.
So Shinjuku is a neighborhood
in the city of Tokyo.
- But Shanghai is a city, right?
- I apologize.
Are you kidding me?
- Kuala Lumpur.
- Pay the ten-dollar fine.
- I was only trying to help.
- Pay up.
- I'm sorry.
- Pay ten dollars.
- Please let it slide this once.
- It serves you right for boasting.
- Coach, you also...
- Okay, fine.
- Thank you.
- Shinjuku? What a joke.
Coach Pak already has her money out.
- Tokyo, Osaka, and...
- Unbelievable.
Osaka is a city, right?
- I'll name the most cities.
- Sure.
- I'll say the most.
- That sounds good.
Here we go again.
Jong Kook, we start with you.
All right.
- Capital cities in Europe.
- Good.
Rome.
Bern.
Vienna and Brussels.
Paris.
Luxembourg.
London and Lisbon.
- How many more do we need?
- Two.
- And Haha must say them?
- You said you'd take care of it!
Hold on.
- How many more do we need?
- Two.
- And Haha must say them?
- You said you'd take care of it!
Hold on.
- I thought it'd come around.
- Must it end with Haha?
- Must it end with him?
- We need to say all ten by then?
- I thought we could say more.
- No wonder it's a tough game.
- I thought it'd come back.
- We didn't know.
One must say at least two then.
- We had no idea.
- We didn't know.
Jae Suk,
- you said you'd name a lot for us.
- We didn't know.
- We had no idea.
- You only said two.
- This is the staff's fault.
- We didn't know.
Jae Suk promised...
He promised to say a lot.
But he named two cities
and glanced over at Se Ri.
(He only named two cities.)
(I'm done.)
- No wonder she was flustered.
- It's because...
- Even I was flustered.
- I didn't want...
to catch the others off guard.
I thought we'd get another chance.
- Me too.
- Same here.
- I thought that as well.
- Me too.
- So much for naming a lot.
- We must say at least two each.
- Only two...
- All I have to do...
is leave you with three.
- Okay.
- That's the plan.
- Good.
Luxembourg is mine.
- Okay.
- No one is allowed to say it.
- London and Lisbon are mine.
- Okay.
- We'll start with Haha.
- Then how many should I...
Jae Suk must say the rest.
- I'll make sure of it.
- Leave them with two.
- I must leave you with two.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Here we go.
- London and Lisbon.
- We'll start with Haha.
- Let's go.
Okay, I won't.
Milan?
- European countries.
- Countries?
What? Canada... No, wait!
Hold on.
(Is Canada in Europe?)
Unbelievable.
- Someone said Canada.
- Get over here.
- Someone said it.
- Why did you change it up?
- Get back here.
- Guys, wait.
- We were doing capital cities.
- I was just kidding.
- It was funny, right?
- France!
- I'll pay the ten-dollar fine.
- Germany!
I'll pay up, so don't be angry at me.
- Canada?
- Don't be angry at me.
- Didn't someone say Canada?
As if!
It did catch us off guard though.
The staff gave us an easy one.
The head coach must pay the fine.
Oh, then she should.
The staff gave us an easy one.
Countries in Europe.
How about a 1-on-1 battle then?
- Fine!
- Okay, fine.
How about a 1-on-1 battle then?
- I hate naming capital cities.
- I'd definitely win.
- We've moved on to countries.
- Countries.
I hate naming both of them!
- Seriously.
- Remember those.
- Let's go for it.
- I'll answer all except for two.
Okay. Let's try it first.
- There he goes again.
- Make sure to do that.
- You should do it.
- Say one answer each.
- Just keep going.
- I'll give five answers.
Let's go.
- Don't be intimidated. Let's do it.
- Let's do it.
All right. Here we go.
Asian cities outside of Korea.
- Cities.
- Three, two,
- one.
- Tokyo.
Shanghai, Osaka.
I was going to say Shanghai.
- All right. Hanoi.
- Okay.
Hanoi, and...
- You can't do that!
- Kuala...
Hey!
(And?)
(Hey!)
You're just too much.
I thought you were going
to say all the answers.
Why did you mention Shanghai...
- when I thought of it?
- Hey.
Is Shanghai the only city in Asia?
- You could've mentioned others.
- That made me flustered.
- There's Hanoi, Ho Chi Minh City...
- I was flustered.
- There's Jakarta too.
- The director is sneaky.
- You can't answer right away.
- He's sneaky.
Also, why do you say "all right"...
before you give your answer?
You were looking to stall time.
"All right."
It's okay. Coach Pak is rich.
- Let's begin with Haha this time.
- Okay.
(They only have two chances now.)
Don't look up!
I was looking up
the capital cities in Europe.
- Let's go!
- Let's start with Haha.
It's confusing because they keep
mixing the questions.
Name the states or cities of the US.
California.
Manhattan, LA.
Manhattan is...
Manhattan is not a city.
- What about Manhattan?
- It's a borough in New York City.
It's a borough.
It's just like Shinjuku.
Isn't that in the US?
That's in the US. The only places I know
are LA and Manhattan.
- Manhattan.
- It's in New York.
There are many different places
in New York?
(He's never heard of it.)
Oh, really? I didn't know.
Brooklyn is in New York.
How come we can never answer ten?
I'll try to answer it all this time,
Coach Pak.
The three of us should say
as many answers as we can.
We should do that.
- Here's the last question.
- Let's go.
It's the last question.
- Give us an easy one.
- This is quite hard.
- Weren't all the questions easy?
- Who would like to go first?
You can decide since it's the last one.
- From this side?
- I'll give only one answer.
You should all pass until my turn.
We can only win...
- if Jae Suk makes it.
- That's right.
Jae Suk needs to make it for us to win.
Seriously... All right. Let's do it.
Here we go.
Excuse me.
How come you keep excluding South Korea?
- Busan! It's a beautiful city.
- I'm just so curious.
- Daegu is such a beautiful city!
- Why do you keep excluding it?
- I love Gwangju!
- I love Korea so much.
- All right. Here we go.
- Why do you keep excluding it?
- Let's take our time.
- Let's do it.
Here we go.
Capital cities in Europe.
Paris.
London.
Lisbon.
Luxembourg.
- Bern.
- I was going to say that.
Rome.
Brussels.
- Three more to go.
- Zurich.
- Geneva.
- One more.
- The last one.
- We're naming capital cities!
Why do you keep mentioning that?
(He just says
whatever city comes to his mind.)
(Zurich, Geneva)
(Oh, right.)
- Zurich?
- Why do you keep mentioning that?
What's wrong with you?
We were supposed to name capital cities.
Why did you do that?
We were almost there.
- I said two answers though.
- I mean...
- I even named three.
- It's capital cities!
I can't remember capital cities,
to be honest.
- He's right.
- I thought of saying Bern,
but Coach Pak said it first,
so I thought the sky would fall.
(It was a bolt out of the blue for him.)
When you mentioned the answers
I had in mind...
Bern.
- So I could only think of Zurich.
- Right.
- Is Zurich a capital city?
- Zurich.
It's wrong, right?
I told you it's Bern. Zurich and
Geneva are cities in Switzerland.
You must love Switzerland.
He just loves Switzerland.
- This is really...
- It's not easy.
- It's because you're flustered.
- Right.
- When you watch it on TV...
- It looks easy.
But now that I'm shooting it myself,
I went all blank.
It's because you're flustered.
I noticed that every time.
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
My niece must be watching.
- Please pay your fine.
- How much did we pay in total?
You spent 90 dollars.
- I can't believe we failed this.
- We spent a lot.
It makes me feel ashamed.
Why did you give me the money
when you were going to take it?
He only gave it to you
so he could take it back.
All right. We'll carry on right away
after setting up the cameras.
- All right.
- We should play it with our senses,
not with our eyes.
All right!
(The players gather to play
the mission for holes 7 to 9.)
Are we jumping over this?
Oh, so there are lines here.
What's with this menu?
- I know.
- Coach Pak.
- The menu...
- Shouldn't we buy some of them?
The Hidden Option costs 200 dollars.
It's 200 dollars? It costs
200 dollars to reveal each option?
Then are you giving us something to eat?
(Hidden Option)
(They were told to pay 200 dollars
to find out the Hidden Option.)
- If you reveal the Hidden Option,
- Oh, only for the Hidden Option?
there's something written under it.
- Oh, if we pay 200 dollars...
- Then I'll pay for it.
- Only if we pay 200 dollars?
- Yes, we must pay first.
- Could it be food?
- Then let's pay up.
But this is... Here's what I think.
Even if we save on the money,
we can't use it outside anyway.
Coach Pak, I think you should
use the money when you have it.
Use it when you have it.
Use it to reveal the Hidden Option.
It'll go to waste if you save on it.
I think the staff hid a good option here.
- Coach Pak, it's a hidden option.
- I don't think it's something good.
We should reveal it now.
- It's all a lie. You've been there.
- Should we reveal it now?
- Don't be like this.
- We might end up...
getting the penalty.
- They already took 90 dollars.
- You're right.
- Coach Pak, listen to us.
- You should spend 200 dollars.
We're a team.
This isn't an individual game.
- Right.
- Coach Pak.
- Coach Pak, you should trust us.
- Let's reveal it.
- Then shall we split it?
- Pardon?
- Shall we split it?
- She's one crazy woman.
- Shall we all pay up?
- I'm sorry.
- She's crazy.
- Since we have the team money...
Coach Pak,
then I'll collect from everyone.
- I'll collect from them.
- You will?
- Give me some of your money.
- Why are you acting up again?
- Who are you to do that?
- Why are you acting up?
- Why?
- Why are you acting up again?
Gook Jin.
- We should pay at least half.
- Let's come up with 100 dollars.
Okay. That'll be better.
Let's split it. We'll pay 100 dollars.
- Okay.
- Here.
- You know when to spend money.
- Give it to me.
- Reveal the bottom option only.
You should reveal it, Coach Pak.
I'm not sure what it is,
but it must be worth...
- the money we spent.
- It must be something nice.
(They open the Hidden Option
with 200 dollars.)
- What is it?
- What is this?
- What does it say?
- "If you pay 500 dollars,"
"the coach can receive
the penalty as well."
- Come here.
- How much?
- Why would I...
- I see.
(Penalty ticket for Coach Pak)
(Come here.)
Why did I have to spend that money?
Give it back.
I don't want this.
- My gosh. This is absurd.
- This is...
- How much?
- I see.
(The opportunists
learned of something fun.)
Coach Pak...
There's no way we can
make 500 dollars until the end.
- This is...
- Hey.
- You can just disregard it.
- We don't have enough money anyway.
- I think...
- You're going to pay for this.
- If I get the penalty,
- I'll never buy it.
I'm going to make the director
pay for this.
- At the end...
- I mean it.
It'll only be possible
if they make us earn money easily...
- Of course, they will.
- toward the end.
- We can never earn 500 dollars.
- Forget it.
- We can never do that.
- I'll never buy it.
If you do, I'm going to slap you.
I decided to sacrifice my life...
- for Coach Pak.
- Okay.
Let's just work hard
and buy our exemption cards.
- Of course.
- There's no point.
Nonetheless, I'll make you pay for it.
The Hidden Option?
- Just wait and see.
- All right.
The third mission
for hole number 7 to number 9...
- is Hazard in the Air.
- I know that game.
- He got it.
- He threw it so well this time.
- How do I do it?
Did I?
- He got it.
What is he doing?
- He didn't look at it at all.
- You should look at it.
- He got it!
- Gosh, that was amazing.
- He got it.
- He got it. Great.
- He got it!
- Did he catch it?
You earned 1,000 dollars in total.
- All right!
- We did it. Good job.
We need to divide it
among ourselves again, right?
That's up to Coach Pak.
- She'll give it to me for sure.
- That was close though.
- This is...
- Who caught the balloon?
- Me. Us.
- Me. We caught the balloon.
- What about the ones who threw it?
- I threw it well.
- I contributed.
- Give to those who caught it first.
- I caught it and threw it.
- You caught it.
- Thank you.
- I threw the balloon.
- What about those who threw it?
- Fifty dollars for you.
- Thank you.
(Se Chan, Jong Kook, Haha, and
Jae Suk all received 50 dollars.)
- I threw the balloon.
- What about those who threw it?
(He's the only one
who didn't get the money.)
They caught it well
because I threw it well.
(Seok Sam is completely disregarded
every time she distributes money.)
- I should keep some for myself.
- No.
(Seok Sam is completely disregarded
every time she distributes money.)
Wait. Coach Pak.
- All right!
- Wait.
I'm done distributing it.
Coach Pak, is there a reason...
- you're acting this way?
- Not at all.
Is there a reason?
- It's not even real money.
- There's no reason.
I should be cool-headed.
He's so desperate.
He's 56 though.
- Coach Pak, don't fall for it.
- She's very adamant.
- Let's move on.
- Everyone.
The final nine holes...
are available on the Running Man's
golf course.
Is that so?
Let's move to the next place
and play some golf.
- All right.
- A golf course?
- We're going to a golf course.
- There's a golf course?
All right. Let's go!
Please put on your seatbelts.
- All right.
- Seatbelts.
- Let's put on our seatbelts.
- Where is it?
- Over here.
My gosh.
- Let's put this down.
- Gosh, that hurt.
- Come on!
- I'm sorry.
Come on, Suk Jin.
(The chair hit Se Ri's hand.)
- Come on!
- I'm sorry.
- She almost hurt her hand!
- Sorry.
- You'll be in big trouble...
- You're not hurt, are you?
- if you hurt her hand.
- Do you even know...
how much her guarantee is?
- Seriously, that guy...
- Be careful!
- You're not hurt, are you?
- How dare a lowly man like you...
- I'm sorry. Are you hurt?
Be careful! I'm apologizing!
How dare a lowly man like you hurt her?
- Are you all right?
- Are you okay?
- It hurts.
- Do you want me to blow on it?
- No, thanks.
- Do you...
(Do you want me to blow on it?)
Why would you blow on it?
What are you, a grandpa?
How dare a lowly man like you...
- I know!
- Which do you prefer?
Will this be better for you?
- This is better, right?
- That's fine.
You can put it here.
- I should text Suk Jin.
- What will you say?
She has her own standards.
She and Woo Sung seemed close.
- You mean Jung Woo Sung?
- He was on Running Man?
- He was.
He loves our restaurant.
- Oh, really? Woo Sung does?
- Yes.
Suk Jin. You got a text.
I got one. What is this?
I can't believe
he comes to our restaurant.
Gosh. Take a look at this.
He's my junior.
I'm older than him, you know.
And he texted me, "Behave yourself."
What do you think about this?
He texted me, "Behave yourself."
- But you're his senior.
- Well done.
Don't be rude...
- What do you think about this?
- Don't be rude to Coach Pak.
- Stop it.
- I said, don't be rude to her.
- This is...
- He wasn't behaving himself.
- Tell me about it.
- He kept acting up next to her.
- Think about it.
- It must be difficult for you.
- No, it's not that.
- You're all bullying him.
- No, that's not it.
- Coach Pak.
- That's not true.
I'm only telling him this on your behalf.
- Excuse me, Coach Pak.
- He deserves to be criticized.
The one who bullied me the most...
was you.
(You're the one who bullied me the most.)
You gave 50 dollars to everyone except me.
I was just being cool-headed.
Until when are you going to mention that?
- Stop with that talk already.
- Stop it.
I know. I'm done with the payment.
- She gave more money to us...
- Exactly.
- because we had too little.
- That's right.
She even gave you ten dollars.
- We've never had a guest like her.
Only those who received the money
are touched.
Suk Jin, you got another text.
- I got another one?
- Yes.
(This time, another junior comedian
sent the text.)
- I'm curious.
- Did he text me through KakaoTalk?
- How come you get so many texts?
- What did he say?
- He's really popular.
- He is.
- No, I'm...
(Laughing)
- What is it?
- Must I let this slide?
- What is it? What does it say?
- What does it say? Who sent it?
My junior comedian...
It's not even Jae Suk. It's Se Chan.
He told me to shut my mouth
and just look ahead.
(Shut your mouth and just look ahead.)
(His dear junior comedian advised him
to keep his eyes on the road.)
Just look ahead, will you?
- Just look ahead.
- I mean...
- Why do you keep turning?
- There's carp bread!
- That looks good!
- Hey!
How can I only look ahead
when a global star is sitting next to me?
That was hilarious.
- She's our legend.
- That's right.
Seriously...
- Okay.
- What is this?
What's this?
(What's this?)
- What's this?
- What is this?
They made a golf course?
What's this? A par-three hole?
- What's this?
- My goodness.
(Welcome to Running Man's Golf Course.)
- Look behind you.
- There's a bunker.
- Gosh.
- What is this?
There's water too.
There's a bunker too!
What's happening? This is incredible.
They made a golf course.
- What's this?
- There's water.
(A detailed replica of a golf course)
- My gosh.
- What's happening?
- This is unbelievable.
- This is...
Running Man is on another level.
You guys did so much work.
What's this?
- Goodness, what are you doing?
- This is so cool.
You spent all the money on this.
- What's this?
- It's like "Let's Go! Dream Team."
(What kind of game will they play here?)
Please gather.
Let me tell you about the rules
of the remaining nine holes.
- All right.
- What are they?
Your high-level golf skills
and a little bit of luck...
will come in handy in this mission.
It's called Sticking Golf.
- What's that?
- It must be made of Velcro.
On a golf course made of Velcro,
you're going to play golf
using a golf ball made of Velcro.
Keep in mind that the ball might not roll
as it sticks on the course.
My gosh.
It'll be a match between 2 teams of 3.
Two balls will be given to each team.
The team that puts both balls
in the hole first wins.
- In that hole?
- Yes.
Oh, to that hole?
(Each team gets 2 balls.)
(The team that puts both balls
in the hole first wins.)
The winning team...
will receive 1,500 dollars
as prize money.
- We'll get 1,500 dollars?
- If Team Se Ri wins,
the three of you will take
300 dollars each.
For the remaining 600 dollars,
Se Ri can distribute it however she wants.
This must be it.
This must be the last round.
All right. Let's do it.
If the other team wins,
the three of you
can take 500 dollars each.
- All right. This must be it.
- We're taking 500 dollars each.
Then which clubs are we using?
Please bring in the clubs.
- We must be using real clubs.
- I don't think so.
- See?
- What is that?
Please bring in the balls too.
Haha, I think it won't matter
for both of us.
- It has nothing to do with skills.
- Right. It doesn't matter.
- This is...
- They're just toys.
- Even I can't play well with them.
- That's true.
You must use both hands
like how you play real golf.
That's a basic rule.
We divided you into different teams,
considering the skill difference.
The first team is Team Se Ri.
- I must be on her team.
- It's Se Chan and Haha.
- Gosh!
- Great. Why?
- Because I love it so much.
- We can do it.
- I love it.
- Coach Pak.
- We should win big dollars.
- Let's do it.
- We can do it. We've done it.
- Let's give it a try.
Give us 50 dollars each
to celebrate us becoming a team.
- What do you say?
- That's right.
If you give us 50 dollars each,
it'll motivate us.
- All right. Give me five.
- I'll really do my best.
- You'll do your best?
- I'll give it my all!
- I'll really do my best.
- Thank you.
Since I have more money...
- Didn't I do well?
- You did.
Stand behind the start line.
You'll take turns to play.
It's going to fall into
the water for sure.
It will.
- Gosh.
- It won't be easy.
What happens if the ball
falls into the hazard?
- We can re-drop it?
- Yes, you can.
Haha. This won't do.
We should play like this.
(Sticking right on the golf course)
Oh, it sticks onto it right away.
Wait a minute.
Has the director tried playing this?
- Have you?
- Of course.
How many times?
How many times have you tried?
(Through many simulations,
we found the perfect grass for the show.)
- Gosh, this is...
- You can't hit it?
- It's difficult.
- Give it a try.
(The amateur golfers can't go beyond 1m.)
- Darn it.
- I'm sure the total number...
Suk Jin, I think
we'll get 400 strokes for this hole.
My gosh, this is...
- I'll play now.
- Yes, let's start.
Here's the first player
for the final hole.
I want to beat them.
- I'm going to beat them.
- It's like gateball.
The key to leading the game
is to hit the tee shot well...
and keep the ball on the fairway.
- You hit so well.
- That went pretty far.
(Nice shot.)
- That was a great tee shot.
- Right?
- It was a long drive.
- You call this a long drive?
I'll hit it first,
then you can hit it over the water.
Would it be better if you hit it?
- All right. We'll play.
- Hit it high and as far as you can.
It'll be embarrassing
if you can't hit it as far as I did.
This isn't easy.
- Don't provoke them.
- That's right.
I think she'll be bad at it.
- Will this work?
- She still got the swing.
It's so funny how she still has the swing.
- How can she still swing like that?
Her swing is incredible. It's amazing.
(She manages to make
the Velcro ball fly in an arc.)
- She hit a long drive.
- Nice shot, Se Ri.
- It was a long drive.
- A long drive. Well done.
Nice shot, Se Ri.
- It was a long drive.
- A long drive. Well done.
You can hit the second ball
or the ball on the course.
You need to put both balls in the hole.
- Oh, there are two balls?
- Yes.
- It's their turn anyway.
- All right.
(Yoo Gook Jin,
an expert talker on golf courses)
It might be better to hit from here.
- Right? I should hit from behind.
- Yes.
Give it an impact. That's what matters.
You got it.
It's pretty good. It's a long drive.
- It's a long drive.
- You did well.
You did well. It's a long drive.
You should try...
and scoop up the ball as much as
you can. You know it, right?
Like this?
- Hey!
- Hey, that's...
We should cut down everything
that gets in the way.
- This is also...
- Be careful.
- This is also part of the game.
- Here I go.
- Hit it high.
- I don't think he can do it.
He's going to drop it
right in front of him.
That's it. All right.
(It only went 1m forward.)
You should hit it high.
Gosh, my back hurts.
- That was weak.
- Gosh, this is upsetting.
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
- Is it my turn?
Let's just avoid
hitting it into the hazard.
(Protein Kim, often appears
at Giheung Country Club)
Just hit it straight.
- All right.
- Good shot.
He can do that?
- You got this.
- We can allow that.
- That was...
- Great job.
Haha, just push it like this.
- What's that? You can't do that.
- Hey!
- You're hitting it with your hand.
- Michelle Wie does this.
- He should put both hands together.
- Michelle Wie?
Coach Pak.
- Be quiet when someone plays.
- That's...
- Just push it.
- He won't do well.
(Ha Dong Hoon, estimated to be 168cm tall)
- Nice!
- All right. That wasn't bad.
(The little golfer
hit it better than expected.)
You hit it well.
Next player. Hey, that's ours.
- That's our ball.
- I'm just pushing it down.
- Hey, punk. That's our ball.
- I just pushed it down.
- How can you touch our ball?
- Why would you push it?
- We'll allow that.
- Hit the bottom part.
Hit the bottom part.
- You touched the ball.
- That's one stroke.
- That's one stroke!
- He touched the ball!
- He touched the ball.
- That's one stroke.
- He really did.
- Stop the nonsense.
It... It doesn't matter
if they touch the ball.
- Just hit it like that.
- It...
If it's allowed, you can do it.
I'm going to hit it however I want.
- What is he doing?
- That's really annoying.
You should pull back a little.
- All right!
- Come on.
My gosh.
- You didn't have to swing so much.
- All right.
(Laughing)
- It's your turn.
- Is it?
- My goodness.
- You should pull back only a bit.
- It's my turn. That's mine.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk presses down the ball.)
- Don't step on it!
What do you mean?
It just happened to be on my way.
- Let me pat it.
- He didn't step on the ball, punk.
My gosh.
(Staring sharply)
Wasn't that the parallel universe theory?
- Right?
- I thought they were twins.
You need to push it.
Gosh, she's indeed great.
- Her swing is amazing.
- She still got her swing.
(They say giving compliments is
a classy way to keep them in check.)
- My gosh.
- Not bad.
What do you mean it wasn't bad?
It was bad.
This isn't easy.
- Darn it.
- Hit it.
- Hey!
- Wait a minute!
Why would you...
- You stepped on the ball!
- It's dented!
- I thought that was allowed.
- She just crushed it.
Wait. The ball is dented.
(She's completely adjusted
to Running Man's rules of golf.)
- Hey.
- Don't be too greedy.
They touched the ball.
- Nice posture.
- It'll be a long drive.
Great.
(Will he do well when they're
endlessly holding him in check?)
He's going to hit behind the ball.
I don't think this will work.
- Wait.
- Wait. It must be in the water.
(He hit it pretty far.)
- It's in the hazard.
- It's in the hazard, right?
- Is it in the hazard?
- It didn't fall in the hazard.
- It's there.
- It's stuck on the wall.
(Luckily, it didn't fall in the water.)
- How do we hit that?
- Well done.
(It narrowly missed the hazard
and is stuck on the wall.)
You hit it well.
- You did well. It wasn't easy.
- You did really well.
- My gosh.
- I'll try and hit it over.
You should hit it to the top.
You can't brush it like that.
- Hey.
- Just let him do it.
It's okay as long as
he does the backswing.
- You can't just push it.
- I'm going to hit it like this.
It's a practice swing.
You're supposed to hit the ball,
not push the ball.
I'm hitting it. Like this.
Go ahead.
Isn't he holding the club too short?
- Nice!
- All right.
Isn't he holding the club too short?
- It's stuck on the wall.
- Wait a minute.
- He held it too short.
- It's stuck on the wall!
How am I supposed to hit it
when it's on the wall?
- You can push it up like this.
- Go for it.
- Hit it.
- Hit it to the other side.
- You must hit it to the other side.
(Current location)
- What are we doing?
- Hit it to the other side.
The crew could make this game
since they aren't exactly normal.
Send it over.
- Okay.
- No.
(A whiff)
It wasn't a stroke.
- It wasn't a stroke.
- Yes, it was.
- It was a stroke.
- We saw it.
- Okay.
- It was a stroke.
- Hey.
- You wanted to hit it.
- The intention wasn't there.
- The intention was there.
The intention wasn't there.
- Yes, it was.
- It was 100 percent there.
It was a stroke.
- Why couldn't you hit the ball?
- It was a stroke.
- I will hit it. Move.
- Why couldn't you hit the ball?
- It was a stroke.
You missed it.
There you go.
- All right.
- Okay. Go.
Hit it hard.
There you go.
(He said golf is all about hitting,
not pushing.)
There you go.
- When will you hit it?
- There you go.
Scrape the floor.
- Okay.
- For goodness' sake.
- This won't do.
- We are in trouble.
- I warned you.
- It will be hard to hit.
We are in trouble.
- Se Ri.
- You should have sent it over.
Se Ri, we need to get the ball
over the hazard.
- I know.
- Things became difficult.
I should really send it up.
She yelled at us about it earlier,
but she is scraping the floor now.
- I watched and learned.
- Scrape the floor.
Sending the ball over the hazard
is the priority. All right.
I can tell that you are having fun.
(Giggling)
- Scrape the floor.
- I hate losing.
(The legendary golfer only made
winning shots in her life.)
(Will she do the same this time?)
- Scrape the floor.
- I hate losing.
(She made a decisive move
by moving the ball by 8cm.)
It was a stroke.
- Okay. You did it.
- You did it.
- Did you see it? It moved.
- I hit the ball.
- You hit the ball. Let's go.
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh, this is bad.
- Both of us need to do it.
- Which ball will you hit?
- It will be a difficult task.
- Send it up like this.
This kind of golf is
absolutely ridiculous.
This is absolutely ridiculous.
- Do it, Jae Suk.
- I will scrape the wall like this.
Keep the club short.
- You have never done this before.
- Keep the club short.
It will come up well.
This is the worst trouble shot.
- Keep the club short.
- You have never done this before.
- You can do it.
- It will be the first in Korea.
I think it will be easy
to send the ball up.
All right.
- Okay.
- Come on.
You need to keep using it.
- You need to keep using that club.
- Hold on.
- Let's go.
- You need to be careful.
There you go.
You are good.
- You are thorough.
- Seriously.
You are like a professional golfer.
Darn it!
(He misses again!)
- Did he miss again?
- He missed the ball.
- Here I go.
- Go.
- It will be a nice shot.
This is so hard.
- Nice. Okay.
- I sent it over the cliff.
This is so hard.
- Nice. Okay.
- I sent it over the cliff.
- Okay.
- You did it.
- All right.
- It's Seok Sam's turn.
Okay. Go first.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
- What?
- You know,
- I will put it on the wall first.
- You should do that.
- I should do that, right?
- Yes. Put it on the wall.
Scrape the floor and send it up.
There is no other way.
- There you go.
- Nice.
- Okay.
- Suk Jin.
- It was a difficult shot.
- That was the absolute worst.
How could you ask me to do
something so hard?
That was the absolute worst.
Go.
- Okay.
- Not bad.
- Gosh.
- We need to work on them.
- Firstly,
- put it on the wall.
- Okay.
- Dig it out.
- Here we go.
There is no need to be ambitious.
- Put it on the wall.
- One.
Okay. It was a stroke.
- Put it on the wall.
- One.
Okay. It was a stroke.
- For goodness' sake.
- What was that?
Why did you send it to a corner?
I told you to dig it up.
(He sent the ball to a corner.)
Everyone, this is a gentlemen's sport.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Now...
I will hold the rope.
- Go ahead.
- We have a lot of money.
- I am ready.
- Go ahead.
A bit forward, Haha.
A bit forward. Okay.
(It's time to show the skills
of Dongducheon's Broom.)
Okay.
Here I go.
- Okay.
- There was an intention.
- There was an intention, right?
- No!
There was an intention. Come on out.
- It was a stroke.
- Come on out.
(There was an intention
in his solemn "Here I go.")
- It was a stroke.
- Hey.
- It's impossible.
- How did you do that?
We are in trouble.
- Dig it out.
- Send it up a bit at a time.
(The problem-solver appears.)
Is this really golf?
- What is this?
- No. Golf isn't like this.
- How will he get it out?
- Go ahead.
(The Running Golf Course
is quite suspicious.)
Go ahead.
(Screaming)
You did it.
- You are a technician.
- He used his strength.
He used his strength.
This is driving me crazy.
Do you want me to hold it?
Send it up gently.
(The wall-climbing match continues!)
Okay. Nice.
Send it up.
- It wasn't that bad.
- Good job.
- Se Ri.
Hold on. Don't touch me.
My shoulders got dislocated.
Your shoulders got dislocated.
That's right.
You need to watch your shoulders.
- Her shoulders got dislocated.
- Why?
I don't know. I guess they can come off.
(He suddenly says that
Se Ri's shoulders can come off.)
Nonsense.
- Her shoulders can come off.
- They are like Lego.
Hold on.
- Can you do that?
- You can't do that.
- Coach Pak.
- The ball has to hit here.
- There has to be a swing.
You can't do that.
You can hit it like that.
No, you can't.
- How is this so different?
- There has to be a swing.
- You can't do this. Watch.
- You are talking nonsense.
You have to hit it like this.
- Come on.
- How is this so different?
- There is no difference.
- You can't do that.
- They look good together.
- Watch.
- Decalcomania.
- If you do this,
- it will be like the pool.
- This could be a meme.
It will be like the pool.
- Listen.
- Hit it like this.
- You need to swing the club.
That's right. There has to be a swing.
Are you calling this a swing?
That's right. You should do that.
Hit the ball like this.
- Unbelievable. Come over here.
- Listen. The handle is the axis.
The head should move.
There you go.
Just send it up a little.
If it falls into the water...
Why are you being so chatty
when I am playing golf?
- I was just giving advice.
- Fine.
- All right.
- I will hit it in my style.
Stop telling me what to do.
Go ahead. Swing.
Okay. That's the way to do it.
There you go. That's good.
- She did it.
- See?
- You are so good.
- My advice helped!
- Where did it go?
- It went up.
- Good shot.
- We need to work on that one next.
- Jae Suk.
Nice one.
- You saw what she did.
- Yes, I did.
You should do it like that. Hold on.
What are you doing?
Why are you using your left hand?
You aren't left-handed.
I have my right hand on the handle.
- I don't think that's correct.
- It's correct.
Shouldn't you hold it backward?
Shouldn't you hit it like this?
- Go ahead.
- I plan to send it up.
- It will go up.
- Okay.
- See?
- What did I tell you?
- Hey.
- It will go up.
- Okay.
See?
- What did I tell you?
- Hey.
- You should hit it like this.
- Watch.
You should hit it like this
with your right hand.
For goodness' sake.
Why did you hit it like this?
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
(Each team has one ball in the hazard.)
You should hit it like this
with your right hand.
(Se Chan, the professional golfer,
thinks about what will be funny.)
(Is he reenacting that moment?)
(As if he made up his mind,)
(Se Chan takes off his socks.)
(In 1998, Se Ri gave energy
to the nation.)
(Like her, Se Chan
will hit a shot barefooted.)
- Haha, support him.
- You know,
his feet stink.
The sour smell is traveling up.
- Seriously.
- His feet really are a hazard.
- They really stink.
- They are a biohazard.
(Every spot Sour Feet touches
is a hazard.)
You shouldn't go into the water.
His feet stink.
- Hey.
- Haha, hold the rope.
There you go.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Lean back a bit more.
- A bit more.
- So Min will fall for you.
Se Chan.
If you fall backward...
- It will be funny.
- Send it to the left.
Send it to the left.
It will be really funny
if the ball falls into the water.
- Like this?
- It should hit the camera first.
- There you go.
One, two.
- Okay.
- It was a stroke.
- I can't send it up.
- It's our turn.
Since you took off your shoes,
you should go into the water.
- Okay.
- Okay. We did it.
- Are you calling this a swing?
- Nice.
- We won.
- We are at an advantage.
- Okay.
- Things are getting serious.
- This is bad.
- Scrape the floor.
Don't think about sending it up. Okay.
- It won't end today.
- Okay.
(The petty golf round continues on!)
- I think it will work.
- It's okay.
I will send it up.
Watch.
- Suk Jin.
- I am the king of approach shots.
- Okay?
- Move out of the way.
Suk Jin, don't hit it hard.
No. It will be too hard.
- No.
- It will be too hard.
(However, the green has a steep slope.)
The closer you are to the hole,
the slope will be steep.
(There is a danger of sending
the ball to the other side.)
Don't hit it hard.
It just needs to climb up the hill.
He doesn't even listen to Coach Pak.
You need to put it on the top.
- You need to put it on the top.
- I knew it.
I told you so!
(It passes the hole
and stops at the velcro slope.)
We can hit it from there.
Will you send it over there?
Why don't you send it that way?
It won't go as I plan.
This isn't proper golf.
This is ridiculous.
Isn't she exactly like Jong Kook?
Daejeon Loser.
(They even get angry the same way.)
Okay.
- It's okay.
- It's here.
It's hard to put it on the top.
Yes. You need to measure
the distance right.
A bit more. Okay.
That's good.
This is hard.
It's on the velcro.
It's a good spot.
Jae Suk, it's close to the hole.
Let's go.
(Team Se Ri has a long way to go.)
All right.
- Nice.
- Good.
- Go ahead.
(The little golfer's long shot
helps them advance.)
- Is it our turn?
- Hey.
If you get the direction right,
- it will go in.
- They are almost done.
- Jae Suk.
- Aim to put it into the hole.
- Okay.
- If you get the direction right,
- it will go in.
- Okay.
The hole is very big. It will go in.
- It's very big.
- It will go in.
- Aim to put it into the hole.
This isn't easy.
- Here I go.
- Aim to put it into the hole.
- Let's put it into the hole.
- Don't hit it too hard.
- Okay.
- Hit it gently.
(This is Jae Suk's chance to get ahead.)
This is hard.
- Let's put it into the hole.
- Don't hit it too hard.
He might succeed.
The direction is off.
- Adjust the direction.
- Okay. There you go.
- That's good. Hit it.
- Hit it hard.
- Okay.
- He touched the ball.
- Hit it.
- Hit it hard. Okay.
He touched the ball.
Good job.
Hey. Who is going next?
- Do you want to try it?
- Go ahead.
- It's not easy.
- I will try it.
You need to hit it gently. Not yet.
Not yet. It isn't our turn.
How do you push it?
I think she will put it in the hole
in one go.
The velcro is in the way.
Put it on the top of the slope.
- Not bad.
- Okay.
We are set.
- I am so annoyed.
- Scrape the floor.
Scrape the floor.
Hit it gently. There you go.
Just get the direction right.
- It will be too hard.
- The direction.
The hole is big.
It will come this way.
- Gosh!
- I told you it will come this way.
- Okay.
- I told you it will be too hard.
- I hit it too hard.
- I told you so.
It's not easy to control your strength.
This is hard.
Send it on top of the hill.
It will be better
to send it over the hill.
- You know,
- Not bad.
- this is hard.
- I will hit this one.
- Aim to put it into the hole.
- Here.
- I will do that.
Jong Kook,
aim to put it into the hole.
- Suk Jin seems to be on the field.
- I will put it in.
I will put it into the hole.
If you want to see the line,
you should hit it this way.
This way.
It will hit the ground and...
Why didn't you do that?
The distance was too short on this side.
- I will aim to put it in.
- This way.
- Totally.
- Yes.
All right.
- It's coming.
- Gosh.
- Stop.
- Okay.
It's our turn.
I think it will go back and forth.
I don't think
we will get it done by today.
- This is getting serious.
- I know.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
- Well done.
- Put it here.
- Aim to put it in the hole.
Get the direction right.
- Get the direction right.
It's okay if it goes to the other side.
(Dragging)
What was that?
(His chance evaporates
with a petty sound.)
- Can't you move it more than 10cm?
- Why are you so timid?
You are so timid. Just hit it hard.
You need to put the ball
on the top of the hill.
He really looks like a coward
from the back.
Seriously. Gook Jin.
Seriously.
- We will go.
- You moved it 3cm and 10cm.
I can't see it.
- She is serious.
- Let's move a little at a time.
She has a serious look on her face.
I hope I can send it into the hole
at once.
The two teams are
in similar positions now.
They might succeed first.
(What will be the result?)
She sent it up.
- She sent it up.
- Okay.
(A nice chip shot
sent the ball close to the hole.)
It was an approach shot.
- Good.
- Get the direction right.
You will hit it too hard.
- No. Look.
- Listen.
There is no angle.
- It's...
- I think the ball will go...
- in a curve.
- No.
It won't happen. It looks that way,
but the ground is flat.
You need to focus on the direction.
Hit it like that.
It will be impossible to succeed at once.
He is done.
I am sorry,
but are you a comedy team?
(I am sorry,
but are you a comedy team?)
- No, we aren't.
- Se Chan, go ahead.
Go ahead.
I am sick and tired of this.
- Good. My goodness.
- That startled me.
Okay.
- We are in the same position now.
- Yes.
- Not bad.
We are set.
- Here I go.
- Practice.
- Go.
- Push it forward.
(At that moment,)
(Haha's shot heads toward the hole.)
- Gosh.
- You did well.
- Jae Suk.
- This is it.
Don't hit it too hard.
It will reach the flat ground right away.
- There you go.
- Gosh!
We are in the same position.
- It's okay.
- This is...
(It's a nerve-racking match.)
We can send it onto the mound.
- It's my turn, right?
- One by one...
- This is so stressful.
- Try hitting that ball.
- No. I will hit this ball.
- This is so stressful.
- I will put it on the mound.
- That's right.
- Hit it gently.
- This ball.
- What do you think?
- That's a good idea.
What?
That's a good idea.
(Se Chan makes a lucky shot
and surprises everyone.)
He did it.
(It goes into the hole cleanly.)
(Dongducheon's Tiger Woods
putted the ball nicely.)
- Good job.
- Nice.
(They got ahead of Team Old Men
in the end.)
- We can put it in the hole.
- I will keep it there.
- Let's put it in the hole.
- I can't believe it went in.
Unbelievable.
I got so lucky.
Jong Kook, let's put it in the hole.
- Here I go.
- Three.
(The ball rolls toward the hole.)
(Will it go into the hole?)
(It passes through the hole.)
It almost went in beautifully.
I think she will succeed.
Se Ri, just put it on top of the mount.
I want to do that.
Hit it gently.
Se Ri, hit it gently.
It's okay if it goes over.
- Not bad.
- Okay.
- Stop.
- It's pretty bad.
It's very bad.
Suk Jin, hit it gently.
- Like this?
- No. It will be too hard.
- Will it be too hard?
- Just put it on top of the mound.
- Here?
- Yes.
- That's right.
Hit it like that.
Just get the direction right.
- Nice.
- I told you to put it on the top.
Stop.
(Suk Jin misses once again.)
I told you to put it on the top.
Gently.
- I told you to put it on the top.
- It was hard.
Hit it gently like the last time.
You did it just now.
(The man who succeeded first,
Yang Woods goes next.)
Just put it on top right here.
It's better than sending it down.
- You did it.
Stop. Oh, yes.
- Nice.
- Oh, yes.
- Yes!
- Nice!
- You did it. Stop.
- You did it.
(The ball rolls beautifully...)
(and lands next to the hole.)
- You are a genius.
- It was a good shot!
(We are ruined.)
(Try to push their ball away.)
- Try to push their ball away.
- You are a genius.
It was a good shot!
Mark the ball. Hold on.
- Jong Kook, hit this ball.
- Mark the ball.
- Can't we mark the ball?
- We will keep going as we are.
- Hit this ball. You have to do it.
- No.
- That's the only way.
- You have to do it.
- Send it through here.
- Yes.
You have to hit it.
(It's their last chance,
so he must hit the ball.)
- Good.
- Hit it.
- You have to hit it. Good.
- He missed.
- Hey.
I told you to hit this ball.
- I tried.
- Hey.
- Who will finish it up?
- Me.
In my time playing golf...
Haha, this is an easy shot.
Don't be flippant.
- Hey.
- Don't be flippant.
- Hit it gently.
- Hit it hard.
Hit it gently.
- Haha!
- Nice!
(Haha wrapped it up.)
- Good shot.
- Nice!
- It was impossible to miss.
- We almost lost, right?
- We should have won.
- Good job.
- Good shot.
- Nice!
- It was impossible to miss.
- We almost lost, right?
- We should have won.
- Good job.
Se Chan, thank you.
- Golf is really fun.
- You did really well.
You are good.
Nice.
Haha, take it home.
- We were losing.
- I know.
(So Wool, did you see that?)
I can't believe we won.
- When it went into the water...
- I know.
We fought well.
- We fought well.
We couldn't wrap it up nicely.
Team Se Ri will receive 1,500 dollars.
(They receive the prize money
of 1,500 dollars.)
This is the money you will distribute.
I will give 300 dollars to each member.
- We will receive more money.
- Their situation suddenly improved.
- I will distribute this money.
- Oh, yes.
Their situation suddenly improved.
- We fought fair and square.
- Yes.
We didn't want to be on a different team.
- Things were decided that way.
- I know.
- I will give you 50 dollars each.
- Thank you.
All right. It's time for the ending.
I will let you see
the price on the menu now.
How much is it?
- Penalty.
- This is insane.
I bet it's ridiculously expensive.
- Penalty exemption card.
- How much is it?
Let's see it.
- It's 300 dollars.
- You can buy the exemption card.
I will be exempt.
(Haha and Se Chan can purchase
the penalty exemption card.)
- There is nothing to buy.
- The sirloin set.
The Korean beef sirloin set
costs 500 dollars.
I want to buy it.
You should purchase it.
The pork set costs 300 dollars.
The Waffle maker and dough set
costs 200 dollars.
Why is everything so expensive?
Look at the Korean beef.
The grade is two plus.
Say the item name as you pay.
I have 30 dollars.
You said it's 300 dollars, right?
- Haha.
- Hold on.
Hold on. I can buy something.
- Please give me 70 dollars.
- Is the pork set 300 dollars?
Hey.
Don't you think my life matters more...
than the pork set?
I will buy it for you afterward.
Three, four...
- I will buy it for you afterward.
- Four, five...
- I will...
- I can buy the waffle maker.
I will buy you a waffle maker.
Please give me 70 dollars.
- Jae Suk.
- Thank you.
- Seriously.
Thank you.
- That's incredible.
- Would you give me ten dollars?
Thank you. She is the best.
- I just need 20 dollars.
- In that case,
I will purchase the exemption card.
- Are you exempt now?
- She is incredible.
- Coach Pak is incredible.
- The pork set.
The pork set
and an exemption card for Haha.
I will purchase an exemption card.
Jae Suk purchased an exemption card.
- It was exhausting.
- The pork set.
Thanks to Coach Pak,
I can purchase an exemption card.
- Counting 10, 20...
- Do you have enough?
Don't you need to buy something?
- Come on.
- Like the Korean beef set?
(She even saves her doppelganger.)
- No.
- Will everyone be exempt?
- No one will receive the penalty.
Would that be okay?
- That would be okay, right?
- Would that be okay?
Would that be okay?
I will purchase a waffle maker
for my niece.
(She purchases a waffle maker
for her niece.)
You should take one for your children.
It's okay. I have one at home.
- A waffle maker?
- Yes.
- Then please give me one.
- Okay. Give me another one.
- What was that?
- Hey.
- Why are you...
- Hold on.
- She offered it.
- Why are you taking a present?
Why are you taking a present?
- It's 300 dollars.
- Is it 300 dollars?
It's less than 200 dollars.
I will give you 30 dollars as a tip.
(She uses up the prize money
in a heartwarming way.)
She used the money in a cool way.
Se Chan, what will you purchase?
- Everyone is exempt.
- Coach Pak used the money for us.
What will you do?
Can I purchase
the penalty ticket for Coach Pak?
Hey.
Can I purchase
the penalty ticket for Coach Pak?
I can purchase it
because I have 500 dollars.
I have exactly 500 dollars.
Give me back the money.
That transaction is over.
- Give it to me. It isn't over.
- It's over.
I will pay up.
- Are you a thug?
- Penalty ticket for Coach Pak.
Are you a thug?
Se Ri, you visited the show.
- Coach Pak will take the penalty.
- That's right.
- She is cool.
- She is cool indeed.
She gave us everything.
It's quite original.
"Are you a thug?"
In that case, Se Chan and Se Ri...
- will receive the penalty.
- Okay.
Here is the penalty.
We put a lot of work
into this golf course,
so please have another match
before you go home.
(Have another match before you go home.)
It's an honor for me.
When else would I play golf
with the national hero,
Se Ri?
That's so funny.
The generous woman, Coach Pak Se Ri.
Thank you so much.
She is really generous.
I won't let you off.
- We should have another round.
- Yes.
Let's have another round.
(It's a perfect day to gamble.)
(Card Shark Association is back...)
(for a higher play.)
(We have enough people to win money.)
(Now we need people to lose money.)
(Pushover Joo is back.)
(They need some
under-the-table negotiations.)
(Psychological warfare is optional.)
(You can't trust anyone!)
(There's no winner or pushover
in the world of variety shows.)
(You try to seize a chance of victory,)
(but you might end up
becoming a pushover.)
(You can't become a card shark
without risking your life.)
Together?
I'll definitely go.
(Flustered)
(Who will win this round
and make a fortune?)
(Chairperson Ha)
(Corporal Kook, Yoo Gook Jin)
(Jjabkku, Ppikku)
(And Pushover Joo)
(Card Shark Association,
Through the Card Sharks' Minds)