(A live cafe in Gangnam)
(The opening takes part
on the stage with a mirrorball.)
Hello, Suk Jin.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Gosh, So Min.
- How have you been?
Hello.
You're suffering.
- I'm not suffering.
- Suffering?
- It breaks my heart.
- Suk Jin.
- Hello.
- It's not...
It's not that she's suffering.
She's just injured.
Injured?
She's suffering from injury.
- Here.
- Are you okay?
Hey, don't use the foot.
- Be careful.
- I'm being careful.
She's obviously not using the foot.
And he made me really upset.
Should I talk about it?
- What?
- Why?
The floor level wasn't right
for So Min's wheelchair.
And Suk Jin was like,
"Hang on. What do I do?"
Then he just pretended to lift it up.
He's the worst.
Why?
Do you know what Suk Jin just said?
- What did he say?
- I just managed to sit here,
but he told me to move over.
Why would you say that?
So Min is back after a long time.
- Isn't this nice?
- She was waiting at a cafe...
having some coffee.
- She's really happy.
- She said she was happy.
Anyway, So Min and Ji Hyo are back.
But where's Haha?
Why isn't Dong Hoon here yet?
Haha and Se Chan.
- Se Chan is...
- Se Chan is in quarantine.
- Did you not know that?
- He's in quarantine.
- Is he in quarantine?
Do you not know what happened?
She has no idea.
He came in close contact
with Hyun Moo.
- That's right.
- So he's in quarantine.
He's in home quarantine for a week.
- Today...
- So Se Chan is not coming today.
- Right.
- He's not coming?
Hello.
- Haha.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- What? Haha.
- You look good today.
- Thank you.
- Haha.
- He shaved his head.
- Did you shave your head?
- What's with your hair?
- He's bald.
- Right.
- Show us your hair.
- Show us.
Why did you shave? What happened?
- Let us see.
- It's nothing.
- Did you shave your head?
- Why would you...
- Why?
- Why did you shave your head?
- Why would you do that?
- Why? Is it defiance?
- Are you heartbroken?
- For fun?
Can you show us? Just once.
- This is no big deal.
- My goodness.
This is no big deal.
(A bald kid)
It's a gesture of defiance.
(He finds it hilarious.)
- People say...
- You punk.
- Gosh, Haha.
- I look like an old baby.
It will be fun to tease him.
Don't make me angry.
I'll take off the beanie.
- He's a rebellious kid.
- He's a rebel.
We have a lot of news today.
First of all, Jong Kook got...
partial microblading.
- That's right.
- Really? Let me see.
- What?
- Here.
- On the empty part.
- I see.
- I'm getting one tomorrow.
- It looks good.
I got one a year ago.
And So Min is back.
It's not getting better soon, right?
- It's not like when you were young.
- It's so uncomfortable.
She had an operation.
You shouldn't just rest.
You should do leg exercises.
- He keeps saying that.
- To recover your balance...
Your leg will be hairy
when you get the cast off.
- Right. It will be very hairy.
- Is that true?
And it will look like a skewer.
It happened to me before.
Your leg becomes thin.
My legs have been thin since then.
- You've always had thin legs.
- You just have thin legs.
You wore a cast on one leg,
but both your legs are slim.
Because they've been balanced.
Why are your legs so slim?
It's just that I'm slim.
Suk Jin, calves are
like the second heart.
Your heart looks horrible.
Right. Those with slim calves...
You need to work out.
- That's not true.
- Calves are the second heart?
- I've never heard of that before.
- I'm serious.
- That's true.
- You just made that up.
- It's the legs.
- Your calves...
They say
calves are the second heart.
It's true that legs are
important for your health.
- Of course.
- What about you?
- Look at my legs.
- Your legs are like skewers.
I have firm legs.
- My legs are firm too.
- Where?
- They are solid.
- Can I give it a squeeze?
Go ahead and squeeze it.
- They are really firm.
- Let me see.
- Squeeze them.
- Darn it!
- They are not firm at all.
- Gosh.
- It shouldn't hurt when I squeeze
- He's right.
I work out a lot,
so it doesn't hurt.
Of course not.
Those who work out a lot
don't feel pain here.
- Hit me hard.
- They are firm.
- Hit me. It doesn't hurt.
- Hit you?
(Punching)
(A fiery fist on his skinny thigh)
- That was really loud.
- It doesn't hurt at all, right?
(A fiery fist on his skinny thighs)
It made a loud noise.
- It doesn't hurt, does it?
- Of course, it hurts when...
Hey.
I can't make a joke.
- Gosh.
- They are firm.
There's the line that
you're not supposed to overstep.
- I can't even make a joke now.
- They are firm.
I can't look at Dong Hoon.
- Why not?
- I don't know. You look scary.
- You look threatening.
- The thing is...
What did I do?
Look at that. My goodness.
- He looks like a thug.
- I'm scared.
My goodness.
- Oh, dear.
- It's like the movie "The Roundup."
He looks like a street gangster.
(Slapping)
(Awkward laughing)
It's good to have them back anyway.
He's acting strange today.
- Right?
- He's being awkward.
He pretends to be cool.
- Suk Jin...
- He's being pretentious.
I read some articles about today.
So I know what's going on.
- Is that why he's being quiet?
- I guess so.
He's being quiet today, right?
I know.
- He's a singer today.
- And today...
- He's a guest today.
- We have a lot of news today.
I heard you two kissed.
Right. I saw that.
- What?
- My gosh.
About that?
I have a lot to talk about.
It's not like that.
You hugged each other.
And Ji Hyo was like...
- No, Jae Suk. It's not like that.
- And she said...
she was having
a good appetite these days.
- A good appetite?
No, it's not like that.
She said she was hungry.
She meant she was just hungry.
Ji Hyo doesn't usually act cute, but...
She wasn't acting cute.
She just said she was hungry.
She did things like that.
- She was just hungry.
- "Jong Kook."
"Jong Kook, I have
such an appetite these days."
When did I say that?
"Jong Kook. Jong Kook!"
- I didn't sound like that.
- "I have such an appetite."
- Then Jong Kook...
- What was the scene about?
Jong Kook sounded shy. "Oh, you do?"
Hang on.
- Jae Suk, that's not true.
- What?
- It's not true.
- No. Listen.
- You did that during the shoot.
- It happened.
What am I supposed to say
when she says she has an appetite?
What should I say? It's just part...
of the music video.
But you did that
when you weren't shooting.
We did it when we were shooting.
There were cameras!
(We did it when we were shooting.
There were cameras!)
It was a scene
when we were a happy couple.
- It was part of the scene.
- It wasn't the main story.
It was a scene
when we were a happy couple.
- I guess it looked natural.
- It was natural.
Right.
- They look good together.
- That's the people's wish.
I hope things will work out for them.
- The people are busy.
- It's not like that.
- Right. They all are...
- They already have...
- a lot to care about.
- I just mean...
The presidential election is coming up.
Everyone's busy.
It's not like I asked the people
to care about it.
We all are going through hard times.
I didn't ask them to care about it.
You can't force people
to wish for something.
- Right.
- I mean they look good together.
Why are the three of them
sitting together?
You should just be grateful
for their interest and support.
- Now I feel bad for you.
- I know.
- That's not right.
- Why do you feel bad?
Don't pity me.
- You're being...
- I don't pity you.
Hey, Wonstein.
- Jae Jung.
- Hey.
Hello.
My goodness.
They are my singers.
- Hey.
- My artists.
- Hello.
They're finally here.
Hello.
(Suk Jin's colleagues
from "How Do You Play?")
(Park Jae Jung of M.O.M)
(Wonstein of M.O.M)
(He's here as Byeollu-Ji today.)
(The men of Saturday are here
to unite the two universes.)
(They say hello
to their CEO, Yoo Yaho.)
Hey.
Onto the stage.
- Hello.
- Straight to the stage?
- Onto the stage?
- Here's the microphone.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- My goodness.
- I feel nervous to sing in front of you.
- My gosh.
Hellucca, Running Man.
Hello.
He works as a comedian now.
Jae Suk loves him these days.
- Right. KCM.
- Chang Mo.
Guy, I'm serious about this.
You're not supposed to laugh
when I sing.
We won't laugh.
- They recently released a new song.
- I know.
We've never
performed this song before.
Really?
This is our first performance.
- This is "How Do You Play?"
- Give them a big hand.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- This is their first performance.
- I hope you will enjoy it.
Okay. We will listen carefully.
This is very meaningful.
It feels like I'm watching TV.
- Don't look at me.
- The collaboration finally happens.
This is the beginning.
This is so nice.
I can't watch this.
It sounds great.
Unbelievable.
This is so thrilling.
This is so nice.
I love it.
(This is amazing.)
It's so good.
- I love the song.
- Do you like it?
- I do.
- It makes my heart flutter.
My gosh.
Let's go.
Wonstein!
It sounds wonderful.
It's going to make me cry.
This is so good.
It's so good.
- Thank you.
This is amazing.
You look so cool.
- That was great.
- Hey.
- I love it.
- Unbelievable.
- Do you really like it?
- I do.
It's great.
- Wonderful.
- Are you serious?
- He's making a fuss again.
- Hey.
- Stop it.
- My gosh.
Gosh, that was amazing.
- Do you like the song?
- I love it.
It's really nice.
- It's great.
- I think I picked good members.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- I did a great job.
I hated it when Suk Jin...
danced to the rhythm.
(I hated it
when Suk Jin danced to the rhythm.)
The bounce...
- How could he dance like that?
- I know.
Wonstein and the other guys
looked so cool,
- but he was like this.
- It was off the beat.
- You were a little...
- It was strange.
(Embarrassed)
It was like the dance from the '80s.
- Like a show-off.
- He was like this.
Why would he dance like this?
- It won't be shown on TV.
- You think?
Wonstein and Jae Jung were great.
- It was so cool.
- We look hip, right?
The live performance was impressive.
That was crazy.
I know.
Actually, we are grateful
to Jong Kook for this song.
- Right.
- The thing is...
- Was the song for Jong Kook?
- Actually,
Jong Kook and I were
supposed to sing this song.
- Really?
- That's what Keun Tae wanted.
So he sent the guide song to me.
You know everyone feels...
uncomfortable around Jong Kook.
Keun Tae was...
How many people feel
uncomfortable around him?
- Even Keun Tae feels uncomfortable.
- He does?
- Keun Tae...
- Keun Tae does?
Keun Tae asked me.
"Chang Mo, are you
close to Jong Kook?"
"Yes, we are close friends."
"I want you to send him the song."
"I'm afraid I can't."
"I don't feel
so comfortable around him."
He could've just sent me.
So the title of the demo was "KJK."
- Really?
- That's true.
- Jong Kook, this is...
- The song is perfect for my voice.
- It would've been really nice.
- You would've made a perfect duo.
Right? You can wear
matching tank tops.
Matching tops?
You could've worn matching
tank tops and arm warmers.
- I love the song.
- It's really nice.
- It's perfect for spring.
- It really is.
Anyway, these four are...
promoting their new song now.
And they are here
since Suk Jin is our member.
- I'm grateful that they're here.
- Me too.
It's something that wouldn't
happen on other TV shows.
- They wouldn't do this.
- Of course not.
It wouldn't happen.
Because the band started
on a different TV show.
Back in the day, they would just
perform one song and leave.
- This is very rare.
- And...
You couldn't even promote your song.
They wouldn't get to sing like this.
I know. This wouldn't happen.
- They wouldn't get to sing.
- But they sang the entire song.
Right.
I'd like to talk
about them one by one.
- First, we have KCM here.
- Yes.
I think KCM is...
- as funny as a comedian.
- He's hilarious.
You recently appeared on the show...
- I host.
- I did.
- With No Noo.
- Right.
I burst into laughter
as he showed up.
(Shocked)
(KCM showed up
in a sleeveless shirt.)
It's even funnier...
- because he put on some weight.
- I know. It was so funny.
The thing is,
KCM works out a lot.
But he wasn't in shape at all.
Seriously.
He wasn't in shape at all,
- But he sings so well.
- but he was wearing a tight shirt.
He looks just like...
a retired bodybuilder...
who runs a gym.
- Exactly.
- There are trainers like him.
That's how he looks.
I laughed a lot that day.
- So this is what I imagined.
- What?
In about 10 or 20 years,
Jong Kook will show up
after putting on some fat like KCM.
(Jong Kook will show up
after putting on some fat like KCM.)
I want to see that.
- I'm excited.
- In a sleeveless shirt...
There's a man
(Jong Kook sings "One Man"
in a sleeveless shirt.)
- It will be hilarious.
- That sounds humane.
- Like Ma Dong Seok.
- Exactly.
It will be hilarious.
- I don't think it will happen.
- It will be a nice surprise.
It will be so funny.
So Wonstein and Jae Jung are here.
When I was talking
to So Min on the phone,
she asked, "Is Wonstein..."
"about my age?"
He's very young.
Wonstein is like a baby.
No. That's not true.
I'm not that young.
- I'm 28.
- He is young.
- Wonstein, are you 28?
- Yes, I'm 28.
- Really?
- I thought you were only 24 or 25.
He was born in 1995.
Jae Jung and I are of the same age.
- Right. Jae Jung.
- Are you two of the same age?
- They are of the same age.
- What?
- Are you two of the same age?
- They are of the same age.
I thought it had been
20 years since your debut.
This must be a joke.
- I know.
- He looks experienced.
I look old for my age.
- He debuted when he was 19.
- I was only 19.
It's been a long time
since your debut.
Jae Jung looks his age.
- And Wonstein looks young.
- He's like a peach.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
Do you know who they are?
(Do you know who they are?)
- On behalf of the viewers...
- She doesn't seem to know.
She's here as a representative
of the viewers.
She doesn't know.
She's the representative
of our viewers.
- I know them.
- You do?
- Wonsteim.
- Right.
He's not Wonsteim.
- That's not it.
- It's Wonstein.
- Wonstein.
- Wonsteim?
You know Jae Jung, right?
- Of course I do.
- You know him, right?
And you know
that we are a band, don't you?
Sure. I just saw you sing.
This isn't the first time.
We did it before.
Really?
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo's head
needs some updating.)
And Wonstein has a younger sister.
- He and his sister are...
- She must be lovely.
He tells her
that he loves her all the time.
- Really? To your sister?
- I was really surprised.
That's true. We are very intimate.
- Do you really say that?
- Jae Jung also...
says that to his younger brother.
They all are full of love.
But why do you not love us?
I love you a lot.
Then tell me that you love me.
He can't say that.
We send messages like that a lot,
but he never says that.
- He never answers.
- I'm just shy.
- But...
- I'm shy.
But he leaves
a lot of sweet comments...
- on their social media.
- Really?
- He says that he loves them.
- I don't say that.
- I never said that to them.
- But you are totally different...
- when you're with them.
- He changes completely.
Suk Jin is not
so affectionate to others.
He's just indifferent.
It's not like he's not affectionate.
- This is what it is.
- I just feel bad for them.
He doesn't say anything sweet
to his close friends.
But he tries to express affection
to his new friends.
I'm not his old friend though.
- It's been only 5 years.
- We've known for 5 years already.
- It hasn't been so long.
- I just can't say that.
You were mean to me
when we first met.
(You were mean to me
when we first met.)
(She reveals
that he was mean to her.)
That's true.
- You were mean to me.
- Stay quiet.
- My goodness.
- The viewers don't know that.
He's mean to newbies.
- This is hilarious.
- I wasn't being mean. Jong Kook.
- You know me.
- I do.
It takes time for me
to become friends with others.
- He looks lonely today.
- That's it.
By the way, this is...
turning into a talk show.
- We are today's guests.
- But...
- This is fun though.
- We will go home after talking.
- I'm having fun.
- This is really fun.
- It's really fun.
- I like it.
We will continue talking
after the song.
(The talking never ends.)
All right.
- Good.
- It's Jong Kook's turn...
- to perform a song.
- That's right.
Jong Kook will sing a song for us.
Can you sing a song for us?
- Why do you not release a new song?
- I'm working on it.
Haha and I have
improved a lot in singing.
We can help you
with your new song. We can rap.
(We can help you
with your new song. We can rap.)
Haha has improved.
- He raps really well now.
- You two?
I'm a vocalist now.
He's really good.
The reason I wanted you
(The old school rappers want to ride
on Kim Grand Award's coattails.)
- He's good.
- The rap from the '90s.
Really?
- We should do that sometime.
- We should.
- The three of you should do that.
- It will be fun.
It will be great.
Let me tell you about today's race.
With the members of Running Man
who are always on Suk Jin's side...
and the members of M.O.M
who are supportive of Suk Jin,
we will have As Ji Wishes Race.
(As Ji Wishes Race)
- It's perfect for Suk Jin.
- I knew it was about him.
- I didn't know.
- He seemed nervous.
Today's race will take place
with Suk Jin as the center,
and it will have individual games.
There will be
separate rules for Suk Jin,
and the rest of you
will compete against each other.
But all the episodes where
Suk Jin was the protagonist...
suffered low ratings.
(All the episodes about Suk Jin
suffered low viewer ratings.)
Our ratings did drop.
- Hey, don't say such a thing.
- True.
- People might think it's true.
- Why?
- Those episodes were boring.
- The viewers might think...
- that it's true.
- Why are you yelling at me?
- Why would you get upset?
- Think about it.
- If you say such a thing,
- It was a joke.
since you're a top show host,
people will believe you.
All right. I understand.
- Viewers, it's not true.
- Okay.
He was just joking. Believe me.
But I didn't make that up.
- I said it based on the data...
- It sounds real as you got upset.
- Exactly.
- No, it's not like that.
- You went overboard.
- Just laugh it off.
But it's not fair.
I can't just laugh it off.
Anyway, at the end of the race,
only Suk Jin will spin a roulette.
You'll see "Prize" and "Penalty"...
- written on the slots.
- Oh, I see.
That's the rule for Suk Jin.
As for the other eight members,
the person with the highest score...
will be the MOM,
the Man of the Match,
and will win a prize.
And the person in second place
will be exempt from the penalty.
One person chosen by
the winner of the race...
and one chosen by Suk Jin...
- will receive the penalty.
- Oh, gosh.
- Two people will get the penalty?
- Oh, boy.
Gosh, Suk Jin will probably...
However, if Suk Jin gets
the penalty, he can't choose...
anyone else to receive the penalty.
- Oh, I see.
- I'll spin the roulette.
Today, Suk Jin will choose
the members...
- to be on his team.
- Yes.
The members Suk Jin chooses
will be on Team Ji,
and the others will be
on Team Others.
- You'll be divided into two teams.
- Team Ji and Team Others.
- Team Others.
- We'll see how he feels about us.
We'll see which one of us
he cares more about.
And Suk Jin, if Team Ji wins,
one prize slot will be added
to the roulette.
One penalty slot will be added
if your team loses.
- It's time to team up.
- Okay.
- What is this?
- "Guess the members of Team Ji."
Each of you should predict
the members Suk Jin will choose.
(Lucky Ji Lottery, Predict
the members Suk Jin will pick!)
- This is easy.
- If you guess every member right,
- Bingo?
- you'll be exempt from the penalty.
(They have a chance to be exempt
from the penalty.)
- If I guess every member right?
- Right.
- I wonder if they could do that.
- It's impossible.
- How do we guess everyone right?
- If any one of them succeeds,
a penalty slot will be added
to the roulette, Suk Jin.
- I think I know who he'll pick.
- So try to make it hard to predict.
Okay.
- Pick at least one female member.
- I'll do that.
I'm pretty sure that he'll pick
Jong Kook...
- No, he won't make it that easy.
- Don't talk. You're confusing me.
- He could choose KCM.
- And...
He probably wants to pick So Min,
but in the end,
- he'll decide not to pick her.
- Please be quiet.
- Why?
- I don't think...
I don't think he'll pick me
because for him,
- winning is more important.
- Ji Hyo is more cooperative.
He must think I'm at a disadvantage
because of my leg injury.
- But what you just said...
- Come on. Please stop talking.
- must have changed his mind.
- I agree.
It's because Suk Jin is
an opportunist.
(He's the sly type.)
- Why would you put it like that?
- Sorry.
He'll definitely pick Jong Kook.
It's because...
- Right. He's strong.
- Quiet down, will you?
- No. He might...
- I think he'll pick KCM.
choose KCM since he's here.
He'll pick the ones I said
he'd pick.
I know him well.
I tried not to let what you were
saying affect my decision.
Shall I hand it in now?
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
I bet none of you guessed it right.
All right. Now, please reveal
your predictions 1 by 1.
We'll see the predictions first.
It'd be a miracle
if anyone predicted right.
- Ji Hyo, you go first.
- Gosh.
I thought he'd pick Jong Kook,
Wonstein, So Min, and KCM.
I picked exactly the same members.
- Really?
- Haha's prediction is the same.
Next up is So Min.
I thought he'd pick Jong Kook,
Wonstein, KCM, and Ji Hyo.
(So Min's prediction:
Jong Kook, Wonstein, KCM, Ji Hyo)
- Jae Jung, you're up.
- Okay. My prediction is Ji Hyo,
Jae Suk, Haha, and me.
KCM, Jae Jung, So Min, and me.
(The members reveal
their predictions 1 by 1.)
Jae Jung, Wonstein,
Ji Hyo, and me.
Jae Suk, Ji Hyo,
Wonstein, and KCM.
I see. Our predictions are
similar to one another.
All right.
- This must be the correct answer.
- I bet I got only one member wrong,
or I got every member right.
- I'm sure I didn't guess...
- Right.
- more than one member wrong.
- Of course.
- Jae Suk is...
- That's amazing.
- He definitely picked Jong Kook.
- He's amazing. Right.
- He knows Suk Jin so well.
- He definitely picked Jong Kook.
And he picked Jae Jung
and Wonstein too.
Because Jong Kook and KCM are
similar, he probably separated them.
- That's a good point.
- Yes.
So the question is which of Ji Hyo
and So Min he picked.
I bet he was going to pick So Min,
but he decided to choose Ji Hyo...
- for his team to win.
- He picked Ji Hyo.
That's why I picked these members.
Jong Kook, Wonstein, Ji Hyo,
and Jae Jung.
- I'm curious. Show us, Suk Jin.
- Me too.
(The long-awaited announcement)
- I bet I guessed almost all right.
- One of you...
- One of us predicted right?
- Yes.
(One of them predicted right.)
I was surprised.
- It must be Jae Suk.
- I think it's Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is unbelievable.
- He guessed everyone correctly?
I'm impressed. How did he guess
all of them right?
- I'll announce my team members.
- Okay.
"I'll announce my team members."
Let's check how many we got right.
Check your answers.
(Predict the members
Suk Jin will pick!)
- Jong Kook.
- I knew it.
- Okay.
- There was no doubt...
- that he'd pick Jong Kook.
- I got one right.
Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
- Just as I expected.
- I failed.
- And...
(Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo)
- Jae Jung.
- Yes, I knew it.
- Oh, my. Jae Jung?
- Raise your hand...
if you predicted all three of them.
- The last one must be Wonstein.
- And...
- Wonstein!
- Yes!
- Hey, how did you know?
- My goodness.
- Wonstein!
- Yes!
(Jae Suk won.)
- How did you know, Jae Suk?
- That's amazing.
- It's not that he predicted.
- Awesome.
You did just as Jae Suk said.
You chose the members
that Jae Suk said...
- you would pick.
- That's not the case.
- Seriously.
- I didn't do that.
- Unbelievable.
- I...
- It wasn't like that. Trust me.
- Why did you do that?
- I didn't...
- Jong Kook, you're wrong.
- It's obvious.
- Jae Suk kept talking,
- You're mistaken.
- and Suk Jin chose them...
- How did he do that?
As if he had hypnotized Suk Jin.
- How does he do that?
- This is the correct answer.
- He's incredible.
- How did he do that?
- I'm impressed.
- You're amazing.
- Hey.
- As a result, Jae Suk...
got an exemption from the penalty,
to our surprise.
Okay!
Gosh, I can't believe him.
I was going to pick him.
Suk Jin, you lost 1 prize slot
and got 1 more penalty slot.
- Okay.
- Gosh. What an idiot.
- Make your own decisions, will you?
- How would I have known?
- I said that wasn't the case.
- I mean...
- He never makes his own decisions.
- I didn't pick the people...
that Jae Suk said I'd pick.
You might end up giving him
all your assets.
- What?
- Right.
- I've been saying this for a while.
- You're incredible.
- If I set my mind to it,
- Yes.
I can make him and Yong Man
live on the streets.
(I can make him and Yong Man
live on the streets.)
I'm capable of doing that.
I don't doubt that.
- He's a scary...
- The two of them...
- He's a scary man.
- How does he do that?
- How come it happens every time?
- My gosh.
Shall we get going now?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I didn't know...
- It might be too small.
- Haha was older than KCM.
- Here you go.
Of course, he's older than KCM.
KCM is not as old as he seems.
- How old are you, KCM?
- He's younger than Haha.
I'm 42.
- Sorry?
- I'm 42.
- You're 42?
- Yes.
Now that I know that Haha is
older than KCM...
- He was always like a baby.
- I may be the youngest among us,
but I'm older than
most entertainers.
- Hey, is Rain 40 years old?
- He's 41.
- Is he 41?
- Yes, he's 41.
What kind of relationship
do you have with Rain?
A dominant-subordinate relationship?
Gosh, Suk Jin.
How could you put it like that?
- What's your problem?
- Is it?
What kind of relationship
do you have with Jae Suk?
- Are you a subordinate?
- He's a friend in my neighborhood.
- A friend I like.
- Hey.
I think this shows what kind of
relationship they have.
That's not true.
All of our staff members are
over there.
Hellucca.
(Hellucca.)
What was that?
- Hey.
- I hated that at first.
- I told KCM not to do that.
- Really?
But I found myself
saying it unintentionally.
- Were you the first to say that?
- "Hellucca."
- Yes.
- Jong Kook hates things like that.
But I think it's funny
because it's you.
- It suits you.
- It's funny.
- Wonstein, you feel awkward, right?
- Yes?
(Wonstein still feels shy
around everyone.)
- Wonstein has such a cute face.
- How cute.
- You see, Wonstein...
- He's like a cute doll.
- doesn't just look cute.
- He's so cute.
- He has a cute personality too.
- Right.
(Wonstein is
the cutest hip-hop artist.)
- He's the best.
- Haha used to be like him.
- Haha was like him?
- He's the type that shares love.
Haha was nice
to his senior entertainers as well,
- but he could be defiant too.
- True.
- He acted up once in a while.
- Really?
See? Look at him.
- He did?
- Look at him.
He's loyal though.
I don't think he's ever acted up
in front of me.
- Why would I do that?
- Hey.
(Polite)
Why would I?
No one would dare pick a fight
with you.
- When I started making music,
- Right. Absolutely.
- I often listened to Haha's songs.
- Which ones?
- It could've gone wrong.
- Really?
- Z-KIRI.
- That was a bad choice.
- I knew he had great taste.
- Z-KIRI?
- Which song?
- That was a bad choice.
- "Love Song" and many other songs.
- "Love Song?"
You might've forgotten it
since he's been maintaining...
his funny image from variety shows
for a long time,
- but he's a great musician too.
- Yo, yeah
- Hey
- Yeah
- Here we go, yeah
- Hey
- Hey, hold on.
- All right
- Hold on a second.
- Yeah
Ah, yeah
- I usually agree with Jae Suk.
- That was funny.
- My goodness.
- But that's enough, Jae Suk.
- Stop it.
- Haha is talented.
- What do you mean?
- Talented in what?
He's good at it. Yeah
He's good at luring customers.
- I know that.
- Gosh. I did it only twice.
- He's good at running a business.
- Come on.
"Let's make our customers happy!"
- He's good at sales.
- My goodness.
So Min looks as if she were
tagging along with a couple.
Oh, right. I shouldn't have sat
between them.
It's not like that.
There's nothing going on between us.
Don't deny it.
You two used So Min's injury
as an excuse to meet up.
What?
"Let's eat together
since So Min got hurt."
since So Min got hurt." Like this.
I think that's what's happening.
(Cheeky)
- You're quite far away from me.
- Exactly.
- Hey, that's why...
- That was unexpected.
- That's why I can talk freely.
- I didn't see that coming.
- He's talking recklessly.
- Exactly.
- I can say whatever I want.
- He's being reckless.
He's talking recklessly.
Jae Jung, is your skin
naturally dark?
- The skin on my hands is dark too.
- What I'm saying is...
- He likes soccer.
- That's right.
- The K League...
- Are you good at soccer?
I'm not good at playing it.
I'm just a fan.
- He's a big fan. He also...
- Yes, I'm a big fan.
- Suwon Samsung Bluewings.
- He has almost all the teams'...
- soccer jerseys.
- It's a different team.
- That's how much I like soccer.
- Right.
- Yes, he likes it so much.
- Really?
I'm a big fan of the K League too.
- Right.
- If Jong Kook sets his eyes on you,
- You would be...
- just think that it's over.
- You would have no private life.
- That's right.
(The potential soccer club member
caught Jong Kook's eye.)
Don't worry. There are perks too.
- The perks are...
- No one would dare hit you.
- No one would.
- He'd give you his full support.
- Absolutely.
- That's a good thing.
No wonder why I couldn't look him
in the eyes.
- Once he sets his eyes on you...
- Where do you live?
- Well, I live...
- He got caught.
- Seolleung? Yeoksam?
- I live in Seocho-gu.
- Near Gangnam?
- Yes.
- You can pick him up on your way.
- I can give him a ride.
(I can give him a ride.)
- Pick him up on your way.
- We can carpool together.
- This is great.
- Congratulations, Jae Jung.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations. It's very hard
to join his soccer club.
When a member of our club can't
attend practice,
he must send me photos to prove
that he has a reasonable reason.
(Only a certified document
can be accepted.)
DinDin once had to ask his mother
to call Jong Kook.
No, we can check up on him
by listening to his radio show.
- Really?
- He hosts a live show.
- Just know that he's so persistent.
- That's unbelievable.
You wouldn't be able to
get away from him.
I understand.
- Hey, I just realized something.
- Just a little bit.
- Haha seems cheerier than usual.
- Yes.
I bet it's because of those
who appeared on "How Do You Play?"
Hey!
- Enough is enough. Seriously.
- I wondered why...
- I see that it's true.
- Gosh. Stop it already.
- Shut it!
- "What's going on?"
Stop saying that. The fans believed
what you said and commented...
- during the live broadcast...
- Really?
we did for "How Do You Play?"
It's true.
So many people mentioned Running Man.
What am I supposed to do?
You just have to work hard here too.
I always do my best!
- He's stressed out.
- But you seem so cheery...
- today.
- He's doing so well.
- Haha.
- I like that cheery tone.
- Right?
- I do my best on this show too.
- But many of us are veterans.
- It's hard to stand out.
- That makes me look...
- No. That's not the reason.
It's all your fault! You jerk!
- This is funny.
- They hate me no matter what I do!
I want to do well too!
(The bald kid rebelled
for the 1st time at the age of 44.)
- He won awards from this show.
- Okay. I'll see.
- He shaved his head too.
- I'll see how he does.
- Gosh. He drives me crazy.
- Do your best.
- You...
- Hey.
Don't pretend you're not related.
- He seems indifferent.
- Look at his face.
- He's trying to stay out of it.
- Gosh.
I can tell by the look on his face.
As if he were saying,
"You're on your own now."
(Haha's Saturday coworker
became quiet for some reason.)
- You're on your own.
- He complimented Haha...
for his rap skills and everything,
but now...
he's trying to keep a distance
from Haha.
Yo, Yeah
- Fine. I'll figure it out.
- He won't help Haha anymore.
My, that was hilarious.
What are we going to do here?
- That's right.
- What?
Isn't that my seat?
I should be the referee.
- I'll help you. That's your seat.
- I should be the referee.
- The referee's seat... Hey, move.
- Hey.
So Min should be the referee.
That's my seat.
Suk Jin, why did you suddenly
help her? You didn't do that before.
- Because she was alone...
- I'll tell you what happened.
- He came...
- He hadn't helped her before.
- Why...
- He didn't when the camera was off.
(The icon of fake kindness)
- Here we go
- Honey
- Yes, honey?
- You see,
since she had leg surgery,
So Min gets excited
when others come to her.
- I missed talking to others.
- She seems excited, right?
- She gets excited to see others.
- True.
- She's happy to meet others.
- Yes, I am.
We changed our clothes.
Then why are you...
- still standing with them?
- Oh, I see.
- You should stand on this side.
- Right.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Should I move to that side?
- Suk Jin.
- We're on the same team.
- Hey.
- We look much stronger, right?
- They're five.
- I picked the right ones.
- Hey.
- We look much stronger, right?
(Looking around)
- Yes, you did.
- By the way, the words...
- They all look weak.
- "Team Others" as in "husband"...
- As if we were So Min's husbands.
- We're all her husbands.
- It sounds similar to "husband."
- Right.
- We're all her husbands.
- As if you were So Min's husbands.
It's as if all of you were
So Min's husbands.
- Exactly.
- So Min,
- what's my seniority level here?
- So Min.
- Answer me.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- Why did you make us wear this?
You look happy, So Min.
It looks as if you were
So Min's husbands.
You always wanted to see guys
fighting over you.
- Men fighting over you.
- I like being in that situation.
I see that you like different types.
They're so different
from one another.
- They're all very different.
- Indeed.
- This is funny.
- I can tell you one thing.
I didn't marry them for looks.
- I didn't marry them for looks.
- I can see that.
There's no doubt.
- You're absolutely right.
What's important is...
that we get along so well
with one another.
(We get along so well
with one another.)
(They love each other
more than they love their wife.)
- Right.
- Brother.
- There's no conflict between you.
- Never.
- The husbands get along well.
- Yes, we do.
Sleep over
at his house tonight, okay?
I'll drink some soju with Jae Suk.
- Okay?
- See you later, Haha.
- Take care of her, okay?
- Of course.
- Don't you worry.
- You must be happy.
- It's good they get along well.
- My gosh.
She's a modern woman.
This doesn't happen
even in Hollywood.
- It'd be really...
- Right.
- Can you see the roulette?
- Yes.
That's the roulette
that Suk Jin will spin at the end.
- There's a 50 percent chance.
- I see "Get off Work" too.
- What's "Get off Work?"
- Seven slots are already filled.
There are "Prize," "Penalty,"
and "Get off Work."
"Get off Work" means
you can go home right away.
- Right away?
- Really?
- You mean, I can go home?
- Yes.
Since Jae Suk succeeded in guessing
all your team members,
you should put this sticker
over one prize slot.
- I can make up for it easily.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Put it over a prize slot.
- Got it.
- Oh, over a prize slot?
- Over the letters like this?
- Oh, I see.
- Over a prize slot.
- I see.
- Oh, no.
- I didn't know that.
(The chance that Suk Jin will get
the penalty went up.)
In the first mission, there are
matches between the men...
- and a match between the women.
- Okay.
We'll compete separately?
The game that will be played
by the men is...
the one that became
an official sports game...
in the US this year.
- Great!
- The first official event was held.
- Finally.
- It's PFC,
Pillow Fight Championship.
- What's that?
- What is it?
Pillow fights have become
an official sports event.
- Oh, my.
- Really? That's ridiculous.
There's a league for it,
and the champion gets the prize money.
The organization was founded in the US.
(The official pillow fight match
with prize money held in the US)
- Pillow fight matches?
- Oh, really?
- That's interesting.
- But...
Jong Kook is on the other team.
It's not fair.
- You have KCM.
- Exactly.
He's so weak.
But he seems much heavier than me.
- He weighs more than 100kg.
- Do we lose when we cry?
- Yes. That's the exact rule.
- What?
- You have 90 seconds in each round.
- Okay.
There's one rule we added.
You must keep smiling
throughout the game.
- I see.
- Okay.
You must keep smiling
for 90 seconds.
If you stop smiling or get upset
during a match,
the referee will give you...
- a yellow card.
- Okay.
- You get disqualified for three.
- Got it.
- All right.
- It's a normal pillow fight.
After the game ends,
based on the number of warnings,
the accuracy of attacks,
and how you maintained your smile,
Kang Chan Hee will decide
the winner.
Okay.
- Okay.
- As for the order of players...
There will be 2 1-on-1 matches,
1 2-on-2, and 1 3-on-3 matches.
- There will be 4 rounds in total.
- The 2-on-2 match sounds fun.
- Let's do this.
- Just as we played...
- the floating mat game...
- Exactly.
- We need to decide wisely.
- But...
- This is good.
- Yes.
You have to win this round
no matter what. It'll work out.
- I wonder about their first player.
- I know.
- Right?
- A pillow fight can be intense.
Some kids put rocks in their pillows
when I was in school.
- You can't put anything in it.
- Stop looking at it.
My gosh. He didn't even try to hide.
- What are you doing?
- He startled me.
- You can't do that.
- What...
- Smile.
- Who are you?
Well... Who are you?
- I can't believe him.
- I'm on Team Others.
- Why were you spying on us?
- He doesn't seem strong.
- Are you guys done?
- Yes.
- What?
- They already made their decision.
- We already wrote the list.
- I see.
- We're done.
- All right.
Won't the girls play?
Only the guys play this game?
- Only the guys play this game.
- Ask Wonstein and Jae Jung too.
- I didn't see that.
- In what round do you want to play?
You already finished writing the list.
(You already finished writing the list.)
What's the point of asking
when you've already completed the list?
- He acts like this sometimes.
- Ask them what they want.
- Wonstein and Jae Jung...
- We made a good plan.
- The right men in the right place.
- Why didn't you ask them...
What did they write?
We didn't get to see it.
- Jae Jung, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- It'll be fun if you don't know.
- Right.
- The first round...
- I'm curious.
where the two teams will fight
to get the upper hand...
is Suk Jin versus Haha.
- All right.
- That's good.
- Nice.
- It's a big match.
- It really is a big match.
- My gosh.
- Suk Jin is really strong.
- We chose the right player.
These pillows are too soft
to hit anyone hard.
You never know.
- Before the game begins,
- Give me a heavier one.
you should get hit a few times
like this.
You should do this
so you can get used to it.
- Don't waste your energy.
- All right.
Don't waste your energy.
- It's good, right? That's great.
- I'm starting to feel it.
- Save your energy.
- Those punks.
- It's important to keep smiling.
- It's for getting used to the pain.
Don't forget to keep smiling.
Each round lasts exactly 90 seconds.
- You've got this.
- You can do this.
- Go, Haha!
(Go, Haha.)
(Screaming)
- Go, Suk Jin!
- You've got this.
Go, Haha!
It's over for your husband.
Say goodbye to him.
You should start smiling
when the bell rings.
- You must keep smiling.
- You can do this.
(Ready, fight.)
- Go on.
- Smile.
- You should smile.
- No punching.
- Smile.
- Keep smiling.
- No punching.
- Smile.
- Gosh.
(Suk Jin got a warning
for an upset look.)
- Smile.
- Hey.
(The baldy appears.)
- He looks like Geun Sik.
- He looks scary.
- Hey, you look like Geun Sik.
- My goodness.
- He looks so scary.
- Keep smiling.
He looks too scary.
- Smile. Don't forget to smile.
- Hey, smile.
Hey, smile.
- You can do it. Keep smiling.
- Smile.
- Yes, hit him.
- Keep smiling.
Don't stop smiling.
You should keep smiling.
(Laughing loudly)
(It's getting hard for him
to keep smiling.)
Hey, smile. Keep smiling.
Keep smiling. Smile.
You have 30 seconds left.
- See if there's blood on it.
- They're doing well.
They're good at this.
Both of them are fast.
(Hitting hard)
Smile.
Great. That was good.
- Smile.
- You should keep smiling.
- Good job, Haha.
- Keep smiling.
Suk Jin, you should smile.
- I think he's tired.
- Haha looks like a martial artist.
- Keep smiling.
- He's too tired to smile.
(Breathing heavily)
You should keep smiling. Smile.
- Keep smiling.
- You should smile.
Smile!
(Right on target)
(Suk Jin can't see straight
after getting hit on the nose.)
Is Suk Jin bleeding?
(Time's up!)
(The two middle-aged fighters
are rescued before they crash.)
- No way.
- Ninety seconds is quite long.
That was exhausting.
- Good job.
- Nicely done!
- Of course you're exhausted.
- You won with your expressions.
Team Ji has two warnings stacked.
Team Others has one.
Kang Chan Hee will decide
on the winner.
Okay.
Kang Chan Hee,
please name the winner.
(Who will the referee choose?)
- Well?
- Team Ji.
(Did Suk Jin win?)
(Round 1 goes to Team Ji.)
Let's go!
Seriously?
Chan Hee, are you kidding me?
- But he fouled.
- Nicely done.
He grabbed me from behind.
Are you kidding me?
- He considered all the aspects.
- Chan Hee, how could you?
Suk Jin forced himself to smile.
- Yes, he laughed.
- He kept his smile.
Chan Hee and Suk Jin
have a connection...
of some sort.
- What kind of connection?
- There is one.
- What do you mean?
- That's absurd.
- It's true though.
- Seriously?
You're barking up the wrong tree!
- Suk Jin just did well.
- Not in this day and age.
Anyone can tell who the winner was.
He punched me with his fist.
Exactly. I saw that too.
Suk Jin punched him with his fist.
Just a second.
- Haha...
- You were as light as a feather.
- Suk Jin...
- He punched Haha.
He punched Haha with his fist.
He punched him right here.
I admit that there was physical contact.
That can happen, you know.
It's understandable.
It's an accident that can happen
in this game.
What?
(It's an accident that can happen
in this game.)
- What?
- That's just how it is.
- What did you just say?
- It happens in the US too.
What is it that you just said?
It's an accident that happens
in the US as well.
(He gained victory
but lost his language skills.)
- It's time for the next round.
- Good.
The next round will be...
Kim Jong Kook versus KCM.
(Kim Jong Kook versus KCM)
(The best players from each team
go head to head.)
My gosh!
This wasn't rigged,
so what a coincidence.
- No way.
- This is incredible.
Hey! Don't you know that
I always carry a smile?
- This was inevitable.
- I'm famous for always smiling.
(Episode 339, 2017)
(Kim Jong Kook and KCM
went head to head in arm wrestling.)
(The match was close.)
(But KCM defeated
the protein monster.)
- Is this fun for you?
- I'm having a blast.
Think of this as a bullfight.
A bullfight?
Did you really refer
to yourselves as bulls?
- Jong Kook.
- Hey, KCM.
- Gosh, I'm trembling.
- Bring it on, KCM.
- Nice.
- Warm up.
What for?
Get ready!
- Good luck.
- Jong Kook.
- Let's go.
- Don't give it too much too early.
Get ready!
(The two bulls get overly excited
even before the game begins.)
Get ready.
- This really is exhausting.
- This is nerve-wracking.
- Good luck!
- Go!
(The Running Man Bullfight begins.)
- Go for it.
- You've got this.
Nice!
- Get him.
- Go for it.
- Why is it in your left hand?
- You have 90 seconds.
(Swish)
Go for it. That's it.
(The two bulls
approach with caution.)
They're both being cautious.
Jong Kook, smile!
You need to smile.
- That's it.
- Jong Kook, you must smile.
- Smile!
That's it. You're doing great.
(A right hook)
You're doing great.
Look. Jong Kook's
not having it anymore.
- Look at them!
- What on earth?
Smile!
You must smile.
Look at them.
What's happening?
(It goes from a bullfight to a dogfight.)
You both must smile.
KCM's in tears.
Should we do something?
(The wailing bulls)
(Giggling)
That's him laughing!
- You must smile or laugh.
- Smile!
Please smile!
- KCM's crying.
Keep smiling.
You're in tears!
He's exhausted now.
(Between smiling and wailing)
(Nine drops of tears
that are to reach you.)
- Attack!
- Just keep smiling.
Smile!
Oh, dear.
(Chang Mo is admitting defeat.)
Smile!
(The game ends.)
- Unbelievable.
- That was incredible.
- Gosh.
- This game depletes your energy.
- It's fun though.
- Yes, that was fun.
- It was a good workout.
- A workout?
How was this fun for you
when all you did was take a beating?
- Did I take a beating?
- Yes, you did.
That was enjoyable.
I don't remember
the latter half of the game.
- He just...
- What happened?
The referee will declare a winner.
Who will Kang Chan Hee choose
as the winner?
- Team Ji.
- Team Ji wins!
- Nice!
- Let's go!
- Gosh.
- Chan Hee...
That was a lot of fun.
- You kept smiling.
- Exactly.
- It was a good workout.
- The third match...
will be between
Park Jae Jung and Wonstein...
versus Yoo Jae Suk and KCM.
Seriously?
(Jae Jung comes out attacking
right from the start.)
(However, he runs out of energy.)
Jae Jung's out of energy now.
They're all exhausted.
You did great.
Let's see who won the third round.
- Team Others?
- Team Others wins!
(Team Others wins Round 3.)
That was close but well done.
- Congratulations.
- Get in here.
- You never know.
- It's the last round.
Go, Team Others!
- All right.
- Let's do this.
Go, Team Others!
Go, Team Ji.
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
Don't forget to smile.
All right.
Get ready.
Speed things up a little.
Rather than blocking them...
(The final round begins.)
Don't forget to smile!
Why are you in front of me?
Smile, everyone!
Get him!
(Jae Suk takes the first strike.)
(However, Jong Kook counterattacks.)
Get over here.
(Laughing)
Look at him.
(Chucky armed with pillow
attacks sporting an evil giggle.)
(His pillow bursts open.)
(We sense Chucky
amid the floating feathers.)
His pillow burst open.
- What happened?
- Get him!
- This is your chance.
- A pillow...
- Attack him now.
- I need a pillow.
His pillow burst open.
- Over here.
- There.
This is your chance. Attack!
(While Jong Kook
is out of commission,)
(Team Others fight back.)
- His pillow.
- He doesn't have a pillow.
(Stealing pillow)
Hold on a second. I'm really sorry.
(Chucky is armed again.)
(Chang Mo gets beaten again
for going after Jong Kook.)
I don't have a pillow!
Seriously?
(Jae Suk is his next target.)
(The husbands get a beating
from Jong Kook.)
- Get him.
- They're all exhausted.
(They still maintain their forced smiles.)
(It takes a toll on his heart again.)
(The game ends
due to them all being exhausted.)
- His pillow burst open.
- That was hilarious.
There's no way we can beat him.
- Everyone's exhausted.
- That was exhausting.
Are you all right?
It serves as a workout.
Jae Suk's in tears!
You got in your cardio workout.
This is why it's an official event.
Crying makes you a loser.
- I love it.
- This is the time to smile.
(Smiling while in pain
proves that you are a champion.)
That was a close game.
Anyway, please show us
who won the last round.
- We managed a lot of hits.
- I maintained my smile.
- You saw us.
- We kept on attacking...
with our pillows intact
and we kept smiling.
- I hope you saw what happened.
- We kept on smiling...
- I subdued all three of them.
- We...
We never stopped attacking.
- I kept on smiling.
- We...
- Thank yucca!
- Okay.
- Team Ji.
- Nice!
- Nice. Good job.
- Team Ji wins.
(Sighing)
Chan Hee...
He will side with
whatever team Suk Jin's on.
That's absurd.
(The men's event ends
with Jae Suk in doubt.)
That's absurd.
But the battle isn't over yet.
The women's event remains.
(Team Ji versus Team Others,
Women's Event)
The women will play omok instead.
- Omok?
- I'm the best at that.
- I'm not good at it. Oh, no.
- I'm the best at it.
The standard rules will be followed.
However, you are allowed
to take back a move.
(The standard rules apply,
but a take-back is allowed.)
- They can take back a move?
- Only on one condition though.
Another teammate...
must paint his face
in exchange for a chance...
- to take back a move.
- Sounds good.
- It will be a best of three.
- Okay.
We'll see who has the stronger brainpower.
I'm a master at omok.
Me too.
I have never lost a match before.
I have been crowned a champion
in my neighborhood.
- Really?
- I'm not kidding.
I have never lost a game
of omok before.
- Omok is fun to play.
- In my case...
Do you know how to play it?
You need five in a row.
Do you really think
I don't know what omok is?
No, I...
- Of course you know the game.
- Are you kidding me?
- You need five in a row.
- Right.
It gets risky when the opponent has
three pieces in a row.
There's a rule you must follow.
If the opponent has three pieces
in a row with both sides open,
you must block them.
When there are three pieces in a row.
There's no going back for me.
Of course I know how to play omok.
We'll attack first.
- All right. We're attacking first.
- Sounds good.
If you give your player a tip,
you'll have to apply...
- the ink on your face too.
- We can't give them tips?
Oh, I see.
Ji Hyo, think before making a move.
- I'm really good at it.
- Think before making a move.
- Let's play!
- My hands are shaking suddenly.
But even if you think a lot,
you can't play well.
I'll start. Let's begin.
- You just go for it.
- Good one.
No, every player has a strategy.
She put it right next to So Min's.
She's making the same move.
What?
(It looks like Ji Hyo
will focus on defense.)
- That was...
- What was that?
- She's a good defender.
- What?
(Attacking)
(Defending)
That's not it. Hey.
- If she plays like that from now...
- She's in trouble.
Ji Hyo, yours isn't on the line.
She's in trouble.
Where did she place
her second piece?
- That's...
- What?
(Going back and forth)
You should think ahead
before attacking.
Slow down!
- Think before attacking.
- You should slow down.
(Super fast omok)
- All right.
- Whatever.
- It's your turn.
- If she keeps attacking...
Hey.
(So Min places
3 pieces in a row first.)
- Hey.
- It's over.
- That's it.
- It'll be over soon.
All right. So Min.
(So Min still has many chances
to attack.)
Wait. That's it.
It'll be over soon.
All right. So Min.
- What? She blocked it?
- Why did you place it there?
- All right.
- No?
That's it.
All right. So Min.
(She made
a completely useless move.)
- It's our chance.
- Why did you place it there?
Wait! Let me undo it.
Then put some ink
on one of your team members' faces.
You can choose whoever you want.
(She has to put ink
on one of their faces to undo it.)
That's kind of cool.
(A receding M-shaped
hairline tattoo)
Hey.
She made a hairline for him.
- Can you fill the other parts too?
- She made a hairline for him.
It's because it looks awkward.
It looks okay.
- It's cute.
- It looks nice.
I'll play now.
- I will...
- Thank yucca!
(She places it again
after undoing her move.)
Please be careful.
That's good.
Take your time to think.
No, that's not it.
Just keep going.
- That's it.
- You're almost done.
Don't tell her.
She's doing well.
It's your turn.
- What?
- Why did you place it there?
All right.
Hey, undo it.
Why did you...
- Why did you place it there?
- All right.
Hey, place it now.
- Why did you...
- Place it.
- All right.
- Hey, undo it.
- Why did you place it there?
- Hey, place it now.
Why did she...
You shouldn't have...
- That's it.
- You should've placed it there.
We won.
(Ji Hyo found the exact spot
where she'll form double 3 rows.)
- We won.
- That's not it.
- She got it. We won.
- We won.
That's four.
- Wait. I'll undo my move.
- That's four!
- You can't undo it now!
- No.
- You can't undo it now.
- Double three rows aren't allowed.
- That's not it.
- It's not double three rows.
- That's not it, you guys.
- Thank you!
If she places a piece here and here,
it'll be over.
- Aren't you giving her tips?
- No.
- No, we're not.
- What? We're not giving her tips.
- You got it, Ji Hyo.
- You can place it. Just place it.
- You're giving her tips.
- You can place it here.
- Isn't that...
Isn't that considered giving her a tip?
- What?
- That's not it!
We're telling her to place it
where she was going to.
The place where she put it before.
But the fact that you told her
to place it wherever you want...
is giving her a tip.
- No! We just told her to...
- We said it after she placed it.
- We can't undo it?
- Mister.
- She had placed it already.
- Ji Hyo, can you undo yours once?
- No.
- Please, just this once.
- No, I don't have to undo it.
- She had placed it already.
- Then she'll undo it once.
Look at this guy.
What?
- He almost...
- How dare you stop my arm?
Did you just hit me?
If you were to make your move,
you should've placed it here.
He's giving her tips!
- He gave her tips.
- Hey, Spotty.
- She lost already.
- Spotty.
- "Spotty?"
- Hey, Spotty.
(Spotty, Has a huge mole)
She lost already.
- "Spotty?"
- What was that?
- Is that a spit curl?
We didn't mention that
double three rows weren't allowed.
That's right.
Then can she please undo it once?
- That's...
- Then put ink on the two of them.
- That's the general rule.
- It's the basic rule.
- It's the basics.
- Wait. Why don't you refute that?
I think you can just tell him
that it's allowed.
- Tell me what?
- A rule on double three rows.
- You should say it.
- Double three rows...
Don't you want to do that today?
- Hey, that's...
- It looks like he does.
(When the staff decided
against Team Jong Kook...)
(This is what I want to do today,
I guess.)
(He must've been holding grudges
against it since then.)
He decides the rules.
"This is what I want to do today,
I guess?"
Doesn't he decide the rules?
Hasn't it been a month
since that incident?
I think so.
- You're still holding grudges?
- Is he sulking over that?
- I think that's what you'll say.
- He's still...
Don't you feel like doing so today?
- Well...
- Can you undo your move once?
Even if you do...
- You have no chance anyway.
- She'll lose for sure.
- It's because...
- That's right.
- Let's play the next round.
- Right.
- All right.
- You should block hers too.
- Okay.
- That should be your strategy.
It's 1 to 0.
(Team Others 0, Team Ji 1)
- We won, right? Yes!
- All right.
Hey, Ji Hyo won...
without realizing it.
- Because...
- You're so good at this game.
- So Min...
- I didn't realize it.
So Min placed her pieces weirdly.
So Min, you can do it well.
Will I be able to do well this time?
- I missed it.
- Watch her moves as you play.
- Watch her moves.
- This time, since you...
- Mister!
- So you should attack first.
- I'm right, aren't I?
- Just stay still.
- How dare you call me that?
Just stay still, mister.
- Mister.
- Why you little...
You're a funny man, aren't you?
- You look like a pickle.
- You're one weird man.
What did you call me?
- A pickle!
- What's wrong with you guys?
- What's with you?
- You...
- What are you doing, greengrocer?
- Sorry.
Let's play.
- Round Two will begin.
- All right.
I should win this time.
- This time...
- Do I get to attack first?
Yes, go ahead.
(This time, Ji Hyo attacks first.)
Let's play.
Wonstein, aren't you glad
that your team won?
- I cheered earlier because I was.
- You did?
Tell that guy to stay quiet.
The two of them...
I've never seen a play like this.
Make a careful move.
Think before making a move.
Where did you place it?
Don't joke around and play properly.
- Good job in coming in between.
- Okay, Haha.
- That's it. Good job.
- That's it.
It's okay.
- You must defend.
- You'll get a chance.
That's right!
That's where I was thinking of placing it.
- So Min.
- Just defend it well.
Go over there.
That's it. Good job.
- "Go over there?"
- That wasn't a great move.
- Wait. Take your time.
Rather than there...
What are you talking about?
- I mean...
- What are you saying?
- No. Stay quiet.
- Good job in coming in between.
- Stay quiet.
- That's a warning.
- I mean...
- What are you saying?
- No. Stay quiet.
- Good job in coming in between.
Stay quiet.
- So Min, you should...
- At this rate...
take a look
at the whole thing first.
- At this rate...
- That's it. That's good!
We're going to win
for sure this time.
Right there.
(Right there.)
That's it. That's good!
We're going to win
for sure this time.
(So Min can make double three rows
which guarantees her a win.)
- So Min, up there.
- Right there.
- No, don't put it there!
- No!
- Be quiet!
- No, right there.
(So Min, up there.)
(No!)
- Be quiet!
- No, right there.
- That's a bit...
- No!
- Mister!
- No, not there.
Mister.
- Be quiet!
- No!
- Mister!
- No, not there.
- Go for it.
- Mister.
- An arrow shape.
- No!
(She understood it wrong.)
- So Min, why did you put it there?
- An arrow shape!
- Hold on.
- She already put it there.
Undo it right now.
That's it.
- Let's do it.
- I wasn't supposed to put it there?
- I mean...
- You should pick someone else.
- You should put it on someone else.
- Why do it on Haha only?
- This doesn't even show much!
- You should put it on someone else.
Put it on someone else. All right.
Put it on KCM too!
Jae Suk, close your mouth tight.
Like this.
Wait.
(Mexican omok player)
(The beard transplant
was a huge success.)
(Bushy)
- It's the best.
- Well done.
Look at it.
- It's so cool.
- Jae Suk.
- Really?
- You look like a foreigner.
There's a character
that looks like him.
- Do I look okay?
- What was it again?
- I've seen him in an animated film.
- There's a character.
Good.
- Well done.
- You should grow your beard.
- It looks great.
- I want it too.
That's...
He looks like a Mexican man.
So Min, make an arrow. That's it.
That was good.
(By undoing her move,
she made double three rows.)
- Right?
- Good.
She won. It's over.
- It's over.
- Double three rows are allowed.
- There!
- All right!
She won. It's over.
- It's over.
- Double three rows are allowed.
- There!
- All right!
(So Min wins.)
You should undo it.
- We can't. She won already.
- That's it.
All right. It's 1 to 1.
The last round.
I'm relieved.
So Min, you should
keep watching her moves.
If you keep putting yours here,
it'll be disadvantageous for you.
- Even them out.
- I got it! I know it too!
What do you know?
- Do it as I say!
- I know it too!
- Excuse me.
- Are you two brothers?
- Bodhidharma.
- Use your head.
- Sir. Where are you from?
- What is it?
- What did you say?
- Where are you from?
- Are you Mexican?
- Mexico.
- Hey.
- You two...
- Spain?
You're good at Korean.
- Barcelona.
- You're good at Korean.
I was born in Korea.
- You were?
- Yes.
You have to see the whole thing.
The whole thing.
Don't focus on one side only.
- I've seen you from somewhere.
- Got it?
How did So Min
put the ink on his face like that?
- She's skilled.
Let's play.
Is there a version
where you say "sorry?"
They're placing their pieces.
- Ji Hyo, take your time to think.
- Go.
- Ji Hyo...
- Ji Hyo does think. She's good.
- It's because...
- What's with her play?
It's not bad.
Shouldn't she undo it?
- You don't have to.
- What did you say?
I just don't get it.
What was that for?
Wait.
Ji Hyo is following her.
- Why did she block it?
- That's good.
What are you doing?
That's it.
She lost earlier with a similar move.
Don't go easy on her.
So Min, make an arrow.
That's a great move.
- So Min, make an arrow.
- What was that?
That's a great move.
Are you allowed to give such a tip?
- That's great!
- An arrow...
My gosh.
- My gosh. Just put it there.
- That was...
- Stay quiet!
- That's it.
That was great.
- That's too...
- You're giving her tips openly.
They're telling her tips too openly.
We were just cheering her on.
That was great.
There's a great spot.
- But that's a bit...
- Don't tell her tips.
There's a great spot.
- Will you keep giving her tips?
- There's something on the board.
- No, mister.
- I was just removing the dust.
Wait. We should put the ink on him.
- What?
- We should put the ink on him.
- That was too obvious!
- He should put the ink.
We should put the ink on him. Ji Hyo.
What?
I'll put it on you.
Remove your glasses.
Wouldn't the black one be better?
But you are on the white team.
What do you think
about a white beard?
- Okay?
- Like the blue whale.
(Well...)
(It's neither cool nor funny.)
That's... I'm sorry.
It's not so funny.
This isn't funny at all.
This is even funnier.
- I told you to use the black ink.
- I'm sorry.
- I told you it wouldn't be funny.
- It's not even funny.
- Why would you put it on like this?
- It's not funny.
It's not funny at all.
I told you to use the black ink!
I had it all panned out.
- It was... I'm sorry.
- It doesn't even look cool.
- It's not funny.
- It's not funny at all.
- No.
- Wait.
My goodness!
- Undo it!
- Block it! Undo it!
- You can put it on me.
We almost won though.
- Hey, you have thicker hair now.
- Well done.
That's it!
- That's it.
- Undo it.
- You're undoing it again?
That's not allowed.
You've undone it many times.
We almost won.
Hold on. I won.
Undo it now!
- Ji Hyo wins.
- Undo every move!
- Ji Hyo won.
- This is...
- Why?
You should've made a row
with five pieces.
Why make another row
with four pieces?
- She had a row of five pieces.
- That's right.
- We won!
- That's right!
- That's right.
- Double four rows.
- We won.
- Team Ji won.
Suk Jin, there are points
from 1 to 5.
Give one each to your teammates.
- I can do that?
- Yes.
- Is it good to get five points?
- Yes, five is good.
Since you don't have to
give yourself a point,
you can just use four.
All right.
I worked hard earlier
when we did the pillow fight.
I should give five points to...
Jong Kook, you're sitting down.
Well... It's not that.
- Still...
- We've been standing, so...
Jae Jung worked really hard earlier.
- Suk Jin.
- Thank you.
Jae Jung earns five points.
That's so disappointing, Suk Jin.
And...
No wonder you're upset, Jong Kook.
Right?
- No wonder you're upset.
- I worked so hard.
I saw how Wonstein
gritted his teeth and worked hard.
Come on, Suk Jin.
(What's worse is that 4 points
went to Wonstein.)
Actually, Wonstein...
- I was really surprised by him.
- Hold on.
M.O.M... My gosh.
I'm so ready to ruin their album.
(I'm so ready to ruin their album.)
- You should hurry and record a song.
- Suk Jin.
You did so well in omok.
I'm sorry. Wait.
I forgot about you, Jong Kook.
- That was awkward.
- You forgot about me?
- Well...
- Why did he take Jong Kook...
if he was going to do this?
- Well, Jong Kook is...
- He just made use of him.
- Jong Kook is...
- You used him and threw him out.
You're always number one
in our hearts.
All right.
The point distribution is over,
and the losing team
got a point each.
(Team Others earned a point each.)
You guys are really tight.
M.O.M is quite tight.
- They're tight.
- I didn't know...
- they'd be this tight.
- All right.
All right, then.
Let's see where he lasts longer.
M.O.M or Running Man.
You're about to do
your last mission.
Like earlier, if you guess...
who Suk Jin will choose
as his teammates...
- Again?
- We're changing teams?
If you guess correctly again,
it'll be disadvantageous for Suk Jin.
He'll not stick with Jong Kook
this time for sure.
- Stay quiet.
- That's right.
Because he's uncomfortable
with Jong Kook.
He knows that I won't try my best.
Sir, can you take a look at mine?
Can you check if it's correct?
Are you getting tutored?
- Am I right?
- There's a high possibility.
- Right?
- There is?
Then I'll go ask for your advice.
Can you please keep quiet?
Sir, I'm sorry,
but can I compare mine to yours?
Can you take a look at mine too?
- It's because...
- There's only a slight difference.
Mine too.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
The eight of you should open it
at the same time.
- All right.
- In 1, 2, 3.
Let me check them.
Let me see if anyone
has guessed correctly.
I'm certain...
I'm certain that he picked them.
I think he picked the members
of M.O.M...
and So Min.
The members of M.O.M and So Min.
(Jong Kook thinks he picked
M.O.M and So Min.)
I get a space for the penalty
if I overlap with one,
and two spaces
if I overlap with two?
- That's right.
- That's how it works?
(The more they overlap,
the more spaces he'll get.)
It's so obvious.
I guess a lot of ours
overlap with yours.
So many people guessed it
correctly at a glance.
- Are you all in my head?
- It's guaranteed.
- Why are you so obvious?
- It's guaranteed to overlap.
- I told you it was guaranteed.
- Please announce the result.
It was a choice between
So Min and Ji Hyo.
- Of course.
- All right.
I'll announce the result.
- Drum roll.
- If you picked the members...
- of M.O.M, tell us.
- Right.
I did include the members of M.O.M!
All right!
Raise your hand if you included
the members of M.O.M.
Let's see. Everyone did?
Except for you two.
I just wanted to play a game
with the members of M.O.M.
- Please...
- Please let there be So Min.
So Min!
(Jeon So Min)
We won!
So Min!
- We won!
- I should've picked So Min.
- So many overlapped with mine.
- I might get the penalty.
- Yes!
- I'm exempted.
How many are exempted already?
I got all the others right,
but why did you have to pick me?
- Seriously, Suk Jin.
- He's so obvious.
Let's move to the next spot
for the last mission.
- Let's go!
- Yes!
I'm exempted from the penalty!
I can't wait to see
what kind of game we'll play.
Is this the last game?
It's hard for me to come out.
I'm having so much fun today.
Can we extend the shoot a little?
Come back next week.
I won't be here next week.
- Come back next week.
- Jae Suk...
- I won't be here next week.
- Let's have more fun next week.
What do I do? I seriously...
- I don't want it to end.
- I'll see you next week.
- That's right. Let's go home now.
- So Min, let's go home now.
- Jong Kook.
We should get some rest too.
This time,
we're all Ji Hyo's husbands.
- They're my husbands.
- We're Ji Hyo's husbands.
- Ji Hyo has many husbands now.
- Let's win.
But the real husband among us...
- There's only one, right?
- Stop it!
There's only one, right?
For the first time...
Can I sit next to her?
(Giving him a 2nd warning
with his looks)
- What's wrong with you?
- Fine!
Come on, Haha. Gosh, my husbands.
Suk Jin won
in the previous mission,
so you'll earn three spaces for prize.
But the three of them
guess the teammates correctly,
so it's the same thing
as adding three spaces for penalty.
Don't they cancel each other out?
No, the latter ones
cover the previous ones.
It's better than getting...
- just three penalty spaces.
- I get it.
I might get the penalty.
(Suk Jin is getting closer
to receiving the penalty.)
My gosh.
The last mission...
is advantageous
for those who love music.
It's called
Do You Want to Hear the Song?
(The last mission,
Do You Want to Hear the Song?)
Do you want to hear it?
All nine of you will play.
Each team will be divided
into two groups.
So for your team,
1 group will have 3 people.
Each team will roll the die.
If you get 1 and 2, that'll be 12.
Then we'll let you listen
to the song at 12 seconds.
You'll guess what the song is
after listening to it for a second.
But if none of you
can't guess the song,
then we'll play the song
at 1 minute and 12 seconds.
- I see.
- Okay.
You can't just guess it though.
You need to shout out the answer
to the quiz we give you.
Then you'll earn a chance
to guess the song.
- We need to get the answer?
- We'll never be able to guess it.
For instance, the question will go,
"Who invented the Korean alphabet?"
The members of the group must
divide the answer and answer it.
So for us, it'll be
Sejong, the, Great.
It doesn't matter
how you divide the answer among you.
It could go, Se, jong, the, Great.
I'm only looking at the back
of Ji Hyo,
but I can see her brain
working fervently.
She's trying to sort things out.
The songs we'll play...
are the hit songs
released from 2000 to 2021.
All right. We got this.
We'll play a song...
- I'm an expert in this.
- from each year.
We picked a hit song from each year.
Those are the exact songs...
- He knows a lot of songs.
- I'm listening to.
- Because I love music.
- Jae Suk knows a lot of songs.
If Wonstein picks the year,
we'll play a song from that year.
Pick one
that's advantageous for you.
- I'll choose 2010.
- That's great.
- He picked 2010?
- That's when...
Wonstein was in high school.
You were a teenager.
I was 25.
That's when you listen
to music the most.
You listen to music the most
in middle school and high school.
- That's right.
Ji Hyo's die will be the 1st digit,
and Wonstein's will be the 2nd.
Please roll it.
(A hit song from 2010,
The section to be played)
- That was great.
- Next.
The first part is better.
- No, the latter part is better.
- Is it?
That's 0 and 4.
- At 4 seconds?
At 4 seconds?
We'll let you listen to the song
at four seconds for a second.
- This will be too hard.
- It's the prelude.
- The prelude.
Play the song.
What are we supposed to say?
- Let me answer.
(Both teams called to answer
as soon as they heard the song.)
- Let me answer.
- No, we must answer the quiz.
- We must answer the quiz.
- All right.
Here comes the question.
She's a genius poet
from the mid-Joseon period.
She's also known as the sister
of Heo Gyun who wrote...
- "The Tale of Hong Gil Dong."
- Let me answer!
Heo.
- Nan Seol.
- Let me answer.
- What?
- KCM.
- Let me answer!
- What was that?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Let me answer!
Heo Nan.
- Wrong.
- Let me answer!
- Heo Nan.
- What is it?
- Wrong.
- Let me answer!
- You don't know the answer?
- I don't know.
- It's your turn.
- Let me answer.
It's our turn. Heo Nan Seol Heon.
No, you have to say it
with your team.
- Let me answer!
- Darn it!
Heo Nan Seol Heon.
(Suk Jin revealed the answer.)
- Heo Nan.
- Seol Heon.
- All right.
- Miss A.
- Five, four...
- "Good Girl, Bad Girl."
- No, it's "Bad Girl, Good Girl."
- Let me answer!
Let me answer!
Heo.
- Nan Seol.
- No! This is your group.
- Nan Seol Heon!
- What's wrong with them?
I guess this is our group.
- Oh, the three of us?
- Yes.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- Let me answer!
- Let me answer.
- Heo Nan.
- Seol Heon.
- Miss A.
- Yes.
"Bad Girl, Good Girl."
- All right!
- We got it.
- Well done.
- That was close.
We could've gotten it.
This is our group?
This is... Where do I belong then?
The three of us.
- Oh, the three of us?
- The three of you.
We could've stolen the answer.
What a bummer.
Guys, it's time
to pick the next year.
It seems like you're telling
the answer to each other...
- because you're sitting close.
- That's right.
The 3 of you and the 2 of you
should switch seats.
- The 3 of you and the 2 of you.
- Us?
- Bring it on.
- It doesn't matter.
Let's switch seats.
This will be less confusing.
I just understood the game.
I'll get it for sure this time.
Jong Kook,
which year would you like to pick?
Pick a year when you were active.
- I'll pick 2002.
- That's good.
- How does 2002 sound?
- I know songs from 2002.
- You know those songs, right?
- From 2002?
- No, we can do it.
Roll the dice.
I'm not sure about 2002.
- It's 3 and 0.
- That's 3 seconds.
Right. It's three seconds.
- Play...
- I know...
- the singers from then.
- Play the song.
(A hit song from 2002
playing at 3 seconds)
- Wait.
- It's a ballad.
I can't tell from this.
- Wait.
- It's from 2002?
There was only the piano.
Here comes the quiz.
Who saved France from crisis
during the Hundred Years' War...
between the UK and France
in the 15 century...
after hearing a voice
that told her, "Save France?"
- Let me answer.
- Joan...
- Of Arc.
- UP's...
- "Puyo Puyo."
- Is it incorrect?
- Let me answer. Joan...
- Of Arc.
- No.
- Come on.
- Let me answer.
- Joan...
- Of Arc.
Hold on.
Kim Gun Mo.
- Joan of Arc.
- Let me answer. Joan...
- Of Arc.
- He said "Joan of Arc" already.
- Joan of Arc.
- Let me answer. Joan...
(He keeps saying "Joan of Arc"
with innocent eyes.)
You blew your chance.
Everyone needs to participate.
Of. Arc.
(They lost their chance
to answer once more.)
I want to get it right.
- For goodness' sake.
- What are they doing?
Joan...
Another team needs to go first.
Music, cue.
(A hit song from 2002
gets played again.)
- I know singers from 2002.
- Hold on.
- I was active back then.
- One more time, please.
- So it was released in 2002.
- Let me answer.
- It isn't that song, is it?
- Joan...
- Of Arc.
- Okay.
And the answer is...
Boohwal's "Never Ending Story."
- Okay.
- We did it.
- We did it. We got it right.
- How did you know?
- It wasn't Lee Seung Chul's song.
All right. It was Boohwal.
- All right. Good job.
- Okay.
We have no reason to fight.
We are on the same team.
- Seriously.
- They got it right.
I loved this song so much.
- Someplace where I can't reach
That's right.
- Was it released in 2002?
- All right. It's okay.
Can I choose the year once?
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
We should take turns.
In the 80s...
Please start from the 2000s.
(Please start from the 2000s.)
- The 2000s.
- I am sorry, but...
- the three of them...
- Never mind then.
- still don't understand this game.
- Seriously.
I understood it perfectly.
There is no need.
- Then...
- Listen to Wonstein.
- Wonstein.
- Go with the year he knows well.
- We believe in you, Wonstein.
- That's right.
- How about 2021?
Let's go with 2019.
- That's a good one.
- All right. 2019.
I was going to decide on 2019.
Hold on. That was 3 years ago.
All right. Music...
(A hit song from 2019
playing at 47 seconds)
Cue.
(A hit song from 2019
playing at 47 seconds)
I knew it!
- I knew it!
- It's from 2019.
Let me answer!
- No.
- The quiz comes first.
Who was
the British political economist...
who first came up with the term,
invisible hand,
- to describe the power...
- Let me answer.
- that moves the market?
Adam...
What's the answer?
- Let me answer.
- You can't tell her the answer. Haha.
Eden...
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
- Adam...
- Smith.
Okay. Please guess the song.
ITZY's "Dalla."
(ITZY's "Dalla")
- I knew it!
- What's the answer?
- Keep listening. I knew it!
- I knew it!
- It must be a famous song.
- I have no idea.
- Let us hear a different part.
- I will jump to a minute later.
- Okay.
Cue.
(Playing the song
at 1 minute and 47 seconds)
I got the hang of it.
- Hold on. It's rap.
- It's rap.
- Hey.
- Isn't it a song by Simon Dominic?
It's someone else.
- Adam...
- Smith.
ZICO's "Any Song."
(Incorrect)
It isn't "Any Song."
- Shall I jump to a minute later?
- Yes.
Now playing the song
at 2 minutes and 47 seconds.
(Playing the song
at 2 minutes and 47 seconds)
- Is it a female singer?
- I don't know.
- I am going.
- Is it a mixed-gender group?
- It's a mixed-gender group.
- I am going.
- Is it a song we know?
Is it a famous song?
I am going.
I am going. That's how it goes.
Right?
- That's right.
- I am going.
- Is it a collaboration?
Please play it one more time.
Cue.
(A longer snippet is played
for the clueless members.)
I am going.
He is making it even more confusing.
- Seriously.
- Be quiet.
He is so loud.
- You know that I
(You know that I)
I am so confused.
- It's impossible to guess with him.
- You know
You know
- I fly
- Hold on. Isn't it a song by BTS?
That's right.
(Is it a song by BTS?)
- You know, I fly
- Hold on. Isn't it a song by BTS?
Hold on. BTS...
- You know, I fly
- What was the title? Hold on.
I am so confused because of him.
He makes...
every song sound like
it's from the early 2000s.
I can't think.
He is too much.
I got the exact melody.
He makes every song sound like
it's from the early 2000s.
- I will play a longer snippet.
- Please do that.
- This is frustrating.
- Cue.
(A longer snippet is played.)
Let me answer.
- Hold on. BTS.
- Right?
- Adam...
- You know
- I fly
- Adam Smith.
- Hold on. BTS'...
- Five,
- four, three,
- What was the title?
- two,
- BTS'...
"Man with..."
No.
- No.
- No?
- Let me answer. Adam...
- Smith.
(Both teams figured it out!)
BTS'...
"Blood Sweat Tears..."
- "and a Spoonful of Passion."
- Hey, we know that song.
- Oh, let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- A...
- Dam...
- Smith.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
- "Boy..."
BTS' "Boy with Luv."
("Boy with Luv" by BTS
was released in April 2019.)
You know, I fly
- You know
("Boy with Luv" by BTS
was released in April 2019.)
(Jae Suk and Ji Hyo
gave away the answer.)
- I messed up the song title.
- I couldn't remember.
This song is about you
so you should have known.
There is a younger boy, okay?
The song title is "Boy with Luv."
It's a song for boys like us.
BTS' "Boy with Luv."
Team Ji got a question right.
- We finally got a question right.
- Finally.
Jae Jung, choose the year this time.
I will go with 2013.
- That's a good one.
- Did you say 2013?
That year is my specialty.
- The year is 2013.
Music, cue.
(A hit song from 2013
playing at 7 seconds)
Chung dung tak!
(Chung dung tak!)
Stop it.
Stop it already.
(Chang Mo's surround sound
began once more.)
Seriously. Please.
- What is up with you?
- I can't think of anything.
I am sorry.
I just heard, "Chung dung tak!"
- This is so confusing.
- Seriously.
I will give you the quiz first.
He was an Italian sculptor and painter...
who left works
such as "Pieta," "David,"
and "The Last Judgment."
Let me answer.
- Michelan...
- Gelo.
Okay.
Oh, I don't know the song yet.
For goodness' sake.
(He just wanted to show off
his knowledge.)
The year is 2013.
Yes, it is.
- Isn't that it?
- Michelan...
Gelo.
- Girls' Generation's "Gee."
- It's incorrect.
- It wasn't released in 2013.
- It was released before that.
- Right.
- Really?
- It was released in 2008 or 2007.
- Shall I jump to a minute later?
- Yes.
Now playing the song
at 1 minute and 7 seconds.
(A hit song from 2013
playing at 1 minute and 7 seconds)
I heard "Inside."
- Hey!
- Inside
Let me answer.
(Will Team Ji score again?)
Michelan...
- Ge...
- Lo.
- Inside
Let me have you
Guess the song title.
He makes it sound like
a song by S.E.S.
(You can't escape Chang Mo's magic.)
Let me have you
I think that's the song.
- Now, 2 minutes and 7 seconds.
- Okay.
(A hit song from 2013
playing at 2 minutes and 7 seconds)
Han ne gang!
- Gosh.
- Which song is it?
- What was that?
- You are right.
Let me answer.
(Did Jae Suk figure it out
despite Chang Mo's sound?)
- Let me answer.
- Yes.
- Michelan...
- Gelo.
Apink's "Nonono."
Okay.
("Nonono" by Apink
was released in July 2013.)
Okay.
- Good job.
- No no no
I can't recognize any songs.
This is bad.
I see that everyone is
an old fossil.
- I don't know other songs.
- Every single one.
- Let's go with 2020.
- That's a good one.
Music,
cue.
- Let me answer.
- This is...
- Here comes the quiz.
- It's that song.
- I know this song.
- Yes.
Its literal meaning is,
"Lying on an uncomfortable bed..."
"and chewing on a gallbladder."
What's the four-character idiom
which means,
- "Persevering for revenge?"
- Let me answer.
Wasin...
- Sangdam.
- Correct.
- Hey.
- That's incredible.
- Correct.
- Hey.
- That's incredible.
- Correct.
Let me answer. Jang Beom June's...
Gosh, what was the song title?
My dear...
- Wasin...
- Sangdam.
Jang Beom June's...
"Your Shampoo Scent in the Flowers."
- What?
- His pronunciation was off.
"Your Shampoo Scent in the Flowers."
- What?
- His pronunciation was off.
- Let me answer.
- Wasin...
- Sangdam.
Jang Beom June's...
"Your Scent..."
"in the Flowers."
- Let me answer.
- Wasin...
- Sang...
- Dam.
Jang Beom June's...
"Your Shampoo Scent on..."
("Your Shampoo Scent on...")
- Let me answer.
- Wasin...
- I know the answer.
- Let me answer.
- Wasin...
- Sangdam.
"Your Shampoo Scent in the..."
- "Bouquets."
- Wasin...
- Wa...
Sangdam.
- Wasin...
- Sangdam.
Jang Beom June's...
"Your Shampoo Scent in the Flowers."
("Your Shampoo Scent in the Flowers"
by Jang Beom June...)
(was released in August 2020.)
- I totally knew the answer.
- Seriously.
I knew it too.
I was so close.
Let's go with 2021.
- Let's go with 2021.
- Okay. Let's go with 2021.
All right.
Music, cue.
(A hit song from 2021
playing at 1 second)
(It's a pretty clear note!)
- What?
- Bam!
- Let me answer.
- I know the song too.
- Bam!
- Let me answer.
- I know the song too.
- Really?
- Let me answer.
This four-character idiom means,
"Using when needed..."
- "and throwing away afterward."
- Let me answer.
- Tosa... Okay.
- Gupaeng.
Lee Mu Jin's "Traffic Light."
Okay.
("Traffic Light" by Lee Mu Jin
was released in May 2021.)
All right.
Let's go.
He knows so many songs.
I don't know any songs.
How does he know so many songs?
Ji Hyo knows
a lot of four-character idioms.
- What happened?
- You are incredible.
Did you look down on me?
- The two of them...
- Tosagupaeng.
- We have good teamwork today.
- We are doing well, right?
You are doing so well.
When he says the 1st half,
she figures out the 2nd half.
Currently, the score is tied.
We need to beat them.
We need to get this one right.
- This is the final round.
- Okay.
We need to do well.
- We got this.
- Let's get it right.
We will get it right.
Let me answer.
Nangong...
- Bul...
- Rak.
Zion.T's "Yanghwa BRDG."
(Team Ji wins the mission
with their perfect teamwork!)
Yanghwa Bridge
(Team Ji's victory was unexpected
as they didn't know the rules.)
I thought it sounded familiar.
Yes. We listened to it many times.
Thus, Team Ji won.
Please distribute the points.
- Okay.
- It's too bad.
- So Min.
- What has gotten into you?
We need to survive as a team.
- Thank you.
- And...
Two points.
Okay.
We can add more prizes.
(Team Ji adds 3 prizes.)
- That's good.
- All right, everyone.
To fill the three remaining slots,
I will give you two questions
for the Ji Suk Jin Quiz.
Since Suk Jin's favorite people are here,
I will give you questions about him.
That's good.
If more than half of the people
get any one of the questions right,
the remaining slots
will become prize slots.
I see.
We will be tested
on our knowledge of Suk Jin.
We know a lot about him.
All right. Here comes the question.
What's the exact title
of the radio show...
Suk Jin hosted for 4 years
from 2016 to 2019?
(What's the exact title
of the radio show...)
(Suk Jin hosted for 4 years
from 2016 to 2019?)
I don't know this one.
I am sure everyone...
- You should know it.
- How do you not know it?
Don't give any hints.
You were on the show.
- Don't give any hints.
- I don't remember.
- You should know it.
- Hey.
- So Min was on the show.
- Don't give any hints.
- I mean...
- Jae Suk was on it too.
- Jong Kook and Haha too.
- That's right.
- I was on the show.
- I know the title.
All right. One.
You should know it.
Two.
- You should know it.
- Five people or more.
Show your answer.
We will succeed.
- Five people or more.
- Show your answer.
("Ji Suk Jin's 2 p.m. Date")
All right. "Ji Suk Jin's..."
"Dawn of the Dead?"
Why would a radio show title be
It isn't a zombie movie.
So Min, how could you write
"Power FM?"
- Hey.
- "Ji Suk Jin's Power FM?"
I had no idea.
- I couldn't remember.
- That's an SBS radio show.
I got it right. "2 p.m. Date."
For goodness' sake.
- I have "2 p.m. Date."
- You have "2 p.m. Date."
You have "2 p.m. Date."
- Okay.
- We did well, right?
- We succeeded.
- What's the title?
It's "2 p.m. Date."
I know the title, okay?
- What?
It's "2 p.m. Date..."
It's "2 p.m. Date by Ji Suk Jin."
Come on!
- Are you kidding me?
- What are you talking about?
Are you kidding me?
- Are you kidding me?
- Hey.
- "2 p.m. Date by Ji Suk Jin?"
- It's "2 p.m. Date."
That's what it says
on the official website.
I had no idea...
that was the full title.
("2 p.m. Date by Ji Suk Jin")
It's "2 p.m. Date by Ji Suk Jin."
Is "2 p.m. Date by Ji Suk Jin"
the full title?
It's the full title on the website.
- I am disappointed in you.
- Suk Jin.
I thought it was
"Ji Suk Jin's 2 p.m. Date."
- I can't believe you.
- It's no wonder...
- he got fired.
- We will get the next one.
- All right.
Now comes the last question.
If you are a fan of Suk Jin,
you will be able to get it right.
What's Suk Jin's birth date?
Okay.
You know it, right?
What's Suk Jin's birth date?
- Okay. You know it, right?
- This is bad. I don't know.
What should I do?
Gosh, hold on.
(His friends of 12 years
write down the answer.)
You know it.
You know you do.
Isn't this the answer?
Earlier today,
a coffee truck came
to celebrate my upcoming birthday.
I don't know.
If you wrote down the answer,
show it to the camera.
Can I check it one at a time?
I am so curious.
You can do that
after the answers are revealed.
- Okay. To be honest,
- Please reveal the answers.
Wonstein, Jae Jung, and KCM
might not know it.
- I am not sure.
- Please reveal the answers.
I don't know. Is this the answer?
I really think you guys should know.
All right.
Let's see the answers.
(Seok Sam was born one day in 1966.)
One day in 1966.
- April 1968.
- Hey.
So Min, did you write down
Valentine's Day?
- I didn't know.
- February 14th.
A holiday.
February 14th.
Did you write 1954?
My mother-in-law was born in 1954.
Seriously.
- My mother-in-law was born in 1954.
- He wrote 1954.
He wrote 1954.
I wasn't born in 1954.
February 13th.
I don't think
two people got it right.
Jae Suk, you should get it right.
- I am not sure.
- I know your birth date.
He wrote 1702.
(Born in 1702)
(Ji Seok Sam, born in 1702,
mid-Joseon Dynasty)
Hey.
Do you think I am a zombie?
(No one got
Suk Jin's birth date right.)
How did no one get it right?
When in February is it?
- Isn't it next week?
- I know it's in February.
Tenth.
- Tenth.
- Thirteenth?
- Tenth?
- Tenth.
- It's the tenth.
- It's 10th.
- I knew it. February 10th.
I won't forget it again.
- Suk Jin.
- I know it now.
I won't forget it again.
- Suk Jin. February tenth.
- I won't forget it again.
You don't know my birth date.
You were born in 1984. August...
- August 14th.
- Forget it.
August 15th.
August 24th.
It's 20th.
We aren't that close.
All right.
- What's the point of knowing it?
- April 25th.
- Right?
- Yes.
Who else?
Never mind.
(Giving up)
- Never mind.
- I am surprised he knows mine.
In any case, the roulette will get
three penalty slots...
- since your friends didn't succeed.
- I am sorry.
For goodness' sake.
That was so funny.
We are bound to get a penalty.
- Five prize slots.
- All the penalty slots are here.
(10 penalty slots 5 prize slots,
and 1 Get off Work slot)
- Counting 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
- There are 5.
Getting off work would be nice too.
- I will announce the rankings.
- Okay.
The first place will win a prize
and be exempt from the penalty.
The second place will be exempt
from the penalty as well.
Everyone else except for those
with the exemption card...
has a chance of receiving
the penalty.
Okay.
I am jealous.
- All right.
- Will the first place be exempt?
- In the first place is...
- Not many people will remain.
(1st place winner of today's race)
Wonstein.
(Wonstein)
- Congratulations.
- Wonstein.
- He did well...
- earlier.
- Hey, Wonstein.
I didn't see it coming.
In the second place is Jae Jung.
(2nd place winner, Park Jae Jung)
- All right.
- How did this happen?
Suk Jin
must have looked after them.
- Seriously.
- I worked hard today.
- I got all the questions right...
- He helped them get exempt.
and did my best
with the pillow fight.
- In the third place is...
- Thank you.
So Min. In the fourth place are
Ji Hyo and KCM.
In the sixth place is Jong Kook...
and in the seventh place are
Jae Suk and Haha.
(Jae Suk and Haha placed last.)
Suk Jin, please spin the roulette.
Hold on. Will the top two be
exempt from the penalty?
- That's right.
- The two of them will be exempt.
- So the remaining ones are...
- I am exempt.
Four of them have the exemption card.
So Ji Hyo and So Min left.
- Yes.
- I will spin the roulette.
- "Ji Hyo and So Min left?"
- What does that mean?
- Gosh.
- Hold on.
Are you going to ignore it?
- Listen.
- He can't talk properly.
Are you going to ignore it?
It's because he was alive
when the Korean language was invented.
Hold on a second.
"So Ji Hyo and So Min left."
- It makes no sense.
- It's because...
- he was born in the past.
- You understood.
That's right. I understood.
What happens if I get a penalty slot?
In that case,
you will receive the penalty.
- One of them...
- And Wonstein will pick...
either So Min or Ji Hyo
to receive the penalty.
If you get a prize slot,
they will receive the penalty.
- Okay.
- You can do it, Suk Jin.
- How does it work?
- I will go at once.
- I didn't hear him.
- Let's go.
Please explain it one more time.
There is no need.
It has nothing to do with you.
If he gets a penalty slot...
- Suk Jin wants to go home.
- Why are you so irritated?
- Seriously.
- It isn't important.
- Ji Hyo asked a question.
- Why are you so irritated?
- Seriously.
You should have listened
to the explanation the first time.
- It might not be related to you.
- If he gets a prize slot,
the two female members
will receive the penalty.
(He spins the roulette!)
If I get a prize slot,
they will receive the penalty.
I am 100 percent sure
you will get a prize slot.
- Can I take a look?
- A penalty slot.
A prize slot.
(Will he beat the odds of 31 percent
and avoid the penalty?)
It's a prize slot.
- It's a prize slot.
- A prize slot.
It's a prize slot.
- It's a prize slot.
- That's insane.
(Suk Jin got a prize slot.)
Suk Jin and Wonstein
will receive the prize.
So Min and Ji Hyo
will receive the penalty.
That makes no sense.
(So Min and Ji Hyo
will receive the penalty.)
That makes no sense.
There were only a few prize slots.
(Suk Jin got a prize slot
against all odds.)
- That's incredible.
- Seriously.
- Here comes the prize.
- I shouldn't use up my luck.
(Screaming)
- What is it?
- I am jealous.
It's meat.
- That's...
- Meat.
We prepared lamb,
which is Suk Jin's favorite.
- Lamb? I love it.
- Lamb.
French rack is the best.
It's so nice.
- You will give it to your juniors.
- That's right.
I will really give it to them.
- The penalty of the day is...
- What is it?
making the nose
that is bigger than Suk Jin's.
- The nose?
- Other people won't participate.
You will flick each other's noses.
That isn't too bad.
It's my first time doing it.
- Go ahead.
- Here I go.
- Be careful.
- I know that it's really annoying.
Seriously.
How do I do it?
- Do I use the middle finger?
- Yes.
The two of them...
That was too weak.
- I don't know how it's done.
- Hold on.
- What was that?
- Shall I flick Suk Jin's nose?
Give them a demonstration.
- Give us a demonstration.
- Would it be okay?
- I am curious.
- Then I will flick your nose too.
- We will flick each other's noses.
- That's right.
You should do that.
- I will flick your nose too.
- That's right.
- Go ahead.
- Let's flick each other's nose.
That's a good idea, right?
(No one asked them
to give a demonstration.)
Why are you doing this?
- Please show us.
- It's because...
- they need to see it.
- I see.
- I want to know how it's done.
- The nose...
should shake like this.
That's right.
- Okay?
- Get it on the high-speed camera.
The high-speed camera.
- It should shake like this.
- Yes.
(Flicking)
It shook.
(The demonstration was on another level.)
- That's right.
- That's how you do it.
The nose needs to shake.
My eyes teared up.
It wasn't that bad.
- Can you pull up your glasses?
- Okay.
All right.
- I will flick hard.
- Okay.
- It will shake.
- Flick the tip of his nose.
Flick the tip of his nose,
not his nose bridge.
(Flicking)
Flick the tip of his nose,
not his nose bridge.
All right.
(He destroyed Jae Suk's nose.)
- All right.
- That was too much.
You guys shouldn't do this.
This is too harsh for you.
- Suk Jin, nice.
- It must hurt a lot.
- That was unbelievable.
- Are you okay?
Great job.
(The penalty is done
with the cracking sound on the nose.)
I hit it right on the nose.
You guys shouldn't do this.
You can't do this.
- All right.
- Okay.
(We'd like to thank Wonstein,
Jae Jung, and KCM for the laughter.)
(Pick the captain
of Running Man in 2022!)
(Jeon So Min's Running Man)
(Yoo Jae Suk's Running Man,
Haha's Running Man)
(Today's special minor candidate)
(Cho Sae Ho)
(I don't even know the ruling party
and the opposition parties.)
(Who is the most dignified
and honest candidate?)
(Resign right away!)
(Breaking News:
Candidate Yoo gets into a scuffle.)
(Win more local voters
with special election pledges.)
(The two strong candidates,
Yoo and Kim in Jeju)
(The presidential race begins.)
(They must finish the race
no matter what!)
(Among the different candidates,)
(who will cast your vote for?)
(Running Man Presidential Race)