(Last week)
(The 3 guests who were born
in the Year of the Tiger)
(Eunhyuk, Hong Soo Ah, Bae Seul Ki)
(The Myth of Dangun
in the Year of the Black Tiger Race)
(Those who were born
in 1986 are tigers.)
(And the rest
of the members are bears.)
(It's an individual event where
they should gather garlic cloves.)
(The top 3 get a present
and the bottom 3 get a penalty.)
(A tiger and a bear
will be partners for the mission.)
(Among 5 tigers and 5 bears...)
(are 2 poachers in disguise.)
(There is 1 among bears
and 1 among tigers.)
(The poacher gets half of
the garlic cloves the animal earns.)
(So the animals don't want
to be partners with the poachers.)
(Those who arrest the poachers at the end,
get 20 garlic cloves.)
(Then they get to choose
their partners.)
She put it in.
(Bear Jae Suk and Tiger So Min)
Eunhyuk, look up.
(Bear Jong Kook and Tiger Eunhyuk)
(There is Eunhyuk's fan
who only looks at Eunhyuk.)
(Bear Suk Jin and Tiger Seul Ki)
(Bear Ji Hyo and Tiger Soo Ah)
(Bear Haha and Tiger Se Chan)
(Now they have a random draw
to choose their identity.)
(One among tigers and
one among bears will be poachers.)
(One of the five tiger cards
is the poacher card.)
(Once a poacher, always a poacher.)
Pick one of the tiger cards.
(So Min chooses
her identity like that.)
(Eunhyuk's turn)
(Eunhyuk is the poacher!)
(Eunhyuk picks the poacher card.)
Wait a second.
My heart is beating fast already.
(Taking a big breath)
Wait a second.
(Once he goes in,)
(he has to face
his partner, Jong Kook.)
Why is it Jong Kook of all people?
(He goes back feeling nervous.)
What?
(Why isn't it opening?)
I hoped things would be easy today.
I won't be able to keep it a secret.
(Now Eunhyuk will get
half of his parters' garlic cloves.)
(Detective Kim's eyes are set.)
(Pale)
You are just...
suspicious of everyone.
Eunhyuk seems a little nervous.
Eunhyuk, are you the poacher?
No, I'm not. It's just Jong Kook...
suspects everyone no matter that.
- Right.
- He has a good hunch.
- He really does.
- It feels somewhat strange.
He tripped twice on his way here
when there was nothing.
- I see. Twice?
- Yes.
And he kept rambling.
He might be the poacher.
(What will happen to Poacher Eunhyuk
who has a scary partner?)
(After the tigers
choose their identities...)
Pick one of the bear cards.
If it says a bear,
you're a regular bear.
If it says a poacher,
you're a poacher.
I've been unlucky lately.
I really don't want to be a poacher.
(Big Nose comes back
after choosing his identity.)
This is funny.
It feels strange.
- Suk Jin is being really strange.
- He's suspicious.
What took you so long?
Suk Jin, what makes you so happy?
- He's being strange.
- Mr. Poacher.
- What took you so long?
- Are you the poacher?
It looks like he's caught in a net.
(He captured himself.)
Look at him.
- He's being strange.
- Don't say that.
- He is strange.
- Isn't that strange?
My gosh.
- He's like this.
- I'll catch him.
- Catch him.
- I'm going to catch him.
I guess he's really the poacher.
- We have the poacher.
- I feel good when I'm suspected.
- I guess it's him.
- Go ahead and suspect me.
- It's him.
- I bet that's true.
- He must be the poacher.
- He is.
- He's the poacher.
- Suspect me.
It's Suk Jin.
But I won't catch him.
On purpose?
(Eunhyuk is the poacher
among tigers.)
(Who is the poacher
among bears then?)
All right.
There are two poachers here.
Those who partnered up
with the poachers will get...
only half of their garlic cloves
even if they win.
Really?
- Aren't you the poacher?
- No, I'm not.
I'll give you a mission
where you can earn garlic cloves.
It's called Furious Race.
- Okay. Furious Race!
- Furious Race.
Okay, Eunhyuk. It's Furious Race.
- He's good at races.
- I can see...
- how things will go today.
- I know.
Hey, your shoulders are curled in.
- All right.
- I have the text neck.
That's not good.
You will pick a toy car each.
And you will have a race
with it on a treadmill.
That will be fun.
The first team that is completely
wiped out loses the game.
Is it a random game?
Your ranking will determine
how many garlic cloves you receive.
We have ten toy cars here.
Choose one each.
- Do we get to choose one?
- Pick one, Eunhyuk.
- One for each?
- One for each.
Should I pick a small one or a big one?
I'll pick a big one.
Can we just pick one?
- I'll choose this one.
- This looks strong.
There are only trucks left.
I shouldn't have chosen this.
I like that car. Do you want
to switch your car with mine?
- Which one?
- I like that car.
Well, I'm sorry.
- I'm ashamed.
- He's...
That's perfect for you.
- It's perfect for me, right?
- I think that's good.
- Gosh.
- Seul Ki wants to switch.
This might be strong.
- This is a patrol car.
- This one looks weak.
This is a patrol car.
But the sports cars were already picked.
Eunhyuk, that's...
Why did he pick that one?
He was very late picking the car.
Because you're the poacher?
- What are you talking about?
- You're the poacher among tigers.
- He is the poacher.
- I think he is.
- Look at the color.
- What?
- Me?
- Yes.
It says "I'm the poacher."
- Who?
- It says NM.
- Does it mean I'm the poacher?
- What?
- Is that it?
- Yes.
You can put it down now.
There's nothing
we can do about this.
- Can we place it anywhere we want?
- Can I put it on here?
In front of yours like this?
- Like this?
- Let's do this. Run.
- All right. Let's do this.
- Good luck.
Don't touch them.
- How would it go?
- Please.
- It should run.
It's starting.
(The race starts.)
- Let's go.
- It's moving.
(Soo Ah, Ji Hyo, Jae Suk, So Min,
Seul Ki, Suk Jin)
(Haha, Jong Kook, and Eunhyuk
are out as soon as it starts.)
- I'm so nervous.
- My goodness.
- Gosh.
- They're out.
(Soo Ah, Ji Hyo, Jae Suk, So Min,
Seul Ki, Suk Jin, Se Chan)
- Okay.
- This is amazing.
(So Min, Suk Jin,
and Ji Hyo are out.)
My gosh.
(There are only 4 cars left.)
- Hey, Seul Ki.
- It's you and me.
(Jae Suk's sports car and
Seul Ki's patrol car are competing.)
- Hey, Seul Ki.
- It's going well.
- Good.
- It's holding mine.
- It's the patrol car.
- It's out.
It's stuck.
I'm winning. I'm the first.
- There you go.
- It's stuck.
- I'm winning.
- Please.
What is this?
- What is it doing here?
- Just go.
No. Don't touch it, Seul Ki.
Se Chan, charge forward.
Hey.
- Just hang on to it.
- No!
Don't blow at it. Stop it.
- Oh, no.
- It's moving.
(Se Chan is out.)
My gosh.
Oh, dear.
This is the final.
(Now only Jae Suk
and Seul Ki are left.)
- Hey.
- It's fast.
- Get ready.
- Oh, no.
- My gosh.
(Which car will survive
until the end?)
- It's holding Seul Ki's car.
- This is so thrilling.
- Seul Ki wins.
- Seul Ki?
It's holding Seul Ki's car.
(Seul Ki wins by a neck.)
- Seul Ki, you're the winner.
- It supported her car.
(Contrary to their expectation,
the patrol car beat the sports car.)
My car helped Seul Ki's.
- This is fun.
- It's so fun.
- Let's play one more time.
- One more time.
- Can we play again?
- Let's play one more round.
Now we know which car is good.
All right then. Without the winners,
the rest four teams
will play it again.
(Without the winners,
Suk Jin and Seul Ki, they play it again.)
- Well done.
- Nice.
Let's play it again.
This is really fun.
Let's go.
- All right. Are you ready?
- Yes.
- This is so fun.
- Okay.
That's good. Done.
- All right.
- This is really thrilling, right?
- It's fun.
- Why is it so fun?
- Okay.
- Let's begin.
I'm so thrilled.
(They are just toy cars,
but it's as thrilling as the F1 race.)
Okay. Mine looks good.
(The race starts.)
- It's moving.
- It's moving back.
Oh, no.
(Soo Ah, Jae Suk, Se Chan)
- Hey.
- Nice.
Oh, no.
- Hey.
- Mine has survived.
(A 5-car rear-end collision occurs.)
- Eunhyuk.
- This is a good spot.
(Both Jong Kook
and Eunhyuk survived.)
- Se Chan.
- It's done.
Go.
- Don't blow at it.
- Go!
- Hang in there.
- Engine!
Superpower beam!
- Hey.
- No.
(Se Chan's car starts to come
to life with the superpower beam.)
Go.
- Good.
- There it goes.
- What?
- Nice.
This is a good car.
- No, don't touch it.
- Touch it.
Hit it.
Go forward.
That one is amazing.
This one is unbelievable.
- What?
- No.
- No!
- Move backward.
No!
(Jong Kook's car starts
to be pushed backward.)
Darn it.
All right.
- Good.
- It's coming.
We're almost there.
My gosh.
Whose car is that?
This is like a scene from a movie.
- What do we do?
- This is a movie.
(Screaming)
(Hey!)
Are you controlling the car?
Okay. It's done.
No!
(Eunhyuk, Se Chan)
(Se Chan's car
suddenly drifts backward.)
No!
(It's finally out.)
(The winners are
Jong Kook and Eunhyuk.)
(Se Chan's car failed to finish
despite the power beam and booster.)
He won.
- This is really fun.
- That was unbelievable.
I guess this car knows
how a variety show works.
All right.
You are number 2,
and you are number 3.
We're number three.
Team Song Ji Hyo is number four.
Team Yoo Jae Suk is number five.
- That's disappointing.
- It was so much fun.
The winners are
Suk Jin and Seul Ki.
You two get ten garlic cloves.
And you get 8, 6,
four, and two garlic cloves
respectively.
We get 4 and 2 garlic cloves?
- We get 6.
- We get only 2 cloves.
- But the thing is,
- Eight cloves.
those who partnered up
with the poachers...
will lose half of
their garlic cloves to the poachers.
(The partners of the poachers lose
half of the cloves to the poachers.)
(If Jong Kook is not the poacher,
Eunhyuk should have 15 cloves now.)
- But we don't know that.
- Right.
- We will find out later.
- Of course, we will.
You will find out at the end.
- I see.
- At the end?
- We don't know that now.
- What?
Haha took
three of your garlic cloves.
- What?
- That's not true.
Now that he says that,
he seems really suspicious today.
- Okay.
- Seriously, it's not me.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
- Can you give us some hints?
I'll give you a hint.
I said those who placed 1st and 2nd
would receive special benefits.
Those who place first...
(The benefit for 1st place)
get to know the number
of their garlic cloves...
and the identities
of their partners.
- Then it's over.
- The first place?
Both members will
get to know all that.
- If one of them is a poacher...
- What happens then?
If they reach an agreement,
they can switch their partners.
If they don't want to,
they can keep the team as it is.
Haha is really shocked.
No. I don't care.
- You're busy doing some thinking.
- Who placed first?
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
If there's a poacher...
Jong Kook, what if it turns out
I'm not the poacher?
- I'm not the poacher.
- Just keep it up.
- All right.
- Keep up the good work.
For the second place,
we will give the information
to only one of them.
(Only 1 member of the 2nd place
will get the information...)
(on their identities and the number
of their garlic cloves.)
That's really nice.
We will pick one member
through a random draw.
Can we switch partners...
- when both members are animals?
- You can do that.
Eunhyuk wants to switch partners.
I want to switch partners
even if he's an animal.
- Hey.
- Jong Kook.
All right then. The first-place
team will leave the room first.
Let's go.
(Suk Jin and Seul Ki are going out
to check their identities.)
- You're not the poacher, are you?
- What?
- No, I'm not.
I'm not the poacher.
It's in there.
All right. I will tell you...
the number of your garlic cloves
and the identities of your partners.
How many did we win?
We got ten cloves, right?
You got ten garlic cloves each.
Please open yours. Both of you.
Open it together.
(One of them has
only 5 garlic cloves.)
What would you do?
(Will they switch partners
after checking their identities?)
- We still have a long way to go.
- I won't switch.
- Good.
- We won't switch.
You may go back in.
(They didn't switch their partners
after checking the identities.)
(The 1st-place team is done.)
- What?
- What's all this?
All right. Only one of you...
will get to know
your partner's identity.
You will play rock-paper-scissors,
and the winner will hear it.
(They play rock-paper-scissors,
and the winner gets to hear it.)
You...
Are you sure you're not it?
I'm not the poacher.
- Are you serious?
- I'm serious.
If you're not the poacher,
I want to show you...
whether I'm not the poacher or not.
(I want to show you...
whether I'm not the poacher or not.)
- What do you think?
- Then I'll hear it.
(Jong Kook suddenly wants
to show Eunhyuk his identity.)
- Then I'll hear it.
- All right.
I'll show you...
- my identity.
- Okay.
- But...
- Them I'll hear it.
Hang on.
(Viper realizes
that something's strange.)
If that's what you want,
I'll get the information.
Are you sure you're not it?
I'm not the poacher. I'm a tiger.
I'm just a tiger.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
Gosh, I won.
(I'm doomed.)
You know what?
If you check it right now,
you will feel bad
that it's just over like that.
"What? Is this it?"
- You think?
- Yes.
Then I should take a look.
(Then I should take a look.)
(His trick doesn't work.)
I'll show you
the number of your garlic cloves...
- and your partner's identity.
- Okay.
I knew it.
(Your partner is the poacher,)
(and you currently have
4 garlic cloves.)
- Jong Kook, it's not like that.
- Come here.
- Jong Kook, listen to me.
- I knew it.
Seriously,
I find myself surprising myself.
When he walked back,
he tripped like this.
And he kept rambling.
So I thought he was suspicious.
Why is it Jong Kook of all people?
I got goosebumps.
If I arrest him at the end,
how many garlic cloves will I get?
If you catch the two poachers,
you will get 20 garlic cloves.
I'll get 20 garlic cloves?
(The one who arrests the poachers
will get 20 garlic cloves.)
I have to catch one more.
You have to arrest
both the poachers.
Is it better for me
to keep it to myself?
It has pros and cons.
If you keep your team as it is,
you can hide
Eunhyuk's identity from others.
So I don't have to tell people...
- that he's the poacher.
- That's right.
(Hiding Eunhyuk's identity
from others can be a good strategy.)
All right then.
You'll keep it as it is, right?
(Polite)
Do you want my help?
Yes.
I'm making it look
like Haha is the poacher.
All right then.
If we stay here for too long,
people might find it suspicious.
Shall we go?
Even if we don't switch partners,
someone else might switch.
- Right.
- Let's go.
(Jong Kook decided to maintain
his team to keep his secret.)
Shall we go in with a smile?
With a smile.
Who received the information?
How did it go?
- We?
- We're keeping the team.
- Did you switch partners?
- We'll be happy together.
Hang on.
So one of you doesn't
know the information?
- One of us doesn't know,
- Right.
- but we have faith.
- Sure. What matters is...
that we win the games.
All right then.
The 1st and 2nd-place teams
have decided to maintain the teams.
- They are not switching teams?
- No.
You will get changed
for the next mission then.
Okay.
Please sit with your partners.
- Eunhyuk.
- Yes.
- Gosh, Eunhyuk.
He will come to play soccer with us.
- Who said that?
- Sit.
I'll just give it a try.
- Just come.
- Jong Kook.
It will never end there.
- Eunhyuk...
- What?
took the bait.
- He took the bait.
- Why?
Gosh, when I heard
their conversation,
I thought he shouldn't go.
He has a good reason to join us.
He lives with his manager,
- and his manager plays on our team.
- Right.
So he should join us too.
But my manager always comes home...
looking depressed
after soccer games.
He gets scolded a lot.
- He's not easily daunted.
- "Hey!"
- I know.
- "Take good care of it!"
"Take good care of it."
All right.
This is the first mission.
It's a game...
where you should protect
your partners with faith.
It's called
Bodyguard Cham, Cham, Cham.
- Bodyguard Cham, Cham, Cham?
- Cham, Cham, Cham?
Two teams will play
against each other in each round.
The representative of each team
will play Cham, Cham, Cham...
using this finger.
The other member will...
attack and defend
instead of the representative.
(The remaining 1 member
will attack and defend.)
- Like this?
- That means...
(The bodyguards will
attack and defend.)
So I should be the bodyguard.
No, I can be a bodyguard.
So the representatives will
play Cham, Cham, Cham.
And the bodyguards
will either attack or defend.
The bodyguard whose representative
loses will have to defend.
And there's more.
If you fail to attack,
you're supposed to lose
the right to attack.
But in this game, your
opponent can attack you right away.
The opponent can attack.
It counts as success.
You will get to attack
five times each.
The team that attacks more
will win the game.
Then the team that has
a poacher in it...
should lose the game then.
But the poachers also
need to earn more garlic cloves.
- So they try their best.
- That might be better.
Really? Isn't it better
for them to hide their identities?
It's up to them.
- So what's your plan?
- What do you mean?
What's your plan?
I'll just try my best.
- Don't you have a special plan?
- I'm not the poacher.
I'm just a bear.
- You are?
- Yes.
That's exactly what
a poacher would do.
Exactly. Right?
You're being completely fooled
by him.
- That could be the case.
- You don't have any plans.
You might be embarrassed at the end.
Jong Kook will probably say,
- "Why didn't you deny more firmly?"
- Right.
- Yes, that's right.
- "You seemed suspicious."
"You acted weird."
That's not it.
You won't do your best.
- No. I'm not a poacher.
- Right?
- He can't deny it.
- He's already acting suspiciously.
- He speaks strangely.
- Today, Jong Kook is Detective Kim.
- "I'm not a poacher."
- He's driving me nuts.
If Haha were one of the poachers,
I'd be shocked.
- I told you I wasn't one.
- It'd be shocking.
We'll decide the teams to have
a match by drawing lots.
- E would be the best.
- Indeed.
- Seul Ki, go ahead...
- and pick one. Pick E.
- I want E.
If you pick E, you'll be ranked
no lower than third.
- They must've picked E.
- I picked E.
(Jae Suk and So Min picked E.)
- E!
- Who picked A?
- Okay.
- Who picked C?
- This is great.
- Stop it.
- Oh, this team?
- We picked B.
The first round is Haha and Se Chan
versus Soo Ah and Ji Hyo.
Okay.
- All right.
- But I don't know the rules.
We'll let you play
a practice game first.
Haha, you can attack first.
Cham, cham, cham
(Soo Ah failed to defend.)
- Then I hit her. You must block it.
- Right. Good.
- You're supposed to...
- You should've blocked it.
- Ji Hyo should block the attack.
- Correct.
- Try not to hit me with the lid.
- I won't hit you.
- Why are you so anxious?
- I might accidentally hit you.
Be careful not to hit my nose.
(She informed Ji Hyo
of what she should know.)
My gosh.
(She warned Ji Hyo not to hit
her nose hastily.)
- Okay. I'm glad you told us that.
- I can't...
I can't get another nose job.
- "I can't get another nose job."
- I can hit your head, right?
- This is my last nose.
- She's funny.
- Her last nose of her life.
- Her last nose.
Let's continue the practice game.
Soo Ah will attack this time.
Cham, cham, cham
- Then...
- Right. Good.
- That's good. Ji Hyo.
- Like this?
I'll use my right hand.
- That's not how you should hit him.
- Exactly.
- I'll show you.
- You don't have to.
(The entertainer with 31 years
of experience will demonstrate.)
- You should hit him hard like this.
- Don't hit me with the edge.
You should hit him hard like this.
- Jae Suk.
- Come on. It's okay.
It doesn't hurt at all.
- Se Chan, hit him with it.
- Go ahead and hit me.
- Okay. Here I go.
- It doesn't hurt.
Jae Suk, you need to...
(Hitting hard)
- It doesn't hurt at all.
- Really?
It doesn't hurt. Does it hurt?
- It could make you upset though.
- No, it doesn't hurt.
- It doesn't hurt.
- Right?
- Give it to me. It looks fun.
- That was funny.
(Seok Sam tries getting hit
with a foam sword too.)
- It doesn't hurt at all.
- Right. Exactly.
Hit me. It doesn't hurt.
(Annoyed)
Hey.
- You told me to do it.
- It doesn't hurt.
- It doesn't hurt at all.
- But it was annoying.
- Anyway, it doesn't hurt.
- It doesn't hurt.
- It doesn't hurt, so don't worry.
- Suk Jin, are you okay?
- I'm fine. It didn't hurt at all.
- Okay. Great.
- Which team will attack first?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Good.
- You go first.
- Soo Ah, you have 5 attacks.
- I have 5 attacks? Okay.
- Yes. You go first.
- I'm ready.
Cham, cham, cham
(Haha defended successfully.)
Hey.
Cham, cham, cham
(Ji Hyo hit Haha
when he defended successfully.)
- You should've hit Soo Ah.
- I won.
- That wasn't all.
This is how Soo Ah moved her hand.
She moved it like this.
Cham, cham, cham
- I thought she pointed upward.
- What was that?
- Soo Ah, did you cast a spell?
- Does she have four attacks left?
I almost turned my head upward.
- Don't cast a spell on him.
- Okay.
- I'll swing it like this. Got it.
- You have four attacks left.
Se Chan was supposed to
hit her, right?
- That's correct.
- Cham, cham, cham
(Haha defended successfully again.)
Cham, cham, cham
- Okay.
- Hey. Gosh.
Cham
(Upset)
- I won, you little...
- I hit her.
- Then why did I get hit?
- I don't know. I hit her.
- Ji Hyo, you were supposed to...
- I hit Soo Ah as I should.
- I hit her. I did nothing wrong.
- I thought we won.
- Didn't we win? I was mistaken.
- Ji Hyo, why did you hit him?
- I was mistaken.
- Ji Hyo.
- Why did I get hit?
- It's 1 to 0.
- Okay.
I'm ready.
- Cham, cham, cham
- Okay.
(Spaced out)
- Right. I was supposed to block it.
- What is wrong with you?
- I didn't know I was good at this.
- Yes, I should've blocked it.
- I'm good at this game.
- You did well.
- Soo Ah.
- Ji Hyo,
- you should block his attack.
- You're doing it wrong.
You say it too slowly.
Cham, cham, cham
- Cham, cham, cham
- Oh, I didn't realize that.
He could defend
because you said it so slowly.
- I see.
- Cham, cham, cham
Anyone can defend
if you say it so slowly.
- I didn't realize that.
- Why would you tell her that?
- Let's continue.
- You shouldn't...
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Let's continue.
- I want to sit here.
- I almost sat on your lap.
- Why didn't you sit on his lap?
- This is...
- This is my seat.
- Sit on his lap. It's okay.
- But...
- I think it's nice.
- I know. I wish I hadn't seen him.
- You two looked so sweet.
You should say it quickly.
Ready. Go.
Cham, cham, cham
- That's good.
- That must hurt.
Ready. Go.
(Soo Ah lost again.)
- Okay.
- Good.
- Ji Hyo, you should've moved fast.
- I think...
- You should do your best.
- I think I'm not bad at this game.
- It's Haha's turn to attack.
- Got it.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
(It's Haha's turn to attack.)
Cham, cham, cham
(Soo Ah defended successfully.)
No, that's not what you should do.
Cham, cham, cham
(Soo Ah won, but Se Chan hit her.)
- Did I do something wrong?
- Hey.
Ji Hyo only blocks,
and Se Chan only hits Soo Ah.
Ji Hyo, you were supposed to
hit Haha.
- Aren't they just simple?
- I got hit here.
Aren't they all idiots?
I could see him hitting me.
This is like an idiot's game.
Cham, cham, cham
(What?)
(Ji Hyo picked up the foam sword.)
- She blocked it with the sword.
- He hit me again.
- Instead of the lid.
- She can't use the sword.
- Ji Hyo, you blocked it well.
- You were amazing.
- That was hilarious.
- Soo Ah.
You shouldn't turn your head
in the same direction.
- Why do I keep following his hand?
- She got hit again.
- Just look at my hand.
- Turn your head to the other side.
- To the other side.
- Turn it in the opposite direction.
- Cham, cham, cham
- Good.
- She couldn't help it.
- Exactly.
- She just followed his hand.
- She's too naive.
Cham, cham, cham
(Ji Hyo hit Haha.)
(The zoned-out sisters
finally pulled it off.)
- I did right, didn't I?
- Why was I hit with the blue one?
- Yes, you did.
- No, you weren't hit with this.
I think I saw this blue sword
when I got hit.
You were mistaken.
The game is over.
The score is 5 to 1.
- Haha and Se Chan won.
- Okay.
(Haha and Se Chan won
with a score of 5 to 1.)
- Okay.
- We're up next.
Next, Jong Kook and Eunhyuk
versus Suk Jin and Seul Ki.
This game requires...
Are you good at this game, Eunhyuk?
- I'll play the game.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Do you want to play the game?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Wait. Gosh, I have to hit a girl.
Oh, no. I'm scared.
I'm sure it'll hurt so much.
- It's okay, Seul Ki. This is...
- Really?
My gosh.
- This is...
- Really?
(Startled)
You said it was okay.
Look at his hair. His hair got flat.
- Why were you so surprised?
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- His hair got flat.
- You said it was okay.
- Yes, I did.
Suk Jin was startled.
- I meant it, but it swept my face.
- Was it okay?
- I could see his hair flapping.
- He still looks scared.
- Suk Jin, be confident.
- Hey. Then should I play the game?
- Yes?
- It's okay. I don't mind being hit.
- Good. Absolutely.
- I don't want to hit her.
- All right. Jong Kook...
- You made the right decision.
- But getting hit by Jong Kook...
would be a good memory.
- Stop it. Come and sit here.
- Okay.
- Would you choose a good memory...
- A good memory, my foot.
or safety?
- I'd be in a difficult position.
- Let's play two rounds for now.
- Okay.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
(They switched their seats
in the end.)
- Rock-paper-scissors
- The pot lid if he loses.
Rock-paper-scissors
Good. Do you want to attack first
or not?
- Will you attack first?
- I'll attack first.
- All right. Go on.
- Okay.
You can do it.
- I've already made up my mind.
- Cham, cham, cham
(Oh, gosh.)
- Great.
- My goodness.
- Oh, gosh.
- Seul Ki, lift it up more quickly.
- Cham, cham, cham
Cham, cham, cham
You're so fast. Can you slow down?
- Hey!
- It's over.
(They attacked 5 times consecutively
at high speed.)
We won.
- Hey, that was too fast.
- Great job.
- That was too fast.
- That was neat.
- Great. You should do it fast.
- Good job, Eunhyuk.
- Speed up. Move fast.
- He was amazing.
- You punk, I told you to slow down.
- I knew he'd do well.
- Wait. Did he attack five times?
- You did great.
You blocked 1 attack,
so they got 4 points.
- Seul Ki blocked it well.
- I blocked it.
It was so funny
because she was holding the lid.
- It's Suk Jin's turn to attack.
- All right.
(It's time for Suk Jin
to have his revenge.)
- I should prepare to block...
- Cham, cham, cham
Oh, gosh. Jong Kook.
- I should prepare to block...
- Cham, cham, cham
(Jong Kook hit the top of his head.)
- My gosh.
- Are you all right?
- That was quick.
- I was...
- I swung it downward.
- I'll make sure to block it.
He was so fast.
(Chuckling)
Who said it didn't hurt?
- Hey, listen.
- I'll do it well next time.
- I'll focus on blocking attacks.
- Listen.
- Seul Ki, watch your foot. Oh, man.
- Yes?
"Watch your foot?"
(He said,
"Seul Ki, watch your foot.")
- Watch her foot?
- He meant, "Watch carefully."
- I'm watching my foot right now.
- He said, "Watch your foot."
- He told her to watch her foot.
- Watch carefully. I mean...
- "Watch your foot."
- Why must we look at our feet?
- Let's do as he said.
- Watch your foot and speed up.
- "Watch your foot."
- He can move ridiculously fast.
- Right. He's so fast.
- So...
- Don't look at him. Look at me.
- Got it.
Lift this up as soon as you know
I lost.
- Understood. I'll do that.
- All right?
He's not on the human level.
- I know. I understand.
- Okay?
Also, I don't think you'll ever
have to use the sword.
I have a feeling that you won't ever
use the sword.
Focus on the shield.
- He's not on the human level.
- Okay. Got it.
- Let's go. You're so good at this.
- Let's begin.
- Okay. Let's begin.
- We can't grab any of them now.
- "Watch your foot."
- It's your turn to attack.
- That's right.
Oh, really?
- Get it together.
- My gosh.
- We've got this.
- Get it together, Suk Jin.
- Get it together.
- What's wrong with you?
Cham, cham, cham
(His attack was successful.)
- What? Oh, boy.
- You were supposed to hit him.
(Seul Ki can't seem to
think clearly either.)
- Why did you deliver it to him?
- I got startled.
- Hey, it was a rare chance.
- Hold on.
I'm so upset.
I wanted to see him getting hit.
It would've motivated me.
Seul Ki, come on.
You told me to focus on the lid.
It was unexpected.
I have a feeling
that you'll use the sword this time.
- Okay. Got it.
- Okay? I have a gut feeling.
Cham, cham, cham
Oh, gosh. What's going on?
(What a lousy teamwork.)
- He keeps getting hit. Poor him.
- That was hilarious.
My, that was funny.
- Gosh. Suk Jin, be a man.
- How many times did you attack?
- Suk Jin seems happy.
- Right. He's happy.
Hyun Woo, watch your foot.
- "Watch your foot."
- Hey...
Your father seems happy.
(Suk Jin likes this game
although he got hit many times.)
"Watch your foot."
- "Watch your foot."
- "Watch your foot, Suk Jin."
We might not get any garlic
this time at this rate.
- Exactly.
- I can guess his move easily.
- Can you? Are you sure?
- Yes, I can.
- I'll swing it to my left.
- Okay.
- "Watch your foot."
- Cham, cham, cham
- I'm sorry.
- You did great.
- Good job. Okay.
- Impressive.
All right. The final score is...
seven to two.
Jong Kook and Eunhyuk won.
- That was disappointing.
- Okay.
- It's okay. We won many before.
- We did well. Right.
- So Min, it's our turn.
- Oh, that's right.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
- We've got this.
- Okay.
- Let's begin.
- They're good at this game.
You see, I'm really good at
this game too.
- Can you beat them easily?
- Jae Suk.
Watch Eunhyuk's hand and your foot.
- Okay.
- "Watch your foot."
Rock-paper-scissors, again,
one more time
- Okay.
- I knew it.
- The king of games.
- Will you go first?
- Sorry?
- Do you want to attack first?
- I'll let your team attack first.
- Okay.
- He got intimidated.
- We go first? Okay.
- He already got intimidated.
- My gosh.
- He should've attacked first.
- Okay.
- I'm nervous. What do I do?
- If he fails, I can attack him.
- Okay.
- Cham, cham, cham
- Oh, I grabbed the wrong one.
- Hey. Gosh.
Cham, cham, cham
Wait. Hold on.
You guys are really fast.
- I mean...
- Why do you keep losing?
- Slow down, will you?
- You have to do better than that.
- Move your head to the other side.
- Cham, cham, cham
- Oh, okay. You won.
- Come on. Just hold on a second.
- You should've stopped it, So Min.
- We're done.
- You still have 2 attacks left.
- Do we have 2 attacks left?
- Really?
- So Min, you should stop it.
- It didn't count... Oh, I see.
- They attacked successfully.
He's looking at Eunhyuk's hand.
He's too kind for this.
That's not true.
I've made up my mind.
That won't work. I bet you will...
- fail again.
- Cham, cham, cham
Cham, cham, cham
(His glasses were hit.)
- Oh, no.
- His glasses came off.
(Jae Suk stood up
as he felt humiliated.)
- Why? She grabbed it again.
- That was funny.
- Hey.
- She should've picked this up.
- My glasses came off!
- Right. I should've picked that up.
It's good that we created
a funny situation though.
- That was an ideal sight.
- You should've left it as it was.
So Min, do your job.
So Min, you should
attack Eunhyuk too.
- Come on, So Min. Do your job.
- He's upset.
Cham, cham, cham
(Jong Kook hit his glasses again.)
That was just perfect.
- He got hit all five times.
- Oh, dear.
- I feel bad for him.
- I know.
- Jae Suk, it's...
- Why can't you defend?
It's your turn to attack, Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- It's our turn to attack.
All right. So Min, do you want to
play the game?
- Shall I?
- Yes, give it a try.
(They're switching their positions
before attacking.)
- She'll play the game?
- So Min...
- So Min could do better.
- She's good at games like this.
- This isn't good.
- I think she'll do better than me.
- It's unpredictable now.
- She's quite tactful.
- But she could get hit too.
- True.
Cham, cham, cham
Jong Kook blocked the attack.
(Hitting)
(Hold on a second.)
Hey, calm down and sit down.
I got flustered.
I didn't mean to hit you.
- He got flustered, Jong Kook.
- I got flustered.
- I just got flustered.
- He got flustered.
- I didn't mean to hit you.
- Jong Kook.
- He just got flustered.
- Trust me. It wasn't intentional.
- Could that explain what he did?
- Of course. He was flustered.
- I was flustered.
- Look. He's intimidated.
- Could that happen?
- Yes, when you get flustered.
- It wasn't intentional.
- What was that?
- You know he always gets nervous.
- Exactly.
- It happens when he's flustered.
- He was taken aback.
- I was just flustered.
- Because it was his first time.
- Okay. I understand.
- Try not to get flustered.
- Okay.
- It wasn't intentional.
- It's okay if you get flustered.
- I was flustered.
- Cham, cham, cham
(Jong Kook hit him
while biting his teeth.)
- Why did you do that?
- I'm sorry.
- I got flustered.
- Why did you hit me?
- Besides, we won.
- Okay.
- So I got flustered.
- I'm sorry, Eunhyuk.
- Right. You won.
- We won.
Cham, cham, cham
(Jae Suk hits him nonstop.)
- What was that?
- Did you get flustered again?
- I'm sorry.
- Were you flustered?
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- He's angry.
You should've stopped
after hitting me once.
- I'm sorry.
- You hit me so many times.
- I apologize.
- You got flustered too many times.
I'm sorry.
You should've learned
from your mistake...
- and made sure not to do it again.
- I'm sorry.
- I mean...
- I won't do that again.
- You should stay alert.
- He has a problem.
- I'm really sorry.
- Seriously.
- I must've lost my mind.
- Stay focused.
- Jae Suk is...
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh. Jae Suk is the real bully.
- You wouldn't stop hitting me.
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh, seriously.
- It's like a battlefield.
- No more getting flustered.
- Understood. I'm sorry.
- Do they have one attack left?
Okay.
(After Jae Suk got a warning
the game resumed.)
- That's good.
- Right. Keep going.
- Here you go again.
- Pardon?
- Oh, my.
- Is that a love bullet or what?
She might shoot him.
Cham, cham, cham
- Great. She pulled it off.
- Good.
(Her cheesy strategy worked.)
- Good job, So Min.
- That was a good move.
- She's fast, right? Let's win this.
- Yes.
- That's great.
- She put her foot on the table.
- So Min, you're doing great.
- Why did you put it on here?
- Her foot...
- I'm ready.
Cham, cham, cham
(Jong Kook hit her face
unintentionally.)
(Taken aback)
Are you okay?
- I'm fine, Jong Kook.
- Hit him back.
(Slapping)
So Min, that was great.
- What's with that reaction?
- I really liked it.
- I couldn't hit him hard though.
- She slapped me in the face.
I couldn't hit him hard.
- You got slapped after a long time.
- Exactly.
(She knocked him out
with a single slap.)
- No one has slapped him... Right.
- I didn't see that coming.
Cham, cham, cham
Okay. That was good.
- Are they tied?
- Okay.
- I'm sure we won.
- I think we won.
- No.
- We won.
- We were neck and neck.
- I think we won.
We did better than them.
The score is 5 to 4.
Jong Kook and Eunhyuk won.
- Okay. We won.
- We won.
- I'm sorry, So Min.
- Don't be.
- We won by a narrow margin.
- You did well. That was fun.
- Let's begin the final match.
- They're good at this game.
In the final match,
you will dump water on the opponent.
- Dump water?
- My goodness.
Make sure to fill your glasses.
(Jong Kook and Eunhyuk won
2 matches in a row.)
- Haha, make sure to block it.
- I'm not sure if I can do well.
Let's go.
(The eyes of a viper)
(Scared)
Gosh.
Cham, cham, cham
(Jong Kook dumped water on him.)
- My gosh. He moved so quickly.
- Good job.
- That was impressive.
- You didn't even try to block it.
- He moved too quickly.
- I'm impressed.
- That was amazing.
- He was so fast.
- He dumped water right on his face.
- You should at least try.
I can block it next time.
- Block it no matter what.
- Se Chan.
- Cham, cham, cham
- Block it.
Oh, gosh.
- Cham, cham, cham
- Block it.
(Jong Kook dumped water
on him again.)
He's too fast.
- You didn't even try.
- I'm not lying.
I could see it too.
Block it as I told you.
- Okay. I'll do that.
- Block it, okay?
- All right.
- You can block it.
- Block it when I fail to defend.
- Okay. I'll do it this time.
- Just block it.
- But he's so fast.
- Cham, cham, cham
- Good.
- You should dump water on him.
- Like this?
(Splash)
- Gosh.
- You should've attacked Eunhyuk.
You should've dumped water
on Eunhyuk.
- Okay. I understand.
- It's confusing.
- Okay.
- I was just confused.
- It's okay. Let's switch our seats.
- Believe me.
- It wasn't intentional.
- Let's switch our positions.
- Let's just switch our positions.
- I didn't do it on purpose.
- Let's switch our seats.
- Okay.
- Okay. I'll sit here.
- Do I use this to block?
- Correct.
- And I use this cup, right?
- I got confused. I'm not lying.
They switched their seats.
He's in trouble.
- Goodness, you.
- That team is so good at this game.
- They're amazing.
- Goodness.
- But...
- It's our turn to attack, Haha.
- You don't have to be nervous.
- You're right.
- It's up to us.
- That's right.
Don't be scared.
- Okay.
- He did really well before.
This is the final match. Let's go.
(The final match will decide
the winning team.)
Cham, cham, cham
(The unexpected team kill)
I'm sorry, Haha.
I should've blocked it. Oh, gosh.
- No, but the wrong target.
- Okay.
- Did you get confused?
- Yes, I was confused.
- He got confused.
- Were you taken aback?
- Yes, I was taken aback.
- He was taken aback.
He was just taken aback.
Hey, focus on the game!
- You can do this.
- Focus!
- Let's begin.
- Listen. "Watch your foot."
Got it. I understand the rules now.
- Se Chan, stay focused.
- I know what to do now.
I can't help but follow his hand.
Cham, cham, cham
(Haha's attack was successful.)
- Oh, no. I was...
- He failed to defend.
- Cham, cham, cham
(Se Chan dumped water
on Haha anyway.)
- That was a mistake.
- Haha won.
- Did you get confused?
- Yes, I did.
- Why is it so confusing?
- I got confused.
- It's confusing.
- I made it confusing.
- It's confusing. Yes.
- It really is confusing.
- Really?
- It was a mistake.
- I got confused.
- It's confusing.
- Okay.
- You came up with a fun game.
- It's confusing.
- It's really confusing.
- Did we lose a point? We can do it.
- I was...
- My movement must've confused him.
- Right.
- It's so confusing.
- It was my fault.
- Do you understand the rules now?
- Yes, I do.
Suk Jin seems to be so jealous.
He wishes he were in that situation.
(Seok Sam wants to be in every
situation where he can be funny.)
- I'll block it this time.
- Why would you put it there?
It's easier for me
to pick up the cup.
I'll show you. See? It takes me
more time to pick it up here.
- Right.
- I can dump water right away.
You're going to
block it this time, right?
Se Chan, stay alert.
I've got this.
Why am I getting nervous?
Haha, move your hand.
- Okay. Good.
- I'll just look down at this.
- Okay.
- Ready.
(Sighing and chuckling)
Eunhyuk hasn't been attacked
until now.
(Haha's last attack)
The winner has already been decided.
Let's go.
Cham, cham, cham
I blocked it.
Cham
(He said, "I blocked it.")
- Oh, no. Darn it.
- Hey.
- What was that?
- It was too late.
- You moved too slowly.
- I should've blocked it and...
- Hey, what was that?
- You moved too slowly.
- I moved too slowly.
- Yes.
- Oh, no.
- Se Chan, get it together.
- Believe me, Haha.
- They're really good at it.
- We couldn't beat them.
They were unbeatable.
Jong Kook and Eunhyuk...
- came in first.
- Okay.
Each of you will receive
ten garlic cloves,
and get a chance
to change the team members.
Haha and Se Chan came in second.
- Each will get eight garlic cloves.
- Okay.
Jae Suk and So Min who came in 3rd
will get 6 each.
- Six? Okay.
- Six?
Suk Jin and Seul Ki came in fourth.
- Are we in the last place?
- You'll get four each.
Soo Ah and Ji Hyo came in last.
- You'll get two each.
- All right.
The poachers already got
half of their partners' garlic.
The winning team will get a chance
to find out each other's identity.
- Okay.
- I see.
(Jong Kook already knows
Eunhyuk's identity.)
Okay.
(Jong Kook already knows
Eunhyuk's identity.)
I trust you, Jong Kook.
- Of course.
- Yes.
- I'll reveal your identities.
- Okay.
- As you know, he's a poacher.
- Yes, I know that.
And Jong Kook is...
- an animal.
- I see.
(Jong Kook is not a poacher.)
Exactly.
- Currently, Jong Kook has...
- You were an animal.
Jong Kook, you had
four cloves before.
- You won 5, so you have 9 now.
- Right.
- As for Eunhyuk...
- Then I must have a lot of garlic.
You had 12 cloves before.
- You just got 15 more cloves.
- I have so many.
Now you have 27 cloves.
Why does he have so many?
- Is it because he's a poacher?
- I took half of yours.
- What?
- I took four cloves from you.
So I had a total of 12 cloves.
Hey.
- Jong Kook, didn't you know...
- Why would he take...
- Don't we share the garlic evenly?
- No.
- He takes half of mine?
- Yes.
- Gosh, you little...
- You knew about that rule.
You should've explained it to me.
I thought you understood the rules.
So that's why
we should switch partners.
Anyway, you know
how many cloves you have.
Are you going to swap partners?
If you think about it,
as long as we find
who the bear poacher is...
(As long as we find
who the bear poacher is...)
It'll benefit both of us.
You...
This can benefit us both.
- Together...
- In that case,
you can't afford to get caught.
It should only be me
who is suspicious of you.
- I...
- Only I need to win.
- Do your best in the games though.
- Of course.
(They agree to stay together
so that they can score big.)
All right.
You'll keep losing cloves
to Eunhyuk then.
(They agree to stay together
so that they can score big.)
- Study their expressions.
- Can we go?
- I'm not a poacher.
- Go ahead, then.
They don't seem too happy.
- One out of the two, right?
- It's Eunhyuk.
- They seem frustrated.
- Did you switch partners?
We will...
- Do you both know now?
- We...
- We didn't switch partners.
- They already knew.
Yes, of course.
We should've made sure
that they won instead.
I thought that's what
you were going for.
Haha said...
that he should check
what Se Chan is.
- Did Haha say that?
- Yes, he did.
It seemed to me...
like Haha wasn't interested
in winning.
How is it done?
Only one of you will learn...
the identity of your partner
and how many cloves you have.
Please play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Okay.
- Only Se Chan...
will receive the information.
- Don't you want me to see it?
- It's fine.
Got it.
I'm really not a poacher.
(Haha has been suspected
since early this morning.)
(What role is Haha playing?)
They're taking quite a long time.
It's true. They must have
a lot to talk about.
Judging by
how long they're taking...
They probably have
a lot to think about.
They wouldn't take this long
if they were both animals.
- You know from experience.
- Right.
If they were both animals,
they'd come straight back out.
Here comes the sheriff.
- What?
- What's with that tone?
Everything is clear to me now.
That's an odd thing to say.
- They could be in cahoots.
- How can everything be clear?
- Right.
- This team decided...
(The team in 2nd place decided...)
They decided to switch partners.
- What?
- Really?
- Why?
- Why are you switching partners?
- To find the poacher.
One must be a poacher then.
- Between the two of them...
- One of them is a poacher.
- I'm sure of it.
- Check Jong Kook out.
- How can that be?
- Exactly.
It's not like that.
- I'm sure of it.
- There's no need...
to find the poacher.
- We have to.
- It has to be done.
After each game,
- one's identity is revealed.
- If I win the game...
- or win second place...
- We learn one's identity.
It's why we should split up
and discover your identities.
One of them is a poacher.
One of them has to be a poacher.
- You're right.
- We need to figure out who it is.
That being said,
these are the teams they chose.
- We should stay clear of them.
- Se Chan...
chose Jae Suk.
(Tiger Se Chan
chooses Bear Jae Suk.)
You're coming after my garlic!
What?
- No, I'm not.
- You...
- He's trying to take what's mine.
- Of course not.
- I'm not a poacher.
- That's a good choice.
- And Haha...
Haha chose Soo Ah as his partner.
(Soo Ah over Se Chan)
He's trying to...
brush away any suspicion.
Our goal...
is to identify you all
through the games we play.
- That's odd.
- Are you switching partners?
If you think about it...
- Right.
- Of course.
- Do well in games, okay?
- With her,
he won't be able
to win a lot of games.
It's why he chose Soo Ah instead.
You're right.
Being in 1st or 2nd place...
It'll be hard for his team
to win the games.
I'm not a poacher.
Se Chan knows for sure.
- He's not a poacher.
- I'm not.
I learned about his identity.
- He knows.
- He's not a poacher.
(What role could Haha be playing?)
They make a good couple.
- Hey!
- That looks good.
Nice!
- Gosh.
- No way.
- We have pizza.
- We're having pizza.
One pizza per person, right?
Gosh, that looks good.
- Is that coke?
- Yes.
- That one's mine.
- All right.
- It's lunchtime.
- Right.
But it's also time
for product placement.
In order to provide
a seamless advertisement,
we will be offering you
additional garlic cloves.
- In what way?
- Additional garlic?
- Only the tigers will participate.
- The tigers?
- The tigers.
The tigers...
will call someone you know...
and eat a slice of pizza
within 100 seconds.
You should not be asked
if you're eating anything.
(They should not be asked
if they're eating anything.)
The game will be over
once you hear it.
Those who manage
to stay undetected...
will be rewarded
with cloves of garlic...
depending on how well they did.
- Do you understand the rules?
- Who should I call?
You can call anyone.
But only the tigers
are playing this game.
- Just the tigers?
- So Min's not a big eater.
Maybe Sang Yeob.
I'm going to call Sae Ho.
Please keep it down
while Se Chan makes his call.
Is this my pizza slice?
He's going to call Cho Sae Ho.
Sae Ho, got it.
The countdown will begin
as soon as he picks up.
Hey, Se Chan.
Sae Ho, where are you?
I was out exercising...
and now I'm on my way home.
Are you heading home?
- Yes.
- Sae Ho!
- Hey, So Min.
- Gosh.
Sae Ho, I hurt myself.
Yes, I heard about your toe.
So Min injured herself.
Tell me about it. I feel terrible.
She...
tripped.
I know. Why did it happen though?
Was there no one there
for her to grab?
- Where are you right now?
- What?
(Where are you right now?)
Where are you right now?
I'm in Gangnam.
Did you say Gangneung?
No, not Gangneung.
Wait.
- Did you say Gangneung?
- Seriously.
I'm in Gangnam.
Gangnam?
Yes. Gangneung is miles away.
Who are you with?
- I'm with Kyung Ho.
- Kyung Ho?
(Se Chan just stuffs his face.)
Who's Kyung Ho?
Kyung Ho used to be
a fellow comedian.
So that's who you're with.
Have you eaten, Sae Ho?
I'm thinking about
grabbing a salad or something.
A salad?
(How can Sae Ho not be curious?)
You know what I mean. Vegetables.
Oh, vegetables.
What on earth?
- This is crazy.
- He's not even being careful.
- See?
- Okay!
My gosh.
Hold on.
You can't eat that last bite.
- Sae Ho.
- How can he not know?
- Thanks, Sae Ho.
- How can he not tell?
- Jae Suk, is that you?
- Yes, it's me.
Are you guys filming something?
He probably knew.
- Unbelievable.
- I'm sure he knew.
- He knew, didn't he?
- You didn't know,
but yet you gave us a laugh.
- Did I?
- Yes.
Wasn't it difficult
to understand Se Chan?
It was terrible!
Didn't you know
that he was eating something?
I thought he had...
a question to ask
while eating lunch.
It did seem like
he wasn't listening though.
- I see.
- That's right.
Anyway,
former-Mr. Cabbage-now-Mr. Cho Sae Ho,
thank you.
- Could I say hello to the viewers?
- I'm sorry?
- He wants to say hello.
- Would that be all right?
- Since this will air on TV...
- To the Running Man viewers.
- Oh, right.
- Wouldn't that be better?
I'm afraid...
the other guests
have to make phone calls too.
But it'll only take
about five seconds.
(Running Man won't even
let him have 5 seconds.)
Then,
please make sure
you only take five seconds.
Sure. It's a pleasure to greet you.
Thank you, everyone.
Happy New Year.
I hope to see you soon
on Running Man...
(He hangs up.)
I hope to see you soon
on Running Man...
(Jae Suk hangs up
after 5 exact seconds.)
Well...
- He made a promise.
- It was agreed upon.
Of course.
- Right.
- I counted it down.
- Nicely done.
- Next up is Soo Ah.
- Soo Ah's next.
I don't have any celebrity friends.
- It can be anyone.
- It can be any friend.
- It can be a family member.
- What if no one picks up.
- This friend is an American.
- Nice.
We play tennis together, you see.
- Sounds good.
- They're entering...
a tournament next week.
- Really?
- What if she doesn't pick up?
- A tournament?
- Soo Ah's athletic.
(Will she be able
to stay undetected for 100 seconds?)
What if she doesn't pick up?
Isn't this Lee Hyun Woo's song?
This song...
She answered!
- Hello?
- Hi, Manda.
- Hey.
- What's up?
I'm at work.
Are you on set right now?
Yes, I'm on the set of Running Man.
(Soo Ah frantically
stuffs her face.)
Could this be a scam?
I'm filming...
I'm...
I'm filming something right now.
Are you eating something?
(Are you eating something?)
(She gets caught
only after 19 seconds!)
- Nice!
- Okay.
- Nice timing.
- All right!
Nice!
(Soo Ah's perceptive friend
might have her finish last.)
Nice!
It's over for you.
- How did you know?
- You can hang up now.
- So Min, who will you call?
- What if he doesn't answer?
- I'm calling Sang Yeob.
- He'll probably answer.
He texted me yesterday,
but I didn't reply.
- Why didn't you?
- Soo Ah's friend was hilarious.
It ended as soon
as the call went through.
- It ended the second I started...
- Yes?
- You need to wait.
- Sang Yeob.
Jeonsobari.
- I...
- Yes?
got injured.
Why?
I tripped on the stairs and fell.
But...
(But...)
This must be a prank.
(He thinks it's a prank call.)
I...
- Yes?
- My foot is in a cast.
(Laughing)
(He bursts out laughing.)
Why is he finding this funny?
(He seems to be aware
of what's happening.)
So Min!
- It hurts.
- So Min.
Are you hurt?
- Yes.
- He's using his acting voice.
Where are you right now?
- Did you hear that?
- He's putting on a show.
He thinks we're playing a game.
- Right.
- He's trying to guess the phrase.
I'll come to you this instant.
He thinks she's trying
to get a phrase out of him.
- He's trying to guess the answer.
- That's right.
- It's what So Min wants to hear.
- "I'll come to you this instant."
So Min, where are you?
I'm...
So Min.
- I...
- Did you hurt your teeth too?
Her teeth too?
(Sang Yeob's passion
is pointed in the wrong direction.)
So Min!
(So Min!)
He knows how to give people a laugh.
(Sang Yeob cries out
as 100 seconds pass.)
- Sang Yeob.
- He thought this was a game.
Sang Yeob thought
that this was a game.
- Right.
- That's what he thought.
Mr. Substitute!
I see that it's Monday.
You should know that
you made a mess of things.
I'll be right over, Jae Suk.
Him and his ambition.
Well, it's not...
- That's not...
- Jae Suk,
I haven't greeted the viewers
of Running Man in a while.
- It's been so long.
- Just hang up already!
- Come to Dosan Intersection.
- That's enough.
(Throwing the bait)
- That's enough!
- We're at Dosan Intersection!
- It's a mission!
- That's enough!
- Come to Dosan Intersection!
- Stay still.
Come now!
You must come to Dosan Intersection!
- No!
- Dosan Intersection!
- Sang Yeob.
- Sang Yeob, go work out now.
- He might actually go.
- He could be there for real.
- I think he'll really go.
Don't go to Dosan Park!
Come to Dosan Intersection!
- Don't trust him! No!
- Don't go to Dosan Park!
- We're at Dosan Intersection!
- Save us!
- Don't trust him!
This is not a mission.
Do not go to Dosan Park!
- Go work out!
- Did he actually leave home?
(Confused)
- All right. I'll call you later.
- He's going to contemplate.
- All right!
- He's contemplating.
- He might actually go.
- I think he already left.
- He's immersed in the game now.
- It looks like that.
- Hurry up and text him.
I'm going to call Shim Chang Min
of TVXQ.
- Eunhyuk?
- Chang Min.
Can you sing for me a little longer?
(Countless times)
He's so slow-witted.
How does "Fever" go again?
(Vocalizing)
(Singing passionately
for the second time)
(He enjoys the pizza
while listening to Chang Min sing.)
- What did you say?
- All right.
- Amazing.
- He ate quite a lot.
You can put it down. We did it.
- Seul Ki will call her husband.
- All right.
Is it lunchtime?
No, it's not lunchtime.
We're just taking a break.
What were you up to?
Tell me what you did today.
I called to ask you that.
I didn't do anything much.
(He's the type
who gives only short answers.)
- She's done.
- What?
What?
It's the end of the conversation.
(She's facing a crisis.)
- Ask him if he loves you.
- Do you love me?
(She held out for 100 seconds
but couldn't eat much of her pizza.)
- She couldn't eat much.
- Oh, gosh.
- Hey!
- Bye.
Let's weigh the leftover pizza...
- and add the seconds.
- We won.
Sae Ho helped out a lot.
All right. Please place your pizza.
That's right. You ate a lot.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan,
Ji Hyo and So Min...)
- You should've finished it.
- Mine is too big.
We got it.
All right. Here's the result.
You're not going to measure ours?
(They nonchalantly skip Team Haha
who is obviously in last place.)
All right. First place...
goes to Jae Suk and Se Chan.
- Well done!
- Thank you, Sae Ho.
- You guys won?
- Thanks, Sae Ho!
No, we're in second place.
Next. Second place...
goes to Jong Kook and Eunhyuk.
They keep winning.
(Jong Kook and Eunhyuk
get 8 garlic cloves.)
They shouldn't keep winning.
- You're in second place?
- We should stop them.
- Next...
- It's an individual match though.
Third place goes to
Ji Hyo and So Min.
Suk Jin and Seul Ki
are in fourth place.
For real?
- What? Us?
- You're in fourth place.
That's it. Now, you can have
the pizza.
(The bears finally
get to taste the pizza.)
It's really good.
All right.
- It's good.
- It looks so good.
- Take it.
- It's really good.
Thank you.
- Isn't it really nice?
- The toppings are really nice.
They added a lot of toppings.
I can definitely finish
a bowl of rice with this bulgogi.
I miss my kids. They'd love this.
You always say that
when you're done with your meal.
Can't you pay my performance fee
with pizza?
- We can.
- You can?
- It's a PPL. He's working hard.
- I thought you wouldn't be able to.
I guess they can.
Sang Yeob actually said he'd call me
when he gets to Dosan Intersection.
(The bears and tigers'
lunchtime ends.)
Let's check it.
(Third time to check
their identities)
You're not a looter, are you?
A looter? It's supposed to be a poacher.
How did it become a looter?
You're a looter
since you steal goods from me.
No. You must be feeling guilty.
- Why would you call me looter?
- No, I'm not it.
- Right?
- Of course not.
- If you're it...
- Come on.
(Is Jae Suk, who tends to get
talkative when he's given a role,)
(a poacher?)
- It's you. Darn it.
- I'm really not it.
The two of you can open
your garlic can and check.
- I should open mine?
- Check the number of garlic cloves.
- I collected a lot so far.
- You did. I collected a lot too.
You collected a lot.
You have so many.
I'll tell you your identities.
- Se Chan is a tiger.
- I'm a tiger.
(Se Chan is a tiger.)
- What about Jae Suk?
- Jae Suk is...
(Jae Suk's identity is...)
(a bear.)
a bear.
(Both were not poachers.)
- A looter?
- I see. You're not.
- I'm not a looter. We both are not.
- He's not.
- You can make your choice now.
- We should switch teams.
- Is that so?
- We need to switch teams...
- So we can find out.
- so we can see who they are.
Also, Haha is not a poacher.
- He's not?
- Haha is not a poacher.
- Then who should I team up with?
- We need to divide them up.
They seem suspicious.
- Let's divide them up.
- We'll divide them up.
- Then I'll team up with him.
- Then I'll team up with Jong Kook.
- Is that your final decision?
- Yes.
(Their plan is to enter
the tiger's den.)
- Why did you think I was?
- So you're not a looter.
No, I'm not.
We'll give information
to only one of you.
- But I already know who he is.
- But we already know.
So you are...
(They know each other's
identity as it's their third visit.)
Then it's useless
to switch teams now...
because there's no one else...
- who can help me win.
- That's true.
- Then I'll stick with him for now.
- All right.
- We have no other choice.
- You're right.
Darn it. We have no other choice
than to wait.
Eunhyuk, what took you so long?
Gosh. What happened?
- What took you guys so long?
- They're fishy.
He said they were fishy.
We got you. You're done for.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
The first top three teams...
- are done checking identities.
- Are we switching teams?
The team in first place
decided to switch teams.
(The team in 1st place
decided to switch teams.)
The team first-place team
switched to...
- is Eunhyuk and Jong Kook.
- Eunhyuk.
- Eunhyuk and Jong Kook,
- Come here.
- the first-place team chose you.
- We switched teams.
- We are going to separate you two.
- With whom?
- Sorry?
- Jae Suk and me?
- Also... It's Jong Kook and me.
- It's Eunhyuk and me.
Then your identity will be revealed.
What are you talking about?
Don't you think one of them
is a poacher?
The two teams are divided.
- Then it's not me, it's not you...
- I'm not a poacher.
- Jae Suk is not a poacher.
- Jae Suk is not?
Se Chan and I are not poachers.
- Me neither.
- You're not it either.
- I'm not a poacher either.
- Jong Kook and I are not it.
Jae Suk, don't be so sure
that Haha is not a poacher.
Why do you think he's not a poacher?
I'm not!
(Jae Suk is only trusting
Se Chan's words on Haha's identity.)
Why are you so sure that Haha is
not it just because Se Chan said it?
Why would he lie?
- The two could've plotted this.
- Se Chan is not a poacher.
- No, they could've plotted this.
- Come on. I'm not a poacher.
- Okay.
Everyone, please gather.
- Gather up.
- Yes, sir. Salute!
This mission...
is a game where you have to keep
your eye on the ball until the end...
while avoiding
the tiger's sharp eyes.
It's called
More and More Foot Volleyball.
- More and More Foot Volleyball?
It follows the rules
of foot volleyball,
but the longer the rally lasts,
the more points will you get.
Which means, every time
the ball touches someone's foot,
- one point will be added.
- That sounds good.
And the team that wins the attack
will take all the points.
(The team that succeeds
in the attack takes all the points.)
(They'll be able to win
all the accumulated points.)
The longer the rally, the better.
Each team can kick five times...
- at most.
- Five times per team?
Oh, I get it.
- More and more points accumulate?
- We should receive the ball well.
What about us?
I'll tell you.
We couldn't change the game
because it was last minute,
so So Min can take
the role of a referee.
We prepared a referee uniform for you.
- Finally!
- All right! At last.
- Your dream came true.
- Can't I be the referee?
- That's the coolest role.
- Can't I be one, Jae Suk?
- I've really wanted to be one.
- I've really wanted too.
- She gets a whistle too?
- It's the most desired role.
- I hate to be the referee.
- She gets a whistle too?
- She gets a whistle.
- She's like Thanos.
- Only So Min can be a referee.
- Why?
- This is too... Okay, fine.
- What can I do?
- I want to be a referee too.
- The referee...
can declare the opening of the game.
- My gosh.
- She gets to declare it too?
Hey!
Hey! You were born to be a referee.
She's good.
- Gosh.
- You're a superb referee.
We divided you into two teams.
- We divided you fairly.
- Did you?
- On this side, Jae Suk, Eunhyuk,
- Okay.
Haha, Soo Ah, So Min, and Ji Hyo
will be on one team.
- All right.
- This is great.
There are only four of us?
No, it's better without So Min.
- It's better without So Min.
Let's always have two men
and two women on the court.
- Two men and two women?
- I'll sit on the bench first.
There are no limits
to how many points you can earn,
so we'll tally up the scores
after exactly 15 minutes.
We should kick as much as we can...
- before passing it over.
- That's right.
- I should kick like this...
- when it comes to me? Got it.
- That's right.
- All right.
- Now,
More and More Foot Volleyball Match
will begin.
- All right. Hit it.
- Let's start.
- "Hit it?"
- Serve it first.
- Did you say hit it? Not serve?
- "Hit it?"
"Hit it?"
(At Referee Jeon's whistle...)
- My gosh. How charismatic.
- Who will receive it?
- Who will receive it? I will.
- Nice serve!
- One.
- All right. That's one. One point.
- Two.
- Two points.
- Wait. I should pass it over.
- That's it.
- Receive it. That's it. Good job.
- One point.
One more time. That's it.
- That's it. Great job.
- Pass it over.
How many points did we earn?
- It's 8 to 0.
- All right!
- I'll hit it.
- We got eight points.
- I didn't do anything though.
- It's 8 to 0. My gosh.
- Serve it.
It was close.
- All right.
- All right. I got it.
(Haha serves again.)
- We got it.
- That's one point.
- One.
- Two.
- Seul Ki, take this.
- You won't be able to pass it over.
My ball.
We got it.
- Take it easy.
- One. Oh, no.
- He got it!
- There you go. Good one!
One. Oh, no.
(Haha quickly received
the ball that almost went out.)
- He got it!
- Pass it over.
Three.
- Pass it over, Haha.
- Pass it over.
- There you go.
- That's it!
- Good one. It's okay.
- There you go.
- Go for it.
- Pass it over. There you go.
- Go.
- Good one.
Good one. Take it easy.
This is worth so many points.
- We must take this.
- It's worth so many points.
- We must take it.
- Good one.
- Two.
- Ji Hyo!
- Three.
- Pass it over!
Four.
We took it!
How many points did we win?
- We took it!
- What was that?
- I'm so sorry, Haha.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Or you could move over for him.
- They earned 14 points.
You should let him take it.
We got 14 points.
- Team Suk Jin earned 14 points.
- We're winning.
- It's okay, everyone.
- Let's just pass it over.
I'll give it to Ji Hyo.
Take it, Ji Hyo.
My ball!
(Screaming)
- All right.
- She received it.
- Good job.
- She's good.
Pass it over.
It's more important to pass the ball over.
Take it easy, Suk Jin.
- He got it.
- That's it.
- Go ahead.
- Just pass it over.
- Hit it. Pass it over.
- That's it!
(Slipping)
- Go ahead.
- Just pass it over.
- Hit it. Pass it over.
- That's it!
Yes!
(Big Nose's smashing
is especially on point today.)
- Why are you so good today?
- Why is he so good?
- Why are you so good?
- Why am I?
- Why am I good?
- Why are you so good?
- Soo Ah.
Switch with her.
- Jae Suk, join us. You must join.
- Okay.
- Soo Ah, come. I'll play.
- Me?
- You must kick it in the air.
- Why am I so good?
(Seul Ki gets ready to serve.)
It's not that.
Se Chan saved your pass.
- All right.
- I'm sorry.
(My goodness!)
- It's okay.
- That was intense.
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry!
The referee is at a dangerous spot.
Can she sit at the back?
- Sit behind the cameras.
- Is the referee okay?
- It's dangerous, that's why.
- What's wrong with you?
- It's because it's dangerous.
- So Min is doing well as a referee.
Seul Ki, take this.
- It's mine.
- Seul Ki.
- Give it to Se Chan.
- All right.
- Do you want to kick it?
- Okay. I'll hit it lightly.
Go for it, Suk Jin.
Oh, no!
(Oh, no!)
(Receiving it with her stomach)
Oh, no!
- You did it. Well done.
- Are you okay?
- Well done.
- "Oh, no!"
- "Oh, no."
- Well done.
It was like a comedy skit. "Oh, no!"
- But I like her mindset.
- What's the score?
Wait. I think Soo Ah
will be a good referee too.
I think you will be.
Do you want to give it a try?
- Let's just play first.
- My gosh.
- I didn't go after it either.
- Soo Ah is indeed athletic.
- I'll pass over whatever comes.
- Let's pass over the ball.
We need to catch up.
- I'll pass it to Eunhyuk.
- Go ahead.
- Here, Eunhyuk.
- Give it to him.
- Eunhyuk.
- Okay. Pass it.
- Leave it, Suk Jin.
- He told you to leave it!
(Hitting the bull's-eye)
(Grunting)
(Seok Sam received
a tornado shot with his forehead.)
- Suk Jin.
- Nice one.
- It wasn't expected.
- I thought he was doing well.
Good work.
- Nice.
- Good work.
It's 44 to 15.
- That's it. It's out.
- Catch it. There you go.
- Catch it.
(A perfect receive)
- You shouldn't have caught it.
- Wasn't it out?
- Nice catch.
- Hey.
- Seul Ki, give it to me.
- Nice catch.
- We lost.
- Thank you.
- You shouldn't catch it.
- It's okay. It was only one point.
- Nice catch.
- Good job, Seul Ki.
(Team Jae Suk carefully
collects even 1 point.)
Good one.
- Nice receive.
- Let's pass it over no matter what.
- One.
- Do you want to hit it?
- Should I do it or you?
- What?
That's not it.
(The worst ball control)
- That's not it.
- Hey, Eunhyuk!
Why don't you
just leave it to your team?
He's terrible at it.
- Eunhyuk is a terrible player.
- What's with Eunhyuk?
- What's wrong with Eunhyuk?
- He's horrible.
- Leave the back to me.
- Are you going to...
- Hey, Eunhyuk.
- play soccer this week or what?
It's because she suddenly ran away.
We should stay in the back.
I'm sorry about that.
- We caught him off guard.
- Here we go.
- Let's earn some points.
- Eunhyuk is...
- It's for Eunhyuk.
All right.
- Jae Suk hits to a certain spot.
- All right.
- What do I do?
- There really is.
(A tornado shot)
(But Jong Kook predicted it
and received the ball.)
- All right!
- Use your head!
- It's Ji Seok Sam!
(Delayed attack)
Suk Jin!
- He tried to make it funny.
- How could you...
- It was really hard to receive it.
- You shouldn't do that.
- He couldn't hit it.
- That's old-fashioned slapstick.
- It was really hard to receive it.
- He couldn't hit it.
- It wasn't close enough.
It was old-fashioned slapstick.
Thank you for your slapstick.
All right.
- We should keep the winning streak.
- Go ahead.
- Here we go.
- One point.
- Two points.
- It's Ji Seok Sam!
Suk Jin! You should receive it.
It worked.
(With an intensive attack on
Seok Sam, they got 3 more points.)
- That was great.
- It worked.
That attack was useful.
You should've
passed the ball nicely.
How much nicer could it get?
Suk Jin, you should've
attacked back right away.
Please don't say,
- Suk Jin, watch carefully.
- "It's Ji Seok Sam."
- Referee!
- What?
He can't yell out Ji Seok Sam
during a game.
- What's wrong with it?
- Ji Seok Sam!
Red card!
(Ji Seok Sam gets a red card.)
- It's my fault?
- Good one, So Min.
- I got a red card?
- She has the authority.
Suk Jin, watch carefully.
Let's turn the tables.
That's it! Hold on.
- Pass it over!
(Screaming)
- What's wrong with him?
Why did he come to me?
- All right!
- You guys are so good.
- We won.
- All right!
- You guys are so good.
- Good job.
- All right.
We won.
- We did it.
- All right.
(Ji Seok Sam and his friends
lost just like that.)
(The final whistle)
- No!
- I'm sorry.
Hey, that's my role!
- Sorry.
- I mean...
- Come on. She's the referee.
- That's...
I can't believe we won.
(The production crew unintentionally
breached the contract.)
You guys are so good.
- What's wrong, So Min?
- So Min, we won.
(Blowing whistle)
- I mean...
- That was my role.
(She fulfills her wish
although it's late.)
- I can't believe we won.
- Announce the winner.
- You should announce the winner.
- All right.
They win!
- "They win?"
- Now, switch sides.
- We're switching sides?
- The match is over.
We're not switching sides?
(The match is over.)
So Team Jae Suk won.
You guys are so good.
The representatives of Team Jae Suk
will play rock-paper-scissors.
- Soo Ah, you play it.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
Suk Jin and Seul Ki are 4th.
Jong Kook and Se Chan are 5th.
Rock-paper-scissors
- All right!
- You're in first place.
- We're in first place?
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- We're in first place.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Gosh, we lost.
- We're in second place.
(2nd-place team can also find out
one of their identities.)
We can now reveal
each other's identities.
- I'm glad we're in second place.
- Really?
- What?
- Now we'll know.
Soo Ah, watch carefully.
Okay. Let's go, Soo Ah.
We should've won first place.
I feel so wrongly accused.
I'm really not the poacher.
Why do they keep accusing me
of being one?
- Are you suspecting me?
- I think you are the poacher.
To be honest, you seem suspicious.
I'm not the poacher.
- I'm really not.
- I'll tell you your identities.
- I'm a bear.
- Haha is...
- Please return to the hall.
- Okay.
(Tiger Soo Ah found out
Haha's identity.)
How many more games
are we going to play?
We only have one last game.
We only have one more?
Then we should know
who the poachers are by now.
I suspected Eunhyuk,
but he doesn't seem like one too.
My only fault is playing hard.
Doesn't Eunhyuk seem fishy?
I think he didn't try hard...
- because he's the poacher.
- I'm not really good...
at foot volleyball, to be honest.
- It's not that.
- You're confessing that now?
- You didn't play intentionally, no?
- I'm better at soccer.
- If you won, you'd be revealed.
- I think you're the poacher.
- I was so out of it earlier, so...
It didn't look like Eunhyuk
played terribly on purpose.
(Right then, Jong Kook
defends Eunhyuk.)
- I think...
- What?
- He's just bad at it?
- He didn't do it on purpose.
You're striking
a deal with me again.
A deal.
- Gosh, who could it be?
- Hold on.
(Eunhyuk dodged a bullet
thanks to Jong Kook.)
Did I pick the wrong one?
Why? What happened?
Haha is the poacher, right?
- He must be.
- Haha...
- Haha is the poacher, right?
- What is it?
What's Haha's identity?
Tell us honestly.
- What?
- Haha's identity.
He's just an animal.
- Who? You?
- Who?
- Haha?
- Haha is an animal.
- He is just a bear?
He's not the poacher.
I think it's either
Ji Hyo or Suk Jin.
If no one is the poacher,
then who could it be?
I think you're the poacher.
- Me?
- Aren't you the poacher?
Because if we won this time,
his identity...
- would've been revealed.
- It would've been revealed.
- So he...
- But I...
I only played hard. That's all.
You didn't play hard.
I did. I scored so many times.
Gosh, this guy...
Suk Jin is not the poacher.
I can guarantee that.
- I'm not the poacher.
- He's not?
- I can guarantee it.
- Listen to her.
- It must be him.
- He's not the poacher?
I can guarantee
that he's not the poacher.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Then it must be Ji Hyo.
Will you decide
with rock-paper-scissors?
Yes.
- Okay.
- I'm really not the poacher.
- I'm not the poacher either.
- Rock-paper-scissors
Whose identity did you check?
Ji Hyo.
- What is Ji Hyo?
- What is she?
- No, Ji Hyo checked mine.
- I...
- Then what is So Min?
- Why...
- You must've told each other.
- Did they tell you?
- I won in rock-paper-scissors.
- You should've checked Ji Hyo's.
- So Min is not the poacher?
- I'm not.
- Well, So Min...
- She's not.
- I'd be too weak to be a poacher.
- So Min is not the poacher?
- What?
- Then what is So Min?
- She seems tied up.
- I didn't see it.
- It's her.
- You should've checked Ji Hyo's.
We decided with rock-paper-scissors.
That's not it. We gave you an order
to check Ji Hyo's identity.
(She's definitely the poacher.)
So what is she? Tell us.
- Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry. We wanted to...
You must hate me right now.
So after the game,
the 1st-place and 2nd-place teams
made their choices.
I didn't see it.
The first-place team,
Haha and Soo Ah,
decided to switch their partners.
- They did?
- They should.
They should
if they're not the poachers.
So Soo Ah picked Jong Kook.
Haha picked So Min.
- Who?
- Haha did.
That makes
Se Chan and Ji Hyo a team.
Let's change your vests
and play the last mission.
Okay.
(They'll play the last mission
after changing their vests.)
Gosh, it's been a while
since I teamed up with Ji Hyo.
Should I get hit?
Or do you want to get hit, Eunhyuk?
I should...
- Are you sure?
- get the taste of it.
You can if you want.
- The taste of the variety show.
- I don't mind.
- I'm fine with...
- You're on different teams.
- You and I are on different teams.
- Oh, right.
(Forming alliance out of habit)
- Jong Kook, you're my partner.
- Oh, right.
- He just adores Eunhyuk so much.
- Jong Kook.
Eunhyuk, Jong Kook
must adore you so much.
I accidentally almost followed him.
I thought we'd always
be on the same team.
I almost followed him.
Soo Ah, you can sit in front.
Ji Hyo, I'm sure I'm right.
These two are the poachers.
Everyone, this is the last mission.
After the mission,
the 1st-place and 2nd-place teams...
will get a chance to check
each other's identities.
Then we'll carry on
with the vote right away.
I'm not sure who the poachers are,
to be honest.
In the last mission,
you can check the patience
and knowledge you have.
It's called Heart Attack Quiz.
Heart attack.
Everyone has a chance to answer.
Only the members
under the metal trays...
will get hit with them.
The questions we give...
will have multiple answers.
If you know an answer,
yell out, "Let me answer."
The next person to answer...
must give a bigger number of answers
than the previous one.
So if the first person
got one correct answer,
the next person must give
two or more correct answers...
- to avoid the tray.
- It won't be easy.
- It will be better to go first.
- It will be incredibly hard.
A question might be,
- "What does KBO stand for?"
- Right.
Let's say someone said "Korea"...
and got the other two wrong.
Then he or she will be
in the first place.
The next person might get,
"Korea Baseball."
Then that person will survive.
It ends when someone has
the full answer,
- Okay.
- What does O stand for?
Orange.
- What does O stand for?"
- Orange.
- Is it "Orange?"
- Organization.
Why would it be "Orange?"
She said it's "Orange."
She said it so confidently.
I thought
it stood for "Orientation."
This is fun already.
- Is it an acronym?
- This is fun already.
I thought we just had to say...
- the fitting words.
- That was insane.
"Korea Baseball Orange"
sounds ridiculous.
So it's an acronym.
I thought, "Orange must have
a different meaning."
I didn't know the last one either.
Here comes the first question.
The first question is...
CNN.
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
(What does CNN stand for?)
It will be hard.
- Do you know the answer?
- Christmas.
- I think I knew the answer.
- Cinema.
Choo...
- Christian.
- Choo...
Congratulations.
Pass.
Let me answer.
- My goodness.
- Let me answer.
So Min.
Central...
Night Night.
Pass.
Let me answer.
I don't know what C stands for.
- Let me answer.
- CNN.
CNN.
- Control...
- CNN.
- Network...
- That isn't it, is it?
Where did "Network" come from?
- Natural.
- All right.
- One word is correct.
- What?
What did you say?
- Control... What?
- Did he get one word right?
He got one word right.
- What did you say?
- He is in the first place.
He didn't get C right.
- I got a word right.
- What does C stand for?
- "Control?"
- What does CNN stand for?
I will give it a try. Central...
Network News.
- Jae Suk got two words right.
- Let me answer.
For your information,
the latter part is "News Network."
- News Network.
Let me answer.
- Cyber News Network.
- It isn't "Cyber."
- Cyber.
- Let me answer.
- What?
- I figured it out.
- What is it?
Cross!
No.
- Why would it be "Cross?"
- Let me answer.
It must be the name of a place.
- So Min.
- Comedy.
- Let me answer.
Gosh, it hurts.
Coca-Cola News Network.
My goodness.
All right. Let's go.
- Coca-Cola.
- Let me answer.
Combo... Combo News Network.
- "Combo?"
- Is it a pizza?
- It isn't a burger.
- "Combo?"
Why do you keep hitting me?
- It wasn't Suk Jin's answer.
- I let it go once.
(There are mistakes
since the operation is manual.)
It was my answer,
but Suk Jin got hit with a tray.
He should have gotten hit.
Would you tell us
the letter that comes after C?
- The letter that comes...
- The letter that comes after C.
- after C.
- The letter that comes after C...
- is A.
- Let me answer.
- In 3, 2, 1.
- A?
- Let me answer.
- Cacao.
- "Cacao?"
- Let me answer.
So Min.
This can't be the answer. Camera.
(Laughing)
Number three, what is up with you?
- So it starts with "Co."
- Is that person angry?
- Number three, what is up with you?
- It starts with "Ca."
- "Ca?"
- Candy.
"Candy?"
- Is that your answer?
- No.
If everyone gives up,
Jae Suk and Eunhyuk will score.
- Ca.
It starts with "Ca."
In five,
- four, three,
- Do we know the word?
- two...
- I have no idea.
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- Cable...
- News Network.
- That must be it.
- Cable News Network.
That must be it.
("Cable News Network" is correct.)
Suk Jin, that was incredible.
My memory suddenly worked fast.
"My memory suddenly worked fast?"
That was incredible.
We did it.
Suk Jin, that was incredible.
- It's "Cable."
- Cable.
- It's a word we know.
This time,
- the answers are predetermined.
- Predetermined?
- Thus, speed is essential.
- That's what I like.
- What? I didn't hear him.
- The answers are predetermined.
Name the four members
of The Beatles,
the legendary British rock band.
- Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
John Lennon.
- I don't know their names.
- Shooting Star.
Hey, that's...
- That's ice cream.
- Isn't it "Shooting Star?"
- I know their names.
- Let me answer.
- So Min.
- John Lennon, Paul McCartney,
Ringo Starr...
- Who was the last one?
- Let me answer.
- You got three names.
John Lennon, Paul McCartney,
Ringo Starr, and George Harrison.
(Correct)
I gave away a hint
with my answer, "Shooting Star."
When did his name change
to Ringo Starr?
- It used to be Shooting Star.
- Hey.
- What is up with "Shooting Star?"
- It's at Baskin-Robbins.
- At least he came close.
- I am so annoyed.
(His answer was pretty close.)
- Right?
- I am so annoyed.
- "Star" part was nearly the same.
- I know.
Name the members of BTS,
the global star group.
- Let me answer.
- Seul Ki.
Jungkook.
- Hold on.
- Let me answer.
- Why can't I remember them?
- Haha.
- B.
- B?
- It isn't B.
- V.
- Let me answer.
- Hey.
- V,
- Jungkook, RM...
- So Hee.
- So Hee. Hey.
- You got three names.
- Let me answer.
- Hey.
- V.
- V, RM,
- Jin...
- Dae Kwan.
Dae Kwan.
(Did you call me?)
- Dae Kwan.
- Let me answer.
- Jimin.
I will give Haha a chance.
Why would you give him a chance?
V,
RM,
- Jungkook,
- Did you say "AM?"
- Jimin...
- Doo Shim.
- Dae Kwan.
- Doo...
- You punk!
- Let me answer.
(It's effective to blurt out
the names of random people.)
- Let me answer.
- Jong Kook.
- V,
Jin, RM,
- Suk Jin.
- Jungkook...
- Hyun Cheol.
Ji Suk Jin.
- Let me answer.
- V, RM,
- Seok Sam.
- Jin,
- Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo...
Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- Eunhyuk.
- V, Jin, Jungkook,
- Si Won.
- Jimin,
- Tae Jin Ah.
- Jungkook... Oh, I said it already.
- Let me answer.
- RM, Jimin,
- Jimin.
- Jin,
- Ha Dream.
- Suga,
- Ha Dream... Gosh!
- Ha Dream.
Let me answer.
- Jong Kook.
- Suga,
- Jin, Jungkook,
- I am so annoyed.
- RM...
- Kang Chan Hee.
- Ji Hyo.
- Kim Jeong Soo.
- Kang Chan Hee.
- Jin.
- Let me answer.
- It's so confusing.
- V, RM,
- V.
Suga, Jimin,
Jungkook, and Jin.
- You missed one.
- Let me answer.
- Whom did I miss?
It's my turn. Here I go.
- V, RM,
- Where are you going?
- Jungkook, Jimin,
- Jin, Suga...
- Where are you going?
- Son Heung Min.
- Jimin.
- Let me answer.
- What?
- Suga, V, Jungkook,
- Didn't I name all of them?
- Jimin, Jin...
- Hyo Im.
Hyo Im.
Hyo Im?
Hyo Im isn't a member of BTS.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hyo Im isn't a member of BTS.
- Let me answer.
- Whom did I miss?
- V, Jungkook, Jimin...
- Dong Hae.
- Lee Soo Man.
- Come on.
- Let me answer.
- Lee Soo Man.
- V, RM,
- That's so funny.
- Suga,
- Yoo Hui Yeol.
- Jin,
- Kim Jeong Nam.
- Jungkook...
- Yoo Hui Yeol.
- Kim Jeong Nam.
- Time's up.
- For goodness' sake.
- Let me answer.
- Ji Hyo.
- You need to hurry up.
- V, Jungkook,
- Suk Jin... What?
- Ji Hyo.
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
- V,
- Ji Ho.
- RM, Jin,
- Jimin, Suk Jin,
- Jang Woo Hyuk.
Jang Woo Hyuk.
- Stop it.
- It's so confusing.
- Let me answer.
- Currently, the one...
who gave 6 names is
in the 1st place.
- Let me answer.
- Jimin.
- Si Won, Dong Hae.
- V,
- Jungkook,
- Dong Hae.
- Jimin, Jin,
- Si Won, Hee Chul.
- RM, Suga...
- Hee Chul.
- There you go.
- j-hope.
I missed j-hope.
- There is j-hope.
- You did it.
- j-hope.
- j-hope, I am sorry.
- I am sorry.
- I was so confused.
- j-hope, I am sorry.
- I am sorry.
- Here comes the last question.
- Okay.
Is it already the last question.
I want to answer more questions.
Name the Chinese zodiac signs...
in the right order.
- Let me answer.
- Bakumaru, Hols, Gao, Cream...
- That's how I remember the order.
Bakumaru, Hols, Gao, Cream
are the Rat, Ox, Tiger, Rabbit
Drago, Nyorori, Pakaracchi, Souffle
are the Dragon, Snake, Horse, Goat
Monk, Tart, Pochiro, Urii
are the Monkey, Rooster, Dog, Pig
- We are the Eto Rangers
- Please say my answer is correct.
Please.
("Juuni Senshi Bakuretsu Eto Ranger"
is a cartoon series about...)
(the 12 Chinese zodiac animals
aired in 1996.)
(Bakumaru, Hols, Gao, Cream
are the Rat, Ox, Tiger, Rabbit)
Drago, Nyorori, Pakaracchi, Souffle
are the Dragon, Snake, Horse, Goat
Monk, Tart, Pochiro, Urii
are the Monkey, Rooster, Dog, Pig
- We are the Eto Rangers
- Please say my answer is correct.
Let me answer.
- We are the Eto Rangers
- Rat,
- Ox,
- The Eto Rangers
Tiger...
Gao, Cream... Rabbit.
- Isn't she answering too slowly?
- Drago... Dragon.
- Nyorori.
- Snake,
- Horse, Goat...
- Cat.
- Go ahead.
Time's up.
- We are the Eto Rangers
- Bakumaru, Hols...
Let me answer.
- Rat, Ox, Tiger, Rabbit,
- There you go.
- Dragon, Snake,
- Horse, Goat...
- There you go.
You are almost done.
- Monkey...
- You are almost done.
- Three...
- Rooster and Pig.
Rooster.
Time's up. You named nine signs.
(Seul Ki named 9 signs.)
Is it okay to get the order wrong?
You need to get the order right.
- Do we need to get the order right?
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo, do you know the songs?
- No.
Rat. Bakumaru, Hols...
Ox.
Gao. Tiger.
(Gao, Tiger)
Tart.
- Rabbit.
- Tart.
- Water deer.
- Drago.
- Dragon.
- Tart.
- Snake.
- That's exactly what So Min did.
- Horse.
- Thomson's gazelle.
Goat.
- Are we allowed to go that slow?
- Monkey.
Rooster. Pochiro is...
Dog. Pig.
I answered the same way.
We are the Eto Rangers!
Monk, Tart, Pochiro, Urii
are the Monkey, Rooster, Dog, Pig
We are
The Eto Rangers
It's from our generation.
- What is it?
- A cartoon series.
A cartoon series
from their generation.
- That was so funny.
- Was it from your generation?
- Yes, it was from our generation.
- That was so funny.
We don't know what it is.
- My goodness.
- All right.
The game has ended.
Jae Suk and Eunhyuk placed first.
(1st place, Jae Suk and Eunhyuk)
Who placed second? That's important.
Suk Jin and Seul Ki placed second.
Ji Hyo and Se Chan placed third.
Jong Kook and Soo Ah placed fourth.
Haha and So Min placed fifth.
For the last time,
the top two teams
will receive a hint.
This is an important moment.
- Eunhyuk.
- It's over for Eunhyuk.
- This is a very important moment.
- But Jong Kook saw his identity.
I am telling you that I saw it.
- Isn't it Haha?
- Eunhyuk isn't a poacher.
Se Chan said Haha isn't a poacher.
Seul Ki, did you see
Suk Jin's identity?
- Isn't he a poacher?
- I saw it. He isn't a poacher.
Soo Ah and Se Chan saw my identity.
- Haha isn't a poacher.
- Eunhyuk isn't a poacher.
- Se Chan said Haha isn't a poacher.
- He isn't.
That means no one is a poacher.
- I want to check your identity.
- I am not a poacher.
Many people think
Eunhyuk is suspicious.
That's because Se Chan started
that rumor.
That poacher is framing me.
It's a witch hunt.
I don't know who the poacher is.
- I love how he doesn't give up.
- I really don't know.
Someone is lying.
(This poacher is under suspicion.)
I got a sense of it after checking
two people's identities.
The first person...
- Eunhyuk, let's go.
- No one checked your identity.
(Jae Suk and Eunhyuk
go to check each other's identity.)
- Should I check mine?
- All right.
- My garlic cloves.
- Open your container.
Should we check our baskets?
Are there more garlic gloves
than there were earlier?
(Full)
(This poacher has stolen
garlic gloves from animals.)
Hold on. This...
- Can we check each other's garlic?
- I bet you have a lot.
(Gasping)
It's you.
What? I played the games well.
- I played the games well.
- Really?
All right. Jae Suk is
a regular bear.
Eunhyuk is a poacher.
For goodness' sake.
The two of you can't switch teams.
(The two of you can't switch teams.)
The only thing that remains
is arresting the poachers,
so it won't help you to reveal
that Eunhyuk is one.
- At least you know one poacher.
- That's right.
You just need to find out
who the bear poacher is.
- Still...
Each member has to guess
who the two poachers are, right?
Yes. You will receive garlic cloves
if both answers are correct.
Why did you take
so many garlic cloves?
Eunhyuk has 63 garlic cloves.
(Eunhyuk has 63 garlic cloves.)
I think I will be
in the first place.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- All right.
(Jae Suk learned about
Eunhyuk's identity.)
- If multiple people get it right,
- That's right.
- the garlic cloves must be shared.
- Yes.
- It's Eunhyuk.
- I think...
the tiger poacher is
either Eunhyuk or Se Chan.
I want to know
who the bear poacher is.
- It's either one of them.
- The bear poacher.
The bear poacher is
either Haha or...
- You.
- But Soo Ah said it isn't him.
- She said it with seriousness.
- It isn't Haha. It's Jong Kook.
- It's Jong Kook or Haha.
- You aren't a poacher, right?
- I am not a poacher.
- It isn't Haha.
- It's me.
- It's Jong Kook.
- Is it you?
- Isn't he a poacher?
- He is acting. I know it.
He keeps saying
that he is a poacher.
Don't be fooled.
Jong Kook is a poacher.
I think it's him. I am certain.
- Is it you?
- It's Jong Kook.
- He was Seul Ki's partner.
- Suk Jin must be a poacher.
- I am not a poacher.
- He isn't a poacher.
- I saw her identity.
- He really isn't a poacher.
- No?
- Isn't Seul Ki a poacher?
- No.
- She isn't a poacher.
- Is Se Chan a poacher then?
- I am not a poacher.
- I think it's him.
- No one is a poacher.
Then who is a poacher?
Everyone became a good liar.
- Eunhyuk isn't a poacher.
- Of course not.
- Everyone.
- It isn't him.
I will give you the rules
of the final vote.
- I have no idea.
- All right.
Write down
the names of the two people...
whom you suspect are the poachers.
(They will each vote on two people
suspected as poachers.)
If you arrest both poachers,
- you will receive 20 garlic cloves.
- Did he say 20 garlic cloves?
Getting one name right
is meaningless.
- We need to get both of them.
- Yes.
As for the poachers,
they will lose
twice as many garlic cloves...
as the votes they receive.
So a poacher who received 10 votes
will lose 20 garlic cloves.
The person whose eyes shifted
upon hearing those words...
So vote well to make them lose
their garlic cloves.
My goodness.
But you will win more garlic cloves
if you answer correctly by yourself.
(They might aim
to answer correctly by themselves.)
All right. I will hand out
the ballots.
- Let's vote.
- This is so hard.
Poachers can write down any names.
Their votes are meaningless.
I will go with my initial hunch.
I am sorry.
- For goodness' sake.
- I know who the tiger poacher is,
- but not the bear poacher.
- I changed my mind.
Arresting the poachers
is the only solution.
There is no other way.
I didn't go with my initial hunch.
I changed my mind.
(Jong Kook chose Ji Hyo
as the bear poacher.)
I think it's him...
because Eunhyuk and Jong Kook
teamed up for a while...
- before they split up.
- You are right.
- Go with your hunch.
- Isn't Eunhyuk a poacher?
He is bound to say no.
- That's right.
- He wants to get it right alone.
That's how it is.
Even if he is a poacher?
- But Eunhyuk...
- Seul Ki, are you done?
Yes, I am done.
- She was torn until the end.
- Didn't you turn in the ballot?
Gosh, I was so torn.
- All right, everyone.
- I trusted my hunch.
- The results are out.
- Okay.
- I trusted Soo Ah.
Firstly...
- Did someone get them right?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Both poachers?
Someone got both poachers right.
(There is an animal
that got 2 poachers right.)
- Really?
- Both poachers?
Someone got both poachers right.
- Really?
- Are there more than one?
- I will tell you soon.
I bet we got them right.
Eunhyuk and...
- That's impressive.
- All right.
(Before announcing the result)
I will first reveal
how many votes everyone received.
- Okay.
Eunhyuk received six votes.
It's Se Chan's doing.
For goodness' sake.
(Eunhyuk worked hard,
but he received 6 votes.)
- Most of us voted for him.
- Everyone was swayed by him.
Jong Kook received five votes.
- You received many votes.
- Gosh.
He is a good actor.
He should debut as an actor.
- People are quick-witted.
- He should debut as an actor.
- My goodness.
- Next.
- Se Chan received 2 votes.
- Only 2 votes?
Did Se Chan receive two votes?
Haha, Suk Jin, and Ji Hyo
received one vote each.
I will reveal
the poachers of the day.
- Who are they?
- Jong Kook and Eunhyuk.
Firstly, the poacher
who hid among the tigers is...
Eunhyuk?
(The poacher
who hid among the tigers)
It must be Eunhyuk.
- Eunhyuk.
- It's Eunhyuk.
Roar.
(The tiger poacher, Eunhyuk)
(Roar!)
- Roar.
- From the start...
- He hid his identity well.
- Everyone suspected him.
- He is sneaky.
Next.
(The poacher
who hid among the bears)
- The one who hid among the bears.
- Who is it?
- I am so curious about this one.
- Jong Kook.
- He tortured me all day long.
- Haha.
(The bear poacher hid
behind Jong Kook's back.)
- He tortured me all day long.
- Haha.
(The bear poacher
sent everyone into confusion)
I am really not a poacher.
It really isn't me.
- The one who hid among the bears.
- Who is it?
- He tortured me all day long.
- Haha.
It's Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin)
No way.
(Suk Jin was the bear poacher.)
(Frozen)
(Everyone is shocked,)
(but Seul Ki and Suk Jin cheer.)
I thought about picking
between the two of them.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo)
This is so satisfying.
- I fooled everyone.
- This is so satisfying.
You are the only one
who got both names.
I thought about picking
between the two of them.
I told you that I am not a poacher.
My goodness.
- How did he stay hidden?
- Seriously.
(During the role selection,)
(Suk Jin picked a poacher.)
(His team placed 1st
and his cover got blown right away.)
- How did we place first?
- I can't believe you are a poacher.
- I will switch teams.
- No.
It would be more advantageous
to maintain this arrangement.
If you catch the poachers,
you will receive a big benefit.
- We should be a team until the end.
- I understand.
Let's not switch teams.
- We won't switch teams.
(Thus, Seul Ki formed an alliance
with a poacher.)
(Everyone time
people suspected Suk Jin)
(Suk Jin is not the poacher.
I can guarantee that.)
(Seul Ki actively protected
Suk Jin.)
(Seul Ki was the only one
who knew about his true identity,)
(so the members trusted
Suk Jin to be a bear.)
I want to know
who the bear poacher is.
(It was all thanks
to the smart tiger.)
- Did you know?
- I knew.
You knew.
- It was Suk Jin.
- I knew.
Haha, why did you pretend
to be a poacher?
I didn't do anything!
- He seemed like a poacher.
- What did I do?
- We had a good plan.
- I know.
- Seul Ki.
- Seul Ki did an incredible job.
- Only Seul Ki got both poachers.
- Seul Ki...
totally fooled us.
- Seul Ki fooled us.
- I trusted her.
- Seriously.
- That should have been me.
Thus, Seul Ki received
20 more garlic cloves.
- Yes.
- Eunhyuk lost 12 garlic cloves.
- Did I lose garlic cloves?
- Yes.
Oh, no. Oh, my goodness.
Suk Jin lost two garlic cloves.
- Two?
- Yes.
Now, you will see the present
the top three members will receive.
- What are those?
- This will air on Lunar New Year.
(Barley croaker
and king-sized rib set)
It's the barley croaker
and king-sized rib set.
- One each?
- Yes. One each.
- Gosh, please.
- It looks delicious.
The 1st, 2nd, and 3rd-place winners
who will get the prize are...
The first place is...
Eunhyuk with 51 garlic cloves.
Gosh. After losing
some of his garlic cloves?
- Who's the second?
- And the second place...
is Suk Jin with 43 garlic cloves.
(The 2nd place is
Suk Jin with 43 garlic cloves.)
- Well done.
- The third place...
is Seul Ki with 35 garlic cloves.
- Congratulations.
- Okay.
These three will get the prize.
So Min is the 8th, Soo Ah is
the 9th, and Jong Kook is the 10th.
(So Min, Soo Ah, and Jong Kook
will get the penalty.)
- Why Jong Kook?
- Are you the last?
He's been the 1st and 2nd
the whole time.
- I took all his garlic cloves.
- He took mine.
Really?
I protected him to win.
I wanted to arrest
the poachers myself.
So the three of you
will get the penalty.
(The last 3 members
will get the penalty.)
You will mince...
the garlic you earned today
before going home.
- My goodness.
- That sounds like a lot of work.
- I'm good at mincing the garlic.
- Good.
- Mince the garlic.
- I'm good at it.
Is there an easier way
to mince the garlic?
Should I crush them all?
We should crush them all.
I made my bid for victory
after a long time today.
This is my first time here,
but I'm crushing garlic.
Gosh, this helps me
work out my forearm muscles.
- Seriously.
- Is this part of your workout?
This gives me a good workout.
- I'm good. They are all minced.
- This is good enough.
(Running Man Country Club
located in Ilsan)
(Without the female members,)
(they are like reckless
middle-aged men at a golf course.)
(To meet them,)
(a strict variety show director,)
(Pak Se Ri is here.)
(Variety hole-in-one:
A body for a slapstick comedy)
(Risk your life
for the variety show golf.)
(Variety show lie:
Body type that makes people laugh)
(Isn't that the parallel universe theory?)
(Variety show hazard: Obstacles that
you have to overcome for laughter)
(They are the most difficult
students to deal with.)
(However...)
(I will break through)
(And pull ahead)
(And I'll finally win)
(Se Ri and Birdie Buddy)