In May, 2020, NASA scientists...
reported they've found
a parallel universe.
("Parallel Universe,
Another Earth And Me")
Where Another Me Lives?")
(Two different universes...)
(Under the same name)
(The beginning of the beginning...)
(is ungraspable.)
(Two similar,
but unlike universes were born.)
(Somewhere in Korea
on another earth)
(A man reads the world news
in the quiet morning.)
(Kim Suk Jin of BTS)
At 8 a.m., every morning,
I drink Americano.
I drink black herbal tea.
So hot.
Darn it.
(Ji Suk Jin as an independent)
(While Ji Suk Jin sucks
his fingers greedily...)
(Dad Joke Collection)
How did one think
of a joke like this?
If one handwrites...
a letter of apology,
it's a "handy apology."
I like dad jokes.
I'm a dad.
(Massaging his wrinkles)
Coldplay is cool.
I know Coldplay.
They're good.
Coldplay knows me.
Hello?
Hey, Jimin.
I'm the oldest member of BTS.
Want to meet up there? Okay.
I was home all day.
I'm the oldest member
of Running Man.
I wouldn't be weaker than you.
I'll go. You punk.
I'm...
- Suk Jin.
(The border between two universes
is torn down.)
(Two universes that aren't
supposed to collide.)
(Only one universe will survive.)
(Suk Jin Universe began just
because they have the same name.)
They'll be shocked to see this.
To see that.
(Acting cute)
I'm excited to be on TV.
This is my first time
on a variety show.
- Really?
- I'm so thrilled.
Just have fun.
I'm charming. Don't worry.
You and Jin are the captains
of each team.
Every member is waiting
in a different place.
- Hello.
Hello.
You'll be riding the car
that looks the same...
and stop right in front
of each member.
Each member will choose the car
based on the remaining seats.
People in the same car
will form a team.
This is going to be fun.
They better choose carefully.
Is it going to be Jin of BTS
or Suk Jin the Big Nose?
Now, we will start.
Let's go.
Do both cars stop at the same time?
- Two cars will arrive soon.
- Really?
There are captains in each car.
I see.
- We don't get to know who they are?
- No.
Which one should I choose?
The remaining seats?
Yes.
By remaining seats,
do you mean the available seats?
(What will they be riding?)
(Who do you want to team up with?)
Me?
If I think only about the game,
Jong Kook would be the best choice.
Jae Suk has good hunches.
He'd get in this car.
I'm curious.
I can't wait.
They'll wander around...
and think about which car to choose.
I see Jae Suk.
He's confused.
It's Jae Suk.
I'm excited to see celebrities.
I heard that Jin of BTS would be
on our show today.
I have a feeling...
that I'll have to choose
between Jin and Suk Jin.
Gosh. This is ridiculous.
Do you think this makes sense?
Jae Suk, we're here.
The two vehicles arrived.
Jae Suk.
I'll be very sad
if Jae Suk doesn't choose me.
It will be very disappointing.
Oh, man. I have no idea.
I can't see the inside at all.
Jin or Suk Jin.
Of course, I would choose Jin.
There's no need to ask.
I mean, I see Seok Sam so often.
We talk on the phone often too.
Of course, I'd choose Jin.
All right. I choose Jin!
He's coming.
Which one of us will he choose?
(Could Jae Suk choose
Jin's vehicle?)
My gut is telling me
that Jin is in here.
(Which of the team captains
did Jae Suk choose?)
I have a feeling that Jin's in here.
Darn it.
(He chose Suk Jin, not Jin.)
(It ruined Jae Suk's day
first thing in the morning.)
Why...
Why is this van here?
Why is it here?
- Hey, get in.
- But... Hyo Im.
- Then the van... Gosh.
- Get in already.
- Gosh. Jin!
- Just get in.
Jae Suk!
- I'm disappointed.
- He's in the other van.
I'm so disappointed.
I want to cry.
- Seriously. I'm so upset.
- Hey, it was 1 of the 2 vans.
- I know, but...
- Right?
Gosh. I joined Suk Jin's team.
This is the worst.
(Welcome. I love you.)
Gosh. This is frustrating.
Darn. I can't believe this.
- Can I move to another team later?
- No, you can't.
I heard about the rules. This is it.
This is it.
You'll be on my team all day.
Oh, man.
I wanted to join Jin's team.
(He feels hopeless
about today's race.)
(Without knowing how upset
Jae Suk is, Jin finds it funny.)
Now, I see that Running Man
really is an unscripted show.
(Jin confirmed
that it's an unscripted show.)
- Gosh. This is the worst.
- Oh, my.
Hey, why are you so downcast?
Who's next?
I can recognize him by his legs.
He must be Jong Kook.
I hope Jong Kook will come to me.
(Trainer Kook is doing
shadow boxing as always.)
Jong Kook, I'm bored.
Please choose my team.
If you go there as well,
I'll be so sad.
There are 3 and 2 seats left
in the vans?
Here I go.
(He walks straight to one
of the vans without hesitating.)
- I think he's coming to us.
- Is Jong Kook...
- going to join us?
- I think he is.
- If he comes, our team...
- Great.
Jong Kook, please come to me.
(Will he join the members
or the person he rarely gets to see?)
(Jong Kook is slowly approaching.)
(Which team did Jong Kook choose?)
- Hey, Jong Kook.
- Oh, my. Hey.
- Hi. I'm so happy to see you.
- I'm surprised. Hey.
Hi. I thought...
I would've been so sad...
- if you chose the other team too.
- Hey.
Why did everyone go there?
I don't understand.
- Only Jae Suk is there.
- Really?
Oh, no.
Jin must be uncomfortable with him.
- I wish I were there.
- Jin must be uncomfortable.
- I wish you were there too.
- Gosh.
It's because
you're good at buttering people up.
- How dare you?
- You're good at it.
- Don't say that.
I'm caring
and considerate of others.
Jong Kook can never
butter others up.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Gosh.
Hey, I haven't seen you
in a long time.
- I saw you...
- Have you been well?
We ran into each other...
- at a restaurant in the US.
- Right.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- That was 3 or 4 years ago.
- Yes. You remember that.
- After my group's concert.
- Right.
- We heard you were there too.
- Yes, that's right.
- So we went to say hi to you.
- Yes.
You and your group members came.
I was enjoying the food.
It was so unexpected.
(I was enjoying the food.
It was so unexpected.)
Most of my close friends
live in Los Angeles.
- Really?
- Yes, it's true.
You see, I'm from Anyang.
- But rather than Anyang...
- Oh, I'm...
- Anyang in Gyeonggi Province?
- Yes.
Anyang is my hometown too.
- Where in Anyang?
- I...
- I don't know. I was born there.
- Really?
- You were born in Anyang?
- After that, I lived in Gwacheon.
Oh, that's... I had no idea.
I didn't know you were from Anyang.
I've never seen any celebrities
from Anyang.
Hey, I was born and raised
in Anyang.
- No wonder why you chose this van.
- Hey. I...
Hey.
Despite our age difference,
- Come on.
- we seem to have things in common.
I'm not so young. I'm 31.
- Really? Then...
- Yes.
Aren't you in your late 30s?
Did I go too far?
- Oh, no.
- That's nice. I'm flattered.
That's not too much.
Foreigners think I'm in my 30s.
- Of course.
- Yes. They say I look young.
Some people think I'm a teenager.
You look like a teenager.
- Did I go too far?
- Not at all.
Foreigners would think
you're in high school.
People would definitely think
you're a high school student...
- if you go to the US.
- Jong Kook.
Are you flattering me
because I'm a superstar?
No, I'm not.
I haven't heard anyone who called
himself a superstar in a while.
- People like it when I do that.
- Of course.
- They don't want me to be modest.
- Right.
That's true. Times have changed.
- I hope So Min comes to us.
- Me too.
- I want to see her disappointed.
- Exactly.
(They're on the same page.)
- I really want...
- I want to see her disappointed.
to see her disappointed face.
If she sees Jin,
she'd say hello coyly. "Hello."
- I hate it when she does that.
- I don't want to see that.
- I hate the sight of that.
- She'd tug her hair like this.
- "Hello."
- "Hello." I hate that.
"I'm a fan of yours."
- Gosh. I hate the sight of that.
- I hate the sight of that.
Why are you swaying my heart?
Why are you...
- I think you sang the wrong lyrics.
- Did I?
(Is she already singing BTS' song?)
We'll be having a guest today, right?
There must be our guests
in the two vehicles. Right?
(It seems that her secret informant
told her about the guest again.)
I'm excited... Stop laughing.
(She's elated while waiting.)
Could there be no remaining seats?
That won't happen, right?
This must be it. I think we're here.
She might be able to see my face.
You look so different from Jin.
Covering your face is pointless.
But she might be able to
get a glimpse of my face.
No. She can never see your face.
- She might.
- She can't see through the window.
Who is that?
He has his back toward us.
That's Haha.
- Haha...
- I hope he won't turn around.
Haha should absolutely join us.
Okay. Got it.
(The two vehicles stop
in front of Haha.)
There are two remaining seats
in this one...
(Both of the vehicles have
two remaining seats.)
Gosh. What do I do?
- Who is that?
- Haha.
- Oh, Haha?
- Hold on.
I absolutely have no idea.
Gosh.
This one caught my eye
as soon as it arrived.
He should be with us.
He'll make Jin uncomfortable.
He'll make Jin so uncomfortable.
I'm sure he will.
(The kid goes crazy
when he sees a hip celebrity.)
I've made my decision.
(He goes with his first instinct!)
Here...
(Chuckling)
- Gosh.
- Is this van for old fossils?
(They're not happy
to have him on the team either.)
- Gosh.
- Is this van for old fossils?
Jae Suk, are you the captain?
- Hey, Haha.
- Hey.
- I'm really...
- I'm the captain of the team.
- Oh, you're the captain? Okay.
- Hey.
You should've chosen Jin of BTS.
You didn't know?
Why did you...
- I didn't know.
- Did you really not know?
Is Jin of BTS in that van?
Yes, he is.
- Is Jin in this van?
- I guess he really didn't know.
- He doesn't seem to have known.
- I think he didn't know.
- Gosh.
- He didn't know?
He has no global vibe.
- Having a global vibe is important.
- Yes.
- We've both been to LA, you know.
- Exactly.
- LA and Anyang.
- That's right.
Gosh. This is driving me crazy.
Oh, man.
(He lost the world star
in front of his eyes.)
My gosh. I could've chosen him.
- Is it Suk Jin versus Suk Jin?
- Yes.
- I was going to...
- You didn't know, did you?
- give you a chance...
- I didn't know.
- My gosh.
- Gosh, seriously.
Suk Jin versus Suk Jin?
That's unexpected.
- What a shame.
- How come you didn't know?
- This is amazing though.
- Right.
I'm surprised you made it this far,
Suk Jin.
- What do you mean by that?
- I was just saying...
- that this is great.
- What do you mean?
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
Don't get me wrong.
You're surprised I made it this far?
I mean, you're incredibly lucky.
Suk Jin is never on par with
Jin of BTS. Not even close.
Hey, we have a lot in common.
This is so amazing.
- Wait. Who's that? Is she So Min?
- You're so lucky, Suk Jin.
- I think she is. She's with a dog.
- She's So Min.
- Isn't she So Min?
- Is she?
- Is she So Min?
- No, she's Ji Hyo.
Oh, she's Ji Hyo?
It has 1 remaining seat
while the other has 2.
I choose the van
with one remaining seat.
- Oh, she's coming. Hey.
- Hey.
(This is the van
with one remaining seat.)
I hope she won't come here.
(Silent)
- Get in.
- Why are you guys here?
Our team is full now.
The rest will join the other team.
- It's a shame.
- Yes, it's a shame.
Do you know who's in the other van?
- No, I don't know.
- You don't know?
- They didn't tell you, right?
- They didn't tell you?
- They didn't tell me.
- Jin of BTS is in there.
- Jin of BTS is in that van.
- Jin of BTS.
Hey, stop.
Wait.
Hold on a second. What did you say?
- Jin of BTS is there.
- Jin of BTS is in the other van.
Jin of BTS is in that van?
- Yes.
- Really?
Don't come here.
(Knocking)
I won't get in.
Just open the door...
so that I can see Jin.
- No.
- I want to see Jin.
I'll roll down the window instead.
There. What is it?
- Jong Kook.
- Yes? Why?
- I heard Jin of BTS was here.
- Yes, he's here.
Open the door for me.
I'll leave after seeing him.
- I already chose my team.
- No. Since you've made...
- Since you've made your decision...
- I know.
- I just want to see him.
- He's right here.
- Hi, Jin. It's good to see you.
- Hi, Ji Hyo.
Hey. I should've chosen this van.
I'm sorry, but don't be like this.
- I won't get in. I chose my team.
- Good.
- Let me at least shake his hand.
- No. Wait.
- It's good to see you, Ji Hyo.
- I wish I had chosen this van.
I missed you.
- You guys are...
- Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
So unlucky. Both you and Haha.
Then...
So Min will join you guys.
So Min and Se Chan will be
on our team...
- automatically.
- Yes, they'll be on our team.
- See you later, Ji Hyo.
- See you in a bit.
You must be disappointed.
Gosh, why did I choose this van
and team up with you guys?
(Looking at their faces
makes her feel even angrier.)
We feel the same way.
Our van smells like an old man.
Can you put something else on the screen?
That drives me crazy.
- Gosh.
- Your team is complete now.
- Got it.
- We'll get going now.
Our team is complete?
Gosh. This is ridiculous.
(The team combination ruined
their mood from the start.)
(The vans arrived
in front of Se Chan this time.)
Can you step away from the van
a little bit?
There's no remaining seat?
No remaining seat?
(Team Suk Jin was sold out
very quickly.)
Does it mean
I can't choose that van?
I can't join that team? Is it full?
Should I get in that van?
So it's not that I have a choice,
right?
Is something wrong?
- Hello.
- Hey.
- You startled me. Oh, my.
- You're lucky.
(Jin appears.)
You startled me. Oh, my.
- You're lucky.
- Hello.
- Hold on. Goodbye.
- Where are you going?
- Hello.
- Hold on.
(Hello. Goodbye.)
- Where are you going?
- My gosh. What's going on?
Jong Kook. Hello, Jin.
- Hello, Se Chan.
- You're so lucky.
This is...
- Oh, no. It's closing again.
- It's refusing to let you in.
It won't let me in.
(This van won't let me in.)
Oh, my. Jin is here.
- Hello.
- Hello. It's nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you too.
- Right.
- Are we on the same team?
- Please get in.
- Yes, we are.
- Yes!
- Hey, get in.
- My goodness.
Why are you dressed
like Inspector Gadget?
The weather is quite...
- I mean... Hello.
- Hello.
I've watched many videos on YouTube.
- Really? Do you know who I am?
- Yes.
- Of course, I know who you are.
- "Do you know who I am?"
- You're a popular celebrity.
- Yes, he is.
I'm so excited to see him.
This is hard to believe.
My goodness. Jin of BTS is here.
It's my first time
seeing him in person.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Don't you know Jimin of BTS?
Jimin? No, not at all.
- Oh, I see.
- He knows Comedienne Kim Ji Min.
I do know Kim Ji Min.
He knows Comedienne Kim Ji Min
for sure.
I don't know
Jimin of BTS personally.
Do you prefer being called
Jin or Suk Jin?
I don't mind.
You can call me whatever you want.
- I'll call you Big Brother Jin.
- "Big Brother Jin?"
- He must be younger than you.
- Are you...
- It doesn't matter.
- Okay.
I address any rich men
as my big brothers.
- I have the same mindset.
- All rich men are my seniors.
- I call rich men big brothers too.
- Oh, I see.
I'll address Jin as my big brother.
All right, Se Chan.
Thank you.
I'll address Jin as my big brother.
All right, Se Chan.
(The superstar has
a great sense of humor.)
Just so you know,
Jin doesn't try to be modest.
- Really?
- He's rather straightforward.
- That's true.
- Great. Do whatever you want.
That's one of the social trends
these days, you know.
- One of the social trends.
- He calls himself a superstar.
- That's so cool.
- Indeed.
- I don't deny it.
- He doesn't deny it.
- It's true that I'm a superstar.
- Yes, it's true.
(While Se Chan is learning
how a superstar should behave...)
Thinking how excited So Min will get
annoys me a little bit.
- Jong Kook, is So Min joining us?
- Yes.
- We have the last seat.
- That's right.
I'll fall in love with So Min today.
- Good.
- All of a sudden.
- That's a good idea.
- So Min seems...
- to fall for every male guest.
- Yes, she does.
- You're right about that.
- I watch this show very often.
She liked every one of them.
And she has never said a word
about you.
- I'm disappointed. I really am.
- You should be.
Could I be alone in the car again?
(So Min has no idea
what's going on.)
Will I be abandoned like this?
I think I've been abandoned.
They must've chosen everyone else...
and had no choice but to pick me up.
Are they here?
(The vehicle that has no choice
but to pick her up arrives.)
- I remember...
- See? So Min is all dressed up.
- Look at her.
- Gosh. So Min is so...
I hate the sight of her.
- I'm so upset.
- She said she'd trim her bang.
- I guess it was because of this.
- How did she get the information?
- Exactly. How did she find out?
- We should catch her informant.
She always knows
what we'll get up to.
- How should we catch her informant?
- I really had no idea.
- How does she get the information?
One of the vehicles has...
no remaining seat.
There's no remaining seat.
How many seats are there
in each vehicle?
Anyway...
(She gets upset to find out
she has no option.)
I knew it.
No wonder it was taking so long.
My gosh. Why...
I mean, there's no remaining seat...
- Hello, So Min.
- Oh, my. Hello.
- Gosh. She'll be so excited.
- I can't wait to see her reaction.
- There's no remaining seat...
- Hello, So Min.
Oh, my. Hello.
Hey, look at you.
You look as though you knew
he would be here.
I'm sorry, but I told him.
How come there's a seat left
in this van?
That's your luck.
Look how she's smiling.
She looks so excited.
Has she met Jin?
- Gosh, seriously.
- She looks so excited.
I don't even want to see her.
I hate the sight of her. Gosh.
- Gosh. I can hear her laugh.
- Gosh.
- I'm so upset.
- Jin must be...
Gosh. I wish I had chosen that team.
No.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Usually, men put their jackets
on a girl, right?
But Se Chan puts it on him too.
Isn't it strange?
- Why would you share it with me?
- It means that I own this coat.
- Maybe he wants to hold hands...
- This is how a romance is created.
- He wants to hold your hand...
- Exactly. Jin, just as I told you.
So Min, hold my hand under the coat.
- Come on. Hold my hand.
- No.
- Hey, look.
- You can't create a romance today.
- There are stars on the ceiling.
- Oh, my. What is that?
- What is this?
- It's for the superstar.
- Right. Look at the lights.
- Wow. It's nice.
What's with the mood lights?
Only luxury cars have stars
on the ceiling, right?
It says,
"This is Team Kim Suk Jin."
- "This is Team Kim Suk Jin."
- And Team Ji Suk Jin.
(They're moving to the place for
the Suk Jin Versus Suk Jin race.)
- Should we get out now?
- Let's get out.
- Thank you.
- Ji Hyo, it'll be crazy today.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hey, Jin!
- It'll be crazy today, Suk Jin.
Jin, were you uncomfortable...
Where is he?
- I'm here.
- Were you uncomfortable?
- No, not at all.
- Weren't you?
- Was it okay without me?
- It was totally fine.
- Hey, Jin!
- My gosh. Jin.
- I mean, I'm so surprised.
- Hey, I...
- It's good to see you.
- Come here.
- I tried so hard to find your van.
- This is so unexpected.
- I was so sad you didn't come.
- I happened to join his team.
- Right. He must've been really sad.
- I really wanted to join his team.
- They're wearing the same sweater.
- Of course, I was sad.
It's so nice to be on Running Man.
I feel so welcomed.
Of course, you're welcome.
My gosh. I'm so upset.
- Yes.
- Hello.
Hello.
I was so lucky.
- I was lucky. I got in his van.
- Darn.
It's such a shame.
- I'm so upset.
- Okay.
Darn it.
Go away. He's on our team!
- Why did you come here?
- He's right.
- Seriously. Jin, listen to me.
- Gosh. I got so unlucky.
I think Haha is most disappointed
among you guys.
- Haha is greedy for such a thing.
- He always wants to look hip.
I'm here
because I let go of my greed.
Haha, there was only one seat left,
and I'm here now.
All three of them chose
the other van.
- Exactly.
- Oh, no. I'm sorry.
- Jin of BTS is here!
- He's here.
This is incredible.
- Jin of BTS is on our show.
- This is hard to believe.
(Jae Suk dances to "Fire"
frivolously.)
- Jin came on Running Man.
- Yes.
Whenever I met Jin at events
like a film premiere,
he said,
"I want to be on Running Man."
- He told me that many times.
- Yes, I did.
- He told me that five times.
- I said it many times.
- Exactly.
- But I didn't get a chance.
BTS appeared on our show...
- when they just released "Fire."
- That's right.
- Yes. For about ten minutes.
- They appeared for a while.
(All members of BTS appeared
in the 300th episode 6 years ago.)
(All they did was
move 300 boxes in 10 minutes.)
- That was a shame.
- It must've been hard for them.
- You only made us move boxes.
- We pulled one another.
- They pulled a handcart too.
- That's right.
- Right.
- Yes, I remember that.
- They left after moving the boxes.
- Yes.
I revealed Jungkook's abs
by pulling his shirt up.
- Many of his fans thanked me.
- Really?
Yes. For showing his abs.
- V hugged me from behind...
- By the way...
- wearing my glasses. It went viral.
- He put on Haha's glasses.
- It's famous among BTS' fans.
- Oh, I didn't know that.
- Actually...
- You're talking like an old man.
- We're like old people chatting.
- The top star hugged me.
Really?
That was so funny.
- You see, in 2018, Suk Jin...
- Yes.
called Jin, and he was asleep.
- Yes. I felt so bad about it.
- Oh, right.
I felt bad about it.
Hello.
Oh, my. Hello, Suk Jin.
Jin, were you sleeping?
(Suk Jin woke Jin up while he was
sleeping in the Netherlands.)
- He picked up while sleeping.
- I'm in the Netherlands.
- Sorry.
- I'm in the Netherlands now.
Since then, I put my phone
on silent before going to bed.
I'm really sorry about that.
I felt so bad back then.
- It must've made you uncomfortable.
- To be honest,
- you would understand me.
- Good for you.
- Good for you, Jin.
- I didn't know he was overseas.
He was in Europe when I called him,
and due to the time difference...
- I didn't know that.
- Why did you call him?
- Was it a mission?
- He pestered me to call Jin...
- to prove I knew Jin personally.
- Who did that?
- Oh, did I?
- He didn't believe me.
I said, "I could call him, but..."
- Suk Jin, I'm so sorry,
- Don't make him uncomfortable.
- but I want to hear from Jin.
- Right.
- But...
- We need more of Jin's voice.
- I'm just adding details.
- I know.
- But still...
- They'll edit it out anyway.
- Don't do that.
- Oh, they'll cut the part out.
Yes.
Suk Jin's comments will be
edited out.
- Actually...
- You'd better not tell the story.
- Continue.
- I really am close to Suk Jin.
We have had a drink together
on a private occasion.
- Really?
- Jin, when Suk Jin told me that,
I almost ran to you
to tell you not to do that again.
- Why?
- I heard you had paid the bill.
- I knew it.
- What?
- He didn't pay, right?
- I can't believe him.
- Suk Jin...
- You let him pay for your drinks?
- He let Jin pay for his drinks.
- I was going to pay...
- You should've...
- I was going to pay,
but he insisted on treating me.
- It's because he's a nice person.
- That's true.
- Gosh.
- Tell them what really happened.
- I treat others too, right?
- My gosh. Suk Jin.
As a superstar, I wanted
to treat my friend to a drink.
If that's the case,
we'll believe you.
- Okay. Since he put it like that...
- Suk Jin, why did you...
- Suk Jin isn't as rich as him.
- I mean...
When Suk Jin came,
we had already finished 1 or 2 bottles.
- But still...
- So he only had one glass.
- I said I would pay.
- He's so nice.
- He's explaining for Suk Jin.
- Exactly.
- He made Suk Jin look good.
- Jin's fans, you heard it, right?
Gosh.
Are the two of them really close?
- That can't be true.
- No!
(He doesn't want to believe
that they're friends.)
- But...
- Why wouldn't they be?
As you can see,
they're wearing the same clothes.
Hold on. Is yours a replica?
- Of course not.
- Suk Jin.
- Why doesn't it suit you?
- It's like you're in rags.
This costs 1,400 dollars!
- Aren't those rags?
- Seriously?
- This?
- I mean...
Is it that expensive?
The staff told my stylist...
that anything similar would be fine.
But my stylist wanted me to be
in the same sweater.
- So she got you that?
- How cool of her.
- Was it bought?
- Yes, it was bought.
- You bought it?
- Personally?
- That's right.
- Are you sure it's not a rag?
And the pants were provided
by BTS' staff.
The pants and the shoes.
- Originally...
- They provided them?
- So they weren't rags.
- You need to return them.
- Don't dirty them up.
- Of course.
- You can keep them.
- Really?
- You're giving them to him?
- For free?
I want to be generous.
- Thank you so much.
- Keep them.
- Jin gave them to him.
- When they're expensive?
- Are they expensive?
- Yes.
That's a different story, then.
You should return them.
- But...
- Jin's a superstar, Suk Jin.
You should return them
if they're expensive.
This isn't us
blowing things out of proportion.
- BTS truly is...
- Of course.
- Right.
- They're world-class.
And Jin...
called himself a superstar.
(A self-claimed superstar)
- Right?
- But it's true.
I'm not wrong, am I?
- I'm not wrong.
- Right.
- He's not wrong.
- It's not a lie.
- I agree.
- This...
- is what I love about him.
- So this is what I said.
- What did you say?
- This is what I said.
That we have a superstar...
- on the side of Running Man.
- Who?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- But he's...
- Compared to Jin...
- Unbelievable.
- Will you just stay put?
- Out of all of us,
- there's the one.
- Jin's an international star.
- International.
- You're a local star.
And I heard you were a rising star.
- A rising star?
- That's what we call him.
- A rising star.
- For 30 years...
- A rising star of 30 years.
- Still?
I should be on the rise,
but I haven't caught my break.
That's hilarious. Anyway...
Jin, you released a new album.
I guess you can say that.
It's a single, actually.
- What's the song?
- Tell us about it.
- It's called "The Astronaut."
- "The Astronaut."
(The Astronaut by Jin of BTS,
a collaboration with Coldplay...)
(brought us a light but dreamy
pop rock number.)
There's a band named Coldplay.
- Yes, we know them.
- They're a famous band.
And we collaborated with them
as a group before.
- Of course.
- We remember.
- This time around...
- Is it another collaboration?
- Yes. I expressed...
- Really?
how I'd love
to work with them again,
- and they...
- They got on board.
- They did.
- Of course they did.
Why would they decline
when it's Jin of BTS?
Just like I'd contact Rado,
you contacted Coldplay.
- No, not in that sense.
- Rado?
- You're comparing them to Rado?
- Rado and Coldplay?
I can easily contact Rado, you know.
- But Rado...
- Yes, Rado.
I'm impressed since
I usually work with KCM.
Yes, KCM.
- What a collaboration.
- I can't believe it.
Anyway, what will we be doing today?
Welcome to Team Transfer:
Suk Jin Versus Suk Jin.
- I see.
- That's it.
The winning team
will get one penalty ball...
while the losing team
will get two penalty balls.
All those on the team
that gets chosen at the end...
will receive the penalty together.
Since this is
the Team Transfer Race,
the winning team...
will randomly be given
exchange tickets.
With this ticket,
you will be able to choose yourself,
a teammate, or even the captain
to be swapped.
A ticket booth will be set up today,
and the tickets can only
be used when it's open,
- not when it's closed.
- Right.
Before we begin the race,
the captains will be given...
three exchange tickets each
as an advantage.
- Nice.
- You can keep up to two.
The rest can be given
to any member on your team.
- Suk Jin, choose me.
- Hand them out right now.
- I'll swap teams with So Min.
- Sure.
- Exchange tickets.
- Thank you.
We don't need any
since we don't want to swap teams.
- They're coming for So Min.
- I should get one.
They're trying to drag
So Min over there.
- I should get one.
- Why?
- Because I should swap teams.
- Ji Hyo should have it...
so that she can
drag So Min off that team.
The ticket went to Ji Hyo.
What? If you hand it to me,
- I'll stay loyal to you.
- I'll do my best.
- Good luck.
Well, Jin is from Anyang.
- Anyang?
- Yes, he was born there.
- Are you from Anyang?
- I was born there.
- He was born there.
- Really?
- Around Indeokwon Intersection.
- No wonder.
- My gosh.
- Then it's already over.
- Is it?
- From this moment on,
Jin will be my bias. That's right.
Says the man living in Gangnam.
- Then...
- You never know.
Since our hometowns are the same...
- Thank you.
- And you got on the van first.
- That's fair.
- The ticket went to Jong Kook.
- Well...
- I should've gotten in his van.
We'll proceed with the first game
after you change.
- All right.
- Sure.
Jin, how are you at foot volleyball?
- Here.
- I'm not that good at it.
- You're not good at it?
- It's all right.
- I'm glad.
- Why?
- Because it'll be fun.
- I'm bad at this too.
Jin, come to me with any complaints.
- You're making him uncomfortable.
- They all answer to me.
They all answer to you?
- Yes, they do.
- Okay.
Here are the rules.
- Sure.
- Go for it.
The first game is...
the Global DNA Rule Foot Volleyball.
It'll be a three-on-three match...
of foot volleyball
but with an add-on rule.
- Three-on-three.
- Violate the rule,
and the opposing team will score.
There's an add-on rule?
When one team
first scores 11 points,
- the add-on rule will change.
- Eleven points?
The first team to reach
21 points will win.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook won't get mad...
- even if Jin messes up.
- You won't have to worry.
Come on.
We all make mistakes in life.
Messing up is part of the fun.
- That's how you get better.
- Of course.
- You know how it is.
- No one's perfect.
This game is particularly important
because the winning team...
will not only win tickets
but also today's lunch.
- Then we must win.
- Let's get us some lunch.
- The jjamppong...
- The city is known...
- for its jjamppong.
- Top three in the country.
- One of the top three.
- Stay put, will you?
Just eat what is served.
(Upset)
- We're just saying.
- But I want the jjamppong.
Eat what is served.
- We're just telling you that.
- Jae Suk.
- We want the jjamppong.
- You've changed.
Paju is famous for its jjamppong.
- Really?
- Whenever we film in Paju,
we always order...
- the jjamppong you love.
- Right?
Nice!
- I must say this though.
- What is it?
Shouldn't we have
what Jin wants to eat?
Jae Suk, I also love jjamppong.
The jjamppong here is famous.
- Don't make him uncomfortable!
- I just...
- He says he likes jjamppong.
- Have whatever you want.
- It's famous here.
- Jin, ask for whatever you want.
I go around
eating nice things all the time.
- I mean it.
- See?
He always eats the best food.
- Hear me out.
- He always eats the best food.
Since you're in Paju,
you should have the jjamppong here.
- Guys, you know this, right?
- Know what?
He's young and rich, guys.
Of course he is.
He's the wealthiest
out of all of us.
Shut it, Suk Jin!
Did you tell me to shut it?
Are you kidding me?
Must we shut it
if we're not wealthy enough?
Move! I'm the captain of this team.
(Old and poor Suk Jin
takes the back seat.)
This is Running Man,
so just accept what's happening.
Okay, got it.
I'm loving your teamwork.
- You...
- Move it, will you?
- How dare you.
- Move!
- Move, Suk Jin!
- You're not worthy enough.
Exactly. Don't let yourself
get caught on camera with him.
My gosh.
The winning team
will have jjamppong...
while the losing team
will have a packed meal.
- Okay.
- I want the jjamppong.
What is in the packed meal?
- Do we get ramyeon?
- No.
It'll be hard to eat it
without ramyeon.
We should at least get some ramyeon.
The losing team will be in tears.
Exactly. Jin, isn't it sad?
I should post on social media
about how harsh the staff is.
(A chilling joke)
That's right.
He doesn't mess around, does he?
- He's a fun one.
- Ramyeon should do it though.
- Exactly.
- We should at least get ramyeon.
- Spare the losing team.
- Tell me about it.
- On your left is the ticket booth.
- Right.
Anyone who has a ticket
can go up to it at any time...
and make the exchange.
- Can we swap out the captains?
- Really?
- Yes, you can.
- What?
Even the captains?
(Even the captains can swap teams.)
We can swap out the captains later.
We should wait
and swap teammates out later.
- To keep the team intact.
- Let's not waste the tickets.
Here's the first add-on rule.
(First add-on rule:
Speak only in English)
You are to only speak in English.
- Okay.
- If you're ready,
- please choose your three players.
- I see.
- How do I do?
- Can you speak English?
- Yes.
Speak in English? Okay.
- How do I look?
- Okay.
Can you speak Korean?
Korea, what?
- Korea.
- He said "Korean."
- The south, why?
- Go, South!
- South Korea.
Can you speak Korean?
- Why? I'm South Korean.
- We can only speak English.
- Okay, good.
- Do it.
- Let's do it.
- I can do it.
The add-on rule will now be applied.
It will now be applied.
You are to play, okay?
- Will you rest?
- I'll rest.
Sure. You rest.
Okay. I'll rest.
I'm defense.
Okay. Defense.
- You, offense.
- I'll take the side.
- The offense.
- Right, and you...
- Yes?
- Let's change places.
- Change it up.
- Play defense.
Let it bounce three times. Okay?
Yes.
Okay, let's go.
Game... Three of us.
- Three people.
- Three members.
- Okay.
- Right.
- So Min.
- Can I play?
- Sure.
- Okay!
We have to.
- We have to.
- I understand.
I can play!
Se Chan, aren't you playing?
No. I'll stay here.
- You'll stay?
- That's the rule.
- What about our positions?
- Positions?
You can stay right here,
and you can stay right here.
- Okay.
- I'm here.
- All right.
- Let's get it!
- Come on.
- Start.
(It begins with Jong Kook's serve.)
Okay, go.
- Okay.
- Nice.
Okay.
- Okay, you.
- Okay.
- Okay!
- Me!
- Hey, Jin.
- Okay, Jin.
- Okay!
- Out!
- It's okay.
- Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
- Sorry.
You did a good job.
Very good, Jin.
- Very good?
- You...
- You were very good.
- I'm sorry.
- Very good?
- Yes.
You played fantastically.
Okay, right. But I'm sorry.
My team first.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
What are you doing, Ji Hyo?
- Come on.
- What are you doing over there?
What are you doing right now?
Are you changing the teams up?
- Really?
- What are you doing?
What are you doing, Ji Hyo?
- I'll spend my ticket.
- What are you doing over there?
I'll swap teams with So Min.
Already?
Yes, I'll swap teams with her.
(She swaps teams with So Min
just like she planned.)
- Really?
- Yes.
Who?
- What are you doing?
- You're swapping teams?
Change.
- Who?
- Ji Hyo...
used the exchange ticket
to switch with So Min.
(So Min transfers
to Team Ji Suk Jin.)
Okay.
- Very good.
- Let's go.
- Goodbye.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Come on.
- Oh, no.
- Come here.
- Me too.
- Goodbye. Hello.
- Very good.
- Come on.
- Hey, So Min.
- Hey, Jin.
- What?
So Min is out. Why are you smiling?
Sorry.
(Well...)
- Okay.
- That's okay.
You're a referee. Okay?
Referee?
- Hey.
- Here.
- Your spot.
- You...
- You stay.
- Sit down.
- My home.
- Sit down please.
- Sit down.
- Hey.
- You're very small.
- You're glued here. Okay?
- Glue?
- Glue.
(He's telling her
not to move from here.)
- Let's go.
- It's a team play.
- Go.
- Okay. Play.
- Jin.
- Okay.
- You.
- Work hard, okay?
Mine?
Good.
(Ji Hyo's sudden smash)
Yes. Nice.
(Referee Jeon saved it.)
- Hey.
- You.
(Jong Kook's unexpected mistake)
- Hey. Go.
- What are you doing?
- What was that play?
- Ji Hyo.
- That was a terrible play.
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- Sorry. It's okay.
Ji Hyo did well.
- So Min. You did well.
- Yes.
Ji Hyo did well.
- You did well.
You were very nice.
- Well done. Okay.
- Unbelievable.
Let's go.
(They begin with Haha's serve.)
Go.
Why is that whistle so weak?
It was so weak.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Hurry up.
- Okay. Mine.
- Jin.
(Jin loses a point.)
Header.
- Jin.
- Mine.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
- It's 3 to 0.
- It's okay?
(That was okay?)
- Yes.
- That was okay?
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
- Jong Kook.
- Are you sure?
How come you don't blame him?
My leg is broken.
- Sorry.
- Why don't you blame him?
- Good. It's okay.
- Jin.
- Oh, my gosh.
- You're terrible.
- I'm terrible. Sorry.
He's terrible, but it's okay.
- Sorry.
- No.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
Do you have Instagram?
- Sorry.
- Good.
So sorry.
- No Instagram.
- No Instagram?
- You're very good.
- You're good.
- You're playing good.
- Okay.
- Instagram?
- You're very good.
- No Instagram.
- Instagram?
Just joking.
- I'm funny.
- No jokes.
- Come on. Hurry up.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- You.
- Great.
Okay. It's out. Good.
- Jong Kook.
- You're terrible.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo. You're terrible.
- You're terrible.
- You're the same.
- You're also terrible.
- Okay.
- Hey, referee.
- Go.
- What?
- Your zone.
- Excuse me.
Hey. Start the game.
Why? I'm lonely.
- Okay.
- Okay. Jin.
- Use your head.
- Good.
- Mine.
- All right.
- Good.
- Nice.
- Nice. Hey.
- Hey.
- Nice.
- Good.
- Very good.
- Nice teamwork.
- Good.
- Concentrate, okay?
- Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- Yes?
- Use your brain.
You want to use your brain?
Head touch play.
You want to use your stone brain?
- Oh, my gosh.
- Your head is a stone.
Your head is a stone.
- My head is a stone?
- Yes.
You have the bird's brain.
- A bird?
- A bird.
"A bird's brain."
You have the frog's face.
- The bird brain.
- Hey.
- Let's go.
- A chicken brain.
- "A chicken brain."
- Let's go.
Hey. Be quiet.
- I think...
- Jong Kook is...
I think...
you guys are too low level.
Let's change the rule.
Too low?
Hey.
- Thank you.
- Are we changing it?
- This time...
- "Low level?"
- How could you say that?
- We're doing our best.
- What?
Did you say "low level?"
- "Low level?"
- Okay. Good.
Just say no English is allowed.
This time, no English.
- Yes.
- That's better.
This is bad.
We've been talking in English.
- I'm very fluent in Korean.
- I'm used to it now.
I was about to be put off
by a few people.
A few people. All right.
- We can do it.
- Suk Jin. How about a switch?
What? Where?
- Sure.
- I'll play.
- Okay.
- No talking is the best.
- Let's go.
- Don't talk, everyone.
- All right.
- We'll go first.
- Let's go.
- It's hard not to use English...
even though we aren't fluent
in English.
All right. Let's go.
Ji Hyo. I'm sending it to you.
- Me? Why?
- Stand in front.
That's right. Good job.
- All right.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- It's me.
Hey.
(Jae Suk spoke in English
as soon as the game started.)
It only began, and you say okay?
- What did he do?
- Was it you?
- Good job.
- It's my habit.
- I say okay all the time.
- Just don't talk.
Good.
- Good.
- Very good.
- Okay.
- I won't talk.
- Very good.
From now on, if you make a mistake,
you're out.
- Let's do that.
- I'll just keep my mouth closed.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Get ready.
- I'll stay here.
- Good.
- Mine...
- I'll stay here.
- Good.
- Haha said mine.
- Mine?
- Why did you say mine?
"Mine" when you can't
even speak English?
- My name.
- This is nice.
- Good job.
- Good.
Good job.
Why do you keep using foreign words?
- He's right.
- Seriously.
- I'm sorry.
- Let's go.
There's no progress.
English...
- Who is it?
- So Min.
Hey!
Hey. That's the right direction.
- So Min.
- Hey.
(Header in the wrong direction)
- Hey. That's the right direction.
- Nice.
- Good.
- That was awesome.
- Very good.
- What are you doing?
I've never seen anything
like that before.
- Who do you think you are?
- Let me go.
- That was a suicide goal.
- How could you...
- Just don't play.
Haha. You just said "goal."
Why send it there?
- Suicide goal.
- I said own ball.
You said a goal.
- You get a point.
- That's good.
- Good. Very good.
- That's very good.
You're the Justice Pao.
It's nine to six.
- We're six?
- Get ready.
- What's our score?
- We've got to win this round.
- Focus.
- Haha.
Give me the ball no matter what.
Jae Suk. Pass it in two chances.
We got this.
We won.
Get ready.
- Pass in two chances.
- Hurry up.
The net.
- The net.
- Why did you say that?
- Here...
- You said the net.
- Why did you say that?
- He spoke in English.
Just now,
Jin said "net."
- He said it first.
- Okay.
- Suk Jin said it first.
- No.
- He said it first.
- It was Jin.
- They both said it.
- What are you talking about?
- He said it first.
- I didn't.
- I heard it. He said it first.
- He said it first.
- They both said it.
I'll give each team a point.
- Okay.
- Good.
- It's 10 to 7.
- No English.
- Let's go.
- Watch your mouth.
- Se Chan just spoke English.
Se Chan spoke English.
- Se Chan spoke English.
- Se Chan said "okay."
- Hey.
- Sorry.
- Sorry. I didn't realize it.
- Did you speak English?
- Sorry.
- Good.
- You can't even speak English.
- What's the score?
It's 10 to 8.
- Ten to eight.
- Okay.
- Good.
Haha said "okay."
- What is wrong with you?
- This is crazy.
- Get out of there.
- Haha.
- Hey.
- Get out.
- I can't take this anymore.
- Give me the ball.
You don't even dare to speak
when you go abroad.
- Can I switch with Se Chan?
- Yes.
Let's switch later.
- So Min is here.
- Haha.
- Right. So Min should change.
- I'll go in then.
- You may go in.
- You should move up.
- Good luck.
- English...
(Good luck.)
- Let's not talk.
- Okay.
- So Min said "good luck."
- Why...
Hey. Get lost.
(They're unable to start the game.)
- This is crazy.
- Why would you...
Do whatever you want.
- I'll bring a point.
- Go, my team.
(Go, my team.)
- Don't cheer.
- You said "team."
(She got caught for cheering.)
Don't cheer.
You said "team."
(Sighing)
(Sorry.)
- She chose another word, but...
- Don't talk.
Go, my colleagues.
- Go, my team.
- Let's go.
- Let me go. Then I won't talk.
- Go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Let's start.
- Let me go.
(Okay.)
- Why do you keep...
- Don't talk for goodness' sake.
- It was out of habit.
- Stop talking.
- Get ready.
- Don't talk.
- We can't kick the ball at all.
- Get ready.
Don't talk.
- Right.
- Do you want to do it?
Okay.
The score gap is huge.
(Because Team Suk Jin took turns
to speak in English,)
(the score gap is increased.)
We're going to win.
All right.
Nice.
You got it?
- Hey.
(Jae Suk lost a point
while trying to smash the ball.)
- Good!
That was necessary.
Good job.
Good job, team.
(Gasping)
(Jin's mistake evens it out.)
- Good.
- We can do it.
Jin, you said "team."
Okay.
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- That was humane.
- I should seal my mouth.
Good job, colleagues.
- You're barely talking.
- Good job, colleagues.
- Let's go.
Jin, you should try.
Jin, you should serve...
Why don't you stand
and kick the ball?
I don't think that's a good idea.
- It's okay, Jin.
- Try it.
- Can I do it as I want?
- Make yourself comfortable.
Good.
Right, you can do it.
- You got it.
- Try it.
- But...
- Make it bounce.
Make it bounce and...
- Try it.
- That's right.
This is nice.
Outside or inside?
(A basic question)
- Outside.
- Give it a try.
(The world star too busy traveling
around the world to play with balls)
- Give it a try.
- He really doesn't play with balls.
Good.
- It doesn't matter.
- That's great.
What are you playing right now?
(Trying to make him speak English)
(Be quiet!)
(His leading question
doesn't work at all.)
Send it.
How should I...
- Good.
(Team Suk Jin scored.)
(Yes!)
- Hey.
- That was nice.
- Nice.
- Yahoo.
Yahoo.
Don't speak.
- Here I go.
- Here we go.
Is it me?
I'll do it.
It went out.
- It went out.
- It's okay.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's fine.
- Let's go.
- My teammates, don't speak.
- Right.
- Close your mouth.
- Don't speak, teammates.
- Don't speak.
I'll do it.
- That was good.
- Attack.
(Smashing)
It's mine.
(Se Chan received.)
(Suk Jin kicks it back.)
Well done.
(Nervous for the 1st time
30 minutes after it began)
- Oh, gosh.
- This is nice.
In the back.
You can kick it over the net.
(Jae Suk has a chance to smash it!)
- Hey.
- You don't have to do that.
Why are you trying to show a trick?
Well done.
What's this?
Here we go.
(Team Jin is leading with
a bigger margin thanks to that.)
- It's mine.
- Yes. It's yours.
- Okay, Jae Suk.
- Oh, my.
What's wrong with you today?
- It went out.
- Your kicks are bad.
I didn't kick it
as I saw that it went out.
Good job.
What are the scores?
It's 20 to 14.
- They got one point left.
- Yes.
(If Team Jin scores one more time,
the game will be over.)
We must win. Let's try it.
One point. I'll end it.
- We must win. Let's do it.
- We got this.
- We'll end it like this.
- Let's focus.
- Do what like this?
- We'll end it.
Here I go, Suk Jin.
- What?
- Are you confident?
Did you say that to me?
- Hey.
- Suk Jin. Him.
- Suk Jin, here I go.
- This Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, I'm confident.
- "Here I go." That's for me.
No. It was
"Suk Jin, are you confident?"
- I'm confident.
- We got this.
- Great.
(Whistling)
Give it to us.
(Team Suk Jin earned 1 point
because of Se Chan's mistake.)
- Give it to us.
- It's 20 to 15.
- Suk Jin didn't answer.
Let's score just five points.
- Let's score just 5 points.
- Just 5 points.
Don't speak.
If you make a mistake, it's over.
Just one point.
- Be quiet.
- Just one point.
(The game to win one point
that will decide their fate)
Be careful not to speak English.
- Is it me?
- Yes.
Suk Jin.
(He flew!)
It touched the line.
(He flew powerfully, but the ball
touched the line and went out.)
- We made it.
- We won.
(Team Jin won.)
- We did it.
Let's pretend that it didn't happen
to make it fun.
It's not fun.
It's fun.
- Let's do it again to make it fun.
- It's so fun.
- It was fun.
- Let it slide.
The Bongsan Mask Dance was good.
- It was hasty.
- Let it slide.
Gosh, I'm disappointed.
(It was close, but they lost it
due to English and bad kicks.)
- Good.
- The winning team will pick...
- an exchange ticket.
- Yes.
Among 4 tickets, only 1 of them
is a real exchange ticket.
Go to the booth one at a time
and draw a ticket.
- Okay.
- The winning team only.
- One at a time?
- Yes.
- You go first.
- Me first? Okay.
Okay. What is it?
(He got a losing ticket.)
Gosh.
(Next is Se Chan.)
(Dud)
(He also got a losing ticket.)
Hello.
(Next is Jin.)
(How lucky is the superstar?)
(It's dud again.)
Nice.
- Did you get a good one?
- Yes, it's a good one.
(Ji Hyo goes in a relaxed manner
at the end.)
(She got an exchange ticket.)
(Golden Hand Ji Hyo
gets a good one regardless.)
All of you drew an exchange ticket.
As I told you, the winning team
will get jjamppong,
and the losing team
will have a lunchbox.
- I want to have jjamppong too.
- Move to the next room and eat.
- A lunchbox isn't bad, but...
- Okay. Jjamppong.
- Jjamppong.
I'm hungry.
It's a pity
that I can't have jjamppong.
Did you already start eating?
I'm just eating.
(Team Suk Jin
just got simple lunchboxes.)
- Did jjamppong not arrive yet?
- No.
Thank you for the food.
- I want to have jjamppong.
- Jjamppong must be good.
As I told you, only the winning team
will get jjamppong.
Please serve it.
That jjamppong.
The jjamppong is...
Look at this. Isn't it amazing?
This is incredible.
- Can we have more chopsticks?
- The broth must be so good.
- We got ones here.
- We got them.
- Isn't it amazing?
- This is incredible.
(A table full of Chinese food)
- It looks delicious.
- Yes.
It can't be bad with the broth.
- It's...
- It looks delicious.
It has arrived just now.
My goodness.
Gosh, this is...
Suk Jin...
(At that moment)
Suk Jin used an exchange ticket
to switch with Jin.
- What?
- He switched with who?
(From the beginning
when the jjamppong was served,)
(Seok Sam couldn't take his eyes
off of it.)
(He got up in the end.)
Excuse me.
I'd like to switch with Jin.
I want to have jjamppong.
(Bewitched by the smell
of jjamppong, he used the ticket.)
Suk Jin used an exchange ticket...
- Gosh.
- to switch with Jin.
- What?
- He switched with who?
- Isn't this crossing a line?
- With Jin?
- Jin, the lunchbox looks good.
- Why Jin?
- What?
- You should've picked another one.
- Why?
- Why do you not let him eat?
Suk Jin, stand still here.
I'll switch and come back.
- Stand still here.
- What are you talking about?
- Don't sit.
- Why?
- I'll switch too.
- He's so...
He should've switched
with another person.
- Why Jin?
- You should've chosen Se Chan.
- Pick Se Chan, not Jin.
- Right.
Why are you saying that?
So that you can eat there.
- I mean... Hey.
- Is he dumb?
I'll switch with Suk Jin.
(Bewitched by jjamppong, he didn't
think about what would happen next.)
- Jin will switch again.
- Right. My goodness.
He switched again,
so it's back to the original state.
- I'm sorry.
- He's so...
- I only got cursed.
- Jin got an exchange ticket.
- I'm sorry. I have to eat too.
- Right.
That's true.
- Suk Jin.
- Eat your food.
Why did he do that?
You're a fool, Suk Jin.
(Team Jin starts eating jjamppong
elegantly.)
Thank you for the food.
Jin is doing an eating show.
Jin, eat a lot.
Can we use the exchange ticket
until the end?
What are you doing, Jae Suk?
- What?
- I'm going to eat here.
(The jjamppong hunter squeezes
himself between them.)
The jjamppong does look good though.
Eat this.
- Can I?
- No.
Are we allowed to give them
pickled radish?
- Suk Jin.
I'm not eating pickled radish.
How about onion?
- Onion?
- How about chunjang?
You're quite a prankster too.
He's very playful.
I'm in charge of that in our group.
Suk Jin, do you want some too?
Is this squid?
- Hey, it's onion.
- I'm sorry. I thought it was squid.
It's onion, not squid.
There are circles and stuff.
I think we should guess something.
I think it's a quiz.
Suk Jin, are you good at quizzes?
I know a lot of common knowledge.
(Confidence)
- Do you?
- Are you sure?
For real.
Suk Jin, I'm so curious.
During the world tour,
you meet international superstars.
- Yes.
- Right.
I'm so jealous.
I thought
you were asking a question.
- It wasn't a question.
- You said you would ask something.
- Wasn't he going to ask something?
- Suk Jin.
I'm jealous.
Who were you fascinated by the most?
Suk Jin.
Famous celebrities would come
and ask for a photo, right?
- Who was it?
- Who? Tell us.
- Someone who is famous in Korea.
- Who is it?
In Korea?
- From another country.
- I can't remember the name.
- He's forgetful.
He has common knowledge,
but he's forgetful.
An actor or a singer?
What's the matter with you?
- Let's find out together.
- Suk Jin.
- A singer.
- A woman or a man?
- A man.
- Let's do a quiz.
- A man?
- A singer?
- R&B or what?
- A singer.
Pharrell Williams, no?
- It's not him.
- Snoop Dogg.
No.
What's his hit song?
What kind of songs did he release?
Rap songs?
- He does soul music.
- Soul music.
I know who he is. What was his name?
- Sam Smith.
- Bruno Mars.
- No.
- Bruno Mars? No.
- Anderson .Paak.
- What?
- No.
This happened years ago.
- Is he a singer from the past?
- Usher.
- Usher?
- It isn't Usher.
- Hold on.
- Nelly.
I might not know
even if I hear the name.
How many years ago was this?
- About three years ago.
- Three years ago. Hold on.
- Three years ago.
- Chris Brown.
No. It has been a few years
since his song became a hit...
- in Korea.
- Really?
(Clue: He is famous
in Korea as well.)
I know who he is.
I don't know. I was too focused.
(I don't know. I was too focused.)
Who was it?
Let me go and hear his name.
- John Legend.
- Let me go and hear his name.
I know John Legend.
- John Legend.
- I knew it.
(The answer is John Legend.)
- John Legend.
(John Legend!)
- I love John Legend.
- John Legend.
- I said it.
(The man who answered correctly
wants to be praised.)
- John Legend.
- I love John Legend.
- I said it.
- John Legend.
- That's right.
- I know who he is.
- John Legend.
- So it was John Legend.
- Go on.
- What happened?
We went
to John Legend's waiting room...
- to say hello.
- Okay.
He suddenly took out our album
from his backpack.
- Really? Did he do that?
- BTS' album.
He said his relative is a fan
and asked for our autographs.
John Legend.
- No way.
- That's incredible.
The Beatles?
(The Beatles?)
That's right. He is a member
of The Beatles.
- Isn't he a member of The Beatles?
- Really?
- What are you talking about?
- BTS' album.
Is that John Lennon?
Have you ever been invited
to someone's house? A home party.
- A famous celebrity.
- What kind of a question is that?
That's the worst question.
- A home party?
- Hurry up and tell us.
- I did get invited.
- Like a house with a pool.
I did get invited, but I didn't go.
- Why not?
- Who was it? Who invited you?
I don't remember.
- Tell us.
- Let's guess who it is.
- Who is it?
- Let's guess.
- Was it a man or a woman?
- Tell us.
- He doesn't have good memory.
Jin, tell us.
Have you been on a yacht?
- A yacht?
- "Have you been on a yacht?"
- Yes, I have.
- I have been on a yacht too.
We have been on a yacht for a show.
- I mean... A yacht party.
- A yacht party.
I haven't been to a party.
I guess he doesn't party much.
Jin is very...
- He is down-to-earth.
Aren't you an I type?
- E?
- INTP.
See? I can recognize
a fellow I type.
- Are you an I type?
- It's ISFP.
- No way.
- You are a fellow I type.
Jae Suk is an ugly I type
and Jin is a handsome I type.
Jin, my MBTI type is INFP.
INFP? We are friends.
Jin, I am an I type too.
- Same here.
- IN.
(Haha, an E type)
- Why?
- An immature I type.
Why are all these celebrities
an I type?
- He is an E type.
- Are you an E type?
- An ugly I type, a handsome I type.
- I am an E type.
- I see.
- Then you are an old E type.
(Then you are an old E type.)
He is an old E type.
- An ugly I type, a handsome I type.
- I.
- An old E type.
- A short I type.
- He loves it.
- A short E type.
- He is a short E type.
- A young E type.
- A short E type.
- I am a young E type.
A short E type.
I want to hear more from Jin.
- Let's keep going.
- What do you want to know?
- Ask me anything. Ask me.
- That's right.
- Will you tell us all?
- I will tell you what I know.
- He doesn't know much.
- You don't remember.
- I can do it.
- Can you do it?
- I will tell you what I know.
- He doesn't know much.
- Really?
Let's say you are giving
a performance.
- Hey.
- Famous celebrities...
Jin, what kind of food
do you get on a private jet?
- Hey.
- Famous celebrities...
Jin, what kind of food
do you get on a private jet?
I was asking a question diligently.
I can't believe she interned it.
What was that?
"I can't believe she interned it."
I can't believe she intercepted it.
He couldn't pronounce "Intercept."
Let's say you take the stage
at an award ceremony.
- Stop already.
- Did other nominees...
ever glare at you?
They usually don't glare.
Maybe they got jealous.
Did they ever do that?
This is a miraculous moment.
- I can't believe the fact...
- This is impressive.
- that Jin is here with us.
- You know,
both BTS and Running Man
are incredible.
That's right. Hey, Hyung In.
Give him 50 more dollars
for this week's episode.
(Give him 50 more dollars
for this week's episode.)
- Give him 50 more dollars.
- Deduct the money from his share.
- Don't be like that.
- Hyung In is okay with that.
- Deduct the money from my share.
- Give him 50 more dollars.
- Deduct the money from his share.
- Hey. Use it to buy jjamppong.
- In that case...
Then Suk Jin will only get
150 dollars this month.
- How will you get by?
- It's okay.
- Hey.
- Give Jin more money.
I will give you
a quarter of my share.
Were you getting 200 dollars?
Yes. They say
they will give me a raise.
My heart aches.
- It's okay.
- He is getting a lot.
He enjoys working.
- It's better than staying at home.
- That's right.
What's the use of being idle?
- What's the use of being idle?
- It's better to come here...
- and get paid.
- You are right.
I am so proud.
- Jin is here with us.
- He is cool.
He is lovely.
- You are incredible.
- Seriously.
- You are my hero.
- BTS is the best.
- Do you know how nice Jin is?
- That's right.
- Jin...
- Suk Jin, stop it already.
Jin... I am a witness.
Jin...
Suk Jin, I want to play games now.
- Okay.
- If that's what you want, okay.
That was neat.
During the next mission,
things will get heated up.
It's "No, It's Fire."
- All right.
- The first player...
will pick a member
of the opposing team...
and attack with words
he or she can't accept easily.
The attacked member
will say, "No..."
and use words and actions
to dispute the claim.
Then he or she will attack
a member of the opposing team.
If the defending member
can't think of a reason...
or say something unreasonable,
it will be minus one point.
If the attacking member
misses the timing...
or fails to say something,
it will be minus one point.
If you can't accept my call,
these three production crew members
will decide.
- Okay.
- We just need to say, "No."
We need to dispute
the words blindly.
- "You are handsome." "No."
- "No."
- We can attack that way.
- "You are handsome."
- "No."
- "I am ugly."
- "I am ugly." That's how you play.
- If you can dance well...
Who says "No."
- No.
- I say that often.
That's annoying. That's so annoying.
- No. I say, "No."
- No.
- What?
- He will switch places.
- He will use a ticket.
- With whom will he do that?
- "No. I am ugly."
- He will use a ticket.
With Suk Jin,
I will change places.
- Did he change places?
- He will join this team.
- He changes places.
- With whom did he do that?
Jin used an exchange ticket.
He changed places with Suk Jin.
(He changed places with Suk Jin.)
(The two captains change places.)
(Jin leaves for the members
with a way with words.)
Come back later.
Jin, you should experience
that kind of team.
- That's right.
- You should experience it.
Join that team.
I can't attack the older members.
- Okay.
- He is wise.
- Good call.
- I am the oldest member.
You are right.
- How strange.
- Jin made the perfect call.
- Yes. It's fun to tease Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin is...
- the perfect target.
- Yes.
Jin, get changed.
You knew that they attack me a lot.
All right.
(Haha approaches him.)
Thank you, Haha.
You are wild.
- Hey.
- What?
Give it here.
(He gets apprehended
for stealing a uniform.)
- You caught me.
- Hey.
I am sorry, Jae Suk.
This will be the dance.
- No.
We should do this instead.
Let's begin.
- No.
- It looks strange.
- It's too complex.
- Will you do this?
- We will do this.
- Isn't this too complex?
- How about this?
No.
- I love it.
- Hey.
- No.
- It's the "Fire" dance.
- "Fire."
- Jin, show us the dance.
Show us the original dance.
I want to go back to that team.
- Don't do that.
- You feel uncomfortable, right?
- Come here.
- They don't stay still.
- Give it a go.
- No.
I want to go back to that team.
- It's nice.
- Come here.
- You don't have a ticket anymore.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
- No.
Jae Suk, you like BTS.
I love the group so much.
- Fire
- You should say, "No."
I love the group so much.
Fire
- You should say, "No."
- "No."
(You should say, "No.")
- Is he a fool?
- He is intimidated.
(He was so nervous
that he forgot the basic rules.)
(The teammates give Jin a headache
in different ways.)
You should say, "No."
- What was that?
- You must have been scared.
- He couldn't say, "No."
- Do I say, "No?"
- "No."
- That's the game.
- Okay.
- Right.
- That's how you play the game.
- I get it now.
I get it now.
That's how you play the game.
That's how things go.
You didn't know, did you?
- No.
So Min, you don't have a boyfriend.
- Say that you have one.
- No. I have one.
- Who is he?
- He is over there.
- No. I am not her boyfriend.
- No.
- He is over there.
- No. I am not her boyfriend.
- No.
Yes. You are her boyfriend.
- I am not her boyfriend.
- No.
Behind the set,
you guys held hands earlier.
- No.
- You guys held hands earlier.
- My goodness.
- Yes.
- Don't lie. We didn't hold hands.
- Your fingers were intertwined.
- We didn't hold hands.
Se Chan, you hate me, right?
No. I like you so much.
Here is a heart.
(Catfish's careless confession
annoys her.)
(That's so funny.)
That's strange.
- That's no fun. I don't like it.
- No.
- I am her boyfriend today.
- He is your boyfriend today.
No, he isn't.
He is her boyfriend today.
- No.
Haha, you like BTS, right?
(Haha, you like BTS, right?)
(No.)
It's okay.
- Hey.
- Just say it.
(He can't bring himself to say no.)
- Hey.
- Just say it. It's a game.
It's a game.
Just say, "No."
Are you going to be like that?
Let's go.
Let's begin.
- No.
Suk Jin, you are handsome, right?
No. I am really ugly.
(He makes an effort.)
- He looks cute.
Shouldn't you deduct a point?
It should still count.
- No.
Jong Kook,
you like to work out, right?
No.
I like to lie down all the time.
I can even lie down right now.
(Lying down)
(The pose doesn't suit
Jong Kook at all.)
He doesn't like to work out.
No.
So Min, your bangs are
very pretty, right?
No. They aren't pretty at all.
They make me look like Yeong Goo.
- No.
Jong Kook, you are good
at soccer, right?
You are good at soccer, right?
No.
I have lousy feet.
No. I have lousy feet.
(The lousy feet performance)
(He disputed Haha's words easily.)
- No.
Jin, you like
the leader of BTS, RM, right?
No.
I am pretty sure I dislike him.
How is he so smart?
He is annoying.
- That was nice.
- That was nice. Good job.
- Okay. It's only a game.
- That was nice.
I don't need to apologize, right?
- Of course not.
- Of course not. It's only a game.
- No.
Suk Jin, are you 40 years old now?
No.
I will turn 60 next year.
(I will turn 60 next year.)
- I actually won't turn 60.
- You need to show an action.
- "I will turn 60 next year."
- Good job.
- Come to think of it,
- You need to show an action.
I actually won't turn 60.
- Seriously.
- You are close...
- to that age.
- No.
That was nice. Let's begin.
Jae Suk, you think
you are really handsome, right?
- No. I am totally ugly.
- That counts.
- I agree.
(His very existence
quickly convinces everyone.)
- It's true.
- I agree.
- You shouldn't get angry.
- This is only a game.
- Correct.
- I shouldn't get angry.
- It's true.
- There is no need to get angry.
- No.
Se Chan, you think
you are uglier than me, right?
No.
- I am handsome.
- Let's see.
- Why?
- I am handsome.
- Let's see.
- Why?
- Why? It's up to him.
- I have...
- I have my own preference.
- Hey.
- He has unique charms.
- I am handsome.
- Hey.
- My jaw is pretty.
- It's rare among comedians.
- It was ridiculous.
All three judges held up the X sign.
- Okay.
(Team Suk Jin lost 1 point.)
- No.
- We can go slow.
- Ji Hyo,
you don't like Jong Kook, do you?
No.
I really love Jong Kook.
What?
No. I really love Jong Kook.
- What?
- My goodness.
It's love.
- It's real.
- Accept it.
- What was that?
- It's true love.
(They never expected to see
such a fun sight.)
(Truly happy)
- What was that?
- It's true love.
- It's love.
- It's a game.
- Gosh.
- Accept it.
- You did something similar.
Accept it.
She went overboard.
(Glaring)
- My stomach hurts.
- No.
Haha, you are happily married,
right?
No.
- Why?
- Aren't you happy?
- At times, I want to take off.
(At times, I want to take off.)
That counts.
- That counts.
- I want to take off.
Both Jae Suk and Suk Jin
said that.
So we decided to take a trip
by ourselves next month.
- No.
- I won't go!
- He says he won't go.
- I will stay at home!
- He suggested the trip.
- I hate traveling the most.
- No!
- I heard it.
I hate traveling so much.
(Team Jin resumes.)
That was funny.
- No.
Suk Jin,
you want to continue being
a member of Running Man, right?
(You want to continue being
a member of Running Man, right?)
- No.
- Good job.
Next week's shoot will be my last.
Bye, everyone.
(He gets caught up
and says goodbye.)
Is that why we are doing this today?
Hey.
(He announced
that he will leave the show.)
- I see.
- Suk Jin, this isn't real.
- I see. That's very nice.
(The game ends with Suk Jin's
shocking announcement.)
- Okay.
- It's minus 4 to minus 6.
- Team Jin won.
- Okay.
You are the fairy of victory.
My team always wins.
- You are the fairy of victory.
- Yes.
- You need more exchange tickets,
- so the winning team will get two.
- Okay.
The losing team will get one.
Let's go first.
(One member of Team Suk Jin
will get an exchange ticket.)
Will we get one?
I might get it.
- Please take turns to pick one.
- Is it random?
(Two members of Team Jin
will get an exchange ticket.)
You should save up
on the exchange tickets.
Okay. The floor is slippery.
Is it soap water?
I guess...
we need to do something fast
when the pirate pops out.
Good.
I think someone wore
the socks I took off.
Who did that?
- The socks I took off...
- Se Chan...
Se Chan did it because he likes you.
I like you.
- I only have eyes for you
- Stop it.
- So Min.
- I only have eyes for you
Stop it.
- So Min's socks.
- So Min looks happy.
Did you take my socks?
Where did my socks go?
I only have eyes for you
I am sorry.
Jin, come here.
- I am sorry.
- Why would you be sorry?
- Don't be sorry.
- We are the ones who came early.
- That's right. We came early.
I won't sit still
if you say that again.
Why did everyone come early...
- and make him feel uncomfortable?
- Seriously.
- Sit down.
- You are right.
- Why did everyone come early?
- Seriously.
You are right.
Why did everyone come early?
- Seriously.
- That's right.
We came early
for some strange reason.
- Go along with us like that.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- Go along with us like that.
- You are right.
- We shouldn't have come early.
I didn't do anything wrong.
- Of course not.
- It's true. Don't be sorry.
He is so nice.
He didn't do anything wrong.
Both Team Suk Jin and Team Jin
lost once.
Both teams have three penalty balls.
- Okay.
- This is the last mission.
This time, only the losing team...
- will get three penalty balls.
- Okay.
For the last mission, you must move
like an astronaut in space.
It's the Astronaut on Soap Water.
(Astronaut on Soap Water)
What is she saying?
(What is she saying?)
Two members of each team
will enter each round.
All members will be connected
by their waists.
Acquire the pirate roulette knives
in the balloons...
and stick them
in your team's pirate roulette.
Your team wins
if the pirate pops out first.
- I see.
- Okay.
- We will win.
- It needs to pop out first.
- We have an advantage.
We have you, Jae Suk.
- Win 2 rounds for victory. Yes.
- Did you say 2 rounds?
For fairness,
the players will be decided
by the opposing team.
- How will we do this?
- So Min will surely get included.
- Yesterday, I did it at home.
- Do you pop the balloons?
- The pirate popped out quickly.
- The pirate roulette?
- Yes.
- You pop the balloons.
How do you do it?
- It just pops out.
- You just need to be unlucky.
You just need to be unlucky like me.
Do you try
the pirate roulette at home?
- Seriously.
- I have it at home.
He practices at home.
Firstly, please choose...
the members of the opposing team
who will enter the first round.
Suk Jin.
So you want to win this round.
No. Don't say that.
- You are good.
That's right. You might win.
- That's right.
- The two who didn't get picked...
this time will enter the next round,
- so try to balance things out.
- We will do that. Okay.
- Let's pick Suk Jin and Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Suk Jin and me? Okay.
- Yes.
- It will be fun.
- Okay.
Shall we make it a match
between the two Suk Jins?
- Jin versus Jin.
- Jin.
- How about Jin and Jae Suk?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Come on out.
Let's go. You need to win, okay?
Let's do this.
- Good luck.
- Yes.
- Jin, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Okay.
Kim Suk Jin!
- Kim Suk Jin!
- Let's go.
- The best Suk Jin, Ji Suk Jin.
- The Gwangsan Kim Clan.
(The game starts.)
- This is hard.
- What are you doing?
(Trainer Kim easily acquires
a balloon.)
Hey, come here.
Hurry up.
Jin, I love the slapstick comedy.
(Jin shows slapstick comedy first.)
- This is hard.
- What are you doing?
They are outmatched.
- Go over there.
- Hurry up.
- Hey, hurry up.
- Jin.
(It's a one-sided match.)
Suk Jin, get the other balloon.
(Jong Kook goes
for the yellow balloon.)
Get the other balloon.
Hurry up and grab it.
- Come here.
- Grab it.
- Where did it go?
- It's here.
- Grab it.
- Hurry up.
Jin.
(Growling)
(With a scary facial expression,
he pushes in the first knife.)
Did you do it? Hurry up.
Jae Suk, hurry up and pull it.
What's this?
Hurry up and go.
(Jumping)
(Giggling)
Jin is enjoying this.
Jin, go!
Go!
(Slipping)
- What's this?
- They are no match.
(Kim Suk Jin is
the same as Ji Suk Jin.)
- He is like a paper doll.
- They are no match.
- Suk Jin.
- Grab this.
- Why? Is it ours?
- Yes.
(Screaming)
(Everyone gets pulled
in Jong Kook's direction.)
Is this ours?
(The paper doll is busy
falling down.)
(Meanwhile, Team Suk Jin
gets more knives.)
It's here.
What?
(Dizzy)
(Horrendous)
(He doesn't care.)
(Running with knees)
(While Jae Suk's balloon
is in danger,)
(Jong Kook tries again.)
Gosh, why is it not working?
(He stuck many swords,
but the pirate won't come out.)
Where are they?
- Where are they?
- I got them. I saw them.
(Jin found many swords
at that moment.)
Jae Suk, there's a lot here.
- Suk Jin.
- There's a lot here.
- Give them to me.
- Where are they?
- There you go.
There's a lot here.
(Jin still stuck one sword.)
Suk Jin.
Hey. Suk Jin.
(Jong Kook got more swords.)
I trust my luck.
(On the other hand,
Jae Suk hasn't stuck anything yet.)
Why does it not burst?
(It's about time
for it to come out.)
(It's already the 10th sword.)
The other side.
(Will it come out this time?)
Here.
Give it to me.
(Jae Suk can reach
the pirate for now.)
- Jae Suk.
- This is crazy.
Come out.
I hope Jae Suk's come out.
Ours won't come out.
(Both teams need more swords.)
It's here.
(He took all of them.)
Jae Suk, I took everything.
Where are they?
Suk Jin.
- Do you have more?
- Two. On the other side.
- Hurry and stick it.
- The other side.
Here.
Jae Suk can do it.
- Hurry and stick it.
- The other side.
We'll win if we just do this.
(Did it really pop up?)
Did it come out?
We'll win if we just do this.
(He got it.)
- We won.
- Did it come out?
We won.
- We won.
- I knew it.
(Jae Suk did it
exactly at the 2nd try.)
Seriously...
He's incredible.
- This is unbelievable.
- I stuck so many swords.
This is unbelievable.
(The come-from-behind victory
made by an unlucky guy)
- This is luck.
- He's indeed BTS.
(Being mean)
Team Jin won.
- Okay.
(Team Jin won.)
I got dragged helplessly.
Isn't it amazing?
How many swords did you put in?
- I stuck so many swords.
- We stuck ten.
(Three swords, Twelve swords)
I'm amazing.
- We stuck so many swords.
- I played the game with my kids.
I made it pop up every time.
(Proud)
(He's almost a dog
that searches dud.)
I think I got something for it.
This is really a hard game.
(Haha and So Min,
Ji Hyo and Se Chan)
You're so lucky.
- Isn't it amazing?
- It's amazing.
Se Chan used an exchange ticket...
- to switch with So Min.
- Okay.
(Se Chan from Team Jin
and So Min from Team Suk Jin)
I'd like to switch with So Min.
(Ssaebssaeb switched immediately
after his team lost round 1.)
(Happy)
Hey.
I'll win.
He picked Jin.
- It's a perfect victory.
- A perfect victory.
You chose a winning path.
- I choose a winning path.
- You chose a winning path.
If you don't use the ticket,
it will become useless.
You're so...
He's the best.
- Se Chan, take this.
- Okay.
(Se Chan, take the Team Red outfit.)
Yes.
Gosh.
My feet are cold.
Can I use an exchange ticket?
You can use it over there.
Did you use it?
- I guess so.
- Ji Hyo used an exchange ticket...
- to bring Se Chan back.
- Come here.
- I should win.
- Yes.
- I should win now.
- We should win.
(Ji Hyo who has to win
summons Se Chan again.)
Stick them as you want.
We'll win then.
Okay.
We should win this time.
Right. Let's do a 2-on-2.
What happened?
- Suk Jin used the ticket again.
- Okay.
Haha and Ji Hyo will switch.
We should win.
Hey, this is fun.
Haha and Ji Hyo will switch.
(It's girls versus boys again.)
- We should win!
- Hey, this is fun.
- We should win.
- Right. We should win.
Haha, this is what I wanted
in the end.
Gosh. Haha is so strong.
(Screaming)
(Little One starts playing Jong Kook
against the girls.)
My balloon.
- He's so...
- Teasing me and calling me short.
These guys...
Where are you going?
- Where are you going?
- Se Chan.
Where are you going?
You punks!
(At that moment)
Where are you going?
(An uninvited guest
rushed into the place.)
You punk.
(He starts taking his revenge
with wrestling skills.)
Who are you to...
(The big guy from the opposing team
came as well.)
Why are you messing it up?
My gosh.
(During the chaos)
Ji Hyo.
- Come on.
- Ji Hyo.
(Haha is peacefully
sticking swords.)
That's bad manners.
What is that?
Gosh, why won't it come out?
(The pirate got stabbed many times
already.)
- Hey.
- It came out.
(The pirate escaped.)
We're Kim Jong Kook.
(Little Jong Kooks won in the end.)
Okay. We're done.
- Well done.
- You're so uncool.
We were perfect.
- We were the best duo. Okay.
- It was so cool.
We have no rival in the world.
- That was so sexy.
- That was nice.
You guys won in a cool manner.
- Yes.
- Okay.
The production team acknowledged us.
It's not cool at all.
Let's play the last round.
Two people from each team
can volunteer.
- Jong Kook and...
- Okay.
Jong Kook and Se Chan.
Okay. Se Chan and me.
- It's going to be fun.
- I'll be doing it.
It's Suk Jin and me.
- What?
- Suk Jin and I should do it.
Yes.
Let's just get a few and...
Jong Kook came out again.
Even Se Chan came out.
Let's hurry up and go home.
Let's do it at the first attempt
and have a thrilling win.
(Which team will win?)
- Let's do it. The final.
- Let's do it.
- Are you ready?
- ARMYs around the world will cheer.
(Go.)
You got this.
(Shouting)
(It's going exactly the same
as how round 1 went.)
(Se Chan bursts a balloon
comfortably.)
Collect all of them.
Hold them.
(Two-on-one tug-of-war)
My goodness. What's this?
(Shouting)
Collect all of them.
(Tripping)
(It's a balloon!)
(Popping)
(Crying)
(Paper Doll
is crying his lungs out.)
They're no match. My gosh.
I'm sorry.
(Shouting)
I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
What?
(Trying to cheat)
Give it to me.
What? Is it not out?
(The two became fitness equipment
for the gym-goer in the town.)
Is it not out?
(Meanwhile, Se Chan
starts attacking the pirate.)
Come here.
Stick them.
Wait.
Come here.
Okay.
(It came out.)
(Team Suk Jin won.)
It was perfect.
Okay.
They're so annoying.
(Team Jin couldn't stick
a single sword in the end.)
- Are you okay, Jin?
- Okay.
- Are you all right?
- I'm mad.
I wanted to put just one sword in.
I'm so upset.
(Jae Suk
went to stick just one sword.)
I'm so upset.
(Popping up)
You did it at once again?
If I had one more chance...
This is Running Man.
They're strong.
- You're on my team.
- The mission is over.
- Team Suk Jin won.
- Okay.
- The winners will get 1 ticket.
- We get 1 ticket?
Pick a ticket, one at a time.
- One ticket?
- Okay.
It's a pity.
Right?
(Whistling)
So Min used an exchange ticket...
so switch with Haha.
- I can't pick a ticket then?
- No.
I can't pick a ticket?
(Shouting)
(Ha Jong Kook throws her
to vent his anger.)
Those with exchange tickets...
We can draw just one, right?
Someone used it again.
Haha and So Min should switch.
- Okay.
- Why?
- Se Chan picked him.
- He picked him.
- Okay. It might not be a penalty.
- Okay.
If they get the penalty,
- that's amazing.
- I know.
What should I do? I hope
they receive a penalty.
- We don't know yet.
- I hope they receive the penalty.
I'll reveal the number
of penalty balls right now.
- Okay.
- I think we got a lot.
Team Red got six penalty balls.
Okay.
- Team Green got half of it, three.
- Okay.
Okay. It's good.
If they get it,
So Min will look more annoying.
- I hope you get a penalty.
- Yes.
We'll now draw the penalty ball.
(Drawing the penalty ball)
Please.
Here it is.
(The color of the ball determines
the team for the penalty.)
I will reveal the result.
Team Jin lost.
- Okay!
Okay!
(Everyone in Team Jin
gets a penalty.)
Nice. There was no twist.
Bring in the penalty item.
It must be paint.
- It's the whipped cream.
- That's better.
(The whipped cream machine enters.)
- No, it's whipped cream.
- It's whipped cream.
- I think it's better.
- It's a relief.
(At that moment)
(Kim Suk Jin visits the booth.)
I think he has an exchange ticket.
I'll switch with...
(There was an important announcement
about the booth use.)
(As long as the booth is open,
the exchange ticket can be used.)
(I'll switch with...)
(The booth was still open.)
(Jin saved his exchange ticket
until the penalty was determined.)
Wait a minute.
I should've saved
the exchange ticket.
You should've saved it.
Jin just used...
- the last exchange ticket.
- He just used it.
He's switching with Se Chan.
(Se Chan)
What?
(What?)
- Come here.
- Jin.
This is my first time meeting him.
Se Chan. You're the youngest.
- Okay.
- You're the youngest.
He's moving
to his girlfriend's team.
Get the penalty
with your girlfriend.
Four people should stand.
Everyone in the team gets a penalty.
It's been a while. I've missed you.
Webfoot octopus?
Again? Who?
(Who used the exchange ticket?)
- Who is it?
- Jong Kook...
- used his exchange ticket.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook saved
his exchange ticket.)
Se Chan and Suk Jin are switching.
Okay!
(Se Chan and Suk Jin
are switching.)
(Ji Suk Jin is getting
the penalty.)
(After Jin and Se Chan switched...)
Good job.
(No look pass)
I'll switch with Suk Jin.
(Se Chan backstabbed Captain Ji
who was acting annoying.)
- You were too...
- In the end,
I'm getting the penalty
for Suk Jin.
I don't mind.
No, that's not how it works.
- Jin, I don't mind.
- No.
Jin, it's okay.
You're doing it for Se Chan.
- No.
- You're doing it for Se Chan.
I didn't say anything, Suk Jin.
- I knew it. Thank you, Suk Jin.
- Thank you.
Here we go. Seriously.
Careful with the aim,
so you can get it at once.
- Thank you, Jong Kook.
- Does it hurt?
- No.
- You saved me. I knew it.
One,
two, three.
Suk Jin. That's too little.
(Suk Jin looks different.)
I'm sorry. It went up.
- See?
- What are you doing?
- It went up.
- Seriously.
- Why did you make it go up?
- Suk Jin.
- I still got hit.
Let's do it again
after hearing from Jin.
Still, you can't do that.
Suk Jin ruined it.
Jin. I'll do it again for...
Where is he?
- Yes?
- Jin. I'll do it again for you.
Suk Jin. You can do it
three more times if you want.
You're doing this for us.
What?
Close your trap.
Why is this for you?
(Getting angry)
Jae Suk got it perfectly.
- Why would you curse?
- When did I curse?
You just did.
Let's hear from Jin first.
I've always wanted to be
on Running Man.
Thank you so much for inviting me.
This is my favorite show.
Send lots of love to Running Man.
If you love my episode,
I'd really app...
- Appreciate it.
- Thank you.
- That's what I like about you.
- Yes.
- It's humane.
- No one is perfect.
- Of course.
- That's your charm.
- One, two,
- Come forward.
three.
This is what I'm talking about.
Good job, everyone.
Good job.
(Thanks to Superstar Jin
for his appearance.)
- Thank you.
(This fall arrived later
than usual.)
(FW hot trend fashion show
in the middle of Seoul)
(Are you a carrot?)
(Fashion keeper)
Not everyone...
(However, not everyone can
wear fall clothes.)
(Today, they're going to
look for fall.)
(Like this.)
(In the sight of fall foliage,)
(the cool breeze blows.)
(It's so cold.)
(A quiz with citizens...)
(in the season for reading)
(You're very intangible.)
(They're purely embarrassing.)
(They're getting far away
from their destination.)
(Will they...)
(be able to go home today?)
- Close your mouth.
(Looking For Fall)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)