(3 days before the shoot)
(A rainy Friday night)
- Isn't that it?
- No.
I think fortune-telling is...
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hey.
(The empty seat was for Se Chan.)
- Are we starting right away?
- Yes.
What's going on?
Gosh, I was surprised.
This is funny. This doesn't
happen a lot on Running Man.
It feels like we're shooting abroad.
I know.
It's funny that you and I
are doing something together.
It feels like we're shooting abroad.
Captain Ji picked you two for us.
- The two of us?
- Yes.
- For what?
- Why?
This is Captain Ji's
last race as a captain.
That's what we don't have on Running Man.
We don't have to play games every time.
How did you come up with all these games?
The writers of Running Man
need to take a break.
Whatever Running Man does
is what Running Man is.
- Then what do we do?
- Like what?
We should think about it now.
(We should think about it now.)
- On your last week as a captain...
- Yes.
- Only the members?
- Yes. The thing is,
- we were inspired by you.
- Like what?
You guys will just have fun.
You can play games
to decide who will do the dishes.
- I'd love that.
- Anything you want.
I've always wanted to do things like this.
- Like a school trip.
- Exactly.
What do you think
the members can try then?
You would need to suggest a theme though.
For players, it is easier that way.
You can't just tell them to have fun.
- You could give them a jegi.
- Okay.
- It's me.
- Hey.
- Captain Ji.
- You guys are having a meeting.
That's right.
Is there anything you need to decide?
Yes. I'd like you...
to pick a few members
who can discuss things with us.
- Well... I think Ji Hyo...
- Yes.
(Ji Hyo)
- and Se Chan.
- Why?
I guess these two are the least busy ones.
(I guess these two are
the least busy ones.)
He said you two are...
the least busy ones.
I'm the busiest one here.
- Ji Hyo.
- I'm busy.
You sleep a lot...
So he thinks we are like leftovers.
Ji Hyo, he thinks you and I are leftovers.
- So we should...
- That's ridiculous.
(He calls Captain Ji feeling upset.)
All right. Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
- What?
Suk Jin, I'm with Ji Hyo now.
- Suk Jin.
- Ji Hyo?
- Yes.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
(Yes, I can see you.)
- Do you see me?
Yes, I can see you.
Why do you look so horrible today?
Why is your face all swollen?
What's the problem?
You need to put on some makeup.
(Something needs to be done
about Captain Ji's face.)
Suk Jin. Isn't this his first time
to show his bare face?
Suk Jin, do you not mind
showing your bare face like this?
My face has always been an issue.
I guess he's right.
Suk Jin.
What are you two doing?
What's with him? Suk Jin.
You made us plan an outing.
You picked us.
If you were going to stay home,
- you should've joined the meeting.
- You should come.
I worked my socks off.
Gosh, Suk Jin...
You're the captain.
You should attend the meeting.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Hang on.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
I don't think it's a meeting.
You're just having dinner.
No, we are...
You're not committed to this.
What are you talking about?
You can't come up with
good ideas when you are full.
What do you know about meetings?
You should stay hungry for good ideas.
You can't eat that.
The destiny of Running Man
is in your hands now.
What are you talking about?
You just put it on us.
I did put it on you.
He's scratching his body.
- Gosh.
- This episode is up to you.
Why is it up to us?
You're the captain.
- Why is it up to us?
- This isn't about us.
Is there anything
you want to try with the members?
We could have some drinks on an outing.
What do you want to do on an outing?
Let's have some beef barbecue.
- Isn't that nice?
- That sounds like a good idea.
Everyone likes beef. All our members do.
How about we make Suk Jin cook for us?
Suk Jin will cook ramyeon for us.
It would be nice if we had
things like a popularity award.
We don't need a big prize.
Something we can use at home.
- Like detergent.
- I see.
- A prize like tissues.
- Tissues.
- Detergent.
- Tissues sound good.
That would be the best.
When we get there,
it will be fun to wear a uniform.
It will bring us together.
A team uniform? It's a little...
I know it will bring us together, but...
I want to play the Informal Talk Game.
If we play the Informal Talk Game,
So Min and you will be first in line.
We will be first in line.
I'll be number one.
I don't want to do it.
(She suddenly feels tired.)
- You should use honorifics.
- You should use honorifics to me.
Why don't we write down our complaints?
(An idea for their outing,
writing down complaints)
- Anonymously?
- Yes, anonymously.
- I guess you have many complaints.
- No.
Who do you hate now?
- Who is it you hate?
- Haha?
- No.
She's not saying anything.
There must be someone.
Or you could suggest that...
they decide on seniority for the day
before we start.
We can play games
to decide seniority for the day.
Do you think it's possible
to have Jong Kook below you?
- Jong Kook?
- Yes.
He's too stubborn. You know that.
He wouldn't listen to me.
It's impossible. He's too stubborn.
You know him.
"All right, Ji Hyo. Okay, I'll do it."
"Would this work?"
Then he would throw a tantrum.
"Do you want me to eat this or what?"
"All right." He would be like this.
It's not going to work.
- Forget it.
- I know. Forget about it.
Let's not do that.
- I guess this is it.
- Okay.
- Clap once.
- One, two, three.
(And 3 days later!)
- Jae Suk.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- You look nice.
- You're here.
- Hey.
- It is sunny today.
- The weather is nice.
It's really good.
- Haha.
- Hey.
- Look at him.
- He's wearing a sweatsuit again.
- Hello.
- As always.
Did you get your pants from
the Korea Expressway Corporation?
- No.
- What's with them?
- Aren't they pretty?
- What happened?
- This is...
- Suk Jin, if you lie down here,
- you can be part of the line.
- It should be the same fabric.
You can lie down on here.
- There he goes.
- It's nice to be out.
I bet he's just got joint pains.
- He groaned.
- Isn't it nice to be out?
- His joints just popped.
- After staying home the whole time.
Don't pretend to be excited.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- It's been a long time.
- I've missed you all.
- Hey.
- Stop it.
- Don't walk around.
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm just glad that I'm back.
- You might break your leg again.
You can't be like this.
- You might break your bone again.
- You know what?
You're likely to get injured
when you work out in good condition.
- Exactly.
- That's true.
"Gosh, what's with me today?"
- That's not good.
- Then you could get hurt.
That's when you get injured.
You just saw what Suk Jin did.
When he got off the car...
"Oh, dear."
- But when the camera is on...
- When we got here...
"Gosh, this is so nice!"
He's healthy.
- That was fake.
- He pretended to be excited.
- I was really excited.
- That's a fake life.
- I was excited to be out.
- He forced himself to be excited.
- It is nice to be out.
- Suk Jin's mood.
- True or false?
- I'm not lying.
- I don't fake anything.
- False!
- You're lying again.
Ji Suk Jin's Fake Life!
(Ji Suk Jin's Fake Life,
to be continued)
- Se Chan, you look nice today.
- You think?
- Yes. Today...
- I went to a beauty salon.
By the way, are you going...
to Gwacheon Racecourse today?
(Giddyup!)
Why? A racecourse?
He imitates horse racing right away.
That's what comedians do.
He makes jokes about it.
Ji Hyo, your hair looks great.
- It's grown a lot.
- It looks the best.
- This is the hairstyle I want.
- You do?
You'd look like Lee Kwang Soo then.
It will make you look like Lee Kwang Soo.
No, it's not Kwang Soo.
I want to be like Ji Hyo.
- I like her hairstyle.
- Like this?
Hey.
Her hair looks nice because of her face.
I guess it's really sunny today.
Suk Jin, I can see your earwax.
(Suk Jin, I can see your earwax.)
(His earwax is shown.)
I saw that last week.
- Really?
- He always has it.
It must be clear today.
Your earwax...
- During the opening...
- Hey.
- I can see earwax in his ear.
- He has that all the time.
Is it okay to talk about earwax...
- on a variety show?
- What about it?
Have variety shows come this far?
It must be really sunny today.
- It's a sunny day.
- The weather is nice.
I can see through his ears.
I made a big contribution to this episode.
- Hey, I'm still the captain.
- Until today?
Until today.
- Forget it. You are not a captain.
- Is that true?
What are we having for lunch?
- Isn't it over?
- Today is a good day.
- What?
- Isn't it over yet?
Will we be cooking ourselves?
- I only care about lunch.
- We will be cooking then.
What are we having for lunch?
- We can cook anything we want.
- What are we going to eat?
- Jae Suk, you know what?
- Are you a restaurant owner?
It's ridiculous
that Suk Jin is the captain.
He shifted his work to me and Ji Hyo.
So the two of us had to do an extra shoot.
- Really?
- Yes.
He didn't attend the meeting.
He just made me and Ji Hyo
come up with some ideas.
So Ji Hyo and I had a meeting
at a Chinese restaurant.
Suk Jin, you're the captain.
- You should attend the meeting.
- You should've joined us.
I had something else to take care of.
- You were home.
- I know you were home.
He was lying down at home.
- He said "Hey" with a swollen face.
- He was wearing a loose shirt.
True or false?
False!
- He's a liar.
- He's unbelievable.
I had to spend some time
with my wife at home.
- That's not work.
- Why at home?
- I had plans with my wife.
- My gosh.
What are we doing today?
As you just heard,
today is Suk Jin's last day as a captain.
There's something
Captain Ji said every time.
We should forget about missions.
We should try to do what we want
to do without playing games.
This is what he said, so...
That means he doesn't
want to do this show.
That's not true. I just want
things to be spontaneous.
What is it he wants to do?
- He wants to slack off.
- Aren't you tired...
of playing games every time?
- I'm fine with it. It's fun.
- I find it interesting.
(They prefer games.)
That's what I come here for.
"What game are we playing today?"
I want to fight and betray others.
- I want some quizzes too.
- Well...
- All right. I know it's fun.
- It's fun to solve quizzes.
To be honest, there are
a lot of observation shows...
- on other channels.
- I don't like it.
- We should play more games.
- Exactly.
We can take a break today.
I'm not saying we shouldn't do it at all.
- But that's what we do.
- That's not what I meant.
- Jong Kook, stop frowning.
- I love to play games.
- Just stop frowning.
- My gosh.
I love it.
(Captain Ji suddenly
touches Jong Kook's face.)
I love it.
- I'm punishing you out of love.
- My goodness.
I care about Jong Kook a lot.
Why are you doing that?
- In a lovely way.
- Do you really have to do that?
He's afraid you might get upset.
- He did this in a cute way.
- In a lovely way.
(Acting cute)
As Captain Ji requested,
you're not going
to have any missions today.
- Really?
- That's great.
- I'm here for missions.
- Why?
We will show you how we have fun.
- I hate things like this.
- I hate it.
- Suk Jin.
- What are we doing then?
- This is even harder.
- This is what I hated the most...
when we did "Family Outing."
They don't tell me what to do.
Like Jong Kook said,
I hate it when our production crew
says things like that.
"You can just have fun
without doing anything."
- I hate it a lot.
- I like it though.
- It's really difficult.
- We've never done it before.
And do you know what happens
when we actually have fun?
They are like this.
That makes me nervous.
(Upset)
- That makes me nervous.
- I feel really uncomfortable.
- They are displeased.
- Right.
"You told us to have fun."
"I know."
- Then they have a meeting.
- They discuss things.
Why did they tell us
to have fun in the first place?
- We will have fun doing nothing.
- So, today,
there won't be any missions.
You will just hang out
and have fun with the other members.
But it's up to you to finish the shoot.
Hey.
- Don't say that.
- I don't want things like that.
They feel uncomfortable
when you say things like that.
- See?
- I'd rather do as I'm told.
If you think you are done filling up
the airtime of 90 minutes,
you can ring the bell
you will see at the outing site.
(The shoot is over
as soon as the bell rings.)
- Really?
- You mean 90 minutes?
- Do you want us to ring the bell?
- Yes.
How long has it been?
I guess it's been eight minutes.
- No.
- What?
- I bet it's worth 10 minutes.
- No, it will be 10 minutes.
- Ten minutes?
- We did a lot of things.
Including the walking,
it will add up to 12 or 13 minutes.
We walked all the way here.
We just walked. That doesn't count.
We put on the microphones.
- Hey, the microphone.
- That's ridiculous.
- He's the worst.
- Jae Suk is a popular MC.
- It should be about him.
- You're the best.
If we have him on TV,
we will get good ratings.
Once you ring the bell,
today's race will be over.
- Really?
- Are we going home like that?
Yes. But if you fail
to fill up the airtime...
- You should take care of it.
- Additional shooting?
We have your schedule...
for the next 3 or 4 weeks.
There might be additional shooting.
This is worse.
- It's like a penalty.
- They want us to try our best.
It would've been easier
if we'd played like three games.
I know.
What's with you, Suk Jin?
We could've had some guests
and played games together.
This will become a good memory.
It is going to be fun.
What if Running Man comes to an end?
When Running Man comes to an end,
we are going to cherish this moment.
- Why would it come to an end?
- Why would you say that?
- We're doing a good job.
- Things are going well now.
It will eventually come to an end.
I'm sorry, but it won't be over.
You will leave the show,
but we will stay here.
It's just you who will leave the show.
That's plausible though.
- That's what I look forward to.
- What do you look forward to?
One day, Jong Kook... No, you're Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk.
- You seem flustered.
This is what I'm waiting for. One day,
I will leave this show.
And I'll hand over my position
to my replacement.
That's going to happen next week!
(That's going to happen next week!)
(Silent roars)
This is true!
That's too soon.
- True.
- Give me some more time.
Can you stay a little longer?
Isn't that cool?
For the first time on a variety
show, I will have my successor.
Your successor, my foot.
Who do you want...
- to be your replacement?
- Someone clumsy.
- Like who?
- Your replacement?
- I haven't thought about it.
- Do you think...
is there anyone who can replace you?
- Someone like you.
- What do you think?
Someone to replace Suk Jin?
It should be someone younger than me...
- and older than Jae Suk.
- Really?
It's hard.
So you want someone who was born in 1971,
All right then. Suk Jin will go...
and find someone who was born in 1971.
- Go!
- Let's go!
We never know where he's going.
It will be fun to find
Suk Jin's replacement.
Who will be Suk Jin's replacement?
- Let's go find it!
- Born in 1970 or 1971.
Either 1970 or 1971.
- Doesn't it sound fun?
- That's a great idea.
- So...
- We might...
find your replacement
sooner than you thought.
When I...
When I have to leave this show...
- He's crying.
- Isn't it now?
It will be worth four episodes.
- Looking for my replacement.
- Suk Jin.
- Four weeks.
- Go ahead...
- and apologize.
- Just wrap it up.
Just say you will try your best.
- Tell them you'll work hard.
- They might find your replacement.
Just tell them that you will work hard.
Running Man is part of my life.
He apologizes.
He was born in 1966,
- and he's apologizing.
- I've been apologizing a lot.
He was born in 1966.
- I'm sorry.
- That came out wrong.
- "I don't want to leave the show."
- I'll try my best.
I will give it my best shot.
What I just said was a lie.
(What I just said was a lie.)
(False)
- That's right.
- The fake life!
- False!
- I'm sorry.
- Ji Suk Jin's fake life!
- I carried my joke too far.
- I know.
So, as Captain Ji said,
you will have fun together.
It ends when the bell rings,
and if it's not enough,
- we'll shoot a little longer.
- Got it.
- That's not a problem.
- Okay.
Obviously, there's no mission
or penalty today.
- Now, we'll move to the location.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
This is so nice.
- Something like that.
- Push it back. It's 90 degrees now.
No, it isn't.
(- It's 90 degrees now.
- No, it isn't.)
- What?
- Yes, it is, Suk Jin.
- What do you mean it's not?
- It's 90 degrees.
- It must be uncomfortable.
- What...
- Push it back a little.
- Then...
- That's a lie.
- Why do you keep denying things?
- Come on. Lean back, Suk Jin.
- What does he mean?
- Lean back, Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin. I mean, Captain Ji.
- It's uncomfortable.
- I was going to give him a massage.
- I prefer sitting like this.
- I'll do it for you.
- That's okay.
Suk Jin, you're upset now, right?
No, I'm not.
(- You're upset now, right?
- No, I'm not.)
- Again, he said, "No."
- He's lying.
People often think I'm upset
when I'm actually not.
- Right.
- Then when you're upset,
- how do you look?
- It happens at home too.
- What do you do when you're upset?
- Exactly.
- I...
- What do you do when you're upset?
People would walk away from me
when I get angry.
- Do you yell at others?
- Who did that?
When I was in middle school,
kids all ran away immediately.
- Why?
- You cry when you're angry, right?
- I guess Haha is right.
- You cry and yell, right?
- He'd pee himself too.
- Right.
- He'd pee and cry at the same time.
- Exactly.
- While peeing himself?
- "Go away! Stay away from me!"
- Then he starts peeing.
- "I'll throw poop at you!"
I bet he peed.
That's why everyone ran away from him.
(The young Seok Sam beat his enemies
with a biological weapon.)
Right.
He said everyone walked away from him.
- By the way,
- That was hilarious.
I talked to So Min on the phone...
- while she was quarantined.
- Yes.
She seemed to feel so cooped up.
- Of course.
- I was the last one to get it.
- So Min was the last one.
- Yes.
Suk Jin, Haha, Jong Kook, and I...
- talked in a group chat room.
- True.
- We had video chats too. So Min...
- I remember that.
- joined us when she wasn't sick.
- That's right.
But when So Min was sick,
we were all working busily.
- Right.
- Exactly.
- So we missed her calls.
- Right.
- I felt bad about it.
- No one spoke in the chat room.
And Suk Jin and Jong Kook had
a video chat with me.
- We had a video chat once.
- Then they said it was enough,
- and they had done enough for me.
- But...
- You know...
- We had a long chat though.
We chatted for 40 minutes,
but she wouldn't hang up.
Right. Suk Jin actively joined the chat.
He came up with various topics
to talk about. I was impressed.
- I thought,
- He sure is our captain.
- But it was funny...
- "He's participating passionately."
- that they told me to hang up...
- Yes.
during the video chat.
I thought it was ridiculous...
because they were talking to
each other while looking at me.
They had a chat without me
and then told me to hang up.
- They had nothing to talk about.
- That's because they're men.
- They didn't have a chat with me.
- Right.
We didn't know what to talk about
after talking about each other.
- They told me to leave suddenly.
- Right.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
What did you do yesterday?
I stayed at home all day yesterday,
Jae Suk.
(What a simple, clear answer.)
That was a simple and clear answer.
- It was simple and nice.
- How she said it was funny.
Can somebody make a collection
of clips where Ji Hyo says,
- "I stayed at home all day?"
- "I stayed at home all day."
- The collection of Ji Hyo's clips.
- That sounds funny.
- "I stayed at home all day."
It's a short sentence.
- That was a clear answer.
- "I stayed at home all day."
- We'll arrive at a grocery store.
- I see.
- Already? That's sad.
- It's about time.
In the meeting, we came up with
this idea for motivating everyone.
We'll buy some products
to be given as prizes.
- We'll get what we use at home.
- Like what?
- I like that idea.
- Such as detergent,
- toilet paper, or ramyeon.
- Good. I like that.
- I want to win such prizes.
- What we need in daily life.
- Such products will be the prizes.
- I like the idea.
We're out of diapers.
That can be a prize too.
But no one else but you want it, Haha.
- I mean, you and Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin wears diapers.
Only the two of you want it.
Suk Jin.
- Start crying.
- It's useless for us.
- And scream too.
- As I said before...
Pee your pants now.
Then we'll run away.
Fine! I heard you!
Just stop it, will you?
(Suk Jin showed the original version.)
"What did I ever do wrong?"
I would never yell like that
when I'm angry.
- That's not a cool way.
- That was hilarious.
Everyone, we're going grocery shopping.
Right. There are no rules for it.
Let's get enough food for us
to eat for the day.
- No. Hold on.
- Let's not make things complicated.
- Let's just have a simple meal.
- This is not an overnight trip.
- We shouldn't get too much food?
- Let's buy just enough food.
- You can get personal items too.
- Right.
- Just one personal item for each.
- Of course.
Bring one more cart.
- The grain syrup snack.
- Don't get too much food. Okay?
- Don't get too much food.
(Haha picks up a snack
even at the entrance.)
- The grain syrup snack.
- Pick up what we'll actually eat.
- That one is good.
- You won't eat this?
- Indeed.
- You guys won't eat this?
- I'll eat it.
- I want M snack.
- It goes well with this ramyeon.
- Hey, we'll get B bibim ramyeon.
- Where is it?
- Gosh, seriously.
Have you lost your mind?
(Yoo Jae Suk,
the model for B bibim ramyeon)
How dare you pick that up in front of me?
Guys, we'll go get some meat.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Hey, don't get too much meat.
- Let's go, So Min.
- Hello.
Hey, this one is really good, right?
It's just amazing.
My gosh.
You guys all have the palate of a child.
- Hey, stop. That's too much.
- These two too.
- You're not allowed to eat this.
- Haha.
- I love this one.
- Why did you pick so many snacks?
- This one is awesome.
- Hey.
- You mean, this?
- Your sugar level will be so high.
Guys, we won't stay the night there.
So don't buy too much food.
We won't cook rice, will we?
We should cook rice in a pot.
- Will we cook rice?
- Will we?
- Let's get some instant rice.
- Right.
- We don't have to cook it.
- Of course.
Two packs will be enough, right?
I think it's too much.
- Shall we get just one?
- Yes.
Hey, how about some canned ham?
It's good, right?
Suk Jin, don't pick up too many.
Canned ham is a must.
Suk Jin, stop putting any more food
in the cart.
I just put two things in it.
Wait. I want...
Se Chan, we need mushrooms too.
- Let's eat some beef.
- Sure.
- Come over here.
- Let's eat beef.
- Some rib fingers and...
- Boneless short ribs. This one.
- Right. Good. And...
- It looks good.
Don't pick up something to cook
through a lot of work.
We just have to grill beef
and eat it with some salt.
(Beef is good.)
- Put them in the cart.
- We need this.
I just said that because of Jae Suk.
Hide the meat.
Put them under the other stuff.
Jae Suk would complain about it
if he saw it.
Don't let him see it. Flip it over.
Put it on the bottom,
and cover it with the other stuff.
That's good. Cover it.
(Even the tough Jong Kook is worried
about what Jae Suk might say.)
Don't get too much food.
Get just enough food for the day.
We must not waste food.
Hey, we do need some bananas, right?
Guys, we need some bananas, right?
I'll put in the mushroom.
I don't see any cucumbers here.
- Can I get some coffee?
- We don't need cooking oil, right?
No, we don't need that.
Are we going to make some oil sauce?
What are you two doing now?
Why are you going around alone together?
The two younger people are
shopping together. That's all.
But why just the two of you?
(A romance control officer showed up
this time.)
- What's going on?
- There's nothing going on.
- What's your problem?
- Come over here.
- What's going on between you two?
- Se Chan.
(Come over here.)
These are mine. Don't eat them.
All four of them?
You'll eat all four of them?
- We have drinking water, right?
- Are you sure you won't eat this?
I don't see anything we should buy.
(Trainer Kook is very strict
with spending just like Jae Suk.)
What's smoked duck? Let's check it out.
(He showed interest in
high-protein food for the 1st time.)
This will be a good prize.
- Are you getting a razor?
- Can I get this?
Why would you pick up a razor?
This is what I really need.
I'll get a bottle of
windshield washer fluid.
(He's getting daily necessities
for personal items.)
- No.
- Suk Jin, I found diapers.
It says it won't leak.
Se Chan.
- So Min, get whatever you want.
- I want this. The whole set.
Guys, let's pay now.
Okay, Jae Suk.
Let's just order some delivery food
instead of buying all these.
Goodness, they put a lot of snacks
in the cart.
- Have ice cream if you want.
- Okay.
Eating ice cream on a bus
while chatting is fun.
- When we get there,
- Yes.
don't open everything.
- What we don't need is a prize.
- Right. Just in case.
Okay.
Are we going to eat right after we arrive?
It's part of our plan.
Suk Jin will cook for us.
Captain Ji said in the meeting
that he would make...
- cookies for you.
- Really?
- Cookies?
- What?
Is there anything you want to do
for the members,
like cooking?
- There's something I'm so good at.
- What is it?
I make amazing cookies.
- Cookies?
- My cookies are amazing.
That's so unexpected.
- My cookies are so good.
- Then...
do you make the dough too?
I have my own recipe. I use
140g of oat flour, 60g of flour,
and 40g of sugar
although it says to put in 60g.
I make cookies every single day.
- Because everyone likes it.
- Really?
My mother-in-law was so surprised
when she first tried it.
You will make it interesting
to watch, right?
I guess
I'll have to improvise something...
in order to make it interesting.
Don't worry.
I make people laugh so easily these days.
(Captain Ji said he'd make cookies
on the trip to Daeseong-ri.)
He said he would make cookies for you.
- That's right.
- Really?
- What?
- I don't like cookies.
- Just cook some ramyeon instead.
- No.
- I don't like cookies.
- You should try my cookies.
- I'm good at making cookies.
- So I'm going to make some for you.
- Why would you make cookies?
- He seemed confident.
- But why would he...
- Stop complaining and just eat it.
- We don't want to.
- No, we don't want to.
- You said you made a good ramyeon.
- Why...
- It's a healthy cookie.
- How about ramyeon?
- I'll make oatmeal cookies.
Just eat it.
But we don't have an oven.
- Sorry?
- There's no oven.
- I'll use an air fryer.
- We don't want to eat your cookies.
- You should still eat it.
- I don't want your cookies!
I don't like cookies.
I hate cookies.
- Cook ramyeon for us instead.
- Why should we eat your cookies?
You will be surprised
and enjoy my cookies.
- Cook ramyeon for us instead.
- Just eat it as your captain says.
- Also...
- My gosh.
I'll teach you how to make it if you want.
- No.
- I don't want to.
Come to my class.
- There will be a cooking class.
- We'll eat ramyeon instead.
- Right. We'll eat it without you.
- We'll eat ramyeon.
- What time is it now?
- We'll grill some meat too.
- Great. That sounds so delicious.
- It's 10:40 a.m.
- I'll eat bibim ramyeon.
- It sounds delicious. Me too.
I'll add some green onions.
- The cooking class begins at 11 a.m.
- Ramyeon with meat.
- I'll take care of everything.
- I won't go.
- I'll be a no-show.
- I refuse.
- No.
- I'll be a no-show.
A no-show? That expression doesn't
suit this situation.
You can be a no-show
if you made a booking.
- Say you'll boycott his cookies.
- He meant he wouldn't go there.
- I know.
- I'll boycott your cookies.
- You're not allowed to do that.
- Why?
- I'll boycott his cookies.
- Then just one of you should come.
- Just one is okay, right?
- Then I'll go.
- Sorry?
- I'll go.
- You will? Why?
- Yes.
I'll be a no-show...
- if I don't show up, right?
- Correct.
- That's right.
- That's exactly what it means.
- I'll be a no-show.
- Good.
- Got a death wish?
- I'd like to book your class.
- He said, "Got a death wish?"
"Got a death wish?"
- Got a death wish?
- My goodness.
- Guys, I see a soccer field.
- I guess this is it.
- I see a basketball court too.
- We're here.
- Nice. We can do everything here.
- Oh, my.
We're going to have so much fun.
It's so nice here.
The weather is good as well.
- It's great.
- Let's play foot volleyball.
We can do that too.
There are so many things we can do here.
It's huge.
- This room looks nice.
- Hey.
It's really nice here.
- Sorry?
- It's so big.
- There's a karaoke machine too.
- There's a lot to do.
We can sing, play basketball,
and do so many other things.
Let's move our stuff inside.
- So Min.
- Yes?
- Come over here.
- Why do you keep calling me?
This is the youngest member's duty.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Jeonsobari.
- Stuff like this...
Let's not waste any minute
and start cooking ramyeon.
That's a good idea.
- So Min.
- I'll get changed.
- Go change your clothes first.
- Why are you calling me this time?
Hurry up and move the boxes.
- It's a modernized hanbok.
- That's right.
It's a modernized hanbok.
Oh, gosh. There's a huge bell out there.
- Can you see the bell outside?
- Yes.
Ring it when you think you've done
enough for one episode.
- Got it.
- I think...
- we can ring it right now.
- You see, usually,
- Yes.
- we play 3 games for 1 episode.
The 1st part is about our lunch.
- We can divide it into three parts.
- And...
we can play a sports game outside,
and then do something else here.
- Exactly.
- Since we're here...
- Captain Ji is over there.
- I mean, the cooking class...
- Captain Ji.
- Right. Go ahead. Tell us.
- He was adamant about his class.
- Let go of me.
- I want to play darts.
- Let's discuss...
- what we should do.
- Right.
- On the whole...
- We don't have to discuss it.
- We're here to have fun. Yes?
- Come on. Captain Ji.
- On the whole...
- Yes.
I mean... Why did you change
your hairstyle?
I got all dolled up.
- But, you see, So Min...
- On a group trip like this...
- So Min.
- Yes?
I'm sorry, but this isn't
a group blind date.
- That's not the case.
- This isn't "The Mate."
- I mean...
- This outfit may remind you of it,
- but this isn't "The Mate."
- You know... It's not like that.
- This isn't a dating show.
- We're on a group trip.
- Why are you trying to find love?
- Does anyone want to eat with me?
(Woman 2 came to find a man to eat with.)
- Anyone?
- All right.
It'll be lunchtime shortly, right?
- Yes.
- We should have lunch.
- How about bibim ramyeon?
- Bibim ramyeon and soupy ramyeon.
- Sounds great.
- I'll...
- I'll grill meat.
- Let's eat it with some meat.
I'll cook the meat.
- Okay. You do that.
- Yes.
The cooking class will be held
in the next room.
Go ahead and do it alone.
- I'd like to book it.
- I have a good idea.
- I'll cook ramyeon.
- I'll help him.
- I'll make bibim ramyeon.
- Let's do it together.
- You make bibim ramyeon, then.
- Who will attend his cooking class?
He will.
- All by himself?
- Yes.
- I don't want you to come.
- Okay. The problem is solved.
- Make sure not to interfere.
- You can't make cookies.
- Jong Kook, cook with him.
- Se Chan.
- Attend my cooking class.
- Grill some chicken breasts.
- Sure. I'll do that.
- Let's move.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Guys.
- Yes?
What about my cooking class?
I'll begin the class
when you guys finish eating lunch.
But if I grill meat there...
- We need a pot.
- You should grill it outside.
(For a short period of time
when they're cooking...)
(We'll show you how different
their personalities are.)
I think we could use a frying pan,
don't you think?
- I'll make cookies for you guys.
- A frying pan.
Let's decide how many portions
of ramyeon we'll eat first.
Ramyeon? I want to eat a lot.
- Four packets of bibim ramyeon,
- Four packets?
- and 3 packets of soupy ramyeon.
- We'll need more than 4 packets.
- Four packets are too many.
- It's not enough for us.
- It's too much.
- Four packets are enough.
- What about the soupy one?
- No, it's not enough.
- Let's cook just four packets.
- We'll eat soupy ramyeon too.
Let's finish cooking in 30 minutes.
- Let's do that.
- Pour water into the pot.
Pour 550ml of water
for 1 packet of ramyeon.
- With 550ml of water...
- No, that's not the ideal amount.
- Then pour 500ml for each.
- Okay. Got it.
- Four packets? Pour it four times.
- Yes.
Ji Hyo, pour it four times.
(Ji Hyo is good at cooking ramyeon,
and Jong Kook is bad at it.)
- Should we cook it all together?
- Okay.
- Good job. Okay.
- It's done.
(He drops the lid.)
(He puts in
the whole sachet of seasoning.)
(He's not used to cooking ramyeon.)
I'll cook bibim ramyeon.
We didn't buy any cucumbers, right?
- They didn't have cucumbers.
- I see.
Let's boil some eggs.
(So Min will boil eggs.)
- Right.
- Don't make the noodles soggy.
So Min, you should put the eggs in
when the water starts boiling.
You're wrong. You should put them in
from the beginning.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Ramyeon...
You should. Or else... Seven minutes
after the water starts boiling.
Exactly 12 minutes
- Seven minutes to soft boil them.
- For soft-boiled eggs,
- it takes exactly 12 minutes.
- No, 7 minutes.
- No, 12 minutes.
- In total...
- It takes 12 minutes in total.
- It takes 7 minutes.
- No, 12 minutes.
- No, 7 minutes.
Forget it. Do whatever you want.
Jae Suk, why have you become so stubborn?
Gosh. I'm so annoyed.
(The 2 chefs are adamant
about how they cook eggs.)
Everyone.
(While everyone else is busy,
Captain Ji is wandering around.)
Flour. Where is the mixing bowl?
Where are the mixed nuts?
- I saw it in there, Suk Jin.
- Where?
- Check the fridge.
- Suk Jin.
You've been just walking around
without cooking for so long.
Oh, they're all in here.
The cooking class will begin shortly.
I'll be there.
(He will be a no-show.)
Since you all look busy,
I'll put my class off a little bit.
It will begin a little while later.
I'm announcing it to all of you.
(Staring)
Are you playing house?
(Ji Hyo walks toward the stove
with pepper.)
- Se Chan.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- Prepare plates for bibim ramyeon.
- Why are you adding pepper?
It makes it tastier.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Jae Suk.
- Are you sure?
- Yes. Trust me.
- It's already in the seasoning.
Does pepper make ramyeon tastier?
- Yes, it makes the ramyeon tastier.
- Oh, I see.
- I didn't know that.
- Why didn't you believe me?
- Also...
- It wasn't like that.
- You didn't set the timer, did you?
- I was just curious.
It's easier if you put in
the seasoning from the get-go.
(Thinking hard)
- Jong Kook, it hurts my feelings.
- Did you put it in?
- What do you mean?
- "Why didn't you side with me?"
- Listen. It wasn't like that.
Was it wrong of me to ask him
because I didn't know?
That's not the point. When Haha told you,
- you believed him. "Oh, I see."
- "Why didn't you side with me?"
- This is so childish.
- But you didn't believe me.
- Are they a married couple?
- It wasn't like that.
- They're having a lovers' quarrel.
- That wasn't my intention.
- I was just curious.
- The seasoning is also...
They look like the couples on "The Mate."
- Pardon?
- You and Ji Hyo...
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Come on, Jae Suk.
- Don't say that.
- Aren't your numbers both one?
- What?
- Man 1 and Woman 1.
- That's ridiculous. Gosh.
- Come on.
Ji Hyo, I didn't know that.
Thanks for the tip.
- I'll add pepper...
- I'm so upset, Jong Kook.
- to ramyeon from now on.
- I'm serious.
I'll start cooking the meat!
(In the living room,
Se Chan is ready to cook the meat.)
(Sizzling)
I hear the rain sound.
It smells good.
Bibim ramyeon is ready. Come, everyone.
- Good. Let's eat.
- Hurry up.
- Come here.
- We should eat it with the meat.
Hey, Haha!
We're almost done here too!
(The bibim ramyeon man is impatient.)
- Hurry up!
- We're almost done!
Eat it before the noodles get soggy.
- Let's leave it and eat some.
- Hurry up!
- Okay.
- Let's eat some and come back.
- Let's go!
- Go on without me.
- Come on. Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
- Eat bibim ramyeon with meat.
- Let's eat.
- Go ahead.
- Put it into the pot.
- But the eggs aren't ready yet.
- Good. Put it in.
- Here go sea snails. Hey, So Min.
- Jae Suk.
- That looks good.
- I'm wearing a cooking glove.
(The model of the bibim ramyeon ad
will distribute the food.)
- Now, Suk Jin, try it.
- Yes?
- Se Chan, come over here.
- Okay.
Come here.
Guys, hurry up.
Come here now.
This is...
(You did a great job.)
It's good, right? Isn't it amazing?
(Even the cookie artisan is
impressed by the bibim ramyeon.)
My, it's so good.
Guys, come here and eat with us.
Hurry up and come. Eat up now.
Come here.
Eat the noodles
before they get soggy. Gosh.
Is this some kind of competition?
Why are we in a hurry?
Soupy ramyeon is done too.
- Have some meat.
- This is really good.
(Jae Suk wants them to try
the noodles while they're firm.)
- Hurry up.
- You should've cooked more of it.
We have more packets.
It's really good.
Have a piece of meat with the noodles.
(He starts devouring the food.)
Move. Make way.
Here comes the soupy ramyeon.
Put the meat aside.
- Hey, it's tasty.
- See?
We wouldn't spend much time on food.
We'd finish cooking
and eating quickly and move on.
- Ta-da!
- It looks amazing.
- You guys...
- Why didn't you shoot inserts?
Hurry up and shoot inserts.
- I'll open the lid again.
- Wrap it up quickly.
- It was too tough.
- Okay.
It's expensive.
(The ramyeon with green onion, eggs,
and extra pepper)
- It's so good. I mean it.
- It's good, indeed.
(The soup is refreshing
thanks to the pepper.)
- Ji Hyo, the soup is amazing. Yes.
- Right?
This is so fun. Right?
I'm happy that everyone is enjoying
themselves on the trip I organized.
We're eating here. Quiet down, will you?
(Everyone likes Ji Hyo's pepper recipe.)
The meat is cooked well.
(The beef is being cooked too.)
- Was it okay?
- The meat is tasty.
My, this makes my stress go away.
- Guys, try the meat.
- It's so good.
My, it's so tasty.
This is amazing.
The meat is incredibly good.
We're dressed like members
of a fasting club.
- That's right.
- It's so good.
They wear clothes like this.
Without letting the director know...
(They're having a secret party.)
And it's nutritionally balanced.
We have meat and everything.
Oh, right. We have rice too.
Who wants rice?
- It's here.
- Oh, you brought it here.
- Do you want some?
- No, I won't eat it.
- What?
- My gosh.
- What was that?
- That was so unexpected.
- It was so weird.
- I won't eat it. Who wants it?
- I asked if anyone wanted it.
- I see.
- It wasn't for you.
- Suk Jin always...
puts on an act in front of cameras.
And I truly believe
that he should stop doing that.
I ate a lot. It was so good.
I'm so full.
It's amazing.
- Then...
- Eat a piece of meat with it.
Wait. Now that I've had lunch...
- But I don't...
- It's not that hot.
- Jae Suk, do you have plans later?
- Sorry?
Why are you rushing everything?
Jae Suk, you don't have any plans
after this, right?
- Of course, not.
- The green onion is good.
- I have no plans afterward.
- Right?
Do you want some strawberries?
- Will you wash them for us?
- Do you want some?
Please wash some for us.
Of course, I'll do that for you.
It's not a big deal.
- Remove stems, please.
- Of course.
I really enjoyed it.
But who will do the dishes?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors
to decide that.
Let's play a game to choose
the person to do the dishes.
How about a game of wits?
Let's not play the game of wits.
How about this? We point at someone
and say, "You wash the dishes!"
- I like the idea.
- Just say, "You wash the dishes!"
- It sounds fun.
- Let's try it. It's a new game.
- I don't think that's a good idea.
- Let's see if it's fun to play.
Why? All you have to do is say,
"You wash the dishes!"
- I don't think that's fair.
- Why?
I know who will be chosen.
- No way. Why do you think so?
- Who do you think would be picked?
Well, I think I know
what you're trying to do.
- I like the idea.
- Right.
It's quick and easy.
- Shall we give it a try?
- Yes.
- One, two, three.
- You wash the dishes!
(Suk Jin's prediction was right.)
- I knew it.
- Guys.
- Let's play 3 rounds in total.
- We'll play 3 rounds.
One, two, three.
- You wash the dishes!
(You wash the dishes!)
I love seeing you hold a unified front.
- You.
(They only come together
when teasing Captain Ji.)
You wash the dishes.
(Just then, Jae Suk turns on some music.)
I love this song.
We don't even get a minute to relax.
Can't we take a break?
You're making me dizzy.
- What's with him?
- Beats me.
Why can't we like the same music?
(He moves on
before they finish their meal.)
Shouldn't there be a break?
(He moves on
before they finish their meal.)
- He...
- It's a little sad though.
I'll be back with clean strawberries.
Don't forget to cut off the leaves.
(Captain Ji is in charge of dessert.)
It's a green onion flute.
(A green onion flute)
(He shakes his head.)
Jae Suk's on form today.
Can't we rest for at least a minute?
Jae Suk, please.
Let us take a short break.
Please sit still.
Please!
Jae Suk, let us take a break.
(He won't stop despite their requests.)
(They eventually get him to stop.)
It's been a while since I enjoyed meat.
What a blast it has been.
(He got to enjoy worldly flavors.)
That's what I'm talking about!
Gosh, I'm full.
Let me play a song for Jong Kook.
("Yoo Jae Suk's Drawing Paper")
No matter how much I think about it
("No Matter How I Think about It"
by Sweet Sorrow)
This calls for a bathroom break.
(Act 2 begins.)
Jae Suk, let us rest for about a minute.
Jae Suk, please.
Let us take a break.
Give us a break!
This song doesn't feature a flute.
He...
(The flute master can play every song.)
Why is he on it
when a flute can't be heard?
(Why is he on it
when a flute can't be heard?)
I do
What on earth is that?
Are you kidding me?
(Them getting together
seems out of the blue.)
What is this?
- Let's drink.
- So Min, are you kidding me?
(They must've met at a bar.)
This is out of the blue!
Must you be so annoying?
- What is the meaning of this?
- Look at those two.
- They're hilarious.
- I thought you were Suk Jin.
This is hilarious.
(She's unabashed
when it comes to role-playing.)
- This brings back old memories.
- Why?
- Really?
- Old memories?
Yes!
Then I'll switch it up.
Nice!
(Act 3 begins.)
Jae Suk.
Let us rest for a minute.
Please.
- You're spilling water.
- It's leaking.
Yoon Eun Hye!
(Summoned)
Darn you!
(He can't help but call out her name.)
Only So Min gets the vibe.
- It's so much fun.
- Right?
What a blast.
I love it.
Can you play a song by Travel Sketch?
- Travel Sketch?
- What did he say?
Scotch Blue?
- What?
- Which song by Scotch Blue?
- What did he say?
- A song by Scotch Blue.
I said Travel Sketch!
- Sorry?
- Travel Sketch!
He means Scenery of Riding Bicycle.
Is it Scenery of Riding Bicycle?
Play the band's song so I can reminisce.
- Got it.
- Suk Jin,
- we don't like the same music.
- All right.
Scenery of Riding Bicycle.
(He plays a different song.)
(Bouncing)
Darn it.
This isn't what I requested.
(Jae Suk sticks to songs...)
(he enjoyed at the roller skating rink.)
Scenery of Riding Bicycle.
Scenery of Riding Bicycle!
(A regular at the roller skating rink)
(She knows how to sway to the rhythm.)
- Scenery of Riding Bicycle!
(They fool around even though
they're bad at partying.)
- Scenery of Riding Bicycle!
- I to you, you to me!
This isn't what I wanted.
"I to You, You to Me"
by Scenery of Riding Bicycle.
(Bouncing)
I used to sway to this song often.
This brings back memories.
It was frequently played
at roller skating rinks.
What about my favorite dance song?
Amok!
- This is a good one.
- "Rumors" by Storm.
- Isn't this good?
- It's good.
If you can be, be the wind
- "If you can be."
- Oh, that one.
So Min, bring it in.
(The party girl instinctively responds.)
Can't we digest the food first?
- Did someone spike your food?
- I'm not kidding when I say...
- that I'm close to vomiting.
- That's the spirit.
(She lets it build up.)
Have some strawberries.
If you can be
(Just party!)
How can I not dance to this?
But I'm seriously close to vomiting.
What's with him today?
- Have a strawberry.
- Thank you.
A strawberry.
- Have a strawberry.
- Goodness.
- Go ahead.
- Is this for us?
Of course. I washed them all.
Have a strawberry.
- The strawberry's delicious.
- My head's spinning.
This is great.
I can't stop though.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
Can we digest the food first?
Was something odd in your food?
- Did someone spike his food?
- His food?
- I mean...
- He won't let us rest.
I'm having a blast.
I request "I to You, You to Me"
by Scenery of Riding Bicycle.
I'm exhausted,
- but I can't sit still.
- By SRB?
- Yes, I'd like to reminisce.
- Sure thing.
- Suk Jin.
- It rains
"It rains."
("I to You, You to Me"
by Scenery of Riding Bicycle)
This song...
It brings back memories.
Seriously?
Why are you doing this?
(This scene...)
He plays along with her.
(The rain scene from
the movie "The Classic")
(It must be acid rain
judging by his face melting.)
He plays along with her.
(The acid rain
is more toxic than he thought.)
(The middle-aged men are eating it up.)
He plays along with her.
- I to you
- He plays along with her.
So Min's a beast, isn't she?
She can role-play every song out there.
- She can role-play every song.
- No way.
- This is why I like So Min.
- There's...
a story behind every song.
This is why I'm fond of her.
This song brings me to tears.
- I'm almost in tears.
- Right?
Reminiscing
- You were playing Zo In Sung.
- Right.
It's from "The Classic."
- I to you
- Please.
Throw the green onion away.
- Throw the green onion away.
- What's with the green onion?
- Jae Suk...
- Is the green onion the issue?
- What did he have that we didn't?
- Beats me.
What?
(The mic is tossed at him.)
He took it.
(He naturally receives
the green onion mic.)
Seriously?
(That triggers a lip-sync relay.)
Pass it to Jong Kook.
After this line.
Haha.
I to you
(I to you)
(Instead of dumbbells,
the singer grabs a mic today.)
Pass it to Ji Hyo.
(The precious)
I love it!
(The lip-sync relay is on point!)
I love it.
(Without regret,
let us remember it like a painting)
- The song's over.
- It is.
And we're done.
- Next...
- Was this "I Can See Your Voice?"
The song that has me on my feet.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo, we'll go with you.
"You in My Blurred Memories."
By Hyun Jin Young.
(Jong Kook stands as the song begins.)
Why can't you sit still to this song?
(The role-playing expert
starts setting the tone.)
Trudging around is crucial
in this performance.
You can't acknowledge the song yet.
We should look like we don't care.
He switched over to a dumbbell.
Be careful not to throw that one.
Don't throw it.
We won't be able to catch it.
Just know that
we won't be able to catch it.
Don't throw it.
- Not yet.
- Is that alcohol you're drinking?
(The long intro is over
and now the song begins.)
(Spurt)
What's the matter with her?
(Spraying water)
- What's wrong with you?
- Seriously?
I mean...
Why would you shoot water at me?
Seriously?
(She does it once again.)
- Are you kidding me?
- What's your problem?
What was that?
- You...
- Nicely done.
Why are you doing this?
That's right.
That's the move.
(He goes from complaining to dancing.)
My feet...
- I'm not kidding.
- Are you all right?
Shouldn't we ring the bell?
- All right.
- Okay.
Ji Hyo's next.
Keep this up and we'll ring the bell.
We'll ring the bell.
We have enough
for about 40 minutes of the show.
- Only 40 minutes?
- Are you sure?
We already have enough
for about 40 minutes.
- Definitely.
- You know what?
Let's film enough for two episodes.
- What?
- Two episodes.
Let's film enough for two episodes.
While we're here,
let's film enough for two episodes.
- At least one and a half.
- Right. One and a half.
One and a half. Let's not get greedy.
All right.
- This is the song Haha chose.
- Which one is it?
- I'm not messing around.
- Really?
(Oh!)
On your feet.
(The intro that has our hearts pounding)
On your feet!
- The Republic of Korea!
- The Republic of Korea.
The Republic of Korea, on your feet.
(We remember the cheers from that day.)
We can do it!
We've got this!
The Republic of Korea!
For victory
(Off the rails)
(A hooligan has entered the room.)
Unbelievable.
- For victory
- Hold on a second.
You look like a prisoner.
That looks like the rope
used to restrain prisoners.
A rope used to restrain prisoners.
Get him!
(Arresting the hooligan has been ordered.)
Unbelievable.
Who spiked his food?
The World Cup takes place this year.
- Right.
- Yes, in November.
That rope... You look like a prisoner.
- Here. Check this out.
- Who's that?
Can we take a break?
(The prisoner is transported.)
Look.
You look like a prisoner.
Check him out.
That's the case for everyone.
(I won't ever disobey the law again.)
- Can we lie down for a bit?
- We need a break.
- Exactly.
- Let's take a break.
- Jae Suk.
- Let's take a break!
I'm so exhausted. I'm done.
Let's rest.
This is the finale.
Let us rest!
(It's not over yet.)
Just tell me, Suk Jin.
Should I knock him over or what?
Knock him over.
What do you want me to do?
What should I do?
- What's that?
- You want me to knock you over?
All right, then. For the finale,
let us listen to Chan Hee's...
- Look at him.
- song that can't stop him.
A song that can't stop him.
Let me ask him.
This will be the last song.
- All right!
- Chan Hee's pick! Great.
Chan Hee, just tell him already
and get this over with.
Please choose a ballad.
- I'm exhausted.
- Me too.
I can't digest it.
I feel like throwing up.
I learned jiu-jitsu.
Should I bring him down with a chokehold?
- Go ahead.
- I can't stand it.
- Please do.
- Can you calm him down?
- I should make him pass out.
- I feel like throwing up.
Can someone shut his mouth?
- So? Did you get his request?
- Did you get it?
I did.
- But if this song starts playing,
- We need some rest.
you shouldn't be behind the camera.
- Suk Jin.
- You shouldn't.
It's a song that can't stop you.
Of course. You can't help but dance.
It can't stop you,
so you should come on out.
What is this song?
(What is Chan Hee's immortal song?)
(It's "In the Bus" by ZaZa.)
- Bombastic!
- Let's go!
Bombastic!
This is...
It's "In the Bus."
(You can't help but dance to this song.)
Hurry. You must rap.
(A solo shot on Chan Hee)
There you go.
Chan Hee!
I say, Kang. You say, Chan Hee.
Kang Chan Hee!
(Shout out Kang Chan Hee!)
What is he doing?
- What are you doing?
- What's he doing?
- Hey.
- What's wrong with you?
(A weird mid-aged man
behaves unpredictably.)
- What on earth is wrong with you?
- What?
I didn't throw it hard.
He just loves being here.
He loves that we're on an outing.
Isn't it so nice?
Isn't it nice to be on an outing?
(Suddenly acting like an idol)
So Min, you need to put on gloves.
(Laughing)
(It's been a while since we last
saw her acting as an old-time idol.)
(Falling)
(But her age is telling on her.)
Gosh, that was hilarious.
That hurt.
- Jae Suk, let's rest up for real.
- That was hilarious.
- That was nice.
- Wasn't it hilarious?
Let's play a slow song.
A slow song?
Hold on.
Wait. What is this?
Is it really Suk Jin's last day?
Why are you doing this?
Is that why you brought us here
to make memories?
Why are you trying to break us off?
- But at least...
- Don't break us off!
We can't part ways like this.
Sing with me.
(A song dedicated to Suk Jin
who is leaving the show)
(Because he made a slip of the tongue...)
(during the opening,
he has to say goodbye now.)
(They hold his hands
as they're not ready to let him go.)
Everyone, come here. Don't be awkward.
Thank you for your work.
- I learned a lot from you.
- Finally,
he picked his successor
who was born in 1971.
- And he's leaving us soon.
- I learned a lot from you.
Stay healthy, Suk Jin.
- "Stay healthy?"
- Stay healthy.
- Good work, Suk Jin.
- Thank you for your hard work.
I'm only sharing this now,
but Chan Hee asked
if he could be Suk Jin's successor.
(He'd make a perfect successor
if age was the only condition.)
He went...
Thank you for everything.
I will be... What was that?
(What was that?)
(Jae Suk ruins the grave moment.)
It was about to reach the climax.
- I was about to wrap it up.
- That was enough.
He was immersed in the skit.
- I was about to wrap it up.
- That was more than enough.
- We did more than enough.
- We did.
Let's rest up a little.
- Let's clean up, and...
- Let's take a five.
Let's lie down.
I'm going to take a nap.
He's such a rascal.
What's wrong with him?
But Jae Suk's done enough.
- Right.
- I think he's done enough.
Are you jumping ropes? What?
My gosh. Two, three,
- four...
- Look at him.
- I guess I can't do that.
- You're still really healthy.
What? A 50-year-old
can easily pull this off.
Isn't it really nice?
(Showing off his good health
by jumping ropes)
- He's amazing.
- He really is.
Go for 200.
Suk Jin will try jumping 200 times!
- He'll go for it.
- It's "Dad's Challenge!"
- "Dad's Challenge!"
What if I actually jump 200 times?
- What if you can't?
- For real?
He can't even jump 50 times with this.
It's because of this.
- Fifty times?
- Yes.
- You want to make a bet?
- A bet on what?
- Doing the dishes.
- Okay.
- Doing the dishes?
- I think he can easily jump 50.
No, he'll get stuck for sure.
Let's do it.
- Let's just stick together.
- Me too.
It's not easy to jump 50 times
with normal ropes.
Okay, you guys...
- If it hits the sofa in the back...
- Fifty times.
Doing the dishes and the cooking class.
(A bet with doing the dishes
and the cooking class at stake)
We're all on one team.
You must say, "challenge"
before you start.
- You do it.
- Here I go.
(Who will be the winner?)
Here I go.
- "Dad's Challenge!"
- Let's clean up the table first.
- No, you don't have to.
- Still...
I feel more stable with it.
Or should we play a game
to decide who cleans up the table?
(They start cleaning up the table
although Suk Jin said no.)
- Like this?
- Not even a single person...
is on my side?
What is it?
(Warming up)
I'm kind of losing interest in it.
Aren't you guys going to watch it?
- They are...
- Aren't you going to see him jump?
- This is...
- Should I just do the dishes?
Yes, let's just do the dishes.
Jae Suk, should I just do the dishes?
Just tell me how he did later.
I'll go to the restroom.
I'm losing my will all of a sudden.
Suk Jin, just forget it.
What are they doing?
Why are they paying no attention?
- Let's do it.
- Go ahead and try it.
I'm losing all of my interest.
I'll sit over here.
It's getting boring.
- But I'll have to do it.
- I know.
Still...
(Peekaboo)
(They're all distracted.)
What's up with you?
It's because it's too hot.
I'll put them on later.
What are you...
Oh, you're jumping ropes. Okay.
I didn't know what you were up to.
Gosh, it's making me lose all my will.
Challenge.
("Dad's Challenge" begins
amid everyone's indifference.)
(Uninterested)
That's it.
How many has he done so far?
How many have you done?
No one's been counting.
(Amid everyone's indifference,
he's jumped about 20 times.)
Please count for him.
- Two, three, four,
- Watch out for the back.
- five, six, seven, eight,
nine... That's forty.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight...
(Will he succeed in his challenge?)
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
(Suk Jin succeeded in his challenge.)
(Kids, Daddy's done it!)
(Everyone said it'd be impossible,
but the dad pulled it off.)
Suk Jin restored his health!
All right. He finally restored it.
(The dad restored his health.)
(Smiling)
- No way.
- That was incredible, Suk Jin.
A healthy life.
It was really hard toward the end.
The last two.
You're really amazing. How did you do it?
Look how healthy Suk Jin is.
That's just a grasshopper.
He looks like a master.
It's so funny, Jae Suk.
It looks like he'll pull off
a double under.
(A grasshopper master who can
jump around with his skinny legs)
That was hilarious.
Shall we sing a song?
No, let's rest up.
Jae Suk, the weather is nice,
- so why don't we go outside?
- Shall we do that?
- I want to go out.
- Hey.
- Let's go out...
- Shall we play foot volleyball?
- Let's do that!
- Go!
I never lose in foot volleyball.
- Okay.
- I never lose in foot volleyball.
Look at Suk Jin.
- Be quiet.
- He's...
Was his challenge for nothing?
(They only checked his health
through jumping ropes.)
Why is no one talking about it?
He's just exhausted in the corner.
He's the one who volunteered to do it.
- We couldn't stop him.
- What is that?
It was just a battle against himself.
Let's go, Suk Jin.
Is there a foot volleyball court?
- It's right over there.
- Let's go play!
Let's go.
Haha, let's go.
- I'm in the restroom.
- Hey!
Haha is pooping.
Goodness.
- Hey!
- You pooper!
- "Pooper?"
- He poops all the time.
Wait a minute. Where did my bag go?
Where is my bag?
Where did my bag go?
It hurts so much.
- Is it there?
- What?
That's mine.
What?
(Inside Jae Suk's bag,)
(there's a key.)
(Why is there a key in his bag?)
Gosh, why am I so thirsty?
Myung Jae.
(He carefully looks around for now.)
Why aren't you coming out?
- What is this?
- Like the sunset
(A mysterious key)
Gosh, that was hilarious.
(Jae Suk got suspicious
after seeing the mysterious key.)
(He begins looking around.)
Can you please stop Jae Suk?
Please stop him for at least ten minutes.
(Meanwhile, the rest of the members
are resting on their own.)
(But he didn't find anything.)
Hey, bring the old man out.
- Coming.
- Let's hurry up and play.
Gosh, I'm so full.
(Jae Suk, who's suspicious,
goes outside for now.)
Let's go out.
(Jae Suk, who's suspicious,
goes outside for now.)
What? Are these snacks?
(A pile of snacks)
Why did they get so many snacks?
(He searches here and there
even right before he goes outside.)
(Jae Suk was searching
through the shoe rack.)
What is this?
(Right then...)
(Something is hidden behind them.)
(A Yoo Jae Suk Box...)
(hidden on the shoe rack?)
(Warning: Do not open.)
(He quickly covers it for now.)
What is this?
Gosh, I'm so full.
What's that?
(What is that?)
I'm so full.
(Yoo Jae Suk Box, Warning: Do not open.)
Goodness.
(A box that says "Do not open")
(What could be inside the box?)
(After thinking for a while,)
(he heads straight to the box
with the key.)
(He hurriedly tries to open the box.)
(There's a phone inside?)
(Jae Suk opened the box
that said, "Do not open.")
(And there was a phone inside?)
(Right then, it got a text.)
Because you broke the rule
and opened the box,
there will be a penalty
at the end of today's race.
(There will be a penalty
at the end of today's race.)
(They were supposed to have fun
with no missions and penalties.)
(But as soon as Jae Suk opened the box,)
(a penalty was given.)
Currently, there's only one person
who will get the penalty,
and you will pick a penalty ball
to decide who gets the penalty.
The penalty balls are hidden
all over the premises.
Five balls among them are hidden
in Fiery Room on the second floor.
Write down the name of the member
you'd like to give a penalty to...
and put it in the box
under the bell outside.
If someone rings the bell
and the race ends,
the person to receive the penalty
will be decided...
by picking the penalty ball,
so you should secretly and quickly
find the penalty balls...
and submit their names
before anyone notices.
(Find the penalty balls fast
and write down the others' names.)
(They got a penalty for opening a box.)
(Jae Suk caused trouble by
opening the box out of curiosity.)
(Approaching)
What are you doing?
It's just that...
(Detective Kim smelled something
fishy and came right over.)
- What is that?
- It's nothing.
Is that so?
(Laughing awkwardly)
You came over like a demon.
- Why are you...
- It's nothing.
They were filming you, so I
thought you were up to something.
It's nothing.
- Is that so?
- Yes, it's nothing.
(Detective Kim gets suspicious
as Jae Suk is being awkward.)
I was wondering what you were up to.
- It's nothing.
- Right?
Of course.
The foot volleyball court
is right next to the building.
- Really?
- A small one.
Darn it! This is frustrating.
(Darn it! This is frustrating.)
It ruined my mood all at once!
(I can't believe we got a penalty.)
- What's wrong? Is something up?
- No, it's nothing.
(Detective Kim approaches him again.)
It looks like something's going on.
No, it's nothing.
(Flustered)
- What is it?
- Let's go.
- Old man.
- Coming!
Stop playing games and come out already.
- Suk Jin!
- Jong Kook.
Why didn't you tell me to come out
when you saw me?
You just met my eyes.
- Hey, tell her to come out.
- Jong Kook!
What? Come on out!
Why didn't you invite me out?
- So Min.
- Yes?
- You should get some rest.
- No.
So Min, get some rest.
Jong Kook. Can you kick the balls?
Shall I?
Here we go.
(They all gather
at the foot volleyball court.)
- What is that?
- A ball. Let's play with this.
Let me see. It's...
What's that?
We can't play with it.
It could hurt your foot.
(Screaming)
We can't play with that.
- It'll hurt your foot.
I almost sprained my ankle.
You should use your hands with this.
(What is this?)
You should use your hands.
That was so cunning.
- Move!
- So Min, come over here.
So Min, look.
- Do you have one too?
- What is that?
It was in my bag. Take a look at yours.
- Really?
- Yes.
What is this?
(There's a key in everyone's bag?)
- Does everyone have it?
- I bet.
Jong Kook.
Can you open your bag?
Is there a key in yours?
- What?
- Open it.
- What is this?
- What's this?
What's wrong? What's going on?
What did you get?
(The members have smelled
something fishy going on.)
- What is it?
- Open your bag.
Do you have one in yours too?
- In the front.
- Wait a minute. What is this?
Open it. This one.
- I wasn't thinking about it.
- She has one too.
- What?
- What is this?
- What's this?
- What is it?
- A key.
It must be a car key.
Car keys don't look like this.
Jae Suk's been acting weird.
Earlier, Jae Suk was...
reading a text on the phone...
- and said, "This is frustrating."
- What is this?
Something's up with Jae Suk.
- It's a mission.
- There's a mission. Darn it.
- Something's going on.
- Yes, there is.
- Who came up with this?
- Something's up with Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, you're up to something,
aren't you?
Since Jae Suk gets flustered
when he gets busted,
- let's just play.
- Where did your energy go?
- Just admit it.
Jae Suk, where did all your energy go?
- Look at him.
- Where did your energy go?
- He's flustered. Mister!
- Mister!
Are you flustered?
- Is something going on?
- Where did your energy...
Didn't you blow on
the green onion earlier?
Something's going on!
- Let's just play.
- Let's play for now.
Since Jae Suk gets flustered
when he gets busted,
let's just play.
Let's have Se Chan and Haha
on different teams.
Jong Kook and I
will be on different teams,
and Suk Jin and Ji Hyo
will be on different teams.
- Okay.
- That'll do, right?
Then I'll bet on Jong Kook's team.
- Okay.
- Let's play!
- Mine!
- That's good.
- That's great.
- Ji Hyo.
- Pass it over. That was great.
- Gosh.
- All right!
Our spy is doing well!
- All right.
- Okay.
Hey, I'm not...
- Let's just play with him for now.
- Hey.
- I'm not a spy.
- Let's just play.
Haha!
(They resume the game
while keeping watch on the spy.)
- We got it.
- Should I just kick it over?
- Seok Sam!
- No.
- All right.
- It's out.
It's in.
(Standing still)
You see?
It's out.
Hey, why can't you serve?
Hey, be honest. Who's having fun here?
(Be honest. Who's having fun here?)
(Who's having fun here?)
- I can't focus.
- Hey.
We can't focus on the game.
- This isn't any fun.
- Right.
- Because we're thinking too much.
- Just play it.
I'm not a spy!
- It's not fun.
- I can't focus.
- Let's resume.
- I can't focus on the game.
- What's with the key?
- We can't focus.
- I know.
- I really want to know.
- What's with the key?
- It's no fun!
- Give us five minutes.
- I can't focus.
Give us free time for five minutes.
- Let us have some free time.
- Then...
- let's do this.
- Let us have five minutes.
The team that wins five points first...
gets to leave.
The losing team remains here.
- Okay, let's do that.
- You get to leave.
- That's a great idea. It's set.
- It's set.
- That's a great idea!
- Isn't it?
- Okay.
- All right.
The team that gets five points
first can go around.
- Okay.
I want to win fast and go around.
Gosh, I'm so rushed. I'm nervous.
- Five points.
- Hurry.
Let's start.
(That's how the game with
free time at stake started.)
Nice.
- Ji Hyo, you should get it.
- Okay.
- Darn it!
- What was that?
(Tightrope walking on the net)
- We won.
That's it!
We got it. Great.
Use your head.
- Use your head.
- Hey.
(A new kind of foot volleyball)
That went out anyway.
- Nice!
- Yes!
- Good. We won.
- Let's go.
- We'll get going.
- Count the time.
Start the clock.
- What could it be?
- Get ready.
Go!
Something we can open with a key?
Isn't this one?
Make sure to cut it at five minutes sharp.
If they don't come back,
we'll serve right away.
If they don't come back
after five minutes, we'll serve.
(He's suspicious of Jae Suk.)
I can't freely enjoy the trip anymore.
I thought we were having
an outing for a change.
(Suk Jin tries to look for something.)
Gosh, there's nothing.
There must be nothing here.
Where could a lock be?
(The only clue they have
is the key they found.)
It wouldn't fit this lock, would it?
(It wouldn't fit this lock, would it?)
- Which one?
- This one.
(They're trying to find the locks
they can open with the key.)
I don't think that'd fit.
(So Min has no idea either.)
Why did they give us the keys?
Why is there lighting here?
Why do you think there's lighting here?
They installed lighting here...
(Detective Kim searches the area as
he finds the lighting suspicious.)
(He spots something.)
("The number of people
who'll get the penalty?")
"The number of people
who'll get the penalty?" Hey!
("The number of people
who'll get the penalty"...)
(is written on the clock.)
It's pointing to one o'clock.
(And the clock is pointing
to one o'clock.)
(Jae Suk couldn't resist
the temptation...)
(and opened the box.)
(A penalty was given right away.)
(Currently, there's only one person
who will get the penalty.)
There's only one who'll get the penalty?
(Jong Kook found out about the clock
that shows the number of people...)
(who will get the penalty.)
Se Chan.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan is searching
a different place.)
(He takes out a box in the kitchen
like it's the most natural thing.)
(During the break a moment ago)
Have some strawberries.
(Se Chan was giving snacks
to the staff members.)
Do you want anything? Do you want snacks?
(Do you want anything?
Do you want snacks?)
(He looked for snacks in the kitchen.)
(His movements became erratic
as if he had found something.)
(Then he took out a box.)
(Yang Se Chan Box, Warning: Do not open)
(Yang Se Chan Box had the same warning.)
There is no key.
(There is no key.)
(He revisited the place
after finding the key.)
(He opens the box.)
What is this?
(Se Chan secretly opened the box!)
Hey, the bell...
There is nothing.
(He takes the phone inside the box
and hides in a room.)
There is nothing.
You are the second person...
who broke the rule and opened the box.
Due to the first rule breaker,
the penalty came to be.
Due to you, the second rule breaker,
the number of people who will get
the penalty increased to two.
Today, penalty balls will be picked
to decide who gets the penalty.
Five among the hidden penalty balls
are at the commissary.
(The secret of today's race)
What is this?
(All members have a mystery box
at different places.)
(If you fail to resist temptation...)
(and open the box with the key,)
(the number of people who will get
the penalty goes up.)
(Submitting the penalty balls
with other members' names...)
(gives you an advantage in this race.)
(Only Jae Suk and Se Chan
know about this hidden mission.)
This is driving me crazy.
(Only Jae Suk and Se Chan
know about this hidden mission.)
Suk Jin.
It says "The number of people
who will get the penalty."
- Where?
- Over there by the cuckoo clock.
- People who will get the penalty.
- The clock
- There is something about this.
- People who will get the penalty.
People who will get the penalty.
- It's pointing to two o'clock.
- What?
- It was pointing to 1 o'clock.
- It's pointing to 2 o'clock now.
- It's pointing to two o'clock.
- What?
- It was pointing to 1 o'clock.
- It's pointing to 2 o'clock now.
(The clock is pointing to 2 o'clock now.)
Was it pointing to 1 o'clock?
The hand was at 2 when I saw it.
Did you move the hand?
- The cuckoo comes out.
- Why is the hand at two?
(Se Chan heads over to the clock.)
- When the cuckoo comes out,
- It's about the number.
it might have the number in its mouth.
No way. Since the hand is at two,
- the number is 2.
- Is the number 2?
The number must be two.
- The number of people...
- Hold on.
The hand moved from 1 to 2
in a matter of minutes...
after Se Chan came to me.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You...
- What about me?
You did something.
- Jong Kook.
- What did you do?
- It's not like that.
- Sit down.
- Some people will get the penalty.
- Why?
- Sit down.
Listen, Jong Kook.
Talk. What is this about?
(Se Chan is unsure
how much he should reveal.)
- I will tell you honestly.
- Okay.
- Talk.
- I did find something.
- You found something.
- That's right.
- You guys need to find it too.
- What do we need to find?
- Tell us what we need to find.
- What is it?
- What comes with a key? A lock.
- That's right.
- You guys need to find that lock.
- But what is it?
- What's inside the lock?
You can decide
if you want to open it or not.
Just find the lock.
Why is time passing so slowly?
Why is five minutes so long?
How many minutes passed?
Let's get ready to attack.
All right. You have 30 seconds.
(30 seconds remaining.)
Five among the hidden penalty balls
are at the commissary.
Okay.
This must be a penalty ball.
(Se Chan found a penalty ball
at the commissary.)
Ten seconds!
(10 seconds remaining.)
Why is there a hole?
(Detective Kim found
a hole for the penalty balls.)
Why is there a hole?
Are we supposed to put something in here?
(Detective Kim found
a hole for the penalty balls.)
- Let's go.
- Let's begin.
Se Chan, we will begin.
- All right.
- Hurry over here.
Hurry over here.
There is nothing.
(Se Chan doesn't move away
from the commissary.)
Why is no one coming?
(No one is coming.)
- I don't think they are coming.
- They aren't listening.
They should listen.
Why aren't they listening?
Then why did I wait?
- I don't think they are coming.
- Are you going to ignore the rules?
- I am going to leave.
- I am going to leave too.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
- What is this?
- Only we followed the rules.
(All members began to walk around.)
All right.
Suddenly...
(Haha and JI Hyo begin
to search the place.)
Did you search here?
I don't know what's going on.
I haven't searched so cluelessly
in a while.
(Jae Suk gets started with the mission.)
Five balls among them are hidden
in Fiery Room on the second floor.
(Fiery Room)
This is nerve-racking.
(He enters the Fiery Room
to find the penalty balls.)
(He acquires 1 penalty ball
upon entering.)
The text said
there are five penalty balls.
(1 more penalty ball)
(He finds another one.)
Good.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan...)
(writes a name on the penalty balls
he found earlier.)
(He put down So Min and Haha's names.)
(He submitted the penalty balls.)
(They sail through the mission
with the information they gained.)
Where are the other penalty balls?
(So Min searches the hole
for the penalty balls.)
(What is this?)
Why is there a hole?
(Why is there a hole?)
Am I supposed to put it in here?
Like this?
(It's her key!)
(She drops the key through the hole.)
(Even the production crew
gets startled by her action.)
Is it wrong?
(She made the mistake
of dropping her key.)
There is a hole.
(Thus, she lost
the crucial piece of the race.)
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin)
What is this?
(He found a penalty ball.)
(He puts it back.)
(It's a complete mess.)
(Haha is searching the room
on the 2nd floor.)
(He finds Suk Jin's box.)
(Glancing over)
(He hides the box
in the guise of his belly fat.)
(Haha hides Suk Jin's box!)
There is a pen.
- Seriously.
- I think this is...
Will there be a poll?
(A pen?)
What's going on?
I don't have a clue.
(They stick together and guess
that there might be a poll.)
Is the hole for the ping pong balls?
That hole?
I saw ping pong balls earlier.
- You might be right.
- It's the size of a ping pong ball.
- Right?
- Yes.
That must be it.
You are supposed to put something.
You are supposed to put something
like a member's name.
I saw ping pong balls earlier.
I see that you are supposed...
- to write names on them.
- Is that it?
(The two of them make perfect deductions!)
Are we supposed to put
ping pong balls in there?
What should I do?
I put my key in there. Oh, no.
How will I get it out?
(She belatedly gets a reality check.)
(She looks, but the key is
already inside the box.)
What should I do?
I need to get my key out.
There were ping pong balls. I saw them.
(He finds something.)
There were ping pong balls.
(He takes out the key from his bag.)
(He takes out the box.)
(However,)
(It doesn't open!)
(It's Song Ji Hyo Box.)
There is a box
that is dedicated to each member.
Suk Jin.
Yoo Jae Suk Box.
(Suk Jin finds
Yoo Jae Suk Box at the same time.)
Jae Suk opened it.
There is a box
that is dedicated to each member.
"Do not open."
Suk Jin, Jae Suk opened it...
and received a text.
- A text?
- Then...
- he groaned.
- Really?
- I guess you shouldn't open it.
- Is that it?
- It says "Do not open."
I won't open it.
Where is Ji Hyo?
(He wants to tell Ji Hyo about her box.)
I found Ji Hyo's box,
so I want to tell her about it.
Where did she go?
I am here.
Your box is in the room.
(Jong Kook gives her
the location of her box!)
It's in the room.
(Jong Kook gives her
the location of her box!)
What?
(She finds the box.)
My name is on it.
(Song Ji Hyo Box, Warning: Do not open)
(The warning says, "Do not open.")
(What will be Ji Hyo's decision?)
(Clicking)
(She opens the box.)
(Ji Hyo ended up opening the box.)
(Thus, the number of people...)
It's a cell phone.
(who will get the penalty go up by 1.)
Seriously.
- Hey, the number... Suk Jin.
- What?
The number rose to 3.
The clock is pointing to 3 o'clock.
- Is it pointing to three o'clock?
- People who will get the penalty?
(People who will get the penalty?)
What is this?
It does say, "The number of people
who will get the penalty."
(The clock is pointing to 3 o'clock.)
What is this?
(Jae Suk found out belatedly...)
Will three people receive the penalty now?
(that the number of people...)
This is bad.
(who will receive the penalty can go up.)
Gosh, this...
If all boxes get opened,
everyone will get a penalty.
So Min, don't open it.
Listen.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Don't open it.
- Is it better if I don't open it?
- Don't open the box.
What is it? You know, right?
- What is it?
- Don't open it.
I know you will open it
if I tell you not to do it.
- I don't have the box.
- I didn't open mine.
I don't have the key.
- I will write it down. Whatever.
- Suk Jin, don't open it.
Ji Suk Jin.
I am sure it's a good thing.
Don't open it.
(Suk Jin suddenly writes
his name on the ping pong ball!)
Why did you write down your name?
Just because. I am sure it's a good thing.
- Just because.
- Aren't these penalty balls?
People whose names are written
will be exempt from the penalty.
Don't open more locks.
- I won't do it.
- Don't open more locks.
Is it bad to open it?
It's bad to open it.
- I am so curious.
- We can tell them, can't we?
- Should we tell them?
- We will lose if they open theirs.
- We should tell them.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Don't open the locks.
- Don't open more locks.
- Why not?
- We shouldn't do that.
- I will tell you.
- If you open the locks,
- The number...
- more people will get the penalty.
- Right?
I knew it.
- Don't open more locks.
- Stop opening them.
Hold on. How many people opened the locks?
- The hand was at one at first.
- One,
- two...
- You opened it.
Three locks have been opened.
The hand was at one at first.
I am telling you not to open them
because I know the rules.
You should have told us sooner.
Seriously.
- I didn't know what was happening.
- Why did you hide information?
- All right.
- What are the ping pong balls for?
- What?
Are they for an exemption
or receiving the penalty?
- Exemption.
That's right.
(They lie right away.)
Exemption? Okay.
I did the right thing
by writing down my name.
- Exemption?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- If you see a ping pong ball,
write down your name.
- Are you certain?
- Yes.
- I don't think that's the case.
- We can't trust him.
- What are you going to do then?
- Whom will you trust then?
- We can't trust him.
- They are for the penalty.
- His reaction is suspicious.
In that case, you should open it.
- Okay.
- Open it and share information.
- If you open the lock...
- Don't open it.
- Be honest.
- Don't do it.
- I am too curious.
If you open it...
If you open it,
all of us will receive a penalty.
- Listen to it.
- The ping pong balls will be null.
- What's inside the box?
- All of us will die!
So whose name do we need to write down?
All of us will die!
- Write down other people's names.
- Don't open the locks.
Write down other people's names, okay?
Write down other people's names.
- I am too curious.
- If we get hung up on this matter,
- it won't be good. Let's go inside.
- And play the game?
(No way.)
- Jae Suk, get some rest.
- Hey.
What kind of noodles did he get?
- Stop it.
- How could you think of the game?
Let's have tea time.
- Okay.
- Tea time.
Come inside.
Had you guys stayed still,
no one would have gotten...
the penalty today.
Why did you open the box?
There were a key and a box.
We couldn't help but open it.
- That's right. You were curious.
- There was a warning too!
Where is it?
Gosh.
Seriously.
I am so curious.
I am at that age
where I am really curious.
- Who?
- Me.
(While the others are resting,
Haha and Ji Hyo come outside.)
Will you write down Se Chan's name?
(Haha writes down Se Chan's name
on 2 penalty balls.)
Do you have two?
I have more.
Yoo Jae Suk.
(What's the name on Haha's third ball?)
- I will write down Se Chan's name.
- This is my third ball.
- I have more.
- Really?
That's incredible.
You should write Se Chan's name.
I will write down your name.
Haha.
- Don't be like that.
- All right.
- Haha.
- Go and find my box.
- Okay?
- Haha.
I really sound like a thug.
You are such a thug.
- Come on.
- But it was so much fun.
Ji Hyo.
- Haha.
- I will write down your name.
- I am sorry. I will be good.
- Ji Hyo.
I will be good. I am serious.
(So Min was searching the barbecue spot.)
(Gasping)
(Seh finally found her box.)
What should I do? I don't have the key.
I thought I was supposed
to put it in there.
I will keep it here for a second.
What should I do?
I can't open it, right?
Where could my box be?
(Haha hasn't found his box yet.)
(He looks around the place.)
(He spots a moving camera.)
(He communicates with the staff
who is moving the camera.)
(Is this the place?)
(Nodding)
It has been a while, okay?
(He finds a penalty ball.)
(Haha found 6 penalty balls.)
(Kim Jong Kook)
I wrote down everyone's name.
I am good at finding these balls.
Why can't I find my box?
(Jae Suk writes something at a corner.)
(He submits two balls.)
(Being the 1st one to open the box,
Jae Suk knows the exact rules.)
(He writes down the members' names
and submits the penalty balls.)
If we ring the bell, the game will end.
Shall we just ring the bell?
- Shall we do it?
- Se Chan is torn about it too.
I think I should write down names
and submit the balls.
Whose name should I write?
My name or someone else's name?
(Suk Jin is still unsure.)
I don't know
if I should write down my name.
I don't think I will be able
to resist opening the box.
I want to find my box and open it.
(He is really curious
about the real rules.)
Should I bring Suk Jin's box
and see what happens?
Whose box?
(Haha brings out
Suk Jin's box he hid before.)
It holds, right?
- Yes, it does. It's nice.
- Suk Jin, your box is here.
Where? Give it to me.
Let's open it.
- Suk Jin, don't open it.
- Maybe you shouldn't open it.
Then more people will get the penalty.
- I am serious.
- Suk Jin.
Aren't you curious?
I am serious.
More people will get the penalty.
- Will you open it?
- Yes.
(He is really curious about
what's inside the box.)
I am so curious.
We should go and ring the bell.
Is it bad to open the box?
- Really?
- Ji Hyo, should I keep it locked?
(Suk Jin wants to know
what the ping pong balls are for.)
I am serious, Suk Jin.
Why would you tell me not to open it
when you opened yours?
- Open it then.
- That's right.
(Suk Jin takes out the key.)
(Haha watches closely
since he is curious as well.)
- You don't know what will happen.
- Will you really open it?
Yes, I will.
It's Pandora's Box.
I want to know the secret
behind the ping pong balls.
- No!
- Why?
(No!)
Shut your mouth.
"Shut your mouth?"
Here comes the royal secret inspector!
What? That's the mission of the day?
- Will you really open it?
- You shouldn't open it.
- I haven't opened it yet.
- Don't do it.
- You shouldn't open it.
- Why not?
Why is he trying to open it?
He wants to open it.
- He wants to open it.
- You shouldn't open it.
It's suspicious that you are trying
to keep me from opening it.
- Se Chan...
- Everyone is against it.
- He opened it.
- Gosh!
- Don't open it.
- Se Chan, just ring the bell.
- It's meaningless.
- He is trying to open the box.
- Don't open it.
- Just ring the bell.
- It's meaningless.
- He is trying to open the box.
(Opening)
He opened it.
(He opened Pandora's Box in the end.)
(The number of people
who will get the penalty)
He opened it.
(Captain Ji's curiosity
made more people get the penalty.)
- Can I read it with you?
- There is a text.
(He gets a reality check.)
Didn't I tell you not to do it?
Even the production crew
wanted you to stop.
Haha, can you turn back time?
- I think I can use it once.
- Really?
Say, "The one who turns back time!"
The one who turns back time!
(Haha's skill allows him
to turn back time by 10 minutes!)
What are you doing?
(The time master's incredible skill
unfolds before their eyes.)
Here comes the royal secret inspector!
Tie him up right this instant!
It worked.
(The box goes back to its original spot.)
He turned back time.
He is doing something!
- He is doing something!
(Did something happen?)
(The superpower skit ends.)
- It worked.
(The skit doesn't change the fact
that he opened his box.)
- It worked.
- Shall we ring the bell?
Shall we play a game outside?
Shall we ring the bell?
- Ring the bell.
- Shall I do that?
- I will ring it.
(With everyone's agreement,
Se Chan goes to ring the bell.)
The race has ended.
Please gather around outside.
- Outside.
- Let's gather around.
- Everyone.
- Yes.
Since the bell rang,
the race came to an end.
As some of you found out,
Captain Ji's last race had a hidden rule.
You were up to decide
whether or not to open the box...
with a warning that said, "Do not open."
Seriously. Why did you open the box?
Had all of you resisted temptation,
everyone would have gone home
without receiving the penalty.
It was impossible since we had the key.
Seriously. Stop blaming me.
The box was asking to be opened.
The opened boxes decided...
how many people will get the penalty.
- Four people will get it.
- Four people will get the penalty.
Inside the box are penalty balls.
Seriously.
People whose names got written
are the candidates for the penalty.
I wrote down my name.
Four penalty balls will be chosen.
Even if the names overlap,
we won't pick more balls.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Then it isn't too bad.
- I will reveal the names.
- There are 15 balls in total.
- That's a lot.
That's a lot.
Jong Kook has one ball.
- Who wrote down his name?
- When did it happen?
Jae Suk has one ball.
Who wrote down my name?
- Haha has one ball.
- One?
Se Chan has three balls.
(Yang Se Chan)
- So Min has four balls.
- Why do I have so many?
- Who wrote down my name?
- You did.
I wrote down my name on one ball only.
Suk Jin has five balls.
(Ji Suk Jin)
- How about Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo has zero balls.
For goodness' sake.
- Hold on.
- Who wrote down my name?
Who wrote down my name?
How do I have four balls?
Everyone's name got written
except for Ji Hyo's.
Captain Ji will pick four balls.
Before that,
I will reveal the penalty.
This is the last penalty
during Captain Ji's term.
(The last penalty
during Captain Ji's term)
The weather is nice
and there is a clean valley nearby.
You will go into the valley.
- Go in?
- Hey!
(Go into the valley.)
(Go into the valley?)
You will go into the valley.
(It has been a while
since a penalty in the wild.)
That's ridiculous.
(The valley is still cold in March.)
What are we doing?
- Are we getting into the water?
- You're getting into the water.
- It's too cold.
- That's too harsh.
I have only one pair of underwear.
Is it going to be okay?
(Captain Ji's term will end
with the grand finale penalty.)
All right. Captain Ji,
come on and draw balls.
My goodness. Please.
Mix them well.
Suk Jin, just pick your names.
I'm sorry, I opened the box.
- Captain Ji.
- Yes.
- Please.
- I told you not to do it.
- I know.
- All right.
(What's the first name he picks?)
Ji Suk Jin.
Announce the name.
(Who is it among the 6 of them
except for Ji Hyo?)
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Announce the name.
Ji Suk Jin.
(Ji Suk Jin)
(Captain Ji takes the initiative.)
I knew it.
Captain Ji, thank you.
- One more time!
- One!
- Pick your name four times.
(What's the name
on the second penalty ball?)
(Laughing)
What is it?
(He can't help but smile.)
Why? What is it?
Ji Suk Jin.
(Ji Suk Jin)
(The captain picked his name again.)
- I can't believe this.
- One more time!
- He's a real captain.
- He's Captain Ji.
- He deserves to be a captain.
Captain!
- It can't happen four times.
- Captain.
Is it me?
(What's the third name?)
- I bet it's Ji Suk Jin.
- I don't think so.
- It's Ji Suk Jin.
- Is it me? He just looked at me.
It must be Ji Suk Jin.
Yang Se Chan.
(Yang Se Chan)
(Se Chan is getting into the water.)
- I'm so unlucky.
- Se Chan is going into the water.
- Se Chan, one more time!
- The last one.
This is the last ball.
Se Chan.
It is most likely to be So Min.
(So Min has the second
largest number of balls.)
I know. I want to run away.
So Min has the biggest number of balls.
- It's you and So Min.
- And me?
We don't know that. We have one ball each.
It has to be Ji Suk Jin.
Captain Ji.
It would've been funny
if he picked his name four times.
Is it Ji Suk Jin again?
(He bursts into laughter.)
- No way.
- That can't be it.
- That's unbelievable.
- What is it? That can't be it.
- No way.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- I knew it.
- Is it me?
- He completes Running Man.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes!
(The last one to get a penalty
is Jae Suk.)
- He had only one ball.
- He had only one!
(It's Haha who wrote Jae Suk's name.)
- He had only one ball.
- He had only one!
He had only one ball, and he got picked.
- There was only one ball.
- It was the only ball.
I picked the only ball.
Yoo Jae Suk completes Running Man.
- This is interesting.
- This is the worst.
How is this possible?
All right. The three of you will
go to the valley now.
- Let's go.
Can you believe this?
It's so cold. I'll freeze to death.
- We're getting into the water.
- I love it.
Your mind is like water,
and water is like your mind.
- The wind is cold.
- I'll get into the water.
(They arrive at the valley
with reverent pride.)
It's the perfect weather
to get into the water.
My gosh. I can't believe this.
- Gosh, this place is...
- Hurry.
Let's just get this over with.
- I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
- I know.
Why did you open the box?
If we don't do this now,
we won't have another chance.
That's not true. We can do it in summer.
When else would I get into the water?
You can try it any time.
Is he leaving?
Go ahead and do it.
What's with the color of the water?
- But...
- Let's do this.
It's not cold.
- It will be all right.
- It's not cold.
You can get into the water one by one.
It's cold, isn't it?
- Go ahead and do it.
- This isn't going to work.
- Why?
- It's too cold.
No. Are you just saying that?
(They start getting into the water.)
My goodness.
(Groaning)
(Screaming)
- My gosh.
- Go to the middle of the stream.
Running Man forever!
- He sounds so silly.
- My gosh.
(He tries to finish it
only with his feet in the water.)
This is so cold.
Hey, Se Chan.
(Se Chan massages his heart
making a fuss.)
Se Chan, you're so cool.
(This isn't like the wild
variety show on other channels.)
(The urban entertainers are
not good with wildness.)
Is it cold?
I can't feel my feet.
You can do this.
(It's time to soak
themselves in the water.)
One, two, three. Let's do this.
(Finally soaking in)
Gosh, it's so cold.
(His vengeance begins.)
(It turns into a water fight
when no one told them to do it.)
Gosh, it's so cold.
Suk Jin is not going in.
(The grand retirement ceremony
for Captain Ji)
Suk Jin is not going in.
He's not soaking himself.
- Come here.
- I don't want to.
Se Chan, you're so cool.
Are you all right?
(We will keep running
with the energy of the stream.)
Okay.
(Captain Ji retires
with the cool water activity.)
- Well done.
- Great job.
(Captain Ji retires
with the cool water activity.)
(In this world,)
(is there anything
you can't buy with money?)
(You need money...)
(to eat.)
(For a private collection)
(You need money...)
(to be good-looking.)
(Trot yellow)
(Auntie brown)
(Even to become hip,)
(you need money.)
This is what I can do for you.
This is so thrilling.
(You're broke.)
(If they spend money recklessly,)
(they will end up becoming a farmhand.)
(The Real-life Fund Management Race)
(Are you an owner of money?)
(Are you a slave of money?)
(How Much Do You Want to Spend?)