It's warm under the sunlight,
but it's chilly like early winter
in the shade.
The weather is so nice.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
Hello. The weather is lovely today.
Hello, everyone.
This is Running Man. Nice to meet you.
This is where I start today.
What's today's mission?
What are we doing today?
Why am I here alone?
I'll betray them.
(Incoherent)
Hi, how have you been?
Hello.
- Isn't Pacquiao coming today?
- Yes.
All right. Pacquiao.
(Pacquiao meets Yoo Jae Suk
on Running Man after 4 years.)
Second time, okay? You remember me?
One, two. One, two.
(The unprecedented legend
who conquered 8 weight divisions)
(The greatest boxer
in boxing history)
(The legendary boxer,
Manny Pacquiao is coming soon.)
In today's race,
R money will be important.
- R money?
- Yes.
So you will go and get
the seed money for the race.
The seed money?
We have three different places
ready in Yeouido.
Okay.
Each place offers 500, 700,
and 1,000 dollars.
The members who come to the same place
will share the money.
- Oh, dear.
- Think carefully before you decide.
This will be very tiring. My gosh.
I'm sure the tiger moths
will go for the 1,000 dollars.
I'm so sick of this.
I can see it already.
I know who will say,
"I'll go for the 1,000 dollars."
You will choose 1,000 dollars
anyway. That's what you do, right?
When I'm to choose between go and stop,
I always choose to go.
- I know.
- That's who I am.
I think there will be three
including Suk Jin.
So Min and you.
- Right.
- You should go with 1,000 dollars.
I'll choose between 700 and 500.
You should arrange things for me.
Okay. I'll take care of it.
- All right.
- I'm on it.
- Okay.
- Bye.
He's so docile.
(He's so docile.)
(A docile friend)
- Hey, Haha.
- Suk Jin.
What are you going to choose?
If you tell me
where you are going now,
I won't show up there.
- Really?
- Yes.
Where are you going?
I'll go for 1,000 dollars.
A thousand?
So you'll be there
no matter what, right?
That's my decision for now,
but I can't be sure.
Suk Jin, can't you make it clear?
I'll go with 700 dollars.
- You want 700?
- I changed my mind.
I hope we won't meet
at the place for 1,000 dollars...
and embarrass ourselves.
- I'll go with 1,000 dollars.
- Let's slap each other in the face.
- If we meet up there.
- That's...
No, I'll go with 1,000 dollars.
If we meet at the place
for 700 dollars, you can slap me.
- Okay.
- If we meet at the place...
- for 1,000 dollars, I'll slap you.
- Okay.
All right.
I'll go for 1,000 dollars.
- I'll put my face on this.
- All right, Suk Jin.
- Bye.
(That's how
they decided their destinations.)
My face will be fine
as long as it's not flayed.
(A sudden change of heart)
This is not my first time.
My gosh.
I can even risk my family.
I'm so sick of this already.
I'm so annoyed, seriously.
I've had enough.
They all would think
the same thing as me.
"Jeon So Min will choose
1,000 dollars for sure."
(So Min is trying to use her brain.)
Today, I'll go for 500 dollars.
Think about it. If 4 people
go to the place for 1,000 dollars,
they get 250 dollars each.
They wouldn't come
to get 500 dollars.
I'm...
a strategist.
(Determined)
I bet Suk Jin and Jae Suk
will go for 1,000 dollars.
And Jong Kook will probably
go for 700 dollars.
Se Chan will go for 1,000 dollars,
but I'm not sure about So Min.
I don't know what she will choose.
Jong Kook will have to use
his fists today.
Jong Kook will...
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Today, you can finally use
your fists legitimately.
Pacquiao is coming today.
Let's have a fight today.
I'll assist you today.
- Hey.
- Yes.
Pacquiao is younger than me, but...
Is he younger than you?
But I'll treat him
like an older brother.
(He will be polite to the man
who's 2 years younger than him.)
No, Jong Kook.
You should show him
what you've practiced.
With your one-two-three punch...
- Today...
- Hey, you know what?
You'll see me
get punched in the chin.
Jong Kook, I'm so excited today.
I know. This is nice.
- I love boxing.
- I know.
(That's how Se Chan chose
his destination without hesitation.)
Okay.
I'll finish him
with my one-two punch today.
Hello.
Today...
(Trifling shadow-boxing)
I'm meeting Pacquiao today.
- He's a national boxer.
- Really?
- Are you a national boxer?
- A former national boxer.
Really?
I'm meeting Pacquiao today.
I saw him earlier.
My friend went to see him,
but I have some work to do.
Really?
I saw you on TV.
You did? Nice to meet you.
- Can I take a photo with you?
- Sure.
(It's photo time.)
One, two, three.
What should I do
when I meet Pacquiao?
Can you give me any good tips?
First...
When you meet with him,
he will get ready to fight.
The basic posture of boxing.
Before that...
(A surprise attack)
I do this right away?
While you pretend to say hi,
just go like this.
- While saying hi to him?
- Then you go like this right away.
While saying hi?
Is this the place for 1,000 dollars?
Hang on.
There's Se Chan.
Why is he interviewing people
on the street?
Thank you.
(Running)
What? You startled me.
Gosh, I was startled.
- Hello.
- Jae Suk.
I just met the head
of the Boxers Association.
- The Korean Boxers Association?
- When I was doing this,
he knew I was
going to meet Pacquiao.
He told me to jab at Pacquiao
when he said hi.
As soon as I meet Pacquiao,
I throw a jab.
While saying hi to him, I jab him.
You've never met
Pacquiao before, have you?
This is my first time.
I'm so nervous.
Real martial artists like me...
Your fist smells sweet already,
Jae Suk.
- Hey.
- You'll attract bees.
If Suk Jin raises his hand
in Yeouido like this,
- Bees...
- bees will fill this area.
If Suk Jin raises
his fist like this...
- Bees will show up.
Because it smells sweet.
- Are you here for 1,000 dollars?
- Sure.
Gosh, you're unbelievable.
I'm here to get 500 dollars.
I'm the one
who will get 500 dollars.
I don't see anyone else here.
All right. Is it over?
Not yet. They are still moving.
Someone might come here.
I hope there won't be anyone else.
It should end here.
I like the Han River.
It's been a long time.
How did it end up like this?
I just came here,
and things happened this way.
Today...
(Will Jong Kook get
700 dollars just like this?)
Pacquiao is coming, so I guess...
luck is coming my way.
- Okay.
- It's us.
- Two.
- Please wait for a moment.
- Okay.
(If it ends like this,
they will get 500 dollars each.)
- Someone's here.
- Who is it?
Yang Se Chan.
(Honey Ji shows up.)
Is he really here?
Are you really here?
Here comes the honey fist.
- Look. It's him.
- My gosh.
- Do you know why he came here?
- Why?
He thinks this place will be fun.
- For fun?
- He's...
- He's unbelievable.
- That's who he is.
- He's here for the show.
- You can't be here.
- He's so weak.
- Hey.
If you fail to step on here,
- You can't.
- you can't get the money.
That's ridiculous.
- I'll block it.
- You have to come up here.
- That doesn't make sense.
- If you fail, you get no money.
- I can get through this.
Darn it.
(The 2-on-1 match begins.)
The honey punch is here.
Bees, gather around.
Bees, the honey punch is here.
Honey punch...
You can't come in here.
- My gosh.
- So you really came.
- Of course.
- You changed your character.
- What character?
- What do you mean?
Hey, I knew you'd come here.
It's obvious who would come here.
- Once So Min comes...
- If this is it, it's fine.
- There's someone.
- No one should come.
Jae Suk, someone else is coming.
Who is it?
Is that Haha?
That's Haha.
Gosh, Suk Jin.
(Haha shows up.)
- Suk Jin.
- Hey.
- Go away.
- What is Haha doing here?
He's unbelievable.
I said I'd go for 1,000,
and you said you'd go for 700.
- My goodness.
- Why are you here?
So the places for 700 and 300...
- He put his cheek on this.
- Seriously...
- I told you not to come.
- You put your cheek on this.
- You came here despite the bet?
- You should get slapped.
- No, you should get slapped.
- It's you.
- Hey.
- You said you'd go for 700 dollars.
What are they doing?
- Why are they here?
- Why did you come?
You know what?
I did some thinking.
It's in my genes.
If I didn't come here, I'd go crazy.
I knew the three of you
would come here.
- That's my DNA.
- You shouldn't come here.
There was nothing to think about.
I chose this as soon
as I heard about the mission.
I gave up on him.
- But what about you?
- I said I'd come here.
We're meeting Pacquiao today.
I need money.
Is it this way?
(Ji Hyo arrives
near one of the spots.)
I don't know.
I don't know where it is.
My gosh.
(Is it the spot for 700 dollars
where Jong Kook is waiting?)
I hope Ji Hyo is not coming.
She said she'd come here.
She's here.
Gosh, it's her.
There's So Min.
- Ji Hyo.
- So Min.
You're here.
(Ji Hyo and So Min get
250 dollars each.)
You should go for 1,000 dollars.
What are you doing here?
There will be too many people.
- He got all the money.
- Four people have come...
- I can't believe this.
- to the spot for 1,000 dollars,
so you get 250 dollars each.
It's 250 dollars. That's not bad.
It's like 2 people for 500 dollars.
But Jong Kook got 700 dollars.
- So this is...
- No.
Ji Hyo and So Min
went for 500 dollars.
- Really?
- Ji Hyo and So Min.
- Why did you come here?
- It's just the way am.
The first choice has come to an end.
Is it over?
Really?
- You get 700 dollars.
- My gosh.
What are you talking about?
(Jong Kook gets 700 dollars
while others get only 250 dollars.)
Are you serious?
How did I get
700 dollars all to myself?
So the first choice
has come to an end.
We will give you another chance
to get more money.
(There's another chance
to get more money.)
You can choose
one of three spots again.
- Okay.
- This is enough.
- One more time?
- I won't move.
How much is it?
We will give you another chance
to get more seed money.
Extra money?
You can choose
one of three spots once again.
Extra money?
They wouldn't bother to move again.
- How many of them will move?
- We should move.
- I'm not going.
- How much is it?
- None of us will move.
- It's 1,000, 700, and 500 again.
I will stay put.
- This is where I live now.
- Haha, listen to me.
I'll make a deal with you.
If you give me 50 dollars,
I'll move.
- I can't do that.
- Then give me 30 dollars.
- Then...
- Otherwise, I'll stay.
- You should give him 50 dollars.
- Just give me 30 dollars.
- And I'll leave.
- If you give me 50, I'll leave.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
- I want only 30 dollars.
- Give me just 50 dollars.
Wait. You two...
- should get only 50 dollars.
- Let's make it 30 each.
- Only 30 dollars each.
- Okay.
Give us 30 dollars each.
- Just make it 50 for you two.
- I won't leave.
- You should give them 10 dollars.
- Let's make it 30 each.
- Pay them.
- Why would I give them ten dollars?
- Just give us 30 dollars each.
- You spend only 20 dollars.
- Give me 30 dollars.
- Make it 30 dollars each.
If you come back here...
- No.
- What if you come back?
Say it to the camera here.
Say that you will pay 100 dollars
if you come back.
- Go ahead and say it.
- If you come back...
If I come back,
I'll pay 100 dollars.
- You did something, didn't you?
- You winked, right?
You crossed your fingers, right?
My fingers? I said it.
If you come back here,
you will let Pacquiao punch you
in the face twice.
Why would Pacquiao punch me?
You should do that
because you broke your promise.
- And you.
- Yes.
You will be separated
from your wife for two months.
Separated?
- For two months?
- If you come back.
- He's mean.
- Just don't come back.
- That's it.
- I'll take it.
I'll take it.
"I'll take it."
Su Jung, you know I'm joking, right?
It's a joke.
- Why is he being like this?
- Is it a joke?
Why is he being
like this these days?
- What do I do?
- I'll stay here.
Should I go to number 2 or 3?
The other members are quite lazy.
So they wouldn't move.
They don't like to move around.
I bet Jong Kook will stay
at the spot for 700 dollars.
I think Jong Kook will stay there.
If I go there,
we get 350 dollars each.
That's not bad.
(Will they be able to come up
with a successful strategy?)
Should I go to number two?
They wouldn't bother to move.
(What's Jong Kook's choice
with a lot of R money?)
I already have 700 dollars.
I don't need to move around.
Don't you think so?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors,
and the loser will leave.
- Go somewhere else.
- Okay.
- Okay? The loser will leave.
- Let's do that.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- You go.
- Go.
Haha, you have to go.
You have to leave.
- Just go.
- Go away.
- We have no other choice.
- Should I go?
- Should we give him 30 dollars?
- I'm leaving.
- Go.
Go ahead and leave.
- I'm leaving. Don't come.
- Okay.
(Between 700 and 500,
which one will Haha choose?)
- Will you leave?
- Because...
Say it to the camera.
- I promise...
- You'll pay 100 dollars.
to pay 100 dollars.
You'll receive 30 dollars...
- Right. Yes.
- You'll receive 30 dollars...
- If you come back here...
- I'll receive 30 dollars...
- and pay 100 dollars if I return.
Good. Say you promise.
Say it.
- I promise.
- Okay.
- Say you promise to your parents.
- I promise.
I'll leave
if you give me 50 dollars.
- Really?
- Give me 50 dollars, and I'll go.
- Fifty dollars?
- Yes.
- Can I believe you won't be back?
- I won't come back.
- You won't come back?
- I won't.
Okay. Then you give him 30 dollars.
- I'll give him 20.
- Me?
- No, you give him 30 dollars.
- Ok, fine.
- Promise you won't come back.
- I promise I won't come back.
Say it to the camera.
- Good.
(Crossing his fingers)
- Say, "If I come back,"
- If I come back,
- "I'll be no longer human."
- I'll be no longer human.
Okay. But I think
he might give up on being human.
- Okay. Here.
- Okay.
- Here you go. Give him the money.
- Don't come back, okay?
- Give him 30 dollars as you said.
- Give me the money now.
- You go first.
- Let's do it on the count of three.
Let's put the money in each hand.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
- I gave him.
- Give me the money.
- Go now.
- Okay. I'm leaving.
Go. Okay. He left.
(Jae Suk received 50 dollars
and left.)
Then shall I look around
and come back?
Leave already.
I'll give you 30 dollars if you go.
Sounds good. Okay. Thirty dollars.
Will you leave
if I give you 30 dollars?
I'll have an extra ten dollars.
- Okay. Sorry?
- It's ten dollars. I'll leave.
- You'll get 30 dollars and leave?
- Yes.
- Really?
- I'll go if I get 30 dollars.
- Say you promise to the camera.
- I promise.
- Say, "If I come back,"
- If I come back,
- "I'll give him 100 dollars."
- I'll give him 100 dollars.
Okay.
- Here.
- Let's do this!
Okay. Go.
(Crossing his fingers)
- I made them all leave.
- Jae Suk.
I still have 190 dollars left.
(He spent 60 dollars
on sending away the troublemakers.)
Since Pacquiao is coming here,
I need plentiful R money...
Let's begin with plentiful R money.
This is so cool and refreshing.
Jae Suk.
I made an extra ten dollars.
Great.
- Will you go back there?
- Of course.
(He had no intention of leaving
from the get-go.)
- I made an extra ten dollars.
- Yes.
I'll go back there.
- You made an extra 50 dollars.
- Yes.
- I crossed my fingers.
- I mean...
If there are two members
at each of the other places...
- Half of 700 is 350, right?
- It's 350.
If one of us goes there...
Then it should be divided by three,
so each won't get much.
- It'll be two hundred and...
- Three...
Seven times three...
Why would you multiply the number?
I mean, divided by three.
- Anyway, it's better to stay here.
- Five times three equals fifteen.
We'll go back when Suk Jin
couldn't be more excited.
Sounds great.
- It means you lied.
- I said I was lying.
- Suk Jin wasted his money.
- Exactly.
Hey, why aren't you guys leaving?
- Why?
- Why haven't you left yet?
Hey!
- What?
- Why haven't you guys left yet?
- The weather is so nice.
- Yes, that's why we're here.
The weather, my foot.
Gosh, those punks.
I have a feeling
that they're up to something.
Are you having an indoor shoot
with Pacquiao?
You must be really excited
to meet Pacquiao.
I can't think of anything else.
All I can think about is...
that I want to make good memories
with Pacquiao.
I want to get his autograph,
but I don't have any boxing gloves.
I can't believe I'll meet Pacquiao.
I'm so excited.
- Oh, my.
- Guys, leave now, will you?
- We're chatting. Don't mind us.
- Suk Jin.
- What's wrong? We're having a chat.
- Why won't you leave?
Don't mind us.
We're enjoying the weather.
That's all.
Gosh. They'll probably run here.
Obviously, they're planning
to come back. Gosh, seriously.
Why must they be so sly?
Three minutes are left.
Hey, don't come here.
(The staff members rush
to the pavilion as expected.)
Hey, they're still here.
(But someone else came here?)
- So Min, I knew you'd come here.
- Gosh.
- I knew it.
- Why didn't you go?
- Go where?
- Why... Where is Haha?
- Haha left.
- He did?
- Hey.
- I'm relieved.
- Where did Haha go? Number three?
- What do you mean you're relieved?
- Oh, that's good.
- Hey, what are you two doing now?
Is this a joke or something?
- Hey. Stop.
- Why?
- What's wrong?
- Are you kidding me?
- Why?
- What's wrong?
- A promise is a promise, you punks.
- But we... She's going up there.
- What are you doing right now?
- Hello.
- She didn't make any promises.
- I crossed my fingers.
- Gosh. We all gathered here.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I thought Se Chan would leave.
- Give me 100 dollars.
- I crossed my fingers.
Give me 100 dollars right now!
No. I crossed my fingers.
- I crossed my fingers.
- That's ridiculous.
- You owe me 100 dollars.
- I lied.
- I wanted to choose 700 dollars.
- I see.
- Then why did you come here?
- I thought Haha and Se Chan...
- would choose the place too.
- The second choice has ended.
- How did it go?
- The number of members...
who chose this place is five.
- What? How?
- Five.
(But we're four people.)
- Is Haha here?
- Why didn't you leave?
- What's his problem?
- You two left earlier.
- Why didn't you leave?
- Is Haha here?
- What's his problem?
- You two left earlier.
(Haha appears.)
- I left as I promised.
- Seriously, what's wrong with him?
I was hiding under the pavilion.
(Haha promised to leave,
but actually...)
I'm so upset.
How about I hide somewhere
and go back?
(He got upset
and refused to keep his promise.)
Think about it. Haha,
Se Chan, and Jae Suk left.
(So Haha had been hiding
under the pavilion all along.)
I was hiding under the pavilion.
Why didn't you two leave
after getting paid?
- Why didn't you leave?
- Is there one member at each place?
Am I the only one?
- Do I get all of it again?
- Yes, 700 dollars.
This is crazy.
What's wrong with them?
Gosh. So this is how shallow...
- the 13 years of our friendship is.
- I crossed my fingers too.
- It's not about our friendship.
- I'm so upset. Give me the money.
- Give me the money right now.
- I'll give you 200 dollars each.
- Okay.
- Haha, why did you do that?
Ji Hyo has 750 dollars.
And Jong Kook has 1,400 dollars.
They'd be rich if they get married.
(1. Jong Kook: 1,400 dollars,
2. Ji Hyo: 750 dollars)
Whenever we do this,
I end up feeling bitter.
- I can't believe he got all of it.
- I mean...
Knowing your personalities,
I knew you guys would fight
until you all lost.
- He always sticks to the same plan.
- I knew he would stay there.
But if you had been reasonable,
you would've come to where I was.
- I mean, considering everything...
- We went beyond that point.
We went beyond the point
where we fight until we all lose.
This is what we're like now.
"What is wrong with you?"
- "Why are you here?"
- I would say,
- "What is your problem?"
- You're unreasonable.
- Right?
- Yes, we're unreasonable.
- We don't think reasonably.
- We're unreasonable.
If you had thought reasonably,
you would've...
- made a different choice.
- I thought he had left.
We played rock-paper-scissors,
and he left.
And I gave them 30 dollars each
to leave.
- But...
- I came down and hid under here.
I was going to come out
when the two of them left.
- Then I could get 500 dollars.
- Right.
- I thought it was worth trying.
- Yes.
But the two of them didn't even
run away or hide anywhere.
They were just standing here.
They were just chatting.
- What was that? I was so upset.
- They're like thugs.
They refused to leave.
- Really?
- Yes.
- They had no intention of leaving.
- I could see them.
- They didn't even hide?
- You see,
Jong Kook didn't win the money...
- because he had a good strategy.
- Yes.
- That's not true.
- It was possible...
because we always make it easy
for him to win.
That's true.
- "Help yourself."
- True.
- That's embarrassing.
- We set it all up for him.
Then we start fighting
over food on a much smaller table.
- You know what I mean, right?
- That's true.
- That's precise.
- We pick up food on the ground.
- And we tell each other...
- Exactly.
- where we'll be.
- Food fell on the ground!
(The tiger moths barely survive
by eating food off the ground.)
- This is what it's like.
- Hold on.
- It's frustrating.
- What did you say?
Does R money play an important role?
- It's Show Me the Fight Money.
- Oh, boy.
Before each round,
you turn in fight money.
- I see.
- You get twice as much if you win.
And you lose the money you turned in
if you lose.
- Okay.
- I've already made my decision.
I'll go all-in in the first round.
I bet he'll lose all his money...
- and beg us for money.
- Jae Suk, please.
- Don't do that.
- You really should stop doing that.
I beg you.
Can you get me a costume?
- I'll dress like a beggar.
- I'm sure he'll do it again.
It'll be just like the game
where we chose between Go and Stop.
- Really?
- Yes.
- He'll push forward no matter what.
- My point exactly.
There will be a war of nerves
between him and the staff.
- I'll just go for it.
- Go for it no matter what.
With your fight money,
you can purchase
a penalty exemption card.
- There will be a penalty.
- Or you'll get a penalty.
- A penalty? Gosh.
- Oh, boy.
You can win the first game
if you get lucky.
- Before we begin,
- I'm not so lucky.
turn in as much money as you want
as the registration fee.
We have to be in the top three?
- It requires good eyesight?
- I...
- No. You need good luck.
- Oh, good luck?
- Luck?
- Oh, we need good luck?
- Then I'll go all-in.
- I'll bet 200 dollars.
- Two hundred dollars?
- For the first round.
- You're betting 200 dollars?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Two hundred dollars?
- It's all about fighting spirit.
- I should win this.
It's all about fighting spirit.
- I'll bet 300 dollars.
- Really?
- You'll bet 300 dollars?
Hey...
So Min, you shouldn't do that.
It's okay. I could get lucky.
- Even so...
- I need to get more money.
She bet too much money.
Let me think.
If you want to get more money...
I'll see how it goes this time.
I'll bet only 100 dollars.
- I'll bet 100 dollars.
- Here's 100 dollars. Yes.
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, and Suk Jin bet
100 dollars just as Jae Suk did.)
- To be honest...
- I'll bet 50 dollars.
- Fifty dollars?
- Yes.
- This game requires luck, right?
- Good. Let's do this.
- He bet 100 dollars.
We have a good chance of winning
because we'll have three winners.
He's right. We have a good chance.
Yes. The top three will get money.
What's scary is
that none of us is lucky.
- The game you'll play is...
- That's good.
Random Korean Style Bowling.
- What is it?
- Random Korean Style Bowling?
You have 30 seconds to spin
your head wearing a sangmo...
- and knock down...
- Got it.
- as many pins as you can.
- I see why we need luck.
- I'm worried.
- The object tied to your sangmo...
- will be chosen randomly.
- I see.
(They will do the sangmo dance?)
- The top three will receive...
- What should I do?
- twice as much money as you bet.
- Okay.
- Okay. It's not about luck.
- It's not about luck.
I don't think I can win this.
I'm in trouble.
- Why did you bet 300 dollars?
- You know what a sangmo is, right?
I know what it is, but...
- This is not about luck.
- The object tied to your sangmo...
Doesn't it require flexibility?
- No. The object is important.
- It requires luck.
It'd be hard to knock the pins down
with some tissues.
Starting with Ji Hyo,
you'll choose your sangmo.
(Ji Hyo is the first
to choose the sangmo.)
Pick one ball.
Darn it.
(She's upset about the result.)
Gosh. How am I going to win
with an anchovy?
Ji Hyo chose an anchovy
as her object.
(Ji Hyo chose an anchovy.)
- An anchovy?
- No. It's not so bad.
- How can she win with an anchovy?
- An anchovy won't work.
- That's not going to work.
I can't believe she has to do it
with an anchovy.
Exactly. It's not possible.
She just has to be in the top three,
so it's not that bad.
An anchovy?
Just one anchovy.
Ji Hyo, I think you can pull it off.
- I don't think so.
- Shut your mouth, you punk.
- Is it possible?
- You see, anchovies are strong.
- Anchovies are rich in calcium.
- Nice. She might pull it off.
- Ji Hyo, you look cute.
- Is it spinning around?
- Yes, it is.
- Yes, you're doing a great job.
- Hey, it's no joke.
- Do we have to stand there?
- Ji Hyo, you've got this!
- Let's go!
- I can do this!
- Go, Ji Hyo!
- You've got this!
- Ready. Go.
- Stop it. We're competing.
- I wonder if it works.
- No way.
- Hey. Oh, gosh.
- That won't ever work.
- Where are the pins?
- How much money did she bet?
- You have only 30 seconds.
- You can start in front of them.
- Ji Hyo, go closer to the pins.
- You're running out of time.
- Start at the pins.
- Why did I start back there?
Hey, while spinning your head...
- Its head is stuck on your sweater.
- Oh, no.
Gosh. It's on her back.
- It's been separated from its body.
- The head fell off.
- It's too light to knock them down.
- Ji Hyo, it doesn't work.
- Ji Hyo, it's over.
- She only cut its head off.
(Ji Hyo, it's over.)
- Ji Hyo, it's over.
- She only cut its head off.
(Darn it!)
(Bad Ji Hyo showed up
after a long time.)
- It's over. The head fell off.
- Hey, an anchovy is ridiculous.
You try it and see if it works.
This darn anchovy. Get lost!
She looks like a drunkard
from behind.
You looked like Taoist Mutul.
- Hey!
- You're so cool, Ji Hyo.
- The second player, please come.
- Shall I choose mine?
- They keep it fair.
- Is the anchovy...
considered a good or bad tool?
- A bad one.
- Of course, it's a bad tool.
A bad one? Right.
It says "Fan."
- A fan?
- He chose a fan?
- A fan is good.
- What kind of fan is it?
- No, it's not.
It's not so good.
- Well, it's not so bad.
- It'll be hard to move it.
- That won't work. Jong Kook.
- It will be hard.
- Sorry, but I don't want to win.
- Oh, no.
- Okay. You have a lot of money.
- Yes.
I like your positive attitude.
- Right.
- I'm doing this for fun.
- How much did you bet?
- I bet 100 dollars.
- Jong Kook is so meek.
- Yes.
- I mean, he's...
- I'm not doing this for money.
- He's so meek that he's not greedy.
- He's not competitive.
- He looks even meeker in that hat.
- Of course.
He's really meek.
- Oh, he can't move it around.
- I can't move it as I want.
- It doesn't work.
- It's too light.
(Laughing)
(Cheerful)
- He's so meek.
- That won't work.
- This is fun.
- Right. It's hard.
- I said it wouldn't work.
- Ready.
- Oh, good. You might...
- Set.
- Go.
- I wonder if I can pull it off.
No, it won't work.
- I think he'll pull it off.
- There's no way.
- I don't think it'll work.
- Oh, it works.
- You should spin your head...
like the sangmo dance instead of
moving it from side to side.
- There's no way.
- Oh, he knocked one down.
(He began to knock the pins down.)
- I'm impressed. He pulled it off.
- He pulled it off.
- He pulled this off too.
- I can't believe he pulled it off.
- Will he knock down more pins?
- I can't believe this.
- Hey, you should spin it around.
- This is unbelievable.
- He's amazing.
- Spin your head.
I'm sick of seeing him
pulling things off.
- I can't believe this.
- Gosh.
(Please stop!)
- Hey.
- Stop!
Jong Kook.
Time's up.
(The game is over.)
I can't believe he pulled it off.
- I took it easy.
- You knocked nine pins down.
- Did I?
- Yes, nine pins.
- My gosh. He pulled it off.
- You know...
He'll place 1st
if he knocked 9 pins down.
I took it easy.
- I'm not lying.
- I'll choose my tool.
(Next up is Haha.)
Here.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Haha chose a sausage.
- Nice!
(Haha chose a sausage.)
It's not bad at all.
Mine is a sausage. I can win this.
A sausage is quite good.
- That's a great tool.
- It's awesome.
- I'm going to win.
- He could place first.
- He'll place first.
- He looks scary.
Is he Wong Fei Hung?
Hey, he looks...
(Ha Fei Hung with a sausage queue)
- Why don't you open up...
- He looks good with short hair.
a lamb skewer place instead of
running a barbecue restaurant?
- A lamb skewer place?
- You're doing it wrong.
I'll take this out for a second.
Or else, it won't...
Hey, just leave it.
So Min, why did you help him?
- Why?
- You're good to go.
We're competing with one another.
- I'll lend you some money.
- Okay.
What's wrong with you?
I must say, Suk Jin is so...
This isn't a group mission.
- I'm ready.
- Get it together.
He's the worst.
- He said this was competition.
- Stay alert.
- You're ready, right?
- Yes.
Ready. Set. Go.
(The game begins.)
It'll work, obviously.
I'm sure of it.
- One.
- That's great.
- He's invincible.
- It's awesome.
- Yes, he's invincible.
- Move a little further forward.
- They're all falling down.
- A little further.
- Almost all the pins fell down.
- That's amazing.
He's in first place already.
- He's the winner.
- Of course.
He kicked the mat.
- He kicked it.
- Deduct one from his record.
- He'll place first.
- He's the winner.
- Deduct one from his record.
- He knocked them all down.
- Of course, he'll win.
- That was amazing.
- We'll accept 20 pins.
- The sausage was the best one.
I bet he'll place first.
- A chocolate biscuit.
- Oh, okay.
Se Chan chose a chocolate biscuit.
That's good.
He's knocked 4 pins down so far.
Oh, 5 pins.
(While scattering crumbs,
Se Chan knocked five pins down.)
All right. Dried pollack.
(Jae Suk chose a dried pollack.)
(He did well with his exceptional
sangmo dance skills.)
He's in second place.
- Dried seaweed? Is it good or bad?
- That's good.
- Suk Jin is lucky.
- It's good.
(1st: Haha, 20 pins, 2nd: Jae Suk,
18 pins, 3rd: Jong Kook, 9 pins)
Okay. Good.
(His sangmo fell off
as soon as he began.)
(4th: Se Chan, 5 pins,
5th: Ji Hyo, 0 pins)
Great. That'll work.
(1st: Haha, 20 pins, 2nd: Jae Suk,
18 pins, 3rd: Jong Kook, 9 pins)
(He gives off
a salty scent of seaweed.)
- He did well.
- Your record is 14 pins.
- Nice. Okay.
- Okay.
I'm in third place. I made it.
- Gosh, I'm dizzy.
- So Min, you bet 300 dollars.
- I'm done for.
I'm done for.
I hope she'll fail.
That will be funny.
- Gosh, I'm dizzy.
- How can I do it with this?
- What is it?
- A rose.
- That's good.
- It's not bad at all.
- It's great.
- Confess your love.
- It's a rose.
Wait. Okay. It's not so bad.
- It's not too light, right?
- It's not too light.
- Good.
- It's perfect.
The pins fall down easily.
- I want to win for a change.
- Ready.
Set. Go.
So Min.
- Oh, my.
- That's impressive.
(She knocks 2 pins down
with 1 hit twice in a row.)
(No way. She's actually knocking
them down)
- Good.
- Nice.
(The flower fell off the stem!)
- That's great.
- Oh, my.
- The flower fell off.
- It fell off.
(Separated)
- The flower fell off.
The flower fell off. It's over.
- You should hurry up.
- The flower fell off.
- So Min will lose 300 dollars.
- She bet 300 dollars.
- "My money!"
- She'll lose that money.
- So Min will lose 300 dollars.
- The flower fell off.
- She kicked two pins.
- There are many pins left.
- She'll lose the money.
- You can do it!
(Headbanging with no damage)
- The flower...
- You can do it!
- The flower fell off.
- She'll lose 300 dollars.
- She must be dizzy.
- You can't lose 300 dollars!
Oh, no. It's over.
(Goodbye, 300 dollars.)
- So Min lost 300 dollars.
- Oh, no.
- Yes!
- That was funny.
- Poor So Min.
- The flower fell off so early.
- The flower fell off.
- She lost 300 dollars.
- Oh, no.
- Gosh, my money. Hold on.
Darn. My money.
- You did a good job.
- You lost 300 dollars, So Min.
No, my money.
- The game is over.
- So Min, what's wrong with you?
Haha placed first.
- Since he bet 50 dollars,
- Gosh.
- That's so him. He bet 50 dollars.
- he'll receive one hundred dollars.
- I should've bet more money.
- You small fries.
- Did you bet 200 dollars?
- Jae Suk, you bet 100 dollars.
- Yes. I won 200 dollars.
- I should've bet more money.
- Suk Jin, you won 400 dollars.
- Yes.
- This is nice.
Now, we'll move to the next place.
- Okay!
- Let's go.
I should bet more money
in the next round.
I lost 300 dollars.
I'm going to make friends
with Pacquiao.
- Suk Jin, don't do that.
- Don't do that.
- Why?
- Don't make him uncomfortable.
- Don't make Pacquiao uncomfortable.
- He's right.
- Don't make him uncomfortable.
- I won't.
Tom Cruise won't come back to Korea
because of you.
- He hasn't come back since then.
- It's because of Suk Jin.
- He said he wanted to see me.
- Right.
- To whom did he say that?
- Sorry?
- But he won't come because of you.
- Right.
- Come on.
- Suk Jin, you shouldn't do that.
- He always does that.
- I mean, Pacquiao's child...
went to the same school as mine.
Don't make him uncomfortable.
- Come on.
- We have some things in common.
- Don't do that.
- Really?
His child and mine
went to the same school.
- I don't believe you.
- That's enough.
It's true
that they went to the same school.
- Pacquiao's child and mine.
- That doesn't mean...
- you're his friend.
- You didn't go to that school.
- He's not your friend from school.
- They went to the same school?
- My child...
- Hyun Woo.
- Oh, Hyun Woo?
- Yes, Hyun Woo.
- Exactly. That doesn't matter.
- Don't make him uncomfortable.
So I tried to find this photo
of my child with Pacquiao...
- that was taken back then.
- Stop it.
- But I couldn't seem to find it.
- Why would you look for it?
- Protect his privacy.
- Did you find the photo?
- No, I couldn't find it.
- I see.
What a relief.
- He couldn't find it. I'm relieved.
- He couldn't find it.
- What a relief.
- That's a shame.
Viewers in the Philippines,
- fortunately, he couldn't find it.
- Right. That's a relief.
- Please don't worry.
- I'm relieved.
- That's a relief.
- Indeed.
- I'm so relieved.
- It's because...
I like boxing, you know.
- You don't like boxing.
- Stop lying.
You never talked about boxing.
I really like boxing. I'm not lying.
- When did you ever talk about it?
- He's talking nonsense.
I even watched all his matches
including the most recent one.
- What match?
- What did you see?
The one between Pacquiao and...
Was his name Uruso?
- Urusa?
- No, I think his name is Uruso...
(Uruso?)
Suk Jin, did you say "Urusa?"
- Was it Uroson? What was his name?
- Who is Uruso?
Anyway, there's a boxer
with a name like that.
- His latest match...
- You mean, you cried?
- Right. That must be it.
- Did he cry to sleep?
In 2021...
- Did you cry? Were you very sad?
- Did you cry? When did you cry?
Hey, Seok Sam, when did you cry?
(They're teasing Suk Jin
by making a pun.)
Hey, Seok Sam, when did you cry?
- That was good.
- He's laughing out loud.
- I didn't cry.
- Didn't you cry?
- When did you cry?
- I mean, Pacquiao...
- Did you cry because you were sad?
- I thought...
- Did you tear up and cry?
that Pacquiao's opponent's name
was Uroso.
I think
I'm quite excited to meet Pacquiao.
- Why?
- I'm feeling so hot right now.
- You're wearing thick clothes.
- Take off your cardigan.
- You're going through menopause.
- I'm feeling so hot.
You're going through menopause.
- It's so hot.
- You ran from the wasp earlier.
- I think that's why he's hot.
- Gosh. It's hot.
- He's going through menopause.
- No, that's not the case.
- Look at Suk Jin's arms.
- He ran around earlier.
- Oh, my.
- Look at his arms.
Stop it. I don't have muscular arms.
Did you cry because you didn't have
muscular arms?
- Did you cry?
- Were you surprised at my arms?
- Were you surprised or not?
- I was surprised.
I lost the muscles in my arms
because I stopped working out.
Jae Suk and Haha have met him.
Right?
- Yes.
- We've met him before.
He said Pacquiao was very nice.
- Yes, he was very nice.
- He looks like a nice person.
And he's been doing
a lot of charity work.
Mr. Pacquiao is very rich.
That's all you need to know.
- What?
- He's not older than you.
- He's rich, so he has seniority.
I'll treat him like a big brother.
- He's a good fighter and rich.
- Exactly.
- Like a big brother.
- He meets all the qualifications.
- He's rich, so he has seniority.
- He's...
He's incredibly rich, you know.
He won champion belts
in eight different weight classes.
- In eight different weight classes.
- Oh, my.
- In different weight classes?
- He's such an amazing boxer.
I can't wait.
We're all warmed up now.
(They arrive excited
to meet Pacquiao.)
(One, two!)
Ji Hyo, be like this.
Bend down like you're bowing
but throw a punch.
He'll be a little scared
by my punch, right?
- He'll at least flinch.
- Are you serious about it?
Yes, I'm going to punch him today.
Did you all hear that?
He's going to punch Pacquiao today.
Would he have
a lot of bodyguards around him?
- He has many.
- Really?
It's no good, then.
He's here.
(Did Pacquiao suddenly appear?)
Hello.
- I'm not him.
- Hello.
- I'm Yang Se Chan.
- Do you remember me?
(He greets Yang-quiao.)
- Wait, are you Haha?
- Yes.
- Hello, my name is So Min Jung.
- Yes, So Min.
Jung So Min. Nice to meet you.
I shouldn't be cheeky today.
Can you...
please edit out the shadowboxing
I did beneath the bridge?
- What's shadowboxing?
- Why did I even do that?
By the looks of it,
Pacquiao must be near.
(Jae Suk and Seok Sam
also join them.)
Right? You can hear
people murmuring.
- He must be coming from there.
- That must be it.
I get to greet him first.
Is he already here?
- My brother.
- I don't think so.
- He'll be here soon.
- Already?
I'm nervous.
If you think about it,
- he should be here by now.
- Yes?
- Is it time?
- Of course.
- I see.
- "Is it time?"
Why do you keep addressing him
as someone older?
It's been that way
since "Infinite Challenge."
- That's how I always address him.
- Of course.
He packs a punch,
is rich, and famous.
- Yes, he's famous.
- He's an international celebrity.
- That's right.
- And a legend.
That makes him our boss.
- Exactly.
- I get that,
but I can't treat him
like he's older than me.
That would be odd.
- Not you.
- It would seem odd.
Maybe I should call him
my younger brother.
- That'd be odd as well.
- Pacquiao wouldn't like it.
- He's here!
- What?
My gosh.
(The siren starts wailing.)
- My gosh.
- What is it?
He's here!
He's here.
(The elevator slowly
comes to a stop.)
He's here.
Goodness.
(He's finally here!)
It's Pacquiao.
(The legendary boxer
appears before them.)
(Pacquiao is here.)
(World champion)
(World champion, Manny Pacquiao)
(The first boxer to win titles
in eight weight divisions)
(With his fast and precise punches,
he overpowers his opponents.)
(The living boxing legend is here.)
He's here.
Goodness.
(The boxing legend enters
while the siren wails.)
It's Pacquiao.
(Manny Pacquiao)
(They've been dying to meet him
since this morning.)
It's been so long.
What the...
(He suddenly ripped off
Jae Suk's name tag.)
What the...
He took off Jae Suk's name tag.
What? Without a warning?
What on earth?
(Their instincts kick in,
and they run.)
Jae Suk, you're out.
Hold on a second.
(That's when something catches
the members' attention.)
I already saw that.
Don't let him rip your name tag off.
What the...
He took off Jae Suk's name tag.
What on earth?
(Name Tag Elimination)
(Chuckling)
Hold on a second.
Pacquiao, wait.
Pacquiao, come on.
No, don't. Please.
Hold on a second.
- What's going on?
- What is this?
Pacquiao, wait.
Pacquiao.
- Is this an actual game?
- He's super strong.
He's really strong.
- I didn't know.
- Get So Min over there.
Her.
(Someone grabs his attention.)
She's right over there.
Here he comes.
She'll be eliminated for sure.
So Min, keep it casual.
She's done for.
(So Min couldn't fight him off.)
I can't believe it.
- He's super strong.
- Pacquiao, come on.
He's really strong.
Of course he's strong.
Long time no see.
- Long time no see. That's right.
- Long time no see.
Is there a particular order?
- Is there a hidden rule?
- Is there an order?
Are we on the list?
- Got it.
- All right.
- Name Tag Elimination is now over.
- What?
He only got three of us though.
- They must be a team.
- Is that it?
It was better to have had
your name tag taken off.
- Are they on the same team?
- Being eliminated is better.
What's the meaning of this?
Long time no see.
(They officially greet
each other first.)
- Long time no see.
Do you remember him?
Yes, of course.
- Of course he does.
- Okay.
We filmed
some crazy episodes together.
Of course.
- He's ugly, right?
- Anyway, Pacquiao...
(He starts to act friendly.)
Anyway, Pacquiao is the best.
- He's adorable too.
- I'm a big fan.
- He's a big fan of yours.
- Right.
Hi.
(Ji Hyo finds her opening.)
- Thank you.
- Oh, my gosh!
- We shook hands!
- I should run interference.
- Oh, my gosh!
- I can't believe it.
We shook hands!
What's wrong?
Let me help.
No!
Block them.
My gosh, Pacquiao.
Raise our guards.
I'm sorry about this but...
I'm sorry about this,
but tell him to knock them out.
Pacquiao, I'm your fan.
Here we are with Manny Pacquiao.
The international legend.
- One, two!
One, two!
Can you please greet...
the many viewers of Running Man?
Hello, everyone. I'm Manny Pacquiao.
- "I'm Manny Pacquiao."
- Hello.
Thank you.
You're here today on Running Man.
How does it feel to be here?
I'm excited.
"I'm excited."
Nice to see you again.
(The former member of
"Infinite Challenge" keeps quiet.)
- I don't think he remembers you.
- He doesn't.
Pacquiao, it's the second time...
Right.
Second time?
He doesn't remember you.
Why did you act like he did?
- Don't cry, Haha.
- It was like this.
(The greeting implies
that he's a stranger.)
- Don't cry, Haha.
- It was like this.
It was like a politician
greeting potential voters.
- He doesn't remember you.
- It's upsetting.
- He said it's upsetting.
- He doesn't remember Haha.
- It's been a while.
- That's right.
But you see...
I don't know how he'll take this,
but you look more adorable.
It seems that way.
He seems even friendlier.
- He looks even better.
- Really?
(Laughing)
(High-five)
I see he likes being called cute.
- It's a compliment in any culture.
- Exactly.
(Even the boxing legend
likes being called cute.)
(Quietly)
He doesn't know you though.
- But he must remember me.
- He doesn't know you.
He doesn't remember you,
so stay put.
- He doesn't remember you.
- He doesn't.
- Anyway, today...
Can you tell him that my son...
- No, don't.
- Don't say that.
You'll make him uncomfortable.
His son and mine
went to the same school.
(Suk Jin wanted to point out
what they had in common.)
(Excited for his reaction)
- Yes, really.
- The kids went to the same school.
He doesn't seem that impressed.
- He's not fond of it.
- He doesn't seem impressed.
- Don't mention it again.
- Brent International School.
- Brent, yes.
- Brent, exactly.
- My kid too.
- The same?
Yes, the same.
- He doesn't seem impressed.
- Exactly.
He just took it
like another fun fact.
It's not like
you two went to school together.
No, that's not the case.
- Anyway...
- Your son and mine...
- Stop it.
- Stop. He got it the first time.
- He understood you.
- Right.
- When they were young.
- He heard you.
Also,
it's been a while
since you visited Korea.
We're curious as to...
- what brought you by.
- Exactly.
(He's here for the special match
that takes place on December 11.)
He's here to promote
the boxing match.
- I see.
- Really?
With DK Yoo, right?
With a Korean, right?
I don't know if I should
still call him a boxer...
or something else...
because he's now a senator.
- What should we call him?
- You're a senator.
My term has ended,
so I'm back to being
a normal citizen.
- He's now a normal citizen.
- Is that so?
- Is he no longer a senator?
- No.
Then we should address him as that.
- Mr. Pacquiao?
- Just Mr. Pacquiao.
No, it's just my buddy Pacquiao.
- Right, my buddy.
- Exactly.
- My buddy.
- My buddy Pacquiao.
- Manny.
- Just Manny?
- Should we call him Manny?
- Yes, that's right.
- Could you please tell him this?
- Manny!
I'm older than him,
but I'd like to address him
as someone older than me.
Same here.
I'd like to address him
that way as well.
My buddy Manny.
- He's actually older than you.
You're younger than him.
(Chuckling)
He must be flustered.
- He's flustered.
- It seems that way.
- Manny's flustered.
- Yes, we caught him off guard.
By the way,
is it true that Manny...
contacted Running Man first?
I just couldn't believe
what the staff told us.
- I'd like to confirm it.
- Is he just being polite?
- The staff's suddenly on edge.
- Exactly.
The truth will come out.
- No way.
- Right.
"Yes, I asked
if I could be on the show."
Why though?
I wonder why.
Because Running Man is a show...
that my family and children
enjoy watching.
"Because Running Man is a show..."
"that my family and children
enjoy watching."
- Do they know us?
- Thank you.
- Could they know me?
- Gosh.
- Manny.
- His family?
- Do you know who he is?
- "Do you know who he is?"
(Right...)
(It looks like he nodded
because he had no other choice.)
He was just being polite.
That was him being polite.
You know what?
I don't need the translation.
I understood what he meant.
"I know who you are,
but not your name."
- Then...
- The name could be too much.
- Do you perhaps know me too?
- Come on.
Well...
- You get it, right?
- I see.
He knows the show which is enough.
We don't need him to know our names.
- He just watches the show.
- Exactly.
- And Manny's...
- His family must like the show.
Probably his children.
- His children love the show.
- Of course.
- Them laughing is more than enough.
- I agree.
That's more than enough.
Now, you will begin
your race with Manny Pacquiao.
You will be split into two teams
for this race.
The three that were eliminated
by Mr. Pacquiao earlier...
- will be on one team.
- My gosh.
The opposing team
will consist of the other four.
- Well, this is...
- Right.
Pacquiao doesn't belong
to any of the teams,
and he'll help carry out the game
as an NPC.
He won't be joining us?
It's not a 4-on-4 game?
He'll play for both teams.
Oh, okay.
We'll keep the fight money
system we had earlier.
The total amount of money
that the teammates have...
will be the registration fee
for your team.
If you win, you'll win an amount
double the registration fee.
The money will be divided equally
regardless of how much you paid.
Is that so?
The losing team will lose
all of the registration fee.
Then it's better to be
on the same team as Jong Kook.
So Min has only about 100 dollars.
- She doesn't have much money.
- I'm low on money.
She has nothing.
Please gather again in the studio
after getting changed.
- All right.
- Let's go!
Pacquiao!
What is this?
They prepared a ring, as expected.
What kind of game
are we going to play?
- One.
- One, two.
One, two, three. You're quite fast.
- It's tiring.
- You can't just use your hands.
- You need to shift your weight too.
- How so?
- What?
- Come. One.
- You need to shift the weight.
- That hurt.
- One, two. There you go.
- Two.
One, two.
(Not shifting his weight at all)
Your punches are quite strong.
I think my punches are quite strong.
I didn't know.
I keep doing this
because Pacquiao is here.
Give it a try. Two, three.
Ready, go.
You need to hit it fast.
Your strength is speed.
Isn't she really good?
- You're good.
- She's pretty fast.
You're gifted.
Warm up. Ready, go.
All right. That's great.
- Good job.
- That's great.
(Punching)
- Good job.
- She's so fast.
(The frog boxer
got attacked on her head.)
How did you hit her
when she's this fast?
- You're so fast.
- Why does So Min keep doing that...
when she gets teased all the time?
She's fast.
So Min, I can't even see your hands
because they're so fast.
I'll call you a warrior from now.
Gosh, I brought my gloves
to get his autograph.
But I can't seem to find
the right timing.
(Shy)
I'll ask for it later.
So Min, we should take a photo
with Pacquiao later alone.
- Why?
- To commemorate it.
Pacquiao is milder than I thought,
so I was really surprised.
But when he's on the ring...
He changes as soon as
he puts on his gloves.
You need to bet your money
as a team.
- Text me the amount.
- But there are only three of us.
Do we collect our money
and submit it?
Let's just pay up.
- What about...
- Should we pay 50 dollars each?
That sounded very reasonable.
That meant you were willing to pay.
- You can pay 50 dollars, right?
- I'm good with 50 dollars too.
- Me too.
- I'm good with 50 dollars.
(The team with 4 members
agreed to pay 50 dollars each.)
Let's pay 50 dollars each.
- Are you confident that we'll win?
- That's right.
That, I'm not sure of.
We don't know what we'll be playing.
(They don't know what kind of game
they'll be playing.)
Let's have her pay just 50 dollars.
No, we should pay 100 dollars each.
Okay, I'm in.
(The team with 3 members
agreed to pay 100 dollars each.)
Do we pay it now or do we text?
Text us, please.
(Studying their faces)
Wait a minute.
(They figured out
that something was off.)
Please don't do that.
Can't we just pay it to you?
We need to see for it ourselves
that everyone paid.
We might lose our trust in each other
if we send texts instead.
- The text...
- First off,
are you sure this is 100 dollars?
- It is.
- We need to text.
I'll text instead.
I'll pay 100 dollars.
Just pay 50 dollars.
You should pay 50 dollars, at least.
- Press it, everyone.
- You press it first.
They can't... Look at them.
They can't trust each other.
Just press it for now.
Se Chan.
(They're all so very serious.)
What takes so long to pay
100 dollars through text?
I'm talking with my mom right now.
Why...
His sweatsuit looks amazing.
It's amazing.
He has a big build.
(Pacquiao, who got changed,
enters the ring.)
(He jumps onto the ring.)
(Pacquiao is getting all the attention
from Trainer Kook.)
Gosh, Manny Pacquiao is...
This time, we'll be playing
Relay Speed English Quiz.
Come on.
- This is great.
- They're done for.
This is perfect for Jong Kook.
- This is great.
We paid too much.
It's a speed quiz,
but we can't beat them
even if they give us two hours.
Just like the speed quiz
we've played,
you'll take turns
to describe the word.
The last player will guess
what the word is.
But Pacquiao will be
the first player for both teams.
You need to explain everything
in English.
The team that guesses more words
in the given time wins.
Also, you're not allowed
to use your body.
You should put your hands
behind you.
- We can't use our bodies?
- This is driving me crazy.
We can't use our bodies
when we're doing an English quiz?
But I'm a body language expert.
- What should we do?
- Then you should've told us.
We paid way too much.
There are only 3 members
in the 3-person team.
You can choose
one of our staff members...
and play the game with them.
We can pick one of you?
I mean...
Don't you think Chan Hee
will be good at it?
- At least he's experienced.
- He has experience.
Why do you keep staring
at the viewfinder?
- Why does he keep looking at that?
- I think he's avoiding our eyes.
Don't you think he'll be good at it?
- No, I don't think so.
- I think he'll be amazing at it.
- Wait.
- You don't speak English?
No... Do you speak English?
"You don't speak English?"
What did she say?
- I don't speak...
- You don't know me?
- Do you...
She just said
"You don't speak English?"
And he went...
(The cameraman refused strongly.)
That means he can do it.
It means he can do it.
Can you speak English?
Choose one quickly.
Can't we have him to choose for us?
- Let Manny decide.
- Manny's choice.
- Manny, make your choice, please.
Someone who looks like
they'll be good in English.
(Which staff member will be chosen by him
and join the 3-person team?)
He's having fun.
Manny, it's your choice.
Oh, he picked Seung Hyun.
(He's done choosing.)
(Manny picked...)
- All right.
- Come on!
- Okay!
Come on!
- Yes, come on!
- It's done for.
- Good choice.
- Good one.
- Good choice! Yes!
- Sung Ho, come on over.
Sung Ho went to film abroad
many times.
He really did.
When he went abroad for a shoot,
I saw him being scolded
by an officer at the immigration.
"Sorry!"
Sung Ho is a changed man.
- Well, then...
- Can you start?
- Okay, we'll start first.
- Okay.
All right. We can go first.
All right.
- You're the first to go.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Manny.
Sorry.
Do we put these on?
- Wait.
- We're in trouble.
(Singing)
Guess what this song is.
It's "Attention."
(Surprisingly,
it's one of the latest songs.)
I thought it was a traditional song
from the way Suk Jin sang.
It sounds like a traditional song.
Guess what this song is.
It's "Attention" by NewJeans.
(He demands them to guess the song
when he doesn't even listen to it.)
(Attention)
(Seok Sam is excited.)
Suk Jin doesn't even
know that song that well.
But he's just trying to sound young.
Did you get it?
Get ready.
(The mission begins.)
(They'll describe the given word
in English, starting with Manny.)
That's too difficult.
(Refrigerator)
- That's too difficult.
- What is that?
I didn't know it was called that.
What does it say?
Regetor? What is it?
- Refri...
- Retri...
(He begins describing it
in English.)
- It's...
- equipment in the house.
- House?
- House.
Like... You can put something...
You can put something...
- like food or drinks.
- Food. Drinks.
Okay, I got it.
- Okay.
Don't use your hands.
House.
Drinks.
Food.
House, drinks, food?
House. It means a house.
- Yes.
- Water and food?
- Yes, and you should...
- House, drinks, food? I have...
- no idea what it means.
- You can't speak in Korean.
Only English.
House, drinks, food?
What does it mean?
Buttons.
- Buttons?
- Buttons.
(Oh!)
- Oh, yes. I know.
- Buttons.
- House, drinks... All right.
- Hurry. Speed up.
(Will he explain it well to Haha?)
- If you know water... In house...
- In house?
You put button...
- "Put button?"
- Water...
Yes, put it in.
- Put it in?
- Yes. Water...
(Put button, water, put it in?)
- Clean water...
- Put water...
- House, clean, water, machine.
- House, clean, water, machine?
Yes, house, clean, water, machine.
- But we need to put water in?
- No.
- He got it wrong.
- Clean, water.
He must've thought it was
a water dispenser.
- Isn't that a water dispenser?
- It is.
Clean, water, house, machine.
- Clean, water, house, machine.
- Yes.
- I see.
- You don't know?
Is that Woongjin's?
- No.
- Good.
- Is it Woongjin?
- Yes.
Yes!
He needs to understand it
for him to enjoy this.
- Go.
- Okay.
Hey, say exactly what I said.
(Suk Jin asked for the delivery of
water dispenser.)
- A house.
- A house?
- Clean...
- Say it exactly as you heard.
- water, machine.
- Machine.
- You mean a water purifier?
- That's right!
No?
- It's correct.
- That's not the answer.?
("Water purifier"
is not the answer.)
- It's not correct?
- It's a refrigerator.
I'm so sorry, though.
Why would you bring water up?
I also said food!
- Water...
- Put on your headphones.
We're on standby.
My gosh. You need to hurry a bit.
Let's finish this quickly.
You need to listen to the word.
Gosh, it's supposed to be easy.
How can you not get that?
That's not to be put in a fridge.
Yes?
It's...
useful in the house to clean.
- Yes.
- To clean in the house.
- Like...
- A machine?
A machine to clean the house.
- Okay.
- Like...
A machine that cleans the house?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Okay. No problem.
Because you're a legend. No problem.
- Hurry.
- Yes!
He's trying to befriend Manny.
Don't use the scene with them.
He's trying to follow Manny.
(Trying to befriend Manny
during a mission)
- A machine that cleans the house?
- Yes.
Yes, that's it.
(Vacuum cleaner)
- Okay.
Yes. A house.
- A house machine.
- Clean. For cleaning.
- For cleaning.
Yes. I'm finished.
You don't know?
- What?
- Hey.
- He's the villain of the day.
- He's the villain.
He's the villain.
- In the house...
- In the house?
- A machine.
To clean?
Pacquiao, you can't use your hands.
- To clean.
Gosh, it's really easy, though.
(Suk Jin only kept repeating
"a machine for cleaning house.")
(Vacuum cleaner)
- In house.
- Water clean machine?
- No?
- In house,
cleaning machine.
Cleaning machine?
(In house cleaning machine)
(Taking a glance)
House cleaning machine?
Stop looking at Manny.
(Stop looking at Manny.)
Okay, I'll get this.
- House.
- Cleaning machine.
That's it.
- Wait a minute.
- The end. Finished.
Haha should try to get it.
(That's it. The end. Finished.)
House.
Cleaning machine.
- Why would you look at him?
- House.
(He keeps looking at Manny
as though he wants confirmation.)
House cleaning machine.
Hey, it's easy, isn't it?
House cleaning machine?
House cleaning machine.
Okay!
(Okay!)
A washing machine!
- It's a vacuum cleaner.
- Hey!
(It's wrong.)
(A house cleaning machine
is a washing machine?)
Come on!
Hey! I told you
it's a house cleaning machine!
- Of course it's a vacuum cleaner.
- What's wrong with him?
- We just need to get one right.
- If we get it...
- Sung Ho!
- Sung Ho, we can do this.
- We just need to get one right.
- We just need one.
- The last one.
- What's the point?
- You do it.
- Even if I hear his explanation...
- Just do it.
- Will you guess the answer?
- I'll do it. We need to get it.
(Chopsticks)
(It's the last given word.)
It's a matter of which team
gets the answer first.
(Chopsticks)
You use this to eat.
It's something you use to eat.
- A plate?
- Korean, Japanese, or Chinese...
- Chopsticks?
- To...
(Chuckling)
Okay.
- All right.
- Jong Kook can actually talk.
He really can.
When you eat ramyeon...
When you eat ramyeon?
- Ramyeon.
- Ramyeon. Okay.
- What do you use...
- for eating...
- ramyeon?
- You got it?
- Yes, I got it.
What is that?
- Chopsticks?
- Turn around.
- Okay.
- Go!
(Haha took the hint
and got the answer.)
Say it exactly like how I did.
Eating ramyeon.
(Eating ramyeon)
- Eating ramyeon?
- Ramyeon?
Shin Ramyeon, Jin Ramyeon,
Yeol Ramyeon. You know?
- Yes.
- Ramyeon.
- Yes. Ramyeon? I know ramyeon.
- Yes.
- Ramyeon.
- Yes. How do you eat it?
- How do you eat it?
- "How do you eat it?"
- No forks.
(No forks.)
- That's a good one.
- No spoons.
- That's it!
- Okay.
That was a good one.
(If Suk Jin guesses the answer correctly,
they'll win a point.)
- Eating.
Eating ramyeon.
- Eating ramyeon? Yes.
- Eating ramyeon.
How ramyeon?
(How ramyeon?)
- "How ramyeon?"
(An extreme summarization)
(She omitted so many words
in between.)
- How do you eat that?
- No.
(She omitted so many words
in between.)
- In 1, 2.
- No!
- Eating ramyeon?
How you eat ramyeon?
- Four.
- How...
- No spoons, no forks.
- How you eat ramyeon?
- Two, one.
- No forks.
Yes! I got it.
It's...
- Say it!
- Chipsticks?
(Incorrect)
You can say it in Korean.
Chipsticks.
- It's chopsticks.
- There was a time limit.
- They're done.
- How...
- "How ramyeon?"
- We were almost there.
How could you say it's wrong?
Sung Ho, we can do this much.
It's just one question.
- It's just one question.
- We just need to get one right.
- Let's just answer one.
- We just need to get one.
- We just need to get one right.
"How ramyeon?" That was just...
"Eating ramyeon, how ramyeon?"
It's even hard to make a joke
like that.
"Eating ramyeon, how ramyeon?"
"How ramyeon?"
- Sung Ho, we can do this.
- I'm in trouble.
- We can do it.
- It's like an old joke.
We can do this, Sung Ho.
I'll describe it well.
Sung Ho, don't take this too hard.
It's a matter of wit.
We can do this, So Min!
Let's go! We can do it!
- Come on!
We just need to get one right.
(Will they be able
to answer one correctly?)
(Mirror)
(The first hurdle is Se Chan.)
- Okay. Let's go.
- It's easy.
- When you change dress...
- When you...
- A dress?
- You...
- You? "Me?"
- watch in the...
- "Watch in there?"
- Yourself.
- Yourself? I do it myself?
(I do it myself?)
When you change your clothes,
- you look in the...
- It's all about guts.
You need to give them a time limit.
"Yourself?"
- Dressing?
- You watch yourself...
when you
change your clothes like that.
- You watch yourself.
- He's speaking too fast.
"Change?" Could you slow down?
- You're too fast.
- When you get changed...
(He ended up asking Pacquiao
to slow down.)
(You're too fast.)
"Change?" I change?
And then you watch yourself.
- Yourself.
- Oh, it's closed?
Oh, it must be a department store.
Oh, is it Chanel?
What do you mean?
(A pitiful sight)
Your hair. When you comb your hair.
- You watch yourself.
- That's enough already.
- You don't get it?
- Handsome. You...
You look at yourself,
and you think you're handsome.
- Dress? Okay.
- I think he got it.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- You can't use gestures.
- We'll be watching.
- Dress.
- Yes?
- Okay?
- Change.
- A dress change?
- Then look.
- "Look?"
- "Look."
- Close.
Dress, change, look, close?
Go back to the house.
What?
It's "refund."
- You get changed.
- You change your dress.
- You look.
- Look.
- Change, house?
- Okay.
Okay, buy.
- Okay!
- Okay, buy.
- Yes.
- Close.
Is this "mirror?"
- Yes!
- Mirror?
- Yes! Mirror?
- Yes!
Mirror?
- No. Mirror?
- Yes.
- Look. Buy.
- It's not "mirror?"
You look.
(He misses the answer
when it's right there.)
Come on.
- Come on.
- Okay.
This. Buy.
- This is fun.
- Okay.
- Buy. Look.
- That's enough.
- Manny.
- Stop it!
- Change.
That's enough.
It's going on for so long.
Look.
(It's time for So Min
to describe it.)
- Dress change.
- Look.
- Your hand!
- Watch your hand.
Look at me.
"Look at me."
Dress change. Look.
Oh, you're so beautiful.
Bye. Then you go home.
(A mysterious monologue)
(The audience is shocked.)
What was that?
What is she talking about?
I got it! Touting on the street?
No.
Home. Outside. Go outside.
- "Go outside?"
- Manny just sighed.
Why won't my turn come?
Manny must be frustrated.
Manny must want to punch
a punching bag.
He's frustrated.
Okay, go. Sung Ho, go.
- Okay, let's go.
- Okay.
- Sung Ho. Go ahead.
- Dress.
- Dress change.
- You're using your hands.
- Dress change?
- Dress change.
- Wow.
- What?
- Your hands.
Dress change, wow?
Wow... Bye-bye.
(It suddenly ends.)
Dress change,
wow, bye-bye?
Dress change, wow, bye-bye.
We'll give you five seconds.
- Hold on.
- Five, four,
- A dresser.
- three,
No.
- It's not that? What is it?
- What is it?
- The answer is "mirror."
- It's "mirror."
- It was "mirror."
- It's not "department store?"
(The answer is "mirror.")
So Min said the answer.
Se Chan, just follow your guts.
- Okay. We almost got it.
- Manny!
- Please do a good job!
- I got the correct answer.
It was mirror, right?
(The next question)
A frying pan.
It could be a term
familiar to Koreans.
You use this in the house.
You cook.
- Cork?
- You cook.
- Go?
- Cooking.
- Oh, cooking?
- Cooking. Yes.
- Oh, "cook?" Got it.
- Yes, cook.
- You cook eggs.
- Eggs?
- Egg.
- Egg?
A frying pan?
(A frying pan?)
(Suddenly glowing)
(It's as if he found an oasis.)
Look at his face. No, that's not it.
Manny's expression is so cute.
The expression he has on
when they get the correct answer...
- is so cute.
- Cook.
- In the house.
You... It is...
Cooking eggs.
- Cooking eggs?
- Yes.
What are they saying?
Cooking eggs?
Round. It is...
Look at Manny.
I'm sorry, So Min. But don't try to
make a sentence. Just say words.
Instead of saying in the house,
- just say, house, in, eggs,
- Hey.
- fries.
- So Min. Look at Manny's face.
- Chemistry.
- Chemistry?
- Making.
- Making?
- Egg.
- Scramble.
- Yes. In the house.
- Yes.
- Scramble in the house.
- Taesaja in the house.
- In the house.
In the house.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Switch.
- Very hot.
- Thank you.
Very hot.
- In the house.
In the house.
- We just need to get one.
- Egg, cook.
(Egg, cook.)
(Thinking)
Egg...
Start over
from Taesaja in the house.
Taesaja in the house.
(Surprisingly enough,
he's describing a frying pan.)
- Egg. Scramble.
- Egg.
- Scramble.
- Cook.
- Cooking.
(Cameraman Sung Ho focuses
despite his internal conflict.)
- Jae Suk might get it.
- Go.
I don't know this one.
- Good.
- I think he'll get it.
Come on, Sung Ho.
You have to speak in English.
Taesaja in the house. Cook.
What?
(Repeating Taesaja)
- Taesaja?
- Taesaja in the house.
(Cameraman Sung Ho delivers
what he heard.)
"Taesaja in the house."
Taesaja in the house?
- "Taesaja in the house."
- Taesaja in the house?
- In the house. Cook.
- Don't look at people in the back.
Taesaja in the house cook?
Egg, cook.
Egg, cook?
- Taesaja.
- You know what it is.
- Taesaja in the house?
Frying pan.
That's correct.
- How did you know?
- I told you.
Egg.
- Egg.
- Correct.
Where did Taesaja come from?
After she said in the house,
I said Taesaja in the house...
as a joke.
Okay. We got it.
Now, I will tell you...
- each team's registration fee.
- Good job.
(Announcing the registration fee
each team submitted)
Four-person team.
- It was 110 dollars.
- What?
Only 110 dollars for 4 people?
- My goodness.
- Who paid only 10 dollars?
Who paid 10 dollars
and who paid nothing?
- One person didn't pay.
- Right.
Be honest, who paid 10 dollars
and who paid nothing?
- I paid 50 dollars.
- Ji Hyo and I paid 50 dollars.
- I'm innocent.
- I know you didn't pay.
I'm innocent.
- I'm not paying anymore.
- Me neither.
I'm not paying anymore.
I have lots of money anyway.
Keep that in mind.
- I'm not paying anymore.
- You lost my trust.
I'm not paying anymore. Forget it.
For three-person team...
- We paid 100 dollars each.
You paid a total of 210 dollars.
You only paid 10 dollars? Seriously.
- What's wrong with you?
- You get 140 dollars each.
I had no money.
- I thought we were going to lose.
- Hey.
- Go home.
- What is wrong with you?
You go home.
I'm not paying anymore.
I'm locking up my wallet.
- It's closed.
- I'll pay this time.
Before the game,
text me the amount
within your budget.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- How much?
- Is this the last mission?
Yes, it's your last mission.
Do you want to pay
for real this time?
- I'm not paying.
- I'm really paying this time.
- I'm serious this time.
- Let's pay.
- I'm not paying.
I'll show you.
- Let's pay 100 dollars each.
- I'm not paying at all.
- One hundred dollars each.
- One hundred dollars.
- No, I'm only paying 10 dollars.
I'm not paying.
I'll pay 50 dollars.
- Okay. Let's pay 50 dollars each.
- Okay.
Pay 50 dollars each.
- I'll pay 50 dollars.
Let's pay 50 dollars.
The penalty has nothing to do with money.
I'll show you
that I paid 50 dollars.
- Whatever. I don't want to.
- Forget it.
I don't want to see it.
The penalty...
The penalty won't cost 500 dollars.
- To avoid the penalty.
- Right.
It'll be over 700 dollars at least.
So my money is pointless.
- Let's go all in.
- But...
- You have to go all in.
- I'll go all in.
- Even if you keep it, you'll lose.
But even in the individual round...
Right, I lose.
- You lose. You must go all in.
I'll go all in.
(Sent)
Done.
- Did you send it?
- Yes. I really sent it.
- This is the last mission anyway.
- Did you all send the amount?
- Yes.
- You may warm up.
- Warm up?
We got up early today.
We're all warmed up.
Come on.
(The cheeky boxer makes a fuss
while warming up.)
- One, two.
- Good.
(They show off what they saw.)
So Min. You're good.
(The town boxer gets ready
for the match with Pacquiao.)
- You little...
- Oh, I know.
(The legend boxer gets ready
to greet the town boxer.)
One, two. Let's go.
One, two. Good.
(Suk Jin approaches Pacquiao
while everyone is warming up.)
Manny. Do you know Alabang?
- Alabang.
- Yes.
- Do you know Alabang?
A city in the Philippines.
My wife and my son...
- In Alabang?
- Two years...
- Lived there.
- In Alabang?
In Alabang.
Suk Jin keeps bothering Manny
in the back.
He keeps talking about
his personal stuff.
He'll later ask him
to follow each other.
Don't do that.
- Don't bother him.
- This mission...
is a chance to spar
with the best boxer in the world.
It's One Punch Three Points.
- One Punch?
- One Punch Three Points.
Everyone will wear a t-shirt
with scores on it...
- and color gloves.
- Okay.
If you punch the number on
Pacquiao's t-shirt,
it becomes your point.
If Pacquiao hits your number,
- you lose points.
- This is going to be hard.
We'll combine the points
you earned within the limited time.
The team that earned more points
wins.
Okay.
At least three people will be down.
Now my right arm can
finally breathe.
Please go put on the target t-shirt.
- Let's play at once.
- I'll get to...
Okay.
That's taekwondo gear.
- I'll show you.
- Show me what? Pull it down.
Speed.
What speed?
I never tried boxing before.
This is my first time.
Manny's warming up.
I'll copy him.
Do we put on the head gear?
If you want.
It's up to you.
Give me the head gear please.
I'll put on the head gear.
- We...
- Just in case.
- Point.
- Good.
Point.
- Jong Kook.
- Point.
Finally, they're sparring.
Point.
He's having fun.
Jong Kook is happy.
- Point.
- Jong Kook...
I've never seen Jong Kook
doing that before.
Are you honored?
He's honored.
It's an honor even if Manny
punches you in the face.
- I'll still be honored.
- So Min.
You need to make a fuss here
when you're boxing.
Right. People do that.
(Too much warm up for what they got)
We invited Director Bae Sung Oh...
of Boxing Association of Korea
for fair judgment.
- Hello.
Thank you for coming.
What are you doing?
Because he's here.
I'm Bae Sung Oh
from Boxing Association of Korea.
- Nice to meet you.
- Judge Bae.
Director Bae looks like...
- one of us.
- I know.
That's Jae Suk's old hairstyle.
He reminds me of Jae Suk
in the past.
He looks like a mix
of Jong Shin and Jae Suk.
The game is going to start.
You seem very nervous.
Yes. I'm very nervous.
(Confessing)
Shall we start?
- Now...
- So Min.
So Min and Se Chan will start first.
- I feel dizzy already.
- So Min.
- You go first.
- You two go first.
Hey. You should go first.
- You think I can do it?
- Go for it.
(Pacquiao versus Se Chan and So Min)
I'm finally released
after a long time.
- I'm already running out of breath.
- A sparring with Manny...
- is an honor.
- Okay.
- It's an honor.
- We should be...
- Fair play.
- honored.
I'm so nervous.
Please go easy on me.
So smooth.
- Okay.
- Box.
Hey.
It's hard for Manny to deal
with two people at the same time.
- Right. It's not easy.
- Hey.
- Running away won't help.
- Manny.
Running away won't help.
Manny is very fast.
- His feet are very fast.
- He can move very fast.
When one person goes in,
the other must go in too.
He's fast just as I heard.
(A sudden right jab)
He's so fast.
- He's fast.
- You must go in.
- So Min. You need to go in.
- Go in.
- So Min. Go in.
So Min.
- What's she doing?
- Are you bowing?
Manny's flustered.
Go in.
- It's not easy for Manny either.
- Manny.
- Keep jabbing.
- Manny's struggling.
Manny's struggling too.
It's hard for Manny
to hit the number.
Oh, I got it.
(The protruding mouth boxer's
counterpunch)
That's three points.
(Boxer Yang earned 3 points.)
- Where?
- On top.
- That's ten points.
- Ten points.
Hey.
He got hit in the stomach.
- Hey.
- So Min. Go in.
Stretch.
So Min. You must go in.
- Go in.
So Min. Go.
- You must go in together.
- Go in.
(Lethargic)
Watch out for low-blow!
- So Min. You must go in.
- Ten points.
That's over ten points.
Go for ten points.
Go in.
(He pretends to look at Se Chan
then hits 10 on So Min's shirt.)
He got your ten.
- So Min.
What are you doing?
Go in. Stretch your arm.
That was great, So Min.
(She goes in slowly
and stretches her arm.)
(Manny quickly touches 3 points.)
(Touching 3 points again)
- He's fast.
- Manny is accurate.
- That's right.
- Manny's having fun.
Come here.
- Manny is laughing.
- Come here.
Manny is having fun.
(Manny decides to play along.)
Manny's flustered.
- Manny got a lot of paint on him.
- So Min.
- He's playing along.
- He's got a lot of paint.
- He's in a mess.
- He got a lot of paint.
- Let's go in at the count of three.
- Okay.
One, two, three, go.
(Laughing)
So Min. Get up.
I'm exhausted.
It's not easy for Manny to deal
with two people at the same time.
My arm couldn't reach him.
Are you tired?
- Manny.
- Manny's tired.
(Children are begging him
to play with them for more.)
- Corner him.
- Hurry up.
(Laughing)
(Play with us, Uncle Manny.)
- Hey.
- Come here.
Do you know how expensive Manny is?
(The game ends.)
- Okay.
- Stand up.
- I can't play anymore.
- Manny got hit a lot too.
He got hit a lot.
- He needs to get changed.
- Manny is...
- I got hit a lot.
- We're calculating the score.
- I'm out of breath.
- I'm so tired.
You should've been
more enthusiastic.
Mark yourself
and punch from down here.
Why would you sit down?
- You need to go in there and fight.
- I'll watch your play.
- Punch right here.
- Okay.
- Who's playing this time?
- You.
- Your team.
- Us?
- Who's playing?
- Ji Hyo and who?
- Ji Hyo and...
Me?
- Suk Jin?
- Okay.
It's going to be fun.
Ji Hyo will be a tough contender.
Can you translate?
Ask him if I can go rough.
- If you can go rough on him?
- Yes.
- His eyes changed.
- Tell him he's Honey Punch.
(Honey Punch is embarrassed
for acting up.)
- "Honey Punch."
"Honey Punch."
Honey Punch. This is only a game.
- Honey Punch.
- Yes, Honey Punch.
Let's begin.
Box.
Good. That was so fast.
I couldn't see you.
(Honey Punch dashes from the start.)
- Suk Jin is over.
- He's tired.
- He's over soon.
(Wasting his energy for nothing)
(Right in 10 points)
(He got punched
while making a fuss.)
Manny.
(At that moment, the old boxer
proves his still strong.)
- Manny.
- He hit Manny for real.
Get over here.
Manny is getting upset.
(Suk Jin goes at him obstinately.)
He's happy.
(However, Manny avoids
all his punches.)
But he's so...
- Suk Jin. You'll pass out.
- It's over.
Punching obstinately consumes
so much energy.
- He's out of energy.
- That consumes lots of energy.
- Punch him now.
- Now is the time.
- Go.
- Punch him now.
Manny, now.
Punch him hard.
(Punching Suk Jin
in groggy condition)
(However, Player Ji makes effort.)
- Suk Jin still hit him.
- He dropped it.
(Manny's glove is off.)
- His glove is off.
- Sorry.
(Apologizing quickly)
- He apologizes right away.
He's afraid of losing a friend.
Before he loses a follower.
He's worried
about losing a follower.
- Sorry.
- Box.
- Manny's angry.
- Ji Hyo. Get closer.
(He pretends to look at Suk Jin
then hits 10 points on Ji Hyo.)
He's so fast.
- That scared me.
- Ji Hyo. You need to go in.
He hit her.
(Two players attack Manny together.)
He blocked them.
Sorry.
- Sorry.
- Why does he keep saying sorry?
In case he gets punched.
- He's getting punched more.
- He might get punched later.
Here.
It's over.
- Okay.
- Suk Jin gave his all.
I'm your legend.
I mean, you're my legend.
"I'm your legend?"
- He said, "I'm your legend."
- "I'm your legend."
You're my legend.
It's not even "You're my hero,"
but "You're my legend."
It's my turn now.
You need to take your glasses off.
Give it to me.
I have to.
Go.
Jae Suk.
(Off the grasshopper goes.)
You got it.
Here goes Baby Punch.
Baby Punch.
Honey Punch.
- Baby Punch.
I have the baby's punch.
The punch that never harmed
anyone before.
- Box.
- He got punched.
- He got punched in the face.
- Baby Punch.
He's acting up.
I wish he gets punched.
- That's right.
- He's acting up.
- Manny doesn't like that.
(Hitting 3 points unexpectedly
while acting up)
He can't see without his glasses.
- Nothing can stop him.
- Punch.
- Hey.
- Nothing can stop him.
(A long distance attack)
- Hey.
- Sorry.
Hey. Apologize now.
Sorry, Manny.
Manny is angry.
Okay.
(Manny's body blow)
Punch him.
Punch him hard.
Punch.
Manny. Strong punch please.
Random punches are harder
to deal with.
- Strong.
- His punches are so random.
- Look at Manny's face.
- Jae Suk is so scared.
- Jae Suk. Give up.
- You can see in his face.
Come on, Manny.
- One, two.
- Go, Manny.
- The look on his face changed.
- Manny.
- The look on Manny's face changed.
- He seems upset.
- He's angry.
Manny's angry.
He's keeping his guard up.
Your stomach...
(Hitting 10 points)
His punches are getting stronger.
(Hitting 3 points next)
Punch him hard please.
(Beating)
I hate seeing Jae Suk trying hard.
One, two.
- You learned it.
- One, two.
(Manny corners Jae Suk again.)
(Hitting 10 points again)
That was fast.
(Player Yoo only acts up, no fruit.)
Punch him hard.
If this was a real game,
you're dead already.
- One, two.
- Go, Jae Suk
- Look at that.
- The windmill.
That's right. Use the windmill.
The windmill.
(Swoosh)
(Laughing)
(Jae Suk couldn't
hit Manny at all.)
Jae Suk is exhausted.
Okay.
(The game ended
after Jae Suk acting up.)
- Nice.
- Yes.
Jae Suk. Your shirt is a mess.
- I got punched so much.
- You got punched so much.
- You got beat up.
- It's so hard.
The players from four-person team
will play a minute each.
If we're tired, we'll switch.
I'll play only for 30 seconds.
I'll switch when I'm tired.
- This is the last game.
- Go, Manny.
He got punched.
- Manny.
- He's so strong now.
Manny, please. Big punches.
(The cheeky boxer upsets Manny.)
(He starts venting his anger
on Haha.)
(Body blow right in the spot)
That was strong.
- Switch.
That's strong.
(He asks to switch
after getting beat up.)
Switch.
That's strong.
Okay.
(He's coming.)
- Okay.
- They switched.
I can't wait.
- Okay.
- Manny.
(Finally, the big match begins.)
(He's been training his fists sharp
for today.)
(He built his body
with realistic training.)
(Finally, it's time to show.)
- Manny.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Don't forget to take steps.
- Okay.
(Unexpected right jab)
Manny, please.
- I want you to win.
- He's a villain.
He's a villain.
(Hitting 3 points)
He's fast.
(Tense)
I want him to hit Jong Kook's jaw
and knock him out.
For two seconds, right?
- Knock him out for a second.
- Manny.
Manny's taking steps.
- Manny's taking steps.
- Manny.
He's fast.
There he is.
(It feels like
something big's coming.)
(Manny corners Jong Kook.)
- Harder.
- Manny.
Give them ten more minutes.
(The two carefully aim for the gap.)
(Even a light touch is fatal.)
Go.
(Finally, Manny hits Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook turns into Rudolph.)
(Pink princess)
His face.
He got punched here.
He got punched right here.
- Okay.
- He got punched here.
(Everyone is happy
except for Jong Kook.)
That's hilarious.
- He hit me in the face.
- Okay, Manny.
- Give up.
- Jong Kook.
- He hit my face.
- He's not allowed to hit the face.
- That was hilarious.
I'm jealous.
(It started as a big boxing match
and ended as comedy.)
Jong Kook was so annoying.
He punched Jong Kook
right in the face.
- He couldn't help it.
- It was his instinct.
Manny.
I can't believe...
I got to see Jong Kook
getting punched.
- Me too.
- Manny hit me right in the face.
My goodness.
Good job.
- It was his instinct.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Three-person team paid...
four hundred and fifty dollars
for the registration fee.
Really?
And four-person team...
paid 30 dollars.
(Only 30 dollars)
- Hey.
- They locked up their wallets.
Hey. I'm the only one who paid?
- This is terrible.
- You paid 30 dollars?
- Really?
- I paid 30.
I paid 20 dollars.
Don't be ridiculous.
I paid 30 dollars.
- Haha.
- I can't believe it.
- I'll now reveal the score.
- Yes.
Four-person team got
minus 78 points.
Three-person team...
(The score of the 3-person team)
is minus 105 points.
What are you talking about?
Who lost all the points?
- Who lost more than 100 points?
- Did we lose that many points?
Did you...
I didn't lose 100 points.
But he's still alive.
(Player Yoo just acted frivolously
without winning any points.)
(But Manny kept scoring
with his punches.)
(Jae Suk kept getting punched.)
I will announce the final results.
(Announcing the final results)
Kim Jong Kook has...
Total of 1,265 dollars.
Jong Kook has a lot.
Me? Right. I received
a lot of money at the beginning.
And Ji Hyo has 615 dollars.
Suk Jin has 585 dollars.
Haha has 515 dollars.
Haha.
Jae Suk has 520 dollars.
- Is it 520 dollars?
- Yes.
Se Chan has 300 dollars.
And So Min has 30 dollars.
- We should've won.
- We should've won this game.
Okay.
How much is the exemption card?
- Only 30 dollars?
- Make it 30 dollars.
What's with her?
- Why did you do that at first?
- What's the reason?
Why do you always end up like that?
Just tell me how to win.
- I will reveal today's prize first.
- Yes.
Honey.
(The gourmet honey set
that will strengthen your immunity)
- That's honey.
- If I win the prize,
I'll give it to Pacquiao.
- What?
- Honey.
About the penalty exemption card.
Both the exemption card
and the prize are...
- Six hundred dollars each.
- Seriously...
(It's more expensive
than what they expected.)
- How much?
- It's 600 dollars.
- We can't buy it.
- Then...
No, Jong Kook can buy it.
Right.
- How much do you have?
- How much do I have?
How much do I have?
I want to get one
and give it to Manny.
Okay. So you buy one prize
and one exemption card.
- All right.
- Okay.
- You buy one.
- But the exemption card.
Can you give me ten dollars?
- I'll give you ten dollars.
- All right then.
Except for those two,
the rest will get the penalty.
- Jong Kook, you're amazing.
- But you know what?
Those who get the penalty today...
are the ones who came
to the spot for 1,000 dollars.
(They ruined it from the beginning.)
- That's true.
- You're right.
Can I borrow 90 dollars from Manny?
My gosh.
(It must be an unfamiliar request
for the world star.)
He hesitates.
Please give Manny Pacquiao
a big hand.
Thank you so much.
- Right.
- We really mean it.
- Thank you so much.
- We all were honored...
to meet him here today.
Please tell him that I'm grateful
for the counter punch.
I was really honored.
Please say goodbye to our viewers.
Thank you very much
for this opportunity.
It's fun.
The games and everything.
Thank you for the opportunity...
where we played together
in this show...
and for inviting me to the show.
I hope that this is not the last.
Please tell him...
we will see him again
when we go to the Philippines.
- Okay.
- All right.
(They promised to meet again
in the Philippines.)
And...
You can tell him anytime.
- Can we really go?
- All right then.
- We can really go.
- We will have a concert.
Oh, okay. You can come.
- He regrets saying that.
- Don't put pressure on him.
He says he will
take care of everything.
No, I don't want
to put pressure on him.
What do you mean?
It's okay.
- He says it's okay. You can come.
- Really?
- Thank you.
- He will be honored.
I brought a glove.
Can I get your autograph?
Why are you saying that?
I should get his autograph.
(That's how they say goodbye
to Manny Pacquiao with love.)
- Thank you.
Thank you.
The five of you will stay
and receive the penalty now.
- The rest may leave now.
- Okay.
Today's penalty is...
known to be the training method
for the best boxers.
It's woodchopping.
You will chop firewood
before going home.
- Chop firewood? I can do that.
- That's simple.
Can I start now?
This is difficult.
Gosh, it's not split.
- This is hard.
- So Min can't do this.
It's not split.
I'm going home now.
- I'm going home!
- My gosh.
All right.
Okay.
Me too.
(Seok Sam enjoys his green old age.)
Go home.
All right.
- You should use your weight.
- So Bal.
Here, So Min.
- Gosh.
- It's ready.
It will be amazing
if she manages to do this.
Be careful.
This is not working.
(She tries her best.)
You shouldn't be afraid.
- But I'm scared.
- Just hit it.
- Hit it.
- I'm scared.
I'll split it this time.
Wait a little more. I'll do it.
- All right.
- Are you knocking?
- I'm almost there.
- All right.
- You shouldn't make cuts like that.
Jae Suk.
This will take a while.
So Min, I should go on ahead.
- Hang on a second, Haha.
- So Min, can we leave first?
(They are trying to run away.)
- This is not working.
- So Min, we should go on ahead.
- If you put it in there, it's over.
- Right.
(Once she hits it right,
it will be over.)
- Watch your hands.
- Watch your feet.
- Gosh.
- We should go.
- I should go home.
- I can't wait.
This will take a long time.
- I have to go.
- Help me leave.
I have to go now.
- See you.
- Don't drop it...
- Don't drop it like this.
- Bye.
- You're almost there.
- Jae Suk is...
- It's done.
- Yes.
(She finally did it.)
- Is it done?
- Goodbye.
So Min, we're here.
- I waited until the end.
- Me too.
- All right.
- We're family.
- Thank you for today.
- We were here for you.
(Seok Sam waits for her to finish.)
At eight every morning,
(Kim Suk Jin of BTS)
(A running middle-aged man,
Ji Suk Jin)
I drink black herbal tea.
Gosh, it's hot.
(The same name, the opposite lives)
(Dad jokes)
I like dad jokes.
I'm a dad.
(The similar but different
two universes meet.)
Hey, Jimin.
Hey, Tae Hyung.
(I'm the oldest member of BTS.)
How dare you talk to me like that?
I'm the oldest member
of Running Man.
- I'm...
Suk Jin.
I bet this is Jin.
Darn it.
(Peekaboo)
This Suk Jin is too different.
Can I change my team?
(I will use the transfer card.)
(The infernal transfer race
where they betray each other)
(Different looks)
(But the physiques are
no different?)
(The Suk Jin
who turns out to be weird...)
(and the Suk Jin
who's always been weird)
(Whose universe will win?)
(Suk Jin Versus Suk Jin)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)