It's chilly. It's so windy.
The wind is chilly.
What's the weather like today?
Is this correct?
- Yes. Good job.
- Hello.
Hello. What's the weather like today?
So windy. Today is so windy.
- Gosh.
- Hello.
- The sun is...
- Hey.
- The sun is my face.
- Pacquiao, how do I look?
The sun is my face.
- How do I look?
- It's too strong.
That's right.
Get out the sun.
- What are you doing?
- No, get out the shade.
- What is she saying?
- Is this right?
- Hello.
- Is it wrong?
No?
- You're here.
- You should study English at home.
I can't do that at home.
- Today, Ji Hyo...
- Yes.
- It's not a big accident.
- It's a minor collision.
- It's just a minor collision.
- It can happen.
So Ji Hyo is running late.
- You're here.
- Hey.
- There's Hancock.
- Hello.
(He shows up in a weird beanie.)
- You look cool.
- You look great.
- You're wearing shorts.
- Your shoes...
- Aren't your shoes...
- too much? These are...
- You're Hancock.
for Alaska or something.
It's not that cold yet.
The weather is warm now.
What's wrong with you?
- I heard it'd be cold today.
- That's not true.
- It's warm.
- It's not that cold. This is...
- This is too much.
- You should wear it in the snow.
I'm just wearing boots.
It must be hard for him though.
They are not just boots.
This is just too much.
- He will get tired.
- It's not right.
- Are you a choir member?
- What?
- A choir member or something?
- No, I'm him.
- What?
- Who is it?
- It's him.
- Right. You look the same.
He always prepares what to say.
- Hello, Suk Jin.
- Hi.
Why are you guys so early?
What is this?
Why are you late?
You're not supposed to be late.
I'm not late. You guys are early.
By the way, this is pretty.
Leave me alone.
I know you're trying to stretch it.
Stop doing that.
You should stretch the bottom.
- Like this.
- Don't stretch it.
- My gosh.
- I stretched his Gucci shirt.
- Right.
- Why would you do that?
- I stretched your Gucci shirt.
- My gosh.
He's wearing expensive clothes,
but the inner shirt is this long.
He keeps stretching it.
He bought an expensive shirt
after a long time.
What's with your outfit?
- What's wrong?
- I think it's pretty.
It looks good on you.
- It's pretty.
- You...
- You shouldn't dress up.
- He looks good.
It looks like you're desperate.
- I'm not desperate.
- Hey.
- Why would you say such a thing?
- It's for the fall.
It's simple, but it looks good.
Right. It's simple and normal.
- You do look nice.
- Okay.
You look great. It's pretty.
Jong Kook, you're dressed up too.
- I am.
- He's all dressed up.
You don't usually wear
things like this.
I didn't know you'd wear
a shirt like this.
- I look like a bear.
- Hey, Suk Jin.
This is a pretty shirt.
Why would you do that?
So Min looks pretty.
So Min, you look...
You look like a college freshman.
Is the purse for cigarettes?
I think so.
So Min,
you should pull it down a little.
(So Min,
you should pull it down a little.)
The wig.
(The wig)
It's done. You look much better now.
- That's better.
- You look better now.
You look a lot better
when it's pulled down a little.
Doesn't she look like a student
of an arts high school?
- She does.
- You look much better now.
She looks like
a high school student.
- I'm sorry.
- Ji Hyo, are you all right?
- Are you okay?
- Sorry.
- What's wrong?
- Are you all right?
- Is your car okay?
- Yes.
So your manager...
(Is your car okay?)
- So your manager...
- Why...
(Upset)
- Why?
- You should let your manager drive.
- So what happened?
- You should worry about me.
- Did your manager cause it?
- No.
- She drove herself.
Why do you drive yourself?
I asked her.
She says she's comfortable that way.
But you should let your manager
accompany you just in case.
So this place is...
Actually, Sinchon used
to be very crowded.
Right. I came here a lot
when I was Turbo.
There used to be a lot of cafes.
This place used to be
the fashion mecca.
Right. It was so popular.
I used to come here a lot.
I got my ear pierced
at the place over there.
- I did it too.
- For five dollars... Really?
(Nice to meet you.)
- Me too.
- You too?
I did it right over there.
- It was only five dollars.
- Turn right, and you will...
find the place.
Me too. They did it
with their hands.
- They just pressed it like this.
- Did you do it for neuralgia?
No.
- For neuralgia?
- It was for fashion.
There was a famous vintage shop
called Nylon here.
Right. It was Nylon.
- I bought many jeans there.
- Right.
My cousin used to run
a clothing store here.
- Really?
- She's in Texas now.
- It was over here.
- That's too much information.
Sook also ran a clothing store here.
- Sook did?
- A clothing store?
- She ran a clothing store?
- She probably met my cousin.
She used to run a clothing store.
This place reminds me
of old memories.
- I used to come here a lot.
- Right. I came here a lot.
Sinchon and Ewha University.
- I used to come here a lot.
- I came here a lot back in school.
- Where's Eagle Cafe?
- What?
- Eagle Cafe was over there.
- Near Yonsei University.
Didn't you go to Yonsei University?
- Yonsei University?
- She went to Yonsei University.
- Was there Eagle Cafe back then?
- Look at her face.
That's why you have that face.
"What do you know about Sinchon?"
When you weren't here,
we all came here and...
- Right.
- We supported the neighborhood.
It wouldn't have lasted
without Jong Kook.
- Of course.
- None of us...
went to Ewha Woman's University
or Yonsei University.
But the country
wouldn't have lasted without us.
- Ewha and Yonsei...
- But we...
- We vitalized the area.
- Jong Kook protected this place.
- You know that?
- They're the ones who protected it.
I protected
Ewha Woman's University and Sinchon.
- I didn't say anything.
- Right.
Are you saying
it's our inferiority complex?
- Hey, I came here a lot.
- Don't make me mad.
What's that face?
We're not saying this
out of an inferiority complex.
- Inferiority complex?
- This is an inferiority complex.
- You're smiling?
(Sinchon lovers
with inferiority complexes)
Fall is the shortest season
of the year.
- That's why I'm sad.
- It's so short.
So, today, we will have a race
that will bring fall...
back to our viewers.
It's called Looking For Fall.
(Looking For Fall Race)
It's your outfit...
- that shows the season well.
- Right.
But I can't let all of you
keep on the nice fall clothes...
- you're wearing now.
- Why not?
(Not all of them can keep on
the nice fall clothes they're wearing.)
You will get outfits of many
different seasons through missions.
- What?
- Oh, no.
Then we might get summer clothes.
- It's too cold.
- Or it could be winter clothes.
If all seven of you find
the fall clothes...
and put them on by three o'clock,
you can go home.
If you all find
the fall clothes before three,
- we will wrap things up right away.
- Really?
- So you need to find them quickly.
- Don't tell me...
you hid the clothes
where we can never find them.
It's not like that.
I won't let it slide.
Don't you dare hide them
at your place.
If you fail to find
the fall clothes by three o'clock,
you will get as many penalties
as the members who fail.
There will be penalties.
Today, Jae Suk will drive as he
knows the streets of Seoul well.
You can count on me
when it comes to Seoul.
You will drive
without a navigation device.
You can only use paper maps
or help from citizens...
You will drive
without a navigation device.
(Only paper maps?)
- to get to your destination.
- Paper maps?
(The reason why they planned
an analog tour like this...)
(Episode 625,
A Tour Around Seoul in Rain)
(I know how to get
to Myeongdong Catholic Cathedral.)
(Jae Suk drove without a navigation
device saying he knows the way.)
(Even when
Big Nose tried to help...)
(I'll figure it out.)
(Driver Yoo seemed quite confident
about the streets of Seoul.)
- He doesn't need navigation.
- You know what?
I don't need a map.
Just tell me where to go.
- Are you sure you don't need one?
- Yes.
- He just needs his feelings.
- Are you sure?
Of course.
The streets of Seoul...
- You should give us a map though.
- Just give us one.
I know every alley in the city...
because I walk around a lot.
He's all talk.
- The streets of Seoul...
- We will wander around a lot today.
The one in the passenger seat
should check the map.
- You know that, right?
- Sure.
- Like an assistant.
- In the passenger seat.
I'm not sure if I can read it.
You should get him
magnifying glasses too.
So he can read the map.
If any members use their phones...
to find the way while he is driving,
- please let me know in secret.
- Don't worry.
- Do we get something for that?
- If you tell me,
you will receive benefits...
when we choose members
for the penalty.
And...
- Those two.
- No. I won't say anything.
Let me tell you something.
We do use our phones a lot,
but we only use them
to search our names...
and check our social media.
- And stock prices.
- To check stock prices.
- These three things are all we do.
- Right.
There's no doubt.
All right then.
We will now decide on your outfits.
You will play the shoe-throwing game
that you haven't done in a while.
We have different sections that say
spring, summer, fall, and winter.
You will wear clothes
for the season you land in.
I don't have to change
if I pick fall.
Summer has to be the worst.
Right. It's too cold
to wear summer clothes.
You have only one chance
to throw your shoe.
If it lands out of the sections,
you will wear summer clothes.
- Summer clothes?
- If it goes out?
I bet you'll have to wear shorts
for summer.
Gosh, I have slim legs.
You will start right away
without any practice.
- Right away?
- We don't need to practice.
We don't need any practice.
- We just throw the shoes.
- This is...
what SoBangCha used to wear.
Why are there so many sections
for summer?
Because summer is long.
We have only one section
for spring and fall each.
There are a lot of sections
for winter too.
What...
There's only one for fall.
Because fall is short.
There's only one for spring
and one for fall.
- Right.
- The rest is for summer and winter.
All right then.
- Do you want to give it a try?
- Let me try.
- What?
- You can start right away.
- We can start, right?
- Yes.
He's shaking.
- Oh, no.
- Fall!
(How will it go?)
- Oh, no.
- Fall!
Darn it.
Nice.
- Fall!
- It's winter.
- Darn it.
- Nice.
You picked winter clothes.
- It's not bad.
- Winter is not bad.
Right.
- Who's next? Ssaebssaeb?
- Me.
I'll go for fall.
- Ssaebssaeb.
- All right. Here I go.
- I'll definitely pick fall.
- It's done.
- All right. Here I go.
- I'll definitely pick fall.
(It goes close to fall.)
- It's done.
- Summer.
- You picked summer.
- It's summer.
Darn it.
- Fall is the best option here.
- Right.
- One of us has to make it.
- You all should wear fall clothes.
- Right?
- We have to.
- We need at least one.
- Go this way.
- I'll pick fall.
- Good.
- At least one of us should do it.
- It's done.
- It's fall!
- Fall!
No.
It's done.
It's fall!
(Summer and fall)
- No.
- It's fall.
It's done.
- It's fall!
- Fall!
- It's summer.
- No.
- It's fall.
- Summer.
- It's fall!
- Fall!
- It's summer.
- No.
- It's fall.
- Fall. This is definitely fall.
Don't be ridiculous. It's summer.
Fall.
- It's fall.
- That's summer.
This is definitely fall.
- Don't be ridiculous. It's summer.
- This means...
- he looks down on Hyung In.
- How can this be summer?
- This is fall.
- It's in summer.
This is...
- It's summer.
- Fall.
Hey, what's with the whistle?
- Because he's...
- Hey.
To be honest,
you're ignoring Hyung In.
- How is this fall?
- This is...
I'm sorry.
I apologize on behalf of them.
They think they can deceive you.
- How can this be fall?
- That's not enough to fight for.
This is fall.
If you used the jimmy jib,
it would look like fall.
(The two unscrupulous members
keep saying it's fall.)
I'm sure. The jimmy jib...
- That was so close.
- Anyway...
The shoe is in summer,
but he says it's fall.
- I chose the wrong shoe.
- I know.
Does anyone of you...
Haha is worried about his shoe.
He says it's expensive.
I don't mind getting hurt,
but this shoe...
- You can use someone else's shoe.
- I'll lend you mine.
You can use mine.
It seems like Haha really cares
for his shoes.
- I guess they are expensive.
- No.
- Even if they're expensive...
- I'll go next.
They are very expensive.
Here I go.
Can I try?
- You look good, Se Chan.
- This is nice.
Hey, you look a lot better
with the sneaker on.
(It's Se Chan's sneaker.)
- Hey.
- I'm serious.
- This is really...
- It's different, right?
Hey, you look much better now.
- I waited for a year to get these.
- This is so much prettier.
It took me a year to get these.
Why would you wait
to get such shoes?
- This is a lot better.
- I really don't understand.
It looks good on you.
You should wear it.
Does it make you look taller?
I go like this, Jong Kook.
You can easily find shoes
like that at Dongdaemun.
- Hey.
- What's with this shoe?
What's wrong?
What is with this shoe?
(He calms himself
and throws a shoe.)
- Bounce out!
- Oh, no.
You get summer.
- That was too short.
- That silly thing.
(Haha didn't even make it
to the target.)
Looks good.
At least you hit the target.
It landed outside, so it's summer.
- You like summer anyway.
- Right. I do like it.
- Ji Hyo, you're the last one to go.
- Good luck.
- Ji Hyo.
- Wish me good luck.
Your odds here are worse than
in Las Vegas.
I know.
- She did it.
- What?
I know.
(Ji Hyo goes for it
in the last turn.)
(To be safe, at least Ji Hyo
should get fall clothes.)
- She did it.
- What?
That was so close, Ji Hyo.
- I know.
- She did it.
That was so close, Ji Hyo.
I thought she would land in fall.
- You were so close.
- It's summer.
Only Suk Jin gets winter clothes,
and the rest of you
get summer clothes.
- Darn it.
- Please bring in the clothes.
- I'm the only one who got winter.
- That was so close.
The winter jackets have
hot packs in them.
- Hot packs?
- Yes.
- Hot packs in them.
- Hot packs?
If he takes off
the jacket in the car,
- please tell me.
- Wait a second.
I don't use
hot packs even in winter.
He can't unzip the jacket, right?
- I get hot easily.
- He shouldn't be cold.
I don't even eat ginseng
because my body temperature is high.
My hands are always warm.
That's underwear.
That's not summer clothing.
(They look like underwear.)
- This is...
- Gosh.
- This is ridiculous.
- We have to wear that?
- This is underwear.
- What is this?
This is absurd.
Gosh, this is...
- What's this?
- Are we wearing only this shirt?
- What do we do?
- What is this?
- But the slippers look horrible.
- I don't wear slippers like these.
(It's a set of cool mesh
underwear and sandals.)
I don't wear sandals.
What is this one?
Are we supposed to wear
this sleeveless shirt?
- You can wear socks.
- Only underpants and this?
Then what?
I have to take this off right away.
We need decent clothes.
- We're celebrities.
- I have my own style.
This is...
- I look terrible.
- Gosh, this is...
Seriously, this is so lame.
It looks so ugly.
The fabric will keep you cool.
- Will you stop talking?
- Even the color...
That's enough, Hyung In.
I can feel that it's cool.
- Gosh.
- Look at Jae Suk.
What do we wear for the bottoms?
- Is this it?
- I...
- Actually, it looks like...
- He looks so funny.
you chose to wear it.
- It's a loose-fitting shirt.
- I...
- You seem to like it.
- It looks like I chose it myself.
- That's better than your clothes.
- You look good.
Jae Suk.
(He's all dressed up in blue.)
You look great.
- Your sandals look fashionable.
- It looks like my own clothes.
We have to go around together
no matter what.
We have to stick to each other.
If you go to the bathroom alone,
you'll get posted on SNS.
Don't go around by yourself.
- We should go around together.
- We have to move as a group.
This is crazy.
How am I supposed to wear this?
(Seok Sam is the only one
who has to wear winter clothes.)
Gosh, it's hot already.
I'm feeling so hot.
Hey.
I'm sensitive to heat.
I'm serious. I'm not joking.
(He puts on a padded jacket.)
My gosh.
Gosh, this is...
This jacket is for climbing
the Himalayas.
(The jacket is made for
the Himalayas.)
This is made for the Himalayas.
(The warmest padded jacket)
Gosh. These are fleece-lined gloves!
Of course. What did you expect?
I get hot very easily.
Isn't this jacket
from a very expensive brand?
Yes, it is.
Suk Jin, you're dressed nicely.
Don't say that, you punk.
- One grilled sweet potato, please.
- Rather than us, Suk Jin...
- Gosh.
What is this?
- I'm jealous. I want to wear that.
- Gosh, I'm so cold.
Se Chan looks as if he's wearing
his own clothes. He looks natural.
- I don't look like a celebrity.
- You look like you got dolled up.
This isn't
how a celebrity would dress.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Hey.
So Min was wearing
such a nice outfit earlier.
- Look how she looks now.
- I look shabby.
- If you complete the mission,
- Right.
- you can change into your clothes.
- It looks like his own clothes.
(They have to complete the mission
to wear fall clothes.)
It's too cold for this outfit.
- I'm so cold.
- This is practically a penalty.
All of you have changed
your clothes.
The first place to go is a book cafe
near Mount Inwang.
(A book cafe near Mount Inwang)
- What did she say?
- We'll go there looking like this?
- Looking like this?
- In this outfit? Are you serious?
- They're just insane.
- Use this map to find the way...
- while driving yourselves.
- This is driving me crazy.
- We need a map, Jong Kook.
- Jongno-gu.
- Hold on. From where we are now...
- Jae Suk.
- It's easy.
- Oh, this is the map we'll use.
You've never been to
Mount Inwang before.
Dongnimmun or Seodaemun Station...
And Baewha Women's University.
- He seems to know the way.
- Of course, I know.
- Where is it?
- Right.
It's near Gyeongbok Palace.
We can get there quickly from here.
- Where you had group dates before.
- What?
You had a group date with girls
from Jinseon Girls' High School.
- It wasn't that school.
- You got rejected there.
No, it was
Pungmoon Girl's High School.
- Pungmoon Girl's High School.
- Oh, I see.
- You got rejected?
- The former one is in Gangnam.
- He got rejected so many times.
- I'm not familiar with Seoul.
Okay. I've got it.
- I'll be counting on you.
- Don't complain...
- that we get there too quickly.
- You'll do well.
- I know Seoul. Just trust me.
- I know that.
- Just as you know Anyang.
- Okay. That's right.
- I know Seoul.
- Of course.
Now that you've checked the map,
you may leave.
- Can we keep the map?
- Sure.
- Let's go.
- Hey, I'm not ready yet.
My hands are sweating so much.
- We're here. On your left.
- Oh, that's the one? Okay.
We'll get in.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Come on.
The youngest members should sit
in the back.
- I'm so cold, Se Chan.
- I'm cold too.
Let's ask him to turn on the heater
instead of the air conditioner.
Jae Suk, please turn the heater on.
- Hey, no heater.
- At least the seat warmer.
- I'm so cold.
- We won't turn on the heater.
- Please turn the heater on.
- Don't say that.
- I'm so cold.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- Here you go.
- What is it?
- The assistant MC should do it.
Give it to me.
Suk Jin, you should help me
while I'm driving.
Okay.
Where is our destination?
Oh, I see the book cafe.
(The destination is
approximately 16 minutes away.)
Let's move toward
Baewha Women's University for now.
Show me.
Daeshin High School
or Baewha Women's University.
I'm so hot. Gosh.
- I have to turn right here...
- Go toward Gwanghwamun for now.
No, we shouldn't go that way.
We should go toward Gwanghwamun.
- Gyeongbok Palace.
- No, we should go to Dongnimmun.
We can go in this direction
to get there.
- I know the way. Listen to me.
- Suk Jin rarely goes out.
Hey. I know the way for sure.
- I'll tell you directions.
- Make a right turn.
- I'll find the way. Be quiet.
- Turn right and enter the tunnel.
- Don't tell me what to do.
- Let's go.
- Turn right and enter the tunnel.
- Be quiet!
- Listen.
- Make a right turn.
- Gosh, I'm hungry.
- I'll find the way.
- Hey, make a right turn here.
- Be quiet.
- Turn right. To the left.
- To the left. Make a turn.
- Hey.
- Turn left.
- Don't tell me what to do.
- Go toward Severance Hospital.
- That's a long way around.
- That's right.
- I'm taking a direct route.
- Turn right toward the tunnel.
- Be quiet.
- I'll tell you something.
- I've been living in Seoul...
- He sounds like an old fossil.
- since I was born...
- Make a right turn here!
- Hey.
- I told you to stay out of this.
- Don't tell me what to do.
- Learn English. "Backseat driver."
- "Backseat driver?"
- Yes.
- A passenger who nags the driver...
- "Backseat driver."
- is called a backseat driver.
- I see.
- Are we all backseat drivers?
- Don't be a backseat driver.
- No, only when you nag the driver.
- I should focus on the road.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Quiet them down in the back.
- Sure. Be quiet, everyone.
Jae Suk is shooting the show!
- Stop nagging at us.
- Can't you see me working?
- He's the main MC, you know.
- Got it?
- My gosh. This is...
- Turn right and go straight.
Don't say anything.
- You tamed such a fierce dog.
- Just let him drive, Suk Jin.
You're an assistant MC.
So just be quiet.
- Hey. Gosh, I'm so hot.
- You see...
I'm sorry, guys,
but I'll roll down the window.
- No. Don't do that.
- Suk Jin, I'm cold.
Suk Jin, I'm cold.
Please roll the window up.
This is driving me nuts. I'm so hot.
Why am I the only one
who has to wear this?
Go straight
until you see the tunnel...
Suk Jin, don't say anything.
- Go straight...
- Just sit there and take a nap.
When I tell you we're there,
you can just say, "Oh, are we?"
Just don't say anything.
They gave us
such an easy mission for us.
- Let's stop there.
- You guys never use a GPS anyway.
- Who doesn't?
- Right?
- Old people never use it.
- Hey.
- I can't drive without a GPS.
- You don't use it anyway.
- They don't believe in it.
- I don't use a GPS either.
- True.
"Turn right? That's ridiculous.
I should turn left here."
- "My way is the right way."
- They're so stubborn.
- While driving, I would say,
- "What's wrong with it?"
"Why is the GPS telling me
to go that way?"
Exactly.
- "Why should I go that way?"
- It's hard.
"What? No."
- "I should go straight."
- "It's a long way around."
They always doubt it.
- Hey, I told you to go that way.
- That's why I don't use it.
And you should know
that it causes a traffic jam.
- Turn right to go to Dongnimmun.
- Go straight.
- Right. I should turn right.
- If you want to go that way.
- Why should we turn right?
- If we go toward Dongnimmun.
- Turn right to go to Dongnimmun.
- Go straight.
(Driver Yoo is going to turn left
when he should go straight.)
- The road condition is quite good.
- And turn right over there.
- Suk Jin.
- I know that.
- Just put it down.
- Suk Jin.
- I told you not to advise me.
- Suk Jin, put it down.
- Hold on. Why are we...
- He doesn't need your help.
Suk Jin, just take a nap.
- We're going the wrong way.
- No. We have to turn left here.
- Switch seats with Se Chan.
- I don't think so.
Doesn't the road
lead to Seodaemun Prison?
- Correct.
- Right?
If we turn left, it leads to
Dongnimmun Station, right?
- That's correct.
- Good. Then it's okay.
- Oh, wait.
- Hey, drive.
- We shouldn't go that way.
- I said, drive.
- See? I told you to go straight.
- I should've gone straight.
(Departed: Shinchon Station,
Destination: Book Cafe)
(ETA: 10:46 a.m.)
It's not a big deal.
Why would you get worked up?
I've been living here...
- for over 50 years.
- We shouldn't go that way.
- Suk Jin.
- Gosh, I kept telling you.
Why won't you trust me?
- Let me explain, Suk Jin.
- We have to go around.
- I thought it was on that side.
- No, it's on the left side.
- I know. I was mistaken.
- I told you that.
- Suk Jin, I'm impressed.
- Don't be mad.
- Why would you get so upset?
- Everyone makes a mistake.
- The traffic might be bad that way.
- He's turning the car around.
- I'll turn around.
- And then make a left turn.
"The map was made
because they took the wrong road."
It was so obvious
that he was turning the car around.
- Hey, what did I do so wrong?
- We're all ganging up on him.
- What did I do, Jong Kook?
- I mean...
- He was turning the car around.
- I perfectly...
- Se Chan, sit in the front seat.
- Jae Suk, can I do it instead?
- Switch seats with Suk Jin. Go.
- That's a good idea.
- Why should I?
- Switch seats with Se Chan.
- I can't get out here.
- I can't drive with you there.
- Se Chan, hurry up and come.
- He'll direct you from the back.
- But I was right all along.
- Hurry up and go.
Give me the map.
I can do it in the back.
- Go and switch seats with him.
- Gosh. This is so frustrating.
Get up here Se Chan.
So we should go straight
toward Baewha Women's University.
Turn left right in front of
Baewha Women's University.
- Okay.
- After Daeshin High School.
- It's in my head now. Tear it up.
- No. I'll keep it.
- Just tear it up.
(Driver Yoo is full of confidence.)
- The staff members must be...
- I told you so.
expecting us to get lost
and create funny scenes.
- I'll prove them wrong.
- You'll...
- Listen. Because you took...
- What?
the wrong turn,
we wasted 15 minutes.
- I can explain. I had no choice.
- Don't be hard on him, Suk Jin.
- We wasted 15 minutes.
- You should've told me directions,
- but you failed to do so.
- That's not true.
I told you to go straight
numerous times.
- You should've pushed it harder.
- I have the map in my head now.
- I feel bad for Suk Jin.
- That was hilarious.
- Suk Jin was right about it.
- In this direction.
- Suk Jin was right all along.
- Really?
He was right,
but we all ignored him.
I was right.
We should've gone this way.
- Stop going on about it.
- Like I said, I was mistaken.
- Why didn't you trust me?
- Jae Suk.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Think about your health. Relax.
- All right.
- Don't get stressed out.
- Think about your health. Relax.
- All right.
("Think about your health?")
"Think about your health?"
- I'm sweating in winter clothes.
- He may...
- He may have a muscular body,
- Aren't you worried about me?
- but he catches a cold easily.
- That's true.
But Suk Jin wouldn't stop
going on about it.
(The friendship between them
grows stronger every day.)
- "Think about your health."
- I know I should always...
- stay positive.
- Look after your health.
- I'll do that.
- Don't get stressed out.
- Thanks to you...
- That's thoughtful.
Gosh, why did you turn on
the seat warmer?
When did you turn it on?
Gosh, I'm already so hot.
We should go toward
Baewha Women's University.
I'll find the way.
Hold on.
I should see the sign carefully.
Look. Baewha Women's University is
written on the sign.
I'm not allowed to
make a left turn here,
- so I'll make a U-turn.
- Make a U-turn.
- And then... We're here.
- We should go that way. Okay.
Let's go.
You're amazing.
- Great job.
- I'm amazing, right?
- When we first came here...
- We have great teamwork.
- It worked out as he was quiet.
- I know every place...
- in Seoul.
- Things are going smoothly now.
- Had you listened to me earlier,
- I know every place in Seoul.
we would've passed here
20 minutes ago.
I know every place in Seoul.
- We're okay now.
- Gosh.
I found the way. Okay!
- Things are working out so well.
- Exactly.
This is what I told you guys about.
- Looking back now,
- This is driving me nuts.
- when I was financially struggling,
- Yes.
- I walked a lot. It all paid off.
- That's a sad story.
- I came here a lot for a date too.
- Who?
- You're lying.
- Stop lying. I don't believe you.
There's no way
you came here for a date.
I'm sure you walked around alone
picking up some cigarette butts...
- because you had no money.
- Hey.
- I bet he asked for cigarettes too.
- Absolutely.
- I'm telling you...
- Jae Suk.
I'm sorry, but I can't help you
if you tell such a lie.
- I guess I made you worry.
- Of course.
- "Think about your health."
- Exactly. Think about your health.
Hey. Make a right turn.
- Turn right.
- This is Baewha Women's University.
- Oh, right. We're on the right way.
- Yes. We're on the right way.
The staff members must be bored.
We didn't even get lost.
I think you should
come up with another plan.
So Min,
tell them to make a new plan.
- Make a new plan.
- In 1, 2, 3. Make a new plan.
- What do you mean by that?
- I'm talking about this mission.
- Why?
- It's too easy for us.
- I know many good restaurants here.
- It's a great photo spot.
- There are lots of nice cafes here.
- That place looks nice.
- It's pretty.
- In this area?
Yes.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- Should I go straight or turn left?
- No.
Hey, Baewha Women's University is
on our left side.
- On our left side?
- Yes.
- Then we're on the wrong way.
- See? I told you so.
(Destination: Book Cafe)
(The route
that Jae Suk should've taken)
- We should go back.
- Then...
- Let's ask someone.
- Se Chan.
- Should it be on our right side?
- Yes, it should be,
- but it's on our left side now.
- We should turn around.
We should turn around.
- I was right about turning right.
- Yes, you were right.
- That place looks nice too.
- I was right.
- Turn right around the university.
- Look, Ji Hyo.
I see a lot of
nice restaurants here.
Sundaeguk sounds so delicious.
- Even in the old days,
- Sundaeguk? Oh, my.
- I like sundaeguk.
- taxi drivers...
- always asked for directions.
- You're right.
- They asked people on the street.
- Yes, in the old days,
we didn't have navigation systems.
- "Excuse me."
- Let's ask. It'll be faster.
- Right. Ask someone.
- We can ask for directions...
- when we're almost there.
- Here...
The stores are cute and pretty.
I really love fall. Look at this.
- It's beautiful.
- It's nice.
- This street is so beautiful.
- Indeed.
- Everything is so pretty here.
- Oh, we're in Sajik-dong.
What's the name
of this elementary school?
That cafe looks so pretty.
- This neighborhood...
- Maedong?
- Seoul Maedong Elementary School.
- Oh, I see.
Right? Look at that.
(There's only a main street
around the book cafe.)
- Jae Suk.
- This isn't the right way.
This neighborhood looks nice.
- It looks so nice, right?
- Yes.
- Hey, I used to come here...
- It's nice.
- We should interview some people.
- I know, right?
I think it would be better
to take the main road.
- I agree.
- Why are we in a narrow alley?
It's okay. We'll find the main road.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
- This is Baewha Women's University.
- We should...
- Where is it?
- Here.
- Are you sure?
- It says it's a dead end.
- This is Baewha Women's University.
- It's a dead end.
- It says it's a dead end.
- This is Baewha Women's University.
(No passing, no roads ahead)
- I think we're lost.
- Show me. No, we're not.
- We're not lost.
- We're going the right way.
- We should keep going.
- Are you sure?
It should be around here
or up there.
It must be on the top.
- But there's a dead end sign.
- I'm sure we're almost there.
I see.
I think it will be a dead end.
He only thinks about the direction.
- Listen, Suk Jin.
- Great. He's like a runaway train.
(It's a dead end.)
- It's a dead end.
- There's no way ahead.
- Turn the car around.
- Jong Kook.
- You can turn it around here.
Jong Kook said it was a dead end,
but Jae Suk didn't listen.
- Let's not get flustered.
- Make a U-turn here.
- They don't listen to others.
- Jong Kook said it was a dead end.
"Too many cooks spoil the broth."
Exactly. Guys, So Min just said,
- "Too many cooks spoil the broth."
Just leave it to me, okay?
- Okay.
- Right.
Had he not come
to this blocked street,
we would never have had a chance
to see this neighborhood.
- You're being too generous.
- Don't you think so?
- The power of optimism.
- You know I'm right.
- You've gone too far.
- I'm speechless.
- What you should see is...
- Yes.
- Look how well I'm turning the car.
- Exactly.
It's an advanced skill.
- Hey, this...
- It's an advanced skill.
Anyone can do that...
- I like the way you say that.
- if they know how to drive.
- Right. Nice!
- Who wouldn't be able to do that?
- This is the best driving skill.
- I should've gone that way.
Oh, no. It's a one-way street.
You can't turn right.
You're right. I should go around.
- Suk Jin is good at staying calm.
- This is driving me nuts.
But didn't you expect this much?
- It's a one-way street.
- I can't know every street.
- Let me ask someone.
- Right. You should do that.
- Let's ask a passerby.
- Ask someone if you don't know.
They say that you should ask others
when you can't figure something out.
- Right. Even when we know the way.
- Go ahead.
- What should I say?
- Suseong-dong Valley.
Sunrise Hill.
- Hello.
- It's a park.
- The map isn't accurate.
- You're right.
- Ask where Mount Inwang Park is.
- Just ask...
- Let me ask. Hey, kid.
- where Suseong-dong Valley is.
- Hey, kid. Excuse me.
- My goodness.
(The kid leaves.)
- Why that little...
- Hey. "Kid?"
How rude. She should've stopped.
Hey, a middle-aged lady is coming.
I think she lives here.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- You should turn left...
Can you tell me how to get
to the park in Suseong-dong?
(She walks past them quickly.)
It's near the park.
- Are you a ghost?
- She didn't want to be bothered.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
Why...
- Are you a ghost?
- The park.
Am I invisible or something?
- How about we ask a realtor?
- Where is Suseong-dong Valley?
- I don't know.
- How about the park?
She has never heard of it.
(They failed to get directions
from citizens.)
- Isn't that a school?
- It's because...
- Wait.
- Jae Suk.
- Sir.
Isn't that a school?
(Someone came out of the store
at the right timing.)
- We saw another way to go up.
- Go straight and turn left.
- Right.
- He said that. Why didn't you stop?
What I'm saying is
that he should've followed...
the main street
instead of turning left here.
It's a faster way.
There's a narrow street here.
Honestly, I can't bear this.
I want to search online.
Look at the map.
We're going this way.
Baewha Women's University is
behind us right now.
- You're right.
- We should go right.
- No. He said to go left.
- Why did he tell us to go left?
- Jae Suk, I think...
- Jae Suk!
we should take the man's advice.
He said we should go left.
This is a one-way street.
- We drove past this place earlier.
- Listen.
- Trust me.
- My gosh.
- You drive me crazy.
- The sundaeguk place looks nice.
- I said this earlier, right?
- I know how I should get there.
(Hi)
(They drove on the same street
15 minutes ago.)
Why are we going the same way?
What is the reason?
Why else? We're trying to find
our way to the destination.
- But we drove past here.
- It's so quiet and peaceful here.
Enjoy watching the stonewall.
- I'm cold.
- Exactly.
There's a road sign over there.
- What does it say?
- We passed this place before.
- Read it out loud.
- We passed this place.
I mean, this map is...
Baewha Women's University is...
- It's because...
- This is Baewha Women's University.
- Maybe it's not. You're wrong.
- It's Baewha Women's University.
This is Baewha Women's University,
Suk Jin.
- Is it really this small?
- Yes, it's written there.
- This is Baewha Women's University.
- Right.
- He's right. I saw it written.
- Yes, it is.
- Yes. Jae Suk...
- This is Baewha Women's University.
- Make a right.
- Turn right!
- Turn right.
- Speak louder.
- I don't think I should.
- He won't listen anyway.
- See? It's allowed. Look.
- Jae Suk.
- It's a kindergarten.
Yes, that's it. Jae Suk,
- we went down the street...
- Sir.
- We went down the street...
(He chuckles.)
- Speak up, will you?
- Sir...
- I can't do that.
- There he is.
Sir, how do we get
to Suseong-dong Valley?
I told you to turn left.
- How do we get there?
- I told you to turn left.
- Yes, you did.
- "I told you to turn left."
- You'll see a pavilion.
Turn left there
and go up the street.
- Oh, I see.
- I see. Thank you, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- Why didn't you listen to him?
- Exactly.
- He said to go left.
- I just wanted to check it again.
- It's not that you wanted to...
- He double-checked it.
- Gosh. You frustrate me.
- That's right.
- You should've turned left earlier.
- I told you to go left many times.
Despite everything, I feel relaxed
since Jong Kook is here.
That's good.
You should all relax a little bit.
- Exactly. Relax a little bit.
- Right. Why are you all on edge?
Hey, guys, look after your health.
Jong Kook is such a nice person.
When you drive a car
with many other people in it,
- you feel pressured.
- You should...
- You need to change your name...
- We shouldn't pressure him.
- to "Honey Kim."
- "Honey Kim?"
(Chuckling)
- I'll call him Honey Kim.
- Honey Kim.
(Laughing)
- Honey Kim?
- He's so sweet.
And he's so gentle.
- Sweet and gentle?
- Honey Kim.
Honey Kim.
- I like that name. It's not bad.
- Right.
- No.
- We'll probably find...
We haven't reached the pavilion.
- Jae Suk, go a little further.
- You should keep going.
- The pavilion...
- He said to go left.
You are off course.
- We haven't reached the pavilion.
- No. You should turn left...
- when you see the pavilion.
- This isn't...
He said we would see it
if we keep going.
- An espresso bar. It looks nice.
- He said to turn when you see it.
- It looks really nice.
- The pavilion...
We're all talking
about different things.
He said you should turn left
when you see the pavilion.
- Yes, that's what he said.
- Turn right here.
Hyung In,
I think you need a new plan.
- We're not working together.
- Exactly.
- Turn right here. Listen to me.
- We're not working together.
- We...
- You can see Mount Inwang.
- Yes, I can see it.
- That's Mount Inwang.
He's following his gut.
I'm sure you'll find the way.
- We're done for. We are...
- Are we?
- on this street right now.
- Tell me.
- Then tell me this one thing.
- And it's because...
Be quiet so that I can find the way.
- I'll show you that I can do that.
- Everyone, quiet down.
- Let's be quiet.
- Okay.
You must be happy to have someone
you can always count on.
- He's more than reliable.
- It's great.
- I'm impressed.
- Honey Kim.
- It's beautiful.
- This must be Suseong-dong Valley.
Go left.
Where should we go?
- Gosh, I'm so hot.
- The road will end.
- This is driving me nuts.
- Where is the book cafe?
- It's really beautiful.
- I don't see it.
- My, look at that.
- We're not there yet.
- There's no road ahead.
- It looks nice.
- Jae Suk.
- This is Suseong-dong Valley.
Look. Suseong-dong Valley is here.
We have to go left
following this street.
We should go back.
But we can't drive on that street.
I think we should park here
and walk to the cafe.
No. They told us not to use a GPS
because we can drive there.
You have a point.
We should've gone this way.
Following the main street...
You empty heads.
Hey, chicken head. Shut it.
- Chicken head, shut it.
- Chicken head?
- You stone head.
- You bird head.
It's the same map.
But this is Suseong-dong Valley.
Jae Suk, let's get there today.
- We can drive up the street?
- But are you sure...
- that the book cafe is up there?
- Jae Suk.
- It's not on a street like this.
- I don't think it's up there.
We should go that way.
- Isn't it around here?
- No.
With the valley on our right side...
- Jae Suk, listen.
- Are you starting to get annoyed?
- This street...
- Jae Suk.
He's starting to get annoyed.
- Jong Kook, tell him.
- It's time to be yourself.
- Stop putting up with him.
- Quit acting like that.
- Jae Suk, I have an idea.
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, please go back...
- to how you used to be.
- Be yourself again.
- Be the tough Jong Kook again.
- You're not "Honey Kim."
- I think he's doing well.
Be the mean Jong Kook again.
- Exactly.
- The mean Jong Kook?
Yes. Be the mean Jong Kook again.
Gosh. I'm so hot.
- It's not on a street like this.
- I don't think it's up there.
- Maybe we should go that way.
- Isn't it around here?
- No, it's not on the street.
- Let's ask a local.
- Let's ask.
- You should speak up.
- He won't listen to me.
- The cafe's name isn't written.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
How about you listen to Se Chan...
- and go as he suggests?
- Sounds good.
- Since you keep getting lost here,
- Yes.
go to the main street...
How about we ask a bus driver?
- That's a great idea. I agree.
- Right?
- We should ask a local.
- I'll ask a bus driver.
There's someone.
- We have to ask a local.
- But...
- Hello, sir.
- our destination is the book cafe.
Sir, hello. Could you please
have a look at this?
- Can you tell us...
- Thank you.
Where do you think
this narrow street is?
- You have to...
- Isn't this the book cafe?
- Where is it?
- It's up there.
- Up there.
- Is it up there?
- "C" cafe.
- Really? How do we drive there?
- Yes.
- Go this way to the main street.
- I see.
- Yes.
- Turn right and take Bugak Skyway.
- I see. Bugak Skyway.
- Really?
- Got it. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Great. Thank you!
- Let's go!
- Gosh. This is so difficult.
- Okay.
- You were right all along.
- Let's go!
I wonder when Jong Kook
will return to his old self.
- Be the mean Jong Kook again.
- Be yourself again.
This is the third time
I've seen this sundaeguk place.
- That's why I told you...
- We've been going around here.
- When we go that way...
- You should turn here.
- Hey, I have an idea.
- Se Chan was right all along.
You shouldn't turn right here.
- Go further and take Bugak Skyway.
- I know. Hey.
- I have an idea.
- I told you that ten times.
- Hey. Haha, get out.
- Keep going.
- Why should I?
- Haha, get out.
- Not here.
- You...
You can walk.
- Get out.
- Why me?
- Why?
- I don't appreciate the blabbering.
- Why me?
- Take a cab instead.
- Take a cab.
- What did I even say?
Jong Kook.
Say you're sorry.
Just say you're sorry.
Don't think less of this van.
If you are to ride with us...
- Apologize.
- I'm sorry.
- Good.
- There you go.
- That's how it should be.
- Make a left up there.
Give him a break this one time.
You brat.
Are we in the military
with you two as our officers?
- That's not it.
- Suk Jin, get out.
What...
He's a real thug.
- Jae Suk.
- Who are you to order me around?
- Because I'm the driver.
- He's the worst.
- How can I get off?
- Just like that...
- You should get off.
- Yes, get off.
I'm telling you to shut it.
He reminds me of my eldest uncle.
On the right.
See? I was right all along.
- Here we go.
- This is the one.
- We're going the right away.
- What a pretty path.
(ETA: 11:27 a.m.)
- We're going the right way.
- Look how pretty it is.
- This is the one. What a delight.
- Look at that.
- I've been here on my bike before.
- Isn't this beautiful?
- What a sight.
- It's beautiful.
- They seem overly positive.
- Why go elsewhere...
when Seoul has these gems?
- Goodness.
- We'll probably be back...
- next year for a drive.
- Exactly.
- It's on the right.
- There it is.
- On the right.
- I can't believe it was this hard.
We're finally here.
- Good job, everyone.
- Nice!
- Okay.
- Good.
Good job, everyone.
It's beautiful here.
- Let's go. Gosh, it's hot.
- I'm glad we're here.
(The roasted chestnut vendor
finally escapes from the vehicle.)
- Jong Kook, come on.
- What?
Okay!
- The clothes are shabby though.
- It's summer.
What the...
The heat pack is boiling.
- We have fine weather today.
- Tell me about it.
- Gosh.
- Let's huddle up.
Let's move as a group.
- I'm embarrassed by our outfits.
- Same here.
- It's like we're dressed as a team.
- That's what people will think.
- Director.
- Yes?
- The guys won't listen to me.
- You were right all along.
I called out the right direction,
but they ignored me twice.
- They kept cutting me off.
- These boomers are killing me.
I could tell that Jong Kook
was forcing himself to stay calm.
- They won't listen though.
- Jong Kook was trembling.
- They wouldn't listen to me.
- It's cold out here.
- And it's cold.
- It's cold.
It's freezing.
Unbelievable.
The map was misleading.
We had too many back-seat drivers.
You are to shut it,
- and you are to sit up front.
- Yes, me.
And Suk Jin should shut it.
- I was right all along though.
- I mean it.
You're sitting in the back
doing nothing,
so why are you complaining?
What's wrong about
enjoying the view?
- I...
- I'll see how long this lasts.
I'm right though.
- Why did we need to rush it?
- Jong Kook.
- You...
- Jae Suk, I...
- Don't stress yourself out.
- I must say this though.
But I was right all along.
He just told Jong Kook
not to stress himself out.
We got lost a while ago
because he took the wrong path.
- Go back to selling sweet potatoes!
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I'm saying I was right.
- Mister.
- You weren't right about anything.
- You shouldn't sit next to me.
- Se Chan should.
- I'll sit next to you.
I need someone who can read the map.
- I'm loving the breeze.
- It's freezing!
- It's windy today.
- What now?
This is the book cafe
on Mount Inwang...
where you'll be first
delivering fall to the viewers.
In accordance with your attire,
those in summer clothes
will get iced coffee...
while those in winter clothes
will get hot coffee.
- Okay.
- Iced coffee?
- Hot coffee?
- Enjoy your coffee and tea.
I always drink iced coffee
even in winter.
This looks delicious.
- It's salt butter roll bread.
- Those are delicious.
This looks great.
- Thank you.
- Here.
- Let's slice these.
- Chocolate.
Step aside.
(Driver Yoo is being childish.)
- Haha.
- Yes?
- One day, we'll turn the tables.
- I can't take this.
- Let's come up with something.
- Jae Suk.
Hey.
- What?
- Don't eat it.
It's not like you bought these.
(It's not like you bought these.)
- What?
- Watch your tone, young man.
- You ungrateful...
- It's all right.
Haha.
Don't eat whatever I buy, then.
One shouldn't be rude.
The two are getting on my nerves.
Unbelievable.
- What the...
- Get over here.
Don't eat anything from now on
since I'll be buying.
I'll be buying from now on.
Anyway, check out the fall scenery.
(In awe)
(He reacts at lightning speed.)
Doesn't he get on your nerves?
- He's incorrigible.
- That was quick, Jong Kook.
I was thinking
the same thing, you see.
- Your reaction...
- Was I...
- Is this how I used to be?
- Yes.
- Was I worse?
- This was you a few years back.
Haha and Jong Kook...
- aren't the same.
- Of course not.
- He's more prudent.
- Exactly.
(He's more prudent.)
He doesn't say things lightly.
(It's like Jae Suk's in love.)
Right, Jong Kook?
I don't agree to things
that are clearly wrong.
Maybe I should appear
on your Youtube channel again.
(Maybe I should appear
on your Youtube channel again.)
(The blood pact was formed
when Jae Suk made his appearance.)
We'll address the idea in December.
(We'll address the idea
in December.)
Gosh, Jae Suk.
(Others suffer the most
when they get along.)
- You two...
- This is the worst.
There's no way out of this.
Haha, you should give up.
- Them...
- Haha, admit your defeat.
- That's in your best interest.
- This won't last though.
- Haha, give up.
- They're playing with fire.
Things got slightly dangerous
back in the van.
- I saw it too.
- He was trembling.
Jong Kook had his shoes off
and was trembling with annoyance.
He was that furious.
They're making this up.
You shouldn't lie on TV, you know.
- Did you see it or not?
- I saw it.
- I definitely saw it.
- Don't lie on TV.
- Haha...
- His right foot.
- No, his left foot was up.
- When?
- I saw it myself.
- He has a mole on his left foot.
- Just give up, Haha.
- I never said such a thing.
Here. Let's have one each.
Hey.
Can't you let us all have one
while you're at it?
At this rate, you'll end up kissing.
You know what?
Keep at it.
Being on his good side isn't so bad.
- Let's get on with it, then.
- Here's your first mission.
First, you will head downstairs...
and ask three citizens who might have
good chemistry with you...
to join you for this round.
- Sure.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- Right now?
Three per person?
- No, all together.
- Three all together?
- Sure.
- Okay.
We should ask if they're okay
with being on TV.
- We must ask that.
- We'll ask them that.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you.
- It's onion mayonnaise.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
Would you mind
filming something with us?
You're taller than you seem.
- Me? Thank you.
- Yes.
How would you like
to be on the show with us?
- What do you say?
- I'd like that.
Jae Suk, he agreed to it.
Really? Could you join us?
Where though?
- Upstairs.
- Sure.
- That's one.
- And...
- We need two more.
- Right.
- So Min and Ji Hyo.
- How about that gentleman?
Right, him.
Sir, could you...
If you're free, would you mind
sparing us some of your time?
Could you join us
for a chat upstairs?
- If you don't mind, that is.
- Right.
- What do you say?
- Shall we?
- Thank you.
- Let's go, then.
- We need one more.
- It won't take long.
Who else would like to chat with us?
Is that so?
Could you spare us some time?
What do you say?
She has the time.
- Really?
- She has the time.
Please join us, then.
Guys, come with us.
- Shall we?
- Let's head upstairs.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
- Do you like being on TV?
- Yes, what is this for?
She must be representing her group.
Will they go up against
the Empty Heads?
They must be going up against
the Empty Heads.
The Empty Heads? That's me.
You can sit over here.
First of all, could you
briefly introduce yourselves?
I retired after being
in public service...
and am now working
as an apartment complex manager.
- He's a manager.
- Welcome.
- After being in public service...
- I retired.
When did you retire?
At the end of last year.
- Congratulations.
- How commendable.
- That was hard work.
- Good job, sir.
Could you also tell us who you are?
I am a mother of two.
A son and a daughter.
What?
- A son and a daughter?
- I thought she was in high school.
- Me too.
- Exactly.
I was wondering
why she wasn't in school.
How old are your children?
They're on the older side.
5th grade and 3rd grade.
- No way.
- Seriously?
- I would've never guessed it.
- I look young for my age.
Your children must
watch Running Man.
Yes, they love the show.
I wasn't keen on coming up here,
but I did it for my son.
- That's why you joined us.
- He would love it.
Sir, may I ask you your name?
- I'm from Gyeonggi Province.
- Right.
The name is Jung Min Woo.
And I own a book store.
- My gosh.
- A book store?
A book store?
You must read a lot of books.
No, I just like books in general.
Right, books.
All three have this energy in them.
- I sense that too.
- It's different.
They'll be tough competition.
- I'll explain the game.
- Sure.
You'll be competing
with the citizens today...
in the 3-on-3 Running Man Quiz.
- Against those three.
- But this...
Considering their age,
they'll be knowledgeable.
The three citizens...
and three from the Running Man team
will write down their answers.
The team with
the most correct answers...
- will win the round.
- Okay.
If Running Man wins
more than five rounds,
you will all obtain fall clothes.
- Let's do it.
- It'll be nearly impossible though.
- You'll get off work right away.
- Right away?
In other cases,
you will obtain clothes...
depending on how well you did.
- It's not a bad deal.
- Got it.
First,
Jae Suk, Suk Jin,
and So Min are up.
Must we all answer correctly?
- No, more than...
- You just have to do better.
- Better than them.
- Got it.
Consider So Min as a loss
and get it right yourselves.
So Min's not so bad.
Of course. She's gotten better.
What is Mount Inwang again?
She sometimes surprises us
by knowing things we don't.
Exactly.
Also, you sometimes forget the answer.
Even if you know the answer,
your mind could draw a blank.
Hold on. I can see
their sketchbooks from here.
- Like this.
- You shouldn't be able to.
- There you go.
- How can you know if it's right?
- Right.
- Of course.
They might look at ours and cheat,
- so we'll hold ours up.
- Exactly.
- We can't take any chances.
- Good going.
- Here we go.
- Sure.
What is the full name
of the novelist...
who wrote "The Old Man and the Sea"
and won the Nobel Prize?
- His full name?
(Mr. Lee writes it down
the second he hears the question.)
I'm clueless.
(Mr. Lee writes it down
the second he hears the question.)
- His full name?
(As always,
So Min isn't considered a contender.)
He wrote something down.
You should know that
he didn't even hesitate.
- That's true.
- As soon as he heard it...
I think that's it.
It's hard to know the full name.
Yes, it is on the trickier side.
I'm not sure if mine is right.
I can't be sure.
- Is there more to his name?
- Don't look.
- Is this right?
- He didn't hesitate.
(Seok Sam writes something down
with gloved hands.)
- Isn't it this?
- I think it is.
- So Min.
- I think he's right.
- Is this it?
- I think so.
- I'm not sure of mine.
- Hold it up on three.
- I think it's right.
- Really?
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Is this right?
- What...
- Ernest.
- Right, Ernest.
- I wrote "August."
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Is this right?
(He withdrew himself from the game.)
- "Ernest."
- I thought it was "August."
- Wait. Who is it?
- Ernest Hemingway.
It's Ernest Hemingway.
Both got it right.
It's 1 to 1,
so this round is invalid.
- It's a tie.
- It's invalid, right?
It's a tie.
- I thought it was August.
- Do you not read many books?
- He's running a bookstore.
He's running a bookstore.
Sir.
- Ernest Hemingway.
- You're highly knowledge.
Don't you have to say
"highly knowledgeable?"
- Highly knowledgeable.
What do you mean
he's "highly knowledge?"
I just got one word wrong.
- I thought it was August.
- By the way...
your children might watch
Running Man.
I'm in trouble.
You don't have to be embarrassed
about not knowing this.
It was cute though.
It's a good thing
that she's wearing a mask.
Why do you say that?
It was on purpose.
Jiroro, why do you say that?
(Before the battle began)
Thank you for doing this with us.
You can take off your mask now.
Can't I keep it on?
- You can wear it.
- I'll wear it then.
- If that's comfortable.
- Do what's comfortable for you.
(She foresaw it
and decided to keep it on.)
Jiroro, why do you say that?
No, I mean... there's nothing
embarrassing about getting it wrong.
- Don't worry.
- I got it wrong too.
I'll give you the next question.
It's the world's oldest extant book
printed with movable metal type.
What's Korea's first metalloid type
added...
to UNESCO's Memory of the World?
- The metalloid type?
- Type?
- It's the metalloid type.
- Hold on.
The first metalloid type.
(The manager immediately writes
this time again.)
- It's no joke.
- He's incredible.
- Oh, no. It might not be right.
- He was a public official.
- Wait. I...
- Gosh.
(Meanwhile, the challengers
are contemplating again.)
Is this not metal?
He was a public official.
Wait. I know this.
- Excuse me.
- I...
He might've worked hard.
Did Jae Suk write the answer?
I'm not sure if it's correct.
Are you not going to tell us
how many letters it is?
"Metal type" is hard.
- Metal printed?
- "Metal type" is hard.
- This is amazing.
- I've never heard of it.
- Yes. This one.
- Reveal your answer.
- Yes. Reveal it now.
- In 1, 2, 3.
I don't know. It's Jikji.
It's Jikji. That's right.
(The answer is Jikji.)
(Seok Sam got it right as well.)
- He...
- Tripitaka Koreana.
- I wrote Tripitaka Koreana.
- It's fine.
- It's Jikji.
- I don't know.
- I couldn't write my answer.
- He...
- I should've not done this.
- It's okay.
The answer is Jikji.
- I'm right.
- Right.
- Old Man.
- Yes.
- As expected.
- Suk Jin got it right though.
I got it right.
You majored in Business
at Ajou University.
- I know this much.
- You studied Economy.
You got everything right.
- Sir.
- I only know this much.
(The manager's answers
were 100 percent correct.)
You're amazing.
- Let's switch the members.
- It's Jikji.
Jong Kook, Haha, and Jae Suk
will do it.
- What?
- Is it over?
Old Man.
- Old Man?
- Old Man is good as expected.
By the way, I think
you're not even trying now.
I'm sorry, but you two...
I'm so sorry to make you do this.
- But it's fine.
- It's okay. It's a good memory.
If only you didn't tell
your profession...
- He's running a bookstore.
But even the owner of a bookstore
won't know everything.
- Right.
- True.
He would know everything
about books though.
Of course. Let's go.
A class system in India that divides
people into four main categories...
based on their profession.
What is this?
Don't let them see it.
(The class system in India that
divides people into 4 categories?)
(However)
- He's stuck.
- Good.
- Finally.
- It's his first time contemplating.
- I wrote it.
- We can win.
- Did you write it?
- I wrote it right away.
Please reveal your answer.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3.
It has five letters?
- Isn't it caste?
- The caste system.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- It has five letters?
- Oh, right.
- Isn't it caste?
(Everyone in Team Citizens gave up.)
- I couldn't write an answer.
- Okay.
- We all got it right.
We all got it right.
- Haha, you too.
- Did you see that, So Min?
- You're cool.
- Yes.
- I should not...
- It's a good memory.
- I should've not come here.
- Don't worry.
It's fine.
Honestly, you've sighed
watching us Empty Heads...
on TV, right?
I did sigh.
- Right?
- "How..."
- You were frustrated, right?
- "How can they not know it?"
- The questions are hard today.
- It's difficult today.
(They were so bright before.)
(A special measure
for those who lost energy)
- Did you see that?
- Let's switch for the last time.
Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and So Min.
- Me?
- Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and So Min.
- We're in trouble.
- Me again?
Go.
- You guys...
- Give us easy questions,
but say that they're difficult.
Okay?
(A chance like this won't come again
for Team Citizens.)
- I should write something at least.
- You should write one at least.
I don't think
I would write anything.
It's okay.
- I'll give you a question.
- It's difficult.
It's a research institute set up by
Sejong the Great...
- I know this much.
- of the Joseon Dynasty...
- to create Hangul. What is this?
- It's easy.
- You guys should be quiet.
- Be quiet.
- They can see it.
- I can't see it.
- Put it up and write.
- Hold it up.
- I'll block it like this.
- Yes. Hold it up.
- There you go.
This is a little...
Is this right?
I wrote something at least.
Hold it up.
- Do you not know it?
- I don't know.
This is a little...
(It seems they wrote something
as well.)
Okay. This is a little...
- Isn't it the answer?
- Hold it up on the count of three.
- Is this correct?
- In 1, 2, 3.
- This is not correct, is it?
- Let me see.
- It's not Sungkyunkwan.
- Oh, my.
- Is this correct?
- In 1, 2, 3.
(Sungkyunkwan)
(Many of them wrote Sungkyunkwan.)
It's Jiphyeonjeon.
- What's "Cheonmunkwan?"
- "Cheonmunkwan?"
- Isn't it Sungkyunkwan?
- "Cheonmun..."
Team Citizens won.
What's "Cheonmunkwan?"
- The answer is Jiphyeonjeon.
- Jiphyeonjeon.
Sungkyunkwan.
It's Jiphyeonjeon.
What's Sungkyunkwan then?
- It's where they teach students.
- It's an educational institute.
It's a university.
You know Sungkyunkwan University.
(Laughing)
Thank you for writing
the same answer as me.
I feel good.
- It's a relief.
- I thought someone would write it.
Wait. Doesn't it seem
like they saw each other's answer?
I didn't see it.
I covered it while writing it.
- Just in case,
- Yes.
can you ask what they do again?
- Should we film it again?
- Let's film it again.
- Because...
- It's for him.
For both of them,
even if they learned it at school,
They might not remember it.
You can't remember it well.
Do you want me to give you a mask?
It's not too late.
It's okay. All right.
I'll give you another question.
What's the name of Korea's first country
founded by Dangun Wanggeom?
- You would know this.
- The level of the question is...
- It's Korea's first country.
- Yes.
- This is so...
- You can do it.
I know this.
You should know this.
I can only think of Hongik Ingan.
Isn't it three letters?
- Then I think this is right.
- You can't say it.
(Se Chan knows the answer as well?)
(Surprised)
The first country.
It's that one.
I can't remember it.
- I wrote something. Just write.
- I can't remember it.
Reveal it on the count of three.
In 1, 2, 3.
(The answer is Gojoseon.)
- Goguryeo.
- I wrote Goguryeo too.
- It's Gojoseon.
- "Goguryoe."
- "Hongik Ingan."
"Hongik Ingan."
It means "to broadly benefit
the human world."
- That's what Dangun said.
- She said it was a country.
"Gojoseon."
It's Gojoseon.
They all got it right.
(Everyone in Team Citizens
got it right.)
- I got one right.
- Congratulations.
- I got it right.
Oh, my, the owner of the bookstore.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
- I'm happy for them.
- Congratulations.
- It's not an easy question.
What's your name?
Kim Kyung Hee.
Kyung Hee's children
watch Running Man.
She can tell them to study only when
she got the question right.
If they say, "You got them all wrong,"
she has no words to say.
- She got Gojoseon right.
- I'm happy for you, Kyung Hee.
This is the last question.
You can pick the members
you want this time.
- Us three.
- The best trio.
- Let's go.
- We should let the best ones go.
I...
- If we get one question right...
- We're good.
- We can get clothes.
- Two pieces of clothing.
We got this.
This is the last question.
What's the color of the ring
on the archery target for ten?
- This is so easy.
- They would know it.
(What's the color of the ring
on the archery target for 10?)
(The manager writes 1st
as expected.)
- Is it this one?
- It's so easy.
- It's that one.
- It's that one, right?
The commentators...
I know.
(As they try to think,
they can't remember it clearly.)
I think it's this one.
I'm confused as I have to write it.
- I think it's this one.
- So we should write the color?
- Not the name.
- The color?
No. Wait. "Not the name?"
- No. It's the color.
- The color.
- The commentators say the name.
- No.
- It's not that one?
- You should write the color.
- Oh, yes?
- "Ten."
(What's the color of the ring
on the archery target for "ten?")
- Let's go.
- He always acts like he knows.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They reveal their answer
for the last question.)
- Yellow?
- Red.
- Is it black?
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Yellow?
- Red.
(Yellow, red, black)
(What's the color of the ring
on the archery target for 10?)
- It's yellow.
- It's red.
- Is it black?
- The correct answer is yellow.
(The answer is yellow.)
(For Team Citizens,
only the ace got it right.)
- It's yellow.
- Team Running Man...
- won.
- We won.
As such, you earned two outfits.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
Thank you.
For those who participated,
we'll give bookstore gift certificates.
That's nice!
- My goodness.
- As expected.
A bookstore gift certificate
to a bookstore owner.
- Here you go, Kyung Hee.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- See you, Kyung Hee.
- See you.
- Thank you.
Two autumn outfits are given.
- Who is going to wear it?
- The member who will wear it...
will be decided by you guys.
How can we decide it?
- We should do rock-paper-scissors.
- We should.
- It can't be helped.
- But they must be cold.
- What about us?
- They must be trembling.
Then you should be exempted.
Let's play among ourselves.
- Ji Hyo should win one.
- No.
- So Min is cold too.
- I'm fine.
Since that's what Jae Suk wants,
let's follow him.
No! I want to play
rock-paper-scissors.
- No.
- I don't want to play it...
now that
you're telling us what to do.
- We should play first...
- We should win.
- and give it to them when we win.
- No, let's not give them.
- Okay.
- We can give one to Ji Hyo,
- not So Min.
- Don't give it to me.
- Also, this is scissors.
- No.
No, that's paper.
- This is paper.
- Why would you play?
Why not? I can play.
- Move, Suk Jin.
- Why are you being like this?
We're all playing.
- I'm okay.
- I'll give you a map...
to the second spot.
- Okay!
- Come to the back, Suk Jin.
- Why?
You should come to the back.
Se Chan, lead the way.
I'm in the passenger seat.
- Okay, you should sit there.
- Of course.
This is the place, guys.
It's Chungmuro. You should drive
toward Myeong-dong.
- Hey.
- Myeong-dong.
I can even keep my eyes closed
to find my way around Chungmuro.
You're at it again.
I got it!
I'll go to Chungmuro Station first.
- Okay.
- Drive toward Myeong-dong.
I used to walk there...
- from Jongno.
- Okay. I got it.
Let's see how well you do.
Suk Jin,
Chungmuro and Myeong-dong...
are my hometown
from my college days.
We're having ribs in soup for lunch.
- What's ribs in soup?
- What is it?
It's soupy ribs.
Like bulgogi.
- GPS Ssaeb.
- To go to Myeong-dong,
- We're going to Myeong-dong?
- we should go this way.
Suk Jin, be careful with what you say.
You might be kicked out.
- What do you mean?
- Also...
When it comes to directions,
everyone except Jong Kook,
Se Chan, and I should shut it.
- Is Se Chan that good?
- Who are you to say that?
- Shut it!
- What's with Se Chan?
They don't know the way.
He won't listen to you anyway,
GPS Ssaeb.
Mister.
- Mister.
- Who are you calling? Me?
Yes. If you keep behaving like that,
I'll drop you
at Gyeongbokgung Station.
How can you say that?
- Also...
- He said he could get off.
I've been living in Seoul
for 50 years.
- What about me, then?
- Then we should trust him.
You came to Seoul
from your hometown.
I was here since I was three.
- Did you walk up to Seoul?
- I was three then.
If you didn't,
then you should keep quiet.
- I wonder how he climbed up.
- I walked around...
every part of Seoul.
How could you have climbed up
when you were just three?
- On a sightseeing bus.
- Stay still.
Did you buy the tickets yourself?
Gosh, you're adding on to this?
You always scold me.
People in this industry
do that sometimes.
Why do you always scold me?
Gosh, the hand warmer is so hot.
This is infuriating!
- Why won't this window open?
- It's cold. Don't open it.
- It's cold.
- It's not cold.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
Let's open the windows.
It's up to me.
From there,
take a U-turn.
Then turn right.
You're heading
toward City Hall, right?
We should go toward City Hall
from here.
Right, we should turn right
Guys, we're heading to City Hall.
- Se Chan.
- Yes.
Let me put it this way.
Now that Se Chan is sitting next to me,
I realized that only one Sherpa
was needed to climb the Himalayas.
This is how it should be done.
- You see? I'm still holding it.
- The Sherpa.
- This is what the Sherpa does.
- I can see his future.
- His attitude is different.
I can see him getting off the car.
- But the thing is...
- Be careful with what you say.
I can see him getting off
while spitting.
Try stopping him.
Jae Suk's comparison is nice.
The Sherpa.
- Hey.
- The Sherpa.
Do you like living like a rat?
- Yes, it is.
- You're sucking up to him.
How can you call him that?
Don't call him a rat
when he's working hard.
- We can't go this way.
- Okay.
- You should've gone to the right.
- No, we can U-turn.
(The way they should've taken)
- I should've gone to the right.
I know. But you can't do that here.
How far will you go to U-turn?
- The lane won't allow us.
We can't break the law.
Se Chan, why didn't you tell him
in advance?
Pull yourself together.
Why didn't you tell him in advance?
We have to make a detour.
No, we're going in the right way.
Leave the directions to him.
Let's talk
about something productive.
Also, you should enjoy this.
We should be able...
- to talk about various topics.
- It couldn't be helped.
We should've taken the other road.
Let's talk about various topics.
- What? You should pull over.
- What?
(The police are controlling
the traffic.)
What happened?
I didn't do anything wrong.
No, it's all right.
(Bursting into laughter)
Why were you intimidated?
- Hey! The police officer...
- Why...
told me to pull over.
- Were you scared?
- I didn't do anything wrong.
"What happened?"
(Getting cold feet)
You got intimidated.
- Gosh, it's so hot.
- You got intimidated.
Gosh, this is no joke. Hey.
What do I do?
You're banned from saying
you're hot.
Next time,
I should wear a fall outfit.
- Why? Because you're hot?
- The hand warmer...
- It's up to you.
- I bet you're hot.
The hand warmer is crazy hot.
And I'm wearing a hat too.
You're the eldest here.
You should be charismatic.
- Charisma?
- You should be charismatic.
- Nothing I say would work.
- Charisma.
Those are rascals.
- Should we exit here?
- Let's do that.
- Let's exit.
- You can change the lane now.
We'll exit now
and take the underpass.
Sounds good.
- I'm upset too.
- Hey.
- We should exit now.
- Here?
- Why didn't you exit?
- It was a solid line.
- What are you guys doing?
- Keep quiet.
- We had to take this lane anyway.
- What are you guys doing?
- Where are you going?
Hey, how far are you going
to U-turn?
Wait a minute.
Jae Suk doesn't listen at all.
He just goes straight.
It was a solid line.
What? Why are you going this way?
We're going this way
toward Seodaemun Gate.
That's right, we are.
Do you know where we are going?
Tell us.
Let me be honest.
We are taking a detour.
We should've exited earlier.
- But we can come back to Sinchon.
- That's right.
I mean, are we going to be
on the road the whole day?
- As long as we get there.
- But we are doing this...
to learn how inconvenient it was
before we had GPS.
But we could've gone the right way.
We're going around too much.
Gosh, why did they make him...
- decide the rules?
- Is this car yours?
- She's right. Is the car yours?
If you have complaints,
then get off.
Why would I get off?
- Why would I?
- Why should we? You get off.
Is this your car?
The thing is,
it's only right to let
the driver decide everything.
- That's right. I have control.
- We should trust him.
Then let's change the driver.
Then you should drive.
Do you have Class One license?
- He must not have one.
- You need that to drive this?
We need Class One license?
- Yes, we do.
- Mine is Class One.
He must not have Class One license.
You can drive up to nine people.
- He came on strong.
- He was like... I know.
He doesn't even have
Class One license.
His must be Class Two.
Check his license...
- if it's Class 1 or Class 2.
- That little guy.
- Even his car is small.
- He can only ride a small one.
- It's Class 2.
- It's Class 2?
It's Class Two, small.
Yours is Class Two, small?
- It's not even regular?
- You can't even drive a stick?
I have a license for motorcycles.
What use is that?
- For motorized vehicles?
- You don't even ride motorbikes.
I can't because I'm scared.
- Exactly.
- I'm afraid I'd die.
- That's not it.
- Listen. Two, four...
Hey. Wait a minute.
What is it?
Is this our staff's car?
Can we follow it?
Jae Suk, no.
Don't follow the car in front of you.
- What is that?
- Go straight and U-turn there.
- Right. I should U-turn there.
- Then you'll go this way.
- But we have to take a long way.
- What is this?
What are you doing?
We're going the opposite way.
- There's no place for us to U-turn.
- How frustrating.
- We are...
- Should we break the law then?
We can't break the law, can we?
GPS Ssaeb, what's the point
of being in the passenger seat?
Gosh, this is where we did
our opening.
- How nice.
- This reminds me of the opening.
Guys, can't you just enjoy
the weather?
- That's right!
- Why are you so strict?
Be more relaxed, will you?
Gosh, it's so hot.
GPS Ssaeb, what are you doing?
Gosh, it's hot.
(Bursting into laughter)
Suk Jin, have some iced coffee.
- They won't allow me to.
- He can't have it.
Gosh, this is crazy. I'm boiled up.
I touched his gloves earlier,
and they were wet with his sweat.
It's hot in the afternoon.
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
It's so hot.
- What is it?
- Suk Jin says he's hot.
Whatever! I'll take it off.
- Suk Jin.
- Whatever!
Report it to Hyung In.
Hyung In, he took off his hat.
(Suk Jin puts it back on quickly.)
No, did you see it?
You didn't take a photo.
It was all caught on camera.
- It was all caught on camera.
- Seriously. It was all caught,
but he was like, "Did you see it?"
The old idol singers, like H.O.T...
- Gosh, it's hot.
- They went this far?
- Yes, here.
- Why did they come this far?
Gosh, we're going around too much.
You need to focus here.
- From here...
- Be quiet, everyone!
If we go straight, it's Jongno.
If we go to the right,
it's Namdaemun,
which is really close to Chungmuro.
All right. Sounds good.
We're going toward Namdaemun?
We're going straight to Chungmuro
from there.
Okay.
Isn't that where Daehan Cinema is?
- Stay still, mister!
- Seriously!
Don't talk to me.
I'm very edgy right now.
If you go straight
from Namsan First Tunnel...
Stay still.
Why does he show off so much
whenever he has a chance?
It's not that. I just know
the way around there.
I know it so well.
I don't even need a GPS.
Suk Jin, I used to study
around this area.
- You studied around here too?
- Of course.
Gosh, then you should know
the way around here.
Jong Kook is so different
toward Jae Suk.
Why would Jong Kook react like that
when he said he just studied here?
It's a fun story, that's why!
- Hey.
- Of course!
Jong Kook, you sound so different
when you talk to Jae Suk.
- What's with you guys?
- Go ahead, Jae Suk.
Let me tell you the story.
You are all in a group chat
without me, right?
That's true.
Jae Suk is sharing his story.
I'm sharing a story here,
which is rare.
All right. Go ahead.
It may be gone now,
but there used to be
an academy around here.
It was around Donam-dong
near Suyu-ri.
That's where my high school
and my house were.
There was an academy near my place,
- but I chose...
- Chose?
to go to an academy here
which took me an hour and a half.
- Why?
- What's the reason?
- Because...
- Because they're good?
That's one thing, but there were...
many pretty girls in this academy.
The news spread.
- Then you should come here.
- There were many cool girls here.
Then you should come here.
- So my friend brought me here.
- He did a good job.
You went home alone anyway.
What was the point of coming here?
You were invisible
to the girls anyway.
Still, it must have helped
to come and study...
- with a sense of excitement.
- That's right.
- Isn't that right?
- It felt different.
- It gave you a sense of purpose.
- It gave you strength.
Of course.
(They are sick and tired
of the duo.)
- So I...
- This is driving me crazy.
I am not used to such reactions.
We are passing the City Hall.
We are nearly there.
- We are nearly there.
- Yes.
The City Hall building is so pretty.
What's the point?
We are going to circle the place.
- No, we are nearly there.
- We are going to circle the place.
There are many one-way streets here.
Just take a nap.
We will arrive in an hour.
- No, we are on our way there.
- We are going.
- Don't talk about the streets!
- Hey.
- You jerk.
- How dare you glare at your elder?
How dare you act out when you have
the class two driver's license?
What? Class two driver's license?
- Haha.
- That jerk.
- That jerk?
- Hey.
Don't you have the microphone?
- He called me a jerk.
- What was that?
- Haha was voicing his opinion.
- I should have gone that way.
- Make a circle.
- Se Chan, what's wrong?
He took a wrong turn again.
- Did you take a wrong turn again?
- He took a wrong turn again.
We will circle the rotary
about three times.
There is nothing wrong with circling
the rotary three times.
- He is so annoying.
- Jong Kook.
- What's up with you?
- Seriously.
Do you have a problem
with circling the rotary?
Do you have a problem?
I am just asking.
- Don't you need to exercise today?
- He took off his hat.
- Why did you take it off?
This is driving me crazy.
(They catch him in the act.)
(Glancing over)
Good shot.
- Okay.
- Euljiro Two-ga.
Nice.
- Good.
- Let's go.
- I think we should go this way.
- Yes. Let's focus.
Quiet down. We need to focus.
Why are you being so loud?
- I didn't say a word.
- I didn't say a single word.
- Turn left.
- Chungmu-ro. We are nearly there.
- All right.
- We are nearly there.
- Okay.
- This is it.
If we turn left,
we will reach Chungmu-ro.
Check the location
of our destination.
- We will get lost.
- We need to make a U-turn.
If we enter through here...
This is our current location.
- Hold on. It's near the station.
- Yes.
The two of you look cool.
They are about to fight.
- It's near here.
- Yes.
This is bad.
I will stay still.
It already looks like
we are in trouble.
We entered an alley. This is bad.
- I think they took a wrong turn.
- We entered an alley.
- The two of you were confident.
- Se Chan,
- stay calm.
- This is good.
Let's stay calm.
Shall we make a big turn instead?
- A big turn?
- Yes. This real estate agency...
- I think it's near here.
- There is a hotel nearby.
- I see a hotel.
There are many hotels here.
It might not be this hotel.
There are countless hotels in Seoul.
- Se Chan.
- This is so hard.
- Turn right.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
No, we need to go one more block.
This isn't the place.
This is the big road.
This restaurant is inside an alley.
It's so hard to find the place
from this map.
- My goodness.
- It's a one-way street,
so you need to go left.
This is the Printing Alley.
- This is the Printing Alley.
- Really?
- A print shop. We are nearly there.
- This is...
- This is the Printing Alley.
- Shall we enter the alley?
Let's enter the alley.
This is the place.
- This is Chungmuro Station.
- We are nearly there.
Here is the important thing.
- It's near here.
- Yes. It's near here.
- Just...
- Ask a local, you punk.
The right side.
We need to find
this ribs in soup restaurant.
- This ribs in soup restaurant...
- Sir, do you know...
a ribs in soup restaurant
around here?
- A ribs in soup restaurant.
- This place...
- He knows it.
- The one with many customers?
The one with many customers? Yes.
This is a one-way street,
so go straight...
- and turn right.
- Turn right. Okay.
- Thank you.
- We found it.
- Why didn't you ask sooner?
- Did you see our teamwork?
- Okay. We are a fantastic duo.
Had you asked sooner,
we would have started eating by now.
Hold on.
Isn't that it? A print shop.
- Here.
- Make a turn.
- Let's enter the alley.
- A ribs in soup restaurant.
- Where is it?
That... What's that?
This is the place.
Let's ask them. This is the place.
I see the staff members.
- This is the place.
- Keep going down the alley.
- I Rye, where is the restaurant?
- The ribs in soup restaurant.
- It's behind you.
- It's behind us. Thank you.
(They get a decisive hint
from Se Chan's manager.)
- We had good teamwork.
- That's right.
You can only turn right.
There are restaurants here.
- Jae Suk, there is the restaurant.
- Where?
- Keep going.
- Do you see it?
- There it is.
- We are here.
- See?
- It's the ribs in soup restaurant.
- We found it.
Really?
This is teamwork.
Seriously.
I am impressed that you found it.
- I am impressed that you found it.
- How did you find it?
- Get out of the van.
- We arrived at the restaurant.
- We almost missed it.
- We finally got here.
- We almost missed it. This is it.
- Okay.
- I saw it.
- This restaurant is hard to find.
- Jae Suk.
- Se Chan.
I saw it.
Suk Jin, you should have seen
the sign.
- Gosh.
- You found it.
- You found it well.
- I saw the sign.
You found it well.
- Hey.
- What?
You look like a thug.
You did a good job
finding the place.
- It looks delicious.
- Hello.
I saw the sign.
- We are the best. Nice teamwork.
- We had nice teamwork.
On your way here,
many members reported...
- how Suk Jin took off his hat.
- What?
Five penalty balls will be added.
Okay.
- It's not like that.
- You took it off five times.
- He took it off many times.
- Five times?
(This is how he got
multiple penalty balls.)
(The 1st time he took off his hat)
(Citizens made reports right away.)
(They continued to make reports.)
(We will deduct one penalty ball.)
(Thank you!
He took it off the second time.)
(- He took it off again.
- You will receive a benefit.)
(He did it again.
He keeps doing it.)
Think about it.
You could take off your hat...
- and put it back on like this.
- No.
Sit down.
You were supposed to sweat.
(He is so annoying!)
He is so annoying.
You will enjoy your meal...
- here.
- Let's eat.
After the meal,
you will have a short mission.
- Then you will hit the road.
- Okay.
It's sliced garlic.
Ribs in soup.
It contains noodles.
We can eat it when it boils, right?
I will take some out here.
I will eat this much.
There are spoons.
All right.
- Thank you.
- Eat up, Jong Kook.
- You gave me meat.
- Here, Jong Kook.
- You gave me protein.
- Why did you give him meat?
- What?
- There is no meat.
Why are you so jealous?
- For goodness' sake.
- Why are you so petty?
- What's wrong with you?
- You are 44 years old.
- I am the jealous type.
- Why are you...
- They called me jealous.
How old are you?
(The jealous man gets tormented
all day long.)
It's like a love triangle.
It's a unique dish.
You should eat it like this.
- Jong Kook.
- It's a wrap.
- My goodness.
- Try it.
- Did he make Jae Suk a wrap?
- My goodness.
- How is it? Isn't it good?
- That was cringe-worthy.
- Listen.
- I hate it.
- That was cringe-worthy.
I was going to eat it myself.
Then I thought,
"Why don't I give this to Jae Suk?"
That was cringe-worthy.
- Jae Suk gave me meat.
- That's right.
So I wanted to do something for him.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
You should drive next time
with So Min as the GPS.
- Okay.
- Suit yourself.
- GPS So.
- Yes.
I will make sure...
no one says a word in the back.
We should all take a nap.
- Why don't we take a nap?
- Yes.
(They really won't say a word.)
- We should all take a nap.
- That would be funny.
That would be nice.
We should all snore.
A sweet nap.
Is it good?
(The Korean dessert,
fried rice is ready.)
- Give me your plate.
- We will give you some rice.
Okay.
- Jae Suk, this is yours.
- Thank you.
It would be tastier if it's crunchy.
We should push it down.
- Hey, don't say such nonsense...
- Thank you.
while eating.
Seriously.
Why would you complain...
- when they made it with care?
- What did he say?
Did I do something wrong?
Haha, what did you say?
I said it would be tastier
if it's crunchy.
Then he said,
"Don't say such nonsense."
That's...
Think about it.
There are people
who always complain...
- when they eat.
- That's right.
- I hate such people.
- "It's salty. It should be bland."
- Gosh.
- Don't be like that.
- Eat without complaint.
- That's right.
Gosh.
I will tell you
how close of a relationship...
Jong Kook and I have.
- Do you know why?
- Listen up.
What? I am going to eat this.
Let us eat.
- All right.
- You keep giving a speech.
- "Listen up."
- All right.
Everyone.
Listen up. Pay attention.
- You must be curious about...
- This is so annoying.
how Jong Kook and I manage
to stay so close.
- No.
- I am not curious.
- We are curious.
(We are curious.)
- Everyone.
- What's this? A talk show troupe?
- Yes. We are a talk show troupe.
- We are a troupe.
- A talk show troupe.
- Yes. Two, three.
Hey.
They have nice teamwork.
- I am annoyed.
- A talk show troupe.
You are good.
So the two of you are
a talk show troupe.
- We are a talk show troupe.
- That's right.
- We go anywhere to tell stories.
- We go anywhere.
- We travel around the nation.
Let's scrape thus rice.
- "Let's scrape thus rice."
- You mean "This."
(He makes a mistake
whenever he opens his mouth.)
- That came out wrong.
- Suk Jin is old.
- Seriously.
- The master of talk.
"Let's scrape thus rice."
I had shrimp in my mouth.
Suk Jin became flustered.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
Did you enjoy the meal?
- Yes.
- It was very tasty.
- Citizens will join you...
- It was so tasty.
for this mission as well.
The mission is a success...
if a citizen says
all members' names in five seconds.
- I see.
- Really?
It will be hard.
You get three tries.
(They go in search of a citizen
who will bring back fall.)
- Four, three, two,
- Song Ji Hyo, Yoo Jae Suk, Haha,
- one. Time's up.
- Ji Suk Jin, Kim Jong Kook...
Gosh.
(Gosh.)
- So Min.
- She was so disappointed...
that she went, Gosh."
Five, four,
- three,
- Ji Suk Jin, Kim Jong Kook,
- two,
- Yoo Jae Suk,
- one. Time's up.
- Jeon So Min, Haha...
(She failed because she hesitated
at first.)
Ha Dong Hoon, Yang Se Hyeong,
- Yang Se Hyeong?
- Kim Jong Kook.
(Yang Se Hyeong?)
- Yang Se Hyeong?
- All three attempts failed,
so no one will get fall clothes.
- I am so upset.
- Let's move to the next location.
- Let's go.
- We need to keep going.
- She called me Yang Se Hyeong.
GPS So.
- Give me the map.
- GPS So.
Let's see. Where are we going?
- I will check the map.
- Okay.
All right.
We are starting
from Chungmuro Station.
Our destination is L Tower.
You know how to get there.
- Are we going to L Tower?
- Yes, take a look.
L Tower.
Gosh, it's easy.
You can just follow what you see.
It's easy.
L Tower.
- You don't even need to look.
- Everyone.
We are going to L Tower.
I will give you a comfy ride.
L Tower is an easy destination.
It's easy.
We won't need to complain.
- I will give you a comfy ride.
- Okay.
Please give me a round of applause.
(Uninterested)
No one is clapping.
It's okay.
- Suk Jin, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Let's take a sweet nap.
- Suk Jin's era is here.
Be careful.
(They are off to a shaky start.)
- It was nothing.
- You can do it.
Please be gentle
with the brake pedal.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
- Suk Jin.
- For goodness' sake.
I am getting motion sickness.
- Suk Jin, we need to sleep.
- All right. What?
Hey, you are having a shoot.
You can't sleep.
We already talked in the car.
There is nothing else to talk about.
I am going to sleep.
- "I am going to sleep."
- If you do that...
People are yawning already.
- I know. I am so tired.
- Listen.
If you don't talk,
the entire ride will get edited out.
The distance is quite long.
You should go this way.
It won't take that long.
- Already...
- Where are you going?
- Suk Jin.
- It's this way.
Suk Jin, Jae Suk is sleeping.
Please quiet down.
- What?
- Sleep tight.
- He is sleeping.
- Sleep tight, everyone.
- Okay.
- All right.
Is everyone falling asleep?
Yes. Everyone is tired.
- Is everyone falling asleep?
- Why are you sleeping?
- Hey.
- Yes?
GPS So, take a nap.
- Take a nap?
- Take a nap. It's okay.
- Really?
- Everyone is sleeping anyway.
- This will get edited out anyway.
- It will cut to us getting out.
- Don't be sullen and talk that way.
Seriously.
Why are you so petty?
- I am not petty.
- We were making a funny situation.
- Don't say it will get edited out.
- It won't get edited out.
It will be funny if we fall asleep.
- Don't say it will get edited out.
- Don't be like that.
I had to react.
Did you expect me to keep quiet?
- For goodness' sake.
- I...
Suk Jin, you need to make a U-turn
and go to Dongho Bridge.
(Suk Jin misses the timing
and goes straight.)
Dongho Bridge. That's right.
Give me a break.
- I will take Namsan First Tunnel.
- Dongho Bridge. That's right.
- Where are you going?
- I will take Namsan First Tunnel.
- Suk Jin.
- What?
Make a U-turn
and go to Dongho Bridge.
- You have a point, but...
- You will make a detour.
There will be heavy traffic.
You should make a U-turn
and go to Dongho Bridge.
Suk Jin, we are supposed
to be done by 3 p.m.
- What time is it now?
- It's 2:30 p.m.
- Already?
- It's game over.
You gave me the wheel too late.
We wasted time.
I should have gone.
- We should have done that.
- Hey.
I should have made up my mind.
"I should have gone?"
You are the one who got lost.
- Dongho Bridge has less traffic.
- No. Dongho Bridge...
You should have taken
the Dongho Bridge.
Had I had GPS,
I would have taken that route.
- Suk Jin, take the right lane.
- You shouldn't say that.
- What did you tell me earlier?
- What?
His tone is sullen.
- Suk Jin's tone is sullen.
- He is sullen, right?
- I can tell from his tone.
I am not... Not sullen.
"I am not... Not sullen."
There is a traffic jam.
What should we do?
- It gets bad here.
- A traffic jam gets bad here.
- It would be better to run.
- It will be like this...
until the Banpo Bridge.
Would Dongho Bridge be
any different?
- It would be much better.
- There would be a traffic jam too.
- We took a detour too.
Dongho Bridge would be much better.
Suk Jin, what's
the estimated time of arrival?
Fifteen minutes later.
- What?
- Don't lie. That's impossible.
- To L Tower?
- Yes.
It's game over.
All of us will get the penalty
if we don't arrive by 3 p.m., right?
I think it will take 30 minutes.
No. It will take 20 minutes at most.
- No way.
- It will take longer than that.
I can't see.
- He is cold.
- Suk Jin.
If you were going to be like that,
why did you make her sit
next to you?
Why did you sit her there?
So Min, I am sorry.
I was looking at the side mirror.
- Your paper blocked my view.
- That's right.
- That was why I did that.
That was so funny.
- What?
- My goodness.
- Suk Jin.
- Mister.
Wake up.
- I am sorry.
- I was so startled.
- Mister.
Don't suddenly step on the brakes.
Ji Hyo is sick.
I didn't step on the brakes.
- You did that.
- We almost threw up.
- I stepped on them gently.
- Ribs in soup almost came out.
- I heaved two times.
Do you want to fill the car
with ribs in soup?
(Suk Jin receives
so many complaints.)
- Suk Jin.
- We won't get there on time.
How many minutes remain?
Ten minutes remain.
- We won't get there on time.
- A traffic jam is inevitable here.
- It's inevitable.
- There are so many cars.
A traffic jam is inevitable here.
- Suk Jin.
- What's wrong with you?
- I am scared.
- You need to keep a safe distance.
You need to keep a safe distance
when you drive.
- So Min.
- What are you, a magnet?
You aren't in a parking lot.
Why do you put our car's mouth
to that car's butt?
Seriously.
That's an expression
my dad always uses.
- So Min.
- Keep a distance.
- I know that, but...
- Keep a distance from the butt.
So Min is a bit annoyed too.
- We can't get there on time.
- We don't have much time.
- What time is it now?
- Suk Jin, don't feel so pressed.
- You need to turn right.
- I plan to do that.
We are here. Lotte World.
Isn't that the L Tower?
We need to go inside.
Where is the destination?
The shooting location.
The meetup place.
I see. Is there such a place?
(There is no confidence
in his voice.)
We will see it when we make a turn.
Right? We will see it
when we make a turn.
Why do you suddenly want
my approval?
- My heart is beating fast.
- Suk Jin's heart is beating fast.
I can hear your heartbeats
from here.
Your heart is pounding.
You didn't wet your pants, did you?
(His heart rate escalates
as the stop sign goes on.)
It's so hot.
Your heart is pounding.
Why is the stop sign so long?
- Suk Jin, it's 3 p.m.
- We won't get there on time.
- Suk Jin, you ruined it.
- What are we going to do?
It's over.
I told you it was impossible.
- You arrived at the last place.
- Yes.
I told you earlier
that everyone must change...
into fall clothes
to succeed in the mission.
- My goodness.
- We failed.
- Only two people changed,
- Okay.
so you must pick penalty balls.
Okay.
But we will allow
the overlapping names.
Okay.
Suk Jin has five penalty balls
in there, right?
- I am bound to get picked.
- I will give you the number.
For goodness' sake.
- I feel bad for Suk Jin.
- Jae Suk has two penalty balls.
- Suk Jin has seven penalty balls.
- What?
- Earlier...
- Seven?
- Jong Kook has two penalty balls.
- Okay.
Haha made reports,
so he has one penalty ball.
Thank you.
- For goodness' sake.
- Ji Hyo has one penalty ball.
- Se Chan has one penalty ball.
- Okay.
So Min has two penalty balls.
Why does So Min have two?
- I made a report.
- Those with one penalty ball...
- made reports.
- Reports.
- Let's go.
- What's the penalty?
- You had the fall race.
- Yes.
The fall sky is well-known
to be high and clear.
Go on.
So the penalty involves...
taking a photo at a place
that is the closest to the fall sky.
(Taking a photo at a place
that is the closest to the fall sky)
On a bridge that is 541m
above the ground,
take a photo with a designated pose.
- Where?
- Not here?
- It's on the top.
- There is the Sky Bridge.
- Not here?
Okay.
(We will reveal the romantic place
for the penalty.)
(They will get a bird's-eye view
of Seoul in fall.)
(They won't forget this fall.)
It's a serious penalty,
but she said it as if it were nothing.
- "That's the penalty."
- She said it as if it were nothing.
Pick the balls.
- Please.
- My one ball wouldn't get picked.
I would get picked, right?
- You would get picked.
- Will you pick five balls?
You will pick five people, right?
- Overlapping names count too.
- Let me take out one penalty ball.
- Come on.
- I hope all five balls...
belong to Suk Jin.
Gosh, this is...
- Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook: 2 penalty balls)
This isn't much of a penalty
for Jong Kook.
I will make a good memory.
- He would enjoy it.
- I can't help but be expectant.
- Se Chan.
(Se Chan got picked
despite the low chance.)
- I had one ball.
- Good.
You still got picked.
You never know.
- You might avoid getting picked.
- That's a possibility.
I am surprised
that Suk Jin didn't get picked yet.
- Suk Jin.
- He got picked.
(Suk Jin got picked without fail.)
- He didn't get lucky.
- Two more penalty balls.
- I don't want overlapping names.
- Mix them up more.
- Two more penalty balls.
- I had one penalty ball.
- Seriously.
I hope I get picked again.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook got picked again.)
- It's strange.
- One more penalty ball.
- One.
- What are the odds?
Is this the last one?
Let me avoid this one.
- Let me avoid this one.
- Please.
Please. I am so scared of heights.
- I hope Jae Suk gets picked.
- I don't mind the penalty,
- but I will go home late.
- Jae Suk.
- Please.
- Did you pick it?
- It's Jae Suk.
(Yoo Jae Suk)
Did you check the name first?
They didn't check the name.
- I avoided that fate.
- This really is...
Yoo Jae Suk's Running Man.
- He never gets left out.
- I...
- Four people.
- What should I do?
I am so scared of heights.
Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Suk Jin,
and Se Chan. Four people.
I only had one penalty ball.
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Suk Jin,
and Se Chan will get the penalty.)
Let's hurry up.
Let's film it and go home.
The other three members can go home.
- Bye.
- Go home.
- I feel so bad.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- I feel so bad.
All right. Let's go.
We can't avoid this fate.
- This is...
- We are doing it since it's safe.
- Is it safe?
- Yes.
It's safe.
We get scared of such things.
We get scared.
Do many people get scared?
Many people get scared.
Of course. Although they get scared,
they enjoy the thrill.
What's the age restriction?
You need to be 12 years old
or older.
Do children do this?
- Do middle schoolers do this?
- Yes.
So far,
Who was the oldest one to try this?
Only those under
the age of 65 can try this.
Suk Jin, you barely made the cut.
If he was a little late,
he wouldn't have gotten to try this.
Only those under
the age of 65 can enjoy it.
- Gosh.
- You narrowly made it.
- I think the zipper is broken.
- Let me do it for you.
- Isn't it broken?
- No.
Why are we wearing this suit?
- He keeps asking questions.
- Because he's scared.
Too many questions.
To avoid getting my clothes stuck?
That means it's dangerous.
- Gosh, I'm so scared.
- Oh, dear.
My heart is pounding already.
The highest place
in the sky of Seoul.
Today, the wind is strong.
It's very windy.
This is so scary.
Gosh, it's too high.
(The view makes them
give an exclamation of surprise.)
Gosh, what is all this?
It's unbelievable.
My gosh.
(He can't help but give
a side glance at the blue sky.)
This is terrifying.
Is this it? Where is it?
I think we're almost there.
No way. It can't be that short.
Is this it?
(The cool wind and magnificent view
make them feel liberated.)
Jong Kook, the floor is
transparent glass in the middle.
- What?
- Look over there.
- I can't look down.
- I think they are acrylic plates.
This is...
There are gaps in the bridge.
(The bridge has gaps in it.)
There are transparent plates
in the middle.
- What?
- The four plates are transparent.
- No.
- Between the plates?
You should be careful.
There are holes.
(He can't believe his eyes.)
You should be careful of the holes.
Gosh, this is...
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk should...
be in the middle,
but we can switch places.
(He plucks up his courage
and takes a step forward.)
- My gosh.
- He must be scared.
(He plucks up his courage
and takes a step forward.)
My gosh.
My goodness. I'll go...
Darn it. My goodness. I'll go...
(He shivers with fear
and turns around.)
This is so scary.
- Jae Suk, come here.
- Do you want to switch places?
- I'll go first.
- You go first, Jong Kook.
- I can't do this.
- Let us switch places.
How many safety devices are there?
Stop asking questions.
I'm so sorry.
He's been asking questions
about the safety devices all day.
- Shall we go? Let's do this.
- I'll go first.
- Wish me good luck.
- This is crazy.
Hey, don't look down.
You should be careful.
Okay. All right.
This is no joke.
Jae Suk, watch out for the holes.
Be careful of the holes.
(He takes a step toward the fall
one by one.)
(This is the only place
where you can feel the fall sky.)
(There's no way he can feel it.)
I just looked down.
I'm so terrified.
Hurry and come here.
Hurry, Suk Jin. I'm so scared.
It's very windy here.
Hurry, Suk Jin.
- You have to hurry.
- Darn it.
(They have to get together
to take a commemorative picture.)
Why are we doing this?
Hurry, Suk Jin. I'm so scared.
(The ones at the head are
struggling because he's late.)
- Sorry.
- Hurry, Suk Jin.
There are holes.
It's so windy here.
Please stop it.
(Shaking)
It's so windy here.
Please stop it. I'm so scared.
(He's begging sincerely.)
The wind... Don't move.
Gosh, it's a hole.
- Hurry.
- My gosh.
- Hurry and come here.
- Okay.
My goodness. Don't come close.
- Please.
- Hurry.
Hurry. Come here.
All right.
- Make it quick.
- Look at the camera.
Hurry and take it.
Make it quick. Hurry.
- One, two, three.
- Hurry.
(They completed the penalty.)
- All right.
- Let's go back.
(The season of the high sky)
- Why did you take this off?
- Go?
Gosh, the wind is so strong.
Darn it.
This is driving me crazy.
Hurry. I have to pee.
- It was so scary.
- I wouldn't have done it alone.
I would be too afraid to do this
if I were alone.
(We'd like to thank the citizens
for helping us find the fall.)
(Running Man Original Film)
(What does the bomb look like?)
(The bomb seemed big.)
(It's here.)
(Ten bombs...)
(with six cords each)
Please.
(There's a designer who planned
the whole thing in this building.)
(Kim Rae Won)
(Two spies among the ten members?)
Who did this?
(There's no progress
in the investigation,)
(but the timer keeps ticking.)
(- I have 5 minutes left.
- I have 9 minutes left.)
(If you want to stop it,)
(you must catch the designer.)
No!
(Operation: Pass the Bomb)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)