The shoot begins now. Hello.
Hello.
We are Running Man!
(So Min is acting frivolously
early in the morning.)
Is it a mission or what?
I didn't sleep very well.
Look at this. Isn't this cute?
- This is like a Running Man badge.
- What's that?
These are badges from some brand.
I got them from someone.
What is she doing?
Is she getting a mission?
- Hello.
- You're a spy today.
- We are Running Man!
Did you get a mission or what?
Man!
It's delicious, isn't it?
This is...
- It's from fans.
- It tastes so good.
- I ate it already.
- We got churros and...
This isn't product placement.
It's from our fans.
- Thank you so much.
- You want to eat with rice, right?
- Thank you.
- This must be good with rice.
- To celebrate our 12th anniversary.
Did you see the menu?
- My gosh.
- The menu is amazing.
- It has our names on it.
- It's our names.
The churro is warm.
It tastes so good.
Why do we begin the shoot so early?
I guess he's going on an outing.
Suk Jin, it's hot today.
- You must be hot.
- No.
- It's out of season.
- It looks cool, doesn't it?
Don't I look cool? Haha,
you do have a good fashion sense.
- I think his stylist...
- What?
- is a nice person.
- What about her?
But I don't understand
why she's doing this.
This is a lot better
than what you're wearing. Look.
- Look at us.
- I hate this.
He says, "This is a lot better
than what you're wearing."
It does look nice,
but why does it have so many studs?
This is fashion.
You must be hot.
- Really?
- It's not right for the weather.
Why not? I'll take it off
after the opening.
You know what he says
when he's flustered.
"Why?"
- I just...
- It does look good.
- Isn't this nice?
- I like it.
It's not so bad.
People are talking a lot...
about Suk Jin's fashion online.
They say he's dressed
like a man in his 20s.
- I know. There was an article.
- That's what fans say.
- Which one?
- Oh, right.
- He looks cool.
- You made your legs too long.
- That's not true.
- You look like Dhalsim.
Actually, my manager
touched it up a little.
- But...
- I don't agree though.
- They look too long.
- The red pants. He wore them...
- as a penalty, right?
- Right, So Min. That's it.
I took the photo during the shoot.
It's not like he can hide them.
- Right.
- That doesn't look like you.
He covered his face
with sunglasses and a mask...
to create a silhouette
of a man in his 20s.
- What?
- The reporter is so mean.
- That's how the reporter felt.
- So his body is fine.
That doesn't mean anything.
You can always retouch your photo.
Anyway,
he's following in
Im Ha Ryong's footsteps.
- Exactly.
- Ha Ryong is very fashionable.
That's not true.
Seriously, Ha Ryong is
a sharp dresser.
- Right.
- He's quite a dresser.
- He's very fashionable.
- He is.
The difference is that
Suk Jin doesn't own a building.
- Suk Jin does.
- He does?
- No, I don't.
- His wife does.
- He owns land in Paju.
- No, I don't.
- Paju?
- You have an estate in Paju.
Why do you deny it?
I don't own a building.
- I heard that.
- But you have an estate.
- Hey.
- He has something in Dongtan.
- What?
- You have one in Dongtan.
- Dongtan?
- Does he have something in Dongtan?
- Hey, stop talking.
- Why?
- In Dongtan?
- Will you disclose all my assets?
Really? Does he have
a building in Dongtan?
How do you know about Dongtan?
- That's all I have.
- It's a secret.
- It's top secret.
- Really?
- So he has 2, not just 1.
- That's enough.
- I didn't know that.
- Right? He hesitated.
- That's true.
- You're a building owner.
- In Dongtan.
- That's not true.
- My gosh.
- It's not a building.
If you say that,
one in a thousand might believe it.
- That's right.
- They would think it's true.
- They believe it and...
- That's the problem.
We need to perform a fact check.
- Right.
- We should be careful.
There's one more thing
I want you to talk about.
- What is it?
- There's a song...
that recently made
a comeback on music charts.
- That's right. I know this song.
- Is it "I Know"?
- That's right. Se Chan.
- I got it first.
- Right.
- What is it?
No!
That's right.
I posted the video clip.
- I know.
- Let's hear it then.
(Se Chan, Yong Jin, and Jin Ho made
their debut as singers in 2008.)
- Se Chan.
- Right.
- You sing pretty well.
- Let's meet them now.
- Music, start.
- Start.
(24-year-old Se Chan)
No!
- Jin Ho and Yong Jin.
- "All I Want Is You".
No.
You might get
to perform the song again.
- I like the song though.
- Me too.
(Rapper Yang Se Chan)
Gosh, I can't watch this.
(Embarrassed)
- Hey.
- What's with my hair?
- Look at his hair.
- Hey.
- He's serious.
- Why do you look so serious?
I can't stand the sight of him.
My face is flushed.
- Gosh, it's so annoying.
- I think...
I think I saw him at SBS.
- I posted this...
- Please turn it off.
That's nice.
(He can't stand the sight
of himself from 14 years ago.)
My goodness.
It's really annoying.
(Please help me.)
- What's funny about Se Chan is...
- Isn't that amazing?
He looks so cool
when he holds the microphone.
But it's just Se Chan
when he puts it down.
- I should cover my mouth.
- He's cool with his lips covered.
- Isn't that when you stole a bike?
- No.
- No. I was a singer.
- He pretends to be a celebrity.
To be honest, those three were...
- drunk with popularity back then.
- Right.
- So they were being frivolous.
- I was really arrogant.
- Really?
- I was being condescending.
They were idols
in the comedian world.
They were very condescending.
- I know.
- What's with his hair?
- The back...
- What's that ponytail?
This is...
what a famous hairdresser
in Gangnam did.
- She did it for me.
- Really?
"What are you?" "I'm a rapper."
"You need a ponytail."
That's how I got it.
I didn't like it,
but I had no choice.
And the other idol artists were
surprised to see me.
It's a good memory.
- I got goosebumps.
- It's a nice song though.
All right. Let me tell you
about today's race now.
- Okay.
- Today's race...
is called the RTT.
It's The Running Tag of Tails.
- What is it?
- You guys will be...
- scattered around Sangam-dong.
- Sangam-dong?
And you will hide your name tags
in places you want.
(The members will hide their names
in places they want in Sangam-dong.)
You can go anywhere in Sangam-dong.
And this is your name tag.
- My gosh.
- How can I hide it?
You can go anywhere in Sangam-dong.
(The race will take place
in the whole neighborhood.)
Gosh, how would we...
(The race will take place
in the whole neighborhood.)
So are we going to use
the whole area of Sangam-dong?
We will give you this map.
(They will get a map
of Sangam-dong for the race.)
- That's big.
- How is that possible?
And this is your name tag.
- Nice.
- I like that.
- Really?
- Gosh, that's big.
How would we hide it?
We have the rules
about hiding the name tags.
You can't hide it
in a place where you can't find it.
You can't use locks or hide it
in a place that is off limits.
It should be a place
that's easily accessible.
I see.
You should be
able to retrieve it yourself.
These are the rules
you should remember.
Once you hide your name tag,
you can start looking for
other members' name tags.
It won't be easy.
If you find a name tag,
the member will be out.
Really?
And the member
whose name tag is found...
will be your tail.
(The member whose name tag is
found will be the captain's tail.)
That sounds interesting.
If Jae Suk finds Haha's name tag,
Haha will stop his mission...
- and become Jae Suk's tail.
- Jae Suk's tail?
(Those who are eliminated join
the captain's team right away.)
- That's how it goes.
- It will be thrilling.
You will look for
each other's name tags...
until there's only one member left.
For those who have difficulties
finding the name tags,
there will be hint spots.
There will be four mission spots.
If you complete a mission there,
you will get an address
or a photo of the place...
where the name tag
you're looking for is hidden.
It will be easy if I get an address.
It will still be hard to find it
even if you know the address.
- Right.
- I guess so.
- I think a photo would be better.
- And let's say...
Jae Suk gets a hint
about Haha's name tag,
Haha will be told about it.
Haha will hear that Jae Suk got...
the address of the place
where Haha's name tag is hidden.
And if Haha wants,
he can go there and hide
his name tag somewhere else.
But he gets only three minutes.
- And I might run into him there.
- That can happen.
You can hide it again
for three minutes,
- but you can only walk.
- Walk?
Once the time is up, you have to
place your name tag there.
The race will be over
once one of you collects six tails.
- It will be difficult.
- Then we will continue...
- the next race in the SBS building.
- We can do it. It won't be so hard.
Let's start the race then.
- Yes.
- Okay.
(They are ready to start the race.)
- It will be tricky.
- Gosh, this is...
- That's too big.
- It won't be easy.
- It's not easy.
- Where...
- Okay.
- Where should I hide this?
I'm familiar with Sangam-dong.
- I'm not.
- I don't know much about it.
Let's go.
- Shall we go?
- Let's go to Sangam-dong.
- Let's go.
- Shall we go?
Where should we go?
Hang on. I should hide
my name tag first.
- Let's go.
- I know this area inside out.
I'll just put it on the street.
That's all you need to know.
Don't be so uptight.
So Min, listen to me.
I know all the places
in Sangam-dong.
- Let's go.
- So what?
Whatever TV, so what TV,
Jeonsobari TV.
- Whatever.
- I don't care.
You will be my tail anyway.
What did he say? What was that?
- What did you say?
- You'll be my tail.
You will be my tail.
- Hey, So Min.
- My wagging tail.
Why don't we show our teamwork...
after a long time?
Don't fall for it.
- I can't let them win.
- I'm serious.
If you don't want it,
just forget it.
Okay. I'm in.
What do you want to do?
We should stick together.
Okay. Let's go together then.
- Let's go together.
- I'll call you later.
I'm serious. Don't you want to win
the race with me today?
- Okay.
I'll trust him.
Good luck, So Min.
Is that it?
(Suk Jin goes to his car.)
- Is this the car?
- Yes.
Are we moving in this car?
Will Jae Suk drive?
Should I go alone?
Oh, right.
This is an individual game.
This is where I am now.
- Can I go anywhere I want?
- Yes.
Where should I go?
The Community Service Center?
Did you get permission
for the shoot?
You should get permission yourself.
Really?
How would I do that?
- It's up to you.
- Up to me?
Hey, that's...
This is crazy.
Am I supposed to ask
if it's okay to shoot there?
My gosh.
They would let me in though.
They don't mind it in most cases.
My face is like my ID card.
I've been doing this show
for a very long time.
We should go to Sangam-dong first.
I should hide it downtown.
Let me see.
(Jae Suk is thinking
about where to hide his name tag.)
I might come back here later.
Sir, please go to Nanjicheon Pond.
I don't think the other members
have a specific destination yet.
Do you have any plans?
It's not even started yet.
What plan would there be?
- You're not good at hiding things.
- That's not true.
I did stuff like this a lot
on "Infinite Challenge".
Gosh, this is...
I'm...
I'm serious.
This is where I go to walk my dog.
The green ones.
This is where I walk my dog.
I've been to all these places.
I think Pyeonghwa Park.
I should go to Nanjicheon Pond
in Pyeonghwa Park.
They have a nice park there.
My dog is finally helping me
in the race.
My dog is really energetic.
Well... What about...
Can I hide it in the MBC building?
(Can I hide it in the MBC building?)
I'm thinking of going
into the MBC building.
(His idea isn't any different
from Jong Kook's.)
Then...
I'd say...
the beacon does not
shine on its own base.
I think it sounds really cool.
This is what celebrities
like and fear at the same time.
It's the director of
the Variety Production Bureau.
I'll put my name tag under her desk.
- So are you going to SBS?
- Let's go to SBS.
I'd like to meet Young In
after a long time.
And going to Sky Park
can be very tiresome.
The wide field.
But that's what Se Chan would do.
Those who are like...
mice or wild dogs will go there.
But I'm different.
I'll go to Sky Park.
(Haha was right about the mice.)
I'll go to the peak. Okay.
This is war.
(He goes to Sky Park
as Haha predicted.)
Gosh, they will have to...
go all the way up
to the top because of me.
I need an alliance here.
(I need an alliance here.)
- Haha.
- Hey, Se Chan.
I will be your loyal tail.
Don't say that.
I mean it. I need you...
in today's race.
Go ahead and rap for me.
The day I confessed my feelings,
I swore to you
(The rapper
with a ponytail is back.)
(Satisfied)
Haha.
I will tell you where I'm going.
Where are you going?
I'm going to Apartment Ten.
Apartment Ten?
Yes. That's where I'm going.
I just wanted to tell you.
Where are you going?
- I'm telling you the truth.
- Okay.
Se Chan, I'm serious.
- I'm...
- Yes.
going to Sky Park.
I'm going to Sky Park.
- You're going to Sky Park?
- Yes.
I'll put my name tag
in the middle of the open field.
You can go to Sky Park too.
No, why would I go there?
Okay. I'm going to Sky Park.
Okay.
- Bye.
(Se Chan is swayed by Haha's lie.)
I think he's
really going to Sky Park.
I think So Min is...
going to Sky Park now.
- Sky Park?
- Yes.
It must be...
really hot up there.
- You think?
- Yes. It's dangerous.
- Okay. I get it.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
I don't think that's true.
(Se Chan is worried he will meet
the other members at Sky Park.)
There's the ticket office.
Please drop me off here.
I'll go up to the left.
(He arrives at Sky Park
filled with worries.)
My goodness.
Is Haha going to Sky Park?
Hello. Can I buy a ticket now?
- How much is it?
- Three dollars for a round trip.
Three dollars?
Here.
(He buys a ticket for the shuttle.)
If someone...
asks you about me,
please say you didn't see me.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's get on the shuttle.
Oh, dear.
(He gets on the shuttle.)
It feels like
I'm going on an outing.
Here we go.
(It feels like a picnic.)
This is nice.
So Min?
(Se Chan heard
these two were coming here.)
I'm supposed...
to hide this in a place
where people can't find it.
I can dig in the ground, right?
I would need a shovel.
There are a lot of snakes here.
Snakes?
(Nervous)
I should go anyway.
- I'm worried.
- You should be careful.
(So Min calls Haha.)
So Min, is there anything
you need to know? Ask me anything.
Prince Haha.
- Yes?
- Where are you headed?
- Princess So Min.
- Yes?
Princess So Min?
Yes, Prince Haha.
How about we trust each other
since this is the first round?
Yes, let's do that, Haha.
Then I'll trust you and tell you
the truth. I'm serious.
- I'm going to the SBS building.
- I'll trust you too.
(I'm going to the SBS building.)
(Haha told her the truth.)
Then let's meet up there.
You're lying, aren't you?
I'm not lying. Let's meet up there.
Let's meet up there
and get the first hint.
Sounds good. I understand for now.
We're a team, okay?
Okay. Let's meet up
after hiding our name tags.
Princess So Min!
Prince Haha!
Cross!
Gosh. I don't think I can trust her.
At least once... I mean,
she and I have been distant...
for about two years, I think.
There were times when we were
so tight. We rooted for each other.
And we called each other often,
but we became a little distant...
because she kept having doubts
about me.
But I always trust her
although she often fools me.
I really hate where we are now.
I want to get our friendship back.
I want to go back to the days when
I called her "my dear princess".
So I'm going to show her
my passion and affection...
that are as hot as the summer sun.
(Haha arrived at the SBS building
as he promised to So Min.)
(Haha arrived at the SBS building.)
(And he found someone.)
Let's go.
(Haha meets Jong Kook.)
He was too lazy to do so.
- I'm here to see Hwan Jin,
- Yes.
help him promote his new show,
and leave.
- That's sweet of you.
- Yes. I'm here to help him.
- You're so kind.
- Of course.
- I'm just...
- What a coincidence.
- I'm just stopping by.
- I see.
- I'm here to see someone too.
- Right.
I wouldn't hide my name tag here.
- Hold on. So Min might come too.
- Exactly.
Sorry?
Hey, a black vehicle is coming.
Over there.
My goodness. This is awesome.
I think I'll get emotional
if So Min gets out.
(Who could be in the vehicle?)
(The two of them are trying to
recover their faded friendship.)
(Could the prince and the princess
have the same goal?)
- Hey, what are you doing here?
- Gosh, it's Suk Jin.
Hey, why did you come here?
Suk Jin is in there.
(Middle-aged men tend to go only
to the places they know.)
You were too lazy to go
somewhere else, right?
Am I right?
I'm not going in there now that I've
seen you and Jong Kook.
Gosh, So Min.
Why on earth can't she trust me?
Think about what you've done to her.
How can she trust you?
There's no way I told him the truth.
I'll hide my name tag
at the place I like.
(What place did So Min choose?)
Aren't you going to talk to
the other members?
You see, I'm not that type.
Are you the type
that's always in last place?
No, not the type
that's always in last place.
I'm the type that figures out
what to do on my own.
(While wandering in Sangam-dong
and talking nonsense...)
Wait. Isn't that our staff's car?
Oh, I think I was wrong.
Our staff members are in that car,
right?
(He found a vehicle
that he assumed to be the staff's.)
- Right?
- I can't tell you that.
I think I'm right.
Sir, can you follow that car,
please?
- Follow that car?
- Yes, please.
(A vehicle caught Jae Suk's eyes.)
Then I'll find one name tag
for sure.
(If I follow the car,
I'll find one name tag for sure.)
We're following it.
We're following that car.
(He smiles from ear to ear
as he gets lucky.)
I wonder who's in that car.
(While following the car...)
Why is it stopping?
Did they notice we were following?
Hold on. A cameraman is filming
whoever that is.
The cameraman is getting out.
Please drive past the car.
I don't mind if we go past them.
Hold on.
Someone else is getting out.
Who is that?
It's So Min.
It's So Min, right?
(So Min got caught.)
What do you think? No one would know
that it's a name tag, right?
(She's so naive that she doesn't
know what's going on.)
Oh, no. Gosh. No.
My phone.
(And she dropped her phone too.)
Thank you. I'll be back shortly.
Look at her. Sir.
We can go now.
I know she'll be around here.
What time is it now?
(He's watching her to find out
the direction she's moving in.)
(Thinking hard)
But So Min would only annoy me
if she tagged along with me.
I should hide my name tag
before finding hers.
Sir, please drop me off here.
- Here?
- Yes.
Since I've found one member...
(He gets out to hide his name tag
after checking So Min's location.)
Am I at the right place?
(At that time, So Min is also
looking for a place.)
Wait. I should
hide my name tag somewhere...
(He should hide it quickly
so that he can chase So Min.)
and locate her.
It's too hot.
Gosh. So Min is over there.
Hey, move. Come on.
(He found So Min in front of him.)
It's in the DDMC building.
(So Min didn't see Jae Suk
who was right in front of her.)
In which building
is the Channel A office?
Oh, I'm at the wrong place.
(So Min came right behind Jae Suk.)
She's walking past us.
So Min didn't see us.
(So Min couldn't see...)
(Jae Suk and the staff members
who were with him.)
It's so hot.
It's hot, right?
(This man here is Jae Suk.)
So Min... I know. I saw it.
I saw the reflection of her.
I saw her just walking past us
without noticing us.
We just have to go straight.
We'll find it.
(But then...)
(So Min suddenly turns around!)
(And she walks back
the way she came?)
I think...
(What?)
(Suddenly,
she looks at the utility pole.)
No one could find it
if I hid it here, right?
(She's simply cheerful
when she can't even hide herself.)
I think it's a good idea
to hide it here on the street.
I don't see anyone here.
I think no one is coming here.
She didn't see me, right?
She just walked past me.
She didn't see any of us.
I told you so.
This is why
eliminating her would be pointless.
She went down there, right?
(She even let Jae Suk know
the direction she was moving in.)
I'll hide my name tag first.
Let me think. I think
I should hide it around here.
I should make sure
that no one sees me hiding it.
(Right then...)
(At a place with no passers-by,)
(Jae Suk found a good spot
to hide his name tag.)
(He slid it
under the snow removal box.)
Wait.
They won't tell the others, right?
(He feels anxious
even after hiding it.)
(Jae Suk successfully hid it
without leaving any witnesses.)
(Now, his goal is to catch So Min.)
So Min went down the street
without a particular destination.
(Meanwhile,
Se Chan who went to Sky Park...)
I'm really enjoying riding this.
I feel like I'm going on a picnic.
I feel like
I'm here to promote Seoul.
"Yang Se Chan's Tour of Seoul".
(Yang Se Chan's Tour of Seoul,
Part One)
Nice cornering.
Great job.
(He takes photos of the scenery.)
Sir, is today's weather good
to enjoy the view?
It's too hot in July and August,
so it's off-season now.
(It's off-season at Sky Park
from July to August.)
In July and August?
We came here during the off-season.
When will this air?
- Pardon me?
- "Infinite Challenge".
"Infinite Challenge"?
We're shooting Running Man.
When will this episode of
Running Man air?
This part will make it on air
only if I do well.
If I don't make it interesting,
it could be edited out.
- I'll do my very best. Yes.
- Good luck.
- You explained it to me so kindly.
- I hope it works out well for you.
Thank you.
(Exclaiming)
Look. This is
what Sangam-dong looks like.
It's much prettier than
the night view in Hong Kong.
It's hard to believe that there's
a place like this in Seoul.
Right.
(He's going to hide his name tag.)
I think...
no one will come up here.
My gosh.
There's no one else but us here.
I can't see
how popular this place is now.
It should be crowded with people
enjoying the scenery.
This is a lonely fight.
I want to interview a few citizens.
But I see no one here.
(He found the first citizen
when he came up on the observatory.)
I found another person
who is fighting a lonely battle.
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
Didn't you say you wanted to
interview people?
"Yang Se Chan's Tour of Seoul".
But he doesn't seem to
care about me.
Sir, did you come up here alone?
Did you come here alone? I see.
- We're shooting Running Man.
- I see.
- Yes. I'm Yang Se Chan.
- It must be hard to shoot outside.
It's okay.
Did you ride your bicycle alone
all the way up here?
That's amazing. Wasn't it hard?
- It was, obviously.
- Right.
What do you think?
The scenery is magnificent, right?
(He keeps asking boring questions.)
Enjoy the scenery
and have a great time.
(Enjoy the scenery
and have a great time.)
(The first interview ended up
in failure.)
Okay. I still have a long way to go.
- Hey, Hwan Jin.
- Hi, Jong Kook.
I came all the way
to the SBS building...
to promote "Go Straight for Crush".
I mean, "Go Straight for Love".
I'm here to help you
promote your new show.
Where are you?
Couldn't you say the right title?
(The person whom Jong Kook is
looking for is...)
(Lee Hwan Jin,
the former director of Running Man)
(Likes stir-fried pork)
(He directed Running Man
for so long since the beginning.)
(He's preparing a new dating show
called "Go Straight for Love".)
(Why did Jong Kook call him
when he's busy preparing the show?)
- I should hide my name tag...
- Is it a poster? What is it?
- My gosh.
- I should...
hide my name tag.
Is there a good spot to hide it?
- Is this really a name tag?
- Yes.
We have to hide our name tags
anywhere in Sangam-dong.
It can be anywhere in Sangam-dong.
- Aren't you a star director?
- Yes, he is.
- He's a star director.
- He'll launch a new show soon.
The word spread widely
among TV celebrities.
We all have our eyes
on your new show.
What's the title of the show?
Isn't it "Love Goes Straight"?
(Isn't it "Love Goes Straight"?)
I said, "Go Straight for Crush".
Is it "Go Straight, No U-Turn"?
When will it premiere?
On August 3.
On August 3? What time?
At 10:30 p.m.
- On August 3.
- August 3.
- At 10:30 p.m.
- At...
"Go Straight for Crush"... No.
"Go Straight..."
- "for Love".
- "For Love".
("Go Straight for Love")
"Go Straight for Love".
My gosh. That was funny.
All right. "Go Straight for Love".
- Okay.
- You must hide it by 11:00 a.m.
- Where should I hide it?
- You have to hide it...
in a place that's too obvious.
- Where? What's an obvious place?
- For example...
No one would search the cafe.
Won't they search the cafe?
Of course, they won't go there
during the opening hours.
- I'm sorry,
- Yes?
but can you hide this
in the cabinet?
- I'll hide it in there.
- Thank you.
- No one will be able to find it.
- Right.
That was easy. Nice.
This won't work.
I'll go somewhere else.
I'll go to the building next to it.
Not far away from it.
- I need permission for shooting?
- You should get permission.
What's in this building?
It's the YTN building.
YTN?
I'm sure they'll let us shoot...
Let's see how it goes.
I'll face it head-on.
(The top star with 30 years of
experience whose face is his ID)
I should hide it
in a hard-to-find place like this.
Excuse me. Hello. We're...
May we shoot our show here
for a while?
- You're shooting a show?
- Yes.
- Please give me a moment.
- Maybe we can't, right?
I'll hide something here and leave.
It's a mission.
- Please wait a moment.
- Sure.
Right. He must talk to someone.
Since it's a news network,
they're very strict...
You said your face was your ID.
Hey, be quiet.
Edit out the part where I said that.
- Yes?
- The person in charge will be here.
- The person in charge? All right.
- Yes.
See? This shows how good
this place is at hiding my name tag.
If I hid it in the office building
of a news network,
then the other members would
do the same thing.
They wouldn't care
what Jae Suk does.
Hello.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
You must be the person in charge...
- I'm from the security team.
- You're from the security team?
- We're shooting Running Man.
- I see.
I just need to hide this.
May we have permission to shoot?
In that case, you need to talk to
someone from another team.
I see. Oh, you're calling someone.
Wait. I don't have much time.
I understand.
(The top star's face ID doesn't
seem to have much credibility.)
(The employee seems to be in
a difficult position from behind.)
Maybe we won't get permission.
I'm running out of time.
(The phone conversation is
going on for longer.)
I'm embarrassed.
I said my face was my ID.
- Understood.
- Okay. Yes.
I'm sorry, but I was told you must
get approval in advance.
(His ID has been rejected.)
- I understand.
- I'm sorry.
Please don't be. It's okay.
- We can include this scene, right?
- Pardon?
- Probably.
- Yes.
(Mr. ID walks with a hunched back
as he's embarrassed.)
Right. I see why.
(He tries to justify himself
while talking to himself.)
I'm so embarrassed.
Of course,
I should get approval in advance.
I understand. Darn it.
Let's go to the next building.
What's in that building?
- CJ.
- CJ?
Gosh. Why are so many news networks
located around here?
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
- May we shoot here for a while?
- Hello. Oh, I'm sorry,
but you need to make a request
in advance.
- Right?
- Yes.
- I understand.
- I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
I might run out of time
while trying to get permission.
(Meanwhile,
Jae Suk is hunting for So Min.)
Hello.
Have you seen Jeon So Min?
- No, I haven't.
- No?
She went this way.
(He starts tracing her
at the last place he saw her.)
You're on social media, right?
Can you search posts
about Jeon So Min?
(Can you search posts
about Jeon So Min?)
Some people post about the places
where they see a celebrity.
That's why I should be careful
not to be spotted.
How smart am I? Right?
- I can't find such posts.
- What are you talking about?
I'll teach you a lesson. Gosh.
(His social media
investigation method failed.)
Seeing that she went this way,
(Detective Yoo decided to
do the footwork in the end.)
she most likely went to
a network's office building.
Hello. Sir, by any chance,
did you see...
a team of staff shooting
on your way here?
I saw Ji Suk Jin over there.
Over there?
(I saw Ji Suk Jin over there.)
Thank you.
(He was tipped off about
Suk Jin's location by chance.)
He was grumbling
while walking around.
I see. Thank you for telling me.
- Hello. May I ask where you work?
- Hello.
- In that building.
- What kind of company is it?
- It's called Dexter Studios.
- Pardon?
Dexter Studios.
That's the company name.
Really? Do you think we can shoot
in your office for a while?
- I don't think so.
- You don't?
Not again.
I'm sorry.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
This is the last place...
(When Seok Sam left
to find another place...)
There's one of our members there.
(There's one of our members there.)
Quiet down.
(Detective Yoo noticed
that someone had just passed by.)
I can tell
by seeing where they all look.
Suk Jin is over there.
Ji Suk Jin went that way, right?
He just went inside the building.
- Which building?
- This one.
This building right here?
Did he go into this building?
All right.
Excuse me. I'm sorry, but...
- You should talk to the manager.
- The manager?
But the manager stepped out.
The manager stepped out?
I'll wait here and go in to find it
after he leaves the building.
Shall I tell you when he comes out?
Please do that.
Hey, So Min.
- Jae Suk.
- Why?
- Have you hidden your name tag?
- Sorry?
I've hidden mine.
I'm having a cup of coffee now.
Really? Where are you?
I'm at this place... You know...
I heard that you were at Sky Park.
- Pardon?
- Sky Park.
No.
Everyone went to Sky Park
to find your name tag.
Really?
I made a lot of good memories
at Sky Park.
Gosh. You're so good at hiding
things like this.
You will never find it.
I'll see you
when you become my tail.
Okay.
I think he hasn't hidden it yet.
He sounded so busy.
He tried to hang up quickly
because he was busy.
You can look for it
after he hides it.
I know. I'll start looking
as soon as he hides it.
What I'm going to do...
(He's going to wait
although it'll take a while.)
is not against the rule, right?
That's right.
It's taking him longer
than I thought.
- Hasn't he hidden it yet?
- Not yet.
I can go in once he hides it.
I guess you'll have to wait
a while longer.
Then how about I find
So Min's first?
(Then how about I find
So Min's first?)
Hold on.
Then... Please...
don't tell Suk Jin you saw me
if you see him again.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
(He leaves after getting
the citizens on his side.)
Entertainers who do variety shows
have this habit.
We tend not to go far away from
the area we often go to.
- Find her name tag first.
- What?
Find her name tag
before saying such a thing.
You know...
that I have a lot of experience
chasing the other members.
No one else has
as much experience as I have.
So Min just called me, right?
(Detective Yoo found out that So Min
was having coffee at a cafe.)
She said
she was having coffee at a cafe.
For example, when I see a place
like this, a burger place,
I can just ask if they saw her.
I'll just ask them the question
even though I know nothing.
Hello.
Have you seen Jeon So Min here?
No? All right. Hello.
Did Jeon So Min come here,
by any chance?
- I didn't see her.
- Okay. Thank you.
Has Jeon So Min come here, sir?
- Who?
- Jeon So Min.
- No, she hasn't.
- I see.
- Have you seen Jeon So Min here?
- Who?
- Jeon So Min.
- No.
You haven't seen her? Hello.
(Unlike his expectation,
she doesn't seem to have come here.)
I found So Min. There she is.
(Right then!)
(So Min appeared?)
(So Min showed up in front of him
right at that moment.)
(Here's how So Min ended up
showing up in front of him.)
There's a place I want to go to.
A friend of mine runs a cafe.
Can I hide it at his cafe?
It's in the DDMC building.
(So Min went to her friend's cafe
to hide her name tag.)
(Gosh. So Min is over there.)
Hey, move. Come on.
(Without knowing that
he had found her,)
(she focused on finding the cafe.)
She's walking past us.
So Min didn't see us.
- Hello. Can I hide this here?
- Sure.
Please don't tell anyone
that I hid this here.
Okay? Make sure not to tell anyone.
What do I do?
I'm running out of time.
(She hid her name tag
behind the cafe's promotion poster.)
Could anyone find this?
I bet no one can find it.
Let's have a cup of coffee
before leaving.
Order what you want.
There's no way they can find it.
(She got excited
and had a photo taken.)
It was so easy.
Whenever I come here...
After having udon and rice balls,
we have coffee here.
(While she enjoys her free time
sipping coffee)
- Jae Suk's over there.
- Jae Suk's in the building.
(Startled)
Hurry. We need to hide.
Come on. We must hide. Oh, no.
Thank you so much.
Gosh. We need to hide immediately.
We have to hide right away.
Hurry up and hide. Oh, no!
Oh, no.
(She makes a run for it
with her ponytail waving.)
(Screaming!)
So Min's worried, isn't she?
That means
she hid it here somewhere.
(She made a run for it
into Jae Suk's line of sight.)
So Min, come on.
Where were you just now? Hello.
- Hello.
(The master pursuer closes the gap.)
Where were you just now?
You must've hid yours around here.
(Chuckling)
You must be here
because you hid it close by.
- Yours must be hidden here too.
- What?
- You hid yours here too.
- Right.
(So Min is close to getting caught.)
Hold on. I must look for it then.
She seemed really worried just now.
I should see where she's going.
Where did he come from?
(She puts distance between
her and Jae Suk first.)
So Min,
where are you off to in a hurry?
How are you here out of all places?
- Where are you going?
- How...
I wouldn't have been that scared
if I had seen a ghost.
Where are you off to in a hurry?
Well...
- Jae Suk, I...
- So Min,
this is how you react
when you're flustered.
How can you be here out of
all the places in this neighborhood?
How did you know to come here?
Why are you leaving the building?
(Why are you leaving the building?)
- Well, it's...
- Are you moving away...
from where you hid your name tag?
I'm thinking that you
hid yours around here.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
(Just then...)
(Detective Yoo
has his eyes on something.)
- So Min.
- Yes?
- Can I take a sip?
- No, you can't.
Just a sip.
(He finds out
which cafe So Min visited.)
Here you go.
Go, just go!
Get going.
- Go!
- Let me see.
Can you come over here for a second?
- No, you can't.
- Come over here.
- Just a second.
- You can't!
No, you can't. Wait!
- Jae Suk, this is wrong.
- How so?
"With more coffee."
- "All day."
- Don't.
(So Min's close
to losing the race...)
(only after 15 minutes
of hiding her name tag.)
This is the place.
(He's where So Min
hid her name tag.)
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
Didn't Jeon So Min come by?
- No, she didn't.
- She wasn't here.
- Isn't this yours?
- It isn't.
You seem highly flustered.
This is the place.
Jae Suk.
Jae Suk!
Why aren't you leaving this spot?
(Jae Suk keeps questioning them.)
So that I can take orders.
Right, I see.
Just a second.
This.
She was in such a rush
that she forgot her phone.
(She was in such a rush
that she forgot her phone.)
I mean...
Jae Suk's in the building.
(When she was caught earlier)
(She left her phone on the table.)
(She made a run for it
but left her phone.)
Things must've been
that urgent for her.
This... I mean...
(He can't make an excuse for her.)
- Even a drink was left behind.
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, let's go play...
- the 2-on-2 game.
- What?
- The 2-on-2 game.
- So Min.
- What?
- You left this behind.
(You must've been in a rush.)
(Gosh!)
- Jae Suk, I...
- And this.
You must've just
popped the straws in.
(You must've just
popped the straws in.)
- Right?
- Jae Suk, hold on.
Let's go for now.
Just a second.
- Why...
- So Min, wait.
You hid it here somewhere.
No, I didn't hide it here.
You can't.
Jae Suk, what can I
do for you right now?
Let's go play the 2-on-2 game first.
- Jae Suk.
- I know this is inappropriate,
but could I...
- You must put on the apron and cap.
- Is that so?
Jae Suk, must you go this far?
- You shouldn't go this far.
- I'm not taking it too far.
Let's go play the 2-on-2 game.
So Min, give me a second.
Why...
I apologize for the inconvenience.
- I'm really sorry about this.
- It's all right.
I won't touch any of the food.
This is bad. What am I going to do?
Why did you let him
see your coffee cup?
(Why did you let him
see your coffee cup?)
(The master pursuer investigates
where So Min was at.)
I'm really sorry about this.
(The master pursuer investigates
where So Min was at.)
(A part of the name tag
can be seen behind him.)
- When the owner gets here...
- That's why...
I can't rummage through the drawers.
- The owner will be here soon.
- Right.
(Jae Suk hovers around
where the name tag is.)
I can see a part of it.
- I can see it.
- This...
What do I do?
(Will Jae Suk be able
to find the name tag?)
When the owner gets here.
When the owner gets here...
(He leaves without saying anything.)
I'm sorry about this.
He just left which means
he hasn't seen it.
Even though
it can be seen from here.
(Jae Suk just leaves the kitchen.)
This was stuck on here, right?
Can I have my phone back?
- Let's go play the 2-on-2 game.
- Just a moment.
Give me a second.
(But...)
- Why did I leave my phone behind?
- Can you hold this for me?
We should get going.
- Got it.
- Let's go play the 2-on-2 game.
- Let's get going for now.
- All right.
(Oh, no!)
What do I do? I think he found it.
(He checks the exterior
of the cafe.)
Gosh.
(Ripping off)
So Min has been eliminated!
(So Min has been eliminated.)
How can you do this to me, Jae Suk?
Come on.
(Ms. Tail is close
to being in tears.)
Why did you even come here?
I worked hard to put that there.
(So Min becomes his tail
30 minutes into the game.)
- A lot of thinking went into it.
- Come on.
You're my tail now.
Here.
(He gives her the phone back
and claims her as his tail.)
- So Min...
- Put it on.
- Put it on already.
- You must put this on.
Honestly though.
Why did you come here?
- Would you like a cup of coffee?
- Sure.
Gather around, then.
Once again, I apologize.
It turned out to be outside.
But the race just started!
How is this fair?
- An ice Americano.
- Got it.
Three of them.
We'll take three of those.
So Min, you must stay
with Jae Suk from now on.
Help Jae Suk
complete his missions...
- and you'll earn extra points.
- How many points?
It depends on how well he does
on his missions.
- Captain!
- Right.
I'm sorry to ask,
but where did you hide yours...
and why did you come here?
Thank you.
Where did you hide yours?
That I can't tell you.
You should know that...
you weren't aware of my presence
down by the bus stop.
(Shocked)
What the...
- Were you at the bus stop?
- You walked past me.
(While the first captain
was being crowned...)
(Se Chan is still
seeing the sights of Seoul.)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Do you know me?
- Yes, you're on Running Man.
(Running Man)
My gosh.
Yes, you're on Running Man.
(Running Man)
My gosh.
- Can we take a photo?
- Okay, thank you.
Sure.
(He's glad to receive this request.)
We're from Singapore.
Oh, Singapore.
Singapore. Marina Bay, right?
- Yes, Marina Bay.
- I know Marina Bay.
Singapore, gosh.
This is nice.
It's our first time in Korea.
Nice to meet you.
Are you here on business?
(Are you here on business?)
- On holiday.
- I see.
That's right.
Now...
Do you like the view up here?
- Yes.
- Yes, it's lovely.
- Amazing?
- Yes, amazing.
- Okay.
- It's beautiful.
Let me hold this up. Just a second.
(Yang Se Chan)
In 1, 2, 3.
(After talking briefly,
they take a meaningful photo.)
- Thank you.
- It was nice seeing you.
- Bye.
(They immediately part ways
after taking the photo.)
Have a good time.
How can I tell them
to enjoy their trip?
Enjoy.
Have a nice day.
- You too.
- Take care.
Yes, enjoy.
- Bye.
- Thank you, bye.
(Chuckling)
What on earth are we filming today?
I need to hide this, right?
Yang Se Chan's Tour of Seoul.
This is our last episode...
and I got to meet foreign tourists.
I was able to enjoy
the affection we have for the city.
Now, I'll find a spot
to hide my name tag.
(Now that the tour has ended,
Se Chan's off to hide his name tag.)
We're currently here on the map.
We're crossing over here
and headed this way.
I couldn't make it
to the first floor.
(Where did Ji Hyo
hide her name tag?)
Here.
Let's go someplace nearby.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook takes on
the one-man mission.)
I love cold chicken noodles,
you know.
Hello, everyone. Okay!
- Is this a one-man mission?
- Yes.
But there's still another chair.
This is
an individual mission called...
About You.
(About You)
You'll have three minutes
to freely interview...
the staff member that we choose.
To win, you must answer...
two out of the three
predetermined questions.
Got it.
I'll go with the camera director.
(Camera director, Park Sung Bae)
I'll start by asking you your name.
He's already here. Keep going.
- His name.
- Right.
- And go.
- How much time do I have?
Three minutes. Ready...
(He has 3 minutes to get
as much information as he can.)
Three minutes. What's your name?
It's Park Sung Bae.
Park Sung Bae. Right.
Park Sung Bae.
Just a second.
It doesn't feel right though.
What if they hear
the information I get...
- and ask non-related questions?
- Exactly.
The questions
have been predetermined.
- Is that so?
- That's how it should be.
So the questioning... Got it.
What can I ask him?
What should I know?
Your shoe size.
My shoe size is 275mm.
Right, 275mm.
They don't look that big.
Be quiet over there. Your vision.
- I bet he has bad vision.
- My vision...
- is around 0.2.
- Got it.
How tall are you?
Around 174cm.
- No way. I say 172cm.
- Right, 174cm.
- It's 172cm.
- Be quiet over there!
- It's 172, not 174.
- Got it.
What else can I ask?
What else should I ask about him?
Which clan of Park are you from?
- Miryang.
- Of course it's Miryang.
- Can you stay quiet?
- Parks are mostly from Miryang.
- Park of Miryang Clan?
I'm going to go look for Hwan Jin.
I'm taking a risk by doing this.
(Haha is looking for Director Lee?)
- You left it with Hwan Jin?
- Yes.
I'll get going, then.
Cafe? Which cafe
are you talking about?
If you were to hide a name tag,
you must hide it somewhere obvious.
- Like where?
- For instance...
(Haha was watching them from afar.)
It's room number two. Right?
(So Haha visits Director Lee's
new projection room.)
It's fun.
It looks fun already.
(Flattering without even
watching the show)
- It's "Go Straight for Love".
- Isn't that the show...
that will air
on August 3, at 10:30 p.m?
"Go Straight for Love"?
It looks fun already. It's crazy.
This will be a hit.
Where is the name tag?
(This will be a hit.
Where is the name tag?)
Until when
will you be his underling?
It will air at 10:30 p.m.
"Go Straight for Love"!
(Clapping for no reason)
Hwan Jin, this is your chance.
(The name tag thief
is setting the scene.)
This is your chance.
Where is the name tag?
I can promote your show
about 5,000 times.
"Go Straight for Love"!
Today is your only chance.
- Haha.
- Yes.
This is the hint.
(A coffee sleeve?)
(Haha earned a big hint
on where Jong Kook's name tag is.)
You're the best.
I'll go find it now.
(After giving him a hug,
Haha sets out to find the name tag.)
Hello.
(Exclaiming)
This is so fun! Gosh.
I've never been so excited
on Running Man.
Which high school did you go to?
So it's at a cafe.
All right. Let's go.
Hello.
I'm on the same team as Jong Kook.
(He starts lying shamelessly.)
I swear. I'm on the same team
as Director Lee too. I'm serious.
Look. What we hid before.
It says "Hwan Jin", right?
- Sorry?
- I need to take...
what Jong Kook left here.
I'm serious! It's for real.
We're on the same team.
(The staff brings something
to Haha.)
- All right. My gosh.
- Is this the one?
Thank you.
(Haha acquired
Jong Kook's name tag.)
No, we're on the same team.
- I don't think so.
- We're on the same team.
(Haha got Jong Kook as his tail
pretending to be an errand boy.)
(Kim Jong Kook)
We're a team now.
Why are you laughing?
Hwan Jin did something sly,
didn't he?
But I promoted his show a lot.
(Going to Haha while fuming)
How can he betray me?
Jong Kook is so funny.
He's so simple-minded.
I'm calling Jong Kook.
I got a scary tail.
The tail could become crazy,
so I should be careful.
I need to be nice to him.
He gets mad if I get cheeky.
He's coming.
See? I'm being so polite already.
Is this the car?
Hello, Mr. Tail!
- Hey, you punk.
- Hello, sir.
- You punk.
- Please get in.
- Sit over here.
- All right.
- Okay.
- You know me, right?
- Sure. Good job.
- I'll treat you real good today.
- You're only a tail by the title.
- Oh, gosh.
- Please support me.
- Go ahead.
I'll do my best.
- Just be the captain here.
- All right, sir.
- Captain!
- Don't even call me that.
- Captain! Just be one.
- No, I'm not a captain.
- You can do whatever you want.
- I'm Little Captain.
- Little Captain. LC.
- LC.
- Not a boomer but an LC.
- Yes, I'm LC.
- That sounds great.
- That sounds good.
- Gosh, it sounds good.
- You're LC.
We should go and get Suk Jin.
- I mean...
- I'll get the weak ones first.
Tell me where he hid it.
- Come here.
- Please.
You should tell me about yours too.
No, I can't. Why? Because you'll
text others about it for sure.
Hurry up!
(Sighing)
Gosh, I became an underling
as soon as the race started.
Hurry up!
I'm going after Suk Jin now.
(Captain Yoo's next target
is Seok Sam.)
I know where Suk Jin's name tag is.
What's more important is that...
once I'm at the place where he hid
his name tag,
I can tell where he hid it
by my hunch.
Gosh, seriously!
Hurry up.
What is this?
Seon Myung, put on the vest.
Hurry up and put it on.
- These guys are out of it.
- What is this? I'm like Bo Pil now.
So Min, this is like a field trip
for you. Watch and learn.
Come here. I'll show you.
- Look here.
- Hello.
- Jae Suk.
- You have to check the passersby.
They'll look like they want to share
where the members are...
if they saw one.
(Take a hint from the passersby
who wants to share things with us.)
Hold this.
(Hold the coffee.)
(While Tail Jeon carries out
her role as an errand girl...)
Gosh.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
Suk Jin just received a hint
on the location of your name tag.
He won't be able to find it anyway.
(Suk Jin got a hint
on where Jae Suk's name tag is?)
Here's the second question.
Seoul!
- The answer is...
- It is Seoul.
- All right!
- Correct.
We'll give you a hint on the
location of the member you pick.
I pick Jae Suk.
Would you like the picture
or the address of it?
(He can get an address or a picture
of the place...)
(Jae Suk hid his name tag.)
I'll go with the address.
Oh, right.
(That's how Suk Jin
got the address of the location.)
Mount Maebong is around here?
Let's go to 37, Maebongsan-ro.
I must make Jae Suk my tail.
(While Suk Jin is on the way
to find Jae Suk's name tag...)
Did you see Ji Suk Jin
around here?
- No.
- You didn't?
Hello.
Did Ji Suk Jin come here earlier?
I haven't seen him.
You haven't? I see.
Oh, Jae Suk prefers
the analog method.
So he likes to ask around.
Did you see Ji Suk Jin
around here?
(Doing legwork and asking around)
He was here, right?
No, I haven't seen him.
There's not a good spot
to hide your name tag here.
They'll find my name tag right away
if they get the address.
Sir, how long will it take?
- It's about 2km away.
- Oh, it's nearby.
Jae Suk, let's go get hints.
Can we?
(Jae Suk was all confident, but
he is about to get eliminated.)
Jae Suk.
(He's slowly looking around
the place he got intel on.)
Jae Suk, let's go get hints.
Hold on. I have to find
Suk Jin's name tag...
before he finds mine.
- Otherwise...
- It'll be over once he finds it.
Exactly.
Hold on. It must be around here.
How can we find it
when we have no hints at all?
- So Min, hold my coffee.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk heads inside
the cafe in front of him.)
This is bad.
I might run out of time.
(Actually, this cafe is...)
Gosh. All right. I'll hide it here.
(It's the cafe Suk Jin went to
when he was running out of time.)
I'm sorry, but can I hide this here?
The other members might come find
it, so don't give them any hints.
- Is this Running Man?
- Yes, it is.
Here. My name tag.
(He's wearing his clothes
with no name tag.)
Who is your favorite member
of Running Man?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk? I see.
What?
- You want me to hold your coffee?
- Hello.
(He enters the cafe
where Suk Jin hid his name tag.)
Did Suk Jin come by?
- Did Suk Jin come by?
- No.
- He didn't?
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Okay. Thank you.
- Have a good day. Hello.
- Bye.
- Hello.
- Please don't leave!
- Have a good day.
- Don't go!
It's here!
What is?
(It's here!)
(Jae Suk's fan hurriedly told him.)
Suk Jin is here?
(Jae Suk comes back in.)
Where is it?
(Hesitating)
Suk Jin is looking for my name tag,
so I'll be in trouble
if I don't find his first.
- Really?
- Yes.
I know you might feel guilty,
but I might get eliminated.
(Right then, Seok Sam calls him.)
Hey, Suk Jin.
Where are you?
You know where I am.
So you hid your name tag
at Maebongsan-ro.
Try and look for it.
Yes, I will.
You came
to this cafe earlier, right?
A cafe?
You came
to this cafe earlier, right?
(Laughing awkwardly)
(It's obvious that he's flustered.)
- Suk Jin.
- I went to many cafes.
- You can't find that cafe.
- Should I look for it?
What did you say?
What? A video call?
You're there?
(Hello.)
(Reuniting with the cafe staff
he saw earlier)
Hello.
- You seem very surprised.
- That's not true.
I took a photo with her earlier.
I see.
Thankfully,
they let me in their storage.
So I came in here
even though it's an inconvenience.
- I see.
- Yes.
Go ahead and look for it.
Okay.
Darn it. How did he find the cafe?
It makes no sense.
How did he find it?
He didn't even earn a hint, did he?
He must've asked around.
Is this the place?
Gosh, what's with Jae Suk?
How did he...
How did he find the cafe?
(Now it's a matter of time before
either one finds the name tag.)
You told me no one has
succeeded in the mission.
(If he turns the corner, he'll find
the spot Jae Suk hid his name tag.)
It seems like he found the cafe
by coincidence.
(But Suk Jin heads straight
into the building.)
They gave us their permission
to film in here?
Hello.
Did Jae Suk drop by here,
by any chance?
- No.
- He didn't? Okay, thank you.
This is driving me crazy.
Tell me up to where I can go in.
- Can I go in this much?
- You can go in.
- I can go inside?
- Yes.
(Jae Suk begins searching
after getting their permission.)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(But Jae Suk seems lost too.)
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
Didn't Jae Suk stop by here?
- No.
- He didn't?
- All right. Thank you.
- Okay.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Then where is it?
Where did he hide it?
Is it outside?
Did he hide it outside?
If he came inside the building,
he'd have asked where to hide it,
given his personality.
(While Suk Jin and Jae Suk are
madly looking for the name tag...)
Gosh, where could it be?
- Are you filming Running Man?
- Yes.
Has anyone seen a member
of Running Man?
No one?
I wouldn't tell you even if I did.
Tell me. I'm eliminated anyway.
Hello, I'm So Min.
Well...
I'm doing a drama called
"Cleaning Up" on JTBC.
The last episode will air next week.
Please show your support.
And please watch "Running Man"
on Sunday at 5 p.m. on SBS too.
It's very fun.
I watch the show every day.
Thank you.
And I'm not dating Se Chan.
Don't misunderstand.
We're joking to make it funny,
but many people are mistaken.
There's nothing going on
between Ji Hyo and Jong Kook either.
You guys know it, right?
What are you doing?
I should speak for them.
I wanted to say it
in front of people.
But why is he not coming out?
Did he leave without me?
Jae Suk is still searching.
It might not be there.
(At that moment)
(Jae Suk
holding Suk Jin's name tag?)
It's inside?
For real?
(He found it?)
(Jae Suk who has been searching
for a long time)
(He finally found
Suk Jin's name tag.)
- Yes.
- I'm out?
- Suk Jin is eliminated.
- Gosh.
- Jae Suk found your name tag.
- Oh my, he found it.
So you lose 100 points.
- Gosh, I knew he would find it.
- From now on...
I'm mad.
Jae Suk, say hi here.
(Captain Yoo has returned
with confidence.)
(Screaming)
I did it thanks to you guys.
(I did it thanks to you guys.)
- Jae Suk.
- Thanks to you guys.
(Thank you.)
How did you find it?
- What do you mean how?
- How did you know it was here?
So Min, come here for now.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Work hard.
Hearing "Work hard"
makes my heart...
(Hearing "Work hard"
makes my heart...)
Don't work too hard.
You can work a little bit less.
Thank you.
(He coolly leaves
after throwing a dad joke.)
We must catch Haha.
Why don't we make Se Chan join us?
Come here quickly for now.
- And there's one more thing.
- Okay.
While...
you were filming Tour of Seoul,
many things happened.
- Already? Okay.
- Yes. So...
So Min was eliminated.
- Already?
- Yes.
So was Suk Jin.
Already?
Jong Kook was eliminated.
I should've not done
that useless thing.
I spent most of the time hiding it.
Hello.
(He met the narrow-mouthed toad
driver again.)
I had a good time thanks to you.
Will I appear in the show this week?
(Will I appear in the show
this week?)
I came to Sky Park for no reason.
(He was filming Tour of Seoul alone,
while many things were happening.)
I should've not filmed
"Yang Se Chan's Tour of Seoul".
(It's likely to be edited out.)
- Sir.
- Yes.
You might not see this scene
in the show.
Yes.
Don't watch this week's episode.
Don't stay tuned either.
I think it'd be right to show
how I do it next time.
As expected, I don't see
a big picture by myself.
(Yang Se Chan's Tour of Seoul.
The end)
Oh, my.
(I should call So Min.)
I should call So Min.
(He's calling So Min
to understand the situation.)
I'm busy. Just hang up.
- I'll hang up. I'm busy.
- Okay.
(Beeping)
I feel sad today somehow.
And I'm a little lonely.
Everyone is not picking up.
(And I'm a little lonely.
Everyone is not picking up.)
Do you know why it is more tiring?
The interviews didn't go well.
It made it even harder.
(The interviews with people
are ruined on top of that.)
What did I say? Did I say
they should enjoy Seoul?
Why did you do it, Se Chan?
It's been 17 years in the industry.
And you asked a useless question.
It's because I didn't learn.
If you lose the file,
send me one so that I can keep it.
(If you lose the file,
send me one so that I can keep it.)
Tour of Seoul.
And the one that was edited out.
I should post it
on my YouTube channel.
(I should post it
on my YouTube channel.)
I should earn some money
even if it's a little.
The first place might appear
in the show more.
That's the only way.
I should become first.
(Se Chan wants to be 1st
to have enough footage to be aired.)
- I should find Jae Suk's.
- The head.
- I should find the head's.
- Yes.
Then I should find Jae Suk's.
(Ji Hyo is also having an eye
for Jae Suk at that moment.)
Now...
(Jae Suk became everyone's target.)
I should be careful.
Both would go for mine first.
- I'll be their target.
- Yes.
If they make you join, the others
behind you will also join.
- I know.
- That's why I'm in danger.
First, So Min.
- We should go to the game spot.
- Okay.
We should find out.
Come here quickly.
(They arrived at the mission spot.)
Hello.
Oh, my goodness. Seok Sam.
(They found Seok Sam
who was waiting.)
The tail.
How did you find it?
What do you mean how?
Everyone is searching like that.
- And you're younger than So Min.
- Yes.
- What did you say?
- I'm younger than So Min?
She's younger than me.
But there's a hierarchy here.
- I'm younger than her?
- Yes. You joined me.
Welcome, the second tail.
Okay. Bring me the vest.
- Just wear it.
- Okay.
I walked around with Jae Suk.
- His feet are as fast as his mouth.
- Can you help me?
Put it down for me.
- Gosh.
- Say "Please".
- Tail.
- Gosh.
The daughter-in-law and
the father-in-law...
met after a long time.
My goodness.
Just thinking about it...
What's the mission?
- Okay.
- Go to the center.
- Shy Suk Jin.
(Jung Ji Yoon, the floor director)
- Oh, my.
- Hello.
She's a shy fan.
That's right. Shy Suk Jin.
- How have you been?
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- What?
- It's three minutes from now on.
- Ji Eun.
- I'm Ji Yoon.
Ji Yoon. Oh, right.
You're Lee Ji Yoon.
- I'm Jung Ji Yoon.
- Jung Ji Yoon.
Hey, do it properly.
Jung Ji Yoon.
You're 24 or something, right?
- I'm 27.
- You're 27.
- I don't...
- They asked me...
about hometown and eyesight earlier.
Where are you from?
- Tongyeong.
How's your eyesight?
It's 0.2, 0.3.
- Are you...
- They might...
- ask this.
- living alone?
- You're living alone.
- I gave her a gift. Ask what it is.
- About the gift I gave to her.
- About a year and a half.
- What did Suk Jin get her?
- The gift I got for her.
They might ask it.
What did Suk Jin give to you?
Don't ask her. He's trying to make
her say a nice story about him.
No. It's because they might ask
about it.
He's trying to make her
say a nice story about him.
- They might ask about it.
- He got a gift for you, right?
- Yes. A cushion for my back.
- Right?
A cushion for your back.
Have you been using it?
- Yes.
- Do you have...
a different wallpaper
on your laptop?
- It's Suk Jin.
- You still got it.
Yes. Ask her about the color
of the cushion. It's green.
- Is the cushion green?
- Yes.
- And...
- Her ideal type.
- What's your ideal type? Yes.
- My ideal type?
(Ideal type)
A handsome type.
(A handsome type)
- And she likes Suk Jin?
- It has nothing to do...
with her ideal type.
- They're different.
- She said it's a handsome type.
- A handsome type.
- A handsome type. Okay.
Then...
- Your blood type.
- It's A.
- A.
- Ask her about her MBTI type.
- What's your MBTI type?
- It's ENFP.
ENFP.
You should memorize them all.
ENFP. Can you drink...
- a lot?
- How much she can drink.
I like drinking,
but I can't drink much.
A half bottle of soju?
- Yes.
- A half bottle of soju.
When is your birthday?
- September 27.
- Time is up.
- You guys can't tell him.
- You can't.
- But we're his tails. We're one.
- Pardon?
- We're the tails.
- You helped him with questions.
- We're attached to his body.
- We're tails.
- It's...
- Only the head can answer.
We're tails though.
Number 2 and 3. Stay over there.
Keep Suk Jin on your side.
You should get it right.
- Get it right.
- No matter what.
The first question.
- Don't give him a hint.
- Okay.
How old is the staff member
in front of you?
- I know.
- Earlier.
- You asked her.
(How old is the staff member?)
She's 27.
(Twenty-seven!)
- That's correct.
- I'm 27.
- Yes.
- Hey.
Hey, we got what we had expected.
- Okay.
- The second question.
What does the staff member
in front of you do...
when she's drunk?
- He didn't ask.
- We don't know.
She might not do anything specific
when she's drunk.
We can discuss, right?
- No, you can't.
- But...
she only drinks a half bottle
of soju. She won't get drunk.
- Think about the get-together.
- Ji Yoon.
- Usually,
- those who can't drink much...
- like me just sleep.
- That's it. I agree.
- Does she cry?
- What?
- Don't...
- Don't ask her.
Am I not even allowed to think?
- I can think.
- Usually,
- those who can't drink much sleep.
- Sit down, little one.
Okay. Master.
- Get him some jjondeugi.
- Sit.
My goodness.
Those who can't drink much
just sleep.
Does she dance?
- It can't be.
- She wouldn't dance.
Do you feel excited?
- Yangsebastien.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
- Did you get caught?
- You came.
No. I hid it in Mount Maebong
and just came back.
Really? You went to Mount Maebong?
- I almost died.
- You're lying again.
It's true.
- Why are you such a liar?
- It's real.
- I went to Mount Maebong.
- Come here.
- Sit.
- You didn't sweat enough...
for someone
who went to Mount Maebong.
You didn't sweat enough.
Don't say nonsense.
So what does she do
when she's drunk?
In 1, 2, 3.
She eats.
- She eats?
- It's not.
- It's sleeping.
- What is it?
I repeat what I said.
- This...
- She gets talkative.
You should've said
"She gets talkative."
- After drinking a half bottle only?
- Hey.
Ji Yoon.
- She gets talkative.
- I...
can't drink much either, but...
- The youngest. Sit down.
- I mean you can make a deal.
- If you say, "She gets talkative",
- No, little one.
you can negotiate with the staff.
I'll give you the third question.
This is driving me crazy. We'll be
in trouble if I don't get it right.
If you get it right,
I'll give you a hint.
- Okay.
- Or try again ten minutes later.
This is driving me crazy.
What's her MBTI type?
You remember it, right?
(What's her MBTI type?)
Jae Suk, I said
it's the same type as mine.
It's E.
Come on.
- ENF...
- Don't give him a hint.
Don't give him a hint.
(Pressuring him with her eyes)
What's this? Hurry up.
I want to try.
- ENFP.
- At least...
Hey.
Why?
It's...
It's ENF...
- Guys.
- It's ENFP.
If you spit it, it's over.
My answer is...
- ENFP.
- The answer.
- It's correct.
- Okay!
It's correct.
Because I'm ESFP.
You can get the address or a photo
of the name tag of your choice.
Get Haha.
- That's right.
- Haha's name tag must be near here.
- Shall I get him instead?
- I think Jong Kook got caught.
Please hurry up and get me.
What I did earlier won't get aired.
What I did earlier won't get aired,
so please hurry up and get me.
Please save me
so that I can get some screen time.
If you catch Haha,
- Jong Kook will come as a tail.
- Yes.
(But the tails think
he should get Team Haha.)
Pick Haha...
and get the photo.
I know in which building
his name tag is hidden.
Really?
(Suk Jin ran into Haha
at the SBS Prism Tower.)
I am 100 percent sure
it's the Prism Tower.
Excuse me. Haha, please.
- Haha.
- Yes.
- Ask for a photo.
- The address or a photo?
- A photo, please.
- A photo.
- Jae Suk.
- You won't be able to find it...
- from a photo.
- It's the Prism Tower.
Find my name tag.
- Jae Suk.
- Hold on.
But he might end up winning.
- Ji Hyo or Se Chan.
- All right.
- Then let's get him.
- That might happen in the end.
Get me.
It will be meaningless to wait.
- You need to get me now.
- This is driving me crazy.
- How did you gain so much weight?
- What?
- You became chubby.
- That came out of nowhere.
Why are you hurting his feelings?
- Seriously.
- You became chubby.
I lost weight since the opening
because I sweated.
- Look at his belly.
- How did you gain so much weight?
You gained so much weight.
- What happened in a week?
- I was so surprised.
Yesterday, I had
two servings of galbitang.
Jae Suk, here is a photo.
- A photo. Where is it?
- Here you go.
I am 100 percent sure
it's the Prism Tower.
- I think he is right.
- It's the broadcasting station.
It's the broadcasting station.
(The location of Haha's name tag)
It's the Prism Tower.
- These are towels.
- Yes.
- Don't look at other photos.
- I am sorry.
- Towels.
- It's the Prism Tower.
- It's the Prism Tower. Let's go.
- Let me see the details.
Wait for me. Let's take a break.
We don't have time
to take a break. Hurry up.
So Min, hurry up.
- Aren't you going to film me?
- So Min.
- So Min, hurry up.
Suk Jin, hurry up.
- So Min.
- Excuse me.
- I am going.
- Talk about me from time to time.
Okay. I will do that.
Wonder out loud,
"Where could Se Chan's name tag be?
I am sorry. I am filming today.
- They are here.
- My goodness.
- Hurry up.
- Excuse me.
(Haha and Jong Kook learn
that Jae Suk obtained a hint.)
Did you find it?
- He is running.
- Yes.
(Nervous)
Where did he go?
Let's take a taxi.
Why is he running?
It's too far. Let's take a taxi.
Jae Suk,
a tail wants to take a taxi.
- What?
- A tail wants...
- to take a taxi.
- Stop speaking nonsense. Hurry up.
- Let's go.
- He wants to do that.
Hurry up.
Why are we walking?
It's hot.
(Haha chases after them
in order to protect his name tag.)
Jong Kook, let's hurry up
and stop them.
- I need to move my name tag.
- Hey.
Just go with the flow,
- Haha.
- Please cooperate a bit more.
I really want to win today.
Hurry up.
Is the prop container...
in the Prism Tower?
It might be at a different location.
Is it the sixth floor?
(Jae Suk arrives
at the 1st-floor lobby.)
I am sorry,
but please pick up the speed.
- Come on.
- Please help me this once.
This is a hassle. I am exhausted.
Please.
This is where I saw Haha earlier.
Perhaps he moved it
to a different location.
- He didn't have time to do that.
- He didn't have time.
It's a hassle to move it.
- Where are they?
- We need to get them.
- We can take off our masks here.
- Yes.
(Team Jae Suk arrives
on the 15th floor.)
- Ji Hyo.
- There is Ji Hyo.
(They find Ji Hyo
who was on the same floor!)
(What is Ji Hyo doing here?)
- She must have hidden it here.
- Ji Hyo.
(30 minutes ago)
(Ji Hyo succeeded in the mission
and obtained a hint.)
(The address for Haha's name tag:
SBS Prism Tower, 15th floor)
Is that all I get?
(Thus, she obtained a hint
on Haha's name tag.)
(Ji Hyo was searching
the 15th floor...)
(when she ran into Team Jae Suk!)
(Ji Hyo runs at full speed
to find Haha's name tag.)
- She must have hidden it here.
- Ji Hyo.
- Where did you hide it?
- Ji Hyo, where are you going?
- Ji Hyo.
Hurry up and get in.
(Team Haha
takes the elevator as well.)
Hurry up. Run. We don't have time.
- Ji Hyo, where are you going?
- Ji Hyo.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
Se Chan obtained
a hint on your name tag.
- This is bad.
- What are you going to do?
- Just hold on to them.
- All right.
(Haha chases after the team
in order to protect his name tag!)
- It's 7th floor.
- It's 7th floor, Haha.
(He is in a hurry.)
You know that it's here, right?
It's eighth floor.
Oh, no.
You know that it's here, right?
I came to find it.
You don't know the details, do you?
(They found the prop box
in the photo!)
It will be a hassle.
(Haha hid the name tag
under the towels.)
For goodness' sake.
(Haha is close to their floor.)
You don't know the details, do you?
(Who will get the name tag first?)
- You saw a photo, right?
- Where is it?
- Right, Ji Hyo?
- All right. We found it.
(They found Haha's name tag.)
Did you find it?
I did it. You should give me
some points.
Haha and Jong Kook are out.
- You found it.
- Now, Se Chan.
Jae Suk...
found your name tag, so you are out.
All right.
(He suddenly went from a captain
to a tail.)
Let's just go down to the lobby,
Haha.
(Kim Tail is relaxed
because it doesn't concern him.)
You will feel miserable
if you meet him up there.
(Sighing)
You know what I mean, right?
I see that Jae Suk is sharp.
He is sharp.
(Haha becomes Jae Suk's tail
with the relaxed Kim Tail.)
It's over. We will have
everyone behind our backs.
- Jong Kook will be added too.
- I know.
Now, Ji Hyo, Se Chan,
and Jae Suk remain.
- Hold on.
- It will be over if you get them.
Myung Jae, let's go.
Let's hurry up and go.
Let's go.
Where is Se Chan?
- Should I do the mission?
- Seriously.
Did you see
where Se Chan hid his name tag?
Se Chan said it's at Mount Maebong.
- It's a lie. That can't be it.
- It's a lie.
- He is bound to come near here.
- You got Haha, right?
I should ask Haha
because he is the newest addition.
He might have gotten a hint.
- Hello.
- We are a team now,
so don't speak nonsense.
Where is Se Chan's name tag?
- Did you find my name tag?
- Yes, I did.
Where is Se Chan's name tag?
Congratulations.
Jong Kook.
- He is so simple-minded.
- All right.
How could you hide it
inside the Running Man office?
- I found it.
- Jong Kook has no desire to win.
How could you hide it
inside the Running Man office?
- Jong Kook has no desire to win.
- Hey.
Where is Se Chan?
Se Chan is over there.
Did he obtain a hint?
It's over.
- Se Chan didn't obtain a hint.
- He is the captain.
- Jae Suk, decide on the ranks.
- Jae Suk,
put them behind me.
I found the name tag.
- Punks, change into this pink vest.
- All right.
- I guess you don't need to change.
- Just keep wearing a yellow vest.
- After So Min comes...
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Then comes Haha.
- Hey!
Okay.
- You are the last one.
- Why am I the last one?
- This isn't about age.
- But I became a tail...
You are the last one.
Thank you.
- He doesn't disappoint.
- This is driving me crazy.
Here is the important thing.
Se Chan obtained a hint.
He is on his way
to find my name tag.
- Your name tag?
- Yes.
Okay.
- So...
- I will get him.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Call Se Chan.
- Jong Kook.
- Please find Se Chan...
- Se Chan.
- and hold on to him.
- Okay.
Things will get complicated
if Se Chan becomes the captain.
- That's right.
- I am currently the second tail.
It's better to stay in this team.
What is that?
Sir, how long will it take?
- We are 1.5km away.
- Okay.
Ji Hyo.
Where are you? I will go to you.
It will end if we get Jae Suk.
- Will it end if we get Jae Suk?
- Yes.
We need to get Jae Suk.
Jae Suk has everyone.
How about you? Who are you with?
I am alone.
You and I should team up...
and find Jae Suk's name tag.
Okay.
Come to the Prism Tower.
- Okay.
- All right.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo
form an alliance.)
Where will we find Se Chan?
Seriously.
- We have no idea where Se Chan is.
- Seriously.
Where is Se Chan?
Se Chan's name tag isn't
in a mountain.
He will go to the location
of your name tag.
We should go there and get Se Chan.
- The elevator is here.
- Let's go and get Se Chan.
- Hello.
- We don't need to film here.
- Sorry.
- All of us can get in.
Not all of us can get in.
- We will go down first.
- No.
Catch the next elevator.
- Don't be like that to my team.
- There are no teams.
We are on the same team.
Why would you divide people up?
- Seriously.
- I got caught because of them.
(The elevator keeps stopping.)
(Jae Suk's tails
talk among themselves.)
The camera isn't running.
Yes, it is.
Really? Is it running?
Hello.
We are stopping on every floor.
I see. Did you open the door?
It might have been better
to use the staircase.
- We are getting off.
- We are sorry.
You should get off first.
- That's right.
- They need to get off.
- We are sorry.
(The shoot gets halted
while they are in the elevator.)
- Okay.
- Hurry up and get in.
Get in. Okay.
You just need to open the door
on the first floor.
We will be late if we take a car.
- And...
- Is it nearby?
- No. We need to take a car.
- You could do that.
- You could show the way.
- We will get exhausted if we walk.
It's pretty far.
He doesn't want to walk.
She asked someone to open the door
on the first floor and show the way.
We need to split up,
but if we do that...
- It's okay.
- Let's split up.
- Okay.
We can't fit in one car.
- What?
- I think someone is here.
- Did someone enter?
- She told someone to open the door.
She authorized a member
to enter the building.
I think a member entered
the building.
A member entered the building.
- Who?
- I think it's Se Chan or Ji Hyo.
- Why would Se Chan come here?
- Your name tag isn't hidden here.
Se Chan must have hidden
his name tag here.
- No way.
- Se Chan didn't come here.
- I hid my name tag near here.
- I hid mine here.
If you go to another building,
you need permission for filming.
- You can't hide it anywhere else.
- She authorized a member.
He must have hidden it
somewhere else.
We reached our floor.
It took so long.
Is it the first floor,
not the lobby?
Gosh.
Someone entered the building.
I am sure of it.
Hyung In.
What did Hyung In say?
"You can open the door."
She said that.
- Which member would call her...
- Someone entered the building.
- at this point?
- You need to use this.
Hyung In, for whom
did you open the door?
Wasn't it Se Chan?
- Hyung In.
- Ma'am, did Se Chan enter?
Here you go.
- She didn't see him.
- Don't turn it in.
- We might enter the building again.
- Hyung In.
Hyung In.
- She didn't see him.
- Don't turn it in.
(Hold on!)
I have no idea.
Can I hide it at a friend's house?
We will take a break here.
A friend's house?
That's insane.
What's wrong with you?
I want to send Jong Kook
to that house.
(All the members heard her.)
I will hide it at a friend's house,
so you should go and look for it.
Hyung In.
(In that case...)
Where is your house?
- It's near here.
- Where?
(Hyung In's house is nearby.)
Whose house?
- Her house?
- Hold on.
- Your house?
She opened the door for someone.
Did she hide it in your house?
Hyung In's house!
Hyung In, do you live in
Sangam-dong?
- You said you have a boyfriend...
- Did you open the door...
to your house?
Hyung In's boyfriend
came to her house.
- I see.
- She opened the door for him.
No. That can't be it.
- Really?
- It makes sense.
She told someone to open the door.
The call must be work-related
since she took it during the shoot.
The call must be work-related.
Hyung In, come here.
Where is your house?
Hurry up. Se Chan must be there.
Didn't Se Chan go to find
your name tag?
- But she...
- Why would he go there?
- I get it!
- What?
- Did he go there to move his?
- Ji Hyo must have gone there...
to move her name tag.
- Really?
- Yes.
- It has to be Ji Hyo.
- She wants to move hers.
- Can she do it in three minutes?
You think she will focus on defense.
That's right.
It will be over
if her name tag gets found.
- Wouldn't she find yours first?
- Why don't you do a mission?
- Seriously.
- No.
- Hyung In.
- Where do you live?
Shouldn't we go to protect
Jae Suk's name tag?
Let's have a vote.
Finding Se Chan's name tag versus
protecting Jae Suk's name tag.
Raise your hand
if you want to protect my name tag.
Of course you should do that.
Raise your hand if you want to find
Se Chan's name tag. One, two, three.
- Okay.
- Se Chan's name tag?
- Come here.
- But...
you need to do a mission.
- Let's take a car.
- Let's go to Hyung In's house.
- But you need to do a mission.
- Let's take a car. Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
- You can take that van.
Hyung In, are we going
to your house?
- Are we going to Hyung In's house?
- Yes.
But this came out of nowhere.
Going to Hyung In's house...
because of what So Min heard
is too outrageous.
(Se Chan arrived near the location
of Jae Suk's name tag.)
Third floor.
(Se Chan arrived near the location
of Jae Suk's name tag.)
Hello.
- It's where Ji Hyo's name tag is.
- I think so.
I got goosebumps.
If it weren't for what you heard,
I would have gone to another place.
When you said it...
Ji Hyo obtained a photo
for your name tag as well.
This is bad.
(At that moment)
I will give all my tails to Ji Hyo
if I am not careful.
We might become her tails.
I want to see a photo of
Jae Suk's name tag.
A photo? Okay.
I think I know the location.
(She gets a call from Se Chan!)
- Ji Hyo.
- Se Chan.
Where are you?
I just completed the mission.
If you completed the mission,
can you see a photo...
for Jae Suk's name tag?
Okay. Now,
I will go there.
Even with the photo,
it won't be easy to find it.
I hope no one moved it.
Isn't it so strange?
- Why did Se Chan...
- Sir, would you turn right here?
- Is it near here?
- Yes.
I will take a quick look.
Let's hide my name tag
someplace else.
Will you be able to hide it
in a good location?
I will have three minutes.
He will go to the place
he hid his name tag.
- I knew it.
- We should go there then.
We should go there then.
- Where did you hide it?
- We will get off here.
- Where?
- Please stay here.
- Where did you hide it?
- Excuse me.
(If the information
of your name tag is revealed,)
Hurry up.
(you can move the name tag
in 3 minutes.)
Three minutes begin now.
(3 minutes begin now.)
(He can only move
the name tag on foot.)
So Min, stay there.
Hurry up.
(While Jae Suk moves the name tag,)
Se Chan.
Where is it?
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo meet
at the back of the building.)
Okay. Hold on.
It must be in a box.
- A box?
- Hurry up and find a box.
(But Jae Suk is already moving
the name tag.)
I need to be careful.
(He arrives at a secluded area.)
This is too...
(He hides the name tag
inside the bushes.)
We don't have much time.
So Min.
Let's go.
We need to make sure
we don't catch anyone's eyes.
All done.
Let's take out Ji Hyo and Se Chan.
(They head back
to Hyung In's house!)
How did she hide it
at a producer's house?
- Seriously.
- Isn't it too much?
Hyung In has so much for the show.
She even provided her own house.
Are we headed to Hyung In's house?
This is ridiculous.
What's the address?
It's...
Hey, let's switch sides.
- Switch sides?
- Yes.
You could do that if you want.
Really? Okay.
It's impossible to find.
Suk Jin.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
Why don't we make a deal?
Se Chan!
- We...
- Se Chan!
Jong Kook, Haha, and I want
to switch to your side.
But you need to make us
high-ranking tails.
If we become your tails,
you will be the captain.
Of course. I will make you guys
the high-ranking tails.
- Make sure you do that.
- Okay.
As for Jae Suk's name tag...
Do you need the address?
I got the address.
I think Jae Suk moved it.
- Did he move it?
- He didn't move it.
- He moved it.
- Really?
I think he moved it.
The address is right,
but he moved it to a nearby place.
You can't go far in three minutes.
- It's nearby.
- It must be at a nearby place.
Ask people if they have seen
Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- Go there.
Where did you hide your name tag?
It's not even a good hint.
- Hello?
- Yes?
It isn't here.
Jae Suk hid it nearby.
(Find the name tag Jae Suk hid.)
We are here.
(Jae Suk and So Min arrive
at Hyung In's house.)
Thank you.
Shall we go inside?
She got here by car.
So Hyung In opened this door.
I think Hyung In opened this door.
This is the place.
Where is it?
- And...
- Yes?
- Jong Kook.
It would be too crowded...
- if the three of you enter as well.
- Shall we keep watch?
- Yes. Please keep watch.
- Come back soon.
- Shall we keep watch here?
- Yes.
Okay.
What's here?
I think he has the wrong idea.
(Is Ji Hyo's name tag here?)
- I think he has the right idea.
- Really?
Hyung In.
It's my first time
going to a producer's house.
I see.
Seriously. I don't understand.
Ji Hyo or Se Chan
can't come up with such ideas.
Don't film it.
She is hiding it.
Hold on.
- Can I enter?
- Yes.
Hyung In, can I enter your house?
- This is...
- Is the mission that important?
(He becomes hesitant.)
- This is...
- We shouldn't stand in the hallway.
(He takes a deep breath and enters.)
Is the mission that important?
Hyung In, your house...
(She reveals her house
in its natural state.)
Hold on. Please excuse me
since I am here with you.
(He cautiously begins
to look around the house.)
Hold on.
Where did she hide it?
Hyung In, can't you look for it?
Hyung In, I can't do this.
Even though you are a producer,
I can't search a woman's house.
Would you please look for it?
- Can I go upstairs?
- Yes.
I am cautious...
because this is your house.
Is it in this building?
(Se Chan searches
for Jae Suk's name tag.)
(He keeps circling
the original location.)
It has to be near here.
Hyung In, can I move this?
- Sure.
- Hold on.
I should venture out.
- You haven't seen Jae Suk, right?
- I haven't.
(Se Chan turns
to a different direction.)
(It's the path Jae Suk took
to hide his name tag!)
(Se Chan follows the path.)
Maybe she opened this.
(Jae Suk's search
isn't going anywhere.)
Did Jae Suk come here? No?
There are only a few places
where you can hide it.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo versus Jae Suk)
He must have hidden it near here.
I am in a hurry.
What?
(He found Ji Hyo's name tag!)
Can I hide it at someone's house?
Can I hide it at Hyung In's house?
I texted her. "Hyung In."
"Can I stop by your place?"
Okay.
(She managed to get
the resident's consent.)
The door is opening.
Follow me.
I should hide my name tag.
(Ji Hyo hid her name tag
under the sofa.)
There's no way
they can find my name tag.
(And she believed
no one would find her name tag.)
(A call from the janitor's office)
(She got a call
regarding the shoot in her place.)
(So Min heard the phone call.)
(And the chase master
found the name tag.)
My gosh.
All right. Song Ji Hyo is out.
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
I'm really good at this.
Ji Hyo, you're out.
(Ji Hyo, you're out.)
(Ji Hyo became Jae Suk's tail
at the last minute.)
Gosh, I was looking
for his name tag!
(Song Ji Hyo)
Now I need Se Chan's name tag.
I hid mine again,
so I'm at an advantage now.
(Jae Suk moved his name tag,
so he's at an advantage now.)
I moved my name tag,
so he won't be able to find mine.
- I'll give you.
- On Monday...
Did you find it? He found it.
- Did you find it?
- How did you find it?
- So it was there.
- That's impressive.
- It was really there.
- You're amazing.
If you didn't hear the phone call,
he wouldn't have found it.
- I could find it thanks to So Min.
- Right.
She deserves to be number one.
- When So Min said that...
- She helps you a lot.
- I just realized...
- She's good.
You tails.
Hyung In wouldn't have told me.
- I know.
- By the way, our ranks...
I don't think our ranks make sense.
Aren't we supposed to alter
our pecking orders?
- What?
- It should be changed.
- Do you want me to change?
- I will...
All right then.
- All right.
- What?
- Jae Suk.
- Se Chan found his name tag?
Se Chan found your name tag.
(Se Chan found your name tag.)
You're just one of us now.
(He found the name tag
in the new place?)
I think...
- one of the tails did it.
- My gosh.
- I can't believe...
- Someone gave him the address.
No, it wasn't me.
Jae Suk, I'm serious.
- I didn't do it.
- I can't believe this.
- You're unbelievable.
- You're really...
- Jeon So Min, you are...
- Seriously, I didn't do it.
You should've kept
your tails under control.
- Was that you?
- Why...
did you tell her
about the new location?
- Who do you think it is?
- Why did you tell her?
We don't even know where you hid it.
(30 minutes ago)
(Jae Suk trusted So Min
and moved his name tag with her.)
(He made a quick decision
and moved his name tag.)
(Jae Suk got only 3 minutes
to move it to somewhere else.)
So Min, stay there.
(Jae Suk even took care of So Min
while moving his name tag.)
Follow him.
Can he really do this
in three minutes?
Where is he going? Is there
any place where he can hide it?
(While Jae Suk was
moving his name tag,)
(So Min called someone.)
Where are you?
I'm looking for
Jae Suk's name tag now.
Where are you?
Jae Suk just moved his name tag
to another place.
Where?
If I tell you that,
will you make me number two?
- Yes, I will.
- Wait. Let me see where I am now.
Hang on. Jae Suk is coming.
I have to go.
All right. Get in.
(Where exactly am I now?)
(He hid it in the flower bed.)
(It's in the flower bed
in front of a convenience store.)
- I should go there.
- Here's the recommended route.
Where's the convenience store?
(Se Chan asked around
to find the convenience store.)
Where?
In there?
Thank you.
My gosh.
(When Jae Suk was looking
for Ji Hyo's name tag,)
I found it.
It's here.
(Se Chan found Jae Suk's.)
Out? What does that mean?
(Yang Se Chan wins.)
Okay.
Ji Hyo is Jae Suk's tail, right?
Okay. So I'm the winner.
(The duo born in 1986 nailed
the race like that.)
We don't even know where you hid it.
- You moved it.
- All right.
So the race is over.
She's the only one
who knows the new place.
You are unbelievable.
- I don't care who wins.
- No.
You are...
(You are...)
Hang on.
- I knew it.
- I can't believe this.
- She is the So Min we know.
- It doesn't matter who wins.
- Jae Suk.
- Let's go.
- You have no choice.
- I know.
- This is how things work.
- It's all for the best.
- When the camera is on...
- You are...
- So you never change.
- Hey.
I almost got disappointed.
- You...
- Seriously, you are...
- Let's go.
- I knew this would happen.
- I knew it would go like this.
- Sure.
Isn't that obvious?
You should watch out for her.
- I know.
- This is really...
So am I the winner?
She just got caught?
Lucky!
Yang Se Chan is the winner.
Please look forward
to the next race.
(The race is not over yet.)
(We never know who will win
before the race is over.)
(The exhausting race)
(The one who survives
until the end...)
(Catch others off their guard.)
(The tails rebel against the head.)
- You fool.
- What are you doing?
(Why did you do that?)
(The traitors are punished.)
(They give...)
(as good as they get.)
(This is no big deal.)
(The race that you can't
take lightly continues.)
(And...)
(The members are
in Yeouido this time?)
(They throw the production budget
away for fun.)
- There's a mountain.
- Who is it?
(Three men are coming
to Running Man?)
(They are here to shake
the negotiation table.)
(You're broke, right?)
(Lee Yi Kyung, Ha Do Kwon,
Joo Woo Jae)
(Those without money...)
(become the prey at the table.)
(Those with money...)
(lead the negotiations.)
(Race of Groups)